It's the Star Race,
with the stars of Republic of Korea.
[The star of each category meets
at the ancient city of Gyungjoo.]
[But today's race can only
consist of one star team.]
[Three guys who take
the Korean film industry by storm.]
[Gentle and charismatic Ji Sung.]
[The prince of chungmuro, Joo Ji Hoon.]
[The newest leading man of the big screen,
Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Team Film Stars]
[Two lovely fairies and Mr. Gary.]
[A-Pink's resident cutie, Yoon Bo Mi.]
[A-Pink's face of youth, Son Na Eun.]
[Hip Hop Idol, Gary.]
[Team Idols]
[The gods of competitiveness have gathered.]
[The goddess of billiards, Cha Yu Ram.]
[Self-proclaimed Mr. Capable,
Kim Jong Kook.]
[Awakened after four years of slumber,
king of ddakji, Ji Suk Jin.]
[Team Sports All Stars.]
[The beautiful faces of
the entertainment world.]
[Ace of looks and skills, Song Ji Hyo.]
[From flower boy to flower man,
Baek Sung Hyun.]
[Who cares about height when I look like this,
Huh Kyung Hwan.]
[Team Beautiful]
[The strongest around the world
have gathered together.]
[Enthusiastic youth, Sam Otswiri.]
[Taekwondo enthusiast, Fabien Yoon.]
[Nation's leading smartass, Ha Ha.]
[Global Team.]
[And the nation's leading MC.]
[The star of all MC's, Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Who will be the ultimate winning team
of today's race?]
[June, 2014- Gwangmyung Station.]
[A train trip? All the stars gather
together on the train platform.]
I need everyone to gather together.
Jae Suk, you're our guide
today, right?
You're our guide, right?
You're dressed the part today.
- You might be hot in that outfit.
- I'm your MC for the day.
[Not a guide, but the MC host for the day.]
You will all be taking the train to Gyungjoo.
[Gyungjoo is their destination for the day.]
I know I've told you this earlier,
but Gary got lucky with his team.
I guess he's a part of the Idol team?
Why don't you come over here
and take care of your own teammates?
No, it's not like that.
She kept nudging me on my shoulder earlier
saying that I was blocking her from view.
- He's just so big.
- Is 'Otswiri' your real name?
Yes, it's pronounced like
'572' in Korean.
- He's '160'.
- Why is he '160'?
[He's 160cm tall.]
No, I'm 170cm tall.
What do you want your number
to be, Ji Sung?
- What do you want your number to be?
- You should be 'Zero' for Lee Bo Young.
[Lee Bo Young, his new bride.]
Lee Bo Young.
[Their train pulls up to the platform
making everyone anxious for what's to come.]
[A cheerful start of the trip to Gyungjoo.]
[Just what kind of an event
awaits them in Gyungjoo?]
Today's race is 'The Race of the Stars'
Played by the top stars of our country.
We will start off by revealing what your
final mission is going to be.
- Already?
- Yes, here's your final mission.
[Final competition- A quiz battle.]
- It's a quiz competition.
- Are you serious?
- A quiz battle?
- My teammates can't handle that!
[From Ghana and France.]
Ha Ha, Fabien and Otswiri are
better than you.
[No response to that remark.]
Can we play a game of pocket ball?
It's not going to be
your run of the mill quiz battle.
What kind of a quiz battle will it be?
Once you get off at your train station
you will have to complete a variety
of missions related to the quiz battle.
Depending how well you do
with each of those missions
you will be given an MC chance card,
which could be of great advantage to you.
- What's the MC chance card?
- I can't tell you that right now.
But these chance cards will be of great help
to you at your final mission
so you have to make sure not to
lose your chance cards.
[Is that so?]
[The key to today's race is, MC Yoo.]
[The team with MC Yoo on their side
will rule the game.]
Today's Race of the Stars,
which all you stars are participating in...
Since this is the Race of the Stars
we have prepared a prize for the victors
in the likes which have never seen before.
[Greatest prize in the history of the show.]
Awesome!
We even had a diamond ring as
the winning prize on a recent episode.
[Jin Se Yeon recently won a one carat
diamond ring as her winning prize.]
Our team is going to win today's race!
Everyone's in such a good mood already.
Wow, everyone's in such a good
mood right now.
I think that teamwork is going to be the key
to winning the race today.
Thus, even though it's a short ride
I think it would be wise for each of the teams
to get to know their teammates well.
That's why we're going to come up with
a battle cry for each of the teams.
- Come up with your own battle cry.
- What should ours be?
Now that you know that a prize is on the line,
everyone's moving at a much faster pace.
Everyone's jumping right into action.
[Everyone's busy trying to come up
with a battle cry for their own team.]
Suk Jin's even trying to come up with
our own team dance moves.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes!
Then we will now hear team by team
to see what you've all come up with.
We will start with Gary's team.
Ready, set, go.
- Mr. Gae.
- Gae!
- On our lips is Gae.
Pink, Pink, Gary, Pink!
[An adorable battle cry for Team Idols.]
[Next up us the Global Team.]
Fabien!
Ha Ha Ha...
[Still unable to overcome the border
that surrounds each of their nations?]
[Time to hear Team Beautiful's battle cry.]
The flowers are blooming,
where the flowers are blooming.
Team Beautiful... Yay!
Kyung Hwan, you've got really
sweaty armpits.
Okay, next team.
- Ready, set...
- Sorry, but Suk Jin came up with it all.
You can't be embarrassed by it.
Stare directly into the camera.
[Team Sports All-stars' battle cry.]
In the pocket, in the pocket,
want to put Cha Yu Ram in our pockets.
[Finishes off the battle cry with
a billiards pose by Yu Ram.]
[Team Film Stars bursts out laughing
before they even get started.]
Set, go.
- Good friends...
- Good friends!
- That's so dull.
Let us give it another try.
- What are you doing?
- Just give us one more chance.
Forget it, we'll just skip you guys.
That's the kind of stuff that I used to
come up with when I was in middle school.
Joo Ji Hoon's 'Joo', Ji Sung's 'Ji',
Lee Kwang Soo's 'Soo'!
We are, Joo Ji Soo!
Joo Ji Soo?
[What the heck is that?]
What the heck is, 'Joo Ji Soo'?
Ji Hoon and I should do our own parts,
so why are you doing it all?
- Let's all do it together.
- Don't try to do it all, Kwang Soo.
- We came up with something new.
- You got something new? Ready, set, go.
Ghana's Ghana!
[Short but effective battle cry
for the team.]
Otswiri can't go back to Ghana right now.
[Otswiri is planning on using the prize money
to return to his home in glory?]
We have such a huge prize
for the winning team on the line.
As you've all been told before,
you will be getting off at Shim Station.
But all five of the teams will have to
participate in simple games along the way.
And the team that comes in last will have to
stay on this train all the way to Busan.
So the team that ends up taking the train
all the way to Busan Station
will be behind the other four teams no matter
what kind of other missions you'll be doing.
[A huge disadvantage of time being wasted
and falling behind the other teams.]
I was looking at Joo Ji Hoon earlier when
the camera wasn't rolling
and I was wondering why you keep staring out
the window with that glazed look in your eyes.
Did you have to come on this show
against your own will or something?
- Ji Hoon's usually a chatterbox.
- Ji Hoon just keeps staring out the window.
He's guzzling down that water
like it's alcohol.
Are you sure that's just water
in that bottle?
[With his sad doe-like eyes...]
[He only keeps staring out
the window.]
Just what is it that you're
thinking about?
I just feel a little awkward being here.
Who do you feel most awkward and
uncomfortable around here right now?
- Ah, Gary?
- Me?
[Scent of awkwardness is
wafting off of Mr. Gary.]
[Of all people, the person he most feels
awkward around happens to sit next to him.]
[Gary pretends to fall asleep
the moment he sits down in his chair.]
Why are you making him feel
so uncomfortable?
[The train arrives at Dongdaegu Station.]
We will now start a simple round of games
which I've mentioned to you earlier.
[Time to start the game.]
Are we at a disadvantage for
sitting way in the back?
No, not at all.
It's a very simple game which you're all
familiar with and play frequently.
It's a very easy game.
All three members of the team have to play.
Please sit down.
- Do we sit down for the game?
- Yes, you have to be sitting down.
Is it noonchi game?
Is it noonchi?
What are you saying right now?
I feel like there's an old Korean man
sitting behind me right now.
Everyone, we will be playing
the noonchi game.
- We will now start the game.
- You'd better stand up at one.
- I'm going to stand up at two.
- You have to listen to me carefully.
We will get started as soon as
you hear me say, 'Ready, set, go'.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes.
- Start.
- One!
Okay, you're disqualified.
You're disqualified.
I said, we'll start at 'Ready, set, go'.
[Not 'Start', but at 'Ready, set, go'.]
[Haroro is immediately disqualified.]
[Whatever MC Yoo says goes for the day.]
- But I said, 'Start', so it's not valid.
- He just didn't know. Give him a break.
- Ha Ha is disqualified.
- It's because one of us is foreign.
Fabien just said that one of
them is foreign.
[The French boy is looking after
foreign Ha Ha.]
It's because he's not very good at
understanding Korean yet.
To Otswiri and Fabien,
Ha Ha is the foreigner.
[That actually kind of makes sense.
To Otswiri and Fabien, Ha Ha is the foreigner.]
- Please give us a break.
- Sorry to say this, but Ha Ha is disqualified.
[Rules are rules!
Ha Ha is unfortunately disqualified.]
Okay, at 'Ready, set, go'.
Ready, set, go.
One.
Two.
- Three.
- Four.
- Five!
[Cha Yu Ram and Yoon Bo Mi
are simultaneously disqualified.]
- Cha Ru Ram and Yoon Bo Mi are disqualified.
- I told you not to do it.
You're the one who got disqualified,
so why are you hitting me?
Cha Yu Ram and Yoon Bo Mi
are unfortunately disqualified.
Ready, set, go.
- One.
[As soon as the game starts,
Blank Ji and Ji Sung are disqualified.]
And with that last round, one
member from each team is disqualified.
[One member from each team is disqualified.]
[Who knew that noonchi game
was such a fierce battle?]
Are you all ready?
Ready, set, go
[Joo Ji Hoon succeeds while everyone's
too busy looking at Kwang Soo.]
One!
[Ji Hoon just said one...]
Disqualified!
[Ah... Big-nosed Brother...]
I couldn't hear anything back there!
But he said it loudly.
He said it loudly enough.
[Big-nosed Brother brings about laughter
with his hard hearing.]
But I really didn't hear anything.
Your team still has a chance at survival as
long as Jong Kook doesn't get eliminated
so don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it myself.
I guess your team is heading to Busan.
I guess your team will be heading
to Busan.
I'm sure it's been a while since
you've last visited Busan.
- So you can take a trip to Busan.
- But we really didn't hear anything.
It's not that you didn't hear,
but you decided not to hear.
Everyone had better speak up.
- How many players are still left in the game?
- Ready, set, go.
One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Four.
- Five.
[Sung Hyun gets flustered
and pops up from his seat.]
He really needs to go to the bathroom.
Sung Hyun is disqualified!
Fabien and Otswiri are quite impressive.
Otswiri is really good at this game.
And they're like experts of this game.
- They seem so relaxed.
- So relaxed while playing the game.
- I will do the best I can.
- Where did you learn to play this game?
Don't you think that
you're too good at this game?
Otswiri just said that he'll represent
Korea in this game.
Ready, set, go.
One.
Two.
- Three.
[Team Sports All-stars' wins
the Busan trip!]
[Remaining stars are celebrating not
having to go all the way to Busan.]
[It's going to take some time to go to Busan,
then having to double back to Gyungjoo.]
Let's give a round of applause to
Team Sports All-stars' for going to Busan.
[Rubbing salt into the wound
by asking for a round of applause.]
Bye, Jong Kook!
[Playing music from his speaker?]
[The music you hear is Grasshopper playing
a song to aggravate the tiger even further.]
[The music ends, and Otswiri now gets up
to dance along to the music.]
[You just wait and see...]
We will soon be arriving at Shin Station.
Your mission will start the moment
you get off this train.
Do you see what's been set up on
the platform?
Don't have too much fun without us.
[Arrives at Shingyoung Station.]
They're all getting off.
[With the exception of Sports All-star Team,
everyone else gets off the train.]
What's this?
[A mission card as soon as
they get off the train.]
Kim Jong Kook and the rest of his teammates
will continue on with their train ride.
[The one team that weren't able to
get off the train with the others...]
Bye.
I can't even see them from here.
What's going on here?
They're filming out there on the platform.
I told you guys not to
shout out too prematurely.
- Yes, we had a plan.
- We actually had good seats for that game.
We could've observed others and
predict what they were going to do.
- Did you hear Ji Hoon earlier?
- No, I didn't hear him either.
- I couldn't hear a thing from back here.
- To be honest, I actually heard him.
You heard him?
[Even though she heard Ji Hoon,
she still argued that she didn't.]
You did good.
I like that kind of mentality.
- We are a team.
- I need to dispute it if I can.
[Have fun conversing amongst yourselves,
during your train ride to Busan.]
We will now start picking your mission cards.
[The rest of the teams busy themselves
choosing their first mission cards.]
Do we just choose whichever one we want?
Yes, all four cards are the same.
[Go to '__' house, and find the 'R' flag.]
If you go to the three locations
listed on the card
you'll be able to find a hint
to help you solve this mission.
[Go to '__' house, and find the 'R' flag.]
If we can figure it out after
going to just one of these locations
then can we just go to the location
that the clue is indicating to?
[Can guess at any time that they want.]
Everyone.
- I will see you all in a little bit.
- Okay.
- Is it a celebrity's home?
- No, it's not.
We need to go to those three locations to
get clues to the home this is indicating to.
If we go to these three locations
I bet someone will be there to tell us
one letter to the three letter word.
That's my best guess.
- I really want to ride this.
- Can we go ride this?
- I really want to go on that ride.
- Can we please go, Gary?
Why are you girls doing this to me?
I really don't want to!
Can we please go?
- It has to be a less crowded space.
- Where are you guys going?
[MC Yoo's thoughtful surprise hearing test.]
Hello, Driver.
We're going to Ahnapji Pond.
I just lied to them thwart them off.
[I don't think anyone was even
listening to you.]
[Off to find their hints!]
Since Gyungjoo was the capitol city
during the Shilla period...
- Seriously? This place?
- Yes, you're right.
- Bulkuksa Temple is very famous.
- Yes, that's right.
- There are so many beautiful things there.
- Yes, you're right.
[Amazing! Fabien is so well knowledged
in Korea's history!]
I wanted to learn as much as I could
about Gyungjoo before coming here today.
If the final mission is going to be
a quiz battle
aren't you pretty good at
things like that?
- No, I don't know much about anything.
- But you read a lot.
But it doesn't matter because
most of the books I read are fiction.
What about you, Ji Sung?
You're good at quiz questions, right?
- Good at what?
- Quiz questions.
I'm not good at thinking on my feet.
How would you describe your ideal man?
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- You like men like Jae Suk?
- He's so amazing.
- What is it about him that you like?
- He really is amazing.
- What do you like most about Jae Suk?
- He's so kind.
- He is so kind.
- He is exactly what you see.
- Totally.
[Gary's first impression was much more
chic and impressionable than expected.]
A man needs to be chic
and kind of mysterious too.
- If a man is too nice...
- Yes, you're right.
- It's not as attractive.
- But there's something about Jae Suk, right?
There's just no way to beat
Yoo Jae Suk.
[This unbeatable man is busy
taking in the sights of Gyungjoo.]
I think we've already been here before.
We've been here before, haven't we?
[Gyungjoo, a city full of history-
Historical ruins as far as the eye can see.]
It's Ha Ha.
- Yes, hello?
- Hello, Jae Suk.
- Excuse me?
- It's Otswiri and Fabien calling.
What is it, Otswiri?
Well, it's nothing important,
but you know how Ha Ha is on our team?
- Yeah.
- But Ha Ha really doesn't know anything.
No, he really doesn't know anything.
We're on our way to the first location,
but we had to call you for some help.
Do you by any chance have any hints
that you can give us?
I really am sorry to tell you this,
but I really don't know anything either.
- But you must know something...
- Ask him where he's going right now.
- Where are you going right now?
- Put Ha Ha on the phone.
- Ha Ha's in the bathroom right now.
- What?
- He's pooping in the bathroom right now.
- Come on, don't lie to me like that.
He's not feeling very well right now,
we don't know where we're going.
In that case, call me back
once Ha Ha comes back.
- Ah... oh, here he is right now.
- Hello?
- Jae Suk.
- There you are, Ha Ha.
- No, I just got here.
That was all a lie, wasn't it?
You guys lied to me, didn't you?
Where are you going right now?
[MC Yoo is headed to the '__' home right now.]
Come on, help us out here.
Just tell us where you're going.
Just follow me.
[Hangs up on Ha Ha and his team.]
[Where is Jae Suk headed?]
[Question- '___' home.]
[Just then, Team Film Stars arrives at
the Palace of the Crown Prince.]
- Thank you.
- I think this is the place.
[Hurried inside the palace
to find their hint.]
I wonder what we'll have to do in here.
[King Munmu's second palace that he had built
to commemorate the unification of Shilla.]
[The palace where King Munmu entertained his
most valued guests and hosted events.]
[Team Film Stars starts to run without
a clue as to what they're looking for.]
- Let's go check it out.
- Did we make a mistake coming here?
[Where could their hint be?]
- That other team is here too.
- This is where all the parties used to be.
Yes, that's right.
- This is where all the royals would gather.
- And they'd drink together.
[Impressively breathtaking views.]
I feel so at peace in here.
- I think that's Kwang Soo over there.
- Yes, I just saw them too.
[Discovers Team Film Stars.]
[Sooner they find the hint,
sooner they can move on.]
Here it is!
I see the 'R' mark.
- I see it too.
- Where? Oh, right over there.
[This place is...]
We're not going to have to
go up in that, are we?
We don't have to go up in that, do we?
[Yes, you will have to go up.]
[Not just that, but very high!]
- We can do it, Gary!
- 150m?
- We really have to go up?
- Come on, we're all friends now.
[On the other hand, the girls
are excited about the balloon ride.]
- This is going to be so much fun.
- Women are always causing trouble.
[Giant hot air balloon ride.]
Gentle!
[It's off the ground!]
Which way are we going?
We're going 150m up into the air
in this thing?
[Flying up into the sky!]
[A wide open view of everything
from the sky.]
We're up really high right now.
You should try looking down below.
Do you think that the hint is
somewhere down below?
- You need to look around you.
- See? We need to search below.
- Hey girls.
- I don't see anything yet.
Hey, since we have to do that thing
from up here...
I mean, down below and from afar...
[Being 150m up in the air makes
Leader Gae tongue tied.]
Wait a minute, why is that music playing?
- I'm starting to feel sick.
- Do you know the song that's playing?
- No.
- Do you know this song, Bo Mi?
Don't you think that the song
means something?
- I think it's our hint.
- Listen carefully to the lyrics.
[The sound of the song fills up the open sky.]
Careless jokes we tell?
Do you know who sings this song?
Do we have to know who sings it?
[I know I've heard this song before...]
Of all the things that I've lost...
Hey!
There it is!
[Did he discover something down there?]
[This is the hint to finding out which
house the mission is indicating to!]
There's an app for the QR code.
Go into the app store.
Ji Hoon, I doubt it's something
technical like that.
We just need to find the hint somewhere.
- Really?
- Yeah, it doesn't require deep thinking.
We're not going to have to solve riddles
regarding the palace or anything.
The hint is probably hidden somewhere.
Ji Hoon!
I'm telling you that's not it.
You're not even listening to me.
[Please listen to me!]
[Okay, let's go look for clues.]
Ha Ha!
[Did they find something?]
Here it is.
[Fabien pulls a trick to throw them off.]
[It was a trick...]
- Did he really trick us?
- Let's go the other way.
A foreigner tricked us in our own language.
Just where in the world is it hidden?
Hey!
Did you find something?
[Just where could their hint be hidden?]
[Just then, Ji Hoon starts heading off
towards something.]
Here it is!
[He discovers the written hint!]
Okay.
Is there only one hint?
This wasn't a game that
required intelligence.
I read too deep into it for nothing.
Be careful not to rip it.
[What kind of a hint is written on the note?]
Chang... Soo?
Bu-chang-Bu-Soo.
(Conjugal harmony.)
[Smart Ji Hoon guesses it correctly
as soon as he sees the hint.]
This has to be the answer.
['__' home-
Palace of the Crown Prince- 'Bu'.]
- We have to go find the hint.
- You go that way and we'll go this way.
- Are you trying to leave me?
- Let's talk only in English from now on.
Do you think that I won't be able to
understand you if you spoke in English?
- Fine, speak in English!
- How about we speak in French instead?
French?
You think I don't know French?
He's going to keep following us.
Watch your language!
Kwang Soo!
[The other two smart guys call out to
Kwang Soo after having found the hint.]
- Did you find something?
- Hurry up, Kwang Soo.
Just come on.
We found it.
[The variety leader who's
not any sort of help.]
They must've found it.
Otswiri.
I'm sorry.
- I have to go, but it was fun.
- Okay.
[Puts on a haughty act
after having done absolutely nothing.]
- I think they found something.
- What? Let us come with you.
- Let's just all go together.
- No, you can't.
- We have to remain loyal to each other.
- Our shirts are different colors.
- But we should still remain loyal.
- I can't do that.
[Ghana and France are pressing
Kwang Soo for his loyalty.]
I told you that he's the worst
kind of traitor there is.]
Where's Ha Ha right now?
[I said, come right now!]
- Sorry!
- Let us come with you!
- We're on different teams.
- Let us come with you.
[Giraffe gets dragged off by
enthusiastic Ji Hoon.]
[Just where is Ha Ha in the
midst of all this?]
['The foreigner' has lost his way...]
[Finds the hint from having gotten lost.]
'__' Chang, '__' Soo.
[Bu-Chang- Bu-Soo. Conjugal harmony.
Wife follows the lead of her husband.]
The clue said, Bu-Chang- Bu-Soo.
But the 'Bu' was omitted.
What's Bu-Chang- Bu-Soo?
- Then should we...
- Let's go to one more place.
[Off to find their second hint to figure out
where the mission was indicating to.]
One was a little park by the pond
and the other was some sort of
hot air balloon.
- Is it close by?
- Yes, it's close.
[Team Beautiful is currently
taking their turn on the hot air balloon.]
When you feel scared,
just stare off into the distance.
Can you see your house from here?
Can you see Tongyoung from here?
[While this team is busy
searching for their hint...]
- We're going to be 100 minutes behind.
- If we calculate all the times...
We have to catch up to them if we can.
- We have to get off.
- Do we have to get off this ride?
[Finally arrives at Busan Station.]
- We can do it.
- Don't worry, Yu Ram.
[Yu Ram is feeling anxious
to get to where they need to go.]
[Must find the train that will get them
to Shinkyung Station as soon as possible.]
I never would've guessed that
I'd be coming to Busan today.
- So this is Busan?
- Yes, this is Busan.
- Wow, seriously.
- There it is.
What time is it right now?
- We can take the 3:30 train.
- 3:30 train?
It's in 15 minutes.
We can take the 3:30 train.
- Okay, this is good.
- Hello.
- How much to Shinkyung Station?
- There are three of us.
[They get lucky and find
three empty seats on the train!]
The train is scheduled to arrive at 3:56.
[A high speed train which will get them
to Shinkyung Station in only 26 minutes!]
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day!
- Good, we're all set.
- I think we should get going right now.
[Not much time before
the high speed train takes off.]
- Let's take a quick picture before we go.
- Okay.
[Even though they didn't want it,
since them came all the way here...]
Let's take a picture with the
Busan Station sign in the background.
[A quick trip down to Busan without even
stepping foot outside the train station.]
[In memory of their quick visit to Busan.]
- Wow, this height is no joke.
- Look carefully below you.
We need one person to look to the right,
and one person to look to the left.
[Just like the last mission, only
these two are carrying on the mission.]
Listen carefully to the song.
- I hear some song in the background.
- Why are they playing a song?
It's 'Here's to Romance' by Choi Baek Ho.
What's the name of this song?
[Team Beautiful seeks help from onlookers.]
Does anyone know what this song is?
- Choi Baek Ho's 'Here's to Romance'.
- Choi Baek Ho!
- Yes, Choi Baek Ho!
- It's Choi Baek Ho!
[That's right! Choi Baek Ho!]
[Smart Ji Hoon correctly guesses
the answer again in first try!]
There it is down there too.
Baek Ho.
[Confirms their answer with
the hint on the hot air balloon.]
- Choi Baek Ho!
- Thank you!
Thank you and we love you!
- Thank you. The hint is, Baek Ho.
- But what does that even mean?
Is it Choi Baek Ho's house?
Is that what it means?
So Choi Baek Ho has to fit
somewhere within this riddle somehow.
[Time to start piecing the clues together.]
['__' home-
Palace of the Crown Prince- 'Bu'.]
[Giant hot air balloon- 'Choi'.]
Ji Hyo!
I found it!
[Team Beautiful heads off to
Palace of the Crown Prince.]
- Bu-Chang- Bu-Soo.
- Bu-Chang- Bu-Soo?
[Sung Hyun figures it out
as soon as he sees it.]
Choi, Bu... Choi Bu Ram?
Choi Bu...
It's supposed to be someone's home.
[Clues they've earned so far-
'Bu' and 'Choi'.
Sir, the final place that we
have to go to is
is a home with the letter,
'Choi' in it.
[Meanwhile, Team Idols is trying to figure out
their hint at Queen Sundeok's garden.]
['__' home.
Clues pieced together- 'Bu-Choi-Ja'.]
- It's someone with the last name of Choi.
- That would be Choi Bu Ja.
[Choi Bu Ja's home?]
Choi Bu Ja?
Who's Choi Bu Ja?
- Choi Bu Ja.
- Who's Choi Bu Ja?
[Other teams slowly start to
piece the puzzle together.]
- Come on, we need to hurry!
- But who's Choi Bu Ja?
[It's now all about who can get there first!]
Is there a Choi Bu Ja home in the area?
- There is?
- It's in Gyochon.
Choi Bu Ja's home is in Gyochon?
Is it a famous place?
[Choi Bu Ja's home is known by
anyone who lives in Gyungjoo.]
Okay, we understand.
Thank you so much.
It has to be it.
I'm sure of it!
Come on, let's go!
Do you know where Choi Bu Ja's home is?
[Then could that be where
MC Yoo is right now?]
Gyungjoo's Choi Bu Ja home?
[Bingo!
This is Choi Bu Ja's home!]
[Choi Bu Ja's home.]
[Other members have to find their way to
old Gyochon town where Choi Bu Ja's home is.]
[Town of Gyochon and Choi's old residence.]
I thought that the driver was going to
answer all our quiz questions for us.
Okay, here's your question.
When I asked him about the house...
[Driver's correct answer was full of
eagerness and enthusiasm.]
You got the correct answer.
[Just which of the three teams
will get there first?]
Time to get off.
[Team Sports All-stars' finally arrives
at Shingyoung after their Busan detour.]
Yu Ram is a perfect fit for Running Man.
[Just who will be the first to touch ground
at Choi Bu Ja's home?]
[Which of these six teams
will get there first?]
There they are.
[That winning team is none other than...]
[Team Beautiful.]
[Reunited with MC Yoo after
only two hours.]
- You guys got here way too early.
- We figured it out pretty quick.
- Why don't you go get a cup of coffee?
- How about a cup of Americano?
- Americano?
- Yes, Americano.
Choi Bu Ja was a very famous nobleman.
- I had no idea who he was.
- No, he was a real man.
- I came here in a daze...
- This is what's so great about Running Man.
You all made it here even though
you didn't know anything about this man.
- We really didn't know anything.
- Go find the 'R' flag quickly.
[Must hurry and find the 'R' flag!]
- Somewhere in this village...
- In the village?
- In this traditional village?
- Yes, somewhere within this entire village.
There is an 'R' flag
hidden within the village.
You have to find the flag and
bring it back to me to win this mission.
[Wait... somewhere within this huge village?]
[And we have to search through
the whole entire village?]
[We thought having solved
the riddle was the end of it!]
[Now we have to tackle
an even bigger mountain!]
Please search carefully for the 'R' flag.
Wow, but you guys are impressive.
How did they ever find this house?
How are we going to search through
this entire village?
This huge village... this whole place?
Just how in the world
are we ever going to find it?
We're here.
No one else is here yet, right?
We're the first ones here, right?
What? We're not the first ones here?
Are we the first ones here?
Just stand still.
No, you're not the first ones here.
Another team already beat you here,
and this is not the end of it.
How did a foreigner like you
find your way here?
[Haroro is the designated foreigner
of this team.]
Then we found the second clue,
Jang-Hwa Ja-Chang.
- Yes, that's right.
- So we pieced the two clues together.
Since he's not from this country,
he was mistaken about the clue for a while.
[It was Fabien
who correctly figured out the clue.]
Once we pieced it all together,
we were able to get 'Choi Bu Ja'.
Now you have to go and find
the 'R' marked flag.
'R' marked flag.
- Let's split up!
- That's what I love about Otswiri and Fabien.
They have the greatest reactions.
Look at how surprised they looked.
[The best reactionary couple.]
- Where have you guys been?
- We just got here. What about you guys?
- I was looking over that way.
- You're looking for the flag, right?
- Kimbap?
- No, the flag. (Word play.)
No, we're going to go on the
amusement rides.
[Tripping up so many native Korean speakers
with his Korean speaking skills.]
- You guys actually went to Busan?
- Yes, we went all the way to Busan.
[Team Sports All-stars' finally joins others
after taking a detour to Busan.]
- You guys made really good time.
- Seriously?
The other teams got here
less than five minutes ago.
You guys got here really fast
for having gone all the way to Busan.
- How did you get here so fast?
- Are you trying to tease us right now?
- How's Busan?
- We just turned around and came right back.
We just hopped on the return train back here
as soon as we got off the train.
- We didn't even get to look around.
- But wasn't it fun?
Yes, maybe for you.
- Just tell us what we need to do.
- You must find the hidden 'R' flag.
You have to find the 'R' marked flag
and bring it back to me.
- Just one?
- Yes, you only need to find one.
- Just one for our entire team?
- Yes, that's correct.
Have you guys seen any flags yet?
- Have you seen any flags yet?
- No, we haven't seen any.
No, I was asking Jae Suk.
[Kkuk leaves all his personal belongings
on the table with Jae Suk.]
- Excuse me, Jong Kook?
- Yes?
This isn't guest services.
- But it really weighs down my pockets!
- Why are you always so angry?
- Let me just leave these here.
- Then why do you even work out?
Why do you even work out if
things like this are too heavy for you?
- Seriously.
- Did you hide the flag somewhere, Jae Suk?
- No, I didn't hide anything.
- Did you try looking for the flag?
No, I didn't look for the flag.
I'm just relaying what the writers told me.
- Don't you think that he hid it somewhere?
- No, I'm serious. I didn't hide anything.
May the heavens strike me down
if I hid the flag somewhere myself.
You've already been struck down
several times.
['R' flag is hidden in a place where no one
could've even fathomed...]
So we're just looking for the flag without
any directions of where we're looking?
- Yeah, we're just on the search for it.
- Seriously?
[From QR code to tracking devices-
He is just too smart for our level...]
Hey, what is going on with this?
Where's the flag?
[No matter how hard they search,
the 'R' flag is nowhere to be seen.]
No one's found it yet, right?
No, no one's found it yet,
and that's why I'm out here.
- Do you not know where it is either?
- No, I don't know.
Had I known, I'm sure I would've
told you two already by now.
- Ha Ha is busy searching too.
- You haven't found it either?
Just look harder.
Search hard enough and you'll find it.
- Hand it over.
- What?
Look here, foreigner.
Foreigner, you need to start doing better.
- Fighting.
- Thank you.
How am I ever going to find it?
- Look very carefully.
- Do you know where it is?
No, I don't know.
- Yes, you do know.
- No, I really don't know.
I'm in the same boat as you.
I just found out myself when I got here.
It's hidden somewhere unexpected?
[It's hidden in the most unexpected place!]
Could it be on Jae Suk somewhere?
[Can't be...]
[Could the flag really be on Jae Suk?]
[Eyes locked on target.]
No, that's not it.
[Aims straight for Jae Suk's handkerchief.]
There it is!
I knew I was right!
[What?]
[Wait, that's...]
[The handkerchief MC Yoo
had in his pocket all day...]
[MC Yoo's handkerchief... is the 'R' flag!]
I knew it!
I saw Jae Suk's handkerchief in his pocket
and this feeling just came over me.
I knew something was weird about it.
- And I knew it had to be on Jae Suk.
- I seriously had no idea.
- I thought it was under your name tag.
- I really had no idea.
- I got it!
- Stop doing that. Someone will steal it.
Someone will steal the flag away from you.
- Huh?
[Keep up the screams of cheer, and
Mr. Capable will snatch it out of your hand.]
You have to be careful.
[Tie the flag onto the flagpole
to win the mission.]
- This is awesome.
- How come no one told me about it?
[Just then, Ji Sung comes onto the scene
and catches sight of what's going on.]
Get him.
That's the flag.
[Flees the scene!]
Everyone, Ha Ha is fleeing
with the flag in his hands.
Everyone!
Wait, let's talk.
We need to talk.
Come on, let's talk.
You really shouldn't be like that.
Jae Suk took it from me.
Jae Suk took it and he has it now.
- Is that right?
- Yes, I'm telling the truth.
I'm being totally serious right now.
- I'm serious. Jae Suk took it from me.
- I just saw you with it.
- I'm serious. Jae Suk has it.
- I know you have it on you.
Let's hide the flagpole for now.
[Something doesn't feel right...]
Come on!
He's somewhere around here.
Come on, and bring Jong Kook with you.
- What did you say?
- Oh, there you are.
- Where is it?
- My handkerchief was the 'R' flag.
- Who took the flag?
- Ha Ha did.
- Ha Ha took the flag.
- Where is it, Ha Ha?
- Ji Sung has something behind his back.
- What do you have?
Is that the 'R' flag?
No, the flag still has to be found.
So the flag has to be found
and tied to this flagpole?
Yes, you have to find the flag
and tie it to this flagpole.
So Ji Sung has the flagpole
and Ha Ha has the flag.
That's right.
Ha Ha took my handkerchief.
Wow, but Ha Ha really is a clever one.
- You have it on you right now, right?
- Yes, he has it on him right nw.
- I think he has it in his pants.
- No, I threw it.
Okay, I would like to
reiterate myself one more time.
My handkerchief was the 'R' flag.
- I was totally shocked.
- Did you bring this?
- Who took it?
- Give me the flagpole, Ji Sung.
- Why?
- I need to put it over there.
You're not supposed to be
carrying it around with you.
- I'll put it back.
- Okay.
I have a feeling that he put the handkerchief
in a place where he never should've put it.
- No, because that would be cheating.
- It's okay because I can still get it.
- It's okay, he can get it.
- I have no qualms about getting it.
I just stick my hands wherever
I need to.
But to tie the flag onto that pole would
result in a bit of a physical struggle.
Yes, but he needs to overcome that.
Yes, I understand what you mean.
I seriously had no idea that I've been
carrying the flag around with me all day.
See?
Everyone's starting to crowd around him.
[The Reactionary Duo makes their appearance.]
Take it from him.
[All sorts of hands starts to search
Ha Ha's body without any hesitation.]
Okay, fine.
Wait, hold off.
Wait, look at all the people
around me right now.
This is turning out to be
quite a scene right now.
But anyway,
I was quite shocked myself.
[Still unable to believe what just happened.]
I had no idea that
my handkerchief was the flag.
Run over that way right now.
[Ha Ha makes an attempt to flee.]
No, You can't take that with you!
No, You can't take that with you.
Wow, Ji Sung.
- What am I doing this for?
- Why are you taking that with you, Ji Sung?
[Why does he keep
lusting after the flagpole?]
- You have it on you, don't you?
- I think he has it.
- I think he has it on him.
- No, he doesn't.
[Second round of flag search.]
[Did Ha Ha somehow manage to hand
the flag over to Fabien during the melee?]
Hey, we have to play defense.
- Speak English.
- No, you can't speak in English.
- Did he find it?
- You can't speak in English.
- Someone found it, I think.
- You know where it is?
[How embarrassing to have them discuss their
plans in front of them and not understand.]
[Time to switch over to French.]
I have no clue what they're saying.
I feel really left out right now.
[Are they speaking in French?]
You speak French?
[Just what is going on here!]
[Unbelievable!
Ji Hoon knows how to speak French!]
Do you know what he just said to me?
He told me to get lost!
[Sorry, but that's all I know!]
Otswiri.
You're going to have to speak in Ghanaian.
[Attack of foreign language.]
What language are you all speaking in?
Why are you doing this in Choi Bu Ja's house?
Why are you doing this in
Choi Bu Ja's home?
- Okay, everyone.
- Calm down everyone.
I don't think we'll ever see an end to this
if you keep up the physical struggle.
So I want everyone to step outside.
I will then take the flag and
hide it somewhere within this area.
[MC Yoo suggests re-hiding the flag
somewhere in the vicinity.]
[The first team to find the flag
wins the mission.]
- So we're starting over?
- Yes, everyone step outside.
[Everyone steps outside the gate
to start the mission anew.]
Okay, is everyone ready?
The first team to find the flag
automatically wins.
You can win the mission
just by finding the flag.
Ready, set, go!
[Find the flag- Round three.]
Just find the flag to win the mission.
There's no need for
a physical struggle anymore.
- Just find the flag to win.
- Where was it hidden before?
[Giraffe carefully searches MC Yoo.]
- What is it?
- Did you find it?
[While everyone is busy looking elsewhere...]
[Oh?]
[That's...]
[Discovers the flag hidden underneath
the flagpole!]
I found it!
[Ha Ha finds it again!]
[Reactionary Duo launches into action!]
[Ha Ha is showing everyone
what he's truly capable of today!]
- Maybe I'll get to go to Ghana!
- Maybe I'll get to go to France!
[Darn...]
Na Eun and Bo Mi look so disappointed.
It was right underneath the flagpole.
[Today must be Ha Ha's day.]
- I told you that it could be under it.
- Wow, very impressive.
The winning team gets two chance cards.
[First place prize-
Two MC Yoo chance cards.]
We still have one chance card left.
The winning team can choose who
they'd like to give this last card to.
- Mr. Otswiri!
- Mr. Ha Ha!
- Mr. Fabien!
[Everyone starts to beg for the card.]
Please!
- One, two, three!
- Mister, Mister!
[The Global Team chooses Team Idols.]
We still have other games left, so I
don't want the remaining teams to worry.
We still have more games left to play.
Let's move on to the next mission location.
[On to the next mission location!]
Otswiri!
[MC Yoo heads off on his own before others.]
- This is going good, right?
- Very good.
I want to feel what it's like to be led
by a five year variety show veteran.
I'm going to put all my faith in Kwang Soo.
I'll put everything I have on the line
and give it my best in the next mission.
- I'm serious.
- Let's do this for real, Kwang Soo.
This is for real, okay?
This is... where I
shot a sageuk film a while back.
What is that up there?
[Gyungjoo's 'M' park.]
There's not much time.
You must all hurry.
- Everyone must come down this way.
- Haven't we been here before?
[MC Yoo's already there to greet everyone.]
- Oh my goodness.
- Are those wind mics?
[What is this mission?
Wind mics are ready and in place?
This is not going to be anything unfamiliar.
Do you see the three mics standing there?
You are going to find several pieces of paper
with the 'R' mark hidden around here.
And there will be different answers
written on those pieces of paper.
Then you must bring the papers over to me
and explain to me what's written on the paper.
You have to use your body
to explain what's written on there.
- Then you'll have to guess the answer?
- Yes, I'll be guessing the answers.
[MC Yoo to guess the answers.]
You can't purposely
not guess it correctly, okay?
[MC Yoo has the fate of each team
in the grasp of his hands.]
You can't do anything like that, okay?
You have to be fair to all of us.
[Wrong guess, and it's wind in the face!]
Why are we the ones getting blown?
We'll get the wind blown in our face
if we get it wrong
but when all this is over,
you'll be the one to get blown in the face.
I'm just making myself very clear right now.
So you'd better not get it wrong on purpose.
I'm going to be keeping my eye on you.
[MC Yoo's chance card will be given to the
team who correctly gets two questions first.]
Ready, set, go!
[Off to find the 'R' marked
pieces of paper!]
- They're hidden throughout the place.
- It shouldn't be hard to find them.
['R' marked pieces of paper are hidden
throughout this historical place.]
Don't feel discouraged just because
you get it wrong on the first try.
[More advantageous to be the first team
to find the scraps of paper.]
['R' paper is discovered!]
So I just take this back to Jae Suk?
[Back to MC Yoo with the paper!]
[Gary also discovers the 'R' marked paper.]
Na Eun!
[Rule- All members of the team must
explain the question together.]
I found one!
[Everyone starts to discover
their own pieces of 'R' marked paper.]
- Did you find one?
- Yeah, I found one.
[Immediately heads back to MC Yoo
as soon as the paper is found.]
Over here, Jong Kook!
Ji Hoon!
Everyone needs to stand in a line.
[Team Global- Geography.]
[30 seconds on the clock.]
[Vomiting?]
[Then a pyramid?]
Vomiting?
- It was Toham Mountain.
- That's how you explain it?
[Toham Mountain- So that's
why they were imitating vomiting?]
- Then you try explaining it.
- What?
- You try explaining it then.
- For Toham Mountain...
Pass.
Let's move on to the next question.
[Explaining is your responsibility.
I only have to guess the answer.]
Ready, set, go.
[Team Idols- Fairytale.]
You're cold, and there's money?
Matches?
You're sorry?
This is just ridiculous!
[Answer- Match selling little girl.]
- You knew the answer!
- You're telling me that you didn't know?
[Must go back to find another piece of paper
if they answer a question wrong.]
Na Eun and Bo Mi looked so cute.
You two look so pretty
all windblown like that.
You look very pretty.
[Team Film Stars: Movie.]
[Screaming out of the blue?]
[MC Yoo joins in on their screaming.]
[Suddenly tackling each other
out of the blue?]
From the Han River...
He just talked.
You can't talk.
[Talking is automatic disqualification.]
[Correct answer- Monster.]
It's a monster.
But you shouldn't have said anything.
[Team Sports All-Stars: Idiom.]
Rowing up the mountain without a paddle!
Get him!
[Fails from Kwang Soo
having guessed the answer.]
- Yes, I knew the answer.
- Seriously, Kwang Soo!
- But that wasn't our fault.
- But he still answered the question.
Go find the paper,
and I'll answer their questions.
Hurry up and go find the paper.
[Team Film Stars- Idiom.]
[Crying... and armpits?]
It's spicy?
Spicy?
And crying from sweaty armpits?
You're measuring your arm?
Measuring your arms?
Mustard?
Mustard.
It's mustard, isn't it?
- Yes, it's mustard.
- Something about mustard making you cry?
Eat your mustard and cry!
- Eat your mustard and cry!
The other team answered your question
when I should be the one to answer it.
[Getting their revenge on Giraffe
using the same technique.]
Fine, let's do this.
No, you can't do that.
You have to get back down there.
- You started it first.
- I have to be the one to answer it.
- Who's going to do it?
- Okay, that's good.
[Team Beautiful- Idiom.]
You guys are really getting into it.
Yes, this is good.
Okay, that's good.
[Putting everything he has into his acting.]
Step on the worm and it'll squirm!
It wasn't
'Even a snail knows how to roll'?
- That's what I thought it was.
- No, it's not.
None of the teams have answered
their two questions yet.
[Team Sports All-stars: Idiom.]
[Goddess of billiards'
enthusiastic demonstration.]
What's that supposed to be?
Licking the watermelon!
You guys have to get into it
for me to guess it correctly like this.
[Yu Ram's clear demonstrations.]
[Team Film Stars- Object.]
- What is that?
- What are you doing?
Emile bell?
That was good.
That was your first question.
[Team Global- Idiom.]
A whale.
The shrimp's back burst
in a whale's battle.
[Bravo, MC Yoo!]
[Ready to celebrate after having
correctly explained their first question.]
Look at how happy they are.
We all have to learn from them.
[Team Idols- Song.]
Twist King.
Look at how happy Na Eun and Bo Mi are.
[Team Film Stars- Movie.]
Look at your acting skills.
Allegiance!
[Allegiance?]
[Correct answer- Wolf Boy.]
[He seems to be explaining Song Joong Ki's
current military service.]
Song Joong Ki.
[Anyone can figure out that
Kwang Soo just said, Song Joong Ki.]
[Still insists on saying Joong Ki's name.]
- It's Song Joong Ki's Wolf Boy.
- Why are you saying his name?
- Why would you say his name?
- He kept saying Joong Ki's name.
You can't say anything.
Okay, next team.
[Team Idols- Movie.]
[They're all trying to explain on their own.]
This team is really awful
at explaining things.
- You guys are really bad at explaining.
- 200 pounds of beauty!
No, I had no idea.
Absolutely no idea!
No, I had no idea!
- Okay, next team.
- Can you back up a little?
[Team Film Stars- Sports.]
- Why are you getting so into it?
- This team really gets into it.
[These three guys really get into it
like the real film stars they are.]
Curling!
[Curling- Correct answer.]
[Miraculously manages to answer
two answers correctly!]
Thank you, Jae Suk!
I couldn't not answer it
when it was so obvious.
Couldn't you say, 'coloring' instead?
No, I couldn't not answer it.
It was too obvious that it was curling.
I don't want the other teams
to get discouraged.
This game goes to Ji Joon,
Ji Sung, and Kwang Soo.
[Gyungjoo's '__' resort.]
[The final competition- A quiz battle.]
Remember running around
the waterfall over there?
[This is the place where they got chased
after by Min Soo, the Hunter.]
[A bloody fierce quiz battle taking
place at a luxury resort in Gyungjoo.]
Congratulations for having made it this far!
No, only one team can become
the champion.
We can't all become champions.
I will now explain
the rules of this competition.
There are three members to each team.
You have to choose who you think
wrote down the wrong answer
by one member from each team stepping forward
to point out that person.
And the other two members who are not
up here solving the question
will just remain in the back
by your respective station.
[One member per teams steps forward to solve
the question and the last team remaining wins.]
Otswiri is up first.
Defense players will write down
their answers to the question
and the person on the attack will have to
choose who they think answered incorrectly.
- Okay, who will Otswiri choose?
- Na Eun.
Otswiri will choose one person whom he thinks
wrote down the wrong answer.
If the person Otswiri chooses
wrote down the wrong answer
then the person he chose will
receive a water shower.
But if the person has the correct answer,
then Otswiri will be disqualified
and receive the water shower instead.
[In case of having written down
the wrong answer...]
[This is... what'll happen to you.]
[Son Na Eun is the first to be eliminated.]
But Na Eun's makeup is totally waterproof.
Her makeup isn't ruined whatsoever.
And with each question
you'll be able to use the MC Yoo chance card
which you've worked so hard to earn today.
[Defense can use the MC Yoo chance card
whenever they choose to.]
Otswiri maintains his attacker stance
from having won the last round.
[Otswiri maintains his attacker status
from having won the previous round.]
And Na Eun's miniature towers now belongs to
Otswiri's team from having
beat her in the previous round.
If Otswiri happens to lose this round,
then both of his towers
will go to the new winner.
[If Otswiri loses, then both of his towers
will go to the new winner.]
Bo Mi has stepped forward to
replace Na Eun for her team.
But one can never guess
what the final results will be.
Otswiri will now choose a category.
Common sense, Literature, Linguistics, Global,
Arts, History, Science, and Psychology.
Please choose a category.
Go with the arts category.
- Linguistics.
- Linguistics!
[Better for the attacker to choose
a more difficult category.]
- Linguistics is your next category.
- I feel confident in this category.
- Did you just say that you feel confident?
- Just a little.
Okay, here's your question.
It's a linguistic question.
A feast is described as a meal that's
of sumptuous abundance.
In that case...
what do you call a meal that
simply consists of only a bowl of rice
and only one or two side dishes
as the whole meal?
I know that you've all seen
the answer to this question before.
[We've seen the answer to this
extremely difficult sounding question?]
Okay, you all have 20 minutes
to study your questions.
[They were given 20 minutes to study for
the questions that will be asked of them.]
Wow, these are really hard.
These are really difficult questions.
[Common sense, Literature, Linguistics, Arts,
Global, History, Science, and Psychology.]
- We'll be able to get the right answers.
- Let's each memorize a few answers.
[A total of 200 questions with
not much time to memorize the answers.]
Ji Hyo, you can't fall asleep.
You have to wake up, Ji Hyo.
[Eureka!]
With only one bowl of rice,
and a simple side dish or two...
What do you call this simple
and humble meal table?
You know this answer, right?
Yes, maintaining
a stoic face is very important.
[Who would've guessed the wrong answer?]
[Escalate the chances of survival by pretending
to know the answer even if you don't.]
[The attacker has a very confused
look on his face.]
If I pretend not to know even if
I actually do know the answer
then the chance to become the attacker
gets handed over to me, right?
What?
What are you talking about?
You may be asked to leave the quiz.
[He may be asked to leave the quiz
for not knowing the rules of the game?]
You seem not to know the rules whatsoever.
If you keep this up, then you have to
start over again from Kwangmyung Station.
- Yes, I understand.
- Please be more cautious.
[Answer- Jwi-ko-Bapsang (A humble table)]
- This was the first answer I memorized.
- Is that right?
[Pretend to know the answer
even if she actually doesn't know.]
Yes, I did see her.
Bo Mi started studying backwards.
[Bo Mi studied her material backwards?]
[30 minutes ago.]
I'm going to start reading from the back.
Bo Mi's studying backwards?
[I'm different from others!
Bo Mi studies the book backwards.]
[From having studied the material backwards,
would she know what the answer is?]
- But this question wasn't in the back.
- It was somewhere in the middle, right?
- No, it was in the front.
- It was towards the front.
[So confusing!]
Do you know the correct answer, Ji Sung?
[MC Yoo comes over to check
Ji Sung's answer.]
You really are cocky, aren't you?
[What could he mean by that comment?]
You can always use your chance card.
You're always welcome to use
your chance card.
What about Ms. Blank Ji Hyo?
Don't you think that you're being
too overly confident right now?
Why?
It's the correct answer.
[Attacker is staring at Blank Ji Hyo...]
[With fire burning in his eyes.]
- Did you memorize the answer?
- Yes, I have memorized the answer.
Let me ask the others in the back.
Do you know the correct answer?
[Does Giraffe know
the correct answer to the question?]
Dried radish stalk soup and rice?
No, that's not the correct answer.
Okay, Otswiri will now make his selection.
This is the nerve wrecking moment.
Time for Otswiri's selection.
Just who...
[If the person he chooses has the wrong answer
then that person is then eliminated.]
[But if the person he chooses has the correct
answer then Otswiri will be eliminated.]
[Who will Otswiri choose?]
Song Ji Hyo.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Song Ji Hyo!
We will take a moment to see what
others have wrote down for their answers.
We will start off with Cha Yu Ram.
Yes, just show us your answer.
Jwi-ko Bapsang.
That is the correct answer.
[Had she been chosen, then
Otswiri would've been eliminated.]
Okay, Ji Sung.
Jwi-ko Bapsang!
Correct answer.
[What a relief!]
[Time for Bo Mi to reveal her answer.]
Simple bapsang!
[Had Bo Mi been chosen,
then she would've been disqualified.]
[Seeming nervous, the attacker
prepares himself for what may come.]
We still don't know what the
outcome may be.
We still don't know what Song Ji Hyo
has written down for her answer.
Song Ji Hyo,
let's get the wrong answer!
Okay, the correct answer is,
Jwi-ko Bapsang.
Time to see if Song Ji Hyo
wrote down the correct answer!
[What did Blank Ji write down for her answer?]
[Otswiri vs Ji Hyo-
What is the result of their battle?]
Jwi-ko Bapsang!
[Waterfall!]
Thus, Sam Otswiri is eliminated!
[Ji Hyo wins Otswiri's two towers.]
Now that Otswiri is eliminated
all of his towers are now in
possession of Song Ji Hyo's team.
[Ji Hyo is now the new attacker.]
What are you all saving your
chance cards for?
[Please start using your chance cards!]
So far, Na Eun of Gary's team
has been eliminated
and Sam Otswiri has been eliminated.
Song Ji Hyo is now the new attacker.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes.
Time to select the new category.
- Psychology,
- Okay, psychology.
Please give us the question.
What is the food that Casanova has said
is the best when seducing a woman?
People in the back can't say
what he answer is.
what the answer is.
I know what the answer is.
Song Ji Hyo is the new attacker
and she's watching the expression
on everyone's face right now.
[Does Ji Sung know
what the correct answer is?]
Can you repeat the question?
Okay, here's your question.
What is the food that Casanova has said
is the best when seducing a woman?
Stir-fried anchovies.
The four of you must now
write down your answers.
Does everyone in the back
know the correct answer?
Ha Ha, do you know the answer?
You have to tell me what the answer is,
not tell me to go away.
Okay? Tell me if you don't know the answer,
but don't tell me to go away.
It's now time for Song Ji Hyo
to make her attack.
Please choose whom you think
wrote down the incorrect answer.
One, two, three.
- Ji Sung.
- Okay, Ji Sung.
Ji Sung's well known for being a romantic.
She just chose to attack Ji Sung.
Let's check other people's answers.
Bo Mi?
Chocolates.
- Fabien?
- She didn't fall for my trick.
Chocolates.
Cha Yu Ram?
[Three people in a row wrote down
chocolates as their answers.]
Ji Hyo.
You thought this question was too easy,
and you yourself knew the correct answer.
[Question was much easier than
she had expected...]
[Correct answer- Chocolate.]
Ji Sung!
She's already preparing herself
for the water shower.
Okay, Ji Sung.
He really knows how to maintain
a poker face.
One.
[What is that expression on his face?]
[A smile full of ease?]
- I couldn't remember.
- He doesn't know!
[Goodbye, Ji Sung.]
[Song Ji Hyo's attack succeeds!]
- Song Ji Hyo.
- How could you not have known that?
What were you doing?
How could you not have remembered that?
I'm so sorry!
I couldn't remember!
I saw Ji Sung earlier during
the study period
and he was so focused on his studies
without even saying a single word.
He really was so focused on his studies.
Okay, let's study hard.
[Ji Sung really was focused on his studies...]
[I know everything else other than
the chocolate question.]
Song Ji Hyo really is impressive with
her ability to read people.
- I'm so proud of you!
- She chose one out of the four people.
- That really is impressive.
- Fabien's bluff was amazing.
Can you repeat the question?
[Fabien bluffs to confuse Ji Hyo.]
I knew he was faking because
he was so serious about it.
As you may all have noticed already
all the gold is starting to stack up
at Song Ji Hyo's feet again already.
[The gold temples are coming home
to their rightful owner.]
It's usually not the case when
it's just one gold prize on the line
but when there's a lot of gold on the line
or a huge gold prize on the line
then it's always Ji Hyo.
Ji Sung is now eliminated.
Now it's time for our next contestant,
Kwang Soo.
[Ignorance is bliss-
Giraffe steps up to the plate.]
[Giraffe's ability to last in these
types of games is a cause for concern.]
[Song Ji Hyo- Eliminated.]
[Bo Mi- Eliminated.]
[Fabien- Eliminated.]
[What in the world is going on?]
Okay, the competition is really
starting to heat up.
One team is already in danger
of being eliminated as a whole.
Cha Yu Ram's team is the only team
with all the members still in the game.
They are at a great advantage at the moment.
We'll just use our chance card.
Unless you use your chance card,
Yu Ram will continue to be the attacker.
I will use my chance card to
steal her attacker position.
[Ha Ha uses his MC Yoo chance card
to steal the attacker position.]
Okay, Ha Ha.
It's time for you to choose the category.
Science.
It's a species of trees that grows in
a damp and humid environment.
These trees provide fruits
which are sweet to the taste and the nose.
Thus, fruits from these trees can either be
eaten raw or cooked.
These trees also provide Chiclet,
which can be made into chewing gum.
So what is the name of this tree?
Please write down the name
of these trees.
I think this is going to be an easy question
to eliminate a player with.
- Come on.
- What?
[Is he laughing because Gary
wrote down an obviously wrong answer?]
Okay, Ha Ha has the chance card which allows
him to see the first letter of the word.
- So you can use this chance card.
- No, I don't want to use that.
If you don't use this and
choose the wrong person
then your team is done for.
No, it's not being ridiculous to use it now.
If you don't pick the right person
then it's all over for your team.
- It's obvious who it's going to be.
- Really?
[Could it be this guy?]
[Or him?]
Okay, then please make your selection.
You two play rock-paper-scissors.
[Play for who's going to get
the water shower?]
I really hope that he chooses me.
[Is he trying to play reverse psychology?]
Lee Kwang Soo, your face is beet red.
Why is your face so red?
[Kwang Soo's extremely red face.]
You want to get picked?
Don't pick either one of us.
Okay, who is it going to be?
[Time for Ha Ha to attack
and make his selection.]
Huh Kyung Hwan.
- Ha Ha, I really know the answer.
- Okay.
Okay, we'll start with Cha Yu Ram.
Cha Yu Ram?
[Cha Yu Ram to reveal her answer first.]
- I got really confused.
- Let's see your answer.
[Focused like she focuses on her sport-
Studies with a laser sharp focus.]
[Chewing gum tree- Sapodilla tree.]
Chewing gum tree is the correct answer.
- Is there even such a thing?
- Yes.
- Correct answer is, chewing gum tree.
- I guarantee...
[I'm telling you that I know the answer'.]
I bet every penny I have!
He definitely doesn't know the answer.
[Ha Ha is too happy about his attack?]
[He could have the right answer...]
Okay, let's see Gary's answer.
He got the correct answer!
The chewing gum tree!
I can be pretty random like that.
Okay, next.
Next up is, Lee Kwang Soo.
Coconut?
[He doesn't disappoint.]
I was going to swing out with an upper cut
when I just saw your answer.
I'm just not familiar with this category.
- I just didn't know.
- You don't know the answer to anything.
[Please Kwang Soo...]
- I'm not even nervous about this.
- Let's check and see his answer.
- Huh Kyung Hwan?
- Who doesn't know the answer to this?
Let's see what you have wrote down
for your answer.
[Time to check Kyung Hwan's answer.]
[Oh?]
[He couldn't possibly...]
What kind of a tree?
[Totally ridiculous answer.]
[Goodbye...]
[Ha Ha's attack succeeds.]
I was pushed back here by the water.
- I really don't want to get hit by the water.
- Ha Ha gets the towers!
[Ha Ha is given the possession of
Kyung Hwan's towers.]
[Team Beautiful's Baek Sung Hyun
takes the stage.]
Ha Ha still has the attacker position.
Please select your next category.
- Common sense.
- Okay, common sense.
Please give us the next question.
The '@' mark,
which is used when emailing someone
is commonly known as,
the 'snail' in our country.
In Denmark, they refer to that mark
as the 'Elephant nose'.
In Hungary, they refer to the mark as
the 'Worm'.
In that case, what is the mark referred
to as in the Netherlands?
I know this one.
I remember studying this one.
You know the answer to this one?
What is it?
Ha Ha does know the answer.
[Even Ha Ha knows the answer
to this question!]
Na Eun does know the correct answer!
[What is the '@' mark referred to as
in the Netherlands?]
[Correct answer- Monkey's tail.]
Shall we check your answer?
Do you know what it is?
[MC Yoo checks the answer.]
It's time to send Kwang Soo out.
Don't you think that Kwang Soo
probably doesn't know what it is?
I just memorized all the answers.
How can you memorize all the answers
without knowing the questions?
[Even his own teammate
has no response to that.]
How can he memorize the answers without
knowing what he question is?
[Is that the Giraffe's special secret?]
So I'll get the water shower if
everyone gets the correct answer?
- Shall we check the answers?
- That question was way too easy.
If Ha Ha doesn't choose the right person,
then it's the end for him and his team.
This is no time to save your chance card.
- I'll use my chance card.
- Okay.
[MC Yoo's chance card is used to check
the first letter of the word.]
- Can you only see the first letter?
- But I can see everyone's first word, right?
I'll be taking a look at the answers
to let you know what the first letter is.
You can only choose two teams.
Which teams will you choose?
You can only choose two.
- Look at the expression on their faces.
- Get Kwang Soo out of the game.
Take a good look at their expressions.
Okay, let's go with Kwang Soo first.
Kwang Soo and...
Cha Yu Ram.
We'll start with Kwang Soo,
and I'll let you know the first letter.
[Answer- Monkey's tail.
MC Yoo takes a look.]
Won.
(Won-soong-Yi= Monkey.)
[Then there's a high chance that
he probably has the correct answer.]
First letter of her word is... won.
[Yu Ram's first letter is also, 'won'.]
No!
Even if they both have the same letter,
wouldn't Kwang Soo be a better chance?
[That's the truth.]
It's time for Ha Ha to make his decision.
Could this be the first question to which
Kwang Soo knows the correct answer to?
[Come on!]
I think everyone knows.
I think everyone knows the answer.
Three, two, one.
[Ha Ha's turn to choose and
make the attack.]
Baek Sung Hyun!
Could he have answered incorrectly?
Okay, time to check Bae Sung Hyun's answer.
[An unreadable expression.]
[Young Sung Hyun showed just how
competitive he could be.]
[Even though others joked around him,
he showed how focused he can be.]
Okay, time to check Bae Sung Hyun's answer.
[Bae Sung Hyun's answer]
- Monkey's tail.
- That's the correct answer!
That's the correct answer!
[Kiddie monkey gets soaked.]
Thus, Otswiri, Fabien and Ha Ha
are eliminated as a team!
[The other teams break out in cheer.]
[Sung Hyun now possesses three towers
and the position to attack.]
- This is the first answer Kwang Soo knew.
- Monkey's tail.
[Giraffe knew the answer!]
Sung Hyun.
It's time to select your category.
- I'll go with, Global.
- Global.
Here's your question.
Even though this act is tabooed in India
since it's viewed as an act of insult...
but in our country, it's viewed as a
type of drinking game.
What is this act the question is referring to?
Please write down the act.
It's time for you to choose a team.
I'd like to use my chance card.
[Using MC Yoo's chance card to
eliminate one team.]
This is the chance card to tell which
team has written down as the answer.
Okay, I will let you know which team you pick
has the correct or the incorrect answer.
Cha Yu Ram.
[Chooses Cha Yu Ram.]
Okay, Cha Yu Ram's answer is...
'Wink'.
It's the correct answer.
[Cha Yu Ram has the correct answer.]
Okay, you have to choose
one of the other two teams.
[Sung Hyun to choose one of
the other two teams.]
- Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo hasn't had a single correct answer
except for the recent monkey's tail.
[Could the Giraffe pull off another miracle?]
Let's check Gary's answer.
[Time to check Gary's answer.]
- I didn't know.
- He didn't know!
- Gary didn't know the answer.
- But you're always out drinking.
But I don't usually wink at anyone.
I've been keeping my eye on Gary
and this is the first time that Gary
hasn't provided the correct answer.
So it's now Kwang Soo's turn.
Please show us your answer!
[Could the Giraffe pull off another miracle?]
- This is really hard.
- Yeah, it looks hard.
I think I'm just going to
memorize the answers.
What use is it if you only
memorize the answers?
[A special technique used only
by the Giraffe.]
[He only... memorized the answers!]
Please show us your answer!
[Giraffe only memorized the answers
during the study period.]
[Did he memorize the answer?]
Wink!
[Correct answer!]
[Crap!]
[Sung Hyun falls trap to Kwang Soo's trick!]
Wink!
How can this be?
[Team Beautiful eliminated as a whole.]
I was wrong about you, Kwang Soo.
I'm sorry.
[Shocking new contender of the Quiz Battle.]
Wow... this really is unexpected.
I think it's time...
to show what I'm truly made of.
There are people who are good test takers
even if they're not normally good students.
[Giraffe is just a good test taker?]
Lee Kwang Soo finally
has the attack position.
This really is unexpected.
Cha Yu Ram still is in the lead
with all the members still in the game.
Kwang Soo, please choose your category.
- Art!
- Okay, art.
Okay, here's your question.
What is the skill called when a glyph
is hand drawn freestyle?
[Answer- Calligraphy.]
[Did everyone memorize the correct answer?]
But what Kwang Soo needs
to really think about
is that Joo Ji Hoon is still left
remaining on his team.
So he must carefully use his chance card to
surpass the team that's currently in the lead.
Why are you saying things like that?
- Are you going to use your chance card?
- I'm going to use my chance card.
Which chance card would you like to use?
The chance to be notified of
one of the incorrect answers.
- Chance to be notified of the wrong answer.
- Let you know if there's a wrong answer.
[If MC Yoo sees an incorrect answer,
then notify the attacker of it.]
[Are there no wrong answers?]
I'll know who has the wrong answer
if you just tell me if there even is one.
- See if you can guess who it is.
- Okay.
One person's answer is,
Sign Language.
[One of the two answered,
Sign Language.]
- Am I free to choose now?
- Yes, please make your selection.
Who would've ever thought that
a day like this would come to find Kwang Soo?
[Think of this as your one and only day,
and enjoy it while you can.]
Use one more chance card.
I don't know what chances you have,
but use it.
[Both defense players avoid
meeting Kwang Soo's gaze.]
- This is a very crucial selection process.
- Can I use another chance card?
- No, don't use it.
- Yes, you may use it.
[Going to use another chance card
to ensure his successful attack?]
- I'm going to use another chance card.
- What is it?
The chance to see the future!
MC Yoo to tell me how many people
has the incorrect answer.
You are so stupid!
That's pretty much the same thing!
I told you not to use it.
You really are using
your chance card so uselessly.
So I have to let you know how many correct
and incorrect answers there are?
There are...
no correct answers.
Then couldn't you have just used that one
in the first place?
[Just leave me alone!]
[They both have incorrect answers!
Who will Giraffe choose to eliminate?]
What are you even hesitating about?
You have to eliminate her!
It's not a bad idea to go one on one either.
That's ridiculous.
All their members are still alive.
[Who will Kwang Soo choose?]
Cha Yu Ram!
[Team Sports All-Stars' first elimination.]
Calligraphy is the correct answer.
[What a moment for the Giraffe!
A total of 11 gold towers!]
Even though Kwang Soo was able to save
his team from a moment of danger
on the other hand, he totally wasted away
both of the team's chance cards.
[A total waste of the chance cards.]
[So as his punishment...
he's eliminated at the very next round.]
[The true face of tragedy.]
Ji Suk Jin and Kim Jong Kook are still alive
for Team Sports All-Stars
and Gary and Joo Ji Hoon are the only ones
left remaining for their respective teams.
It's time for Gary to make his attack.
[Gary, Jong Kook, Ji Hoon-
Down to the wire!]
- Literature.
- Okay, Literature.
Okay, here's your literature question.
Irish poet, William Yates...
I really studied this category too.
What was he referring to when he said,
'Mistake of an angel'?
- This isn't that hard.
- Shall I take a look?
[Correct answer- Dimples.]
- I'd like to use MC Yoo's chance card.
- The chance to see the future.
[Uses the chance card to see
how many incorrect answers there are.]
There are...
[A precise and useful chance card-
How many incorrect answers are there?]
There are...
Two correct answers.
[Two correct answers.]
- There aren't any wrong answers?
- No, there aren't any wrong answers.
Goodbye.
[Shower right now.]
Thus, Son Na Eun, Bo Mi and Gary
are all eliminated as a team.
Now there are only three people left with
Joo Ji Hoon, Ji Suk Jin, and Kim Jong Kook.
[Team Film Stars- One vs
Team Sports All-Stars- Two.]
Okay, Joo Ji Hoon!
Let's go home nice and dry.
Let's not get wet,
and go home nice and dry.
As the rules states,
category can no longer be selected.
If you both answer incorrectly,
then we'll move on to the next question.
Okay, let's give these two
a huge round of applause!
[The final battle between
Team Film Stars and Team Sports All-Stars.]
Who will take home 15 gold towers?
Please give out the next question.
In the royal court
during the Joseon era
a king's face was referred to as 'Yong-Ahn',
his lips, 'Goo-Soon'
and his farts, 'Ventilation'.
In that case, what did they refer to
the king's stool as?
This is the question that could
change it all!
The answer to this question
was actually even in a movie.
'Yong-Byun' is incorrect.
Okay, time to reveal your answers.
'Mae-hwa' and 'Ki-chim'.
['Ki-chim' vs 'Mae-hwa'.]
One of the two answered correctly.
The correct answer is...
Mae-hwa!
[Tiger is eliminated.]
Mae-hwa.
Joon Ji Hoon's 'Joo', Ji Sung Ji's 'Ji',
Lee Kwang Soo's 'Soo'!
Joo-Ji-Soo!
[We are, Joo-Ji-Soo!]
It's now Ji Suk Jin's turn at the podium.
Will be he able to go home in dry clothes?
[Dry Big-nose finally takes his stand.]
I already feels nervous for him.
[Bratty Bid-nose.]
[The final face-off.]
[Ji Suk Jin vs Joo Ji Hoon.]
[Question with the victory of
the Quiz Battle hanging on the line.]
A lone man in the midst of many women
is referred to as, 'The Only man'
and a lone woman in the midst of many men
are referred to as, 'The Only woman'.
'The only woman' means,
the single red blossom.
- So which flower blossom does it refer to?
- Write down the type of flower.
I know this answer!
I have to remember it!
I'm not positive if this is the right answer.
Ji Suk Jin has written down his answer.
[Suk Jin used to be the host of
a very popular quiz show in the past.]
[Easily memorizing the answers
to these many questions.]
Red pomegranate flower.
Can you keep it down a bit?
Sorry, but I memorize better
when I say it out loud.
[The answer to the question-
Red pomegranate flower.]
If both of you answer it incorrectly,
then you'll be asked another question.
One, two, three.
[Answers are revealed simultaneously.]
[Did they both get
red pomegranate flower as their answer?]
[Who will be the ultimate
victors of this battle?]
[Ji Hoon!]
[The degradation of the dry and fluffy man!]
The victors of today's race!
Joo Ji Hoon, Ji Sung, and Lee Kwang Soo!
[Team Film Stars-
The ultimate victors of the Quiz Battle!]
This really is completely unexpected!
[Dry and fluffy man's disappointing loss.]
[Quiz battle genius, Joo Ji Hoon.]
Cha Yu Ram should've just stayed in the game
if you two were going to do it like this.
Why did you have to make me have a turn?
You should've just ended it!
Thus, today's victors...
with a total of 15 golden towers!
Team Joo Ji Hoon!
[Team Film Stars wins the battle
with a total of 15 golden towers!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Today's race is, One Day Tour Race.
[Eat, pray, and endure.]
Fighting, Jong Kook.
[A tour that makes their skin crawl.]
[Their memories are erased...]
[A mysterious revenge is about
to take place.]
- What's Ji Hyo doing?
- What is this!
What do you think you're doing!
[Lone Ranger... Coming soon!]