Running Man
[How do you express feelings of love
in just one single word?]
[Love is extreme!]
[An extreme love race that crosses
both ends of the extreme!]
You girls must've been partiers!
[Opposite ends of the extreme.]
[Giant present boxes?]
- Yoo Jae Suk, please step forward.
- Okay.
- You must have to select something.
- That's good.
- What is that?
- Is someone in there?
[There's a person in the box.]
- It's a very slender arm.
- Who is that?
[Could there be a guest inside the box?]
It's Han Goo Roo!
- It's Han Goo Roo.
- Our Goo Roo.
[The new face of romantic comedies,
Han Goo Roo.]
[Can't get any fresher
or sweeter than this actress.]
[The new queen of
romantic comedies, Han Goo Roo!]
- I really enjoyed watching your drama!
- I couldn't get through it!
- Han Goo Roo.
- She's pretty feisty.
[Han Goo Roo is Jae Suk's partner.]
It's been a long while since I've been on
a variety show, and I'm excited to be here.
My name is Han Goo Roo,
and please take good care of me.
- She's so pretty.
- Lee Kwang Soo, please step forward.
- Me? Don't do that!
- Song Ji Hyo!
If it's Ji Hyo,
I'm just going to kick her!
- I wonder who it is.
- They're going to hurt themselves!
Whoever she is, she's scaring me.
[The star of the box
that Kwang Soo selected is...]
Oh my, hello!
[The queen of weekday dramas,
Jeon So Min.]
[The new face of your favorite
weekday TV shows, Jeon So Min.]
- Were you okay to do that in your skirt?
- Isn't your skirt down too low?
[Comes out smiling even though she's been
crouched down in her hip-hop skirt...]
[Time to reveal Ha Ha's selected partner.]
[The goddess with the perfect figure,
Lee Sung Kyung.]
[The woman who played Kwang Soo's
girlfriend in 'It's Okay, It's Love.']
- It's Lee Sung Kyung!
- It's Kwang Soo!
- Didn't the two of you...
- You two were in a drama together!
You're the one Wang Ji Hye mentioned!
Why are you bringing up
Wang Ji Hye's name right now?
[Could Sung Kyung be the girl that Ji Hye
referenced as Kwang Soo's type?]
We've heard a lot about you.
He said you were a really nice girl.
- Yes, she's nice.
- Yes, I'm a nice person.
- Seriously?
- Even her quirkiness is like Kwang Soo.
[We're just very good friends.]
[Kkuk selects one of the smallest boxes.]
[A clear sound of someone punching
their way through.]
It's Ji Hyo.
- It's not Ji Hyo!
- Who is it?
[It's not Ji Hyo in there?]
- Is it Ji Hyo?
It's Song Ga Yeon!
I'm scared of that couple!
[The fairy of mixed martial arts world,
Song Ga Yeon.]
[The pro-fighter with the looks of a model.]
[The reigning queen of
Korea's mixed martial arts world.]
Hello, my name is Song Ga Yeon,
a mixed martial arts fighter.
- You have a really cool voice.
- No fighting between partners, right?
Jong Kook really likes athletes.
[The birth of the toughest couple to date.]
[Big-nosed Brother's turn to pick.]
- I don't know which one Ji Hyo is.
- Ji Hyo likes pink.
That's Ji Hyo, for sure.
- Why won't that thing rip?
- Wow, Ji Hyo!
- You look pretty.
- She looks pretty today.
- What have we got to lose, right?
- You look really pretty today.
- Suk Jin's face is turning red!
- You look pretty.
- Why is your face turning red?
- Are you attracted to Ji Hyo right now?
- What's the matter with him?
- Get your head on straight!
- What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with him?
Why do you guys always act like this
whenever I put some makeup on?
Excuse me.
[Time to reveal Gary's present.]
It's someone very feminine.
[The only guest who's not using her fists.]
- It's Kyung Soo Jin.
- Kyung Soo Jin?
She's so pretty.
[The woman whose smile can
light up the room, Kyung Soo Jin.]
[The unbeatable air of elegance... the
woman who stole the hearts of all men.]
- Look at her smile.
- Wow, her smile can light up a room.
She's Gary's ideal type.
Hello, my name is Kyung Soo Jin.
Please take good care of me.
[Gathering her two hands in a shy smile.]
Look at how she keeps doing this.
She keeps hiding her shy smile.
- I just feel really nervous right now.
- She's moved onto doing this.
She keeps doing this.
- When did she do this?
- I wasn't doing that.
[Seriously...]
You will all be enjoying a nice
date with your partners today.
It's the Opposite Ends of Extreme Love race.
You will be given a mission to pass
at two different locations
and the first couple to arrive at the final
mission site will receive a great advantage
so please give the missions
your best efforts.
The first team to arrive at the final mission
site has the highest chances of winning.
I've made that very clear.
Give the missions your best efforts as
not to regret it at the final mission site.
Before we leave for the next location
you will have to choose the site of which
your first mission will take place.
The first couple to break down and clean up
all the fragments of the box that your
female partner jumped out of will get
the chance to get to the location first.
The first couple to clean up will get
the chance to get out of here first.
[You want us to break down these boxes?]
[Seriously?]
How are we supposed to
break this down?
[All the boxes are sized differently.]
[Perhaps the smaller boxes will
be easier to break down?]
[Ten minutes ago.]
[The female guests themselves chose
which boxes to hide in.]
I shouldn't have any problems
hiding in this one.
This one is way too small.
[So Min and Ga Yeon
selected the smaller boxes.]
[After having endured a momentary
level of small discomfort...]
[Jong Kook, Ga Yeon, Kwang Soo, and So Min
are far ahead of the other couples.]
[The women who chose comfort earlier on are
now experiencing a late moment of suffering.]
- I think we need to break this down!
- Break it down?
[Attacking it with her high heels!]
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon are almost
finished with their cleanup.]
[But Kwang Soo and So Min
were quicker!]
[With Jong Kook and Ga Yeon
right on their heels.]
[While the rest of the teams also
finishes with their cleanup...]
[Some fraudulent schemes going on?]
[Some remnants are still left remaining?]
[Cleanup session is now over.]
Kwang Soo and So Min
are in first place.
- But they didn't get everything in the bag.
- I still saw some blue fragments left.
- No, I saw her with something.
- What? We're all finished!
- She has something in her skirt.
- Can we play back the video?
- I'm telling you that I've got nothing.
- Hand it over before I let Ga Yeon loose.
[A scary warning.]
- Before I have Ga Yeon go over there.
- I can't believe So Min.
- You guys are so catty.
- When did you stuff that back there?
[Finally fesses up to her tricks.]
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon are the new winners,
and get the chance to choose their site.]
I'm going to pick this one.
- Summer.
- Summer? It must be someplace hot.
- I hope we get 'Spring'.
- I think it's 'Winter'.
- Either 'Autumn' or 'Spring'.
- Winter.
- I don't like being cold.
- Ji Hyo.
- She also got 'Winter'.
- Are there no 'Springs'?
['Summer' is all about a cool convertible.]
Wow, it's summer!
Ugh, I'm cold already.
[A car without a top to help feel
the heat of the summer.]
[Opposite ends of the extremes-
A warm car with a top for the winter teams.]
- You like sports?
- Yes.
- I really like to swim, too.
- Then you should've been on the summer team.
I like to swim, but being in the water...
[Laughing behind her hands again.]
[A refreshing convertible ride
at the start of a cold winter.]
[Screaming out loud from the cold.]
[Trying to relieve the summer
in the winter wind.]
Why are you filming this?
We're freezing over here!
Must be nice to be filming this while
you're dressed in your warm coat!
[The three summer teams' mission site-
A swimming pool.]
[Wide eyed and confused.]
[Two diving boards are set up
in the middle of the pool.]
[Just what kind of a mission
will these three teams have to face?]
Here they come.
Over here, Goo Roo!
Look at the way Ga Yeon runs.
- She's different.
- Ga Yeon's running differently.
[Switches into her running stance.]
[On the other hand,
these two actresses prance over.]
They're running like little girls,
and Ga Yeon runs like an athlete.
[Do not walk, but run!
Running Man's formidable guest.]
Welcome to our summer teams.
Summer is all about swimming.
Your mission is- 'Love is to roll around.'
Both members from each team will tumble
three times while on the diving board.
Then the partners will stand on the red end
of the board without falling into the water
and throw up a huge heart sign
while facing one another.
- Should you fail, you'd have to try again.
- So Min says she can't tumble forward.
- Why not?
- I keep going sideways.
Is it okay if we don't fall in the water?
Really?
It's like this game was
created for these two.
Ga Yeon will probably
be really good at this game.
You'll have to roll three times.
Men and women at each diving boards.
Please go easy on me.
[Ga Yeon's unfailing polite manners.]
Can we just try it?
[So Min and Goo Roo are unsure of their
abilities and attempt a practice roll.]
- You can't practice.
- We can't practice?
See?
What am I going to do?
I can't do it straight.
I'm afraid of heights.
[The diving board gradually narrows.]
We have to roll three times
and stand on the red part?
That's right.
[Summer mission goal-
Roll three times and stand on the red part.]
- We have to roll three times.
- Ready!
[Love is a tumble-
First couple: Kwang Soo and So Min.]
Wait.
[How am I going to do this?]
So Min, let's just get this done
and get out of here!
- Seriously!
- But I keep rolling sideways!
[The fear inducing height
of the diving board...]
- It's okay.
- But I'm scared!
I want to go home and see my mom.
Let's do this, So Min!
[Jeon So Min, fighting!]
- Seriously... I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
- I'm going to cheer you on!
- No, it's okay.
- It's way too narrow!
Three rolls in a row.
[Love is a tumble- Start!]
[Kwang Soo succeeds on his first roll.]
[Who is that?]
[Just like her practice roll,
rolls sideways and falls in.]
[A refreshing failure.]
[While So Min was busy falling in...
add another name to that list.]
[The narrowing diving board is no easy feat.]
Oh no!
This is bad!
[Love is a difficult path to travel on.]
- Goo Roo!
- Seeing them fall in is so scary!
- So Min, are you okay?
- I'm okay, but where did I fall in?
- What?
- How did I fall in?
You were right about rolling sideways.
[Doesn't even know how she fell in.]
[First couple, Kwang Soo and So Min,
fails their first attempt.]
That's really hard.
[Love is a tumble-
Second couple: Jae Suk and Goo Roo.]
How am I expected to do this up here?
- This is scary, Goo Roo.
- This is no joke.
Goo Roo!
It's three rolls, okay?
[Saying it is easy...]
Ready!
Set...
- I'm sure falling in is no big deal.
- Just do it!
[What you're doing is even more scary...]
- Falling in is no big deal.
- Why are you sitting down?
We have to overcome our fear.
You know that, right?
Can we just get it over with?
- Are you getting annoyed with me?
- She's getting annoyed, so just do it!
You have a bit of a temper, don't you?
You're kind of scaring me.
I think we should just do it instead
of scaring ourselves even more.
Ready!
[Love is a tumble-
Jae Suk and Goo Roo- Start!]
Goo Roo is good,
and has good direction!
[Goo Roo successfully
completes her first roll.]
- I fell flat on my face!
- I fell on my face, too!
- Ugh, I fell on my face!
- You can't help but fall on your face!
[Falls flat on his face.]
- Are you okay?
- Excuse me?
- Shall we go?
I was just asking if you were okay.
- I'm not sure.
- Really?
- Ga Yeon!
- Yes?
[Nervous female fighter.]
Why are you so startled?
Is there anything you'd like to say?
- No.
- You don't?
Ga Yeon's deep voice is
very attractive.
My voice is high,
and her voice is deep.
Your voices would be
very good together in a duet.
- It should be the other way around.
- Ready.
[Relax, female fighter.]
- One, two...
- I think we can do this!
One, two, three!
[What just happened?]
[Attacking Kkuk is something that can
only be done from behind his back.]
- That's how you fall in the water.
- What are you doing down there?
Why do you keep grabbing the ledge?
That's how you should fall in.
- Now the game has officially begun.
- This is fun!
[Kkuk is on the move.]
[Immediately changes their tune.]
- We didn't do it on purpose.
- I didn't do it.
- We really could've done it.
- Okay.
- Now that I've fallen in, it's no big deal.
- It really isn't once you've fallen in.
I don't want to fall in again.
So Min.
You should look in the mirror.
Your hair is a hot mess.
Why are you telling her that?
We haven't said anything because she looks
funny, so why are you telling her that?
Her hair looks like strands
of wet seaweed.
[So Min's cool, and laidback attitude.]
- Do you think her forehead's too wide?
- No, it's pretty.
- My forehead?
- No, nothing!
No, not at all!
You look very pretty!
Jong Kook takes the cake when it comes
to upsetting our female guests.
I was really shocked when I saw that
you're much shorter than I thought you'd be.
Me?
- I see.
- He's there, too!
- He's pissed, too.
- He gets pissed very easily.
- How are you any different from Ha Ha?
- Excuse me?
[Kkuk is no match when it comes
to So Min's barbed comments.]
['O' snow park in Ilsan.]
[Wow, it's snowing!]
[First snowfall for these couples.]
- Wow, I'm so happy!
- It's snowing!
[Soo Jin likes to play around!]
Wow, this is really nice!
[An extremely different feel
from our summer couples.]
I'd like to welcome our
winter couples to winter.
- Wow, it's winter!
- Winter is all about sledding, isn't it?
- Yes, that's right.
- Your winter mission is...
none other than, 'Escape the Igloo'.
- Escape the Igloo?
- Are they somehow locking us in?
'Winter is all about sledding, that's why
your mission is, Escape the Igloo.'
[Sledding will have to be next time.]
All the couples will go inside the igloo,
and dance along to the music
and run outside as soon as the whistle blows
and grab a half a piece of the broken heart.
The couple must piece together a completed
whole heart in order to pass the mission.
- What's this?
- It's an igloo!
[The three couples' current half hearts.]
It's an igloo!
- Wow, it's really nice in here!
- It's actually cozy in here.
[A cozy dance space for the three couples.]
[Escape the Igloo- Start.]
[First song-
'To My Boyfriend' by Fin.K.L.]
Let's see Soo Jin's dance.
- So cute!
- She's so cute!
[A cutie with the sweet eye smile.]
Sung Kyung!
[A couple dance with Ha Ha.]
[This is fun!]
Ji Hyo!
[No matter what the song is,
always dancing the 'Hot Issue' dance.]
'I'm yours!'
[Let's escape the igloo!]
[Big-nose's fighting spirit.]
Get out there, Suk Jin!
[You're not going anywhere!]
[Ji Hyo makes her escape!]
[Grabs the sliver of a chance,
and escapes in a blink of an eye.]
[That's our Ace!]
You have to match the heart, Ji Hyo.
[30 different sized half heart pieces.]
I think she's already got it.
[A difference of 5mm-
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo, fails.]
- There's a tiny bit of a difference.
- They're different?
It looks like the right fit from here.
[Mission point- Tell the difference of
by their eyesight only.]
[Song number two-
'My Ear Candy' by Baek Ji Young.]
[Everybody, it's time to dance!]
[Soo Jin, let's go!]
[Couple dancing with Gary.]
[Gary is feeling the groove.]
I love you... I love you!
She's not as sweet and demure
as she seems!
[A new side of Kyung Soo Jin
is discovered!]
My ear's candy!
As sweet as honey!
Melt me with your sweet voice!
[The igloo is starting to get steamed up.]
Ji Hyo!
Wait, I'm going to get in there.
[Discovers some wiggle room.]
[Ha Ha escapes.]
It's small and thin.
Get the small and thin one.
Ji Hyo... help me.
In the middle... but towards the left.
[I don't know which one to choose!]
To the left!
[Ha Ha makes his selection.]
I can already tell that it's wrong.
- I can already tell that it's too big.
- You should've picked that one!
[I'll grind it down to make it fit.]
[Ha Ha and Sung Kyung, fail.]
It's the never-ending game.
We'll never be able to get this
unless we start helping each other.
- There's no way to get this!
- How are we expected to get this?
It seriously is such a miniscule difference!
No, it's not this one!
It's not this one either!
- No, this definitely isn't it!
- This isn't it either!
[All the couples explodes out in anger!]
Even as we're out here...
Oh, it's this one!
- This is it, isn't it?
- I have a question.
Did the summer team go to
a swimming pool?
- Yes.
- What are they doing there?
- Tumbling on the diving board.
- On the diving board?
Thank you for this.
Thank you.
On the diving board?
Let's work hard and match
our hearts.
- We can do this. Thank you for this.
- Sorry for complaining!
- I love Running Man!
- Let's work hard.
[Meanwhile, the summer teams...]
[Jae Suk and Goo Roo's turn.]
[Succeeds the first tumble.]
[Succeeds the second tumble.]
I'm so scared!
[The edge is right in front of their eyes!]
Goo Roo, you go first.
You can do it if you put your head
really close to the chest.
No, it's not going to work. I guarantee it.
You're just going to fall in.
There's no way I'm doing it.
I'm for sure going to fall in.
[She could've said it in nicer terms...]
No, you're going to fall in for sure.
It may be possible.
[Goo Roo maintains her hope
and attempts to make the roll.]
- Hey, I think you can do it!
- No, she's going to fall in.
[Just like So Min said,
falls right into the water.]
Goo Roo, you did it.
That was a nice dive.
That was really nice.
We're going to get it done this time.
[Can't let her show me up!
Jae Suk's own slapstick comedy.]
I think my knee's busted.
- What did you do?
- How did you do that while crawling?
My knee, get out!
Do you know?
My knee, get out.
[Let's all succeed, and let's all get out!]
[Attempting the three rolls
one person at a time.]
Three in a row.
One, two...
[He's already at the edge!]
He already knows! He already
knows how this is going to end.
- I can't even watch this.
- Watch and see how this is going to end.
I wish I could help you.
[A lonely battle against himself
on the diving board.]
I really don't want to do this!
I can't do this!
- I'll take the fall for him.
- No, it's okay.
- I can take the fall for him.
- No, I'll give it a try.
- This might be possible.
- No, it's not.
- I'll take the fall for you instead.
- She's an expert at this already.
- No, I'll give it a try.
- No, it won't work. Your torso is too long.
[Even Kwang Soo can't avoid
So Min's adamant statements.]
- Why is she standing out there?
- Why are you offering to take his fall?
Stop making this more burdensome,
and just go away!
- This isn't a drama!
- Why are you acting like that?
- Why would you take the fall instead?
- I'll be the black knight.
- Why would you do that?
- I heard that So Min likes to drink.
You know what So Min said
to us earlier?
'I wish I could have a beer.'
- Seriously?
- Yes.
When we passed by some snack carts,
she said she wishes she could have a beer.
[Black knight, So Min,
takes the challenge for Kwang Soo.]
So Min!
[The black knight protects
her partner, Kwang Soo.]
[This is for my Kwang Soo...]
[The perfect pose,
and the perfect artistic expression!]
You looked really pretty
as you were falling in.
- I'm serious!
- So Min, you're taking Kwang Soo's thunder.
Give me a chance to make people laugh!
Does my hair look funny?
He kept making fun of my big forehead.
Jong Kook... he's dead.
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon-
The athletic couple's turn.]
[Ga Yeon's short remaining distance
poses a threat.]
- This is already over.
- No, you can do it.
[It's not over until it's over.]
- You can do it!
- It's okay!
- I can do this.
- No, the distance is too short.
- You're just going to fall in.
- It's not bad once you fall in.
So Min is the icon of misfortune.
[Icon of misfortune
hides behind the sweet smile.]
- You can do it.
- Why am I being so whiny?
- No, you're not!
- Ga Yeon's getting mad.
[At a closer look, she's
just a scared twenty year old.]
- Ga Yeon's sweeter than she looks.
- Just roll forward, Ga Yeon.
I thought she was going to
send a flying kick!
[Fighter's true spirits are coming out.]
- Ga Yeon, how about I lower my speech?
- Why bother asking when he already did?
Ga Yeon, you can do it!
Just tuck in your chin.
Don't think about putting your head down,
but tuck in your chin instead.
- Just tuck and roll!
- Why are you trying to coach her?
Why are you coaching her
when she just needs to roll forward?
It's not a difficult task.
You stand in fighting rings.
- Don't worry, you can do this.
- Okay.
Just go for it.
[Ga Yeon, you can do it!]
[At last... she takes the roll!]
[Ga Yeon overcomes her fear and falls in,
and all six have now taken their plunge.]
- You did good.
- Ga Yeon fell in!
[Winter teams, on the other hand...]
[These hearts are still
waiting for their other halves...]
[Form a line!]
Do you think we'll ever get
out of here?
Do you think we can get out of here?
[Gary quickly makes his escape!]
- Pick the right one!
- Wait a minute...
[Checks the approximate
size with his hands.]
[Which one of these numerous halves
is the right one?]
Eight, nine, eight, seven...
[He makes his selection!]
[Please... let it be the right one.]
- It's perfect!
- Is it the right one?
It's perfect!
It's the perfect fit!
[Gary and Soo Jin succeed!]
[First couple to escape the igloo!]
- Get going.
- Go.
You've succeeded the mission.
Choose your next location,
and continue on with the race.
This one?
Or this one?
- This one? This one feels right?
- Yeah.
[Gary and Soo Jin-
Next mission- '100.']
- Bye.
- How can you be so cold hearted?
[Gary and Soo Jin are the first
to leave for their next location.]
- It's 'Crazy.'
- This is how you do it.
[Only two couples left in the igloo.]
Wow, you're serious about
your moves!
[It's Sung Kyung's day!]
[Spot on dancing!]
She's really good!
[What a great dancer!]
Her long body looks so pretty.
[Igloo's own dancing queen.]
[Not a single couple has
succeeded the summer mission.]
[Jong Kook succeeds.]
Ugh, I can't even stand looking at him.
- I can't even stand him.
- He's so cool.
[Response to Kkuk is the polar opposite.]
- I think the body has to be kept tight.
- You can do this.
[Grab the ledge of the board,
and tuck in your chin.]
Did you create this game?
Are you the creator of this game?
Ugh, seriously.
[Ga Yeon succeeds her first roll.]
Tuck in your chin tighter!
Okay, there you go.
You can do this!
There's a lot of distance left.
- There's a ton of distance still left.
- She might be able to succeed this time.
What are Goo Roo and So Min doing?
[Budding friendship over eye goop.]
- You can do this.
- You got this!
[This time...
she manages to stay on the ledge!]
[Now, they must stand up on the ledge
in order to succeed the mission!]
Okay, just stand up now!
- Did we actually do this?
- That's right!
One, two, three!
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon succeed.]
[When will it be our turn?]
Wow, I'm so jealous.
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon's
next mission- '1'.]
[Jae Suk and Goo Roo's turn.]
That's the scariest part.
Your third roll is the scariest.
[It'll soon be my turn.]
[He takes the roll!]
[He maintains the position!]
[Grits down to keep his position!]
He would've fallen in if
he hadn't grabbed onto the sides!
[Jae Suk and Goo Roo succeed.]
[Throws himself in the water.]
[Farewell to the scary diving board.]
[Polar ends of the extreme race-
Time to select their next location.]
You can pick.
[Kwang Soo and So Min
keep rolling and rolling...]
- Show it to the camera.
- 100.
- How did I fall in?
- You looked horrible as you fell in.
You're a gem!
[So Min, the new queen of
slapstick comedy!]
[Who will be the first couple to arrive
at the next mission site?]
[Next mission location for the couples
who chose number one- SBS.]
What's this?
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon
are first to arrive.]
What's going on here?
Where do we have to go?
[What does the number stand for?]
I think we're the first ones here.
[Runs in side by side.]
- You are the first ones to arrive.
- Okay.
Welcome to our 'One' couple.
Your next mission is very simple.
You've made the right selection.
Just need to answer one question correctly.
[Mission-
Correctly answer one quiz question.]
Then will the other couple have to
answer one hundred questions?
I'm not sure.
Listen to the questions asked
by the male partner
and the female partner just needs to
answer it correctly to win.
That's nothing.
The male will be given the question
to ask from here on the first floor...
and ask the question to your partner
who will be standing up on the 22nd floor.
It's only one question and very simple.
Answer the question correctly, and you pass.
It's just one question.
Get it wrong, and the male will come
back down for a new question.
Ga Yeon has a competition in December,
so she needs the exercise.
She has to start her
weight loss program tomorrow.
You can start that tomorrow.
Please go up to the 22nd floor.
- Please show her up to the 22nd floor.
- Ga Yeon.
- Are you good at quizzes?
- I'll do my best.
- Ga Yeon, you have to do a good job.
- Okay.
He has to climb up the stairs?
Wow, Running Man is scary.
- Here's your first question.
- Okay.
I'm only going to read it once.
Here's your question.
It's a luminous effect seen in Arctic Circle
and Antarctic Circle through magnetic force
and the word means, 'New Dawn', in Latin.
What is this phenomenon called?
[Must race up 22 flights of stairs
to ask this question.]
It means, 'New Dawn', in Latin...
She's not going to know that!
Through the earth's magnetic field force...
[Climb up the stairs
while memorizing the question.]
A luminous effect...
[Answer the question correctly
to immediately pass the mission.]
Sun... earth...
what was it again?
I mean, earth's magnetic force.
I'm only on the fourth floor?
[Only on the fourth floor,
and already forgetting the question.]
Through the earth's magnetic field force...
Earth's magnetic force...
Ugh, I'm so hot.
[His partner is...
way up on the 22nd floor!]
[Come on, Jong Kook.]
Just think of it as exercise.
It's just exercise!
This is just some exercise.
Through the earth's magnetic
field force...
Through the earth's magnetic field force...
Ugh, I forgot the question!
[He's only halfway there...]
They look so at ease while they run in here
without knowing what's in store for them.
[Suk Jin, Ji Hyo and Ha Ha, Sung Kyung
are on the first floor.]
Welcome to our 'One' couple.
You just need to correctly
answer one quiz question.
The rules are very simple.
[Finish listening to the rules
before you get too excited.]
[A one question quiz is nothing
to get excited about.]
Ask the question to you partner,
who will be waiting on the 22nd floor.
[Stay strong, Suk Jin.]
Here's your question.
In the Antarctic circle, there exists
a base station called, King Sejong Station.
- Yes, that's correct.
- In that case...
- On the opposite side of the Antarctic...
- In the Arctic?
What is the name of the base station
in the arctic circle?
You may get going.
Wow, even I don't know this one.
Is there a base station there?
There isn't one, is there?
'Taking the stairs will make you
healthier and slimmer.'
It says that taking each stair
will increase your life by four seconds!
It increases your lifespan by four seconds?
Wow, wait a second...
That's not bad.
It's doable.
One, two, three... nine.
Nine times four is 36.
36 seconds.
Wow, this is good.
Taking two flights of stairs will help lose
8.9kcal for male and 6.3kcal for female...
I've increased my lifespan
by five minutes.
This isn't bad.
Wait...
What was the question again?
I think I may have forgotten
the question.
In the Antarctic...
[What was it about the Antarctic?]
[What am I going to do?]
[Number 100's mission-
A cafe in Hongdae.]
[Gary and Soo Jin
are the first ones to arrive.]
Soo Jin.
Here's your mission for
having chosen one hundred.
You next mission is to score
100 goals within 100 seconds.
[Score 100 points within 100 seconds.]
Do you see the basket up above?
The women and the men will play
separate games of basketball
and the first team to score
100 points will win the mission.
[Kwang Soo and So Min arrive
soon thereafter.]
- What is this?
- It's all over.
[Surprised at seeing the basketball goal
setup atop the trampoline.]
This is ridiculous!
This is too hard!
Okay, let's warm up!
[Jae Suk and Goo Roo start their
warmup exercise upon arrival.]
[Trampoline 100 point basketball game-
First round goes to the women.]
- You have to do this.
- Okay.
[The three women showed how tough
they can be at the previous mission.]
Goo Roo, use your elbow
once in a while.
[The men are teaching them
how to cheat.]
I'm the oldest one here,
so don't even think about it.
[So Min is asserting her seniority.]
- Jeon So Min, what are you doing?
- Don't even come close to me.
So Min, I'm still too young
to really care about any of that.
Just show everyone what
you're made of.
- Right, Gary?
- Of course.
[These women are not to be
taken lightly!]
- Jeon So Min, fighting!
- Ready!
[100 point basketball-
Start round one.]
Oh my, Goo Roo!
[So Min does a victory dance
after scoring her first goal.]
Stop wasting time with a victory dance!
[Ten seconds of victory dance
after scoring one goal.]
[The three women keep shooting
without any break in between.]
- Goo Roo!
- Yes?
- Score something!
- Please be quiet!
[Goo Roo makes her first goal.]
Han Goo Roo made a goal.
[Soo Jin immediately follows
with her very first goal.]
[Soo Jin makes single-handed
throws like the men.]
[And makes her second goal in a row.]
Goo Roo, what are you doing?
[So Min also makes her second goal.]
[Follows with another victory lap.]
Knock it off with the victory lap!
- Just make the goals!
- Soo Jin and So Min each have two goals.
[Wow, So Min makes another goal!]
Just go back and score another one!
I'll high-five you all you want later!
Goo Roo!
[Soo Jin makes her third goal.]
[Soo Jin is in the lead with four goals.]
[Soo Jin's impressive shooting posture.]
- You have to stop Soo Jin!
- I'm so tired!
[Even in the midst of the physical tussle...
Remains her composure, shoots, and scores!]
[Soo Jin's unending scores.]
[Makes every shot she throws!
This is Soo Jin's shining moment!]
You have to stop Soo Jin!
[Goo Roo attacks So Min.]
- No, you have to stop Soo Jin!
- She has the wrong person!
You have to stop Soo Jin!
[Goo Roo, immediately switched
her target.]
[Goo Roo's new goal is to stop Soo Jin
instead of taking the shots herself.]
[So Min's sole chance.]
We have to stop her!
[This time, Goo Roo clings
onto So Min.]
What are you doing, Goo Roo!
[Soo Jin doesn't miss her chance,
and grabs a ball in each hand to shoot!]
[Competitive Soo Jin still throws off a shot
even as she takes a tumble.]
[A fierce physical battle
atop the trampoline.]
[Soo Jin still attempts to make a shot
even in the midst of the tussle.]
Come on!
[Time out]
- What are you girls doing?
- It's over!
[Scores 60 points on her own.
Soo Jin shows alarmingly good skills.]
[The battle was fierce enough
to take off one of her socks.]
Sorry, girls.
[These girls are way too scary.]
[Meanwhile...]
[Kkuk is still climbing up
his 22 flights of stairs.]
Don't your thighs feel like
they're about to burst?
The luminous effect in the arctic...
[Repeating the question to himself
in case he forgets the question.]
[The staff members are still
on the 19th floor.]
[Kkuk arrives on the 22nd floor.]
[Did he memorize the question correctly?]
Is he here?
Oh my goodness...
[Wow, he really climbed all
the way up here.]
Kim Jong Kook can't cross the finish line,
and Ga Yeon must stand on her spot.
Ga Yeon...
What took you guys so long?
[VJ drops falls down to the ground
along with the camera.]
- The question is...
- Yes?
It's a very long question.
The question is...
The word means, 'New Dawn', in Latin.
- In Latin...
- 'New Dawn' in Latin?
Okay.
But it's some sort of a phenomenon.
The heat of the sun.
- The earth's rotation.
- Rotation?
The light illuminates because
of those two.
Did you know the answer
when you heard the question?
Why are you asking me that?
This is for you to answer, Ga Yeon.
- You have to answer the question.
- You don't know the answer either?
I came up here to ask you
the question.
[Correct answer- Aurora.]
[Kkuk must go back down to the first floor
to receive a new question.]
My thighs feel like they're
about to burst.
[Two more people whose thighs are about
to burst are coming up the stairs.]
[Which of the Running Man members
has an A blood type?]
[Ha Ha and Big-nose meet up
on the eleventh floor.]
Our writers...
I don't even know the question.
[These two are on the verge of passing out.]
The first person to get the answer
correct will have the advantage.
Does Kwang Soo have AB blood type?
[Finally arrives on the 22nd floor.]
[Ha Ha's here!]
Is it a hard question?
- How have you been?
- Is it a tough question?
[I know that Suk Jin left first...]
- Ha Ha, have you seen Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin's sleeping on the 15th floor.
[Where is the end?]
Give me the question.
- Here's your first question.
- My first question?
If you fail to answer this
question correctly
then I have to go back down
and come all the way back up again.
Suk Jin!
There's Suk Jin!
[Big-nose finally arrives!]
- Suk Jin!
- I'm not walking like this on purpose.
I'm going to kill you
if you don't get this right.
[Jong Kook is already back!]
He's back already?
[Kkuk came back at top speed
by the use of Mr. Capable's powers.]
This is my second trip.
Guys, a whole new world opens up
on your second trip back up.
- I wonder what kind of a world it could be.
- Who could it be?
[Albeit an unknown world,
it's a world I never want to know about.]
Out of all the Running Man members...
which one of us has an A blood type?
- Wow.
- Think carefully about our personalities.
A blood type is more reserved.
Probably not an extrovert like me.
Not so bothersome like Jae Suk,
or anything else like that.
[Please... Get it right...]
- One.
- Kim Jong Kook!
You have to go back down.
[Answer- Jong Kook, Gary, and Ji Hyo.]
- Okay, who's next?
- Wait.
- She was about to say more.
- But the time's already up.
[Ha Ha, back to the first floor.]
Dong Hoon, think of it as
getting exercise.
Just get back down there.
Wait, I want to see
Song Ji Hyo's reaction first.
Ji Hyo.
You're smart, aren't you?
- Why? What's the question?
- I'm going to ask you something.
- Ji Hyo, I'm seriously about to lose it.
- What is it?
I've never climbed 22 flights
of stairs in all my life.
- You need to work out more, Suk Jin.
- Seriously.
- Listen carefully to my question.
- Would I know the answer to it?
- Yes, you'd know. Here's the first one.
- My first?
Are you planning on asking me
a second question?
[Why would you ask
such a frightful thing as that?]
I'm only going to ask one question.
Okay, there's a base station in
the Antarctic circle.
- Antarctic station.
- Yes, what's the name of it?
Antarctic station.
- No, it's King Sejong Station.
- Ah, King Sejong Station?
- There's more.
- Suk Jin, let's just go.
- Let's just go.
- Just go!
- Are you getting the question?
- Suk Jin's getting mad.
So, what's the name of the base station
in the arctic circle?
I'm telling you that it's not
the arctic base station.
[If the Antarctic station is
King Sejong Station, then in the arctic...]
Lee Soon Shin Station!
What is it?
The other was King Sejong Station.
I don't know the answer either!
- You don't know either?
- How would I know the answer?
Because there's King Sejong and
General Lee Soon Shin at Gwanghwamun Gate.
What does that have to do with this!
This is about the arctic circle!
Why are you talking about
Gwanghwamun Gate?
Seriously!
Why is this hot pack so hot!
Taking his anger out on the hot pack.
[Suk Jin must head back down
to the first floor.]
- Goo Roo! Can you start the groove?
- What?
Give us a wave.
There you go!
[Goo Roo's waving cheer.]
That's what we need!
Why didn't you do that sooner?
- What are you waiting for, Soo Jin?
- So Min, it's your turn!
What are you waiting for!
[Truly a unique character.]
- Namyangju!
- What are you talking about!
I've moved!
I'm living with someone!
What?
You're living with someone?
- Who are you living with?
- What are you saying?
- Hey, you're living with someone?
- No!
- You didn't tell me anything about that!
- No, I'm not living with anyone.
[Such a long road to travel...
for a short incorrect answer.]
[Ha Ha arrives on the 22nd floor
for the second time.]
[Ha Ha's back!]
Give me the question.
This question...
I know you're going to get.
- I guarantee it.
- Okay.
Everyone who walks in through that door
has the same expression on their face.
They walk the same, too.
[Try taking the stairs, and you'll know.]
Suk Jin!
Suk Jin, you're back!
[Big-nose is also back.]
Okay.
It's the opposite word.
Just think of the opposite.
- Yes, I understand.
- Think of the opposite word.
- It's the opposite of what I'm about to say.
- Just say it already!
- How many times must you repeat yourself?
- I'm trying to explain it to her!
We have to take our turn, too.
Incheon coastal waters.
[What's the opposite word of
'Incheon coastal waters'?]
- Yen, nine...
- 'Incheon mother'? (Word play)
[Could this be the correct answer?]
Answer.
Incheon mother?
[Correct answer]
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon
succeed the quiz mission.]
You did great!
[A question that utilized the phonetic
sound of 'Incheon coastal waters.']
[Ga Yeon was quick witted enough
to have figured that out!]
But you got the feel for it, right?
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon are
first to succeed.]
- Wow, she's so smart.
- That was hard.
- I had no idea.
- You didn't know, right?
She's very smart.
I didn't know the answer either.
[So envious...]
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon select
the next mission location.]
[Immediately off to the next location!]
- Fighting, Jae Suk!
- You can do this!
Kwang Soo!
[A total score of 100 points.
Last chance of their second round.]
[Kwang Soo vs Jae Suk. Fierce
battle between the two ace players.]
[Thanks to their battle,
Gary now takes the lead.]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo forget the
mission and start to wrestle instead.]
[Forcefully tries to remove
Jae Suk's pants.]
[Thank goodness for his long johns!]
[Gary seizes his chance and
scores another goal!]
[Others might think that this mission is
about taking off their pants.]
Take off Gary's pants, too.
No, you can't!
I only have my underwear on!
[No, I only have my underwear on!]
[The time runs out with all their pants
around their ankles.]
[A close call in such unexpected ways.]
I'm sorry, you didn't
have your long johns on?
They're taking pictures up there.
- Long johns counts as pants?
- Of course.
[As long as they're feeling confident,
long johns can be fashionable, too!]
Please put your pants back on.
- Sorry, Gary.
- It's okay.
- I had no idea you only had your undies on.
Okay, here are the final results.
Han Goo Roo and Yoo Jae Suk-
three goals.
Jae Suk only scored one goal.
Jeon So Min and Lee Kwang Soo-
Five goals.
[So Min and Kwang Soo- Five goals.]
Kyung Soo Jin and Kang Gary-
ten goals.
[Gary and Soo Jin, wins!]
[Ha Ha's on his third attempt.]
[Ha Ha, please succeed this time.]
You look like you just washed your hair.
Oh, no!
What if it's another hard question!
Can I ask while lying down?
Come here, Sung Kyung.
You can't cross the flag line.
- Just relax...
- Rest a bit first.
- Don't let me burden you.
- Ha Ha, did you see Suk Jin on your way?
He passed away on the seventh floor.
[Mom, I miss you...]
What's the name of the base station
in the Antarctic circle?
- King Sejong Station.
- There you go.
[It's the same question!]
Then what's the name of the base
station in the arctic circle?
- Option one.
- Yes?
[Thank goodness,
it's a multiple choice question!]
Yulkok Station.
Option two.
Tosan Station.
Option three!
Tasan Station.
Tell us the correct answer
by the number.
- Number on, Yulkok Station.
- I'm going to get angry if you get it wrong.
You may go back to your spot.
The correct answer is...
[Please...]
[Wrong]
Sorry, but can you move
out of the way?
- Ji Hyo.
- I'm still in shock.
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo's turn.]
It's the exact same question.
- Okay?
- As the one he just asked?
Yes, after having heard it,
it's the exact same question.
[Third time this is being asked of Blank Ji.]
It's the same question.
Number one, Yulkok Station.
Two, Tosan Station,
and Three, Tasan Station.
[Big-nose hints at
the answer being option two.]
- Answer by giving me the number.
- I'm not sure of the answer.
[It's either option two or three.]
The correct answer is?
One, two, three.
- Number three.
- I told you that it's two.
- What was option three again?
- Tasan Station.
Tasan Station.
Are you confusing it with
Tasan Call Station?
- No, I'm not.
- I think it is. He thinks it's Tasan.
Get away from me!
- I told you that I was right!
- Ji Hyo!
[Hurray, Song Ji Hyo!]
- You have to meet the right woman.
- What kind of a hint was that?
[Back down the stairs...]
Are we here?
[Having come in at first place,
Gary and Soo Jin are first to arrive.]
[Is this the final mission location?]
You are the first ones to arrive.
I will now give you a new
address to find for the final mission.
[A new address?]
What is this?
You must go and find the location
where the 'R' marked flag is located.
- You have to go there on foot.
- Do we win once we find the right location?
You may get started.
[Gets on the way without
any set plans.]
Sir, can you tell us where Sim-gok-ro is?
- Sim-gok-ro? It's right down there.
- Down this way?
- Sim-gok-ro.
- Okay, let's go down there.
[Figures out the rough
whereabouts of the location.]
We're in second place!
We still came in at second place.
[Kwang Soo and So Min
arrive in second place.]
Do we just get going with
these addresses?
- Yes.
- But why are we here?
Incheon metro Sim-gok-ro...
it really is an address.
[Kwang Soo and So Min
receive the same address!]
- Do we just go...
- Should we get going?
Sim-gok-ro, road 100...
Sim-gok-ro?
Hey, it says 'Sim-gok-ro' over there!
- You're right, Gary!
- We have to go down to the left.
[Following the road number may
make it easier to find.]
We have to go down more.
- Sim-gok-ro!
- We may find this pretty quickly!
Hello, can you tell us where
Sim-gok-ro is?
- Sim-gok-ro, where?
- Sim-gok-ro, road 100.
- This is...
- This says, Tagok-ro.
- Sim-gok-ro!
- It's Sim-gok-ro!
[Finds Sim-gok-ro by pure chance!]
If we go down further,
we should be able to find 100.
- Look at the address.
- That's 136.
- We have to go down further.
- Nice spotting.
- We're doing good.
- Let's keep going this way.
- It's Kim Jong Kook!
- Hi!
[By the use of street signs, the members
are closing in on the location.]
Going by the street address
is pretty easy.
- It's much easier.
- It's definitely easier.
- Where are the other signs?
- Have you guys seen other RM members?
- Yes, we have.
- Where?
- Where are they?
- They're down that way.
[Haroro is following
other RM members tracks.]
[Must find the correct location
with just the street address.]
Road 100!
[The first couple to arrive at the site
will have the best chances of winning!]
[Must hurry over to the final location!]
- 30! That's 30!
- Where?
- Where is it written?
- Over there.
[If that's 30 of road 100,
then right across the street...]
[Gary and Soo Jin are first
to arrive at the final location!]
[In a few moments...]
[The couples are being
chased after by someone!]
- Don't come any closer!
- What's going on here?
[While everyone's hiding in fear...]
We can't be seen!
[Who are these couples being
chased by?]
[Gary and Soo Jin?]
[Final mission-
1 vs 5- Bell hide and go seek.]
It's a one against five,
bell hide and go seek.
- What?
- One against five?
As winners of the last mission
you will be the attackers with bells on,
and you'll need to eliminate the others.
Since you didn't win first place,
you will have to be on the defense.
[The remaining five couples
are to play defense.]
[The unique feature of this round of
hide and go seek is...]
[Couple name tags and a u-shaped magnet!]
- Are the clothes stuck together?
- We can't have name tags this large!
Are you kidding us?
You have to avoid being eliminated by
the couple on the offensive
and find the U-shaped magnets
that are hidden throughout the building.
The U-shaped magnets.
Once you find the real U-shaped magnet,
you'll earn a clue to where the final site is.
The first couple to find and get on the stage
at the final location will win the race.
You win if you can successfully eliminate all
five couples before the mission is over.
[Must eliminate all five couples before
one of the other couples finds the stage!]
[Love is extreme!
One on Five Hide and Go Seek.]
I'm scared.
[Must find the correct U-shaped magnet
before getting ousted by the attackers.]
[And the couple on the attack is
the fiercely competitive Gary and Soo Jin!]
I can hear the bells very closely.
[Gary and Soo Jin are showing their
eagerness right off the get-go.]
[Where could they be hiding?]
We have to find the magnets quickly.
We have to find them quickly.
[Must find the magnets before
the attackers can find them!]
- What's that?
- They're just dolls.
Hi.
It's possible that they could have it.
[Could it be inside their bellies?]
[In order to escape from this terror,
they must find the correct magnet!]
Here it is!
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo find a magnet!]
Is it real?
The bakery on the second
sub terrain level?
[They find some words written
on the magnet ends...]
[Rushing off to the bakery.]
Excuse me, but can we put
our magnet on you?
[Where do you think you're putting that?]
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon are in search mode
for their magnet.]
There it is!
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon
discover something!]
[Wait, their location is different than
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo's location!]
There's the bakery over there!
Be careful, we have to stick together.
Okay, let's hurry!
[They've arrived at the bakery
the magnets were indicating to.]
Do we have to search for something here?
- Second level underground...
- The bakery, right?
This is the bakery.
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon arrive at
the bathroom on the lower first floor.]
[Keeping her eyes shut tight
in the male bathroom.]
Did you not find anything?
[The final stage is nowhere to be seen.]
[This is where the magnets indicated...]
What are we supposed to find?
Why is there such a huge gap
on that side?
- That must not be a match.
- No, I don't think it is.
[Not the right match.
A real one would stick together.]
- Wait.
- There's Gary over there.
[Gary and Soo Jin are on the other
side of the window!]
I'll search through this floor,
and you can search through the third floor.
- Shout if you find anyone.
- Okay.
- Gary, this is the second floor.
- You're searching where?
[Wait...]
I get the feeling that someone
is hiding down here.
- Above is the third floor.
- I think someone's hiding down here.
[Gary is closing in.]
[Please...]
[Where Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are hiding.]
- It's just an employee.
- It's an employee.
[Whew, we survived.]
- Yell if you need me.
- Okay.
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo barely escape
a huge moment of danger.]
I keep hearing the sounds
of a ringing bell.
I'm scared.
[The fear must be unanimous.]
- Let's check there.
- What if something's in here?
[Such an odd couple.]
[So Min's right on with her intuition
and discovers a magnet.]
See?
I did it.
[You're still unaware that if they
don't match, then it's a fake magnet?]
[Jae Suk and Goo Roo hears their whispers,
and approaches the couple.]
[But just then...]
[Soo Jin is here!]
[Kwang Soo and So Min attempt
to hide behind the cashier's desk.]
[So Min runs past them and
keeps on after Jae Suk and Goo Roo.]
[Come on, feet, save us!]
Shut the door!
[Where do you think you're going?]
[Soo Jin catches up to them right away.]
[Jae Suk and Goo Roo vs
Soo Jin with the door in between.]
[Power up!]
[The door's opening!]
[Amazing! Soo Jin opens the door with her
foot and props the door open with her arm!]
[Powers up once again!]
[Soo Jin is overpowering these two alone!]
[Breaks through the barrier
in the blink of an eye!]
Where are you?
[Gary hears Soo Jin's call for help
and runs right over!]
[Soo Jin detains the two all by herself
until Gary arrives.]
[A rat caught in the trap.]
I know where Kwang Soo is!
[We're out of here!]
[Jae Suk and Goo Roo- Out!]
Thanks, Jae Suk.
Bye!
[Soo Jin's shocking warrior instinct.]
[Just what in the world happened here?]
- Wow, Soo Jin is no joke.
- She doesn't get flustered.
- No, she doesn't get flustered at all.
- She just goes after it!
She just screamed for Gary
to let him know where we were.
- Wow, she's no joke.
- Wow.
[These sacrificial lambs are at a loss for
words after Hurricane Soo Jin swept through.]
Kyung Soo Jin is the strongest
female guest we've ever had.
[The female warrior's role
is only just beginning.]
[Kwang Soo and So Min are caught
during their attempt to escape.]
[Soo Jin isn't letting go of her prey.]
[Ousts So Min first...
and time to oust Kwang Soo, too.]
What's this?
There's something written on there.
[Gary and Soo Jin is sort of
onto defense team's mission.]
Get up, Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo and So Min- Out.]
[Who do we still have left?]
- It's sticking together.
- No, it's not.
[Ha Ha and Sung Kyung have just
found their third fake magnet.]
[Where's the real magnet that contains
the clue to the final mission location?]
Hide.
[Ha Ha and Sung Kyung hide
after hearing the ringing bells.]
- I think they're close.
- Be quiet.
Something feels off.
Something feels very off.
Hi.
[Make way for General Gary.]
How have you guys been?
Why don't you get up?
[This Giant-Kiddo couple have been hoping
to take home the victory today..]
We can tell you where the other teams are.
We know where other two teams are!
- They're right by us.
- Two other teams are nearby!
[Ratting others out to save their own lives
is a way of survival here on RM.]
[The female warrior makes
her way through!]
Let us go just this once.
[Female warrior's way- Once in sight,
you won't get away from me!]
Over.
- Bye!
- Sorry, Sung Kyung.
[Saigon goodbye with a bright
smile on her face after ousting them.]
- Bye!
- Sorry!
Ha Ha and Lee Sung Kyung, out.
Oh my goodness.
[The surviving couples dive into panic mode
after hearing the announcement.]
It's a guaranteed elimination
if they get their hands on us.
- There are only two couples left.
- Wait long enough, and we'll find them.
Can I have one of these baked goods?
Is it okay for me to eat one?
No, you can't.
You seem fine now, but as soon as
you see someone's name tag...
you turn into a total beast.
You're like Wonder Woman.
Wow, Soo Jin is unbelievable.
How can this be growing
without dirt?
What's this?
Soo Jin!
They're growing on sponges.
I think these are grown to be edible.
- That's amazing.
- I think they use these to make salads.
Soo Jin, don't most women want to shop
when they come to shopping malls like this?
But you have zero interest in these things,
and you're just hunting for these people.
[No interest in shopping, and
only in hunting down her prey.]
I don't know!
[The defense teams are
in a state of panic.]
It's me, Jong Kook.
We'll just sacrifice ourselves and
try to stall them for as long as possible
so take your time to freely walk around
and find the clue and the stage.
Jong Kook, I hear Soo Jin
is not to be messed with.
They're coming.
Get going, and we'll stall them.
- Let's go find it.
- We have to hurry.
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo start their search
through their friends' self-sacrifice.]
Let's just go out there confidently.
Walk out there confidently,
and run if we need to.
[Will they find the magnet first,
or will they eliminate their prey first?]
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon make their move
to buy some time for Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.]
[The couple spots Soo Jin.]
I think she saw us.
[Soo Jin picks up their scent
and starts the chase.]
Gary!
- Where could they be?
- Here's one!
[Could this be the right match?]
It's not sticking.
It's a fake.
[Jong Kook and Ga Yeon
lure Soo Jin away.]
Gary!
[Immediately finds another magnet.]
I can't believe we found one there.
[This one isn't a match either!]
Gary!
[Leading her further away to
buy some more time.]
Gary!
[Soo Jin calls out to Gary relentlessly.]
[Time is really starting to run out.]
[Oh? It's sticking together!]
[They just need to safely
get to the final stage location!]
[Just then, Jong Kook and Ga Yeon
run into a dead end!]
- Over here!
- Where?
[Gary and Soo Jin close in
on their prey.]
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are off to the
training room on the lower third floor.]
[And finally- Jong Kook and Ga Yeon
vs Gary and Soo Jin.]
[We have to stall them in order for Suk Jin
and Ji Hyo to get to the final stage!]
[Please stall them for just a bit longer!]
[Hurry!]
[But Jong Kook and Ga Yeon
are ultimately ousted.]
[The only two left... are us!]
[A dead run toward the final stage!]
Where could they be hiding?
[Gary and Soo Jin are hot
on the chase!]
[This way!]
[Will they get to the stage first,
or will they be eliminated first?]
[Carefully makes her way through.]
[Gary is spotted in the distance.]
[Got you!]
[Run!]
[The final stage is right
in front of their eyes!]
[But... Gary closes in on them
like a bolt of lightning!]
Gary!
[Will they hold out... or will he end them?]
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are ousted
right in front of their winning stage!]
[Soo Jin... we did it!]
Kyung Soo Jin won.
It was Kyung Soo Jin's win!
[Gary and Soo Jin takes their place
on top of the winning stage.]
[Love is Extreme Race-
Winning prize is a gold couple ring.]
You did work very hard.
Soo Jin, your smile is...
- It's all a lie!
- Her smile is not to be trusted.
The final winning couple of the day is,
Gary and Kyung Soo Jin!
[Love is Extreme Race-
Gary and Soo Jin are the winners!]
I want to see Ga Yeon giving Gary
a low kick instead of regular slate shot.
Why are you doing this to me?
Ga Yeon, can you show it to us?
- It's the price to pay for winning!
- Come on!
[A payback from all the
defensive teams.]
- It'll hurt more if you try to block her.
- Your think I'm crazy?
- Thank you!
[The first ever low kick slate shot.]
Wow, that looked really painful.
Ga Yeon is awesome.
[Thank you to our guests for
all the laughter they brought us.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
So... I hear that a huge business deal
is about to go down tonight.
Want to hear what it's about?
[Thieves that will turn the game
around are on their way.]
Jong Kook!
[There's only one goal.]
[A case that will shake up our world.]
Will you help me?
[Next week on Running Man-
The Last Case.]