Subtitles by DramaFever
[October 2014-
Gyunggi-do Suwon.]
[A helicopter in the city airspace.]
[The roar of armored vehicles.]
[An onslaught of hundreds
of special task forces.]
[Their target is inside this building.]
You are surrounded!
Surrender yourselves!
[What are they doing here?]
[A beautiful fall day on the streets.]
[A man on the streets...
Lee Kwang Soo.]
This weather...
suddenly makes me feel so
melancholy.
[A violin inside the case?]
[Is he about to put on an impromptu
concert on top of the garbage can?]
[A grotesque sound.]
[People start to gather one by one
at the awful sounding music.]
[Artist Giraffe sheds an emotional tear.]
[With all the emotions that
he's feeling...]
[A sudden explosion of music.]
[A mourning sound of the violin that
portrays the sadness in his heart.]
[How sad!]
[An explosion of tears.]
[A passionate performance that draws
tears from the crowd of audience.]
[A sea of tears on the streets.]
I'm hit with sudden wave of joy.
[Start of a joyful performance.]
[A cheerful performance unlike
the previous performance.]
[The streets suddenly become
a sea of laughter.]
[A genius violinist, Lee Kwang Soo.]
[The honorable nickname of
'Crazy Kwang Violinist' follows in his wake.]
[Clear piano melody.]
I feel the need to play something
that is befitting of this fall weather.
[Fingers are flying over the keys
during this piano performance.]
[The star of this amazing performance...]
[The handsome pianist, Kim Ji Hoon.]
I didn't know you could
play the piano like that.
[The battle of the pianos.]
[Blank Ji, the pianist.]
[The battle of the piano heats up.]
[Ji Hoon's shocking and unique performance.]
[Can't let you show me up!]
[The outcome of this fierce battle is...]
[a draw.]
Ouch, my fingers are burning.
[The side effects of such
a passionate performance.]
- It's good to see you, Ji Hoon.
- Good to see you, Ji Hyo.
We're very close pianist friends.
Ji Hoon's having difficulty breathing
from performing so hard on the piano.
I started playing the piano
as a form of a workout lately.
It's a really great form of exercise.
- I'm actually sweating right now.
- I never realized that he's so funny.
[The pianist with a unique personality.]
Sol, sol, ra, ra...
Sol, sol, ra, ra, sol, sol, mi.
[Could this familiar melody actually
be 'School bell is ringing'?]
[Cellist perfectionist, Kkuk.]
It's still not perfect.
Where's 'mi'?
I feel like I'm going to lose it!
Where did it go?
This isn't perfect!
[Kkuk's credo- 'My performance has
to be as perfect as my muscles.']
[Warm autumn sun...]
[And the beautiful strands of the harp.]
[Pavarotti's pupil, Yoo Jae Suk.]
Wait.
[The sounds of the harp heard
playing through the air.]
This beautiful melody...
Where is this music coming from?
Yeon Seo!
[Beautiful woodland harpist,
Oh Yeon Seo.]
- Yeon Seo!
- You're the world famous vocalist...
Yes, I'm Jae-pavarotti.
Do you have a favorite song?
- O sole mio.
- O sole mio?
[Like magic?]
[A shocking ability to transform
'O Sole Mio' to the sound of 'This moment.']
[Sorrowful sounds of an aria
ringing through this cafe...]
[The voice of an angel, Jung Eun Ji.]
[The climax of the aria!]
[The never-ending high note.]
- Thank you for the beautiful music.
- Thank you.
[The cafe owner hands over
a mysterious card.]
The 2014 Running Man
Music Concourse?
- An invitation?
- What's this?
[An invitation is handed out to
all the musical geniuses.]
[You are all invited to the
2014 Running Music Concourse.]
[Suwon Cultural Center- 'S' Atrium.]
[2014 - The First Running Music Concourse.]
[The stage where
the performance will take place.]
I think we're the first ones here.
[Vocalist- Yoo Jae Suk and
Harpist- Oh Yeon Seo.]
[A fierce competition from
Soprano, Jung Eun Ji.]
[Soprano- Jung Eun Ji.]
[Various genius musical artists are
invited to participate in the performance.]
[Pianists Song Ji Hyo and Kim Ji Hoon.]
[Drummer- Ji Suk Jin,
Cellist- Kim Jong Kook]
[Xylophonist- Gary, Flautist- Ha Ha,
Violinist- Lee Kwang Soo.]
[2014 The First Running Music Concourse.]
My name is Oh Yeon Seo,
the genius harpist.
- She has really cute dimples.
- She's a harpist?
- How many dimples does she have?
- Wow, look at her cute dimples!
You're right, she does have
three dimples.
She wanted four dimples, but she
doesn't have enough money for it yet.
- He's so weird!
- Even he himself admits that he's weird.
- Have you never experienced him yet?
- Ji Hoon's a little weird.
He was so distracting, loud,
and meddlesome on our way here.
- He's a bit strange.
- Ji Hoon's strangely alluring.
I think he's a bit similar to us.
You will all be participating in
the Running Concourse today.
But your application forms
have not been accepted yet.
[Our application forms
have not been accepted yet?]
Then are you saying that we may
not get to participate?
- Yes, that's correct.
- After breaking up our busy schedules?
You guys made me come here,
but I may not even get to participate?
- I will give you your first mission.
- What is it?
Your first mission is, 'Body Performance.'
Listen to the children's tune
that we'll be playing for you
and reenact the performance precisely
within the chances that you're given.
- Are you kidding me right now?
- How is that even a challenge?
[Isn't that too easy?
We're all musical geniuses!]
The instrument which you will be
playing is hung up on the ceiling.
- What is it?
- Is that a piano?
Is that even possible?
[A gigantic piano.]
[A cymbal and a drum are also
seen hanging on the ceiling.]
[Seven people on the piano, one on the drum,
one on the cymbal, and one vocalist.]
You want us to play these with our heads?
That's too advantageous for the Giraffe!
- I think I've done this before.
- Aren't we all on the same team?
[His head didn't even
graze the piano keys...]
- I didn't even hear anything.
- Suk Jin, you got your hair dye on it.
[Big-nose's hair dye leaves a mark
on the snow white keyboard.]
- What are you doing?
- Don't spray so much color on your hair!
- What is that?
- You got the keys all dirty!
Do we have to hit the cymbal
with our head, too?
- Yes, you'd have to use your head.
- You have to hit the cymbal with your head.
[A real piano sound!]
- What was that note?
- Sounds like someone is playing it.
No, it's connected to an
electronic sensor.
[I've got you!]
[The best human sensor that the
21st century has to offer.]
[Why does he have to be
such a curious sort?]
- They almost had me fooled.
- He's so scatter-brained.
- He's really distracting.
- And he's also very obsessive.
He's really suspicious
and not the trusting sort.
Let's pretend that never happened.
I will now play the song
that you will have to re-play.
[A song that we're all familiar with-
'Winter breeze.']
We have to make sure to
get the beat.
[Must be sure to get the right beat between
the piano, drum and the cymbal.]
We have to make sure to get
the beat right.
We have to get the beat right.
- Can you sing the notes?
- Mi, fa, sol, la, sol.
- Fa, mi, rae, do, do.
- She has it perfect!
She really is a genius!
She knows all the notes!
[Able to pick out all the notes
throughout the song!]
- Eun Ji knows all the notes. Gary!
- Yes?
- You take the cymbal.
- Okay!
[Gary to take charge of the cymbal.]
We need another person for 'Do'.
- Mi, fa, sol, la, sol, do.
- Jong Kook can do both.
[Jong Kook to take care of both notes?]
- We need another person for that note.
- Maybe I shouldn't be standing here.
[Since 'Do' seems to be a popular note,
Kwang Soo is given the task.]
- There are a lot of 'do' notes.
- Only one person per note.
If Kwang Soo is doing the high 'Do',
then he has to do the low 'Do' as well.
[Once a 'Do', then always a 'Do.']
- Yes, we should do it that way.
- You take them both.
- Kwang Soo can take them both.
- How can I take them both?
Okay, that's a good decision.
Ji Hoon, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Why is your hand down your pants?
[Ji Hoon's naughty hands.]
We've all been practicing, but
what are you doing with your hand?
My shirt is sticking out as if
my stomach is all bloated.
- I'm going to go very slow.
- Okay, sounds good.
- Challenge! One, two, three.
- Challenge!
[Body performance- First attempt.]
- Challenge.
- Okay, let's do this.
Set, go!
[The piano performance is spot on.]
[But Ha Ha's drum is ignoring
all the beats.]
[He was given the easiest task,
but misses everything from the start.]
- No, I'll do it.
- I'll do better, I promise.
I promise, I know what to do now.
[Last chance for Ha Ha,
the drummer boy.]
If you mess up again, you're finished
here, and we're kicking you out.
Who are you to do that?
Who do you think you are?
[The musical geniuses fierce battle.]
- Tell him that he'll be kicked out.
- I'll be the one to kick anyone out.
Okay, then I'll help you take him out.
Okay, I got it.
Does everyone agree?
- The same rule applies to you.
- Mess up again, and you're all kicked out.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Challenge!
- Set, go!
[Ha Ha misses the beat again.]
- You're not hitting it!
- What?
- Tell me what I'm doing wrong!
- Take that off.
[Forced out as promised.]
You hit the drum
when you weren't supposed to.
[What humiliation is this from
a simple mistake?]
No, just take off his socks,
but we'll take off more next time.
- You'd better watch it.
- That's enough for now.
You better watch it, got it?
Get yourself together.
You'd better watch it if you don't
want to get kicked out for good.
[Pull yourself together!]
- I'll go here, so move over.
- Why are you so much shorter?
Why are you so much shorter
all of a sudden?
[Why do you think?]
Eun Ji, is it like this?
[Big-nose is now in charge of the drum.]
[Practicing his beats to avoid receiving
the same humiliating treatment.]
[Striving for perfection.]
Eun Ji looks like an animal trainer.
[Looking at Eun Ji is like looking
at an animal tamer.]
[Will the animal tamer have an effect
on the outcome this time around?]
- It's already our third attempt?
- Challenge!
Set, go!
[Big-nose, this isn't the time!]
[Perfect varied beats.]
[The drum may be easy to hit,
but the beat isn't easy to match...]
[As before, he's immediately stripped
of his drumming role.]
- No, that's not even right!
- You want the mic clipped to your bare skin?
- Why are you doing this?
[Position elimination is getting harsher.]
No, that's not it!
You guys are moving too slow!
Tell me if you want your mic to be
clipped onto your bare skin.
I thought you're supposed to be
the drumming genius.
- I thought you said you were good?
- You said you knew what to do.
Swap him out.
Let's get it right this time.
[Body performance- Fourth attempt.]
[Ji Hoon is put in charge
as the new drummer.]
- I haven't done this yet.
- 'Ri' is your note.
- Set, go!
- I have to start?
- This is my first time doing it.
- He's making me feel nervous.
Wait!
[Missed beat.]
[Misses four drum beats in a row.]
But you got further than anyone else.
- You're actually pretty good.
- Get his shoes.
No, not my shoes!
- What kind of socks are those?
- What's with these socks?
- What is that on your socks?
What is this, Ji Hoon?
[Air shoe lift!]
You're such a con!
[With the lift out of his shoes, his
eye level is now lower than it was.]
Even I don't use this high of a lift!
- Just pretend that you didn't see it.
- Pretend we didn't see it?
[Body performance- Fifth attempt.]
Now!
[An absurd mistake by Big-nose.]
- Take it off.
- Why did you jump then?
No, stop it!
You told me to do it!
No, you told me to.
Hey, Yeon Seo.
[Why is he calling Yeon Seo over?]
He took off his pants.
[Look is transformed into a skirt fashion
reminiscent of the roman days.]
We had no other choice.
I can't even turn around in this.
This is actually for the better.
Keep facing forward.
[A man should never turn his back.]
- This will help with his concentration.
- Yes, that's right.
Okay, let's try it again.
[Fails the sixth and seventh attempt,
and now on their eighth attempt.]
Okay, we're all set.
Eun Ji, why are you taking off your jacket
when you haven't made any mistakes?
- Because I was getting hot.
- Keep it on in case you make a mistake.
What if you make a mistake?
- What are you even saying?
- How can you even say that?
[We made it very clear that
there will be exceptions...]
- You never know what'll happen.
- What are you even saying?
- Okay, this will be your eighth attempt.
- Get ready! One, two, three.
- Challenge!
- Set, go!
- Run quickly!
- It's okay, take it easy.
- Hurry back!
- Hurry!
[Giraffe's critical role.]
[Giraffe misses his aim.]
I told you to go slow!
You said I was doing a good job!
I'm working harder than anyone else!
[We know you're working hard,
but rules are still rules.]
- We just need to take this off.
- This is going too far.
[Since I've worked so hard,
can't you forego my socks?]
[What utter nonsense!]
- You don't have to do this, do you?
- Look at me!
[The aristocratic fashion prohibits him
from doing anything too active.]
- We have to stay focused.
- We're almost there.
- This is our last chance.
- Seriously?
- Can you give us two more chances?
- No, we can't.
We can't make any mistakes
this time.
- How can you do it like that?
- Saying it once was enough!
I was going to stop saying it, too.
[Why are you yelling like that?]
- Can't you go easy on us?
- Why do you keep repeating yourself?
Okay, get ready.
This is your last chance.
[Everything is riding on
this one last attempt.]
[Body performance- Final attempt.]
- Okay, let's do this.
- Let's get this done.
Set, go!
[The perfect harmony.]
- Slow.
- Slow it down.
[These geniuses are making
perfectly harmonious music together.]
Take it slow.
There you go.
[Giraffe with the
two Do's and two hearts.]
[Almost made a mistake.]
Good, Kwang Soo!
[Giraffe's flying performance.]
[Down to the final bar.]
It's the last note!
[Only one final note left in the song.]
[Their final chance-
We'll get it this time!]
[Admission mission- Body performance.
Mission success.]
[The ten musical geniuses
finally succeeds the mission.]
Congratulations, you barely succeeded
the mission on your tenth and final chance.
Although you've succeeded, since
you succeeded on your tenth attempt
only seven out of the ten of you will have
the chance to participate in the event.
[Only the best of the best are
given the chance to participate.]
Oh Yeon Seo, Song Ji Hyo, and
Jung Eun Ji failed to pass.
They failed to obtain
the admission for the event.
Why is it only the women?
- You're right!
- That's all our top players!
Eun Ji did all the hard work!
- But Eun Ji did all the hard work!
- No, I didn't.
You will be given exactly ten minutes.
Find the blank application forms that are
hidden outside this practice room
write down your names on it,
fill out your forms
and turn it back in to be given
the chance to participate.
- Okay, go!
- How is it be all the girls?
- Did they receive a special mission?
- We'll be back!
[Off to find the blank application forms!]
The rest of you can start practicing.
[Must find the application forms
within ten minutes.]
[The remaining geniuses start
their own individual practicing.]
I feel bad for those three girls.
We didn't mean for that to happen.
That was the best performance
of my life.
- Aren't you a pianist?
- Let's all perform together!
I play the harp as a hobby.
Let's all play together for once.
- Okay, let's go.
- One, two, three, four!
[Right at this moment!]
[The musical geniuses' disastrous harmony.]
Jung Eun Ji, Out!
[Jung Eun Ji... out?]
[How can this be?]
- What was that?
- Jung Eun Ji is out?
- Jung Eun Ji, out?
- Eun Ji is out?
She's ousted?
- Why is Eun Ji ousted?
- There must be something going on.
[Why is Eun Ji suddenly ousted?]
What's going on here?
Why is Eun Ji ousted?
[Just what in the world is going on?]
What is this about?
Why is Eun Ji ousted?
- Ji Hyo, why is Eun Ji ousted?
- Eun Ji's been ousted.
[Just then, Ji Hyo comes back in
with an application form in hand.]
- I don't know what happened either.
- Let me see your name tag.
- Is there something going on?
- How did she get ousted?
- Why would she be ousted?
- Where did she go?
- Where's Yeon Seo?
- Yeon Seo didn't oust Eun Ji, did she?
Something doesn't feel right about this.
[Ji Hyo and Yeon Seo are the only ones
who left the room with Eun Ji.]
I just found this on the third floor,
and there was no one up there.
[I really don't know...]
- What's going on here?
- There's Yeon Seo.
- Yeon Seo's scaring me.
- Does she know what's going on?
- I found it!
- That's not the issue. Eun Ji's been ousted.
- Eun Ji's been ousted.
- Why did she get ousted?
- Did you oust her?
- Why would I oust her?
- You scare me.
- Why are you so happy to hear the news?
[Seeming very suspicious of Yeon Seo
and Ji Hyo for Eun Ji's elimination.]
I heard the announcement,
but I thought it was for something else.
Wouldn't the culprit be one of the girls
who went out with her?
It couldn't have been me because I found
that sheet after I heard the announcement.
[It really isn't me...]
I'm really suspicious of Ji Hyo.
- I swear that I'm innocent.
- Seriously?
- But the rest of us were all together.
- Then there's another culprit out there?
I'm sure that this is all a set up.
Jung Eun Ji is the real culprit.
- What's going on here?
- Why did Eun Ji get ousted?
[Just what in the world is going on here?]
What's that?
Is there an announcement?
This is the Running Concourse Committee.
We have an announcement to make
to all of you in the auditorium.
The Running Concourse will still take
place on stage as originally planned.
In order to participate in the concourse,
you must submit an admission form
and take a picture of yourself with
the instant cameras that we have hidden
and bring them both back
to the admissions office.
- What's going on here?
- Where did our Eun Ji go?
- What happened to Eun Ji?
- The culprit has yet to be found.
[The culprit has yet to be caught.]
Find the hint to determine
who the culprit is
and use the building's telephone system
to report who the culprit is when found.
However, if an innocent person is
falsely reported as the culprit
then the person making the report may be
ousted instead for making a false report.
Please think very carefully
before calling in the report.
It has to be an inside job.
[Everyone's suspecting each other
to be the culprit.]
I'm sure someone is behind all this.
[No one can be trusted.]
Please submit all the necessary items so
that you may participate in the concourse.
[What is the hidden secret behind the
mysterious disappearance of Eun Ji?]
[Musical Geniuses' Symphony Race- Start.]
There's an instant camera somewhere?
But where did Eun Ji go?
[The unknown mystery surrounding
Eun Ji's disappearance.]
I have to find an instant camera?
I have to find something to take
a picture of myself with, right?
[The aura of mystery
that surrounds the auditorium.]
Doesn't it feel like
there's something going on?
- I think it's one of us.
- One of us?
I think someone's been given
a secret mission.
There's someone that we're
not aware of.
- I think Eun Ji was onto something.
- There's something we're not aware of.
- I think Eun Ji's up to something.
- I bet Eun Ji is actually up to something.
We have to find a camera to take a picture
of ourselves and while searching for a camera
we also have to find a clue pointing
to who the culprit actually is.
Where are those things
usually hidden?
- This is my first time being on Running Man.
- But I'm sure you've seen the show before.
[Ji Hoon's following Blank Ji's every move.]
Are you the culprit?
I feel like you're the culprit. You
received a separate mission, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
- Kim Ji Hoon, you're making me nervous.
- Come on, help me out.
- Why do you keep following me around?
- It's because I don't know what I'm doing.
Why are you doing this? You want
to rip off my name tag, don't you?
- No, I'm not going to do that.
- You ousted Eun Ji, didn't you?
How could I?
I was playing the drums.
- No, you're hiding something.
- What could I be hiding?
What's that?
[The reporting telephone!]
That must be the phone we use to report
the culprit when we find out who it is.
- That's right, the culprit!
- But a false report will get you eliminated.
[If a false culprit is reported, then
the one making the report is eliminated.]
I forgot about the culprit!
What?
- It's not me.
- What do you have in that bag?
No, there's nothing.
There's a very high chance that
one of you girls is the culprit.
[Kwang Soo suspects one of the girls
to be the culprit who ousted Eun Ji.]
But it really isn't me.
I really like mysteries and such
and in most cases, it's the least likely
person that ends up being the culprit.
But I really am not the culprit.
What are you saying?
That you are or that you aren't?
No, it's not me.
I'm not the culprit.
[Could Kwang Soo be dumping the suspicion
on Yeon Seo because he's the culprit?]
[Or could it be that Yeon Seo is trying to
deter Kwang Soo's suspicions away from her?]
[The genius flautist, Ha Ha,
discovers the camera.]
[Just then, Gary comes onto the scene.]
[Ha Ha is caught by surprise,
and just leaves the camera behind.]
Have you taken any pictures yet?
[The two children discover
the camera at the same time.]
[The start of the photo war.]
[What's all that noise?]
[The pack of hyenas start to close in.]
[Ha Ha steals the camera away!]
[The owner of the camera swaps
hands every three seconds!]
[There's just one film per camera...]
[But the owner of the camera can't take
more than three steps before losing it.]
[The musical geniuses'
rough tumble for the camera.]
[Oh?]
[Kwang Soo took the picture!]
[But did the camera
capture Kwang Soo's face?]
What the heck?
I bet there are about four
faces in there.
It did capture someone face,
but it's someone else's face.
- Is it my face?
- Who is it?
- It captured someone else's face.
Just rip it up if it's someone
else's face.
[The Grasshopper ruined
the Giraffe's picture!]
[But it has to be a solo picture,
and must not have their glasses on.]
- You found something, didn't you?
- No, I haven't found anything.
You found something, didn't you?
Have you found the camera yet?
- I have no idea where the cameras are.
- I have something to ask you.
What were you guys all doing
when you were together earlier?
When us girls went out to look
for that admission slip earlier.
- We were all on the stage together.
- Not a single one of you went anywhere?
Not even for a moment?
[We were all on stage practicing
playing our instruments...]
Oh, I didn't even think of that.
The culprit could've done something then.
- Right? Come here, Kwang Soo.
- That one, there.
[Like this guy?]
What were you doing earlier?
- When? I've already been searched.
- What were you doing earlier?
But...
[Is Ji Hoon really worried about something,
or is he just putting on an act?]
I really think that Jung Eun Ji
is planning something right now.
[Ji Hoon is trying to convince others that
Eun Ji had masterminded everything.]
Maybe she secretly brought in another
member of A-Pink or something.
- Son Na Eun?
- I told you that he's weird.
- Maybe you just like Son Na Eun.
- No, that's not it.
No, but doesn't it sound likely though?
[Just what is the real truth
behind this mystery?]
I feel like someone is going to
come after my name tag.
[Drummer, Suk Jin, is feeling
weary about what's going on.]
[Just then...]
[Jae Suk ambushes Big-nose!]
Be quiet.
You have to be quiet.
Hurry up and shut the door.
You're curious to know what
happened to Eun Ji, aren't you?
[Could Jae Suk have done
something to Eun Ji?]
I'm curious, too.
What was that all about?
[That was just a prank?]
I thought you were about to give me
a secret mission or something.
[But was that really just
a silly prank?]
[Is Jae Suk searching for a clue
or a camera?]
I'm really bad at searching for things.
[Seriously?]
This is someone's personal locker.
I'm sorry.
[Searching through all the lockers when
the 'R' stickered item is right behind him.]
[Just then, Kkuk also enters the room.]
[Immediately discovers the stickered item
as soon as Jae Suk leaves the room.]
Fireworks of love?
Hey.
Jae Suk didn't even see this in
front of him and he just walked out.
Jae Suk... you didn't even
see this here?
[Did he really not see it, or did
he just pretend not to have seen it?]
Then let me see it.
What is it that you're after?
Where is Eun Ji?
That's what I'd like to ask you.
- Let's look at it together, Jong Kook.
- I looked and there's nothing in here.
- Come on, let's look at it together.
- What are you guys doing?
- How could you have missed this?
- Are you being Yoo-ames Bond?
- Let me see.
[Is Jae Suk acting
particularly suspicious?]
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha
are the only ones in the room.]
[Sheet music to 'Fireworks of Love'...]
I don't think this is about finding
some secret numeric code.
[Could this sheet music contain some
clue as to who the culprit is?]
Wait, look at these candles!
Wait, this music is for 'Fireworks of love.'
[Could these candles contain
some sort of a hidden message?]
Let's try lighting these.
[Lights the candles to see
what may happen...]
Wait, why would these candles
be in here?
Jong Kook!
[Could it be...]
[Shines the candle light
under the sheet music.]
- I think I see something.
- Yes, I see it, too!
I think I see something, too.
[The fire from the candle is showing
something on the sheet music!]
[The sheet music shows a
hidden message!]
I can't believe this!
You are the torch in my heart,
and this life can be so strange.
Okay, you are the torch in my heart,
Okay, let's see what else.
We got it!
I can't believe this!
Look at these letters.
The culprit is...
- The culprit is...
- I actually feel a little afraid.
[When only the dotted letters
are read...]
The culprit is amongst you.
- Look at the dotted letters.
- The Culprit is...
[The culprit is amongst you.]
Wow, we're pretty impressive.
No, wait.
Wait, I have my finger
on the button right now.
Don't do it.
There's only one film in there.
[Kwang Soo, Ji Hoon, and Suk Jin are
on their second round of camera battle.]
- No one's going to get it like this.
- Get off my back right now.
- Don't press the button.
- Okay, I'm not going to run away.
- Let go of me right now.
- You can't press the button.
You'll come out looking hideous like that.
Are you trying to take the picture?
[Ji Hoon takes the opportunity
to attempt to take the picture.]
I'm not trying to do anything,
so you have to be careful right now.
It took the picture!
[Oh no... what a waste.]
Are you guys really going
to be like this?
Can't one of us just take
the picture first?
Ji Hoon found it first, so we
should've just let him have it.
- That's what I'm telling you.
- What? You were holding onto him.
Your lack of loyalty is...
[Ji Hoon pulls himself away from the
Easy Brothers to search on his own.]
[Searches through every nook and
cranny to find the clue or the camera.]
This is really hard.
The dressing room?
[Searches through the dressing room.]
[At last!]
[Another clue!
Finds an 'R' marked cassette player!]
[It probably contains a clue
as to who the culprit is...]
Where's the power cord?
[But it doesn't have a power cord,
or any batteries.]
What am I supposed to do with this?
You have to give me either
the batteries or the power cord.
[Looking at the cassette tape...]
[Park Sang Min's
'Road that isn't a road.']
Does it mean that this
isn't the road?
Does it mean that I shouldn't be here?
A clue.
[Blank Ji is also on the search for a
clue pointing to the culprit's identity.]
[Get rid of the obstacles.]
Wait, it's a water sprayer.
[An 'R' marked water spray bottle...]
Get rid of the obstacle?
[Spraying the mirror
with the water spray bottle.]
[Oh?
The lines are erasing off!]
[Some letters are erasing off,
and some aren't.]
[Wipes off the mirror with a tissue.]
[More and more are erasing,
leaving a clearer message.]
[The remaining word on the mirror...]
Single?
[The culprit is single.]
[If the culprit is single...]
[Ji Hyo's now on a mission
to search for more clues.]
[Discovers another 'R' marked clue!]
A list of items to be repaired.
[A list of items to be repaired?]
What's this supposed to mean?
I can't even understand
what this means.
[Each item has a letter of the alphabet
and numbers attached to it.]
I think it's seat numbers.
Seat numbers.
[Ji Hyo guesses that the letter and numbers
indicate a certain seat number.]
Yes, these are indicating
to a certain seat number.
[Our Ace correctly guesses that the
mysterious sequence indicates to a seat.]
[But why is it indicating to these seats?]
Wow, unbelievable.
I think I get it now.
[Just what is it that
Blank Ji's figured out?]
By any chance, is there a small diagram
of all the seats in the auditorium?
[Blank Ji acquires a diagram
of all the seats in the auditorium.]
[She's checking all the seats that are
jotted down on the itemized list.]
Song Ji Hyo, out.
[Just what is going on?]
Had Ji Hyo figured out who
the culprit is or something?
[Is the culprit still on the move?]
The culprit ousted someone else?
- We can still be ousted?
- Ugh, this is hard.
I wonder if all the girls are in
on some sort of a plan together?
Do they have some sort of a plan
to start ousting each other?
It's begun.
He's on the move.
Even though I've already guessed...
Yes, it ultimately comes down to
a battle between you and I.
I will catch you in the end.
You just wait and see.
[Culprit or not, this Yoo-varotti
is busy playing the rusty horn.]
[Suk Jin is drawn by the sound of the
horn and comes upon the stage.]
What are you doing? You heard
the announcement, didn't you?
- You heard the announcement, right?
- You know of Ji Hyo's elimination?
He's getting closer.
Are you shooting a movie by yourself?
- You don't know what's going on.
- Don't act like you're Sherlock Holmes.
- Don't think that you're Sherlock Holmes.
- You can be my Watson.
- You know who Watson is, don't you?
- That's not bad.
Okay, I'll be Watson.
You seem excited about it.
You like being Watson, don't you?
- Watson is still a major character.
- Okay, deal.
- Sherlock.
- Watson.
[Yoo-Sherlock and Ji-Watson.
Middle-aged detectives.]
Who could've ousted Ji Hyo?
- Oh Yeon Seo.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- Or Jung Eun Ji.
- It's one of those three.
I bet we're going to shock everyone.
- Yes, we're going to shock everyone.
- We're above everyone else's thinking.
Yes, sound the celebratory
music, Sherlock.
[Jong Kook discovers the
'R' marked camera.]
[The goal of all the musical geniuses
here is to participate in the concourse.]
[Jong Kook's admission form
is nearly complete.]
[But this isn't the end of it- He must also
find sheet music of Beethoven's sympathy.]
I look too excited in the photo.
[Yeon Seo also succeeds in getting
a picture of herself.]
I feel like I'm going to have a
heart attack trying to take this picture.
Do you see how my hands
are shaking?
[It's a place full of high energy and fear.]
I look like I'm being
chased after by something.
[She just needs to find Beethoven's music
in order to be able to participate.]
[But she must not get ousted by
the culprit before that happens...]
But you can't be going around
blabbering your mouth about this, okay?
I found this cassette nearby a radio.
[Ji Hoon shares his hint with Kwang Soo
when he's unable to figure it out on his own.]
I wasn't able to play this on the radio
but the title of the song is written on here.
[Shares the hint with Kwang Soo.]
Could this title be pointing to Gary?
['A road that isn't a road'...
could it mean Gary?]
Here it is!
[Gary discovers a camera.]
[But now that we think about it, Gary's
been going around on his own today...]
[Meanwhile, Ji Hoon and Kwang Soo are
busy trying to figure out the hint.]
[Turning the tape around in the cassette.]
[Oh? What are those
white lines on the tape?]
1m?
Doesn't it just mean that we've
turned 1m of the tape?
Maybe you're right.
But why would it indicate that?
[The white lines are still being spotted.]
[And 2m...]
[What could these mean?]
Wow, you're really smart.
[Ji Hoon's pulls out the length of the tape.]
Maybe it's telling us to
use it like a measuring tape.
[Thinking closely, the white lines are
indicating a length of 10cm.]
Yes, that's a nice picture.
[Gary successfully
takes a picture of himself.]
[Hurries to complete the
admission form.]
[Who could that be?]
Gary, out.
[People are being eliminated
one by one.]
Wow, I seriously am so lost.
No way that Ji Hyo would
get ousted so quickly.
[Could this be the work of someone
who's already been ousted?]
[Or could the culprit still be
amongst us?]
- Did Yeon Seo get her picture?
- Yes, she did.
Kwang Soo got one,
and Dong Hoon got one too.
- Gary got one too.
- He had found one too, right?
- Gary had gotten one, too.
- Then only those with a picture are ousted?
- But falsely reporting someone means...
- Yes, that can get you ousted, too.
- But I don't think Gary reported anyone in.
- I know, but there aren't enough clues.
I can't figure out who the culprit is.
Gary played a prank earlier like he was...
[Automatically raises her hand to
hit the person behind her in response.]
- You almost got smacked in the face.
- No, it was just automatic reflex.
Maybe there's a reason why
she hasn't been ousted yet.
Doesn't having my name tag ripped
off mean that I'm ousted?
I've already been around here
several times.
I can't believe that I'm back
in here again.
[Yoo-Sherlock is just aimlessly walking
around the same space in circles.]
[Discovers some sheet music sitting
on tip of the piano.]
Was this here before?
[And when he lifts up the lid
to reveal the keyboard...]
The dressing room?
What does this mean?
Wait, does this song mean something?
[This has to be some sort of a clue
indicating to who the culprit is...]
[Yoo-Sherlock attempts to play
the song on the sheet music.]
[Numbers on the sides of the keys!]
This really is something.
Zero.
Two.
0021?
What does '0021' mean?
Wow, seriously.
[Must mean that I need to go
to the dressing room.]
[Jae Suk hurries to rush over
- Why don't we all try to figure it out?
- But I think... okay, I will.
I will work with you guys on this,
but I think the culprit purposely did it.
Like this?
Be careful, Dong Hoon almost got
smacked a little while ago.
He almost got smacked in the face.
[Was it just a joke or a part
of his plans?]
I'll just figure this out on my own.
[The clue that Yeon Seo found is
a drawing of some sort?]
I thought of Ha Ha when
I saw this picture.
[Playground indicates to kiddo Ha Ha?]
How many kids are there
in the picture?
Let's count to see how many boys
and girls there are.
[This picture definitely has a clue
as to who the culprit is...]
- Do you think the picture means something?
- Come on.
You said yourself that you have read
over a hundred mystery books.
- See if you can figure it out.
- Murder mysteries are what I read.
Why are you reading things like that?
So I'm not good at finding
hidden meanings.
- I wish I could find another hint.
- What's this?
What's this?
I see an instrument here.
Look, here's an instrument.
[This instrument is...]
- Isn't that a violin?
- It's a violin.
- Who played the violin earlier?
[If it's a violin,
then it's Kwang Soo...]
Who played the violin earlier?
That's you.
- It was you, wasn't it?
- Are you confessing?
It's you.
I'm not the culprit!
[Just then, he runs into
Jong Kook outside.]
[Kwang Soo is forced to flee.]
- What is it?
- Kwang Soo is the culprit!
- Jong Kook, I've been wronged!
[Kwang Soo on the run,
and those in pursuit.]
What is it?
- It's not me!
- What is it? Tell me!
- Jong Kook! You have to catch him!
- It really isn't me.
- Jong Kook, it really isn't me.
- Then stop running away.
- You believe that it isn't me, don't you?
- Let's just catch him and talk.
- You can't eliminate me right now.
- Okay, but what is it?
[Violinist Kwang Soo is surrounded.]
- Are you the culprit?
- No, it's not me.
- I want to trust you, but I'm not sure.
- It can't be me because...
- Why did you run away?
- Because you were trying to attack me.
- Why did you run if it's not you?
- You need to calm Yeon Seo down.
- Why, what is it?
- The thing is...
He found the clue, but it
ended up being his instrument.
Then could it be a
smaller version of the cello?
- Yes, it could be the cello.
- Cello.
[But the cello would mean...
that it's Jong Kook.]
Okay, even I admit that
it was a picture of the violin.
- It was the violin?
- You know that it's not me, right?
- No, I don't know!
- You have to believe me.
- Why would I...
- Tell me what's going on here.
I saw a hidden violin picture
in the painting.
- There was a hidden violin in the picture.
- Yeon Seo.
- Yeah?
- Where are you going?
- Bye.
- Yeon Seo, you know it isn't me, right?
[Where is Yeon Seo suddenly going?]
Don't you think that it would be too weird
for me to turn out to be the culprit?
- I have no idea what you are.
- I'm just a clueless violinist.
I'm just a simple genius violinist.
You're 99% an idiot, but there are
times when you're like a genius.
- That's what scares me.
- I'm that 99% today.
[Jae Suk goes down to the dressing room
following the clue that he just found.]
[But... all the doors are locked.]
[A secret code is needed to
unlock these doors.]
[Could it be...]
[The numbers hidden between
the piano keys.]
Ugh, you dummy!
Ugh, you dummy.
You deserve to be beat.
Ugh, you dummy!
[If it's not 0021...]
[It's not 0012 either.]
[1002 unlocks the door!]
[Finally unlocks the door to
walk into the dressing room...]
[That's...]
[Ousted Eun Ji's name tag!]
[And a piece of string?
What could this mean?]
[Eun Ji... could your secret be...]
Jung Eun Ji.
It's has to be
Kim Jong Kook and Jung Eun Ji.
[Ji-Watson guesses that Jung Eun Ji and
Kim Jong Kook must be working together.]
Being alone is making me feel nervous.
[Suk Jin is separated from
all the other musicians.]
Being alone is making me
feel really uneasy.
[Just like he predicted, could
some force be closing in on him?]
I'm suspicious of Jong Kook.
[Must hurry up and find the culprit.]
What's this?
Ji Suk Jin, out.
[Musical geniuses are disappearing
one by one without a trace.]
[No one can be trusted.]
Ji Suk Jin, out.
I'm in trouble.
[Just then... sudden footsteps
are heard out in the hallway.]
[The sounds of the footsteps
are getting even closer.]
[The knocking on the door is
making his heart constrict.]
[Who could be on the other
side of the door?]
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
[The musicians are being eliminated
at an even faster rate.]
[Just who in the world is
the real culprit?]
Jae Suk...
[With Jae Suk's elimination, the musicians
are thrown into an even bigger state of fear.]
Jong Kook, the truth is...
- I'm not sure how much I should tell you...
- Just tell me.
But those two married men
were very suspicious of you.
And now, both of them have
been eliminated.
[Those who were suspicious of Jong Kook
all have been eliminated?]
Why would I?
I've been with you guys all along.
That's what I told them too.
I told them that it isn't you.
- Not when you've worked so hard.
- It isn't me.
- You worked so hard with me.
- It really isn't me.
If you end up being the culprit, I think
I'll be mad at you for like two weeks.
- I'm being serious.
- Then call in and tell them that it's me.
- I'm serious.
- No, you go first.
- No, tell them that it's me.
- I insist that you go first.
[Must find the clues to report the culprit
before they all end up being eliminated.]
Is the piano locked?
[Ji Hoon's on the hunt to
search for more clues.]
[Discovers an 'R marked box!]
What's this?
[Inside the box...
is a recorder and a ribbon?]
Will the culprit come out
if I start playing it?
[The culprit isn't a cobra.]
[Carefully looks over the recorder.]
This mystery is really difficult
to solve.
[And the mysterious strand of ribbon.]
Wow, I'm getting goosebumps.
What have they done to
this ribbon?
I have no idea what this means.
[Random pen markings on the ribbon.]
Wow, I'm getting goosebumps.
Ugh, Running Man is seriously annoying.
Why are these writers so clever?
[He starts to wrap the strand of
ribbon around the recorder.]
This is unbelievable.
[Just what is written on the ribbon strand?]
[How can this be?]
First...
First, the cassette tape said
something about 2m.
I measured it against Kwang Soo earlier,
and it fit Kwang Soo's height perfectly.
[Ji Hoon measured Kwang Soo's height
with the tape measure earlier.]
It's a perfect fit.
Then you're telling me
that I'm the culprit?
[Then could the tape measure have
indicated to the culprit's height?]
And it was really weird that Kwang Soo saw
the violin in the picture when I couldn't.
Because we couldn't see the violin
no matter how closely we looked at it.
[Just what is the hidden meaning
behind this picture?]
- Isn't that a violin?
- Who played the violin earlier?
[The picture that no one else could see...
Was Kwang Soo playing a trick?]
[Okay, Kwang Soo.]
- Ji Hoon.
- Yes?
- Come here, Ji Hoon. Let's end this.
- Let's report this, and end it.
- Who are we reporting?
- Let's each report someone and end this.
- Okay, let's do that.
- Let's go in the order of age.
- Then the youngest one can go first.
Since we're doing it in order of age, let's
start with the youngest person here.
Who are you going to report?
- I have a feeling that it's Kwang Soo.
- I also think that it's Kwang Soo.
[Ji Hoon's convinced that it's Kwang Soo.]
When I piece together
all the clues that I've found...
Kwang Soo is the most likely suspect.
- Then should I just call in the report?
- Yes.
Don't push him into doing it.
It may not be Kwang Soo.
- Should I just guess? Just call it in?
- Yeah.
- Just end the show right here?
- It really doesn't matter to me.
We can start the eight o'clock news
a little early tonight.
Let's see what happens.
[Ji Hoon lifts up the telephone receiver.]
I really want to find out.
- Hello?
- Yes, hello.
- Yes, who's this?
- This is Kim Ji Hoon.
- Mr. Kim Ji Hoon?
- Yes.
[The call has been made, and
now it's time to make the report.]
- I think the culprit is...
- Yes, who's the culprit?
[The culprit is...]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[The culprit is Lee Kwang Soo.]
[The height of 2m.]
[Single and is a violinist.]
[Could Kwang Soo really be the one who
wrote the symphony of elimination?]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Lee Kwang Soo is the culprit!]
[An alarm to sound the report.]
[An onslaught of Running
Special Task Force.]
What's that?
[Suspect, Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Reporter, Kim Ji Hoon.]
[If it's the right report, then culprit
Kwang Soo will be apprehended.]
[But if the report is wrong, then Ji Hoon will
be apprehended for making a false report.]
[Will it be Kwang Soo or Ji Hoon?]
[The special task force's target
is Ji Hoon!]
[The whole task force moves in to
capture one false reporter!]
- Wait.
- You must've made a false report.
I didn't do anything that wrong.
You are under arrest
for calling in a false report.
Can you please let me go
just this once?
[Kim Ji Hoon, out.]
What is this?
Ji Hoon, you said you were sure
that it was Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo isn't the culprit.]
I had so much evidence
indicating that it's Kwang Soo.
[Ji Hoon was convinced that it was Kwang Soo.
Then did he not correctly solve the clues?]
Do you normally come in a
large group like this?
Kim Ji Hoon, out.
Who did he report?
Did he report me?
[Thus, it's been proven that
Kwang Soo isn't the culprit.]
I had so much evidence
indicating that it's Kwang Soo.
What is it?
Is someone in there?
[Could the culprit be...]
- These letters?
- Look at the dotted letters.
- The culprit is...
- Eliminate the obstacle?
[The clue that Ji Hyo figured out...]
[When her clue was solved...]
[The culprit is single.]
What's this?
[The picture clue
that Kwang Soo figured out.]
[The string instrument
that looked like a violin.]
Who played the violin earlier?
[Kwang Soo was suspected for
having solved the mysterious clue...]
[The tape hint that Kwang Soo and
Ji Hoon solved together.]
[The white markings that indicated
every 10cm.]
[And the 2m marking at the end
of those white markings.]
[But there's a small secret that
Ji Hoon and Kwang Soo had missed.]
[Number, 178, was written onto the tape.]
[And the recorder and the ribbon clue
that only Ji Hoon was aware of.]
[A word was created when the ribbon
was wrapped around the recorder.]
It's a male.
The culprit is a male.
[The culprit is a male.]
[The four separate clues indicating
to the identity of the culprit.]
The culprit is amongst you.
[Then who could the culprit be?]
[The moment that Ji Hoon is taken away
for having made a false report...]
[Jong Kook suddenly springs into action.]
Is someone in there?
Wait a second!
Wait!
[Twenty years ago]
The first place winner of the
Young Running Concourse Competition is...
Kim Jong Kook!
[Other young musicians'
jealousy and envy...]
[The genius cellist who celebrated
the glory of his victory...]
[But after the moment of his victory...]
Did you forget everything
that you learned yesterday?
[The pressures and the expectations that he
received from everyone regarding his music.]
[He slowly starts to crumble...]
Ma'am, I think we need to talk.
Ma'am, Jong Kook's skills
and talent...
I'm sorry to tell you this, but I don't think
Jong Kook has real talent to be a cellist.
I don't think he'll make it into
the upcoming musical concourse.
I think it would be better for him
to just play cello as a hobby.
I'm really sorry.
[Twenty years later.]
[R Corporate Marketing Team.]
[Jong Kook gives up being a cellist
to work in the concert marketing team.]
2014...
The First Running Man Music Concourse?
They're actually inviting me?
Ugh, back in the day...
What's this?
The genius pianist who's breaking all
musical records on national stage?
Jung Eun Ji, with the voice of an
angel sings on national stage?
Yoo Jae Suk, touching our hearts
with his angelic voice...
Legendary Gary,
and Oh Yeon Seo, the genius harpist?
Ji Suk Jin, Song Ji Hyo,
and Flautist Ha Ha?
Ugh, seriously!
They were nothing back in the day!
Okay, fine.
I'll go and participate.
I'll go and destroy every
single one of you.
It seems you don't know this,
but I'm the real genius.
Challenge accepted.
[To deter others from participating
in the concourse as an act of revenge...]
[Jong Kook went through
meticulous planning and preparations.]
[Set up for elimination of the other
musicians are now completed.]
You all just wait and see.
You'll be quite surprised.
You will be given ten minutes.
[Four hours ago.]
[Girls' mission- Find the hidden blank
admission slips outside the auditorium.]
[Bring back the slips within ten minutes to
be able to participate in the concourse.]
- Okay, go!
- How can it be all three girls?
- I wonder if they'll be given a mission.
- We'll be back!
Suk Jin, can you put your
pants back on?
[While the girls were busy trying to
find the hidden admission slips...]
[Jung Eun Ji enters the room that
Jong Kook has set up.]
I don't even see anything.
[Discovers the admission slip that Jong Kook
placed in the room the night before.]
This must be it.
[Sits down on the seat unaware
that she's now taped down to the chair.]
[As soon as she's ready to head back to
the auditorium with the admission slip...]
[Her name tag is ripped off just as
Jong Kook had planned!]
[Jung Eun Ji, out!]
Did I just get ousted?
Who did this?
[Jung Eun Ji is no longer able
to participate in the concourse.]
Jung Eun Ji, out!
- Someone's been ousted?
- Eun Ji's been ousted?
[Throws the six men into
a state of confusion.]
[And... one man is left laughing
to himself.]
[It's time to get started.]
[While Ji Hyo was busy deciphering the code
hidden in the seating chart...]
[Jong Kook had been watching
her the entire time.]
[Writing something out with her fingers.]
Does it say 'Kim'?
[The mark on the fourteenth
seat on the chart.]
[When looked upside down with
all the dots connected.]
[Kim]
Why are you so suspicious of me?
You're always so suspicious of me.
It's you, isn't it?
[Ji Hyo, it's time to end this.]
[Doesn't my hand look sticky to you?]
[Starts the elimination with Ji Hyo,
who solved the most number of clues.]
[Pianist, Ji Hyo,
is no longer able to participate.]
[Who should I eliminate next?]
[His next target is Gary, who almost
has his admission slip completed.]
[Notifies him of a crucial clue...]
[Kim]
[Springs out of his seat to
alert the rest of the members.]
[However!]
[Gary's also no longer able to participate.]
[After Kwang Soo discovers the hidden
violin picture in the painting.]
- Why did you run away if you're not it?
- Can you calm Yeon Seo down?
What's this all about?
[Jong Kook's unaware of what's going on
because he was too busy ousting Gary.]
He found that violin himself when
no one else could see it in the painting.
[Violin?]
[A dead stare.]
[Then maybe it's
a smaller version of a cello?]
[The brief moment of uncertainty...]
- Okay, I admit that it's a violin.
- Where did you even see it?
It was definitely a violin.
[Fortunately escapes his moment of
danger thanks to Kwang Soo.]
[Big-nose is now starting to
get suspicious of Jong Kook.]
[And Jong Kook's been listening in
on Big-nose's self-muttering.]
[The moment Big-nose opens the door...]
[Kim Jong Kook]
I knew it!
I knew it was you!
[Ji Suk Jin is eliminated
from participating.]
[Jae Suk gains access to the dressing room
with the lock code that he found.]
[Enters the room that Eun Ji
had been eliminated from.]
[Just then, Jong Kook happens to
discover Jae Suk in the dressing room.]
It's Eun Ji's name tag.
[And also discovers the cello string,
which is a definitive evidence.]
What are you doing?
What are you doing in there?
I saw you going in there.
- What do I do?
- Hurry up and open the door.
- Seriously, what do you want?
- What are you doing in there?
- I'm trying to find a camera.
Let me out of here.
I need to go find a camera.
- Why are you coming in here?
- Why can't I come in here?
- Why are you trying to get out?
- Let's go talk outside.
The painting had Kwang Soo's
violin in it.
Isn't this a violin string?
Come on, let's go take a look.
[Jae Suk walks out with
his trust still in Jong Kook.]
It's a cello string.
[It's a cello string.]
[Yoo Jae Suk-
eliminated from the competition.]
- Ugh, I'm so fired up.
- You're not going anywhere.
Because I'm going to stop every single
one of you from getting up on that stage.
Just like this.
Who else is left?
Ha Dong Hoon.
Lee Kwang Soo.
Kim Ji Hoon.
Oh Yeon Seo.
Only four more left to eliminate.
You guys could never even compare
to the talent that I had.
[Exactly according to Jong Kook's plan,
Ji Hoon's eliminated for false reporting.]
[Ha ha ha... now there are only three.]
[While everyone's thrown into
a state of confusion.]
[His breakout performance.]
[Ha Ha falls right into his trap.]
Is someone in there?
Wait!
[Comes up from behind...]
[Ha Ha is eliminated from participating.]
[Two birds with one stone.
Now the only ones left are...]
Ha Ha, out.
What the heck?
Did they really call someone in?
[The only ones now left are
Lee Kwang Soo and Oh Yeon Seo.]
[And the real culprit, Kim Jong Kook-
Only these last three people.]
Who do I still have left?
Lee Kwang Soo.
Oh Yeon Seo.
It's time for me to make my move.
It's time to start the concourse...
all by myself.
[Time to start the concourse...
on my own.]
Kwang Soo!
Lee Kwang Soo.
[Kwang Soo is his next target!]
[Yeon Seo finds another clue.]
Kwang Soo.
[Desperately calls out Kwang Soo's name.]
[Instead of Kwang Soo...
it'll have to be Yeon Seo.]
What else did you find?
Is it a clue pointing to Kwang Soo?
[It seems that Kwang Soo's still
unaware of the culprit's identity.]
[What is this?]
[Clue- A painting of a starry evening.]
[What could this mean?]
Are you sure that you're
not the culprit?
Why do you think that I'm
the culprit?
I don't think Kwang Soo's the culprit
because he would just be too obvious.
- Jong Kook, you don't have to get up.
- Why not?
- Because you scare me.
- Why?
- Did you feel scared of Kwang Soo, too?
- Kwang Soo?
Yes, I guess so.
But Kwang Soo kept avoiding me.
[Flips over the picture frame.]
What's this?
Musical bars?
Yes, that's what this is.
This is sheet music.
Yeon Seo, please stop doing that.
You're starting to offend me.
- Why are you doing this, Jong Kook?
- What are you doing?
- This won't do.
- Please don't come any closer.
[No, this won't do.]
- Seriously, Jong Kook!
- Why are you avoiding me?
- Why are you avoiding me like this?
- You know I can't beat you physically!
- Are you sure that it's me?
- Yes.
- Why?
- Call it female intuition.
- There's no such a thing.
- Why do you keep coming closer?
[What's the correlation between the painting
and the sheet music on the back?]
Wasn't this sheet placed in the back for
me to put it up against the painting?
Could these stars mean something?
[Could these stars represent musical notes?]
I should see if I can play this.
Let me see that.
This letter...
It stands for 'Jong'.
['Jong' of Kim Jong Kook.]
- Is this supposed to be a thriller?
- 'Jong' of Kim Jong Kook.
- This episode?
- Is this supposed to be a thriller?
- It's part thriller, and part comedy.
No!
- Sorry, but you know way too much.
- Seriously!
[Oh Yeon Seo is eliminated.]
Kwang Soo!
Lee Kwang Soo.
[I just need to eliminate you,
and this will all be over.]
[Kwang Soo attempts to play the piano
with the clue that he's discovered.]
[This familiar strand of melody...]
Kwang Soo!
The hero from the backwoods...
Whose name is that of a tiger.
Lee Kwang Soo!
[The culprit is none other than
Jong Kook, the Tiger!]
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo.
[Jong Kook passes by where Kwang Soo is,
and Kwang Soo successfully escapes.]
[It's now a battle against the clock.]
[Will Kwang Soo make the report first...]
[Or will Jong Kook capture
Kwang Soo first?]
[Finally discovers the telephone!]
[Please answer the phone!]
Lee Kwang Soo.
[Hurry!]
Kwang Soo!
[Which of the two... was faster?]
[The Symphony Race-
Who will be the star of the concourse?]
[Culprit, Kim Jong Kook,
has been captured!]
I'm so angry.
- Did Kwang Soo report you in?
- Did he find the sheet music?
[What is Kwang Soo doing
up on stage?]
[The curtain opens up.]
[And the genius violinist is seen
standing on stage.]
[Posed as if he's standing
on top of the world.]
[Ten minutes ago.]
The culprit is Kim Jong Kook!
[By the split of a hair-
Even though Jong Kook tried...]
[The report is made,
and Running Task Force moves in.]
He's the culprit!
This man is the culprit!
[Jong Kook's moment on stage
will have to wait until next time.]
[Culprit, Kim Jong Kook, is eliminated.]
[Symphony Race-
The ultimate winner is Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Can't believe that
Kwang Soo actually did it.]
I want to sincerely thank all of you for
coming to my very first concourse.
- Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
- Thank you, Suk Jin.
Ugh, I'm so angry!
- My fellow genius musicians!
- Is this the sheet music?
- Jong Kook, the spy.
- I made a huge mistake.
I was really scared when you
came at me earlier.
- Yeon Seo's going to have nightmares.
- So we were all after a solo concert?
Lee Kwang Soo is the only person who
will ultimately hold his own concert.
[Symphony Race-
Violinist, Lee Kwang Soo, wins!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Aboard the train in
the midst of autumn leaves...]
[The lovely beauty, Han Ye Seul, is here.]
[Fall outing of all the hottest stars.]
I'm seriously going to lose it.
What am I to do?
[Actor special-
Introduction to the variety world.]
[Goodbye to their pristine image,
and hello to destruction of status.]
[It'll all be ruined for good.]
I'm never going to run away again.
[On next week's Running Man-
The Return of the Queen.]