Subtitles by DramaFever
[File Number: 660210]
[File Name: Running Man
Mafia Investigation Record]
[Running Man Mafia File]
[14 people who are not connected
to each other...]
[When they arrived at the
southernmost point of Korea...]
[This case began.]
While you are eating...
[The morning after they got together]
We will meet with each of you in private
to give your mission.
Each one of you will get called during this
meal to receive your mission.
[No one had any idea how this humble beginning
would lead up to a tremendous ending.]
[Today, you're either a civilian or
part of the Mafia.]
Today, you are either...
Mafia! / Civilian!
[Mission Notification Complete]
The end.
Staying calm, without panic.
The end!
[The game begins!]
Today's race is the Mafia game.
Mafia vs. Civilian!
Your goal is to identify and capture
the members of the Mafia.
After every mission, you shall decide on
the two most suspicious characters...
and remove them from the game.
If any member of the Mafia survives until
the end, it's a victory for the Mafia.
[Suspect Number One]
[Ryu Seung Soo]
[The main character of the
legendary water bottle fraud incident]
[Gwangju Bus Terminal,
several weeks ago.]
It went in pretty deep!
Are you okay?
It went in this much!
He's fine!
- One minute and 30 seconds.
- Excellent!
Is he going to do the whole thing
by himself?
Good heavens!
You should've performed this well before!
Three, two, one...
Success!
[Seung Soo lasted two minutes
on his own.]
I think he needs to get his
internal organs checked out!
[As everyone was impressed by
his perseverance...]
I knew something was weird!
He has this!
[Everyone was astonished by
the secret of his butt.]
This guy...
[The secret was...]
[a water bottle.]
[The very first incident of water bottle fraud
in the history of Running Man.]
No one had any idea!
[Five minutes before the game]
[Meticulous planning!]
[Bold execution!]
I don't think this guy can do it!
Fighting!
[Completed by his perfect acting!]
[Mr. Ryu the Bluff,
the perfect candidate!]
You have 10 minutes to discuss and
pick the two most suspicious characters.
[He is the perfect suspect!]
If you give it another thought,
you'll know that I'm not in the Mafia.
- Why?
- Your natural first choice would be me.
- That's not it!
- It's because of your attitude.
- How would you deal with this later?
- What?
What if I was a civilian all along?
We'll say sorry and call it a day.
[In a jungle of doubts,
you can't trust anyone.]
Betrayal is second nature to
these people.
They aren't the kind of people
who would feel bad about that!
- But the producer...
- Just stop!
Just stop because anything you say
will impact you negatively!
[Suspect Number Two]
[Yoo Jae Suk]
I choose Ryu Seung Soo.
[He cornered Seung Soo from
the very beginning.]
[Ryu Seung Soo!]
I think we have one guy for sure.
Ryu Seung Soo!
We already have one of the
Mafia members!
That would be Ryu Seung Soo!
I think it might be Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is...
- Hey, I'm a real civilian!
- I think he's manipulating Seung Soo...
- I'm a real civilian!
You have to be careful of the people
who corner others.
I think it might be Jae Suk.
[If you think about it, this man...]
[This man is the legendary spy,
Yoo-ames Bond.]
[He successfully deceived the quick-witted
members of Running Man so many times before.]
- How can you do this to me?
- Goodbye!
[Will the Master of Psychological Warfare
strike again today?]
- Ms. Lee Sang Hwa.
- That's good!
She must be a member of the
Mafia in my opinion.
I think we might be half civilian,
half Mafia today.
I try my best in everything I do.
Mafia! Mafia!
[The Empress of Ice Skating,
Lee Sang Hwa!]
[The best skater in the world
who doesn't know defeat!]
[A cold closer who never loses her
temper in any situation!]
[Running Man was no exception to
the competitive spirit of the Empress.]
You shall never fall!
Never!
[During the crab mission of which the
prize was to be exempt from the selection...]
[She was especially enthusiastic.]
[Equipped with cold logic and
burning passion...]
[She is impossible to read.]
It must be Sang Hwa!
I think there would be at least one Mafia
among us women.
How does that mean that it's me?
[Her strong passion only fuels
people's doubts.]
[Suspect Number Three]
[Lee Sang Hwa]
I think Sang Hwa is a member of
the Mafia.
I think it's you, Ji Hyo.
You're cornering me because
you're in the Mafia yourself.
Ji Hyo just nodded!
[Did she just reveal herself half-consciously?]
[Well, if we think about it...]
[Lying isn't her strong suit.]
Mission Number Six.
Please eat this spicy dish.
- It came! It came!
- It came early for Ji Hyo.
Here, drink some water, Ji Hyo.
What is she doing?
Look at her throwing tantrums!
[When she got the same mission again...]
Fire!
[She kicked it away!]
[She often reveals her thoughts
involuntarily...]
[Has she done it again?]
[Suspect Number Four]
[Song Ji Hyo]
People are always suspicious of the quiet ones!
[And last but not least, someone we can't forget.]
I think it's you, Kwang Soo!
[The Icon of Betrayal, Lee Kwang Soo!]
Are the members of the Mafia
aware of each other?
- You probably know the best.
- Yes, you probably know!
This is driving me crazy!
It's suffocating!
[And this man...]
[He called out on Ha Ha with
gravitas...]
You are the members of the Mafia!
[He managed to put Ha Ha on
the final trial.]
Ha Ha, please stand up and turn around.
[Civilian]
[He was a civilian!]
[But...]
[Is he smiling at the removal
of a civilian?]
You are...
a member of the Mafia today.
[Kim Min Jong, the Second Mafia!]
You'll be exempt from the selection
if you manage to place in this mission.
I just caught three!
[He placed first after destroying
the opponents in the Crab Race!]
- I guess you're safe this time.
- I assume so.
- Can we get out of here?
- Okay, fine.
Now I must act like I get nauseous
until the end!
Look at Min Jong.
He's knocked out!
Does he usually get nauseous
that easily?
Are you okay, Min Jong?
[Perfect acting based on his
26 years of experience.]
I seriously thought Min Jong
might be a Mafia...
- I don't think he's it.
- He didn't really want to win the first place.
He didn't want to fish from the
very beginning.
[Can he continue his success
until the end?]
[Mafia vs. Civilians]
We have one minute.
Before this mission,
we all thought Dong Joon might be it.
It's not me, I promise!
So we don't have an unanimous consent,
right? Then we will vote individually.
- Who thinks it's Sang Hwa?
- Really?
- Who? Sang Hwa?
[Three votes for Sang Hwa]
Next, for Dong Joon!
You'll regret this!
[Four votes for Dong Joon]
Next, for Jae Suk!
[Four votes for Jae Suk]
I'm really a civilian!
For Ryu Seung Soo...
- The Mafia is manipulating the votes!
[One vote for Seung Soo]
He's like a weed that won't die!
- I'm really not it.
- I'm not it either!
Who has four votes?
[Jae Suk and Dong Joon are picked
after the second mission.]
Is anyone changing their mind?
If not...
[Excellent! My plan worked!]
Dong Joon is the member of the Mafia!
You really made a mistake with me!
Well, let's see first!
[Is he really a member of the Mafia?]
[Dong Joon was a civilian!]
I said I'm not it!
I never lie!
You should've been more assertive!
I didn't think he would be it!
Just watch and learn.
The Mafia is among the people
who voted for me and Dong Joon.
Didn't Dong Joon vote for Jae Suk?
I voted for Dong Joon...
- Dong Joon voted for you too!
[Do we have a new couple?]
One of them must be it!
Jae Suk is the member of the Mafia!
It must be Jae Suk.
He's a Mafia.
Dong Joon, it wasn't me!
- I think he might be it.
- He must be!
- Also Gary!
- I'm really not it!
One, two, three!
[Is Jae Suk, who was usually chatty today,
a member of the Mafia?]
I will now give you your identity.
You are...
[He was also a civilian!]
- See? I told you!
- Was he really a civilian?
Look, the civilians must win!
No!
Take a good look at these
three people!
You must remember these three,
along with Gary!
[It's a lucky removal for Min Jong.]
- Can it be you, Jung Nan?
- Hey!
I said it's Sang Hwa!
[You can't trust anyone now!]
Be careful of Jong Kook!
You can rip my tag if you're doubtful.
I don't care.
Gentlemen, please pick up the fish
and go help prepare the meal.
Please don't forget to bring
the chairs too.
I didn't do anything productive today.
Why did people
become suspicious of me?
[Then who are my fellow members
of the Mafia?]
- See you later, then.
[Two innocent civilians are removed.]
- I'm sorry, Dong Joon!
- It's fine.
[Bitterness...]
- How could this happen?
- I'm sorry, Dong Joon.
I'm also sorry for voting for you.
[Two civilians, Kim Dong Joon and Yoo Jae Suk
have been removed.]
Now, we have two more missions left.
And you have four chances to
remove the Mafia members.
You don't know how many members of
the Mafia we have, right?
I'll tell you how many members of
the Mafia are still in the game.
This will make our lives easier!
Currently, the number of
surviving members of the Mafia is...
three.
If any member of the Mafia survives
until the end, the victory goes to the Mafia.
Please make your way to our
next mission.
We can do this!
I'm sorry, but Seung Soo is 100% Mafia!
[Will the civilians be able to remove
the Mafia?]
[Three Mafia Members vs. Seven Civilians]
Where are these latecomers?
I know they've been removed!
Where are they?
My fellow Mafia members
should've had more discretion.
But everyone was after their
own survival!
How can they win without an ace like me?
You are...
not an ace!
This is called the Gargamel Curry.
We charge 25,000 Won per plate.
We put everything that's good for
your body into this.
- Are carrots being cooked?
- Yes, sir.
Why are you working so hard?
The latecomers will do all the work.
Are you sure this is how to cook it?
This is to remove the bad smell of
meat and fish.
We have already exchanged
our numbers and everything.
He really is different from Jung Woo Sung!
I really like you more!
- Why do I feel like I'm getting back-stabbed?
- Nonsense!
You're the perfect match for me!
Hey, after seeing you up close...
I think you look like that guy from that movie.
Slumdog... Something.
- Do you know what you're talking about?
- Millionaire!
You look like that guy from
Slumdog Millionaire!
Can I call you Hassan from now on?
Brother Hassan!
I like it!
Hold still, Hassan.
This is usually when people back out.
But he's still going!
This is warm.
[Brother Hassan is extremely positive.]
You look like a chef.
- From now on...
- That's a good look for you!
We are cooking the Indian curry.
When did you come to Korea?
I came to Korea 15 years ago.
I named myself Man Suk
so I can be rich!
He's really trying hard!
[The Gargamel Curry is also boiling!]
[The other members are
heading to their next mission.]
Seung Soo has given up.
He's sleeping.
He has given up on everything.
He looks too comfortable as a
member of the Mafia.
- You look very tired.
- Yes, I'm so tired.
I feel like I'm really a member of the Mafia
because people keep telling me that!
[Confusion in his identity]
[Or is this his highly calculated acting?]
Have we decided that Min Jong
isn't part of the Mafia?
I don't think he is.
[People shouldn't focus on me...]
I looked at her while she was fishing.
She was especially focused!
- I just wanted to try it!
- I don't think that's it!
I think she was trying too hard.
I just want to take a break.
Seriously.
[Please don't pay attention to me...]
I just want to rest.
That's my honest answer.
If you are a member of the Mafia,
you're really good at this game.
[I've been acting for 26 years...]
[Something is weird...]
[Arriving at the site of the third mission]
[Shopping bags inside of a snack stand?]
- Do you want us to go grocery shopping?
- Please close the door.
Only the top two people will be
exempt from the selection.
As you can see, we are in a market.
The mission is to complete a round of
the market as soon as possible.
I'll read out some Korean initials, and it's
your job to bring back matching items.
If someone brings back the same
item as someone else...
the person who came later must go back
and get another item of the same initial.
Please remember that this is an
individual race.
After this round, the members of the Mafia
will get to know each other's identities.
[I finally get to know my fellow
Mafia members!]
It might end up harming the Mafia.
It might put an extra burden on them.
[Everyone is a contender so far.]
The initials of the first round have
two letters.
One moment, please.
We can't discuss what the item is even though
we might have an idea after hearing the initials.
[What?]
- Of course!
- Isn't that obvious?
- Why would we talk about it?
- What if it just comes out?
Do you think he's capable of being
in the Mafia? He's not!
- He might be acting.
- He's just like you, Suk Jin!
[But what if this clumsiness is a highly
calculated act?]
The initials for the first round are...
G and J.
Something like "Gwajah." (Snack)
Why would you tell us that?
Start!
Where is the nearest grocery store?
I have an idea! An idea!
Vegetable store!
[Sang Hwa has discovered a
grocery store!]
[Along with Kkuk!]
Do you have Ga Ji? (Eggplant)
We don't have that here.
- How about Gam Ja? (Potato)
- Yes, we have it.
Where are the potatoes?
What are you doing?
Are you cutting the line?
No, I'm not.
I'm just going to get one.
How much is this?
She's so fast!
She's indeed a speed skater.
- Quickly, quickly!
[I'm an Olympic gold medalist]
[Jung Nan is also rushing to an item.]
Gook Ja! (Ladle)
Gyeo Ja... (Mustard)
[Min Jong is still playing his
sick character.]
[Waltzing into the
nearest convenience store]
[Min Jong has found a suitable item!]
- How much is it?
- 3,500 Won, please.
[Did he manage to buy an item
that's different from others?]
[Joo Hwan is running...]
[to a restaurant?]
- Do you have Gam Ja? (Potato)
- Yes, we do. Why?
- Can I buy one off of you?
- Just one?
- You look better in person!
- Thank you.
I'm sorry but I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Thank you!
[But Sang Hwa already has a potato!]
[Who will get there first?]
[Joo Hwan is the first one!]
[Joo Hwan passes the first round
with a potato!]
[Min Jong the Mafia is the second.]
- Potato?
- Yes.
[Gan Jang! (Soy sauce)
Min Jong passes!]
[The first hurdle is done.]
[Sang Hwa is next.]
[That's...]
[That's a potato!]
We already have a potato!
[Damn it!]
Where are you going?
[Jung Nan passes with a ladle!]
[Kwang Soo passes with mustard!]
[Big-nosed Brother
takes fifth place with eggplant.]
[A variety of G-Js...]
[The cutoff for the first round is seven.
Two more competitors...]
- What did you buy?
- Soy sauce...
[Please shop again!]
Where is it?
Where is the place?
Awesome!
- What did you buy?
- Let me see.
If another competitor comes in now,
you're losing your slot!
What is it?
- We already have potatoes!
[Huh?]
- Please shop again!
[Despair]
I thought he brought something
very unique!
He really isn't capable of being a Mafia!
[Clumsy]
- You're back.
[What did Kkuk get this time?]
Let us see!
Gang Jeong! (Rice Crispies)
[Kkuk passes!]
[Only one slot left for the first round.]
[Seung Soo's quick comeback.]
Awesome!
What are you doing?
We have two bottles of soy sauce already!
[Overflowing of soy sauce]
- Didn't you see it just before?
[You saw it 30 seconds ago...]
Are you a goldfish?
We already have two bottles
of soy sauce!
[Seung Soo's sweat is getting saltier
than soy sauce.]
See? He's so obvious.
He's been pretty obvious for a while.
[Min Jong trying to corner Seung Soo.]
[Hmm... This guy...]
[And this guy...
Is he a manipulative Mafia?]
[Or just clumsy?]
[Blank Ji returns]
Gang Jeong! (Rice Crispies)
Go, hurry.
Get out of here.
We have it here.
I have chicken rice crispies!
They're different!
- Don't you know this?
- That's chicken!
This is rice snack.
This is chicken!
[Can Ji Hyo be my fellow Mafia?]
Chicken rice crispies don't qualify.
Here is Gae Jang (Seasoned Crabs).
[Gary passes!]
One bottle of seasoned crabs, please.
Wow, you really have it!
Good Job!
[No way...]
- This is amazing.
- Where did you manage to buy it?
- What did you buy?
- Did you actually buy something this time?
These three have been removed for this round.
Please stay here.
We'll begin the next round of shopping.
[I'm almost there!]
I ran here thinking that I'd be the first place,
but this world isn't an easy place to live in.
We have five slots for this round.
The initials are S and G.
Start!
[What can be S and G?]
Su Geon! (Towel)
Sa Gwa! (Apple)
[Tiger at full speed]
He's so fast!
Do you have a towel, ma'am?
How much is it?
[Kkuk has found Saeng Gang!] (Ginger)
[Jung Nan buys the apples.] (Sa Gwa)
We have different items.
How much?
- Where is my 1,000 Won bill?
- Thank you!
Run faster!
Jong Kook is coming!
Jong Kook!
Don't go!
[Kwang Soo and Jong Kook
arrive at the same time.]
- Towel!
- Ginger!
[Kwang Soo takes first place with towel!]
[Kkuk takes second with ginger!]
[Big-nosed Brother is third?]
- Apple juice!
- What?
[That's juice, not apple!]
Why doesn't that work?
I was going to buy a towel,
but he beat me to it.
Can I put it down?
Do you have this?
- Apples!
[Jung Nan passes!]
Suk Jin brought apple juice.
I think he might be buying apples right now.
Joo Hwan is here.
Damn it!
He has a towel!
Si Gye! (Clock)
I need a clock!
- So Geum! (Salt)
[Big-nosed Brother passes on the second try!]
We only have one slot left.
[Joo Hwan is running everywhere today.
- A clock!
[He managed to get a clock!]
You didn't buy this.
You just took this off a wall!
- Did you not buy this?
- I bought it!
- How much did you pay for it?
- 5,000 Won.
- We have a clock.
- What?
He bought a clock?
Wait a minute.
I think he borrowed it.
[A moment ago]
Do you have a clock?
- Do you have any small clocks?
[Convenience stores don't sell clocks.]
- Should I take this off?
- How much is it?
- I can just lend it to you.
- I must pay.
- It's fine, just borrow it.
- No, I must pay.
- Just give me 5,000 Won.
- Okay.
I bought this fair and square!
He said it was on sale as a used item.
He plays so dirty!
[He's learned so much from Giraffe already...]
- I paid 5,000 Won!
[The clock passes!]
[Can this desperate man be Mafia?]
- Welcome!
[Meanwhile, at the camping site...]
Two innocent civilians have arrived.
Did you get removed?
Yes. Kim Jong Kook manipulated me.
Halt!
Come to attention!
I'll beat you up.
[Who do you think I am?]
Obey my orders!
That's my concept for the day!
Get out of here!
This is mine!
[The upperclassmen are losing
to the lowerclassmen]
- This is my spot!
- Get out of there!
I've dedicated my whole day here,
wandering around!
Why were you wandering around?
Why did it have to be you?
Hey!
Keep working while I'm asking you nicely.
Keep cooking the rice while I'm
asking you nicely.
[This lowerclassman is way too tough...]
- This is not a joke.
- What are we doing?
One of you will be our upperclassman,
and the other our underclassman.
We'll play a game to decide that.
Come with me.
Let's go eat at a restaurant outside.
Please have some desire to play!
There is none!
[The underclassmen are not cooperating.]
Hurry up, we don't have much time.
Everyone must be hungry,
and they are on edge from the race.
What are you cooking anyway?
Rice with curry?
- Yes.
- Then get a move on!
- What if we say no?
- Keep cutting the vegetables!
- But we don't have the rice.
- Why?
- We'll eat naan.
[The Indian bread instead of rice.]
- It's the Indian curry after all.
- So you want to dip it?
- This is just regular sandwich bread!
- No, it's naan!
[Only the makeshift mark]
Everyone's been out in the cold for a while.
They probably want something like a warm soup.
Everyone is on edge.
- Is everyone angry?
- Yes, we must cook the fish soup.
Let's go wash the potatoes.
We'll be back soon.
Everything went against our plan.
Why did it have to be Jae Suk?
[The Gargamel Curry continues to boil]
- I think this feels like Gargamel now!
- Yes, it does!
Jae Suk...
Why did it have to be Jae Suk?
It would've been so much easier
if someone like Kwang Soo came.
That Ha Ha....
The water is freezing!
I guess we should wash the tomatoes too.
Hey, our pride depends on this.
- I'll have them wash these!
- Have them wash everything!
- This is our pride!
- We'll be their bosses!
But do you think he'll be angry
if we include scallions?
It'll be a challenge.
Excuse me, Dong Joon!
What's up?
Can you come over?
Come over here.
- Hey, Jae Suk...
- We only need you!
We only need you, Dong Joon!
Where are you going, Dong Joon?
- Just you, Dong Joon!
- It's okay, Jae Suk!
- Would you mind washing these too?
- Not at all.
[Dumping work on nice Dong Joon.]
Just remember this.
You're higher than Jae Suk.
- Is that so?
- Of course.
Go and tell him to do this.
- Me?
- Yes. You tell him.
- I'll be back.
- Alright.
You're higher than Jae Suk!
Jae Suk!
Ha Ha told me to tell you...
that you should wash all these.
Okay!
[Okay?]
Ha Dong Hoon!
- Ha Dong Hoon!
- Yes, sir!
Come here!
Come here now!
- I'm working now!
- Come here!
- I'm really working!
- Come here now!
- Why? I'm working!
- Wash these.
- Wash what?
- I have work to do up there.
- Just come wash them.
Go inside and wash them.
- I'll wash them!
- Hurry up!
- I was working up there before!
- Just wash them! I'll be back.
[I won't forget this...]
[Min Jong and Gary didn't pass
the second round...]
[The third pair of initials are O and Y.]
What do you have that has
the letters O and Y?
Oh Yi! (Cucumber)
Do you have a cucumber! I'll buy one.
How much is this cucumber?
[He must be first or second in this round
to be exempt from the selection.]
I don't have much time, ma'am!
Please!
[Kkuk rushes to the grocery store.]
Do you have a cucumber?
[He is looking for the same thing
as Kwang Soo!]
Is there something else with O and Y?
I don't think this will work.
What else has O and Y?
Oo Yoo is too easy, right? (Milk)
[Jung Nan is the first one!]
[She takes first place with milk!]
You're trying so hard, Jung Nan!
[Is she trying to avoid the selection
because she's a Mafia?]
[Only one slot left for the selection
exemption!]
I'll lose this if they already have this.
[Could it be Big-nosed Brother?]
I'll be back.
[He also got milk!]
[More shopping for him!]
[Who will be exempt from the selection?]
[Fully charged tiger]
What is this?
[Tiger passes Giraffe!]
[Kkuk passes with cucumber by a second!]
It's over!
- Who bought the milk?
- I did.
[Jung Nan gets the exemption
twice in a row!]
We have two survivors.
Jung Nan and Jong Kook will be exempt
from this selection.
Everyone has ten minutes to discuss.
[I can't be picked here...]
In my opinion, it must be Min Jong.
[Surprise]
I told this to Kwang Soo already.
He's been telling us that he doesn't feel very
well because he got nausea from the sea.
But he was completely fine on the bus ride
here even though it was pretty bumpy.
- Are you okay?
[Inside of the bus before the market]
I think the abalone that I had for lunch
is giving me a stomachache.
- Is it indigestion?
- Do you want to take medicine?
- I just want to take a break. Really.
- You do seem like you need it.
[While Min Jong was tricking everyone
to believe him...]
[Joo Hwan was staring at Min Jong.]
[He's a little suspicious.]
[Did Joo Hwan realize something?]
[He's perfectly fine on this bumpy road.]
[Joo Hwan didn't miss the clue, while
everyone was getting duped by Min Jong.]
[Joo Hwan the Sherlock!]
But he was completely fine on the bus ride
here even though it was pretty bumpy.
[Caught by surprise]
He looks angry!
It's just a game, Min Jong!
No, it's a feasible theory.
So he decided to act like he's sick
after getting the motion sickness...
Just think about...
and stop talking nonsense...
[Min Jong's disguise is coming off quickly.]
I thought it would be Jung Nan,
but she's exempt from this selection.
I think Seung Soo was pretty obvious
with his slapstick comedy before.
You can't do this to me.
I think he definitely saw the soy sauce,
but he brought one again to look stupid.
- I can tell from his face.
- I think it might be one of the women.
I think it must be one of the women,
and one of the original members.
And Ji Hyo fits the bill.
So are you saying that if it's not me,
one of these two women must be it?
- It doesn't have to be.
- It doesn't, but think about it.
I'm really not it.
- Hey Sang Hwa, are you it?
- I really am not.
Let's go with Ji Hyo for now.
Gary is trying to protect Sang Hwa.
- I'm really not it.
- Gary has been protecting Sang Hwa for a while.
[Blank Ji thinks it could be Gary.]
- Me?
- Think about it. It could be him.
She can immediately tell when I lie.
There is no one else in this world
who's better at detecting my lies than Ji Hyo.
Better than my own mother!
But if she is blaming me now,
that means she is very desperate!
The fact that she's questioning me now means
she is trying to deflect this!
I don't think it's Gary.
I told you this. I think there is one
or two Mafia members among us women.
But I'm not it.
So it means that it's either one of them.
Why are you being so desperate?
I'm so frustrated!
Just think about it...
Now I know why girls always cried
every time we played this game back in school.
That's right.
Someone always ended up crying.
I lost some friends forever
while playing this game.
There were many times when my friends
flipped the tables while playing.
I think we are most suspicious of Ji Hyo.
Let's pick her.
Fine. But you'll regret it big time
if I turn out to be a civilian.
Can we not play games like this?
Wait a minute.
Shouldn't we bring Seung Soo with her?
I've been suspicious of him since
the beginning.
He's like a grey hair.
You can pluck it anytime.
[Always ready to be plucked.]
But it might be better to pluck it early.
I think the most people talked about Min Jong
and Ji Hyo. Can we go with those two?
Ji Hyo really might not be it.
I think I really know who it is.
- Who?
- I think I know, but I can't speak.
[Excuse me, but we're making a TV show...]
[Would you prefer to keep it as your
personal memory?]
Everyone here is trapped.
Suk Jin is leading every discussion right now.
I just talk a lot!
[Could it be the leader of discussions, Suk Jin?]
- Are you a member of the Mafia?
- Me?
- Are you?
- No.
- What are you doing?
I think Seung Soo has become slightly annoying...
Maybe we can pluck him and Ji Hyo out.
I think Suk Jin is acting right now!
Why are you doing this to me
all of a sudden?
What's wrong with you?
[Who can I corner so I can survive?]
- You're it, Suk Jin. Aren't you?
- You know me well! I'm not it!
Why are you cornering me?
Ji Hyo is being weird!
[Will they find a Mafia?]
- 10 seconds!
[Or will they remove a civilian?]
Please come clean!
I don't think these two are it.
I pick Suk Jin and Joo Hwan.
Five, four, three, two, one...
[Could it be Suk Jin with his awkward face?]
[Or Ji Hyo,
an expert of psychological warfare?]
[Will Min Jong the Mafia get away this time?]
[Discussion Ends]
If you think Kwang Soo is in the Mafia,
please raise your hand.
[Kwang Soo gets zero votes.]
This really feels good.
I love you all.
Don't force me to raise my hand
right now.
Please raise your hand if you think
Joo Hwan is a Mafia.
- Why all of a sudden?
[Joo Hwan gets one vote]
[Criticisms abound]
Please raise your hand
if you think Suk Jin is a Mafia.
[Suk Jin gets one vote]
- She is driving me crazy!
Please raise your hand
if you think Min Jong is a Mafia.
[Nervous]
[Will he be able to survive this crisis?]
[Min Jong gets four votes]
[Is this really the end?]
Please raise your hand
if you think Seung Soo is a Mafia.
[Seung Soo gets two votes]
They're smart. Very smart.
[Zero votes for Sang Hwa and Gary.]
Please raise your hand
if you think Ji Hyo is a Mafia.
She has two votes?
We have a tie then!
We will have a second round of voting.
But let's confirm that Min Jong has
been chosen first.
Who are tied?
We will now vote one more time
between these two.
They're both very strong candidates!
Listen to me rationally.
Please raise your hand
if you think Seung Soo is a Mafia.
[Seung Soo gets two votes.
That means Ji Hyo gets six.]
Fine. Just remember that it's between
those two. Think carefully!
Ji Hyo, if you're a civilian,
think of this as a sacrifice for all civilians.
I'm dying to find out!
[The moment of truth]
[Now that it has come down to this,
Ji Hyo can't be a Mafia member...]
[Starting with Blank Ji]
You are...
[Has Blank Ji, who caught many members by
surprise before, done it again?]
You are...
[Blank Ji was a civilian!]
You are a civilian today.
I said I'm not it!
It's one of those two!
We lost!
It's over!
Why did you start blaming them?
Am I a Mafia?
Now he is confused about his
own identity!
Please remove the tag at three.
[Time to check Min Jong.]
- One...
- It's Suk Jin!
Two...
Three!
[Mafia]
[Ta-da!]
[Min Jong the Mafia has been arrested!]
[I almost made it...]
[Shock and awe]
A shiver went down my spine!
You are a member of the Mafia today.
He's it!
- He was right!
[Sherlock Joo Hwan caught his acting!]
He's not even sick!
He was just acting!
I think it should've been these two!
So you pretended to be sick?
Yes.
We thought you were really sick!
Did Jong Kook catch me?
No, Joo Hwan did.
You were sick from motion sickness earlier,
but you were fine on the bumpy bus ride here.
I should've opened the window
and acted more.
Great job, Joo Hwan!
It's been fun.
[Min Jong the Mafia and Blank Ji are removed
after the third mission!]
Now I'm scared of people.
Really scared.
[Two members of the Mafia vs. Six civilians]
There's no one here, right?
[Instant coffee?!]
This is the main sauce.
[Instant coffee is the secret ingredient of
the Gargamel Curry?]
[One more!]
[Adding three packs of instant coffee.]
You'll soon be speechless
when you taste this mindblowing curry.
[Yes, we're speechless...]
People can't find out that I put these in.
[Quickly getting rid of the evidence.]
It's not really dissolving.
This will be my first attempt at this.
[No! Strawberry Jam!]
My first attempt...
In Korea, we must do things in three.
- Did you talk to Ha Ha about this?
- No, he has no idea.
It looks delicious, doesn't it?
[The chef himself is very satisfied.]
I don't know if they will go well together,
but I'm going to put these abalones in.
We should eat these fried eggs now!
[Jae Suk and Dong Joon fried 30 eggs
in a heartbeat!]
- You are great.
- Of course.
[Confident]
We should eat these now.
- All of you must keep moving.
- Yes, sir. We are.
I thought you said you're the boss?
I'm just letting him have his moment.
Otherwise it'll never end.
You're not just letting me have my moment,
are you?
[He has great hearing.]
I don't know who they are,
but the Mafia is doing very well.
- I think they are doing great.
- Jong Kook must be working hard.
I said Jong Kook is a Mafia!
- Could it be Seung Soo and Sang Hwa?
I can't trust anyone anymore.
- I don't think Gary is it.
- Because I'm not.
He's being very natural right now.
We have two members of the Mafia
in here right now.
And now they are aware of each
other's identity.
It must be hard for them to not laugh
when they look at each other.
I don't think I can perform
regular social functions after this.
I can't trust people anymore!
[Who are the two members of the
Mafia among them?]
But Seung Soo, you're being so natural.
I don't think it's you.
His acting is getting better after
each mission!
It was so awkward in the beginning!
- I think Suk Jin is being strange right now.
- I agree.
[Now Big Nosed Brother is under attack!]
Suk Jin, look straight in my eye.
I'm really not it.
Suk Jin, if you're a Mafia,
then you have played me pretty badly!
I saw it.
What should I do?
[Huh? You saw what?]
I saw the hidden claw.
- I saw it finally.
[His bluffing has gotten better along with his acting.]
I thought it was Jung Nan,
but she's not it.
- She's not capable of detailed acting.
- What kind of detailed acting?
After saying that you've played her if you're
a Mafia, she made that hand gesture.
That hand movement was so
natural and detailed.
- Really?
- Yes!
I promise you, it was all natural.
I can tell that such a natural gesture
can't be acted out.
- But she is a good actor.
- Now we must examine everyone here carefully.
She is a great actor, but such natural
movement can't be acted out.
I saw it. But Suk Jin!
I also saw that your eyes, albeit very slightly,
moved when Jung Nan said that.
- What should I do?
- What's wrong with you?
If I get removed, you guys lose!
This is driving me nuts!
You're a true professional, Suk Jin.
[Seung Soo's bluffing shines when he
makes inferences.]
If Seung Soo is a Mafia, I swear
that I'll never see anyone ever again.
I'll never see anyone ever again!
I'll just go into a mountain and become a hermit.
So would you be surprised more if I'm a Mafia?
Or if I'm a civilian?
- It'd be a surprise either way.
- Right?
This is frustrating.
[We are continuing to the next mission,
full of doubts.]
[They have arrived at the last mission site:
a cabbage farm.]
I wear these quite often!
[The mission begins with work pants
and boots.]
If Seung Soo turns out to be Mafia,
my life would lose its purpose altogether.
If Seung Soo is Mafia,
there is no reason for me to continue living!
I'll give you hope.
I'm really not it.
Why are they sticking together?
That's strange.
Hey! They're sticking together!
[It's time to doubt Suk Jin and Sang Hwa.]
Gary, thanks for that valuable piece
of information!
It must be Jong Kook and Joo Hwan.
They exchanged some kind of signal.
They just looked at each other
and smiled!
- Seung Soo, you're not it, right?
- I really am not.
- Then why did you pretend like you were Mafia?
- What did I do?
- When cornered, people's behaviors change.
- Pretended to be Mafia?
Please stand right here.
Did you find every member of the Mafia?
- Yes, almost!
- 80% there!
I saw everything!
But we have to pick two...
This would be your last chance to pick
those two. The last mission.
It's called
"The Man from the Cabbage Farm"
You'll see cabbages growing in
this field right now.
First, men need to pick five cabbages per person,
and women need to pick three per person.
Second, put your cabbages in those
cartwheels.
Then push your cartwheels to the
finish line right here.
The person who crosses
the line first wins.
- It's quite simple.
- Yes, it's simple.
We'll pick first place from the first round,
then have another round to pick second place.
The first and second place holders will be
exempt from the selection process.
This means that we must stop
the most suspicious character from winning.
That's correct.
It'd be important for the civilians to help
the two least suspicious characters to win.
Then let's have a cheer for the civilians!
Cheers for the civilians!
[Every single one joined in.]
- Get out of here!
- Why?
- This doesn't make sense.
- This is driving me nuts!
So whoever is trying too hard
is a suspicious character.
In both cases of trying too hard to win,
and trying too hard to lose.
I hereby declare that I'll take it easy on
this one! You heard me!
It's better to have someone win.
I'll just take the first place.
What's wrong with you, Sang Hwa?
I'm really a civilian!
I'm really not it.
So Jong Kook, I'll just pick the cabbages and give
them to you. All you need to do is run.
If you all trust me,
I'll try my best to win.
- You can't do that.
- Relax!
What's wrong with her?
Why can't Sang Hwa win?
We think she has to be Mafia.
Now it'd be weird if she's not Mafia.
We've seen too many things...
- I am? I am a Mafia?
[Complete confusion]
How would you be responsible for this later?
This is the Hail Mary pass.
You haven't acted like this so far!
- He saw it!
- Can it be you?
For the sake of time, let's hurry up.
Yes, let's make this quick.
Ready, set...
[Quick harvesting means better lanes
for cartwheel racing.]
[Helping with cabbage harvesting
while finding the Mafia.]
[The Mafia and the civilians have come
together at this very moment.]
[An armful]
[First and second place holders will be exempt
from the selection process.]
[Choosing a preferred lane.]
[After placing their precious cabbages...]
[An unbridled dash across the cabbage farm!]
[Sang Hwa's cabbage field skating]
[From her gold medal race...]
[To her race on a cabbage field]
[The biggest contenders!]
[Jong Kook vs. Sang Hwa!]
Hey, block Suk Jin!
[But at this crucial moment...]
[A dark horse appears!]
[Joo Hwan had a late start...]
[But with his speedy acceleration...]
[The game is between Joo Hwan,
Jong Kook, and Sang Hwa.]
[Joo Hwan is getting ahead!]
[Joo Hwan is the winner!]
Hey, block Suk Jin!
[Bluff Seung Soo is the only one dragging
the cartwheel backwards...]
[A sure last place]
Hey, does this thing even roll?
- Who won?
- I did.
Joo Hwan did?
Are you a good runner?
- Why didn't you tell us?
[Joo Hwan's unexpected victory.]
What's wrong with Joo Hwan?
- How did Joo Hwan do?
- First place.
Are you a Mafia?
[Joo Hwan is exempt from the selection!]
He isn't a good runner.
How could this be?
- He's fast.
- Something is weird.
- What's wrong with you all of a sudden?
- We have one more chance.
[Did Joo Hwan try his best because
he's in the Mafia?]
You said you won't try your best!
- Joo Hwan gave all he had just now.
- Trust me, I'm a civilian!
Why are you doing this to the game?
Yesterday and today...
You told me you'll do whatever
you're told to do.
He really gave all he had...
That's not the problem. Our priority is to stop
the most suspicious characters from winning.
But Joo Hwan just sprinted ahead!
That's something a Mafia would do.
I'm really not a Mafia.
You must trust me.
The quiet ones are more confusing.
- I'll sue you if you're a Mafia.
- I'm serious.
- So Joo Hwan passes?
- Yes, he's done.
You're being really suspicious right now.
Why can't you trust me?
Joo Hwan, please stand away
from the field.
What is it?
Why did you do it?
I'm at a great disadvantage
in this game.
- Could it be Kwang Soo?
- Jung Nan, just take it easy.
- Just don't wear yourself out.
- You don't need to win unless you're Mafia!
- So I can just take the last place, right?
- Of course!
To be honest, I'm not really concerned
about you.
Are you being extra competitive
because you're a Mafia?
- What?
- You don't have to get angry...
- Why are you being so sensitive?
- I'm not angry at you.
I'm getting a headache because
of our unexpected winner.
But this is the situation that we
have to deal with.
- This is never ending.
- One more race?
Joo Hwan! You look very relaxed now!
[Joo Hwan's bright smile is quite
suspicious...]
I have absolutely no idea...
[The winner of the second round also
gets the exemption from the selection.]
We all know who the real Mafia member
is here, don't we?
Why do you keep trying to
put this on me?
Why me?
- Because you saw it?
- Because I saw it.
I must block Sang Hwa!
[A rematch between the rivals!]
[Sang Hwa and Jong Kook!]
[How will this race end?]
[A collision!]
[Doubtful Kwang Soo
checks Sang Hwa's cartwheel!]
[While the collision is happening...]
[Jong Kook wins the race effortlessly.]
This is not fair!
I had no choice!
It's because of the muddy terrain.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Sang Hwa.
I lost control of my cartwheel.
Hey, how could you dare to tackle
an Olympic gold medalist?
We had a plan!
This was our plan!
- What plan?
- Don't you remember?
You should've played fair and square.
- It was all planned by Jong Kook!
- I know of no such thing!
That's not the case.
It's a difficult race for women.
You were lagging behind Sang Hwa!
I was just pushing my cartwheel!
It was a bit too much in my opinion, too.
How could you dare to hurt
Korea's proud daughter?
[Korea's proud daughter is enjoying
this situation.]
- You must apologize!
[Dumbfounded]
You can apologize on the way to the
final location. Let's go.
We had a good show!
[Mafia missions are complete.]
- Sang Hwa, I sincerely apologize.
- It's fine.
[There are two members of the Mafia left.
Will the civilians manage to arrest them?]
Are you a Mafia?
Are you really not it?
We've spent four years together.
Just stop the whole thing!
I'm serious!
I'm a civilian!
I'm really not it.
You're a member of the Mafia!
The winners should sit on
the left side.
This is awesome.
I think the civilians will win.
Seung Soo has confused me
the whole day.
Seung Soo is either a hilarious comedian,
or a manipulative mastermind.
I really won't be able to trust people anymore
if Seung Soo turns out to be a Mafia.
Seung Soo is not a Mafia.
I know.
I'm not it.
I really wish that I could be a Mafia.
If he's not it,
our choice gets much easier.
- He confused me the whole day!
- The choice will be a lot easier if it isn't him!
We should've removed him in the
very beginning.
- I said Seung Soo isn't it!
- Why not?
You have reached the final stage.
Please remember that if any of the
Mafia members are alive
it's a victory for the Mafia team.
There's still hope.
If both surviving Mafia members are caught,
then it's a victory for the civilians.
Each member of the winning team
will get this gold badge.
The civilians must win!
You have exactly ten minutes.
Start!
Let's begin by talking about
your personal picks.
I pick both of the women.
Just pick one for now.
[Gary picks Jung Nan and Sang Hwa.]
We must pick two in the end, anyway.
I thought it would be just
one of the three women.
Who's your pick, Sang Hwa?
Jung Nan is my pick.
- You need to pick two.
[Jung Nan under attack from the beginning.]
I need to pick two?
They were my original picks...
[She suspected Joo Hwan and Jong Kook.]
- But they have been excluded.
- So we can't pick them at all?
So it must be Jung Nan and Seung Soo.
What do you think?
I also pick the women.
- This is nonsense.
- How about you, Suk Jin?
I think one of the women must be it.
But it's very confusing.
Shouldn't you have made up your mind
about them by now?
Didn't Seung Soo say it would be the women?
Gary said the same thing.
But that would be too much of a risk.
Everyone's such a great actor!
I feel like I'm watching a movie!
I pick both of the women too.
Who would you pick, Jung Nan?
Seung Soo and Joo Hwan were my original choices.
But since Joo Hwan's out of reach now...
I have no idea whom the other
person might be.
Let me defend myself briefly.
If you pick me as Mafia right now...
the whole country won't be pleased.
- Enough with your bluffing!
- Stop confusing us!
But if we do end up being right about
both of the women, it would be awesome.
That would be amazing.
- How can two women be the Mafia?
- Maybe the producers anticipated that kind of thinking.
There would be a greater probability of
none of us being a Mafia.
I feel like I'm watching Running Man on TV,
but just in real life.
The saddest part of this whole thing
is that the curry is going cold!
We were making the curry for six hours!
Do you know how many times
we poured more water into it?
- We put abalone too.
- That sounds delicious.
Who are your picks, Joo Hwan?
The members of the Mafia don't stay
loyal to each other forever.
They'll always end up attacking each other.
If we assume that Jong Kook and I are both
civilians, and there are two Mafia members there...
The Mafia member must either sacrifice
his partner or attack a civilian
because that would increase the
chance of survival.
You should think about
studying criminal psychology.
[Birth of a new crime profiler.]
If I am a Mafia, the Mafia member that's alive
right now has no worries. We already won.
[Joo Hwan the Profiler only uses logic!]
I saw it!
So are you saying that both
of the women are Mafia members?
I told you already!
Choosing both women is a risky move!
[Jung Nan and Sang Hwa are being
suspected...]
[They both gave their all to complete
the missions.]
[Is that because they're members
of the Mafia?]
[There were times when they
were suspected...]
[But they brushed it off every time.]
[Could it be possible that both of
the surviving Mafia members are women?]
Sang Hwa.
Make your case and defend yourself.
I'm really not it.
Because during the last race, I was trying to win.
I wanted to win because I wanted to
show that I'm a civilian.
But you guys tried very hard.
So it must be you two.
See? See?
Can't you see it?
I saw it!
What are you talking about?
The curry is getting cold!
Jung Nan, why are you not a
member of the Mafia?
I'm not it. It is highly unlikely
that both of the women are Mafia members.
It's a sure way to lose.
I don't think they're it either.
It'd be just one of them.
Because people associate men with the Mafia,
the producers may have used reverse psychology.
I've been saying that it would be just one of
them. But this is what we have right now.
I'm very confused.
If it has come down to picking
one woman and one man, we've lost already.
If any of the men are it,
it would be either Joo Hwan or Jong Kook.
But if one of them is a Mafia, then the surviving
Mafia in this group doesn't need to defend at all.
Why are you still sitting there?
Losers should remain silent!
- He's driving me crazy...
- Stop being a brat!
Go cook more curry!
He's driving me crazy!
Hey, Mafia people.
Make sure you're hiding well!
What kind of joke is that?
- I think it's Jong Kook.
- I'm telling you, it's him!
- Why are your hands so sweaty?
- My hands are always sweaty!
It's you, isn't it?
I said, I'm not it! How many
times do I have to repeat myself!
But I saw his awkward face that he made
when I pointed at him and called him out before.
- You're thinking too much.
- It's possible because it's you, Suk Jin.
50 seconds!
I saw his face twice before.
I saw Suk Jin first, then I saw Jung Nan...
I'm still lost.
You looked at me?
What did you see?
Let's give the audience
an opportunity to present their opinion.
- It's Suk Jin!
- Not both of the women!
One of the women is a Mafia,
and Suk Jin is also it.
I thought it was Jong Kook too.
But when I pointed at him just now...
- He saw it!
- Did you see it?
He made that familiar, perplexed face that
he's been making for the past 20 years
every time he's befuddled.
I said I saw it before!
Just think about what he talked about
on the bus!
I think it's Kwang Soo.
[The Great Chaos]
Sang Hwa and Kwang Soo!
Sang Hwa and Suk Jin!
Please calm down, everyone.
- I just started speaking!
- No more.
Please raise your hand.
If you think Gary is it, please
raise your hand.
[Zero votes for Gary.]
If you think Sang Hwa is it,
please raise your hand.
[Five votes for Sang Hwa.]
If you think Seung Soo is it,
please raise your hand.
I saw it.
[He sees things anytime, anywhere.]
You shouldn't raise your hand now.
If you think Suk Jin is it,
please raise your hand.
[One vote for Suk Jin.]
If you think Kwang Soo is it,
please raise your hand.
[Zero votes for Kwang Soo.]
If you think Jung Nan is it,
please raise your hand.
- Who? I vote.
- You can't vote again.
[Sang Hwa is being suspicious...]
[One vote for Jung Nan.]
Sang Hwa is the only one
with five votes.
And who did get single votes?
That would be Jung Nan, Suk Jin,
and Seung Soo.
We'll vote again between those three.
You really must think carefully.
If you think Seung Soo is it,
please raise your hand.
[Two votes for Seung Soo.]
If you think Suk Jin is it,
please raise your hand.
[One vote for Suk Jin.]
If you think Jung Nan is it,
please raise your hand.
[Five votes for Jung Nan.]
- That's not it!
- It can't be both women!
This isn't it!
You're a member of the Mafia,
aren't you?
You're making a big mistake.
The civilians have lost.
It's these two!
- Sang Hwa is saying that the civilians have lost.
- Yes, we have.
These two here are the Mafia.
She's insisting until the very end!
It must be her!
- Did you really just pick both women?
- We're done. We've lost.
I shall remind you once more.
If any of the Mafia members are alive,
the Mafia team wins.
If not, the surviving civilians win.
- I said it's Suk Jin!
- No, it's them two!
[Jung Nan reveals first!]
One, two...
[Is she Mafia or a civilian?]
[Even the Mafia members are nervous.]
[Mafia]
[Jung Nan was a Mafia Member!]
[A successful arrest!]
[Jung Nan's acting was top-notch!]
[Everyone's panicking at her true identity.]
You're the one who played me!
A chill just went down my spine!
Awesome!
[Jung Nan was exempt from the selection
by trying her best during the missions.]
Is this thing even rolling?
[She even removed others' doubt
by faking her inability.]
You are...
a member of the Mafia today.
[A lucky arrest!]
So if Sang Hwa is a Mafia member,
the civilians win!
Sang Hwa, if you're a Mafia member, you
should just switch careers and become an actress!
The civilians win if Sang Hwa is
a Mafia member.
I really don't know...
- If she is a Mafia, she's magnificent.
- She really is.
One, two...
[Who will be the final winner?]
[Sang Hwa always tried her best
during the missions.]
[Is that because she's a Mafia?]
[If she is Mafia, the civilians win.]
[If not, then the Mafia wins.]
[What's her true identity?]
[The mysterious facial expressions of
the Mafia members...]
[Civilian]
[Sang Hwa was a civilian.]
[Arresting the Mafia has failed.]
- I told you that I'm a civilian!
- I told you so!
- I said I'm a civilian!
- I said only one of the women would be it!
[Everyone's confused
by this unexpected result.]
[Then who is the surviving Mafia?]
- It must be him!
- No, he's not!
- Suk Jin, you're great.
- It might be Jong Kook!
- He's it! He's cornering!
- Jong Kook, look at me!
Look! Look! Look!
He's the Mafia!
Look! Look!
Rip it!
[With his arms raised...
He really has the feel of a Mafia.]
I'm going to give him a roundhouse kick
if he's in the Mafia!
One, two...
He can't be it, can he?
[Civilian]
[Seung Soo was a civilian.]
[He was just a huge bluff...]
Justice is alive!
It's Suk Jin!
Do you know what made me certain
about Suk Jin?
When the final choice was made on
Sang Hwa and Jung Nan...
He just nodded to himself...
I saw that too.
- You'll find out when you rip it.
- His smirk is out!
[Suk Jin was a member of the Mafia!]
[The Mafia team wins!]
It was so hard,
it was so hard!
[He always had the same attitude.
That of an innocent civilian.]
How can I win this?
I am at a great disadvantage in this game.
Just take it easy.
To be honest, I'm not that concerned about you.
[He helped Jung Nan to avoid suspicion.]
[Every time they began to talk about the Mafia,
he always blamed it on someone else.]
[Every time he was under scrutiny,
he quickly flipped it back to the originator.]
This is very exciting.
A lot of suspense.
You're a member of the Mafia today.
We tried so hard for
the survival of these four.
I think Jung Nan was the best player.
You have no idea how hard it was for me.
You really surprised me.
I had no idea!
[Seung Soo has finally seen the real Mafia.]
[Final victory to the Mafia team!]
Thank you.
- I didn't do much, but I just got lucky.
- Nonsense! Everyone worked together.
[Awarding the gold badges to team members.]
[A jackpot while making curry.]
I got this after making the curry
for five hours.
It's the same color as the curry!
- Get more plates.
- Let's eat!
The Indian curry, Haenam style!
We cooked it for five hours!
I trust anything that's made by my
Brother Hassan!
I don't believe,
no, I can't believe...
Did you forget all the lyrics?
Thank you!
There is no distinction between
the Mafia and the civilians during mealtime!
This is not bad.
- This is good.
- Is it okay?
We cooked it, but it's still very good.
Every curry needs instant coffee!
The instant coffee brings out the taste.
It's been so much fun to come out today.
It was a nice break away from skating.
I'm also very glad that I got to make good
memories with you after the Winter Olympics.
I think now that we're so close,
we must meet again!
Subtitles by DramaFever
I hereby announce the opening of the
Idol Olympics 2014!
What are you doing right now?
Wait a minute.
Where are YG and JYP?
Bring them here right now!
[MC Yoo's live, close-up broadcasting]
[The pride of the entertainment companies
depend on this!]
[The results depend on MC Yoo's decision!]
[The pull-ups that will decide
MC Yoo's destiny!]
[It can't be more live than this!]
[The first live broadcasting of
name tag removal!]
MC Yoo's non-stop commentary!
How are you feeling?
You seem perplexed.
[Next week's Running Man:
I am MC Yoo]