[Mysterious client and troubleshooter.]
[Recover your lost memories
and secretly seek your revenge.]
[The Client]
[June, 2014- Resort in Gyungju]
[With all the romance of a summer night...]
[Like a midsummer night's dream.]
[While all the Running Man members
are peacefully asleep...]
[mystical rain falls down from the sky.]
[What sort of an adventure will this
mystical rain bring about tomorrow?]
[The next morning.]
Hello.
[One by one, they all start to walk in.]
All the girls are here without any
of their makeup on this morning.
But they don't look any different at all.
Bo Mi and Na Eun still look the same.
- What about you?
- I put a little bit on.
[Their lashes looks
a bit different in the morning.]
Bo Mi, I thought you were angry for a minute.
Today's race is called,
'One Day Tour.'
You will be going on an all-day tour.
Even though none of you are
unfortunately able to remember
but you will be participating in today's race
as part of a couple with a special meaning.
[So the rain from last night was a
work of magic to erase their memories?]
You must successfully complete
all of your missions in today's race
and the sooner you arrive at the final spot,
then the bigger your winning prize will be.
Then I will now announce
the couples for the day.
- First up is, Yoo Jae Suk.
- Okay.
Yoo Jae Suk will be coupled off with
Joo Ji Hoon as the Best Looking Couple.
Yoo Jae Suk of Ahpgujeong and
Joo Ji Hoon of Chunhodong
will participate in today's race to gather
the money needed to upgrade their looks.
- Us two?
- Yes, you two are a couple.
Kim Jong Kook and Son Na Eun
will be the Blind Date Couple.
Come on, that's enough.
You two will participate in today's race to
gather the money needed for your date.
[Blind Date Couple-
Kim Jong Kook and Son Na Eun.]
[Beauty and the Rescuer.]
Next couple is, Lee Kwang Soo and Ji Sung.
- They're the Workshop Couple.
- What did you say?
They are here for the first workshop session
for Running Man Trading Company.
Director Ji Sung and
regular employee, Kwang Soo
are here as a work couple to find the funds
needed for their struggling company.
Gary and Cha Yu Ram
are the Billiards Hall Couple.
[Cha Yu Ram and Gary- Billiards Hall Couple.]
We used to play pool together for real.
Why does he always get coupled off
with all the pretty female guests?
Ji Suk Jin and Song Ji Hyo are
the Sibling Couple.
You may not remember this
but your brother, Suk Jin, lost all
your inheritance on a failed investment idea
and Ji Hyo is stepping out as his sister
to help him recoup his losses.
Ha Ha and Huh Kyung Hwan are
the Event Couple.
Fabien and Sam Otswiri are
the Tourist Couple.
Lastly, Baek Sung Hyun and Yoon Bo Mi
are the First Anniversary Couple.
They're participating in this race to gather
the money needed for their couple rings.
Each team will travel in their own car
during the entirety of the race
and we hope that you'll be able to recover
all your lost memories.
[Recover the lost memories during the trip!]
Okay, you will now start to travel in pairs
with your own partner.
Your first destination
is going to be Yeongchun.
- Youngchun?
- That's Je Dong's hometown.
- Beef!
- Je Dong's hometown.
We have prepared a special
Running Tour pamphlet for you.
Your first course is, The Experience Tour.
- Wait, stone grandmother and silk farm...
- Let's go with the wild strawberries.
- I want the wild strawberries.
- Where do you want to go, Na Eun?
- That's going to be up to Jong Kook.
- I want the wild strawberries.
- Me too. I want the wild strawberries.
- Where? The strawberries?
- Is it because of Na Eun?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Where are you two going?
- To the strawberries.
Strawberries?
You're strawberries too?
Everyone wants to follow Na Eun
to the strawberries.
[Everyone is off to the wild strawberries.]
Everyone's following Na Eun
to the strawberries.
- We'll go to the stone grandmother.
- We're going to the stone grandmother.
Then you two go with them
to the stone grandmother.
That's a nice twist to the couples.
[Monday Couple and yesterday's couple,
Suk Jin and Yu Ram.]
You will have to go to the silk farm.
Your VJ's will be following you all day,
including during your meal times.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Let's just relax and enjoy the day together.
[Overly confident Blind Date Couple.]
I feel even shorter with you as my partner.
- Suk Jin's already falling behind?
- Huh? How so?
What about Suk Jin?
Where did Na Eun go?
She's already way down there.
[Why did he just rip off Ji Hoon's name tag?]
Thank you.
- You did good, Ji Hoon.
- The three of us did it together.
[These four men seem to be on
very friendly terms with each other.]
Look at all the men that are following
in Na Eun's path right now.
Look behind you, Na Eun.
Look at all the men that are following you.
- They're all following you right now.
- Son Na Eun!
Son Na Eun!
Wait, let me get it straight on there.
[Huh? Now Ji Sung is ripping off
and reattaching Otswiri's name tag?]
[Why is he doing what Kwang Soo just did?]
Jong Kook is going to be 40 next year.
Kim-forty!
- What are you doing?
- Why would you say that?
It's Na Eun and Forty.
Son Na Eun.
Kim Forty.
[MC Mem's rhyme-
Son Na Eun and Kim Forty.]
Where do we have to go?
- Which car do we have to take?
- We have to be more nonchalant.
[More nonchalant about what?]
I thought that could've been our chance.
[Their chance?]
[Just what are these two up to?]
[One hour ago at 5:25 AM.]
Lee Kwang Soo and Ji Sung,
come down to room 303 immediately.
[Automatically breaks out into a smile at
the anticipation of a secret mission.]
Just me?
[No way...]
This must be something very important.
We woke you two up an hour before
waking up any of the other members.
You are here as the Client
and the Troubleshooter.
You don't remember
any of that right now, right?
- That's because...
- What are you doing right now?
You are suffering from
memory loss at the moment.
[Suffering from memory loss
after last night's magical rain.]
You may use this to help you
recover your lost memories.
[Evidence of Kwang Soo's SNS.]
I don't think that the person
can be trusted.
I ruined myself by following in the lead of
someone who's never won anything before.
I will get my revenge for my ruin.
Just what did Suk Jin do to me?
- Read the next one.
- [I almost got beat up again.]
I even received threats of impending
beatings if I were to betray again.
You know something?
You're just a muscle head dummy.
Kim Jong Kook.
- Why is your life so pathetic?
- Come on, Ji Sung.
[Even his own teammate can't help but
feel pity for Kwang Soo's past.]
[Kwang Soo has pent up anger and
desire for revenge towards other members.]
Ji Sung is so kind.
He event lent me the 23,000 won I needed
when I asked him to borrow some money.
A top star like him
is so different from others.
Ji Sung may be the only person
that I can trust.
I forgot about all that.
As you may have realized, you have a personal
grudge against all the other members.
You only trust Ji Sung.
That's because Ji Sung has always
treated Kwang Soo with kindness and grace.
So you're here as the 'Troubleshooter'
to help Kwang Soo with his grudges.
So we both lost our memories the moment
he asked me for my help?
Yes, that's correct.
- So my memories have just been recovered?
- Yes, that's correct.
Are you starting to remember
everything now?
No, you probably don't.
[Fails at the dramatic enactment.]
Just tell me what kind of a timeline I'm on.
When I should get my headache,
and when I should get my memories back.
When the rest of the members are up in a few,
they will all be coupled off like you two
and we will start today's race.
You two will disguise yourselves
as one of the couples.
You will then successfully complete your
missions and come to the final destination.
And those couples who arrive at the final
destination after you guys
will have to forfeit their prizes
over to you.
In addition, today's filming
of the show will be nonstop.
In midst of putting up the pretenses
you will have to complete your own
secret missions without others finding out.
I will now tell you what those missions are.
You have to rip off and reattach all 14
of other members' name tags.
[Rip off and reattach all 14
of other members' name tags!]
You want us to rip off
and reattach their name tags?
But those name tags
aren't even that easy to rip off.
But won't they get suspicious if
we were to rip off their name tags?
It's more than feasible if the two of you
work together to come up with the right plan.
I feel bad for Ji Hoon.
This is your chance to get your revenge on him
for what he does to you in the movie.
[Rips off the name tag
without any hesitation...]
[And immediately reattaches it.]
[Secret revenge on target, Ji Hoon-
Success.]
But if your mission isn't captured on camera,
then it will not be accepted.
The name tags has to be completely ripped off,
and firmly reattached to their backs.
Ripping it off halfway will not be accepted.
[Ji Sung approaches Otswiri.]
[Ripped off completely...]
[Then reattached.]
- You're all set.
- Thank you.
[No need to thank me.
I should be thanking you.]
All the members are very weary of
anyone getting close to their name tags.
I thought being the Troubleshooter was
a good thing, but this is going to be tough.
- They're all very weary of me already.
- Then I'll do it.
Ripping off their name tag
and attaching it back
is the equivalent of sticking your finger
in their mouths and pulling it back out.
- That's just how weary they are of it.
- This isn't going to be easy.
[Will they be able to succeed
their secret mission?]
Kim Forty...
I just got Otswiri because
I thought he might be tough to get later.
We have to get Jong Kook,
but he'll probably get suspicious.
You have to get Jong Kook.
[The biggest hurdle to their success-
The Tiger.]
- You have to get Jong Kook.
- Okay.
[Polite Sung Hyun opens up
the car door for Bo Mi.]
This car is going to be
full of nervous energy.
[Yoo Hyuk tries to instigate a fight
out of his jealousy.]
- We're starting to get to know each other.
- Why are you opening the door for her?
Come with us, Otswiri.
[Tourist Couple without their license
is to ride along with the Event Couple.]
I'm seriously starting to get
a stomachache.
I don't know what to do.
He says he has a stomachache.
Why are you announcing that to everyone?
- Hey, Yu Ram.
- What am I going to do?
He says his stomach hurts.
[Tiger is discovered.]
Jong Kook, we'll see you later.
[Will he be able to rip off
the Tiger's name tag?]
We have to get Jong Kook early on.
We have to get Jong Kook early on
to avoid his suspicion.
I can't even do it halfway,
but I have to rip it off all the way?
You have to rip it completely off.
He's going to think that I'm weird.
I'm sure he'll just think that you're rude.
[Ji Sung approaches the Tiger's back.]
[Attempts to rip it off,
then leans into a sudden stretch.]
[Gathers up his courage once more
to approach the Tiger's back again.]
- Na Eun feels like my little sister.
- You look like you're having fun with Na Eun.
- Yes, I'm having fun.
- Your name tag is crooked.
[The Giraffe is ready to run off.]
[It's off!]
[Target- Kim Jong Kook.
Secret mission is a success!]
Ji Sung helped me right
my crooked name tag.
- Have fun today.
- Friends are the best.
[The Tiger doesn't suspect
Ji Sung in the least.]
You're a good friend.
[Nice, Ji Sung.]
- My heart was about to beat out of my chest.
- Our car is a bit small.
[Wanting to high-five Ji Sung
out of excitement.]
[Knock it off!]
What are you guys doing?
[Have we been caught?]
- Where are you guys going? Silk farm?
- To the silk farm.
[We haven't been caught!]
[Almost had a heart attack from
Tiger's question of their intended location.]
So far, we've got Ji Hoon, Otswiri,
and Jong Kook.
We got all the strong players out of the way.
Since we're not going to be together all day,
we have to be careful with our planning.
And you need to be more
cautious in front of Jong Kook.
- Stop being so obvious.
- I'm not good at that.
- What were you thinking with the high-five?
- I wasn't even thinking.
I had completely forgotten about it.
- Where's your hometown?
- I'm from Suwon.
- You grew up in Suwon?
- Yes.
- Where's your hometown?
- Me?
I grew up mostly in Gwanmyunshi.
[One year couple, but they look more like
they're on their first blind date.]
- Just give me two million won.
- Do you know how hard it is to earn that?
- You make me come all the way down here.
- I just got a call from my friend.
[Smart and savvy sister, Blank Ji, is
trying to take care of her useless brother.]
There's a newly developed line of batteries
and if you boil the battery in the water
once it dies, then it recharges it.
Then the battery is like new again.
Boil it in the water,
and it's like new again.
I wish I had two billion instead
of two million to invest in it.
Another idea is the tomato and ginseng seeds.
Ginseng on bottom and tomato on top.
- Have you ever heard of such a thing?
- Ginseng tomatoes?
A friend of mine has a farm,
and he raises chickens with six legs.
[Big-nose Brother's investment ideas-
Six-legged chickens.]
All his chickens have six legs.
- His chickens are like insects.
- Chickens with six legs.
[Event Couple and Tourist Couple
are on the move together.]
[Haroro's arm is too short to reach
the ticket of the toll booth.]
Get out of the car if your arm can't reach.
[Fabien reaches out
to get the ticket instead.]
That was embarrassing.
I just did that to make everyone laugh.
I used to just get out of the car to do it.
As if that's what you're supposed to do.
I thought you were just going to sit there
in blank silence, but seriously...
- No, I'm doing my best.
- I still can't believe you won the gold.
[Ji Hoon sweeps the gold towers during
last week's quiz battle.]
- I'm sure my mother will be very happy.
- Yes, I'm sure she'll be happy.
Your mother won't be the only one either.
[I'm sure this woman
will be happy about it too.]
- I'm feeling quite thirsty.
- Yes, I bet you are.
[Best Looking Couple, Jae Suk and Ji Hoon.]
What is this place?
[Silkworm Experience Learning Center.]
[What kind of an experience
awaits them here?]
Wow, they're silkworms!
[Welcome to the silkworm experience!]
Wow, look at the silkworms.
Welcome to your first experience
learning stop of today's tour.
This is the largest
silkworm farm in Youngchun.
You will get to learn and experience
some new things with the silkworms.
- Before we start your mission...
- They won't stop eating.
In order for you to get closer
to these very clean insects
you need to hold up one of the worms
by the palm of your hand.
- You have to learn to be friends with them.
- We thought they'd be much smaller.
But these silkworms are huge!
They're big as snakes.
I can literally hear them chomping
down on these leaves.
They're really chowing down.
You need to grab it with your hands.
- You have to touch them.
- But these silkworms are...
Go on and touch one.
[Ji Hoon makes an attempt to touch one
after a moment's hesitation.]
You can't grab it like that.
You have to grab it with your fingers.
Hey, brother.
[Ji Hoon musters up his courage
to touch one of the worms.]
[Not as bad as he thought...
or maybe it is.]
That's why I think we need to get
Jae Suk out of the way.
- We have to get to Jae Suk now.
- Okay.
But we already got Ji Hoon, right?
- So Ji Hoon could get suspicious.
- I'll be careful around him.
No matter what the case,
I'm happy that I got Jong Kook.
I helped you with Jong Kook too.
It was a fifty-fifty effort.
I helped you with it.
- What?
- Half and half...
[The Client and The Troubleshooter-
a.k.a. Dumb and Dumber.]
Almost half and half?
You 50 percent and I, 49 percent?
[Arrives at the silkworm farm
in the midst of their bickering.]
[Latest target of revenge, Yoo Jae Suk-
We're coming for you!]
Kwang Soo.
Come here, Kwang Soo.
[Approaches their target
in a friendly manner.]
[It's a silkworm!]
Jo Hoon, don't do that.
Please don't do that.
[The Client is starting to back away.]
[Just then, the First Anniversary Couple
also arrives on scene.]
- Did you guys get to talk much?
- Yes, we did.
- Listen to Bo Mi scream.
- It's really eating the leaf.
- It's so soft.
- They're really soft.
I had no idea that silkworms were so soft.
- You have touched them, right?
- Of course!
[Amazing ability to tell how they feel
without even having touched one.]
- Do they bite?
- No, they don't bite.
That was a pretty rough sound
coming from a girl group member.
Wait, let's do this later.
[Ji Sung introduces a silkworm to Kwang Soo.]
No, let's do this later!
Don't do it!
[Three to one silkworm meeting.]
No, wait!
[Jae Suk adds another to the bunch.]
[Silkworm expert, Ji Sung,
puts one on Bo Mi's arm as well.]
Hurry, Ji Sung!
Get it off of me!
Just get it off of me!
Oh, it fell off.
What's this?
What the heck!
What's the purple one!
- The purple one is a silkworm too!
- Seriously?
- The purple one is moving!
- There are purple silkworms?
That happens when a worm eats
some leaves that have been dyed.
[Silkworm changes colors if it eats
leaves that have been dyed a different color.]
[Specialty of Youngchun- Colored Silkworms.]
Okay, as for your mission...
Today is moving day for these silkworms.
- Do you see the two baskets in front of you?
- Yes.
They're already done feeding,
so they need to be moved to their new home.
- You just need to help them move.
- How do we help them move?
Please...
While one member of the team
hangs from the metal bar
the other member has to move ten of the purple
silkworms to their new home.
- You're good at touching the worms, right?
- Ji Hoon, you can touch the worms, right?
[Rushing to dump the silkworm
responsibility onto their partners.]
Just hang from the bar like this?
- You have to have your chin up on the bar.
- With our chin up on the bar?
Ji Hoon, you try hanging from it first.
Ji Hoon sent his girlfriend a text last night
after winning the quiz battle.
- You did?
- And she replied by telling him to shut up.
[That is one tough woman.]
They hid all the purple silkworms
way on the bottom.
Seriously!
I can't see a single purple one!
- Ugh, this is driving me crazy.
- Okay, are you ready?
[As soon as they succeed this mission,
they're cleared to go to their next location.]
Let's finish this quickly
and go to our next location.
[We'll rip off your name tag
before that happens.]
[Best Looking Couple-
Silkworm moving mission- Start.]
- I got this wrong.
- What do you mean?
What did you get wrong?
[As soon as he starts...
something is already wrong?]
- I got this all wrong.
- Hang on a second.
- He used up too much energy from the start.
- I got this all wrong.
I think I got this wrong too.
I don't think...
I don't think I can do this.
- I don't think I can touch them, Ji Hoon.
- Jae Suk, what are you doing?
They're all getting in my way.
They're all blocking me.
- They're all ganging up on you.
- And they're trying to bite me.
- Stop talking and just grab them.
- Sorry, Ji Hoon.
I don't think I can do this, Ji Hoon.
I really am sorry, but I can't do it.
Wow, I can't do this.
I can't even grab a single one.
- What did you do wrong?
- Sorry, what I did was wrong.
Do better next time.
- You should've done better, Ji Hoon.
- I'll work harder.
[You cocky little man... You just wait.]
[One Day Tour- A different location.
Stone Grandmother Park.]
Grandmother, please help my big brother
come to his senses.
Give me a good business tip, Grandma.
Hello, we're here hoping to help
my big brother come to his senses.
This place is a very well-known place
in all of Youngchun.
[Youngchun's claim to fame-
Grandmother helps your wishes come true!]
- We're not here for that.
- Give me a good business tip, Grandma!
- Please help him come to his senses.
- Please give me a good business tip.
Now that you're here,
follow me and I'll show you what to do.
- Are you our guide? You're so pretty.
- Yes, I am and please follow me.
[Off to make their wish.]
If the stone feels heavier after you make
your wish than it did before
then the saying goes that your wish
is going to come true.
- Why don't you experience it for yourself?
- Okay.
Don't wish for your
foolish investment ideas to come true.
But that's what I'm going to wish for.
I'm going to wish for a good business tip to
make up for all the losses that I've suffered.
[Attempts to just lift it first
to check the weight of the rock.]
Oh, it's pretty light.
[Makes his wish...]
[Please, Grandmother...]
Please help my business succeed.
Please let it succeed.
[Will Stone Grandmother help
Big-nose's wish come true?]
It really feels heavier!
It really does feel heavy.
I'm serious.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm being totally serious.
- Seriously?
- This isn't an act. I'm being serious.
This really isn't an act.
I'm being totally serious.
I'm serious!
I swear to you.
- I swear that I'm totally serious.
- Seriously?
[Just then, Billiards Couple, Yu Ram and Gary
also arrive on the scene.]
Wow, this is so amazing!
I'm not playing around right now.
[Big-nose is amazed by
the Stone Grandmother's phenomenon.]
- Let me see.
- This is for real.
- You have to be sincere about your wish.
- Really? Let me give it a try.
Just try lifting it first
to see how heavy it is.
Just try lifting it.
It weighs 10kg, so there's some weight.
So you know how heavy it is.
Now make a heartfelt wish.
Gather your hands together in a prayer.
Just wish for one thing.
[Makes a heartfelt wish from
the bottom of his heart.]
That really is amazing.
It's for real.
That's the real thing.
It really did feel heavy.
[Absolute faith in the magic.]
[Gary now tries to lift the rock again
after having made his wish.]
- Wow, it's totally different now!
- It's different from earlier, isn't it?
Right? That means it's going to come true.
What did you wish for?
Please help me
make a hundred billion dollars.
- But it really does feel different!
- Really?
- It really did feel heavier!
- I know! It's not a lie.
[Since he's already making the wish...
Go big or go home!]
You should invest in my company.
If you think you'll still be alive
and healthy by then.
[Stone Grandmother...
Please keep him healthy until then.]
This really is unbelievable.
I really don't believe in things like this.
- It is amazing.
- I'm a very logical person.
I really don't believe in things like this.
Aren't any of you going to do the mission?
This will be our last one.
This is very important to Yu Ram.
Yu Ram is going to ask the Stone Grandmother
to help her win the race today.
You're going to jinx her.
Yu Ram really wants to win today.
- She can't even lift it.
- Wow, I can't lift it.
- Seriously?
- You can't lift it? Are you going to win?
Are you going to win today?
This is something that can be
verified in a few hours
so we can use this to determine
if this place really is for real.
It'll tell us if you can earn your money,
and if my business will succeed.
[See for yourselves at the end of our show.]
- Maybe I should try it again.
- Yes, you should try it again.
Maybe she'll win today.
Make your wish.
Grandmother,
please help Suk Jin and I win today.
Okay, try lifting it now.
- Can you not lift it?
- No, it's light.
It's light?
[That wish may be too tough for even
Stone Grandmother to help make come true.]
That felt way too light.
[While these guys are
engrossed in making their wishes...]
[One Day Tour- Wild Strawberry Experience.]
[Deliciously ripened wild strawberries.]
- Come on, Na Eun.
- Wow, that looks so delicious.
[Organic wild strawberries.
Eating it right off the berry bush.]
- Isn't it good?
- Wow, it's so good.
- Isn't it good, Na Eun?
- Just put it in your mouth.
[Love from all her male admirers.
Na Eun gets a handful  from the boys.]
I was going to buy some the other day,
but I didn't because it was so expensive.
- You can't even find this in Seoul.
- This is so good!
Look at how pretty it looks.
They need to start growing this in Ghana.
- Otswiri is about to go into business.
- I need to go into the strawberry business.
- This is so good!
- You're going to take this to Ghana?
You can name it, 'The Otswiri berry.'
- Doesn't it have a nice ring to it?
- The Otswiri Berries.
The Otswiri Berries.
It has a nice ring to it.
- Otswiri Berries.
That has a nice ring to it.
Wow, how far does this go?
[A forest of wild strawberries.
This is heaven!]
The experience that you'll be
doing here is...
- It's Ice Wild Strawberries.
- What's ice wild strawberries?
We have hidden strawberries containing ice
throughout this field.
You have to find those blocks of ice
and extract the strawberries just as is.
[Find the blocks of ice and extract
the berries in their original form and shape.]
[Strawberry rescue mission- Start.]
- I'm putting all my faith in you, Jong Kook.
- Why are you putting all your faith in me?
- You have to look for it too.
- I am looking for it.
You're such a city girl.
She's driving me crazy with that.
Wow, this really is driving me crazy.
[Find the ice, then pop a berry in his mouth.]
Let me know if you find any.
Ma'am, where's the ice?
[The Ghana boy gets
a helpful hint from the worker.]
I found it!
[Still the Reaction Duo!]
- I found it!
- Otswiri is the best!
- That's huge!
- What the heck is this!
[Rescue the strawberry from the ice block!]
- Did you find one?
- I found one!
[The other teams soon finds
their own blocks of ice.]
- It's over there.
- Hang on.
[Much bigger than they had anticipated.]
What are you two doing?
[Unexpected hammering
out on the strawberry field.]
[Extract the three strawberries from
the ice block without mangling them.]
[A frost shower in the middle of the summer.]
Yes, I'll start using it.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Are you worrying for me?
Don't fall for her spell.
- Make sure not to mangle the berries.
- You have to chip away at it carefully.
- Okay, that's good.
- Okay, let me see.
There has to be a way
to split this in one chunk.
[Kkuk launches his surgical skills.]
[Wild strawberry... I will rescue you.]
You did it, Jong Kook.
- Look, here's another one.
- You have to find a method to doing this.
Okay!
- Look at this.
- Did you get it?
Chip it off very carefully.
- We have to melt away the rest.
[Must carefully melt the surrounding ice away
as not to mangle the fragile berry.]
- Put it in your mouth.
- You want me to put it in my mouth?
Put it in your mouth and melt it.
There you go.
Melt the ice.
You're doing good.
Okay, that's good.
Hey, why are you guys
shaking the table so much?
[The shaking force of the Tourist Couple.]
[Strawberry surgical rescue
isn't as easy as he thought.]
[But even more difficult is
the silkworm moving mission.]
Was that your first one?
[Jae Suk has to move all ten purple
silkworms while Ji Hoon hangs on the bar.]
- Ugh, I don't think I can do this.
- You have to grab it!
Ugh, seriously!
That's cheating.
[As if he was waiting for that comment.]
- Jae Suk, let's trade off.
- What?
What are you doing?
You give it a try.
Ugh, seriously.
[Next up is,
The Client and Troubleshooter Team.]
[We need to focus on
our secret mission first...]
[Those silkworms are so scary...]
Okay, go on up there.
- I really don't think I can last long.
- You have to stay up there.
[Up... and back down.]
[Unbelievable.]
One look, and I knew he was done.
I'll do that.
I knew that he was done already.
Okay, Bo Min and Sung Gyun.
[First Anniversary Couple's turn.]
[Just then!]
[Ji Sung targets Sung Hyun's name tag.]
[Casually steps behind Sung Hyun's name tag.]
[Checks out his surroundings...]
[While everyone's looking elsewhere.]
[Target locked.]
[As Sung Hyun tries to move...]
It's on crooked.
[Very bold move!]
[But, just then!]
[Ji Hoon sees what Ji Sung is doing!]
[Will this be the end to
their secret mission?]
[Ji Hoon gets distracted by Bo Mi's screams.]
That's not the voice of a girl group member.
I'm just not used to this.
[Ji Hoon fortunately doesn't seem to
notice anything amiss.]
[Almost loses it.]
[Please be more careful, Ji Hoon!]
[First Anniversary Couple makes
their first attempt at the mission.]
It's harder than you thought,
isn't it, Sung Hyun?
Look at how Sung Hyun's body is shaking.
- Look at him shaking.
- This is really hard.
I don't know, Sung Hyun.
I don't think I can do this.
What's that noise you're making, Bo Mi?
[Keeps dropping whatever she
manages to grab.]
I'm sorry, but there are so many of them.
Oh my goodness!
I'm sorry, Sung Hyun.
Come on!
Hang on just a little bit longer.
She keeps grabbing it then dropping it.
Do they feel hot or something?
Sung Hyun...
[She just wants you to come back down.]
This isn't going to do.
You're not going to get this done today.
Why do you keep grabbing it,
and then dropping it back down?
[Will they be able to succeed
before the day is over?]
If any of you guys want to go eat, then go.
I think we're going to be here a while.
You have to do it quickly.
You know that, right, Ji Hoon?
[I will to rip off Jae Suk's name tag.]
[Best Looking Couple's attempt.]
Ji Hoon.
- You see now how hard it was for me, right?
- Hurry up.
Get it all in one shot.
[Working at top speed!
Ji Hoon already has five in his hand!]
[They'll definitely succeed
the mission at this rate!]
[We have to rip off Jae Suk's name tag...]
[We can't let it keep going like this...]
He almost had it.
[Kwang Soo puts his life on the line to
interfere for his own secret mission.]
What do you think you're doing?
[Ji Hoon explodes.]
- What do you think you're doing?
- He had like eight in his hand.
- You know that's how Kwang Soo is.
- How could you have kicked me like that?
[Tries to avoid their suspicion by saying
that's how Kwang Soo normally acts.]
- That's not cheating.
- Ah, you can do that?
- I almost had it.
- You were doing such a good job!
[Good job, Kwang Soo.]
- You should try hanging on the bar, Bo Mi.
- Yes, I think you're right.
[Bo Mi tries her hand at hanging off the bar.]
- We'll lift you up there.
- You won't be able to lift me.
- You can step on me to get up there.
- No, that's okay, Kwang Soo.
- No, it's okay.
- Okay, fine.
What the heck?
What are you doing?
What are these guys doing?
[Sweet revenge!]
Why are you stepping on my back?
[While secret Client, Kwang Soo,
is being abused by others...]
Wait, so we have to beat 180kg?
How much do you weigh, Ji Hyo?
Since Ji Hyo weighs 65kg...
She's so skinny!
What are you saying?
- This won't show my weight, will it
- You and I can do it together.
[Use the see-saw to lift the boulder off
the ground to succeed the mission.]
- I weigh about 71kg.
- Both of us combined weighs less than 150kg.
[Not even budging.]
[With Ji Hyo also on the seesaw...]
[Success!]
- Ji Hyo did it.
- Ji Hyo really does weigh 65kg.
- She really does weigh 65kg.
- We sank right down to the ground.
- Where are we going to find 60kg?
- Let's start looking around.
[Must do what they can to find something
heavy on their own.]
This would be over already
if Jong Kook were here.
[Eye for an eye, rock for a rock!]
Help me lift this.
Ma'am, do you by any chance have
any sacks of rice in here?
- Can we borrow this?
- How much does this weigh?
[Blank Ji borrows a sack of rice
from the restaurant owner.]
This doesn't weigh 20kg.
It maybe weighs about 15kg.
Suk Jin, I found something that may work.
- Wow, that's awesome.
- Okay, put it on here.
See? You got yourself a smart little sister.
You really are the best.
Okay, let's go.
- Be careful not to hurt your back.
- Can you help me with this?
[Ambitious Yu Ram goes after a huge rock.]
- Can you get that?
- One, two, three.
Are you okay?
[Who will be the first to bring back 180kg?]
[Yu Ram isn't even making a difference.]
[Gary steps up to join Yu Ram.]
[Oh?]
[It's going down!]
Is this good?
[A sign signaling their success!]
[Billiards Couple succeeds
the Stone Grandmother mission.]
Yu Ram, you're so strong!
Hey, Yu Ram.
[Will Stone Grandmother really grant her
the wish of winning today's race?]
[Do the best you can do.]
- Here's your next tour location.
- Is it a restaurant tour?
[Restaurant tour-
Beef stew and Dumplings.]
- I want the stew.
- The stew?
You had a burger, kimbap,
and a pastry earlier.
- You want to eat again?
- Yes.
Okay, let's go.
[Rushes off before the other team.]
[The wild strawberry challenge teams
are still busy hammering away.]
[Must extract all three berries from the ice
to get the clear to go to the next location.]
You got it!
[The Tour Couple succeeds in extracting
their second berry from the ice.]
- I got it.
- I got it!
[Event Couple soon thereafter
extracts their second berry as well.]
[On the other hand...]
We're really bad at this, aren't we?
Melt it.
[Kyung Hwan pops another
iced berry in his mouth.]
[Just then...]
It's perfect!
[Otswiri gets his third berry from the ice.]
[Will he melt it... or will he carry it?]
You have to melt it completely.
[Is the Tourist Couple first to succeed?]
[Tourist Couple clears
their wild strawberry mission.]
- Thank you.
- This is our last one.
[As for Kyung Hwan's
melted wild strawberry...]
[Event Couple is also cleared
to go off to their next location.]
I want to mention that Na Eun is
making ice sculptures right now.
[Who cares about the mission?
I'm going to follow my artistic desires.]
- Let's go with the beef stew.
- Beef stew?
- We want the roasted dumplings.
- Roasted dumplings.
They'll take the roasted dumplings,
and we'll take the beef stew!
Since you can't drive ourselves,
do you want to wait for the other team?
I heard that the dumplings are amazing.
We need to go for the dumplings, Ha Ha.
- Come on, let's go for the dumplings.
- You want us to come with you guys?
- Come with us to get roasted dumplings.
- Let's go get roasted dumplings.
- Let's just stick together to the end.
- I have a soft spot for these guys now.
- We keep going everywhere together.
- It makes me sad to have them apart from us.
[The two teams ultimately decide to
go to the dumpling restaurant together.]
- This looks so good in the picture.
- Roasted dumplings.
[Excited at the prospect of eating good food.]
City of stars, Youngchun.
- Okay, I'll go up there again this time.
- Okay, I'll try it again.
[Meanwhile, none of the teams have
yet to succeed the silkworm farm mission.]
[When are we ever going to
rip off Jae Suk's name tag?]
[Best Looking Couple makes
another attempt.]
[Smart Ji Hoon- Gets the branches
out of the way to get to the worms.]
Seven, eight... two more.
[What are we going to do?]
[If they clear the mission and leave,
then they won't be able to get Jae Suk.]
Ten.
Jae Suk, I got them all.
[Ultimate physical interference-
Climbing Jae Suk like a bug on a dead tree.]
[On my, why are you
straightening out your legs?]
- What are you doing?
- He fell off the bar!
[Grasshopper falls off the bar from
Giraffe's ambush kissing attack.]
He fell off the bar!
[But we were so close!]
Why did you climb up there to kiss me?
That was a total accident.
- Ugh, seriously.
- Okay, let's do it this time for real.
Let's play it clean from now on.
He had it all.
[But when are we going to
rip off Jae Suk's name tag?]
Okay, Bo Mi and Sung Hyun's turn.
[Back to the adorable
First Anniversary couple.]
Sung Hyun looks really angry right now.
I really have lost a lot of my strength.
This is going to be trouble.
She's doing it!
[Bo Mi's different!]
[We haven't ripped off
Bo Mi's name tag yet either...]
Her voice really is horse.
- How many do we have, Sung Hyun?
- How would I know how many you have?
I'll count what I have so far.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven!
[Seven are moved already!
Three more, and they clear the mission!]
- Eight.
Sung Hyun!
There's something on your hand, Bo Mi.
Nine!
Hang on, Sung Hyun.
[Only one more left to go...]
[Will Bo Mi be able to pull it off?]
Ten!
[Succeeds in moving ten purple worms.]
Good job.
[We're ruined...]
- Okay, bye. Bye, Bo Mi and Sung Hyun.
- Good luck.
- What should we pick?
- What would you like, Sung Hyun?
Should we both say it on the
count of three?
One, two, three.
- Beef stew.
- I did good, right?
- Yeah, you did really good.
[Off to the beef stew restaurant!]
Jae Suk is looking really tired right now.
[Best Looking Couple's thirteenth attempt.]
Only two more left to go.
[Ji Hoon's now best friends
with the silkworms.]
[All he has left to do is to count the worms
to verify that he has all ten.]
[No, we can't let this happen...]
Eight, nine, ten.
[Best Looking Couple succeeds in
getting their ten silkworms.]
Okay, we're going to take off now.
[They really must rip off
Jae Suk's name tag right now...]
We're going to get going.
- You have to take care of Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Ugh, I just want to...
Ugh, I just want to...
Ugh, I just want to rip off your name tag!
- I just want to rip off your name tag.
- I'm so tired right now.
[Ji Sung... you're awesome!]
[Ji Sung's perfect act of aggravation.]
[Target- Yoo Jae Suk.
Secret revenge- Success.]
Ji Sung.
- Seriously.
- Ji Sung.
[Ji Hoon stops Ji Sung in his tracks.]
[Has Ji Hoon really caught them
in their act this time?]
Ji Sung, good luck finishing the mission.
Good luck finishing the mission.
[Notices nothing!
Ji Hoon leaves with a cheerful goodbye.]
[Whew... we got away with it!]
Let's go.
[With everyone now gone,
no more reason to waste any more time.]
[They must hurry if they're to rip off
everyone's name tags before the tour is over!]
- Eight!
- Take your time!
Are you really taking your time
just because I tell you to?
Hurry up!
[Very loudly succeeds in getting their ten.]
- Good job.
- We did it.
How many have you gotten so far?
[How many members have they succeeded
in getting their revenge on so far?]
[Otswiri, Ji Hoon, Jong kook,
Sung Hyun, Jae Suk- A total of five.]
I only got Ji Hoon.
We really have to be careful now because
a lot of them have seen us do it.
- Okay, I'll be more careful.
- Just follow my orders.
- They might get suspicious otherwise.
- No, I don't want to.
But they might get suspicious.
Only do it when I give you the signal.
How are we going to do it
if I followed your orders?
I'll let you know
when I think the moment is right.
- Let's just go with my plan.
- Okay.
[Off to the dumpling restaurant
to find new targets.]
If what I'm doing looks suspicious,
then give me a sign like this.
- This sign is to tell me to stop.
- Okay.
But someone could see me doing this.
[Well... that's true.]
[Hanwoo restaurant.]
- Are you enjoying your Youngchun Tour?
- Yes.
Welcome to the second course of your tour,
The Eatery Course.
[Second course of their tour- Beef Stew.]
- Just relax and enjoy your meal.
- Really?
- Seriously?
- Youngchun is famous for their hanwoo beef.
They are known for their special
beef stew dish.
- You're here because you chose the beef stew.
- Yes.
[Youngchun's hanwoo... sizzles on the grill.]
Order as much as you'd like for now.
Really?
We can eat whatever we want?
[Grateful... yet somehow nervous too.]
First, we'll take three orders
of the filet to go.
We can do that?
You're saying we can get whatever?
You're saying we really van get whatever?
Even the filet?
You can order whatever you'd like,
and we'll pay for the check.
- Two orders of the filet and two stews?
- Yes.
Look at the expression on Bo Mi's face.
She's wondering why you're being so nice.
You're being way too nice today.
You're usually not this nice.
[Billiards Couple also chose
the beef stew for their Eatery Course.]
Let's order the most
expensive thing on the menu.
Two orders of the filet,
and an order of the stew.
Okay, let's order that.
Grandmother will make my wishes come true.
- Come in, Na Eun.
- Okay.
[Blind Date Couple also
joins the beef stew gang.]
Morning, day, or night,
Na Eun's always so pretty.
You're seriously going to drive me crazy
with how pretty you are.
Yu Ram is pretty during day and night,
but she's a little scary in the morning.
Yu Ram is pretty again
now that it's daytime.
I was really surprised when I saw
how she looked this morning.
I want the filet and the beef stew.
[Two orders each of the filet and the stew.]
We'll also get an order of the steak tartar.
Why are you eating so much
so early in the day?
[Everyone completes submitting
their orders.]
Okay, we will now start your mission.
Please get up from your seats.
[Before we even get to eat?]
We're going to do your mission
while the food is being prepared.
[A simple mission before the food
is brought out to the table.]
[We'll see you in a little bit.]
[Steps out of the restaurant...
and what do they see?]
- Yu Ram, wait for me.
- Hurry up.
[Once the bus moves out of their way...]
[Rodeo]
[If you want the hanwoo meal,
then you need to ride me first!]
That's really hard.
What did I tell all of you earlier?
Youngchun is famous for their hanwoo.
That's why we have prepared
this rodeo game for you.
- I've never done this before.
- It's not easy.
It's going to be a game of trust.
Even if Na Eun doesn't do a very good job,
Jong Kook can make up for the remainder.
So this is going to be up to the men.
Yoo Jae Suk and Joo Ji Hoon ordered two orders
of the filet and an order of the stew, right?
- The total cost of your meal is...
- What the heck is this?
[The requirement of the mission is related
to the cost of their meals.]
You even ordered the steak tartar.
[Best Looking Couple-
Total cost of the meal is 56,000 won.]
[One second per 1,000 won.
Best Looking Couple- 56 seconds.]
- Then we have 56 seconds too?
- Yes, your team also has 56 seconds.
[First Anniversary Couple- 64 seconds.]
We can all split the steak tartar,
so just give them 67 seconds.
[Blind Date Couple- 67 seconds.]
We'll go in the order of the team's arrival.
- Ji Hoon, you take 30 seconds.
- Okay.
[Best Looking Couple's Ji Hoon
to take the first turn.]
Ji Hoon really hates to work out,
and he just likes to lay around at home.
I lead the life of a man in his eighties.
[The elder gets on top of the rodeo bull.]
I can tell you from seeing him firsthand
that Ji Hoon only looks strong.
[Total time for Best Looking Couple-
56 seconds.]
Ready, set, go!
[Dancing along with the bull.]
[The elder gets the exercise
that his body isn't used to.]
You're doing good.
How many seconds was that?
He lasted 13 seconds.
How are we ever going to eat
by doing this?
I'll just take care of it.
You're fine, Ji Hoon.
That was good enough.
How many seconds do I need to get?
- You need to get 43 seconds.
- Okay.
[Total of 56 seconds.
Jae Suk must stay on for 43 seconds.]
[Pulls himself up in a single try.]
- You saw that, didn't you?
- No, we didn't see anything.
- There's a skill to doing this.
- Sorry to say this, but I don't see it.
It's because you guys don't have
the skills to pull this off, okay?
You have to have the right skills for this.
I've done this quite a few times.
- You have to stay on for 43 seconds.
- Okay.
Ready, set, go.
[Thanks for teaching us the skills.]
[Falls off within the first second.]
[Miserably fails the mission.]
What was that?
This thing rides differently
than what I'm used to.
[We'll take it as you not having
any bull riding skills.]
I'm used to it going side to side.
Why does this one go back and forth?
Seriously.
[I really want some beef stew.]
- You can go on to the back.
- Are we the only ones here?
Why isn't anyone else here?
Welcome to the second course of
the One Day Tour, the Eatery Tour.
- That looks so good.
- These dumplings are Youngchun's specialty.
- You can start eating the dumplings...
- We can just start eating?
[Yum!]
[Keeping a constant lookout
for any newcomers.]
I think this sitting position is going to
make our secret mission more difficult.
When other teams start to come in here
then we should stand up to greet them
and maybe while we're greeting each other...
[Troubleshooter, Ji Sung's action plan-
Rip off the name tags during the greeting.]
What do you think of that plan?
Timing is very important.
[Timing is of the essence.]
- Let's go eat some dumplings!
- Let's eat some dumplings!
Let's eat some dumplings!
It's Suk Jin.
It's Ji Hyo.
Hey, Suk Jin!
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo unknowingly roll into
the lion's den of secret revenge.]
Are the dumplings any good?
[Taking advantage of the greeting process
per Ji Sung's plan...]
Can I have some?
[Suk Jin's question scares him
off of his action plan.]
Can I have some?
- Is it good?
- It's really good.
Let's just eat for now.
I feel like there are so many
different games on Running Man.
There are a lot of games that you never
even imagined existed.
But why don't you play that
name tag elimination game anymore?
[Are you asking that question because...]
[He just... rips it off.]
[The Troubleshooter boldly ousts Ji Hyo.]
First timers on our show can't beat us
when it comes to that game.
Dong Hoon is here!
[Victims of the secret mission just keep
rolling unsuspectingly into their lion's den.]
Kwang Soo's here too.
[Really glad that you're all here!]
[The best prey that they could've asked for
on this Eatery Tour.]
- Just enjoy your meal for now.
- Seriously?
- Have a seat.
- Should we start our mission?
[Rip it off right now.]
[Okay, Ji Sung!]
[Giraffe walks over to Fabien.]
[His hand makes a move.]
[There aren't any problems, are there?]
[Boldly goes for it as if
it's something he does every day.]
All 14 of their name tags have to be
ripped completely off their backs
and reattached onto their backs.
Ripping it off halfway won't be accepted.
[He's watching what you're doing!]
What are you doing?
No, it's nothing.
[It's still attached to his back!]
Let's just do our mission.
We want to do our mission.
- Wow, look at the steam rising from it.
- This looks really hot.
[Signaling that it's dangerous to
reattempt it now.]
[You almost got caught.]
I wasn't able to do it.
Kwang Soo.
I think Fabien may have
noticed something.
[That could be very possible...]
We'll save Fabien for later.
I should've just ripped it off,
but I got really flustered.
[Such a bold conversation to have
in front of their prey.]
Okay, like the roasted dumplings
that you're all eating right now...
We have prepared some dumplings that have
been filled with a variety of different fillings.
Succeed the mission by trying the dumplings
and guessing the filling inside.
[Guess the dumpling's fillings to succeed.]
- Number four.
- Okay, four.
[Inside dumpling number four-
Wild strawberries.]
[The dumpling is freshly deep fried
right on the spot.]
Okay, the dumplings are now ready.
- Dumpling number four.
- I'll feed it to you.
[The Client and the Troubleshooter are
just concentrating on the mission for now.]
- You can't tell just from looking, can you?
- Ouch, that's hot.
Okay, Kwang Soo's turn.
- This can't be easy.
- No, it doesn't look easy.
Is the filling still alive?
[Has Ji Sung guessed that it's been
filled with wild strawberries?]
Ji Sung knows.
I think I know.
Wait, don't say anything.
Ji Sung, are we...
[If we guess it correctly,
then we have to leave this place.]
[Unable to read what he's thinking.]
I know what it is,
but are you really going to say it?
We're going to guess this, right?
[Suspicion creeping into his eyes.]
- I know exactly what this is.
- Then guess what it is.
- It's okay for me to guess it, right?
- That's the whole point of this game.
I don't get what you're trying to say.
Be more clear about what you're saying.
[They have to leave the spot if they guess it,
deterring them from their secret mission.]
You get to leave as soon as you
correctly guess the answer.
You have to leave as soon as
you correctly guess the answer.
[So that's what you were trying to tell me!]
Come on, say something!
[We still have to get Fabien too!]
- Can we stay for a bit after guessing it?
- Okay, I think I get it.
[What are those two doing?]
- Go ahead and guess.
- Strawberries!
- Strawberries? I don't think so.
- No, wait!
[Giraffe mistakenly guesses
the correct answer.]
- One, two, three.
- Strawberries.
No, no, no!
Orange!
No, strawberries and oranges
are way too different.
[Something's weird...]
Orange.
[The Client and Troubleshooter fortunately
fails just as they had planned.]
Why aren't they guessing the answer?
[If they're caught by even just one person,
then they fail their secret mission.]
Just let it go.
[Did they escape Ha Ha's suspicion?]
Why are you not guessing the answer?
[Ha Ha's suspicions are getting
stronger and stronger.]
Ugh, I seriously don't get Kwang Soo.
He keeps getting too distracted to get it.
[We're not in trouble, are we?]
What's going on?
[Imminent danger!]
It's all over.
This is too hard. Let's just
get this done and get out of here.
[The biggest danger this team
has had to face!]
Wow, Na Eun looks so pretty
with her bangs hanging down like that.
You look really pretty sitting up there.
[A fairy's scream.]
This is so fun!
[And fall off in just as fun of a fashion.]
- Seven seconds?
- You did great!
Jong Kook,
you just need to get a minute.
What did you say?
- You should use a real bull for him.
- He should go to Texas and try it for real.
He should go and try it out for real.
[The Tiger gets on the mechanical bull
instead of the real thing in Texas.]
[Succeed the mission by
holding on for 60 seconds.]
[Let's do this!]
[Strength!]
[And only by strength alone!]
Look at his arms.
[The Tiger is holding on by
the sheer force of his own strength.]
He looked like he was going to
rip off the handlebars.
- That was 16 seconds.
- 16 seconds?
[Jong Kook has the longest time of 16 seconds,
but still fails to succeed the mission.]
- Good luck, Jae Suk.
- Okay.
[Jae Suk tries to break Jong Kook's record.]
[Starts off pretty well.]
[Second bout of agony.]
[Stabbed twice in the 'x' region by the bull.]
[Inexplicable agony.]
[Ladies got to witness something
that they never should've seen.]
He got stabbed by that point.
[The mechanical bull puts a person out.]
[Painful... and embarrassing all at once.]
When are we ever going
to get to eat?
[Finish up the ride, and let's eat!]
[Meanwhile, at the dumpling restaurant.]
Isn't it good?
[Seems to know what the filling is.]
- Pupa!
- Yes, that's it.
Pupa?
Yeah, that's what I'm tasting.
[If they get it right... when
are we ever going to get Big-nose?]
One, two, three.
Pupa!
Pupa.
[The Sibling Couple clears the mission.]
[This is bad... this is really bad...]
The taste was so strong.
Suk Jin was going to say something else.
You know that, right?
He only went along with Ji Hyo when
she guessed that it was pupa.
[Their anxiety level is rising.]
[Ready to cry.]
[They're probably
going to leave at any minute.]
Your name tag is on upside down.
Okay.
[Target- Ji Suk Jin.
Succeeds the secret revenge mission.]
[Giraffe's bold attack.]
[These two are now ousted!
Goodbye!]
[Tourist Couple's turn
at the dumpling mission.]
I know this.
[The Reaction Duo!]
This is so good!
I know this.
[These two are still eyeing Fabien's back.]
- I know this.
- One, two, three.
- Chocolate.
- Then what else is it?
- It's very similar.
- Choco pie?
- No, I don't think so.
- One, two, three.
- Choco pie.
Choco pie.
[Can't be, could it?]
[Choco pie- Correct answer.]
- What were you thinking?
- Why did you tell them the answer?
Just rip this off his back right now.
[Huh?
He ripped off the name tag?]
Just rip off his name tag.
[Rips off his Ha Ha's name tag as if he's
reprimanding him for giving out the answer.]
[Cleverly succeeds
their secret mission on Ha Ha.]
I just gave them a little hint since they're
foreigners and unfamiliar with things.
[Ji Sung puts the name tag back on
nice and pretty after succeeding his mission.]
Thank you, Ha Ha.
[Time for the Tour Couple to leave
for their next mission location.]
[When are they going to
get their revenge on Fabien?]
- Wait for us, and we'll go together.
- What?
- Wait for us and we'll go together.
- Don't you need a ride?
[But Fabien unfortunately leaves
for their next location.]
Go wait for us in our car, Otswiri.
We'll be right there.
[What are we going to do?]
[I'm sure there will be other chances.]
Since you two are really struggling with this,
you're all going to do this simultaneously.
First team to guess gets to leave first?
[Huh Kyung Hwan is the only one left here
for them to get their secret revenge on.]
What is this?
[No indication of wanting to
succeed the dumpling mission.]
What is this taste?
[Could Kyung Hwan know what it is?]
Don't let him hear what you're saying.
- Correct answer.
- Answer! Sea snails!
- One, two, three.
- Sea snails!
Wow, that's right.
It is sea snails.
[Huh?]
[Focuses on Kyung Hwan's name tag.]
I just want to rip off your name tag.
You're ousted too.
[The name tag is ripped off.]
[But if these two suspect something,
then it's all game over.]
What was that for?
Why are you doing that?
[They're still unaware of the secret mission!]
Why are you guys jumping turns?
It was our turn.
[Giraffe still looks weary of
the other team.]
That should've been our turn, right?
We should've been able to go first.
Okay, we'll accept your win.
[Accepting the other team's win
as if it's no big deal for them.]
[Target- Huh Kyung Hwan.
Succeeds on getting their secret revenge.]
[Since they may still get suspicious...]
[Let's change the subject back
to dumplings.]
[You can leave now.]
[One Day Tour- Third Stop.
Gwiae Traditional House.]
[Youngchun's premiere tourist attraction-
Traditional home full of historical artifacts.]
It's set up for a wedding.
[A traditional wedding ceremony
has been set up on the front lawn.]
- What was that thing called again?
- Jokduri.
[And hanging in midair are Samo and Jokduri.
(Wedding head pieces for bride and groom.)]
This place is known as Gwiae Home,
which is well known throughout Youngchun.
For this mission, each of the couples must
get their wedding picture taken.
[Mission- Wedding photo.]
Do you see the Samo
and Jokduri hanging in the air?
You must jump in the air
and the bride and groom must touch their heads
on the headpieces for you to succeed.
Your full face must show in the picture
for the photo to be accepted.
Then do we get to go off to our next
location once we succeed this mission?
You are cleared to go off to your final
location once you succeed this mission.
[Giraffe successfully got his revenge on
Na Eun during their brief filming break.]
[Still left on their list-
Gary, Yu Ram, Bo Mi.]
[And... Fabien at the other location.]
I have a bit of bad news
to share with all of you.
This place is pretty far out.
So you must work hard and fast.
[This location is further away from the final
location than where Fabien currently is.]
[They must succeed this mission to get
to the final location before Fabien does.]
[Time for an emergency meeting.]
While pretending to trip and fall?
[Troubleshooter, Ji Sung's brilliant plan
to help his Client, Giraffe get his revenge.]
That was good earlier.
[Will Giraffe be able to
pull this one off too?]
Ready, set...
[Competitive energy.]
[Photo session- Start.]
[Kwang Soo heads over towards Yu Ram as
well as attempt to clear the photo mission.]
[Target locked.]
[His target... is Yu Ram's name tag.]
[There's no time to waste.]
[Must attack now.]
[Everyone attacks the giant Giraffe.]
[But Yu Ram is right back
in front of his eyes!]
[Rips off her name tag while pretending
to fall down as planned.]
[Ji Sung, our plan succeeded.]
[I'm proud of you, my Giraffe.]
Something very unfortunate just happened.
Something very unfair just happened.
What the heck was that?
[Why did he rip off my name tag?]
[They must not get caught!]
What's that?
Why did you do that to Yu Ram?
[This certainly isn't easy.
We must be more careful from now on.]
Why did you do that to Yu Ram?
[Target- Cha Yu Ram.
Succeeds in getting his secret revenge.]
[That was good.]
[Time to check the photo.]
[All six people are pushing down
Kwang Soo's head.]
That's totally not fair.
They're all shoving my head down
towards the ground.
[It's okay, you still got
your revenge on Yu Ram.]
I'll be the groom.
- Stone Grandmother isn't pulling through.
- We still have faith.
Bo Mi, you have to pull yourself together.
[Gary and Bo Mi are still left on their list.]
Come on, let's just get this over with.
- We can still win this.
- Get ready!
Ready, set, go!
[Photo time- Start.]
[Casually goes to stand next to Bo Mi.]
[A head on collision.]
[No one pays him the least bit of attention
and are only focused on their mission.]
- Are you hurt? I feel so bad.
- What happened to your nose?
Yu Ram rammed her head into my nose.
There was a huge cracking sound.
[A clear picture of the incident.]
There's a very clear photo
showing exactly what happened.
See that?
- She might as well have just punched me.
- That's like a crime scene photo.
I'd like to file a complaint.
[Agrees to have only one team go at a time
to avoid any further accidents.]
It's our turn.
One, two, three.
[It's not time for us
to clear this mission yet.]
- You got it.
- I think we got it.
[Gary and Yu Ram's turn.]
[Let's see here...]
[While everyone else is looking elsewhere...]
[This is my chance!]
[But, just then!]
[The name tag is off.]
[Everyone's focus is now on Kwang Soo.]
[Has he been caught?]
[But everyone just laughs and
he fortunately escapes the danger.]
- You've got to stop doing that, Kwang Soo.
- Okay, I won't do it anymore.
- Stop getting in everyone's way!
[Target- Gary.
Succeeds by the skin of his teeth.]
[Continues their attempt to
succeed the mission.]
[There's no more time to waste.]
[Target- Bo Mi.]
- Kwang Soo's pushing me down.
- No, that's Ji Hyo.
[Unable to get his hand on her name tag
with all the jumping that she's doing.]
[Hurry, Kwang Soo.]
[Just rips off her name tag out in the open
out of desperation.]
How long are we going to do this for?
There's no end to this game.
[Ji Sung, did I rush too much?]
[No, it wasn't bad.]
This game causes more injuries than
name tag elimination ever did.
[Target- Bo Mi.
Successfully gets their secret revenge.]
I think someone succeeded.
[Time to check the photo.]
[Run, Gary, run!]
She's completely blocking my face.
[Kwang Soo's face is primarily blocked
by Bo Mi's head and hair.]
She's completely blocking
my face from the camera.
- Why are you getting in the mood?
- I wasn't getting in the mood!
No, I wasn't getting in the mood!
How is that getting in the mood?
- No, that's just a huge misunderstanding.
- But you look really weird in that picture.
[Please don't misunderstand.]
[I'm just trying to clear my mission.]
[I'm telling the truth...]
I know we can do this.
[Only thing left to do now is to clear
the photo mission as quickly as possible.]
[Meanwhile, at a different location.]
Let's do this!
[These couples are doing
a paint long jump mission.]
[Unbelievable jumping skills.]
[Amazing athletic abilities making
other people's jaws drop in awe.]
His record is 6m.
- Okay, time to take the picture.
- Okay.
[The Client and the Troubleshooter are now
doing whatever they can to clear the mission.]
You can't shield my face with your hands!
Jump, Ji Hyo.
[Did they clear the photo mission?]
[A perfect success for the giant Giraffe.]
He's just standing there.
[But unfortunately fails the mission due to
the Troubleshooter's shorter stature.]
[A fierce physical battle.]
[Their heading moves are almost
World Cup worthy.]
Do you think that we got it?
We got it!
- Gary is off center.
- It's a perfect shot of Cha Yu Ram.
But Gary is slightly off center.
But that's how I usually wear my hats.
It's the hip-hop style.
[Hip-hop Gary-
Even wears his Samo in the hip-hop style.]
Why can't I wear it my own way?
Set, go!
Hurry, Ji Sung.
Jump.
[Kwang Soo's perfectly in place.
It's now up to Ji Sung to jump in place.]
[Continues to jump
without any rest in between.]
I think these two might've succeeded.
I think we got it with the first shot.
Please.
[Kwang Soo is in perfect position.]
- Okay, I'm good.
- Show me.
[If Ji Sung succeeded too...]
- Yes!
- Ji Sung and Kwang Soo pass.
[Ji Sung and Kwang Soo succeed
the photo mission in first place.]
[Final location- Yusungri Elementary School.]
Here's the address.
We're going to get going right now.
[Off to the final destination.]
[Tourist Couple succeeds their mission
almost at the same time.]
- We don't have a driver's license.
- Seriously? You can't drive?
Then you're going to have to
come with us.
So the first team to arrive wins the race?
[Speed is key to winning the race!]
[The winner of the race
is still undetermined.]
This is really tough.
We just need to get Fabien,
and we're done.
I attempted to get Fabien earlier,
and failed.
[Time to make another attempt at
eliminating Fabien's name tag.]
[Fabien is weary of anyone
getting too close to his name tag.]
If we're not careful about it,
then we could ruin everything.
[Too rash with their move,
then they could lose their chance to win.]
We need to just rip it off in one shot
rather than taking our time with it.
[Arrives at the final location.]
The order of arrival is crucial,
so run over to the mark immediately.
[Blind Date Couple and the Tourist Couple
beats them to the final location.]
- Okay, here's your final mission.
- Okay.
This is the final location,
and this is your final mission.
Do you see the cars parked over
to the side?
Four of those cars contain
a winning prize on the inside.
There are four car keys hidden
throughout this area.
Find the car keys to unlock one
of the car doors and claim your prize.
[Time to find the car keys!]
[Just then, the Client and the Troubleshooter
also arrives on scene.]
[Before anyone else succeeds
at completing the final mission...]
[We must eliminate Fabien's name tag!]
[Kkuk discovers a car key.]
Yes?
[Otswiri also discovers a car key.]
- I found it!
- You got it?
[These two are feeling the pressure!]
I found it!
[Their target... is Fabien!]
[As soon as the Tourist Couple unlocks and
gets in the car, then the race is all over!]
[Before these two
gets in one of these cars...]
[We must stop them in their path!]
[Troubleshooter, Ji Sung, awaits
their arrival in front of the cars.]
[There's only... one chance.]
Which one is it?
[Tourist Couple passes the key back and forth
thinking that's what these two are after.]
[At last... their final name tag.]
[They have managed to succeed in
eliminating 13 other name tags so far.]
[All the anxiety and hard work...]
[It's off!]
[Troubleshooter, Ji Sung,
rips off Fabien's name tag.]
[Ji Sung succeeds in eliminating
the final name tag.]
- What was that?
- Nothing to worry about.
- No, sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry.
[Even reattaches it onto Fabien's back.
A perfect success to their secret mission!]
[Troubleshooter, Ji Sung.]
[Client, Kwang Soo.]
[Completes getting their revenge
on all 14 members.]
I think he did that on purpose
to throw him off.
Run!
[Rest of the couples start to
run in one by one.]
- I think they found something.
- Give me the strength I need!
[They don't even realize that they can't
even take home any of the prizes anymore...]
[Ha Ha discovers the third key.]
[Doesn't he look happy?]
I got it!
[Big-nose Brother finds a key of his own.]
Ji Hyo!
- Why would you announce it to everyone?
- I shouldn't have screamed?
I still don't get it after four years
of doing this show.
It still feels so new to me.
Otswiri said he needed to make rent money,
so I guess he succeeded.
[A suspicious looking smile on their faces.]
So the winning prize goes to the four teams
who got the prize, right?
First place winner?
Come and get your prize.
[Blind Date Team- First place winner.]
- Are the amounts different?
- Wow, look at how thick it is.
- Who came in at second place?
- Otswiri?
[Second place prize goes to
Ji Sung and Kwang Soo.]
- Okay, second place winner.
- Wait, that's ours.
- No, you just stay quiet!
- But we came in at second place.
[Third place prize also goes to
Ji Sung and Kwang Soo.]
Come and get your fourth place prize.
[Fourth place prize also goes to
Ji Sung and Kwang Soo.]
- What's going on here?
- You all participated in today's race.
But remember how you've been told
that you lost your memories?
Before Kwang Soo lost his memories,
he had a grudge against all of you.
So in order to seek his revenge
he sought out Ji Sung's help
as his Troubleshooter
and played the roles of the Client
and the Troubleshooter today.
How could we have known that earlier
before you told us all this?
We only know now because you just told us.
[All the other couples are upset
at having been told what's going on.]
They received a secret mission an hour before
the rest of you woke up this morning.
Their mission was to rip off and reattach
everyone's name tag without being suspected.
- Do you all remember that happening?
- that's crazy!
- They got every one of you.
- Sorry.
- Ji Sung!
- I'm sorry.
That's right, he ripped it off
saying that it was on crooked.
[Everyone's starting to remember.]
Not just a few,
but they got every single one of you.
[Throughout the whole race...]
[They succeeded in getting
their revenge on all 14 members.]
- They made complete fools out of us.
- Ji Sung, can you treat us all out to dinner?
[With the exception of the Blind Date Couple,
who got in the car before they got to Fabien
[the rest of the prize cash goes to
Ji Sung and Kwang Soo.]
- Don't you think that was crossing the line?
- Can we show them how annoyed we are?
Yu Ram says she wants to show them
her three cushion shot.
Congratulations to Ji Sung and Kwang Soo
for winning today's race!
[One Day Tour Race-
Ji Sung and Kwang Soo wins!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Once upon a time...]
[Snow White and the seven dwarfs
lived peacefully in the woods.]
[Then one day...]
[The Witch's black figure covers
the woods with her shadow.]
[Snow White eats the poisoned apple.]
Only the last remaining dwarf can
live happily ever after with the princess.
[What will become of Snow White's fate?]
[Snow White's Final Kiss.]