[What's the furthest you've traveled
in the Republic of Korea?]
[Running Man's Spring Camp.]
[Hidden missions.]
[Who said outdoor camping was beautiful?]
[Unexpected events that
no one could've anticipated.]
[How far will you be taking us?]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Spring 2014- Mokdong SBS.]
[Early morning in the SBS Radio Studio.]
[Kkuk is the first member to arrive.]
- What are we doing today?
- Have you had breakfast?
Of course.
- What time did you have breakfast?
- I had my breakfast at 4:30 AM.
- Couldn't you have gotten here earlier?
- What time? What does the clock say?
It's only 7:37 AM.
- We're going somewhere far away today.
- Really?
But today's race will be done as a pair
with you and another person.
You will start off as soon as
your partner arrives.
[Their unexpected partners will soon
arrive in the studio.]
- We're being paired off?
- We're being coupled off?
Gary usually gets lucky with
his partners.
He usually gets pretty girl partners.
He was the only one partnered up with
the all girls' university too recently.
[All girls' university as his teammates
in a recent episode.]
[Mr. Gary with his luck with women.]
But Kwang Soo has no luck with women.
[Just then, their first guest arrives.]
[Who's the first partner to
enter the room?]
- It's Joo Hwan!
- It's Lee Kwang Soo's partner, Im Joo Hwan.
[Handsome popular actor, Im Joo Hwan.]
- Congratulations.
- You sure you should be congratulating him?
- I sincerely congratulate you.
- Joo Hwan.
- Yes?
- Don't be too shocked.
- But we thought you were going to be a girl.
- Is he really my partner?
We didn't know that there was going to be
a male guest member today.
Tell me your reasoning
for him being my partner.
Joo Hwan, do you and
Kwang Soo know each other?
Well... yes, we're pretty close.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Why are you taking a step back
if you two are close friends?
Just act normal!
[Second partner to enter the room.]
Next is, Ji Suk Jin's partner,
Kim Jung Nan.
[Bright as spring, Kim Jung Nan.]
[Welcome!]
You two look like a rich couple
on your way out to go hiking.
- Let's forget the show, and just go hiking.
- You two look like a rich hiking couple.
[Mr. Big-nose... you can be so romantic!]
Ha Ha's partner, Oh Man Suk.
This is my first time meeting him.
[From Broadway musicals to TV dramas-
Oh Man Suk.]
[With this being their first meeting,
they're a little awkward around each other.]
- Hello.
- Did you two coordinate your outfits?
[They looked like they coordinated
their outfits today.]
[Perfectly in sync right from the beginning.]
- It's Min Jong!
- Kim Jong Kook's partner, Kim Min Jong.
[A well rounded entertainer, Kim Min Jong.]
[Singing his trademark line.]
- You're partnered up with Min Jong.
- Take good care of him.
Just seeing Min Jong's face
is already enough to get me laughing.
[His entrance is already spiking up
the excitement in the room.]
Couple of most popular men
back in the nineties.
Min Jong is totally hilarious!
He really is hilarious.
[Just then,
someone else makes their entrance.]
[Another partner to some lucky member...]
[Ladies' man, Gary's partner.]
[A two time Olympian, Lee Sang Hwa.]
My hero!
[Gary rushes out to greet his partner.]
[Lee Sang Hwa- An Olympian who brought a
smile upon everyone's face with the gold.]
[Look forward to her entertaining antics
later on in the show.]
Wow, this is really amazing.
Who's that walking in?
[This is... the taping of Running Man,
right?]
Dong Jun, a singer from a
popular boy band.
[A rising new star, Dong Jun.]
He's Song Ji Hyo's partner,
who's yet to arrive.
- Ji Hyo's partner?
- Ji Hyo always has good looking partners.
- Glad to see you here.
- Should we all have a seat?
- Please sit with your partners.
- You're not my partner though.
- You can sit with us until Ji Hyo arrives.
- You know what Sang Hwa just said to me?
She just asked me who her partner is.
- It's Gary.
- Gary's your partner.
- How do you like Gary as your partner?
- I like it.
I'm very happy.
- Why don't you two sit closer together?
- I feel too shy to do that.
I can't believe you're partnered up
with Lee Sang Hwa.
I think Gary's really compatible with women
who have an affinity for gold.
[Two time gold medalist, Sang Hwa,
and gold prize sweeper, Ji Hyo's man.]
[Just then, Ji Hyo makes her entrance.]
I thought that was a ghost walking in.
[Arriving as soon as
her drama shoot wrapped up.]
He's your partner.
Oh my goodness, really?
[Seeing her handsome partner
snaps her out of her sleep.]
- Seriously?
- You know who he is, right?
- Of course. We were in a drama together.
- That's right!
[Having been in a recent
drama together.]
- He chased me down to kill me in the drama.
- Really?
- And here you two are partnered up together.
- I'll treat her better today.
Everyone have a seat with your partner,
and Yoo Jae Suk can remain standing.
Who's my partner?
Yoo Jae Suk's partner will be here later
due to a conflicting work schedule.
- It must be a busy person.
- Either busy, or a late sleeper.
[Just who could it be?]
[Most impressive partner lineup
in the history of the show.]
In preparations for
the upcoming spring season
we have prepared something special
for you and your partners.
Today's race is,
Sentimental Spring Camping Trip.
[Sentimental Spring Camping Trip.]
None of you currently knows where you'll
end up with your partners.
I don't even have a partner right now.
You just stay quiet
since you don't even have a partner.
You'll have to figure out your own way
to your final destination.
You're not allowed to drive yourself at all,
and use only public transit today.
- As for the type of public transit...
- What are you going to say now?
You'll roll this die to figure out which mode
of transportation you'll be using.
Since this is Running Man, there will be
missions to complete along the way.
[Complete the missions along the way...]
[And a special advantage will be given to
the team who arrives first.]
We'll just ice skate our way there.
- Why? Aren't you confident about it?
- Let's go for the train!
Airplane!
[Jong Kook and Min Jong- Airplane.]
[Ha Ha and Man Suk- Bus.]
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan- Also the Bus.]
[Gary and Sang Hwa- Train.]
[Suk Jin and Jung Nan- Airplane.]
This is great!
[In this case, then everyone else
naturally gets the train.]
[Travel fees are dispersed to
each of the teams.]
The two airplane teams may step forward
to accept their mission cards.
- You can see how you may travel.
- I should be with Min Jong.
[Take the flight out of Gimpo Airport,
and go to Gwangjoo Airport. Departs at 1:10.]
[Mission cards are issued to
the bus teams next.]
[Platform 2 bus from Central City terminal
to Jungahn Gas Station. Departs at 11 AM.]
Next, the mission cards for
the train teams.
[Take KTX 605 from Yongsan Station to
Iksan Station. Departs at 10:20 AM.]
[Jae Suk is given his partner's
phone number.]
If you call your partner,
then your partner should answer the phone.
- Try calling the number.
- Will my partner answer an unknown number?
- Hello?
Hello.
['Hello'?
Could it be a foreigner?]
Who's this?
Me?
I can tell by his English
that he's not a very fluent speaker.
Seeing how he just said, 'me',
I can tell that he's not very fluent.
We have to be on the 10:20 train.
Then where do I need to go?
Yongsan Station.
Train at the Yongsan Station.
Maybe.
- What's the mission?
- Who could this be?
Seeing how you're mixing up
some English words in there
I can be totally wrong about this,
but I think you may be a bit of a goofball?
I'll just see you later.
Do I need to stay on the phone with you?
Wait!
I just realized by your laughter!
Okay, I got it!
Are you serious right now?
What are you doing instead of
coming down here right now?
- I just finished things up here.
- Really? Then come to Yongsan Station.
- Okay.
I'm right, aren't I?
This guy is a bit of a goofball.
I know that I'm right.
I recognize that voice.
[You will soon find out who
his partner is.]
[SBS- 8:30 AM.
Right before getting on their way.]
Okay, let's go.
[They can only use the money they
were given for their mission.]
[The Plane Team decides to share a taxi.]
[Kkuk will take over the
camera himself.]
- We'll see you later.
- Okay, see you later.
[Team Bus also decides to share a taxi.]
- We're in this together.
- We are as one.
- How many are we?
- We are one!
Yes, we are one.
Please take us to the bus terminal.
You know that we're on
different teams, right?
- They're not with us.
- Yes, I know that.
- So this is how you betray people?
- No, this isn't a betrayal.
- I've seen all your competitions.
- Seriously?
I saw you starting in the outer course,
and come out ahead of all the others.
So you did see it.
It was so exciting and satisfying
to see that.
The emotions that I saw on your face
when you realized your final time
after crossing the finish line?
- I thought I was going to cry too.
- I was so unbelievably shaken up.
That was the moment when everyone realized
that I was going to take home another medal.
Everyone's comments about me taking home
another gold was actually pretty burdensome.
And the other members of the team lost their
chances at taking home a medal the day before.
So that added even more pressure on me,
and that was so difficult.
I couldn't even fall asleep.
I usually don't get any sleep
the night before the competition.
Especially during the Olympic games.
Four years of blood, sweat, and tears
hang on those few short minutes, right?
- It was really hard.
- We're encountering awful traffic today.
What are we going to do?
The train leaves at 10:20.
If we don't get there on time,
let's just get on any train cars
and we'll just have to stand
the whole way to our destination.
[Yongsan Station- 9:10 AM.]
- Yes?
- Where are you?
- I'm around the station already.
- Where?
I'm right in front of the
snack stand.
What are you doing over there when we're
going to have snacks aboard the train?
- We're going to be eating?
- The train departs at 10:20.
Why don't we meet at the platform?
We have a mission to do here.
We have a mission
that we're going to have to do.
Number 605.
[They're about to go camping together...]
[But they're about to meet for the first time
out in front of the train?]
[Seeing the lack of surprise on his face,
is it who he thought it was going to be?]
Seriously.
- Why aren't you in team uniform yet?
- We have a team uniform?
[Jae Suk's camping partner is...]
[Popular actor, Ryu Seung Soo.]
- Why did you already have a burger?
- Huh?
- We're going to get fed?
- We'll buy something onboard.
Where are we going?
- You don't know anything at all?
- I have no clue what's going on.
None of us knows anything either.
All I know is that we get on the train.
We're just going to keep following
you and Jae Suk.
Okay, use us if you can.
Come on, hurry up!
- It's Ryu Seung Soo!
- Oh my goodness!
- Hi, Teach!
- What do you mean, 'Teach'?
- He was my acting teacher.
- That's right! He used to teach there.
- She was your student?
- Yes.
[Ji Hyo's former acting teacher.]
I thought you said your partner
was going to be Jeon Ji Hyun!
I thought it was going to be her,
but it's Ryu Seung Soo instead.
- What do you have in your hand?
- My partner wanted some snacks.
[A bag of snacks for his
gold medal winning partner.]
- You can't spend money now.
- Money is meant to be spent.
You're going to starve later.
You have to be careful.
[Gary is being generous with his money
for his partner.]
- Let's go camping!
- You have to think further ahead.
Don't forget the mission we'll have to do
along the way too.
[Team Airplane is headed to Gimpo Airport.]
You didn't have to prepare all this for us.
You could've just kept it simple.
[Trash cans on wheels?]
Your plane departure time is
at 10:10, correct?
Compared to all the other teams,
you have more missions you'll have to do.
- And they'll be a bit more difficult as well.
- Really?
- Then we won't get much of a lead.
- No kidding.
Only one team, the winning team, will get
tickets for the 10:10 AM departing flight.
And the loser team will take the later flight,
which leaves at 1 PM.
[The loser team will take the next flight,
which leaves three hours after the first one.]
- Can we go to another airport?
- Can we do that?
Stop with all the talking,
and just give us our mission.
- Just give us the mission.
- Can we even get it done?
- Trash can curling?
- Ah, this game?
Everyone gets in the trash can, and the team
with most members in the 'Board' zone wins.
- Okay, we get it.
- We've done this before.
[Shove the trash cans with players in it
into the 'Board' zone to win the game.]
- You have to get in the zone.
- It's just like curling.
- We have to do it quickly.
- Let's move it!
[Two teams are in a rush
to complete the mission.]
[Jung Nan is first to go.]
Stronger than you think you'd need to.
There you go!
[Big-nose Brother's interference plan.]
[Even with all the interference,
'Tiger Curling' is still pretty spot on.]
[Big-nose gets on his way to get the Tiger.]
[Big-nose misses the board zone.]
[Maybe there's still hope for the Tiger Team?]
[So close...]
[Both teams fail their first attempt.]
- This isn't easy.
- There's no time. Let's go back and redo it.
[At the same time,
over at the bus terminal.]
Thank you for the delicious meal.
[The two Bus Teams are enjoying
a delicious meal together while waiting.]
Even though it may feel like we just spent
a lot of money on our food
but that may not be the case either.
We may not even need to eat later.
[Everyone to pay for
their own individual meal.]
- You have the least amount of money, right?
- We have the least amount.
We may not have a lot of money,
but we're rich in other things.
- Consideration... love.
- Love?
Trust.
- Generosity.
- And a bag full of ease.
[The country boy is full of relaxed humor.]
[But why are these two acting
so suspicious?]
Here, have some more fishcake.
[Why is Ha Ha all of a sudden being
so generous to the other team member?]
Here, have some more noodles.
- We're being so generous.
- Here, have some more of this too.
[Why does Man Suk look so nervous?]
[Suspicion alert!]
Let's do this.
Let's play a game and
the loser pays for the meal.
- You guys are really pissing me off.
- Why are you getting pissed off?
- What do you want to play?
- Something we can play now while sitting.
Something simple.
How about a word game
since it's quick and easy?
How about we make it a bit more unique?
I think that would be a lot of fun.
- How about we get some ladies to help out?
- Yeah, that sounds good too.
- Want to do it?
- Okay, deal.
She can just tell us any
letter, right?
She can just tell us any letter character,
and we'll have to play with what she says.
Just anything.
'K' and 'G'.
Cargo.
- 'K'... and 'G'?
- Okay, then 'Cargo' is right.
Kong Gook!
(Pureed bean soup.)
[Ha Ha and Man Suk win the meal game.]
[My precious camping money...]
[They get to save their own
camping money.]
- Wait.
- One more game.
- Let's play best out of three.
- We gave you a chance, so give us one.
Let's play one game of our choice.
If we win, then we'll play another round,
but if we lose, then we'll admit our defeat.
- Okay, fine.
- One more round please.
'K' and 'R'.
- Curry.
- Koran.
Cola!
[Joo Hwan just continues to sit there
with a lost expression on his face.]
What are you doing just sitting there?
What are you doing?
'K' and 'R', did you say?
[Who knew that Joo Hwan would be
such a black hole?]
It's like something out of a movie.
Everything just fell perfectly in place!
[Fell perfectly in place?
Does that mean...]
[30 minutes ago- Taxi ride.]
- We'll do it when the check comes.
- Propose a game?
How about a quick thinking game?
Like the word game?
Okay, that sounds like a good plan.
Did you see how white Joo Hwan was?
[Completely blank.]
He's so white.
Thanks for the meal.
[Devious Ha Ha and Man Suk.]
How could you not have thought of anything?
There were so many words you could've said.
Curry... and cream!
- Curling.
- Curling!
I know that I have experience on this show,
but you have to choose your opponents wisely.
If you have just enough
wit and plan...
[Back to Gimpo Curling event.]
Let's all just take the 1 PM
flight together.
[The departing time is near!]
No!
Let's go, this is our last chance.
Fighting, Suk Jin!
[Rowing with his hands.]
What are you doing?
Come over here.
Fail.
Back to the starting line.
- Everyone just missed the 10:10 flight.
- Then we have no advantage over others.
[When are we ever going to get to leave
on our camping trip?]
[Yongsan Station- 10:20 train.]
[These campers are in a great mood.
Everyone's talking about the latecomer.]
All he's talking about is Ji Hyo
and her acting skills.
He was not just my acting coach,
but he was on my audition panel as well.
He's very famous amongst all the actors.
- Really?
- He's a really great coach.
But he was so busy because everyone
wanted to take his class.
The Seung Soo that I'm familiar with
is when he used to teach his classes.
- My students...
- They didn't really pay for their classes.
I would give them breaks on their fees,
and wait for them to pay when they could.
Who's the most famous former
student of yours?
If I had to name one former student
who's hit it really big...
Right here.
- In Sung?
- Seriously?
- Jo In Sung?
- In Sung didn't pay his tuition?
- I couldn't take his money.
Because I had a feeling that
he was going to hit it really big.
Because you wanted to be able to use
his name to advertise your classes?
Yeah, pretty much.
You're like an acting coach legend then.
- I'm not sure about that.
- Is this like a lecture or something?
It's because he's speaking as if
he's so knowledgeable in his teachings.
You know what he said himself
before the camera started rolling?
'I don't know if I can say this myself,
but I'm a real great acting coach.'
Why aren't you saying that now
that the cameras are rolling?
[In truth, the cameras
were rolling at the time.]
The way I see it...
I think I'm the best in this country.
I told you that he's a bit of a goofball.
[Goofball of a coach.]
No, that's not what I meant.
- You have to show a talent for it.
- What do you think of me?
- I see that glint in your eye.
- Seriously?
- What about Lee Sang Hwa?
- What about me?
You're good.
There's depth.
[Definitely a goof.]
Didn't I tell you?
He's a total goof.
He's a good guy, but...
Who did you learn your acting skills from?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Didn't you have to learn from someone
to be good at what you do?
My teacher was... my own pain...
Stop saying things like that.
[Something smells a bit fishy
about this guy.]
Why are you talking about pain and patience?
You just scarfed down a burger by yourself.
[Goofy Coach Seung Soo couldn't even
endure the pain of hunger on his own.]
Since I'm not familiar with this show,
I wasn't sure if we'd get fed or not.
Sang Hwa just told me that she'll have to
start training again in April.
- She said this is her first time on KTX.
- Seriously?
I've never had the chance to ride
on one of these before.
Then do you normally just walk
everywhere?
[Unexpectedly hilarious goofball Seung Soo.]
- Her lower body is so strong.
- It's because of all her training.
[They can't help but laugh
at Seung Soo's words.]
You know what we talked about earlier?
Lee Sang Hwa is impacting the view that women
have of their own body image.
You really do have an impact on how women
are viewing their own bodily image.
We're serious about this.
You know how Sang Hwa listens to music on
her headphones before her competitions?
- She says she listens to my music.
- Yes, I listen to Gary's music.
I thought that you'd be listening
to some upbeat music.
His song, 'Tears', is very good to listen to
when I'm feeling nervous and need to relax.
- That's when I listen to it.
- Really?
[Perfectly matched team.]
[Bus Terminal- 10:45.]
[Getting ready to board the bus even though
they don't know where they're going.]
- Are we going to Gwangjoo?
- You need to take your tickets onboard.
[Haenam]
- Haenam?
[Confused]
Haenam?
- How long does it take to get to Haenam?
- It takes about five hours to get there.
- Isn't it the southern most part?
- Four hours and 40 minutes?
We're going to the southern most
town of this country?
[Final camping destination-
Haenam in Jeolla-Do.]
[The southernmost tip of the country
is where the campers will be headed.]
- Then Haenam is our final destination?
- I think so.
[They finally learn the name of their final
destination three hours into the trip.]
- Then Haenam is our final destination.
- We can't go any further down from there.
Thinking of the four of us being together
at the ends of this earth...
I already feel overwhelmed
by just the sheer thought of it.
- This is my first time going there.
- To Haenam?
[Man Suk still seems confused.]
[11 AM- The bus leaves the terminal.]
- Your first stop will be at a gas station.
- Okay.
- You'll have a mission to complete.
- What is it?
[Bus Teams' first mission.]
Lunch at the gas station.
Roll the die to determine what you'll
have for lunch at the cafeteria counter
and return to the bus as soon as
you finish eating your lunch.
We shouldn't have eaten earlier.
You'll see counters that are numbered from
one through seven in the cafeteria area.
You'll have to roll the die to see
which one of the six numbers you land on
and you have to eat everything that the number
lands on and return to the bus when finished.
We shouldn't have eaten.
You will only have 15 minutes
before the bus leaves the gas station.
Whether you're back here or not, the bus
will leave at the end of those 15 minutes.
[The bus will leave regardless of whether
they're back on the bus or not.]
Once the bus stops at the gas station
everyone, including the staff members will
have to get off the bus with their belongings.
What if we can't complete the mission
on time?
- That would really be horrible.
- What if we get stuck there?
We should get our money ready.
- Do you know where this train is going?
- Iksan?
This train will arrive in Iksan Station
at exactly 12:17 PM.
The train will stop at the station
for exactly two minutes.
- A mission will be waiting for you there.
- A game?
- Can't we just keep going?
- No, we can't.
Seung Soo's been on a lot of talk shows,
but I think this is his first variety show.
This is my first time
doing anything difficult.
How is this difficult?
[Is it difficult to just sit there
in your seat?]
We're sitting here drinking tea on the train.
What's difficult about that?
- Why do I feel so nervous all of a sudden?
- Don't worry about a thing.
Here's the mission that you'll have to do
at Iksan Station.
There are three teams here currently, correct?
Only two teams will have to get off
the train to complete the mission.
One team won't even have to get off the train,
and just go on to the next station.
- Then we're going to do something here?
- That's correct.
You can decide which game you'll play
onboard right now amongst yourselves.
How about 'The King Game'?
[You expect us to play that
aboard the train?]
I don't think this is the most ideal place
to play that game right now, do you?
This isn't the right place for it.
[How does he expect to play that game
aboard the moving train?]
- How about 'Noonchi' game?
- That's a good game to play.
- Okay, noonchi game.
- One!
Two.
Seriously, what is wrong with you?
We have to agree on it first.
- Don't you know how to play this game?
- Three.
- Four.
- Five.
[Jae Suk loses for now.]
[He seems delighted at Jae Suk's loss.]
You shouldn't be so happy about that.
You two are on the same team.
We're on the same team!
[This man simply just enjoyed
playing the game.]
We're in this predicament because
you got the ball rolling when I wasn't ready.
[Thanks to Seung Soo's efforts,
Jae Suk and Seung Soo will have to get off.]
Seriously, Ryu Seung Soo.
As for you two teams,
how about just drawing a straw?
[Draw of the star to determine which of
the two teams will have to get off.]
The team that draws the short straw will
have to get off at the Iksan Station with us.
[Sang Hwa to draw first.]
[That's awfully short.]
[Ji Hyo and Dong Jun are safe.]
[Wins without any effort on their part.]
Song Ji Hyo and Dong Jun...
you two are so lucky.
I can't believe you drew it right away.
Wow, I can't believe that was
the first draw.
[The short straw!]
He can't seem to do anything right either.
[Could he also be another
Icon of Misfortune?]
[Four minutes before
their stop at Iksan Station.]
- Take your belongings off with you.
- Okay.
But it's no big deal,
because we'll come back onboard.
The way you're packing your bags makes you
look like you're not planning on returning.
[Not anticipating to come back?]
I have a bad feeling about this.
Since I don't know what may happen,
can you take a picture of me with Sang Hwa?
[A new variety star has risen.]
- What are you doing?
- I don't know when I'll get to see her again.
- Seriously.
- I may not see her again.
This isn't the end of the episode.
[This may be the end for us.]
- See you later.
- We'll be back.
[Really hoping to return.]
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo vs
Gary and Sang Hwa.]
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
- Mission will start as soon as you get off.
- Okay.
[Roll the die and one of the two teams
will have to stay behind.]
Let's go!
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo to roll first.]
[Back on the train or stay behind?]
[Who will the smile upon?]
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo to board
back on the train!]
[If they get 'Board' as well,
then it'll be a rematch.]
[Gary and Sang Hwa to stay behind.]
What was that?
[The sinner]
[See you later!]
[Annoyed]
[Sorry]
Why didn't that work?
- What the heck!
- We just got it!
What do we do now?
[Taking her anger out on the die.]
That was awesome.
[I guess this must be the end for us.]
I'm going to get my revenge!
Don't go!
[Gold medalist's tragedy.]
As for the two of you, you'll have
to go to Gwangjoo bus terminal.
[Must find their own way to
Gwangjoo bus terminal.]
[Jae Suk is calling the Plane Teams to
let them know of their status.]
Are you guys on your way?
Kim Jong Kook's there too?
- We're still at the airport.
- Seriously.
Why are you wearing those headphones around
when you're not even listening to music?
[The headphones are just
a fashion accessory.]
Isn't that Lee Hyori?
[What?
It really is Lee Hyori!]
Hey!
[Ran into Hyori at the airport
by pure coincidence.]
- Hi, Ji Hyo.
- This is awesome.
I can't believe we ran into her.
What are you doing there, Hyori?
She says she's heading home
to Jeju Island.
[Hyori is headed back to her
newlywed's home on Jeju Island.]
- Were you in Gwangjoo?
- No, I'm in Seoul.
We're still in Seoul!
We didn't make our flight.
[These two teams haven't made it
to their campsite yet.]
What are you still doing there instead
of heading to your destination?
This superstar is going to
head out now.
Bye, Superstar!
I can't believe that was Hyori.
She's heading to Jeju Island.
Okay, I'll see you guys later.
- Okay.
- Bye.
[Finally getting to board their
1 PM flight.]
[The Plane Teams are finally
getting started on their trip.]
I feel like we're going on an MT.
We will take a brief 15 minute break
at the next gas station.
[Approaching their designated gas station.]
[If they don't make it back within
15 minutes, then they'll be left behind.]
Jae Suk.
We're about to start our mission.
We already finished our mission.
[The ease of a victor.]
Who lost?
- Gary must've lost.
- Gary and Sang Hwa.
You saw that, right?
- This is what happens.
- We have to go!
[There's no time to waste.]
Are we going to start now?
Come on, let's go!
We have to run.
[The bus will leave in exactly
15 minutes.]
To the right!
[Joo Hwan is the first one to arrive.]
- What do we have to do?
- Is this where we order?
We'll take a number two combo.
[His roll of the die determined combo
number two for Kwang Soo and Joo Hwa.]
- 7,000 won!
- Dduk galbi steak?
- We need number six!
- Wait! We have to finish ours first.
[Once comrades on the bus
are now enemies out in the open.]
- Okay, I'll take it.
- Two minutes have already passed.
[Ha Ha and Man Suk's combo number six.]
[Ha Ha and Man Suk are losing precious time.]
- We've only got 12 minutes left.
- No need for it to be hot.
You can just give it to us raw.
- What did we just order?
- It's kalguksoo.
Kalguksoo? You don't
have to give us very much of it.
We don't need any soup with it.
[The dduk galbi steak is out first.]
How about right here?
I'll go get us some water.
[Kwang Soo is getting some water for them
so that they can eat their food faster.]
[Joo Hwan is cutting up all the meat
into bite sized pieces.]
[A big bite of the piping hot steak.]
I think those guys are
already eating.
- Can you cook it any faster?
- It's almost ready.
[Just like how a giraffe would eat
the leaves on a tree...]
It's really good.
[Choking on the delicious food.]
[To save time, Ha Ha and Man Suk's food
is divided up into two separate bowls.]
Thank you.
Let's sit right here.
She already divided it up for us.
It's much hotter than it looks.
[Hot or not... it's time to eat!]
[The scalding hot noodles are being felt
throughout their whole bodies.]
[Why are you looking at your phone
when you have to quickly finish your meal?]
We're finished!
- Okay, mission clear!
- Yes! Thank you!
[Only once they're back on the bus,
will they truly succeed.]
We're in the midst of doing our mission!
[Is he talking to Ji Hyo
on the phone right now?]
Our bus!
Where did the bus go?
It's not there!
[The bus... isn't there?]
[Could it have taken off already?]
[Blindly searching for their bus.]
[Same looking buses
as far as their eyes can see.]
[Ha Ha and Man Suk are
still busy eating their food.]
[That's so hot!]
[Finally finishes their meal!]
Are you sure that this is our bus?
[Which one is our bus?]
No, that's not the one!
[Did it really leave and abandon us?]
Kwang Soo!
I think it's down that row!
Why did it park so far away?
[Did they find their bus?]
[The truth is...]
[The bus moved to another spot
as soon as the members were dropped off.]
Why are they running so fast?
What if the bus is about to leave?
No way!
- Which one is it?
- Haenam.
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan succeed
in getting back on the bus.]
[Whew... we made it.]
Are you okay?
[Ha Ha is running around blindly
in search of the bus.]
Only one minute left on the clock.
[Only one minute left!]
[What will become of Ha Ha
and Man Suk's fate?]
[1:23 PM. The Train Teams
arrive at Gwangjoo Station.]
We'll see you later!
[Next destination- Gwangju bus station.]
- We have to run?
- Of course.
[A huge advantage to the team that arrives
at the camping site first.]
You are such a sly little fox.
[Gwangjoo bus terminal.]
I see something!
Stop running!
We're here.
- Both members have to arrive together.
- Come on, Seung Soo!
[Lost their place all thanks to
Seung Soo and his slow pace.]
They beat us because
you took too long to get here.
- Is that how it works?
- What?
We have to travel together?
[Mission cards are handed out.]
The trust game.
Roll the die and complete the mission
within the allotted time to win.
- What are we doing?
- We have to roll the die.
[A random game of rolling the die,
and leaving it up to fate.]
[Ji Hyo and Dong Jun- Game number six.]
[No drinking of any water
after eating spicy food.]
You have to finish the spicy rice cakes
within two minutes.
And you cannot drink any water
for two whole minutes.
That's pretty easy.
No matter how spicy it is,
you can endure it for two minutes.
- Are you good at eating spicy foods?
- Yes.
[Dong Jun confesses his love
for spicy foods.]
- Yes, I love spicy foods.
- I doubt you can handle this kind of spice.
How spicy can this be?
- I'm not good at eating spicy foods.
- No, Ji Hyo can't. This is great.
- Can you just back off?
- What did you say?
- I have to play this game right now.
- Seriously.
You can move onto the next stage
as soon as you succeed the mission.
Here's a bottle of water for you.
[A mean trick on his part
when they can't drink any water.]
[Cruel Yoo Bratty Suk.]
[Spicy ddukboki game- Start.]
I can't believe you got that game.
You don't feel the heat when you eat it.
- But it'll hit all at once!
- I feel it!
[A full avalanche of the heat.]
[Getting teary in the eye.]
[Thought you said you were good at
eating spicy foods?]
I can smell the spice emanating
from you.
[The spiciness of the dish is pouring out
from every single one of their pores.]
[A huge mouthful.]
That's what a trust game is all about.
That's how you need to play it, okay?
[Regretting his show of chivalry.]
Here's some water.
Drink some water, Ji Hyo.
Here, have some water.
There you go, drink it.
[Here's your water!]
[Shower of water is her response
to his bratty remarks.]
[Spicy food lover, Dong Jun,
finishes up the dish.]
[The spiciness of the dish is making them
breakout into an automatic dance.]
[Must whistle after finished eating
to succeed the mission.]
I can't hear it.
- I can't whistle.
- It's because it's too hot. Drink some water.
Seriously!
Song Ji Hyo and her hot temper!
You really are something.
Drink some water first.
[What is he doing?]
Let me try it one more time.
Why do you keep backing away?
[I can't do that.]
[Time over- Fail.]
Just because you couldn't whistle?
[Nonstop chattering of his
bratty comments.]
Why don't you give it a try?
[We'll say that Dong Jun isn't very good
at eating spicy foods.]
Okay, we'll take our turn.
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo's turn.]
[What's game number three?]
[Stand the flag in their hands for three
full minutes without collapsing to succeed.]
- Hang on.
- We'll start the clock now.
[Seung Soo takes his turn first.]
I think we might be able to do this.
[Goofball Seung Soo is better
than expected!]
What's going on here?
How's the time?
It's only been 20 seconds?
[Time never moves when you need it to.]
Where are you going?
Don't make me laugh.
Okay, we're good.
We may get this done in one shot.
[Succeed at their first attempt?]
[I can't let that happen!]
[Delinquent Blank Ji is on the move!]
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
Hey!
[Succeeds in her interference plans.]
What! Why don't you
try the spicy ddukbokki too?
- See if you can stay sane after eating it!
- Seriously.
[Delinquent Blank Ji Hyo is fully unleashed
after eating the hottest food she's ever had.]
His time was, 55 seconds.
Jae Suk needs a total of two minutes and
five seconds to succeed the mission.
[Jae Suk's turn.]
[Huh?]
[Are you here to samba?]
[His dancing legs know no boundaries.]
[His partner for the day- The flag.]
[Drops his partner to the ground
after only a few seconds.]
Get out of the way!
Where am I?
Who am I?
[Blank Ji still can't get herself together.]
Yoo Jae Suk's time is, nine seconds.
With the total time of one minute and
nine seconds, you failed the mission.
- You were doing so well too.
- I think I could've done all three minutes.
You're really good at this game.
- You did really good.
- What?
What did you just say?
Why are you crying?
Why are you crying on a variety show?
What's going on here?
Sang Hwa's here!
[Just then, Sang Hwa and Gary
arrive at the terminal!]
[12:19- Abandoned at Iksan Station.]
[12:34- Arrives at Iksan bus station.]
[12:35- Boards the bus to Gwangjoo.]
[2:01- Arrives at Gwangju bus terminal.]
[They rushed over to the terminal
without wasting even a single second.]
- How did you guys get here?
- We took the bus.
- We found a bus immediately.
- Seriously?
- You took the bus?
- Fighting!
- My stomach hurts right now.
- Mine too.
[Let's avoid game number six!]
[As soon as number six turns up...
she gets rid of the evidence.]
[A shocking kicking talent.]
- You got number six. I saw it.
- No, it wasn't number six.
- I saw it. It was number six.
- No, it wasn't!
[I can't eat any more of it!]
It was number six.
It was six.
You got number six again.
It was six, for sure...
but we'll give them a break.
- Thank you.
- No, don't mention it.
You guys worked so hard earlier.
- I'm here too.
- Okay, I hear you.
[Number four.]
We can't do that right now.
I'm still short of breath from the spicy food.
For how long?
- Three minutes? I'll do it.
- He's going to do all three minutes himself?
- Dong Jun's doing all three minutes?
- No, a total of three minutes.
- To dunk his face underwater?
- Dong Jun will be dead after three minutes.
[We're just explaining the rules...]
It's not like Dong Jun is a fish.
[Their combined time must be three minutes
for them to succeed the mission.]
- Who would like to go first?
- I'll go first.
- Wow, Dong Jun.
- He's just overly zealous right now!
I thought you said you were good
at eating spicy foods too!
[Makes up the difference of wanting to be good
and actually being good with enthusiasm.]
- I can hold my breath for a really long time.
- Really?
Doesn't that make you dizzy?
- That's going to make you dizzy.
- You're supposed to do that only three times.
Ugh, I feel dizzy.
What are you doing, Dong Jun?
[The rice cakes must've been
really spicy...]
Okay, give it a try.
Don't even think about lifting up your head.
[Enthusiastic Dong Jun dunks his
head in with confidence.]
[What?]
[Overly enthusiastic,
Three-second Dong Jun.]
What are you doing right now, Dong Jun?
- Here's a towel, Dong Jun.
- What just happened?
What is the matter with you?
[You really are a strange child...]
- Just who are you, Dong Jun?
- He has nothing but enthusiasm.
You have to stay underwater
for two minutes and 57 seconds.
Think of yourself as the mermaid princess.
Ji Hyo, I'm sorry.
He's sorry...
Dong Jun says that he's sorry.
You're adorable, Dong Jun.
[Blank Ji makes her attempt to stay
submerged for two minutes and 57 seconds.]
She doesn't submerge her face too deep.
She's so smart.
[Cleverly dips it just slightly in the water.]
She needs to stay underwater for
two minutes and 57 seconds.
Dong Jun, three seconds
really was pretty shocking.
- My nose was running from the food.
- Really?
- The time really goes by slow.
- Goes really slow at times like these.
- Knowing the time...
- Would you like for us to tell you?
Yes, please tell us.
That'll make her feel very anxious.
Ji Hyo's listening to everything
that we're saying right now.
Ji Hyo really is lasting
a long time in the water.
A minute has passed.
If Dong Jun could've stayed
at least a minute...
I can't believe how long you're lasting.
- I think she's still breathing somehow.
- No, she really is underwater.
You're so much better now that you've
quit drinking and smoking.
I just saw her laugh a bit.
Ji Hyo couldn't hold back her laughter
on that comment.
You have to protect me, Sang Hwa.
Ji Hyo couldn't ignore that comment.
[A comment even Mermaid Blank Ji
couldn't ignore.]
Your combined total time is...
one minute and 55 seconds.
Wow, that really is too bad.
You did 1 minute 52 seconds by yourself.
Ji Hyo, you did one minute and
52 seconds all by yourself.
- Dong Jun only got three seconds.
- He's got nothing but enthusiasm.
[I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
From, Enthusiastic Kim.]
There's only a minute left.
[Back at the gas station.]
[One minute before departure time.]
[With the honor of our team on the line...
we can't get left behind here.]
I guarantee that they're going to fail.
[Kwang Soo is guaranteeing
Ha Ha and Man Suk's failure.]
[But just then... the other
team makes it in the nick of time!]
[We should've left them in our dust...]
[Ha Ha and Man Suk were taking their sweet time
because they didn't know the bus had moved.]
Where are they going?
[They got lucky when they accidentally
happened to see Kwang Soo in the distance.]
Why are they in such a rush?
What if the bus is about to take off?
No way!
[They sense something is off,
and take off hot on Kwang Soo's trail.]
[They were able to make it back safely
riding on Giraffe's tail.]
We were neck and neck.
Both teams succeeded their mission,
and we will head off to our next destination.
[Both succeeded their mission,
and off to their next destination!]
Great job.
[That was our chance to
get rid of them.]
[The bus with the two of the most infamous
traitors are back on the road again.]
[Gwangjoo bus terminal-
Back to Jae Suk and Seung Soo's turn.]
Okay, here we go.
- No, this isn't what I meant to do.
- Number one.
[Accidentally drops the die.]
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo are stuck with
Game number one.]
[Cone sitting.]
I have... a very bad condition
back there.
[The cone that we're speaking of is...]
[The very cone that brought RM members down
in crumbling shame in a game three years ago.]
[The day to feel that terror once again
has returned.]
- How long do we have to sit there for?
- The combined time needs to be...
[They must last for the total combined time
of two whole minutes to succeed the mission.]
[But their feet must be off the ground.]
But this will crumble... it's not crumbling.
What are you doing?
You really are something else.
You should go first.
We'll show you a demonstration.
This is how it needs to be done.
He looks so comfortable doing it.
If he makes it look so easy like that...
You have to last for at least a minute
and 50 seconds on there.
[His first contact with the shocking cone.]
There's no room for it to go in.
Where would it go in?
[Where are you trying to stick it?]
[Seung Soo takes his turn.]
His foot is touching the ground.
Can you shoot him from the side?
Why do you have your hands at your sides?
Why are you posing like that?
That's a cute pose.
You have to endure through the pain.
Yes, we can do this.
I think we can do this.
[No, I can't do it!]
What are you doing?
His time is 26 seconds.
There's no way I can do that.
[Jae Suk must last for one minute and
34 seconds for them to succeed.]
Watch from behind and make sure
that I don't start to bleed.
If I start to bleed,
kick the cone out from under me, okay?
[If something starts to dribble out,
then kick the cone away, not me.]
- You need one minute and 34 seconds.
- Okay.
- What are you doing?
I'm trying to massage out the pain.
What are you doing over there?
You think you're over there exercising?
[Jae Suk takes his turn.]
[It's coming...]
It's really getting up there.
I think I should kick the cone out
from under you.
[It's starting to dig deeper and deeper
into a place where it doesn't belong.]
Massage it out.
[Starting the cone therapy session.]
I can't do that.
- There's no way we can do that.
- Your combined time is, 56 seconds.
[With a total combined time of 56 seconds,
they fail the mission.]
[All they can manage to do is to laugh.]
- Gary's really good at eating spicy foods.
- Really?
[Gary and Sang Hwa are hoping for
number six with Gary's love for spicy foods.]
I really love spicy foods.
I hope we get the spicy food game.
- Number five.
- We haven't seen that one before.
No one's gotten that one before,
so we don't know which one that is.
Let's succeed with our first attempt.
- 'Hold the position.'
- What's that?
[Hold the position?]
It's a position that used to be quite popular
on the internet for a while.
It's a position that most couples
have been in at least once.
- Couples?
- Here is your position.
How do you expect us to do that?
[Precisely this position.]
[A position that everyone tried
and became famous throughout the world.]
- I remember seeing that.
- How do you expect us to do that?
That's athlete, Lee Sang Hwa, over there.
That's Lee Sang Hwa.
- Aren't you going to do the lifting, Gary?
- No, I'll get on top.
See?
Did you see that?
Gary's going to get on top?
If Lee Sang Hwa holds him up,
then you must last for two minutes.
But if it's Gary holding her up,
then it's for three minutes.
- Can we try this too?
- No, you have to roll the number.
That's what I meant.
- Stop talking like that.
- In case they fail it.
[Gary and Sang Hwa's attempt
to hold the position.]
Ready?
Want me to go up now?
No, wait.
Sorry, but I wasn't ready for it.
- You'd better not fall.
- Okay.
- Sang Hwa told him that he can't fall.
Stand up!
Gary.
I really tried as hard as I could.
I really did.
Sang Hwa, I'm so sorry.
I can try it again.
Sang Hwa's really angry right now.
[2:10-
Plane Teams arrives at Gwangjoo Airport.]
[First to leave the starting point,
and the last ones to arrive in Gwangjoo.]
[Go to Gwangjoo bus terminal.]
Let's all go together.
It's really nice out here.
Which one should we take?
Let's take this cab.
[Great chemistry.
These four are very tightly knit.]
[And over here...
no one will want these four.]
[2:50- Gwangjoo bus terminal.]
[Six again!]
Hey!
Do you want to die!
[Enthusiastic Kim apologizes again.]
Roll it again.
No more breaks.
If you get six again, you'll have to do it.
I think Ji Hyo's going to start swearing
if she gets six again.
[What will she roll this time?]
[Number five- Couple position.]
[After Seung Soo's recent proposal,
time has been changed from 3 to 2 minutes.]
Look at how enthusiastic he is again!
['Go-for-it' Enthusiastic Kim doesn't even
take any time out to think about it first.]
One, two, three.
[Goes for it with enthusiasm.]
[Looking pretty steady.]
He's shaking.
Hey, Enthusiasm.
- Enthusiastic Kim.
- Did you call me?
- You're looking good.
- You can stop at any time now.
- No, I'm going to last for two minutes.
- Be quiet and stop talking!
[People are talking to him from the sides,
and up top, he's being told to shut up.]
30 seconds.
Two minutes.
We need to hold this for two minutes.
- He's about to break.
- Enthusiastic Kim is about to lose it.
No, he's about to break.
His knees are starting to shake.
- Just a little bit longer.
- Ji Hyo's trying harder than he is.
[Enthusiastic Kim is just hanging on
to Blank-Hangar?]
- One minute and 30 seconds.
- Just 30 seconds more.
He'll drop her at around the 47 second mark.
Enthusiastic Kim will drop her
at around 1 minute 47 seconds.
- Maybe even at 57 seconds.
- Stop talking to me!
- You can do this!
- If you drop her then, you'll be a legend!
- Now's the time!
- Now's the time to drop her!
[Will it be for laughter...
or will it be for the win?]
- Why did you suggest two minutes, Seung Soo?
- It's your fault, Seung Soo.
- Five, four, three, two, one...
- Drop her now!
[Mission success!]
He started shaking from the moment
that he lifted me up.
You did great, Enthusiastic Kim!
I'm proud of you!
- You have to thank me.
- Thank you, Sir!
- Are you okay?
- I don't think I can use my arms anymore.
So it's our turn now, right?
Okay, here we go.
[Ji Hyo and Dong Jun are off to their final
destination after clearing their mission.]
[Final destination-
Songhori Beach in Haenam.]
[Must find their own way
to their final destination.]
[Huge advantage will be given to those teams
that arrives early at the destination.]
- We need a bus to Haenam.
- Haenam.
[Checking for bus times inside the terminal.]
Hello, do you have a bus
that's leaving for Haenam?
- Yes.
- What time does the bus leave?
[Current time- 2:48.
Next bus departs at 3:10.]
- What time is the next bus?
- The next one is at 3:10.
- Really? How much are the tickets?
- 11,100 won.
- How many of you are there?
- Two.
Your total is, 22,200 won.
We're really going to Haenam?
[The other teams must complete their mission
before they can leave for Haenam.]
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo are back at trying
their hand at the cone position game.]
Fighting, Seung Soo.
- He's better than I expected for him to be.
- Seung Soo's an enthusiast too.
I bet he'll last for about 15 seconds.
Seung Soo, are you okay?
Don't act like you're okay.
- This really isn't an easy task.
- One minute.
It's really sticking up there.
Seung Soo, are you okay?
It's really up there!
[That has to be pretty painful...]
[But Seung Soo's still
maintaining his position.]
Can he do the whole thing by himself?
[Then he really isn't just a total goofball?]
Why couldn't you have done this earlier?
[Is Seung Soo really going to complete
the full two minutes by himself like this?]
Success!
[Who knew that goofy Seung Soo
had this side to him?]
Massage...
I knew something was off!
He has something in there!
[Huh?]
[What's inside Seung Soo's pants?]
[A bottle of water!]
[He shoved a bottle of water
inside his pants!]
Seung Soo, seriously...
he really is no good!
[A shocking twist on par with
the ending of 'The Usual Suspects'!]
[While Jae Suk was talking to the producer
before starting the mission...]
[He shoves the bottle of water that he had
in his jacket pocket inside his pants.]
This is taking too long.
Why don't you go first, Seung Soo?
[Positioning the bottle of water
carefully in his pants...]
Fighting, Seung Soo.
[Yeah... this is the spot.]
[That's why he was able to remain
so calm and peaceful.]
Why would you point that out
to everyone!
[Water bottle scheme that no one
could've even fathomed happening!]
[Jong Kook and Min Jong arrives in
the midst of all this chaos.]
I can't believe him!
[Cone schemer, Ryu Seung Soo!]
Hi... it still hurts.
None of us would've known if it hadn't
been for Gary.
I was trying to help him massage his back
when I noticed something sticking out.
What were you thinking, Seung Soo?
[Cone scheme that will go down
in history of the show.]
[Jong Kook and Min Jong take their turn.]
I really hope that you get number six.
[Everyone wants them to roll number six
because they know Kkuk can't handle spice.]
Number six!
- Why, what's number six?
- Jong Kook's in trouble now!
No drinking of water after
eating spicy food!
It's ddukbbokki,
which Jong Kook doesn't normally eat.
[And on top of everything else,
it's food that Jong Kook normally won't eat.]
- That is no joke.
- I really can't handle spicy food.
[Mr. Capable's Achilles' heel is spicy food.]
If you pass on this chance,
then the next team will get a chance.
Don't worry, I'll eat it all myself.
You have to eat the whole thing within
two minutes and whistle afterward.
Then you can't drink any water
until your two minutes are up.
- I don't have to whistle for a minute?
- No, you don't.
[You can't be serious...]
Seriously, what's wrong with that guy?
Knock it off.
- Okay, I'll start the clock.
- Min Jong won't be able to do it.
- Set, go!
- How spicy could it be?
- It's okay in the beginning.
- It's okay when you're eating it.
Five, four, three, two, one.
It'll hit at any moment.
[There it is.]
Min Jong says it's too hard to chew.
- Why do I want to try a bite of that?
- You can't eat spicy food?
- I'm hungry.
- Jong Kook is feeling it now.
[Kkuk, who can't handle any spice
is starting to hiccup from the hotness of it.]
- Spicy food makes you hiccup.
- Jong Kook never eats spicy food.
- Look at Min Jong.
- You don't find that spicy?
[Min Jong is continuing to eat
without any hesitation.]
- Isn't that spicy?
- It's too hard to chew.
[Spice isn't the problem,
but it's too hard to chew?]
- You can't drink that.
- I almost had him.
[One minute]
- Have you always liked spicy food?
- How can you eat such spicy food like that?
Min Jong...
your face is starting to get really red.
Did you see the bottle of water
in my hand?
This is too hard to chew.
- Are you sure it's not the spice?
- It's not the spice you're complaining about?
[We'll say it's too tough to chew.]
You have to eat this scallion.
- You have to eat that.
- You have to eat that scallion.
[Bratty Big-nose is making sure that every
last bite gets eaten.]
[Kkuk succeeds at whistling.]
- It's your turn to whistle now.
- You do it.
I just did!
- I just did!
- Five, four, three, two...
[Min Jong also succeeds at whistling.]
[They must now endure the next minute
without drinking any water.]
Why are you shadowboxing
all of a sudden?
Here, have a drink of water.
[Everyone's trying to ruin their chance
at succeeding the mission.]
[Min Jong doesn't even have it in him
to make any replies.]
Isn't it cheating if they blow their nose?
[Blowing their nose is cheating?]
- No, you can't blow your nose.
- Yes, I can!
That's cheating.
You can't do anything.
- You can't do anything right now.
- Look at his runny nose!
That's really spicy.
[Jong Kook and Min Jong succeed
the spicy ddukbbokki game.]
[Min Jong blows his nose the moment
the mission is over.]
[Even in the midst of his agony,
Kkuk takes care of Min Jong first.]
Can I have some water?
[Big-nose can't get any brattier
even if he tried.]
Let him drink his water.
[Ji Hyo and Dong Jun's awaited bus
finally arrives at the terminal.]
Let's go.
[3:10- Ji Hyo and Dong Jun board the bus.]
We'll see you in Haenam.
There are a lot of elders in here,
so we're going to ride in silence.
[Jae Suk's record- 48 seconds.]
[Seung Soo must last for one minute and
12 seconds for them to succeed.]
[Wait, that expression on his face...]
[That's the same scheme artist expression
we saw on his face earlier?]
[Investigator Gae steps up
to investigate.]
[That's a sad looking face...]
30 seconds.
That's definitely not how he
looked earlier.
[Are those tears in his eyes?]
Your life will be much better
if you just step down from there.
Why are you putting up with
all this pain?
[Where am I...  Who am I...]
[Fighting an internal battle with myself...
or a battle with the cone.]
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo completes
the cone mission.]
[A much lonelier battle without
his beloved water bottle.]
How funny.
[No time to focus on the pain.
Must hurry in order to catch the next bus!]
[Songhori Beach in Haenam.]
[Off on their way to the
final destination!]
- See you later, Gary!
- Okay!
[But the agony still won't fade away...]
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo step inside
the terminal to check out the bus schedule.]
Two tickets to Haenam please.
When is the next bus?
How much?
- 22,200 won.
- Ah, 22,200 won?
Thank you, and have a great day.
[Two tickets to Haenam are purchased!]
3:40?
It's leaving at any minute then.
[Current time- 3:23.]
[Which team will be the first team to
arrive at the final location?]
[Bus Teams' have now been traveling
for over five hours.]
[3:54- Ha Ha, Man Suk, Kwang Soo
and Joo Hwan arrive in Haenam.]
[Finally arrives in the town of Haenam.]
- We're here in Haenam!
- I love Haenam!
What are you guys all doing?
[Are we going to do another mission now?]
[Must succeed in passing out 20 autographs
to go on to the next location.]
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan set up
a signing booth inside the terminal.]
If any one of you are interested in
receiving our autographs...
- Free autographs!
We're giving away free autographs!
[Aggressive marketing of themselves.]
[Suk Jin, Jung Nan, Gary, and Sang Hwa agree
to pool their money together to rent a car.]
Here you go.
So it takes that long to get there?
- I'll start driving.
- You will?
[Extra time for not having to stop at
the bus terminal for ticketing.]
Are we finally getting started
on our sentimental camping trip?
[Filming themselves since there's no room
for the VJ to ride in.]
Hello.
I feel so energized for having
Sang Hwa in the car with us.
[Riding in the car with a gold medalist.]
I wish I could stick ice skate blades
on the bottom of this car.
[The world's first ice skating car?]
- Free autographs!
- Were finished.
- We signed all 20 of them on the table.
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan succeeds at
handing out all 20 autographs.]
[Finally learns of their final destination.]
[Songhori Beach in Haenam.]
- A beach?
- Can we board the earlier bus?
- Can we board the bus right now?
- Would that be okay?
[Even though their tickets are for 4:20,
they're generously being let on the 4:05 bus.]
I think they're leaving right now.
- Bye!
- Bye, we have to get going!
[Running towards the departing bus.]
Please shut the doors.
Are you guys leaving?
[The bus departs at exactly 4:05...]
- Are they going to the final location?
- I think they are.
We did it!
We should've gotten rid of them
a long time ago.
We'll wait for you guys there.
[Happiness of the victors.]
It feels like we just got rid of
a couple of rotting teeth.
It feels so good to be rid of them.
Can you please tell me how long it'll take
for us to get to the beach?
- About 50 minutes.
- 50 minutes?
He says it'll take about 50 minutes.
- We were right.
- Really? They have a stop to make?
They have stops to make
whereas ours is a direct route.
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan must make stops,
while Ha Ha and Man Suk have a direct route.]
[Suk Jin, Jung Nan, Gary, and Sang Hwa are
headed down in their rental car.]
[Sang Hwa's turn with the camera.]
[Gary's turn with the camera.]
They have to stop at the Haenam terminal,
but we're driving straight there.
[Sang Hwa's close-up shot
of Big-nose.]
What are you doing?
[Sang Hwa's having too much fun
with her camera.]
This is really heavy.
[Which of the teams will be the first
to arrive at the final location?]
[Ha Ha and Man Suk are getting close
to the final destination.]
This is the end of our land.
It's the ocean!
[Blank Ji is excited
at the sight of the ocean.]
[A beautiful representation of
spring in the Republic of Korea.]
[Brightly shining sky and the ocean.]
[This is...
the southernmost tip of our country.]
Wow, look at the seashore.
I bet we'll have to do something
out there.
I think we're almost there.
Am I right?
Next stop is, Songhori.
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan are
approaching the Songhori stop.]
I think we're almost there.
I wonder who will be the first to arrive?
We have to get there quickly
no matter what we have to do.
[Which of these teams
will be the first to arrive?]
[Wait, that bus is...]
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan are first to arrive?]
- Yes, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Hello.
I have been on a bus for ten hours today,
We should've taken the plane.
- You two are the first ones to arrive.
- We're in first place?
[Mission card received.]
[Huh?]
[First team to arrive at the campsite with
a local villager wins today's race!]
- We've arrived!
- We're here!
What's this?
We have to go somewhere else?
[Just the sight of the mission card
is enough to give them chills.]
[Ji Hyo and Dong Jun arrive
soon thereafter.]
Can you wait here for just a moment?
- Sir.
- Sorry, but the driver needs to talk to you.
Go in there and talk to him.
- He needs to talk to you.
- Thank you.
[Why is she shoving the PD in the cab?]
Song Ji Hyo didn't pay the cab fare!
[All the other teams arrives soon
thereafter to start the mission.]
[This is... the final camping location.]
[Which team will be the first to arrive?]
Okay, they're here.
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan
come in at first place.]
You can pull it, Do Hyung.
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan
are the ultimate winners!]
[First place winners...
get the ultimate camper!]
[We won't want for anything else.
No matter how drenching the rain...]
[This is where Kwang Soo and
Joo Hwan will be sleeping.]
What's that?
What is that?
Will someone be sleeping in there?
[Someone less fortunate will be
sleeping in there tonight.]
We get the camper!
- You guys won first place?
- Oh, you guys are here.
Congratulations at coming in
at second place.
[Ji Hyo and Dong Jun- second place.]
- Do you know what you guys got?
- What?
[Second place winners gets a
giant sized luxury tent.]
[Ha Ha and Man Suk- third place.]
[Gary and Sang Hwa- fourth place.]
[Jong Kook and Min Jong- fifth place.]
[Suk Jin and Jung Nan- Sixth place.]
Now all the teams have finally made it.
Tonight's lodging for seventh place winners
are behind fifth place winner's lodging.
Are you talking about that pup tent?
[A very modest little tent for the team
that came in at last place.]
Seung Soo already looked drained of his
energy the moment he walked over here.
[End of this country's land,
and end of his energy.]
[Thus, the night find its way to them...]
[And everyone starts getting ready
for bed in the order of their win.]
- How is it?
- it's okay.
- I bet others are even more than okay.
- No, I just need somewhere to sleep.
How can others not be better than this?
They have to be better than this.
I guess I'm not very lucky
this year either.
Wow, this is awesome!
Awesome!
[Tent for the second place winners stands up
to the standards of any luxury hotel.]
[Beds and a wood burning stove?]
- Wow, it's really nice in here.
- This tent is like a house!
[Through Dong Jun's graciousness,
the three women will stay in this tent.]
It's almost too hot in here.
This is so nice!
What do you think?
I can't sleep without music.
What more could I want than this!
- Wow, this is kind of romantic!
- Sentimental camping.
This is romantic.
This is so nice.
What is there to life?
Gary, what is there to love?
When it comes to love...
there are no answers.
Even though I've loved for over 20 years...
I have yet to find the answers.
When it comes to love...
love is the answer.
Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo hears the music playing,
and stops by for a visit.]
- Ji Hyo.
- Wow... it's so cozy in here too.
Your two men are sleeping in here
together.
[Ji Hyo's two men?]
You are such a greedy woman.
- What's the name of this song, Gary?
- This song?
A special song just for you.
[On this rainy evening...
at the end of the earth...]
[A special song, just for you.]
This is so nice!
- Let's go camping every day!
- Don't say things like that, Ji Hyo.
I'm not ready to go to bed yet.
[Even the fifth place winner's tent
is quite warm and cozy.]
It feels like such a waste to
just go to sleep right now.
[Two more people right here
who aren't quite ready for bed yet.]
[A shot of water to help ease
away the pain of their exhaustion.]
[A shot of water...
and a tidbit of love as a chaser.]
[They really... play so well together.]
Here's a tidbit of memories.
[Their water drinking continues
for a while longer...]
[With the memories of their day together
put to bed...]
[They all drift off to dreamland
with their partners.]
[With the anticipation of
more memories to come.]
[A mafia is hidden amongst them.]
There's a mafia member hidden
amongst you.
[We are no longer friends.
We must suspect everyone!]
[The seeker, and the hider.]
[Catch the mafia!]
[A bloody battle of deceit and lies.]
[A shocking turn of events!]
[Who will be the last one left standing?]
[Next week's Running Man-
Civilians vs Mafia.]
Subtitles by DramaFever