- Is this even a fair game?
- Just look at this situation!
What the heck is this!
[A battle out on the mud field
to ring in the summer of 2014.]
[A hardcore neighborhood fight-
There can only be one victorious team.]
[Running Man Idol Wars]
[Summer 2014- A random farm field]
We can handle you going faster.
[Riding on a tractor with
the summer wind blowing on their faces.]
I wonder what they have
planned for us today.
- No kidding.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
Because the weather has
gotten nicer now.
- Don't you think that it's still too early?
- It's the perfect weather for mud flats.
[It sure is the perfect weather
for the mud flats.]
[The same nervousness that everyone
seems to be feeling.]
Don't you think that we're going too slow?
Can't we go a little faster?
[How long will this calm and peace last for?]
- Thank you!
- Hello everyone!
[Finally arrives at their location
for the opening segment.]
Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Drive safely.
- Thank you!
- Have a great day!
You told us to come dressed in tacky clothes,
but Suk Jin's dressed better than usual today.
- What are you talking about?
- He's dressed better than usual today.
What are you talking about?
I'm a real sophisticated dresser.
- I like Gary's concept.
- Why?
What are you guys talking about?
[Fashion of the 90's.
DeMint on denim with the camel worker boots.]
- I haven't seen that look in a while.
- Don't you remember this look?
[Is this a couple fashion?
Blank Ji, the ruler of roller skating rink.]
- She was known for her partying.
- What's that? 'Idol Variety Learning Center'?
Are there going to be Idol guests?
You guys are the ultimate idols
of the rural farm lands.
- So it's us?
- You're saying we're the idols?
Yes, that's right.
We are the idols.
[Rural farm land's number one idol group-
Running Man.]
A group of city idols have challenged you
to a battle for your current title.
I have heard that
they have just arrived on scene.
- Really? They're here?
- Is that what they took down from the city?
Who is it?
- What is this?
- What's this all about?
- This is an old song.
- Kim Gun Mo isn't in that van, is he?
- No way.
- No way, I doubt that he's here.
[Just who could it be?]
Don't act like you're all that cool!
- Is it Chan Sung?
- No, it's SHINee!
Who is it?
[SHINee- Min Ho]
That's Chan Sung!
[2PM- Chan Sung]
[CNBLUE- Min Hyuk]
What?
Sung Gyu and Hoya?
[INFINITE- Sung Gyu and Hoya]
[B1A4- Jin Young]
[Sistar- Bora]
I think Bora alone is enough
for us today.
[Breaks out into a dance out of the blue.]
- What are you guys doing?
- You guys look weird!
- What is all that?
No, this is how you're supposed to dance.
This is the way you do it!
[A nineties style dance.]
[Rural idols are feeling the groove.]
[An age gap that cannot be crossed.]
[The Rural Idol Group feels energized
by their sudden dance moves.]
[City Idol Group feels energized
by their edgy group fashion.]
Hello, I'm SHINee's Min Ho.
He's the most competitive one
out of them all.
He may greet everyone with that
sweet and innocent look on his face
but he's nothing to mess with
once all the games start.
- Look at how red his face is getting.
- You know the look he gets, right?
The look Min Ho gets on his face
when he wins something?
- He is something.
- Min Ho cries whenever he loses anything.
He's not good at hiding his emotions.
Hello, I'm 2PM's Chan Sung.
It's great to be here.
Chan Sung, shouldn't you be
over on this side with us?
- I thought you were one of us!
- How can you abandon us like this?
If we're going to be honest,
Chan Sung has a really big nose too.
- What are you talking about?
- You're the other Big-nose!
Your nose is bigger than mine!
[Big-nose Brother threatens Idol Big-nose.]
Let me see your nostrils.
Wow, yours are huge!
[His nose is even bigger when
seen up close.]
Yes, he does have a big nose.
[Big-nose Chan Sung of the
next generation.]
- He looks like a younger version of Suk Jin.
- Why are you doing that to him, Suk Jin?
[Old Big-nose vs. New Big-nose]
Hello, my name is Min Hyuk from CNBLUE,
and I play the drums for the band.
- He's Song Eun's boyfriend.
- Really?
- That's her boyfriend.
- She really likes him.
[Song Eun wants Min Hyuk for herself?]
- I'm telling you that she really likes him.
- I really like her too.
- She just joined our agency too.
- She moved to his agency recently too.
Song Eun switched her agency
just for Min Hyuk.
She had to pay to get in, didn't she?
How did you know?
Hello everyone.
My name is Sung Gyu from INFINITE.
Hello, my name is Hoya from INFINITE.
- There's something very friendly about him.
- I was a very good student back in school.
Really?
Are you like me amongst your group?
No, I'm like Jae Suk of my group.
- What are you saying?
- I don't know if that's good.
[Sung Gyu seems as though he wants to
come across looking intelligent today.]
Hello, my name is Jin Young of B1A4,
and this is my first time being on the show.
- Weren't you in a movie recently?
- He was in the movie, 'The Suspicious Girl.'
But look at Jin Young's unique hairstyle.
I like it. I think that
hair would suit Gary very well.
- My haircut is very similar.
- Didn't you used to have hair like that?
I was in New York recently,
so I got a New York style haircut.
[Same hair, but a different feel.]
- And last, but not least...
- Hello, my name is Bora of Sistar.
[Middle aged idols' enthusiastic welcome.]
- It's Bora!
- Just stay focused on Bora!
We heard that you're supposed to be
an idol group yourselves or something?
- Yes, we're this village's idol group.
- A rural country village's idol group?
- We're rural village idols.
- Our group is called, 'DoA'.
- Yes, DoA.
- Ah, an acronym for City Idols?
Then our name is, SiA.
Rural Village Idols.
In that case, we've already got
Suk Jin's counterpart in that group.
- Chan Sung.
- I'll take Chan Sung.
- Ha Ha will take Sung Gyu.
- Why am I getting Ha Ha?
You just keep it down over there.
You just stay quiet
while I'm still being nice.
[Haroro's masculine terms of endearment.]
Then it's Gary and Jin Young.
I feel like there's a similarity
between Gary and Jin Young.
Maybe it's the eyes.
- And he looks like he's for Jong Kook.
- Which one?
- Hoya. Hoya is for you, Jong Kook.
- You're going to offend Min Ho.
- No, Min Ho's okay.
- Then who's Min Ho going to be for?
I'm going to take Min Ho.
[Yoo Hyuk is going to take
Idols' Mr. Capable, Min Ho?]
What are you talking about?
He's a lot like how I used to be
when I was younger.
[Just what about him
is even remotely similar?]
- I used to be very fiercely competitive.
- What are you talking about?
- Everyone has a competitive streak.
- And also...
And as for Min Hyuk, he's for Kwang Soo.
No, never mind.
There's no one for Kwang Soo right now.
[Giant Giraffe is no match for
any of the idol guests.]
- There's no Kwang Soo equivalent.
- There's no 'Kwang Soo'.
For today's race,
Rural Village Running Man Idol Team
and City Idol Team will go up against
each other in a fiercely competitive race.
We have prepared a variety of rural
athletic courses for your missions.
[Rule- Carry out the missions by completing
a variety of rural games.]
A great benefit will be given to the winning
team of each of the missions
which they will be allowed to use at the final
mission location to win the entire race
so it would be to your advantage
to make sure to win each of the missions.
Only the team that wins the final battle will
win the title of being the National Idol Team.
[Only one team will be crowned the ultimate
National Idol Team at the end of the race.]
Everyone get changed into your team uniforms
and we will get started with the first game.
[Off to their first location!]
- Oh my, it's finally started.
- It's the season of slapstick comedy.
- I didn't bring any extra underwear.
- I have no extra underwear today.
I told my manager to bring me
some extra underwear to the shoot today.
It's not the ocean mud flats.
- It's a muddy farm field.
- That's no big deal.
- It's not going to be deep at all.
- The sun is so hot out there.
Hoya hates any sort of UV rays.
[These city idols hate any sort of sunlight
tarnishing their porcelain skin.]
Be careful getting out.
- Here we go again.
- So it's that season again, isn't it?
[What is the first battle that
awaits them on this muddy field?]
Do we have to get our feet wet?
[The farm field has been transformed
into a muddy flat.]
[Even just entering the field
is a difficult feat for these city idols.]
You guys are newbies to
the muddy flats, aren't you?
We're out on this field every single year.
- This is no big deal.
- Maybe it was last summer...
But GD came on our show,
and we even made that sweet kid swear.
[GD got to experience the real meaning
of muddy farm field last summer.]
It was really bad last year.
GD laughed a lot that day
but he was laughing because
he couldn't believe the absurdity of it all.
It wasn't because he was having fun,
but because he couldn't believe the absurdity.
- Is this a first time experience for anyone?
- This is my first time being out here.
Then is this even going to be a
match for us?
You're going to end up gargling
with the muddy farm field water.
But in the case of Jin Young and Hoya
with their hair right now...
your new hair color is going to be
a beautiful shade of mud.
- Look at how we're dressed right now.
- We've all got a towel covering our heads.
Remember when GD used to have
that silver hair color?
His hair color was from being out here.
[GD's mud flat hairstyle.]
The first mission between the
City Idol and Rural Idol is
the battle of physical stamina.
[City idol vs Rural idol- First mission.
Battle of physical stamina.]
[Pampered city idols' response of dread.]
- You don't seem very confident?
- No, I feel very confident!
- Min Ho's the only one excited about this.
- I feel very confident!
- This is a tough first battle to open with.
- Min Ho's always confident.
- What's poor Sung Gyu going to do?
- I've been working out lately.
- Sung Gyu's been doing cross fit fitness.
- How long have you been doing it for?
- Two months, I mean, one month.
You should've been doing it for the past year.
A month isn't going to be good enough.
He actually lives in the same building as me,
and he's rumored to be a table tennis maniac.
- Table tennis?
- You just stay quiet.
You just stay quiet.
[You just stay quiet.
I'm trying to look after you.]
He was trying to look after you just now.
If you're going to look after him,
then do a better job of doing it.
If I feed you a line,
you should learn how to accept it.
Then you should do a better job
of feeding me better lines.
[The two teams' fierce battle of the wits.]
Before we get started on the mission
we have prepared a light game
that will help us get started.
This game is called, 'Human rice building'.
- Do you all see the starting flag?
- Yes.
The runners will all run towards the flag
and all the members will create a hurdle
with your own bodies
for your team members to hop over.
Winning will be determined by how well you
form your hurdles for the jumper on your team.
So the team that makes it back across
the starting line first
will be given a great advantage
which will benefit the whole team.
Who's going to be the jumper on our team?
- Why don't we have Gary do it?
- Me?
- Gary's fast.
- Okay, we'll have Gary do it.
But how about we have Kwang Soo do it
since you have to be able to jump high?
- Yes, I think Kwang Soo will be better.
- Okay, then Kwang Soo can do it.
[Giant Kwang Soo is chosen
to be the jumper on their team.]
[Competitive Min Ho's eager demonstration.]
We can do that too!
[Fine, let's see you try!]
[Giraffe demonstrates with his whole body.]
[Their mental battle is proving fierce
right from the start of the game.]
Don't let your feet sink into the mud.
[Big-nose alone demonstrates the beauty
of slapstick comedy.]
I've already told you that the winning team
will be given a great advantage.
- Yes.
- Okay, everyone get ready.
[On the other hand, Rural Idols falter
from the start with the Blank Ji hurdle.]
[Impala hurdle isn't able to endure
the weight of the jumping Giraffe.]
[Kwang-Toad has already become
the Mud-Toad after only three hurdles.]
[This time, Yoo Hyuk hurdle
proves to be too high for him.]
[Faulty hurdles... and even faultier jumper.]
[On the other hand, Min Ho forges on
at a speed equivalent to being on dry land.]
[City idol already grabs their flag
with an amazing gap in the lead.]
[Kwang Soo on the other hand is fighting
a lone battle with the muddy waters.]
This isn't even a game!
[Even his own team members are
berating him for his poor skills.]
[Falls back down as if being pulled
to the mud by a magnetic force.]
Kwang Soo, your pants are falling off!
[Kwang-Toad shedding his skin.]
Laughter is good and all,
but we still have to play the game too!
[Even if he tried to catch up now...]
[City Idols win with ease.]
[Rural Idols lose face
on their own home ground.]
- Can we do another round of something else?
- How about a relay race?
- Relay race?
- Yes, let's do a relay race.
[Members of Rural Idol Team are suggesting
another round of a different game.]
How about a round of name tag elimination?
But we just won this game!
- We just won!
- Hear us out for a minute.
Okay, fine. We'll accept your proposal since
we're probably going to win this too anyway.
- Okay!
- That's our Bora!
- That's so cool of her!
- Why are you choosing for us?
Just look at the condition they're in!
- Our condition?
- What's wrong with the condition we're in?
[Sorry guys!]
- When is Suk Jin going to go?
- Why are you asking that? You gunning for me?
- So that he can go up against Chan Sung.
- I'll go third.
- What about you, Ha Ha?
- When is Sung Gyu going to go?
- I'm going fourth.
- Come up to the first.
Min Ho, Kwang Soo says he wants to
go up against you again.
- Seriously, Kwang Soo!
- I'll bet my whole fortune!
Kwang Soo,
I'll bet my whole fortune on it too.
- Okay, good!
- Kwang Soo has nothing but debt.
I'm going to pass all my debts
over to you.
Okay, here are the rules.
The runner has to go around the flag
- and there will be no throwing of the flags.
- Okay, we understand.
Especially, no running without a baton
will be allowed whatsoever.
- Gary, did you hear that?
- Yes, I know that!
Do you think that I'm stupid or something?
- You think I'll actually do that again?
- It's still so vivid in my mind.
Okay, is everyone ready?
- I'm going to do this for real.
- I'm doing this for real.
Ready!
[First runners- Ha Ha vs Sung Gyu.]
[Wow, Haroro is fast!]
[No!]
[What do you mean, no?]
[Quite the gap between the two.]
[Rural Idol Team's second runner, Gary,
gets on his way.]
[Jin Young from City Idol Team
starts off soon thereafter.]
[Running Gary... and crawling Jin Young.]
Jin Young!
[Jin Young finally finds
both his balance and his feet.]
[Rural Idol Team's third runner, Big-nose.]
[Starts his slapstick comedy routine
the moment the baton touches his hand.]
[Hope shines for the City Idols
thanks to Big-nose Brother's faltering.]
[City Idol Team's third runner, Chan Sung.]
[New Big-nose, Chan Sung,
closes the gap in the blink of an eye.]
[New Big-nose's amazing speed.
Old Big-nose has nothing on him.]
[Chan Sung succeeds in taking over the lead.]
What are you doing?
[City Idol Team's fourth runner,
Min Hyuk, receives the baton.]
What are you doing, Suk Jin!
[Rural Idol Team's fourth runner,
Jae Suk, finally receives the baton.]
[City Idol Team is already onto
their fifth runner, Bora.]
[Bora runs fast enough to have
the hat flying off of her head.]
Hurry!
[Runners still waiting for their turn are
getting frustrated with their teammates.]
[Is there some honey slathered onto
the bottom of the muddy field?]
[In the meantime, Bora is already making
her way around the halfway point.]
[It's almost a full lap's worth of gap
between the two teams now.]
[Rural Idol Team's fifth runner, Blank Ji.]
[Big-nose Brother's interference tactics.]
[But Blank Ji, true to her nickname of 'Ace',
is already about to round the halfway point.]
[City Idol Team's sixth runner, Hoya,
starts off with ease in his steps.]
Hurry up!
[But there's still about a half a length's
worth of gap between the two teams.]
[Finally, Rural Idol Team's sixth runner...]
[The Tiger gets on his way!]
[Oh my goodness!]
[Hoya's ease evaporates as soon as
he sees the Tiger sprinting.]
[Tiger almost closes the gap between
the two teams in the blink of an eye.]
[Last runner for each team-
Kwang Soo vs Min Ho.]
[Neck and neck.]
[The outcome of this race... will
become the outcome for the entire team.]
[A race with both of the runners'
entire fortunes on the line.]
[Neck and neck!
They both round the flag simultaneously.]
[Competitive Min Ho vs. Kwang-Toad.]
[Both cross the line almost simultaneously.]
[City Idol Team wins by one single step.]
[City Idol Team's second win in a row
on Rural Idol Team's home ground.]
City Idol Team has won both rounds of
the preliminary games.
As I've mentioned before
the winning team of the preliminary game will
be given a huge advantage for their use.
And here's the advantage
that they've just won.
It's the chance to disqualify
one member on the opposing team
from participating in the actual game.
[One guess as to who
that person is going to be.]
Don't you think that you should've
told us that before we started the game?
Since this is a variety show and all...
We were trying to be
considerate to the girls.
Had we known this was going to happen,
we could've done a much better job.
We could've definitely won if
we didn't have Suk Jin on our team.
What did you just say?
- But you proposed this in the first place.
- But you still should've told us first.
You can't tell us to disqualify a member.
No, I can't do that!
[Muddy face washing of rage!]
What are you trying to do to us right now!
[An unbelievable amount of dedication
in the name of winning the race.]
- He said dunk your face, and we can do it.
- Do what?
[Tiger is also given a muddy face wash.]
Just dunk your face in.
But since rules are still rules,
as long as City Idols are okay with it
we can allow Ji Hyo to be the one to stay out
of the game since this is a strenuous game.
- We can allow Ji Hyo to sit this one out.
- In that case, how about Suk Jin instead?
- Yes, I'm not in the best health.
- But Suk Jin is our best winning card.
I'd like to see Jong Kook dunk his
head in just one more time.
- If he does...
- But I already did it!
I'll dunk him a hundred times
if that's what you want me to do.
- Let's show them what we can do.
- Let's show them!
[City Idol Team uses their advantage to
disqualify Blank Ji from participating.]
I've never seen Jong Kook get
humiliated like that before!
I will make you regret ever
having angered me.
Okay, here's the first round of
the real official games.
The game will be played in the same method
as you played the strength battle.
But the only difference is, once
you've pushed everyone off the platform
you have to place the weaved basket on your
opposing team's side in order to win the game.
The weaved baskets will be holding
your snacks later on.
- Are you all hungry?
- Yes, we're hungry.
All the snacks will be put into
the winning team's weaved basket.
Hoya, Jin Young and Sung Gyu cannot be left
to go back home with their current hair color.
We're not going to go easy on you guys.
[Dye their hair in the color
of this muddy water?]
- Sung Gyu, what are you doing?
- Just dunk your hands in there!
I was just trying to see.
[Gets his hair dyed before
the game even starts.]
[Did Chan Sung just push me in the water?]
[Half disbelief, and half rage-
Sung Gyu bursts out in laughter.]
If he wasn't my senior...
[If only he wasn't his senior...]
[Sung Gyu definitely has a flair
for the variety show.]
Okay, time to start the game!
Ready, set, go!
[Muddy farm field battle of strength- Go!]
[Tiger proposes a battle of one on one.]
You want to try, don't you, Jin Young?
- I think he wants to try.
- Jin Young.
[Me?]
I've always been curious as to how strong
he really is from having seen him on TV.
[City boy, Jin Young, is curious to find out
the full extent of the Tiger's power.]
Just come at me right now.
[Is this what Jin Young is really like?]
[City boy, Jin Young, shows off
some real slapstick comedy.]
I'm embarrassed for you.
[Jin Young's ability to bring about laughter
is as big as the level of his curiosity.]
- That was funny.
- Sung Gyu, want to give it a try?
- With you?
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's do it.
- You said you were going to pick Chan Sung.
Chan Sung is too much for me.
I'm not going to be that easy either.
- Look at how bright he looks.
- What did you say that you're doing lately?
[A fierce battle of mental games
while warming up their bodies.]
Suk Jin's been working out lately too.
- Show him what you can do, Suk Jin.
- Show him your strength, Suk Jin.
You're still pretty lively.
Am I a grandfather?
What do you mean, I'm still pretty lively?
No, he's still very lively.
What is he saying right now?
- Suk Jin is very lively.
- I can't believe he said that.
He won't have any problems with this.
See if you can take him down.
He's only old enough to be your father.
[Sung Gyu bulldozes on.]
[Big-nose withstands to counterattack.]
- Flip him over.
- Sung Gyu!
[Lively Big-nose throws Sung Gyu
off the platform.]
[This is Running Man's weakest link,
Big-nose's power!]
[Come and get me!]
[How can this be...]
- How could you have let that happen?
- I'm in shock right now myself.
I had no idea that I'd lose.
[I had no idea that I'd lose...]
You have to be careful of Gary,
and just get rid of Ha Ha and Kwang Soo.
- Watch out for Gary and Jong Kook.
- You have no idea how strong Kwang Soo is.
Kwang Soo is really strong.
You have no idea how strong Kwang Soo is.
[Kwang Soo steps off the platform to
hand Ji Hyo the weaved basket.]
[City Idol Team adamantly argues
that Kwang Soo is out of the game.]
Lee Kwang Soo, out!
[No matter what the case, he's out of the game
from having stepped off the platform.]
[The weakest elimination in the
history of this game.]
[I just wanted to have both my hands free
to fight against the other team.]
You guys, watch out for Suk Jin!
What are you doing, Suk Jin?
- I've got something in my sock.
- That's not what's important right now!
But it hurts!
[Old Big-nose... always very unpredictable.]
[A fierce battle position.]
Are you guys that scared?
[City Idol Team initiates the attack.]
[But Rural Idol Team
is not to be messed with!]
[Min Hyuk- Out!]
[Jin Young- Out!]
[Two members of City Idol Team
are eliminated in the blink of an eye.]
[Chan Sung is buried underneath
the human pile.]
[But his team members don't have the courage
to rescue him and only retreat.]
He's still down there!
I can't stretch my legs like that!
- That really hurts!
- Then give up, Chan Sung.
[Chan Sung screams out in pain
from his awkward position.]
[Bora grabs the Tiger by his hair
in an attempt to save Chan Sung.]
[City Idol Team's Joan of Arc, Bora.]
[Tiger is knocked out.]
[This is our chance!]
[Min Ho ambushes the throng of people!]
[Hoya tries to ambush,
but gets pushed off the platform instead.]
[Chan Sung- Out!]
[Min Ho and Bora are the only two left.]
[Tiger in her right hand...
and Haroro in her left.]
[Joan of Arc,
Bora's pivotal role in the game.]
Let's just go down together.
[Min Ho and Jae Suk are
ousted simultaneously.]
[With the exception of Bora,
every other City Idol member is ousted.]
[Joan of Arc, Bora, also gets ousted
after having given it her best shot.]
[Mud farm field battle of strength-
Rural Idol Team wins.]
You have no idea how good we are
when it comes to this game.
[The power of Rural Idol Team is proven
through this muddy game.]
[A feast of snacks fit for a king
for Rural Idol Team for winning the game.]
You cannot share your snacks
with the team that lost the game.
That's really too bad.
They played really hard too.
How do you open this thing?
Seriously!
No, I got it.
I said, I got it.
Right of choice!
Although I don't know what this is for,
I'm just going to be happy about it.
[Big-nose Brother is still battling
it out with his drink bottle.]
I think it means that
we get first choice of something.
[Big-nose Brother must've been very thirsty.]
[Off to their next location!]
Who doesn't have any sunscreen on?
- But the sun's already gone down.
- But you still need to put some on.
You burn more when the sun is like this.
- It's in a mousse form.
- Wow.
- This has a cooling sensation.
- Can you put some on me yourself?
- Where? Let me see.
- I'll put it on for you.
[Cheesy Min Ho steps forward.]
- You're grossing me out. I didn't mean you.
- I'll do it. I can put some on you.
I was told to put it onto your skin.
But this really does have
a cooling sensation, doesn't it?
But when it comes to strength based
battle like that...
How can we ever beat them when they've
got Jong Kook on their team?
- We actually did do pretty good.
- Yes, we did.
But there's one person on our team
who's our main cause of defeat.
- Who, it's not Bora.
- No, it's Sung Gyu!
I see something over there.
[Arrives at their second location
for Idol Experience Training Race.]
Is this an amusement park?
More than anything else, Jing Young
and Min Hyuk look so happy right now.
The expression on both their faces are
so different than what they were before.
- Jin Young, you were seriously so funny.
- What do you think of Jong Kook now?
Someone told me recently
that Jong Kook is actually pretty small
when you see him in person.
- Who told you that?
- Just someone I know.
If you say who that person is,
then that person is going to end up dead.
Don't ever tell who that person is.
Just take that information to the grave!
[Keeping the identity a secret is a must!]
- That person really would be dead.
- My body is actually pretty slim.
[Look at him closely,
and he's actually quite slim?]
If you follow this path
and go over the hill you'll come across
five different adventure courses.
You can go and pick and choose which of
the five courses you'd like to do on your own.
Once you complete the course
you've chosen
then you'll get a special stamp on your hand
to verify that you've completed the course.
You need to collect three stamps as a team
to win this mission.
If you feel that you can't do a certain one,
then you're allowed to leave that course.
- Is that understood?
- Okay.
[I will make sure to win this time!]
[Idol Experience Training Race's Big Five.]
[Rural Idol Team's method is to separate
into two teams to divide and conquer.]
[Only one stamp is given out for any given
course, so only one team can win that course.]
Should we give it a try?
[One of the courses is discovered.]
What's this?
[Water dipper experience.]
- Scoop up the water to wash the dishes?
- What is this?
What you see to your right is a tool called,
'Yong-Durae' (Water dipper).
It's a tool used to irrigate the water from
low level ground to high level ground.
The dishes that you see in front of you
got very muddy because a lady from town fell
while bringing back your snack dishes.
No, this looks like you guys swished it around
in a huge puddle of dirt and mud.
What are you talking about?
This looks like you guys purposely did this.
This course is for you to use this
water dipping tool
to help out with the washing
of these dishes.
Once all the dishes are clean,
you'll find something written on the dishes.
If you configure the letters around,
you'll find either a six letter word
or an eight letter word from
these two pile of dishes.
[First team to figure out the word by washing
the dishes first wins this course.]
- We have to hurry.
- Set, go!
[Letter puzzle- Start.]
[Huh?]
This is hard.
[But why is the water splashing backwards?]
[The farming tools are so foreign
to these city idol boys.]
[Rural Idol members, on the other hand,
show off their real strength.]
Just accept the water shower.
[Are they washing dishes,
or giving Ha Ha a bath?]
- No, we have to really scoop it out.
- That's how we need to do it.
Wait, that's really cold.
One, two, three.
[Didn't they all just recently
shower and get cleaned off?]
We need more water over here.
We need more water in our tub.
[Just as soaked as he was
during their previous mission.]
- Nothing?
- No, nothing.
Look at me.
What is this?
Why am I being made to do this again
when I just got cleaned off after the field?
How many pairs of underwear
do I need to start traveling with?
But this is clean water.
I just had to buy my last pair
from the convenience store.
Seriously.
[City Idol Team has perfected
a method of their own.]
[They need to find a letter written
on some of these dishes.]
Do you see a letter?
- Look on the inside of the dish.
- I see a letter right here.
- What is it?
- It's 'Ri'.
Grab another dish.
You have to catch the water with the dish.
- You're the one who's not doing this right.
- Hurry up and grab the dish.
- Switch. Switch spots with me.
- You're not doing this right.
- Flip the dish over.
- No, switch spots with me.
- No, I found it! I found a letter!
- What is it?
[Ru]
[Must complete piecing the word together
in order to pass this course.]
[The more letters they can find,
the easier it'll be to figure out the word.]
- I found it!
- What is it?
'Al'.
- 'Ru' and 'Al'.
- 'Ru' and 'Al'?
Al-Ru?
Aluminum?
[Soaked... and soaked again.]
[Continue to get soaked
until they figure out the word.]
- What do you think of this one?
- Nice!
- What the heck is that?
This is the black goat experience course.
The caretaker has asked us to attach
the name tags on the goats
because they have a natural tendency
to run off from where they're supposed to be.
Please name four of the goats,
and put these name tags on those goats.
[Put name tags around the necks of
four of the goats in the pen.]
- Are they nice?
- Is there a way to call them over to you?
- Feed them the grass they like.
- Oh, feed them some grass?
[Lure the goats over by offering them
some grass for them to eat.]
What should we name them?
Since there are four of us here,
let's name them after each one of us.
No, that's a great idea.
Let's just name them after us.
Kkyu for Sung Gyu.
- Hi guys. Come here.
- I'll go over to the other side.
[Name the goats- Start.]
[Who's here?]
They're so cute.
- Come on, let's eat.
- Come here, I got you some food.
[Tries to lure them over by offering them
grass as they were told to do.]
[An intelligent family of goats.]
- They can't run away from us.
- Why are they running away from us?
- Want some food?
- Come on!
[These goats are proving to be
much faster than expected.]
Come over here.
You're so cute!
Come on, little cutie.
I've decided to go with you.
Come on and eat your food.
- They're not even paying us any attention.
- Come on! Wow, they're way too fast!
[Come and get me!]
Wow, they're way too fast.
[While these four are busy trying to
catch their goats...]
- We have to dig up 500g of ginseng.
- There's ginseng in this field?
- How much is 500g?
- Is there really ginseng out on this field?
- Does it have to be exactly 500g?
- 500g or more.
If it's 500g...
Two chicken breasts weigh 400g.
Why do you compare everything
to chicken breasts?
Wow, this definitely is a form of exercise.
I can feel my muscles working.
Jong Kook, are you actually happy
about this?
Wow, I'm getting a workout.
If I had a servant like Jong Kook,
then my life would be so much easier.
Why don't Jong Kook and Kwang Soo keep
digging with a hoe in each hand?
If you grab one in each hand
and drag it down the field like this
to create a couple of rows...
Ji Hyo, you're not by any chance
thinking that I'm an ox, are you?
Jong Kook, you can definitely do
the work of an ox.
You're not thinking that I'm
an ox, are you?
[And over here,
we've got a water loving hippo.]
[Or... a water flogged Ha Ha.]
Don't avoid the water.
Just sit still and catch the water.
I found another letter.
'Peu'.
- 'Ru', 'Al', and 'Peu'.
- Rudolph?
- Alps Rudolph?
['Bu', 'Ri', and Hung'.
This team also has three letters found.]
I see one.
'Pe'.
Let's see if we can figure it out.
[The fourth letter for Rural Idol Team?]
'Room'.
Come on, let's keep going.
[Rural Idol Team- A six letter word.
City Idol Team- Eight letter word.]
[Only two letter left to find for
Rural Idol Team.]
- 'Ku'!
- Huh?
- 'Ku'?
- We just need one more letter.
['Ru', 'Al', Peu', Room', and 'Ku'.]
['Bu', 'Pe', 'Ri', and 'Hung'.]
Hungary buffet?
- Is it something we know?
- Yes, you'll definitely know what it is.
- Is it, 'ku'?
- Yes, it is.
Kuala Lumpur!
- Kuala Lumpur!
- That has to be it!
[Capitol of Malaysia, Kuala Lumpur?]
[Correct answer.]
[How can this be...]
Good job!
The other team was pretty close to
figuring it out too.
Budapest!
[Correct answer for City Idol Team-
Hungary Budapest.]
Rural Idol Team wins the stamp
for the water digger course.
Team Running Man wins this course,
and the course is now closed.
You guys had better run
over to your next course.
[City Idol Team is off
to their next course location.]
You need a total of three from the whole team,
so you only need two more stamps.
- You guys can go off to something else now.
- You did great on this.
- Great job.
- You did all the hard work, Ha Ha.
[These group of city idols are still busy
chasing after the goats with the name tags.]
[Runs here... and runs there...
but it still remains impossible.]
- They're way too fast.
- Let's give up on this one.
- You want to give up on this one?
- Let's just give it up.
- Let's just go somewhere else.
- They're just way too fast.
[No match for their speed,
and decides to give up on this course.]
Let's just go off to another course.
Hey, don't worry about me,
and just go on ahead of me.
[Why would we worry?]
I'm totally exhausted right now.
Let's just go off to another course.
[The ginseng field that's been left
abandoned by Ox Jong Kook.]
What?
- Should we at least give it a try?
- We have to try it no matter what it is.
Wow, do you think there are
any out here?
- I'm going to dig up every single one.
- You mean it, right?
I'll show you what a human digger
looks like.
[Enthusiastic digging.]
Am I digging deep enough?
- Are there any out here?
- I really don't see any.
Ginseng!
[It's ginseng!]
[Black hole Sung Gyu finds the first ginseng!]
- Good job!
- I did it!
[How much does that one piece weigh?]
This one only weighs 50g.
- What the heck is that?
- We need to find ten weighing this size.
[500g seems such a long way to go.]
[Hopeless...]
[This team is on their way to the next location
after having won the water stamp.]
[More water!]
- Let's just do it.
- It's like a pond.
Are those loaches?
- They look like loaches.
- This always happens when I'm with you.
[Loach catching-
Catch 1k worth of loaches or more.]
[1k worth of loaches!]
Wow, I bet this is going to be
a ton of fun!
We're the only ones here.
[Muddy face wash in the morning...]
[And a water shower as soon as he gets
changed into clean clothes.]
[And before his can even dry out his clothes,
now he has to catch loaches.]
[He doesn't even have anymore
clean underwear to change into.]
- Hey, what's this?
- This pen is full of pigs.
[Baby pigs.]
It's a mission from the pigs' caretaker.
Do you see the other pig pen
below us right now?
He's asked us to move all the pigs to the pen
below to get these pigs out of the wind.
Do you see the pigs with the ribbons
tied around their legs?
Once you move seven of these pigs with
the ribbons tied around their legs
then you succeed this course.
I'm not good at touching things like this.
- Do you know how to grab them?
- I've never touched a pig before.
[First encounter with a pig for
these city idols.]
Hey guys.
[Oldest of the group, Chan Sung,
gathers up his courage to grab the first one.]
I have to move you guys to somewhere else.
[Two at once?]
Can you hand one to me?
[The younger guys asks to be handed one
from outside the pen.]
No, you guys get one for yourselves.
I'm sorry!
Move only one at a time.
Grab only one at a time.
[Hands one off to Jin Young.]
Calm down, you guys.
Just calm down.
[Hoya nervously enters
the first pig pen of his life.]
I'll move you to a much better place.
I don't know if I can touch it.
Here, I've got some food here for you.
Look, there's food.
[Chan Sung succeeds in moving
one of the seven pigs.]
You have to hold it closer to you.
[Jin Young also runs as fast as he can
with the pig in his hands.]
I feel like I don't even know
if I'm still alive.
[This new house is pretty nice.]
- I found one!
- He found one!
[Successfully finds their fourth ginseng.]
- Hey, Min Ho.
- Yeah?
[Min Hyuk is the only one who has
yet to find one.]
You have to get the feel for it.
You can usually feel out the right spot.
Should I dig with both of these?
[Goes wherever the hoes take him?]
I found one!
[Amazing!
He really finds one!]
How many have we found so far?
- Wow, that's amazing.
- I have to find one too.
There's a reason why the other team gave up.
How in the world are we going to find ten?
I found one!
[He finds another one!]
[Min Ho succeeds in finding one
everywhere he digs.]
I think this is the sweet spot.
[And one person who's starting to
feel more and more anxious.]
[Oh? Did he finally find his first one?]
No, it's just a potato.
[It's a potato.]
I thought I found one,
but it's just another potato.
- What's wrong with you?
- I don't know how... it's another potato!
[Another potato... and another potato.]
[And he continued to find more
and more potatoes even thereafter.]
Why am I the only one
who can't seem to find any?
[Wow, that's a lot of digging they did.]
I found one!
[It's fitting somehow that Sung Gyu
finds one the size of a bellflower root.
That one weighs 10g.
[The result of all their digging...]
[Currently weight- 450g.
Only 50 more grams to go!]
[If they can just find one more
larger sized ginseng!]
[Rage filled digging!]
[Just then...]
No, could it be?
Is it?
[That's...]
I found one!
I found a real ginseng!
[He finally finds one!]
We found them all!
[Persistent Min Hyuk finally gets it done!]
There are two!
I actually found two!
Don't look for anymore.
No, don't dig around for anymore.
[It looks like it would be big enough...]
[Will it surpass the 500g mark?]
Okay!
[City Idol Team succeeds in completing
the ginseng field course!]
I knew that you could do it.
[We're proud of you, Kang Min Hyuk.]
He even found us a big pile of potatoes.
[Persistent Min Hyuk receives the stamp
as the representative for their group.]
Don't forget to give me my potatoes.
- Let's take all these ginsengs too.
- Here, add it to this basket.
I'm curious to see how much
all these potatoes weigh.
- This is what a victory feels like.
- Is there something down this path?
[This pig daddy is moving his babies
as quickly as he can to their new pen.]
Are you guys doing okay?
[Moving of two pigs at once
is now seemingly pretty stable.]
- We did it.
- How many are there?
- There are only five.
- We need to move seven.
[Total of seven are needed-
Succeeds in moving five of seven.]
Okay, I'm moving you to a less windy place,
so just hang on for a little bit longer.
Okay?
[Seven ribbon tied pigs for City Idols,
and seven ribbon free pigs for Rural Idols.]
Jong Kook.
[Rural Idols succeed in moving five at once.]
- We need to hurry!
- Stop Kwang Soo!
Jong Kook!
[If Kwang Soo succeeds in moving these two,
then Rural Idols win this course.]
We just need Kwang Soo to move his.
[Chan Sung is working hard to move
his last two pigs all at once.]
But it's too windy up here.
[In the meantime, Rural Idols are working
together to move their last two pigs.]
[At this rate, Rural Idols may lose again...]
[The goal is to move seven.
Rural Idols succeed in moving six of seven.]
[Chan Sung barely succeeds in grabbing
two pigs at once.]
[Both teams just need to get their
last cargo into the pen...]
[Kkuk succeeds in moving
the final baby pig into the pen.]
[Pig pen course- Rural Idols wins the stamp.]
[Completely exhausted.]
Guys.
This is a safer place for you guys.
- That's right, you guys.
- You guys could've caught a cold up there.
- We rescued you guys from getting sick.
- That's right.
- See? You've got lots of food here.
- And this pen is much bigger too.
That was my first time catching pigs.
[Still bewildered from his
first encounter with the pigs.]
- If I grabbed one just a little quicker.
- You guys worked really hard back there.
- Chan Sung.
[Pig daddy is still exhausted from having
moved five of the seven pigs.]
[Three stamps is the goal,
and Rural Idols succeeded in getting two.]
[After having failed the pig catching,
this team comes over to catch the loaches.]
We have to catch something again?
[Even though they keep losing,
their persistence is still very commendable.]
[Another first of catching loaches.]
Chan Sung, you've never
done this before, have you?
You all grew up so delicately like
an indoor plant in the city.
First, you have to corner the loaches.
[Yoo Hyuk acts like he know what he's doing
and gives them a lesson on how to catch.]
You have to corner them by
swishing your feet around like this.
[Demonstrates how loach catching is done.]
See?
I just caught two.
Here, give them to me.
No, I was just showing you how to do it.
[Steals the loaches that Jae Suk just caught.]
Professional loach catchers
never rush.
- I think I just caught one.
- Here's another one right here.
I don't think you caught any.
No, you didn't catch any.
[Mr. Gary, who seems to fit right in
at this muddy field...]
[A whole basket full!]
Can I weigh them to see
how much I've got so far?
- What's the weight so far?
- We need to catch like 20 more.
[All those loaches still only weighs 500g,
and their goal is to catch 1k worth.]
Ha Ha, go to the local supermarket
and buy us a couple of mackerels.
We can try to pass them off as loaches.
[When are they ever going to catch
a whole 20k worth of loaches?]
Ugh, seriously. How are
we ever going to catch them all?
- Guys.
- Yes?
- You guys have to get this done.
- Why?
- Aren't you going to go somewhere else?
- There's nowhere else to go.
[No more courses for them to go to.]
Ugh, seriously!
Why don't you start from down here
instead of doing all that?
Mister, are you the owner of
this muddy pond?
- I know how to catch loaches.
- Let's keep up the good work!
- Start from way down here.
- We're professional loach catchers.
How about one of you hold onto the basket
and another person push them in there?
[One is telling them to do this,
and another is telling them to do another.]
Who the heck are you, Mister?
- I'm someone who knows how to catch them.
- You guys are all over the place without me.
- Ugh, seriously.
- Do I need to coach you on how to do it?
- Do you need me to guide you?
- Seriously.
- Just listen to what I'm telling you.
- Just stick in one place and dig.
One of you can corner them,
and Jae Suk wait there with your basket.
[They end up doing
as Big-nose tells them to do.]
[There you go!]
[I don't see any?]
Jae Suk.
Why don't you just stop?
- No way.
- Yeah, we got it all.
- We got it all.
- What the heck!
- We already got two stamps.
- We got it done a while ago.
[They were just playing with them
after having completed the whole mission?]
It was nice to see you guys
working so hard.
[Completely... bewildered.]
You guys looked like you were having
so much fun catching the loaches.
- Show them all your stamp marks.
- You guys are the best loach catchers.
[Water digger, pig catching, and where else?]
Come here, goats. We'll go
after we get these name tags on you.
[It's the goat name tag course that
the city idols had previously abandoned!]
[Calmly puts the name tag around
the necks of four goats.]
- We really are good at this.
- There you go. You're all set.
[Even goat, 'Blank Ji',
gets her name tag necklace.]
It took us less than two minutes
to complete that course.
- We cornered them all.
- You're kidding us, right?
You have to hold them with
your hands.
Use your heads.
Did you do the whole course by yourself?
[Seriously, Suk Jin...]
Seriously, I can't listen to you anymore.
Did you do it all by yourself or something?
How many goats did you get?
Nothing.
I helped corner them all.
- You guys all tried so hard.
- You grew up too delicately in the city.
This is the force of Running Man.
Don't you think that we're at a disadvantage?
This is your home ground.
- No, that's ridiculous.
- You know what Jin Young just said?
You know what Jin Young just said?
He says this is our home ground.
How is this our home ground?
It's been years since we've been
out here too.
I live in an apartment building too.
What are you talking about?
We only come out here from time to time
to film out show, but that's it.
But all our families and relatives
live in the city too.
Do you think that we actually
live out here or something?
We all live in Seoul too.
- What are you guys even saying?
- We just want you to experience what we do.
- Really?
- Yes, like dancing and such.
Then we'd definitely win those missions.
[Who are you saying is going to
win the dance competition?]
He used to be a backup dancer.
I used to be a leader of
my backup dancer group.
No, we're being serious.
- I used to dance in H.O.T too.
- Gary too.
[Even Gary is the king of dance from Jamsil.]
Hang on, let me move over there.
- That was a good move.
- I haven't done a glide in years.
[Their battle of wits continues.]
Team Running Man wins another mission.
[Rural Experience Big Five-
Rural Idols wins another chance ticket.]
Is it okay for us to keep winning like this?
- What else can we do about it?
- No, there's nothing we can do about it.
What can we do about it when we're
just too good and keep winning?
If you're going to keep talking like that,
then just give us the chance ticket.
But isn't it against the rules
to give away these tickets?
We'll exchange four kilos of our potatoes
for one of your chance tickets.
- Here, we'll swap you for it.
- You just enjoy these with Eun.
You have no idea how much
she loves potatoes.
- You just enjoy these potatoes with her.
- Will she be good with these?
- Does she know how to cook potatoes?
- Yes, she does.
[Second loss in a row-
Dejectedly heads off to their next location.]
I really have nothing to say
about my lack of contribution.
[Hoya is feeling anxious because he feels
that he still hasn't contributed much.]
- I worked as best as I could.
- But I haven't really seen him do anything.
But you're not doing all that bad.
[City Idols have yet to win
a single chance ticket.]
[They vow to win the next mission!]
[An elementary school in Ganhwado.]
Hey, Chan Sung.
You look really exhausted.
- You really do look exhausted.
- You're looking really tired.
Chan Sung looks really exhausted right now.
- No? You're okay?
- No, I'm not tired at all.
Of all the idols that Running Man members
have ever gone up against
this group is the most sluggish of them all.
[Weakest idols they've ever
been up against so far.]
You know that there's only one more
chance ticket to be won, correct?
If the Rural Idol Team takes all three tickets,
it would mean a huge difference in the game.
We don't know what'll happen either.
That's what we talked about on our way here.
We won't go easy on you at all.
We're a very merciless team.
I had no idea that he was
so formidable like this.
Formidable.
- He just looked so weak on TV.
- Why are you saying it like that, Jin Young?
I believe that the process of how it's done
is more important that the actual outcome.
But neither your process nor
the outcome has been very good so far.
- One or the other has to be good.
- I have nothing to say to that.
That's what I mean.
This next mission will be to test
your abilities to work as a team.
- When it comes to teamwork...
- Then Running Man is the best of them all.
Your next mission.
It's basketball name tag elimination.
[Basketball name tag elimination.]
I played basketball until
two in the morning last night.
- Just put your faith in me.
- Do you know what Min Ho just said?
He said he played basketball until
two in the morning last night.
[Confidence from having played basketball
until the wee hours of the morning.]
You must first find the basketballs which are
hidden in various spots throughout this place.
- You have to find them first?
- I bet Min Ho's disappointed to hear that.
He's disappointed to know that
it's not that kind of basketball.
If you search all around you
you'll find mini basketball hoops
that are set up in various spots.
You'll find them both on the inside
and outside of school.
All fourteen of your names are on
individual basketball hoops.
- Throw the basketball you find in the hoop...
- Then that person is ousted?
Yes, then that person will be ousted.
You have to plan carefully.
Even though it's important to throw the ball
you find into these basket hoops
know that you can also steal the ball in
rebound and put it in your opponent's goal.
Okay, this is a battle of rebounds.
We have to come up with a plan first.
Find out where our opponent's goals are
while we search for the balls
and play defense to our own goals so that
they don't score on us and eliminate us.
Let's keep each other updated on
where these goals are located.
Since we need to defend our own goals too,
we have to eliminate our strongest opponents.
[Eliminate their strongest opponents first.]
- We can't let them steal our ball.
- And defend your own goal.
This isn't going to be easy.
Basketball name tag elimination... start!
- Kwang Soo!
- Push them out of the way!
- Where's Min Ho?
- He's behind us right now.
[Off to find the balls and
the opponent's goal post.]
Min Ho's climbing up two steps at a time.
[The basketballs are hidden both inside
and outside of the school building.]
The balls could be hidden all throughout
places like this, right?
Where are all the balls?
There's Gary's hoop over there.
[Discovers Gary's hoop.]
Here's Sung Gyu's hoop.
We just need to find a ball to oust him.
[Discovers Sung Gyu's hoop
on the ground floor.]
- Sung Gyu.
- Sung Gyu? Okay.
[Important to remember where each
of their hoops are hidden.]
Who's that?
Who's name is up there?
- Who is it?
- Chan Sung and Kwang Soo.
[Right next to one another.]
[Blocking his own hoop like
a wall of bricks.]
If I were the ball,
where would I be hiding?
[Since they've found most of the hoops,
it's now time to seriously look for the balls.]
The balls are way too small.
Hey, I don't see any balls.
I know.
I wonder if they're all outside.
[They won't be able to oust anyone
without these balls...]
No, they're basketballs.
[Jin Young is searching through
the kitchen on the first floor.]
[A basketball is finally found!]
[Hides it underneath his jacket.]
This is ridiculous.
[Finds a basketball in the recycling bin.]
- Ji Hyo's hoop is over there.
- Where's Jong Kook's hoop?
[I'm going to make all the goals.]
[Chan Sung must hurry over to his opponent's
hoop before the ball is stolen away from him.]
[Jin Young rushes along with
his own ball under his jacket.]
Chan Sung!
[His goal is Kwang Soo's hoop.]
[He must make the goal in order
to oust Kwang Soo.]
[They must be stopped!]
[Right into Kwang Soo's hoop!]
I found that ball.
[I should've been quicker about
getting here for the rebound...]
We can't have Kwang Soo be ousted.
Lee Kwang Soo, out!
- What just happened?
- Lee Kwang Soo, out.
- Why is it me of all people!
Why does it have to be me!
Who did this!
- Kwang Soo!
- Who did it? Who got me ousted?
I feel so sad!
Why is it me of all people?
[Giant center, Lee Kwang Soo,
is the first one to get ousted.]
Is it really me?
Wow, they found that one quick.
There aren't even any cameras in here.
[No cameras in the jail cell.]
I wanted to show off my basketball skills.
I should've guarded my own hoop.
Jong Kook's hoop is on the second floor!
[City Idols are working together as a team.]
Is it that one?
[Jae Suk's hoop is Chan Sung's target.]
Let's oust Jae Suk.
Where did you find your ball?
Min Ho, have you found any balls?
- I don't see any balls.
- Yoo Jae Suk, out.
[There's a ball inside your very own hoop.]
- What the heck!
[Rural Idol Team in a state of panic.]
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
Michael Jordon has just been ousted.
Ugh, I'm seriously about to lose my mind.
[Two members of the Rural Idol Team
gets ousted in the blink of an eye.]
How did they find the balls so quickly?
[Throwing the name tag of the fallen
carelessly down to the ground.]
Why are you treating our name tags like that?
[Side by side...]
[Jin Young, the one responsible for
having ousted Kwang Soo.]
[He finds another ball!]
[Rural Idol Team has yet to find
their first ball.]
[Jin Young hides the ball
in the back this time around.]
[Discovers Jin Young with the hidden ball.]
[Is he planning on stealing
Jin Young's ball away?]
What do you have?
No!
He needs to be stopped!
- Give me the ball.
- Stop right there!
[Must play defense!]
Gary!
Stop Min Ho!
Gary, you have to stop Min Ho!
[Jong Kook's tightly guarded hoop.]
[Min Ho's target!]
[Ace Min Ho's full power attack.]
[Min Ho now validates himself
as the ace of this basketball mission.]
Kim Jong Kook, out.
Ha Ha, out.
Why can't anyone on our team
find any balls?
[Amazing City Idol Team!
They're about to oust all the RM members!]
- You should've stopped them by grabbing.
- I did grab them, but I lost.
Jordon's just been ousted.
I, Michael Jordon, have been ousted.
- I'm Charles Barkley.
- I'm Kobe Bryant.
This one is Han Ki Bum.
[One hundred percent in
likeliness of Han Ki Bum.]
- Han Ki Bum was a great player.
- Yes, he was a very great player.
[Han Ki Bum would be more offended
by the Kwang Soo comparison.]
Jong Kook is more like
Coach Moon Kyung Eun.
[Similar Rambo style.]
We have to oust Min Ho fast.
I think that's it.
I think that's it over there.
[Suspicious looking mound of sand.]
[Has Gary found something?]
[From a mound of sand...
is a buried treasure.]
He found one.
Guys, come on!
Hey, he found one!
We have to steal his ball!
[City hyenas sniff out
the scent of a basketball.]
Hey, Min Hyuk!
- Steal the ball away from Gary.
- Let me just make one goal!
Come on, don't you think that
you guys are being too harsh?
Hey, let me just score one goal!
No!
It's three against one right now.
- Suk Jin, they're all down there right now.
- Really?
Gary's down there!
- He's being attacked by three guys!
- Where is he?
- Gary!
- Don't you think that you're being too harsh?
[City Idols are focused on stealing
the ball away from Gary.]
No!
Where is it?
Where's one of their hoops?
[Succeeds in stealing the ball.]
[Big-nosed Brother comes to Gary's defense.]
- Stop him, Suk Jin!
- It's on the second floor.
Ji Hyo!
You have to stop them!
[Bora and Chan Sung block him,
and Min Ho makes it through the line.]
[The basketball ace even breaks through
Ji Hyo's barrier.]
[Chan Sung stays to play bodyguard
on the first floor.]
Gary!
[Slam dunk!]
[City Idols are making a clean sweep.]
Gary, out.
I got ousted by the ball I found.
[This player gets ousted by
the ball he found himself.]
Gary, out.
Why are we the only ones
getting ousted?
[Could this be a perfect game
for the City Idols?]
Do an alley oop.
[Ousts Big-nose with a fancy basketball move.]
Ji Suk Jin, out.
So Ji Hyo's the only one left now?
Ji Hyo won't even be able to make the goal
even if she does find a ball.
- We should've stolen the ball away from them.
- Why can't we find any balls?
[These ousted players sure have
a lot to say on how it should be played.]
I'm the only one left from my team.
Hey, you cruel little rascals!
[It's a basketball party!]
[My poor basketball hoop.]
[A point shooter to see who can make it.]
[Hoya ousts Ji Hyo.]
Song Ji Hyo, out.
[Every member of City Idol Team
is still left alive.]
Hoya actually did something!
How can the score be seven to nothing?
[The final score-
City Idols: 7 vs. Rural Idols: 0]
With the perfect score of seven to zero,
City Idols win this mission.
[City Idols win the basketball
name tag elimination game.]
[Wins the final chance card.]
We will immediately go into
your final mission.
For your final competition...
It's a rural relay race.
- Rural relay?
- Will we be running?
The team that has two chance cards will be
given the first option to choose.
Team Running Man won the first
two rounds of the games, correct?
- Yes, we have two chance cards.
- Swap them in for these.
Here are your two.
Rural Relay.
Big vs Small and Heavy vs Light.
- What's this?
- Heavy and Light.
It's not 'Cham', but it's 'Joong'.
Why would he think that this is 'Cham'?
I didn't see it closely enough.
Okay, the light and the big!
You can take this one and
make your selection.
[City Idol trade in their one chance card.]
There's a vertical oval,
and a horizontal oval.
- We have to pick one or the other?
- I think...
I think it's something
we'll have to climb through.
Don't act like you're all smart.
- Which one should we go with?
- We'll go with the 'won'.
The round one?
Okay, you've now made your selection.
The selection process is now over.
This is your final competition.
This will determine the ultimate winner.
- You may get going.
- Let's go!
[The winning team of this competition will be
crowned the Nation's Top Idol Group.]
[The final competition.]
[A spectacle of a race
in the middle of a farm field.]
This really is a spectacle.
This is the real blockbuster.
- Look at all this setup.
- This truly is a blockbuster.
[An unbelievable scale.]
- It's really overwhelming.
- As I told you all before...
the title of this final competition is,
Rural Relay Race.
You'll have to pass through each
of the courses in a team relay form.
There are a variety of different courses
that have been prepared for you.
Do you see the banner over there
at the edge of the field?
The first runner will start off from there
with the water buckets
and will run towards the first flag
with the buckets full of water.
And if you take a look over there,
you'll see a huge water jug waiting.
You have to pour the water into the jug,
and you'll see a little buoy marked, 'Pass'.
If you pour enough water in there,
that buoy will fall out of the jug.
There's a small and a big water jug.
Your team chose 'large'
during the selection process.
[Rural Idol Team selected the larger size
back during the selection process.]
Since you chose the larger size,
you chose poorly.
We should've gone with the small.
- Who said we should go with the big one?
- Yoo Jae Suk!
There's one more thing.
There's a small hole in the bottom
of the water jugs.
[Must pour the water into
the jug with the hole.]
You have to pour the water into the jug
with the hole on the bottom.
Then the third runner will run
over to the pile of hay in the next course.
The third runner will have to run
up over the pile of hay.
Then you'll have to jump down
from that pile of hay.
Then the fourth runner will have to run
over to the metal bar structure.
Then the fourth runner can throw their bag
over the metal bar.
This course involved another
selection process.
It was light and heavy selection,
and you selected the lighter option.
There are two rice sacks
you'll see over by the metal bar.
[Rice pouch is what they'll have to throw.]
Since you selected the lighter option,
you can throw the lighter rice sack.
[Throw the rice sack.
10kg vs 20 kg.]
City Idol Team will have to throw
the heavy sack over the bar.
Okay, Chan Sung!
[Beast Idol is unanimously chosen
to be the bearer of the burden?]
Then the next runner will have to run
over to the R5 course
with an item on a serving tray
which will be balanced on top of the head.
You made your selection of your own
during your selection process.
Thus, you will have to balance a ball
on the tray on your head.
[City Idol must balance a ball on the tray.]
Which means that Rural Idol Team will
get to balance a shoe on their tray.
[Rural Idol Team gets to balance
a show on their tray.]
If either the ball or
the shoe falls off the tray
then that person will have to go back
and start over from their starting position.
Yes, that's the way to do it!
[A ball will surely fall off the tray...]
Then did you all see the metal structure
by the R5 flag?
The R5 course will require you
to start a fire.
- You'll have to manually start a fire.
- Manually?
Once you succeed in starting the fire
then the final runner will run down
the rest of the relay course
and cross through the finish line
to win the race.
If we lose this,
then we lose the entire race.
- We have to win this.
- Let's all cheers before we start.
[The title of Nation's Top Idol Group
will be ours!]
If you've decided where you'll be going,
then everyone move off to your own stations.
The strongest person
always starts off any race.
You're the leader of your team, right?
I'm the leader of mine too.
- I'm like the leader of my team too.
- Of course you are.
[Run with the water carrying yoke
to fill up the water jugs.]
- This is very heavy.
- Should I give it a try?
[A white rubber shoe is their baton.]
This is making me unsteady on my feet.
[R1- Pouring water in the jar with the hole-
Ha Ha and Sung Gyu.]
You notice that we don't ever get
the really crucial missions?
- We're just given tasks which we can handle.
- The last runner never does things like this.
[But pouring water in these jugs
really is an important role...]
I really want to do this well.
I feel really nervous for some reason.
You're doing this one?
[R2- Climb and jump down from the haystack-
Jong Kook and Min Ho.]
Why are you doing this one?
[Stay tuned for what's to come
on this haystack!]
[R3- Throw the rice sack over the metal bar.
Kwang Soo vs Chan Sung.]
This is sure to fall off the tray.
[R4- Run with the item on the tray.
Ji Hyo vs Bora.]
- It already fell off.
- See?
[The rubber ball is definitely a disadvantage
compared to the shoe.]
[But Ji Hyo is still kindly coaching
Bora on the best way to clear her mission.]
[R5- Manually start a fire to roast a chicken-
Jae Suk vs Min Hyuk.]
I don't know if it's even possible to
start a fire with this.
I think this will be okay.
I've never had to start
a fire like this before.
Me neither.
[There aren't that many people who have
had to start a fire by using a flint.]
R6- Run while wearing the rubber shoe baton
to the finish line- Gary vs Hoya.]
I think Hoya has finally found something
that he'll be good at.
Okay, everyone get in their positions.
[Time to start he final relay race!]
Fighting!
Let's win this!
Just don't spill any water,
and we'll be okay, Jin Young.
[Everyone is waiting on standby
at their appropriate stations.]
Fighting!
Please!
[With the honor of being crowned
'Nation's Top Idol Group' on the line.]
- Take your time, Suk Jin.
- Fighting!
Don't spill any of the water.
[Good luck, everyone!]
- Take your time, okay?
- Don't spill any of the water!
There they go!
There's not much difference between
Suk Jin and Jin Young.
Jin Young!
[Off they go with the water to
fill up the water jugs.]
[Wow, Big-nose pulls the unexpected
and actually takes the lead!]
Suk Jin's going really fast!
- Suk Jin's going really fast!
- Don't spill any of the water.
Don't spill the water.
[Big-nose leading the younger idol.]
[Big-nose is the first to arrive
at the R1 mark.]
[Dump the water into the jug!]
[Jin Young arrives one step being Big-nose.]
[Dump in all the water from the
water yoke first...]
[And fill up the rest from the large jug
with a water scooper.]
You have to do it in quick successions!
The water keeps leaking out!
[No matter how fast he pours in the water,
the water continues to leak out.]
[Pour in from the top,
and leak out from the bottom!]
All the water is falling out of the jug!
[Must pour in a larger quantity of water
than the quantity of water leaking out.]
Calm down.
Sung Gyu, you need to be more calm.
[The buoy marked, 'Pass', must fall out
of the jug to pass this course.]
It has to fall out.
Do it right.
[The buoy is starting to rise to the top!]
I'm almost there!
[The buoy is starting to rise to the surface
for both of the teams.]
[The next runners are hurrying
to get ready at their position.]
- I can see it.
- I can see it. Just a couple of scoops.
[Did Ha Ha succeed?]
[So close!]
I got it.
[Ha Ha succeeds.]
- It fell out.
- You may go!
[Rural Idol Team succeeds first
at the Big-Small jug course.]
- Go!
- It won't fall out.
[R2- Jong Kook is first to head off
to climb the pile of hay.]
[Tiger races through the muddy field.]
- Hurry!
- I can't get it to fall over!
[Climbing up the gigantic pile of hay.]
Look at Jong Kook over there.
Even he's struggling with that pile.
Even Jong Kook is struggling with that.
[The gigantic pile of hay is difficult
even for the Tiger to conquer.]
[Sung Gyu finally clears his course.]
[City Idol's Min Ho gets on his way.]
[Jong Kook succeeds in climbing up
the pile of hay.]
[Touches off the rubber shoe baton
over to Kwang Soo.]
[City Idol Team is starting to
fall more and more behind.]
R3- Kwang Soo runs over to the metal bar
with the 10kg rice sack in his hands.]
If you can't get it done on your first try,
then you'll have to go back.
No!
Hey, Kwang Soo!
[He bites down on the rubber shoe baton
with his teeth.]
[Just then!]
[The speed of light!]
[If I do this right,
then we can take over the lead!]
Come on, Min Ho!
[Quickly succeeds in climbing over the top!]
[Even Jong Kook struggled with the mound,
but Min Ho climbs over it in a single try!]
[R3- Chan Sung gets on his way!]
[Please...]
[An unarguable Beast Idol-
Quickly runs with the 20kg sack in one hand.]
Kwang Soo!
[If he fails again...]
[then they might lose their lead.]
[Succeeds!]
He's got it.
Okay, he's got it.
- Ji Hyo.
- Wait for me, Ji Hyo.
Run, Ji Hyo!
No!
[They drop their rubber shoe baton in
the muddy water from Bora's interference.]
[In the meantime,
Chan Sung arrives at the metal bar.]
You have to get going!
[R4- Blank Ji sets off on her way
with the tray balanced on her head.]
[With the shoe on her tray,
she easily makes it down the lane.]
- Chan Sung is struggling with it.
- Here she comes.
But starting this fire is the problem.
- Okay, good!
- He's doing good.
[This Beast Idol has to throw the heavy
sack of rice over the metal bar.]
[It's caught?]
[Wow! He succeeds in throwing it over
on his first attempt!]
You dropped the ball!
[Quite the chaos with the ball is predicted.]
[Ace Ji Hyo is once again putting quite
the distance between the two teams.]
Starting this fire is the problem.
[R5- Start a fire by using only a flint
to roast the chicken.]
I don't know how
that's going to start the fire.
[Must start the fire and get the fire big
enough for the flames to touch the chicken.]
You almost got it, Jae Suk.
[Come on, Bora!]
Just a little bit more, Bora!
A little bit more, Bora!
[There's not much time...]
[But he can't get the fire started.]
[Amazing sense of balance!
Bora arrives at R5!]
[Min Hyuk's flint time.]
[Flicking the flint at a speed so quick
that his hand cannot even be seen!]
[An unbelievable speed!]
[Speed is the most crucial element.]
[The difference in their speed will
change the fate of the roasted chicken!]
You got it, you got it!
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Rage filled flint action!]
[Just which of the two teams will succeed
in starting the fire first?]
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Kang Min Hyuk!
[Both teams bring in the help
of thin tissue paper.]
[City Idol Team's fire is ignited first!]
They got the fire started.
We're in big trouble.
[Jae Suk also succeeds in starting
the fire immediately thereafter.]
[Crucial to keep the flames roaring
so that the fire doesn't die out.]
[With the gusty winds blowing at it,
the flames are all over the place.]
[Must cook the roasted chicken with the fire
to clear this course.]
Check and see if the fire is
lit around the back too.
We have to keep the flames
from going out.
Block the wind from blowing it out.
[Get the fire going, block the winds...]
[We were able to safely film this segment
with the help from the local fire department.]
I didn't know it would be this hard
to start the fire with the flint.
[The key to winning this course is
to be able to coax the fire into a blaze.]
[Rural Idols succeeds in cooking the chicken
with the help of dry hay straw!]
Give me the rubber shoe baton!
[Gary runs towards the finish line
without a moment of hesitation.]
[Come on, fire!]
[Success!]
[City Idol Team also hands off their baton
to the final runner of the race.]
[Will he be able to take over the lead?]
[If you think you can take the lead,
then give it a try!]
[A farewell to the rubber shoe...]
[His rubber shoe baton falls off of his foot!]
Gary!
[This is our chance!]
[Hoya speeds down the lane!]
[Mr. Gary attempts to get the shoe back
on his foot to resume the race.]
[At the speed of light!]
[Will he take over the lead...]
[Or will he keep the lead?]
[Just how will it end?]
[The title of being crowned
'The Nation's Top Idol Group' is on the line.]
[Too big of a gap for it to have been
possible to take over the lead.]
[Mr. Gary is already only 50cm away
from crossing the finish line.]
Let's start over together from right here.
No, I can't do that.
[Why would I do that?]
[Crosses the finish line by doing the wave.]
[Rural Idol Team wins the race!]
Sorry, Hoya.
I got the fire going first.
Thus, the honor of being crowned the
Nation's Top Idol Group goes to Team RM.
Sorry, but what else could we do?
[Prize of gold rings are given out to
the Rural Idol Team for winning the race.]
We're not familiar with things like this
because we're all still so young.
We didn't live back in
the prehistoric times either!
You think we use these flints to
light a fire every day?
- This was my first time too.
- We're all still very young too!
Thus, Team Running Man takes the crown
of being the Nation's Top Idol Group title!
[Running Man-
Nation's Top Idol Group!]
[A train trip to Kyungjoo.]
[But they were all still unaware
of what was to come at the time.]
[A trip filled with laughter, excitement,
and everlasting memories...]
[However...]
[An unexpected turn that awaited them
when they arrived in Kyungjoo.]
You have to find your own
way to Kyungjoo.
[Find the secret hidden within Kyungjoo...]
[Embrace the thousand year old history.]
Who do you think guessed the
wrong answer?
[A special quiz competition that only
Running Man can come up with.]
[Are you afraid of water bombs?
Then conquer the quiz battle!]
Only one team will become the champion.
We can't all become champions.
Subtitles by DramaFever