Subtitles by DramaFever
[Look out.]
[The ones who control this
neighborhood have arrived.]
[On this street...
only the strongest will survive.]
Hey, I'll see you later.
[The group separated.]
[The Gang of the Lower Neighborhood (GLN)]
[The Gang of the Upper Neighborhood (GUN)]
- Let's go and have a cup of coffee.
Let's go in.
[Coffee Shop]
[They went to the best coffee
shop in the Upper Neighborhood.]
I'm a regular here.
[The GLN are gathered in their hideout.]
- I heard some new ones joined the GUN.
- Is that right?
Three new ones joined the gang.
I heard they are pretty unusual.
How unusual can they be? Can't
be more than what we're used to.
[The very source of the tumultuous rumors.]
[Three new faces of the GLN
have shown themselves.]
[They are here.]
[The ones who could brighten up
this coffee shop.]
[The MC with good looks, Oh Sang Jin.]
[From being a popular MC...]
[He successfully transformed
into a talented actor!]
[Sang Jin, joins the GUN meeting.]
[At that moment...
another guest joins the group.]
[A talented actor with
great presence, Kim Sung Kyun.]
[He leaves an unforgettable,
strong impression.]
[His top notch performance
at being a creepy criminal.]
[Incredibly talented Kim Sung Kyun can
even pull off a comedic character!]
[We only see Sung Kyun in movies but
he's come to a neighborhood coffee shop!]
[And... the last guest.]
[Surprised]
[The Boss has come.]
[Totally impressed.]
You're still alive.
[Absolute charisma, Jo Jin Woong.]
[His excellent acting fills the screen.]
[His wide spectrum of acting talent enables
him to cross between different genres.]
[If Jo Jin Woong is in it, the
work becomes a masterpiece.]
[Jo Jin Woong, commanding over
30 million audiences.]
Good to see you.
I finally get to see you outside of movies.
Actually, I've met Sang Jin
and Sung Kyun before.
But this is the first time
we've met Jo Jin Woong.
- Please try this, It's called 'Ma-cha'.
- Ma-cha?
Oh, no, thank you.
[Somehow, it doesn't make you
want to drink it.]
[No, thank you.]
[The GUN's tradition, Ma-cha?]
I'm not sure about this.
Ah, can I have some water?
But isn't this supposed to be
good for your health?
- Let's go.
- Wait, he's the boss so...
- Of course, we need to give him respect.
- You should be informal with us.
- Boss, shall we go?
- Yes, why don't get up, sirs.
[Now, it's time to act.]
[Let's go, Boss.]
- You're also still alive.
- I'm also still alive.
[Such a caring boss taking
care of his subordinates.]
[The Upper Neighborhood (UN) is alive!]
[And the GLN is waiting for them.]
Hey, you over there.
Come here.
- What's this?
- Going to a wedding or something?
[Don't you dare!]
Come down. We'll duke it out
once you come down.
Come down. You're all alive.
[My legs are crampy...]
- Hi, how are you?
- Say hello to everyone.
Hi, how are you?
Greeting each other will end
right here and now.
[It's a psychological
warfare from the beginning.]
Quite a lot of authority in your voice.
The teams will be competing over
the dominance
of the upper (UN) and the
lower neighborhood (LN).
- You know the Chinese character for 'death'?
- Yes.
This is called 'Death-Bingo Race'.
The team who wins this race
will be granted
a chance in the middle of the mission.
You probably have some idea as to
what chance will work best for your team.
[Using the chance to win
the final Death-Bingo Race!]
[We'll take this Bingo game.]
[The Gang of Upper Neighborhood (GUN)]
[We only played Bingo in school!]
[The Gang of Lower Neighborhood (GLN)]
[Each team is headed to the
site for their first mission.]
Sung Kyun and Jin Woong
are really nice.
Say some of those famous movie lines.
You guys are so different than
the characters you play in the movies.
So I was thinking about this all yesterday.
'Should have a drink before I go?'
Before we start the race,
say some lines
from the movies to get them
under control.
You should say some strong lines
from the movies.
[Yes... this kind of feel!]
Sung Kyun should...
you know, the tone you used when you
asked for the money from Choi Min Shik.
[Making a threat with courtesy...
his chilling acting.]
You know, Sung Kyun wore
a wig in that movie.
At first, I thought he was Shin Young.
[They do look alike.]
He looked like Kim Shin Young.
Anyway, I feel confident
that Boss is here with us.
So I'm not worried at all.
Boss, your arm seems little skinny
compared to your size.
He says he doesn't really exercise.
I really don't like being active.
You look like you'd love to exercise.
[The action actor who doesn't
like to exercise?]
- Here, feel it. It's really skinny.
- No, really?
How come it's so mushy?
[The golden field at the height of Autumn.]
- You guys have no style.
- Let's go.
[What kind of showdown will unfold here?]
What kind of set is this?
[A special mud ring located...
in the middle of a plow field.]
- What's this?
- It's perfect for a face-off.
[Perfect for calligraphy using
the mud as ink.]
They actually dug the ground.
- Go on. Move forward.
- Hey, don't push me.
Should I just dip you in the mud?
[Impossible for them to coexist.]
[Destined rivals, the GUN and the GLN.]
Today, we prepared a very masculine
game perfect for our three guests.
What is it?
[Mud Volleyball]
The difference between
normal volleyball and this is...
you have to use the entire mud ring.
You will play a normal volleyball game.
But if the ball falls outside
the line into the mud...
you can hit it back from the mud.
In a normal volleyball game
you have to receive then hit it back.
But we don't have that rule in this game.
You just have to hit it back.
So long as the ball it doesn't
touch the ground, it's fine?
Yes.
You can use your head and any part of
your body to hit the ball back.
The winning team will be awarded
with the
chance you can use for
the Death-Bingo Race.
Sung Kyun, why don't you say something?
Please say a line.
I don't have anything to say.
He's too nice. It's only in the movies.
In real life, he's too nice.
He's an angel.
Jin Woong is my friend.
- Does Jin Woong consider you a friend?
- He's a real gentleman.
Yeah, I know.
He's a real gentleman.
That's because I haven't
started to say anything, yet.
[Boss Jin Woong has broken his seal.]
Now, let's get going.
Okay, let's get going.
Everyone take your microphones off.
We even have to take our
microphones off?
[You'll find out why we
asked you to take them off.]
[Antsy]
Over there.
Wait a minute.
The urgent business is calling.
He'll be right back.
There is no bathroom around here.
[Purifying his mind and body
prior to the face-off.]
- Hurry up and come back.
- You see? Isn't it brutal?
We have nothing to fear.
- This is awesome.
- Is he really going?
- Sung Kyun, go deep in there.
- I think that's enough.
Your camerman is following you.
[The determination of a camerman not
wanting to lose one precious moment.]
[The actor and the VJ are of one
mind and body in Running Man.]
Sung Kyun, you should go further in.
[In the meantime, Sung Kyun is
going deep into nature...]
Go over that hill!
Heli-cam!
[No, don't shoot!]
That was really quick.
Look, he's coming back already.
You're all dead!
- Look up, there is a heli-cam.
- Look up!
[Urinating in nature broadcasted
live through a heli-cam?]
The heli-cam caught everything!
He goes often but does it quickly.
I can live now.
You look so much better.
[Since the urgent business
has been taken care of...]
[Everyone jumps into the mud pit.]
[Let's have a proper match now.]
[First set, mud volleyball]
[The LN, Fighting!]
[The UN can't be beaten.]
One, two, three, four...
We're alive.
We're alive... The end.
This mud is the mud used
in the Boryeong Mud Festival.
Oh, so it's good for you.
Here we go!
Ready.
[We'll show you the
'Upper' Men's volleyball.]
[Mud volleyball first set... start!]
[Kkuk's strong serve...
Sang Jin's stable receive.]
[It hit the net and then... went over.]
[Big-nose failed to receive.]
[Whether the ball hits the net or the mud,
if you hit it over, you score.]
- You should have jumped in!
- I couldn't jump in.
[Forced diving rehearsal]
[Sang Jin has shown a stable performance.]
[The UN, Jin Woong's serve.]
Sirs, you need to do better.
[Kkuk's nice receive.]
[With Big-nose's toss, Kwang Soo
passed the ball over the net.]
[Slip]
[Again, Big-nose failed to receive.]
[The UN 2 : The LN 0]
Let's start it over again.
I'm finally warmed up.
I'm sorry. Let's consider that
a warm-up practice.
[The whole group needs to
pay respect with deep bows.]
[I'm not going to do it.]
[If you don't want a rematch,
suit yourself.]
[Of course, we do!]
[Giraffe's punch of wrath.]
[Gave a big bow as he fell.]
[The group bow.]
- He just began having a social life.
- He still doesn't know how things work.
I had no idea it'd be like this.
- You'd only listen when you get hit?
- Now we are back to 0:0.
[Totally relaxed, the UN has
even let the LN be on the offense.]
[Mud volleyball, the first set... start.]
[Jin Woong's hustled receive.]
[This ball...]
[I'm going to save it.]
[Big-nose's failed receive.]
[Gary tried to fly over but it was no use.]
[Big-nose receives a lot criticism.]
This really sucks!
Hey, can't you just let me have it once?
[The UN, Sung Kyun's serve.]
[Big-nose's receive.]
[Ji Hyo's mistake.]
What kind of receive was that?
[Big-nose is criticized no matter what.]
[The UN 2 : The LN 0]
We should have a game against
the team that can be our match.
But was it my fault?
She's the one who missed it.
Looks like it's fun.
Do you know what Jin Woong said?
We are doing better but you guys
seem to be having more fun.
Please let us have some fun, too.
When we toss it over,
you should toss back for once!
That way, I'll have chance
to throw myself like that.
[It won't be fun unless we get the ball.]
Please give us the ball.
Please give us a chance to laugh.
Okay, let's go.
[The LN, Kukk's serve.]
That's it!
[Congratulations! It was funny.]
I should have had my my
face go under.
[Jae Suk caught the chance
to make his team laugh.]
[All happy even after losing a point.]
[All puzzled even after scoring a point.]
[The UN 2 : The LN 1]
[Okay... so that's how you do it.]
[Again, the LN, Kukk's serve.]
[Splash]
[For the sake of laughter, he
dives in with no questions asked.]
[Ha Ha followed Jin Woong's example.]
[Even in the midst of all this,
they managed to score.]
[The UN 3 : The LN 1].
I feel heavy now.
Where did you say this mud was from?
[Okay... his physical humor is still there.]
[The UN 6 : The LN 1]
[The UN, Sang Jin's serve.]
Mine. Mine.
[Big-nose's more stable receive.]
[Passed from his team mates...]
[Gary, trying for a spike?]
[Float like a butterfly...]
[A total miss.]
[The moment he made that mistake,
he's committed a high treason.]
- You think you are a superman?
- Why are you trying to fly?
[Blistering criticisms]
[I was wrong...]
[Anyway, the UN won the first set
in the mud volleyball game.]
- Did we win the first set?
- Fine, we'll give it to them.
[With everyone's agreement,
teams change sides.]
[Would the UN dominate
again in the second set?]
- Let's win this time.
- Yes.
[Mud volleyball,
the second set is ready.]
I don't think this is a good spot.
[Would the change of sides
influence the outcome of this game?]
[Totally confident.]
[Mud volleyball, the second set... start.]
[Kwang Soo's whirlwind blocking.]
[Continued with Kukk's bullet toss.]
[Slip]
[The LN 1 : The UN 0]
- I think this side is better.
- Yeah, it's better.
So this side is better.
[That's the side for comedy.]
[Sports... Comedy]
This side was the lucky side.
[The UN, Sung Kyun's serve.]
[Kwang Soo's speed-of-light spike.]
[The LN 2 : The UN 0]
[Since the change of sides, the team's
morale has changed 180 degrees.]
[The LN has gained its momentum.]
[Big-nose's power serve.]
[Jae Suk's spike.]
[Tightly held.]
[Foul. We caught that.]
Hey, what are you doing?
[Haroro made a mistake
while raising a doubt for a foul.]
[The LN 3 : The UN 0]
- He caught the ball?
- Yes, he did.
[According to the PD,
that was okay.]
- But he was playing handball.
- That wasn't a big deal.
[The difference between
a skill and a trick?]
We'll figure it out later.
It wasn't that bad.
- If you have an issue, settle it now.
- This was not a big deal.
[So you're going to take it
like that, huh?]
[The UN, Jae Suk's powerful serve.]
[Big-nose's good defense.]
[Giraffe's lethal move appears again.]
[Gary finishes it off.]
[Scored 4 points in a row.]
[Aggressively making complaints.]
[So you are going to continue this?]
[The LN, Big-nose's serve.]
[Sung Kyun's wrath-filled fiery shoot.]
[The LN 4 : The UN 1]
Don't you think that was too much?
[An eye for an eye, a trick for a trick.]
[I can't lose.]
Fine, let's do it.
[The LN, Kukk 's serve.]
[Is this volleyball or basketball?]
What the heck are you doing?
[No need for a complaint.]
[Willingly handed over by his own team.]
[The end of trickster Giraffe.]
- This is nothing.
- Hey, what are you looking for?
[Became an invalid turn.]
I'm sorry.
I admit I was wrong.
[Again, Kukk's strong serve.]
[Offensive and defensive battle
between two enemies.]
[The LN 4 : The UN 2]
[The UN has rallied their spirit
after the Giraffe incident.]
[The LN, Kukk 's serve.]
[A fierce battle between the net.]
[Thanks to the big hole.]
[The LN 4 : The UN 3]
[Why did I do that?]
Are you going to send it over my way?
I'll send it over your way (Big-nose).
I know you're going to hit it
the other way.
[It really came to me...]
[You were serious?]
[The LN 4 : The UN 4]
[Mumbling]
- I'm sorry...
- Are you avoiding us?
Are you avoiding us?
[The UN, Jin Woong's serve.]
[More stable play by both teams.]
[An overly enthusiastic spike.]
[The LN 5 : The UN 4]
[We must win!]
You must have seen volleyball on TV.
- This is to Suk Jin again.
- Bring it on!
[The UN, Yoo Hyuk, pegged
Big-nose again.]
[He got it.]
[The LN 5 : The UN 5]
- Why did you do that?
- You should have told me.
[Everyone's busy blaming one another.]
It throws off Suk Jin when you
serve to him so target Suk Jin.
This is over now. Almost over.
The ball needs to soak up some water.
Oh, yeah? Go ahead.
We'll feed some dirt then.
Whoa, it's heavy now.
Do you think it's a bowling ball?
[This is like an 'evil-ball' game.]
[The LN 6 : The UN 5]
[The UN is also making an evil-ball.]
Hey, roll it in the dirt.
[Mud + dirt, an evil-ball upgraded.]
Come on. Let's get on with it.
We'll receive it!
[Will it be the one with the
superhuman strength or...]
[will it be the evil-ball?]
[Who will be the winner?]
[I'm going to get this.]
[The evil-ball's overwhelming victory.]
[The LN 6 : The UN 6]
- It's a cannonball.
- This is totally a cannonball.
[Big-nose rushed to make a 'cannonball'.]
- Take your time in releasing the ball.
- I know. I know.
You've got to release it real slow.
[This is no joke.]
Hurry! You've got to hurry!
[The ultra-powerful 'cannonball'
has been loaded.]
[Okay, here it goes!]
[How will we... block that 'cannonball'?]
No, you can't do it that way!
[The 'cannonball' has detonated itself.]
[The LN 6 : The UN 7]
[Mr. Capable and Ace are
preparing the 'cannonball'.]
You have to throw the ball upward.
I'll try to receive it.
- I'll try it also.
- Okay.
You have to throw it like this.
[The LN, Kukk launched the 'cannonball'.]
[The 'cannonball' landed on the face.]
[What are we going to do...]
[The LN 7 : The UN 7]
You can't get it.
[I know that now that I've
been hit with it.]
[Kukk is now preparing a new 'cannonball'.]
Here we go again!
[Here it comes once again.]
[I'm definitely going to get it this time.]
[Here it is!]
[Hit by the 'cannonball' twice in a row.]
[The humiliation felt by the
ace of volleyball!]
[Hooray?]
[Plummeted from 'Brain' to
'Clumsy' in a split second.]
[This round will not be counted
since he made us all laugh.]
So you win if you receive
and hit it back?
Yes, if you can receive and
hit it back, you win.
You can't fill it with water now.
[The current score is 7:7]
[The team that scores two points
in a row will win.]
- Let's win.
- Let us win first.
Fighting!
[Boss Jin Woong alone got
the direction wrong.]
[That's okay.
He did 'fighting' with them.]
[The UN, Jae Suk, strong serve!]
[The LN 7 : The UN 8]
[This is unfair.]
What the hell is this?
[Big-nose avoided the ball
at the decisive moment.]
[The LN, Gary's serve.]
[Ha Ha's continuous offense.]
[Big-nose and Gary enter the
water together.]
[The second set final score]
[The LN 7 : The UN 9]
[The blissful Ring Around the Rosie.]
[Too bad.]
The UN has won mud volleyball.
[Mud volleyball, 2:0, The UN is the winner!]
Our team won so why do we
all look like losers?
I had a lot of spirit this morning but
it's all gone now after all that exercise.
My cold is gone.
- But we still won.
- Of course.
[Self-congratulating Boss Jo Jin Woong]
[Now they need to get in
their car and start get going...]
Before you take off...
you all must be hungry.
The team that arrives later will
buy lunch for the other team.
You should move the car now.
Would you have any strength
left to drive after losing?
Well, driving is different.
Anyway, where are we going?
Why doesn't the car start?
There is no key.
- The car won't start.
- Wait a minute, there is no smart key?
Key, key, key.
There is no key.
- As I stated before...
- We don't have the key!
I said you should move the car.
[Move the car?]
[Move the car.]
There will be shower gowns and
the car keys at the end of the road.
[We need to push it.]
We need to push the car?
[Big-nose is the only one who's relaxed.]
[Much to and fro.]
Only one person should push.
[The LN, Mr. Capable, Kukk]
[The UN, Samchunpo Sung Kyun]
[Car pushing race, start!]
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Release the break!
[Oh, it's moving!]
It's good. It's good.
Sung Kyun's good.
We should rotate the pusher
while maintaining this speed.
Why are they so strong?
We need to keep this speed.
[I'm... Mr. Capable.]
[Even though the car ignition
isn't turned on...]
[if I give all my strength...]
[Mr. Capable's power.]
[He's ahead.]
[Speed increase.]
What? Were they able to
start the car?
[Speed-racer, human bull Mr. Capable.]
Let's change. Change.
[Oh Sang Jin is the next pusher.]
Whoa, he lost his shoe.
[The bare feet with fighting spirit.]
Kim Jong Kook.
Where are we now?
[Jae Suk, his turn to push.]
Let's make it a 'four feet' drive.
[A brand new model,
a 'four-feet drive' car.]
[Good, it's gaining speed.]
[Let's go! Forward!]
[But it's not even close.]
[Completely exhausted.]
[Almost at the finish line.]
[In order to get the car key, the rear
wheels have to cross the finish line.]
[The UN's white car is right behind!]
[The LN has crossed the finish line.]
We did it!
[Exhausted human-bull and
the free riders.]
We did it! We did it!
It's not over, yet. Pick up your
shower gowns and go.
[The race isn't over yet.]
You've worked hard.
[A fit of anger.]
[Free rider Big-nose.]
It isn't over, yet.
Are we all in?
Sung Kyun, put on your seat belt on.
How did he push it alone
all the way down here?
Jong Kook isn't human.
[Fiery Klin Sauna]
- Is this it?
- Yes, this is it.
[Hot sauna]
Wow, it's no joke in there.
It's so hot.
[Boss Jin Woong comes in with a gown!]
Oh, it's a real sauna.
I want to go in later.
[Ah... I'm scared to go in...]
First, you need to make the saunas in
the neighborhood come under your control.
[Kukk used to 'rule' the city
of Anyang as a student.]
If you want to rule all the saunas
you need to put on a gown.
I thought there was a doctor in here.
[The neighborhood dispute
that's hotter than the sauna.]
Watch what you say. What? Doctor?
[Preserving man's pride is
more important than the heat.]
Now, this is your second mission.
- You want to get out get out soon, don't you?
- Yes.
[Of course!]
A sauna is the place that reminds
you of men.
The only person who gets the
answer to the quiz correct
will be allowed to leave this room.
If you look outside,
there are beach chairs...
drinks and iced punch are
prepared for you.
[The privilege you can enjoy only
if you get the answer correct.]
First, I'll tell you the category.
Then one representative from each
neighborhood should give an answer.
The team that has all the members
out of the sauna will win this mission.
Also, you'll have a chance to bring back
a member from the other team.
I'm sorry but please get to
the point because it's hot in here.
- It's not that hot in here.
- You think it's not hot in here?
[Sauna quiz start!]
The first category is... famous quotes.
[The UN recommends Jae Suk]
How about Suk Jin.
- Me?
- You are the oldest.
- I'm the best one?
- Yeah, you lived the longest.
[The LN forces Suk Jin into in it.]
[Instead of Jae Suk, Ha Ha
volunteers to be the contestant.]
- Fighting!
- Let's go out!
Today's quiz is about men.
[Huh?]
[VJ Gwon Yeol, I was told to go in...]
It's this person's famous quote.
Shakespeare...
Isn't this too easy?
Shakespeare said,
'[such and such] men are the best men.'
What kind of man was
Shakespeare referring to?
Isn't this too easy?
The man who knows himself the best.
No, that's not it.
That was a quote by Socrates.
[This is hard.]
Is this a nonsense quiz?
The Upper Neighborhood.
Bad men.
[Punished!]
Come on, it's Shakespeare.
If I were to give you a hint...
this type of man is very different
from our members here.
[Different from the
Running Man members?]
I think I'm going to get it
right this time.
The Lower Neighborhood.
The quiet men.
It must be correct.
The quiet men... must be right.
The quiet men?
The correct answer,
'Men of few words are the best men'.
[Big-nose escapes the sauna.]
I told you it was right.
I don't think he knows
what he's talking about.
- Man of few words aren't all that cool.
- Yeah, he'll just have bad breath.
[Finally, I escaped.]
[Envious]
[Cold shower.]
[Acting silly.]
He didn't even break a sweat.
He must be cold now.
I have no lines anymore.
Adam's apple.
[Next, Mr. Capable]
- Nosebleed.
[Ace, Blank Ji- correct answer.]
The whole team must
not be that smart.
[The UN is in shock.]
It's heaven out here
compared to the inside.
Let's wrap this up quickly.
- Why are you sweating so much?
- Don't shake hands with him.
[Drenched Giraffe.]
[I want to escape.
Give me the quiz problem.]
Give me the problem.
The fourth quiz.
The category is... lies.
I can't lie.
You should just go.
[Samchunpo Sung Kyun vs
Giraffe Kwang Soo]
I think I feel little weird now.
I'm seeing double.
I must be possessed by a water spirit.
[The battle against the heat.]
These are the lies
wives tell their husbands.
I'll tell you from rank number four.
Rank number four...
'Honey, I'm going to see my friend.'
- Wow, it's really scary.
- That's number four?
- We just did the research.
- But why is the result so scary?
Rank number three...
'I'll call your mother often.'
- That's a lie?
- 'Often', 'call her often' part.
Number two... 'Honey, I'll
make you breakfast everyday.'
What do you think the
number one lie is?
- The upper neighborhood.
- Yes, the number one lie is?
'I'm going to lose weight.'
[The married men are
sure it's the correct answer.]
I should thank my wife.
- Did she say that, too?
- She's still saying it.
Is it correct?
That wasn't it?
There is a different lie?
'I love you. I love you.'
No, that's the husband's lie.
I love you. Go ahead.
The Lower Neighborhood.
'I'll only love you forever.'
I told you that's the guys' lie.
'It was cheap.'
That's my mother's favorite lie.
- Is it correct?
- It was very close.
'This is 1.1.'
[Correction, it should be 1+1.]
Please let me out of here.
[Dehydrated Giraffe's 1+1
when there is two percent less.]
'I found it somewhere.'
[The continuous sea of wrong answers.]
'I bought it because I really needed it.'
['I bought it because I really needed it.']
[The correct answer.]
[Boss Woong Jin's anger explodes.]
[You'll see, Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Finally feeling the cool outside air.]
[Ah... this must be heaven.]
We want to use our chance.
We'll use our chance.
Lee Kwang Soo.
Me? Me?
Me? Why me?
[If Jae Suk gets the correct answer,
Kwang Soo will head back into the sauna.]
Okay, I'll give you the problem.
We talked about lies that wives
tell their husbands.
This time, it's about lies that
husbands tell their wives.
Suk Jin should know
everything about that.
That's Suk Jin's problem.
Number one...
'I'll come home early.'
Number two is...
'I have no emergency funds.'
Number three is... 'Let's go
somewhere fun this weekend.'
What do you think the
number four lie is?
The number four is more difficult.
Excuse me. Suk Jin says it should be
'I fell asleep in the car.'
'I had to work late last night.'
- What about going to a funeral?
- That's right.
'So and so passed away.'
That was ranked number seven.
'I'd still marry you even if
I were born again.'
[Correct answer?]
- Was it close?
- No, it's very different.
'Yes, I'm almost home.'
I'm almost home.
I'm parking my car.
I'm in front of our house.
'Let's have a child.'
What about something you eat?
'Wow, this is delicious.'
- This is got to be right.
- Yeah, her food is delicious.
[Correct!]
Lee Kwang Soo.
You need to go in!
[Lee Kwang Soo summoned
back into the sauna.]
Kwang Soo, you're being summoned.
[I shouldn't have cheated before.]
Come in.
The next one is Suk Jin.
[I'll just have a drink now
and worry about that later.]
This time, the category is history.
[Brain Sang Jin is on!]
- You should score one this time.
- Don't use the word 'avenge' on me.
[A mental collapse. Spaced out Giraffe.]
This is about the Joseon Dynasty.
This is court speech.
The word 'bisoo' refers to king's what?
You don't even know that?
Refers to king's what?
The left minister.
- The left minister?
- Yes.
You mean 'king's left minister'?
Nasal discharge.
'Bi' means nose.
'Soo' means water.
[Correct!]
He's really the brain.
Was it that simple?
I'm sorry.
[Such a polite Sang Jin.]
I didn't even know there
was a word 'bi' for nose.
You know, Ear, Nose and Throat.
So it was 'Soo' for water.
He's really a brainiac.
'Bi' for nose and 'Soo' for water.
- Sang Jin is really amazing.
- I've never heard of that word before.
But how come a king's 'bisoo'
is about history?
Because it was a term from
the Joseon Dynasty.
Gary, you're doing good today.
Your feel for the showmanship
is at its best today.
Do I need to be tired to
be a good entertainer?
The next question
is about movies.
Let's go, let's go.
Jin Woong, you go.
But I like old movies.
But we only have two
comedians here.
- We don't need you!
- He's an actor as well.
But they are two
comedians over there.
I liked your last movie.
Don't go easy on him because
he's older, okay?
I'll do my very best.
Be fair.
- The Godfather.
- Godfather!
I watched it this morning!
I know all about it.
The main character says this when
he gives advice to someone.
'Keep your ___ close
and your ___ closer.'
Okay, okay, you got this, right?
Upper.
'Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.'
- Lower!
- Be quiet.
He'll read that line.
'Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.'
[Correct.]
He told me to keep your wife close
and your girlfriend closer...
- He told me...
- When? When did I say that? When?
- Finally, a chance to turn it around.
- Let's get ready.
- I didn't know that one.
- We might lose.
- But... that's a little...
But we'll win because of Ha Ha.
- He doesn't know much.
- I don't.
The next question is
about literature.
I'll give it a shot.
[It's a game decider.]
He writes songs and all.
- We mentioned Shakespeare, right?
- We did mention Shakespeare.
What are the four great
tragedies by Shakespeare?
Upper, Lower.
Upper Lower....
['Who am I and what
am I doing here?']
You said Upper for us.
Hamlet, Hamlet, Othello.
- Macbeth and King Lear.
- King Lear.
The four great tragedies by Shakespeare
are Hamlet, Othello, Macbeth, King Lear.
- These four?
- That wasn't the question?
Then... where was Hamlet born?
Lower!
Oh?
- Wasn't it Netherlands?
- Denmark, Denmark.
Where was Hamlet born?
Denmark, Denmark.
- Oh, so cool.
- He was the prince of Denmark.
Around the time when there
was corruption in Denmark
Shakespeare wrote it
using it as the motive.
You studied in school, right?
- I majored in theater.
- That's what I mean.
I was a man of the theater.
['Which country was
Hamlet the prince of?']
- Upper!
- Lower!
Upper Neighborhood first.
That was it?
Iceland.
Iceland?
Lower!
U.S.A!
[What?]
[USA...]
- He told me too...
- USA doesn't have a king.
USA doesn't have a king.
I know, why would USA have a king?
Why would USA have a king?
The answer is...
- Denmark.
- So, it's North Europe!
I didn't know either.
I did theater but...
how come I don't remember?
[Gary escaped after
getting a question right.]
- Something men like to hear.
- You got this one.
We like it when women say this.
We came up with this question based on the
findings from Wedding Research Center.
This is too hard...
Top six sayings that... men
like to hear from women.
It's about what men like
to hear from women.
Sixth place.
'Women seem you find you very attractive.'
I love hearing them say this.
It's a great thing to
hear from them.
Fifth place.
'You seem to know everyone.'
I didn't expect this one.
Four place.
'Is there anything you can't do?'
Third place.
- 'I think you're very loyal.'
- It's a very nice one.
First place.
'Do you work out?'
- Really? Is that the best one?
- It makes sense.
- Second place?
- Upper!
- 'You dress so well.'
- Yeah, something like that.
'You dress so...'
- What would you know about men?
- ['What did he just say?']
It's something that...
many of our females guests have...
said this to you, Kwang Soo.
Yeah?
To me?
- They did.
- Upper! So that's the answer?
Not sure because it doesn't
make sense.
- 'You look much better in person.'
- That is not it.
'You have clear skin.'
Ah...
'You look younger.'
Oh! That's it.
That's it.
What was it?
Was it a compliment?
Upper! We got this!
We got this for sure.
- 'You look younger in person.'
- That's it.
[Correct.]
['That's the answer?']
To be more accurate, they told
Lee Kwang Soo...
'You don't look your age.'
[But to Kwang Soo, it
doesn't mean the same thing.]
Drink up.
You did so well.
[Haroro escapes the sauna.]
- Go Kwang Soo go!
- Go Sung Kyun!
[The current score is 2 to 1.]
If Kwang Soo wins the next
round, Upper Neighborhood wins, okay?
Yes, yes and we absolutely
have to win this one.
It's your fantasy.
Here is a question.
What is... the number one
hobby men want women to have?
- Yoga, yoga, yoga.
- Cooking.
Cooking.
Cooking is a good one.
It's a hobby that men
prefer their women to have.
- Lower.
If you get this one right,
the LN wins.
Cooking!
Co... co... cooking?
You said 'yo' three times.
Isn't it yo-yo?
- Cooking.
- Cooking?
Could it?
[Correct.]
[LN wins.]
[It's as if they won a world
championship.]
Well done, Kwang Soo!
Well done!
[I lost to Kwang Soo...]
We get to get out
of here, right?
Sung Kyun.
And you didn't know
the answer?
How did you know anyway?
['Something's fishy, Kwang Soo.']
- For the first time ever, I'm proud of you.
- For real.
[LN won a chance card.]
Hey, come over here.
How did you know the answer?
- It's suspicious.
- I escaped the sauna, anyway.
You're very suspicious.
- Jong Kook!
- How did you know cooking was the answer?
And also it's just too suspicious
that you didn't even hesitate.
It's not your style to
answer a question so fast.
- How did you know the answer?
- Sung Kyung, why are you doing this?
- This is a horse riding course in Hongcheon.
- Horse riding.
It's a Death Bingo race which
requires four deadly lines.
This is your last mission.
We'll tell you about
the rules later on.
We'll have you go to your spot.
Let's move!
Here?
Anyone from UN here?
Are we riding horses?
Oh, what's the smell?
['Are you a Giraffe?']
- Let's remove your eye patch.
- Can I?
Please remove your eye patch.
['Hey, Giraffe.']
I'll tell you about the final mission.
From now on, it's a melee, or free for all
where everyone
competes against everyone else.
What?
Ah, it's a melee.
The final mission is the
Death Bingo race.
It's Death Bingo.
- It's Death Bingo.
- Huh?
On your three by three matrices, you write
down the names of everyone except yourself.
Make your own bingo cards.
When someone's name tag
has been removed
You can mark the square of the
person who has been eliminated.
They want us to
fill up the blanks.
It's a game of human bingo.
Whoever is eliminated, I get
to mark that square, right?
The person whose name tag is
intact and has completed four lines
needs to stand on the ending bingo
square and shout 'bingo' to win.
Okay, lastly...
the chance cards you have won give you
the right to choose a particular square.
If you look at your
three by three matrices
On the first square
you have to write a name from Team
LN who lost the first mission.
And on the last square
you have to write a name from
the UN who lost the second mission.
Nine names except mine.
Who should be in the center?
It's a very important square.
I need to choose someone who's
likely to get eliminated first.
I think they will write
my name in the center.
Let's write 'Ji Suk Jin' in the center.
That's the way to go.
I have to write Suk Jin's
name for sure in the center.
I'm sorry, Suk Jin. But you play the
most crucial role in this round.
I shouldn't think too much
about things like this.
The center is the golden spot.
[And Ji Suk wrote Sang Jin's
name in the center.]
It's a melee, you know?
It's not like I've never
watched Running Man before.
It's, it's just exactly
the way it should be.
[Showy.]
This is the answer sheet, you know?
Based on who...
gets eliminated first, I should
make my move accordingly.
From now on, Death Bingo game...
will start in five seconds.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Start!
First of all, walking around so early
in the game only makes me a target.
I should wait for my chance.
Since Kim Jong Kook is a beast,
it take more than just sheer strength.
It seems... this will be a
battle of tactics and strategy.
Sung Kyun!
It's here.
Everyone's gathering.
Jae Suk, Jae Suk, it has
to be Kim Jong Kook first.
We need to remove a
gigantic threat first.
Because we can't win otherwise.
['What did you say?']
[He's listening.]
He's the brain.
Not one person can
complete all four lines.
['You want to rally
up against me, huh?']
Jae Suk ran away already?
[One person here is not involved
in the conversation because]
[he needs to look at his
card and their names.]
[Oh Sang Jin.]
[Ha Ha.]
['Who gets to rest first?']
[He's smiling so innocently but
can't tell what he's thinking.]
Be smart about this.
This is the answer sheet period.
Could I ride a horse around?
['I won't let you.']
Have a good day.
I'm sorry.
I'll be right back.
[I understand.]
[Now he's locked and
loaded or rather 'unloaded.']
Okay, I think I have to
go out there, otherwise...
[Center spot Big Nosed brother
feeling anxious.]
[He walks around and...]
['Hello.']
[As soon as he's out of
hiding, he's spotted.]
['Guys, see you later!']
['Get him!']
[Running at full speed.]
So tired of doing
this week after week.
['But this is our first time.']
Why are you doing this?
My legs!
[Sang Jin and Sung Kyun
won't let up.]
This is not how you do it!
- Come, come, one by one.
- I'll defend.
['Suk Jin']
['I'm here too.']
[That's when...]
[Jin Woong attacks Sang Jin.]
[Sang Jin deflects the attack
and then Kwang Soo attacks!]
Everyone has gone crazy.
[It's a dog-eat-dog war.]
I should...
[Sung Kyun, waiting for his chance]
[ambushes Jae Suk.]
[Sung Kyung the bingo killer
with an innocent smile.]
Sung Kyun, how could
you do this to me?
[There are no friends
on this mission.]
[Welcome to Death Bingo world.]
Hey Sung Kyun,
let's be rational about this.
Sung Kyun, Sung Kyun.
Let's be rational about this.
[But!]
[Sang Jin the passionate
rookie ambushes Ji Suk.]
[Thanks to Sang Jin,
Sung Kyun is alive.]
Thank you Sang Jin!
Seriously, unbelievable...
- Suk Jin, I'm sorry.
- Hey, how is your bingo going?
I'm so mad.
I'm so mad!
[Ji Suk Jin out.]
Ji Suk Jin out.
Right. Just as I expected.
The center needs to
open things up first.
[Everyone is excited
to mark their cards.]
The best spot.
From now, possibilities are open.
Ji Suk, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Ji Suk.
[Ji Suk Jin out.]
Sang Jin...
Oh, that's a good spot.
Not easy for me.
[Action!]
[The target is Sang Jin,
the passionate rookie.]
Hey, hey, please don't run fast.
Kwang Soo!
I have to help him.
[Sang Jin is a fast runner.]
Why do you keep running around and
taking off name tags and all?
I don't know.
[Jin Woong is going
against Sung Kyun again?]
There he goes again.]
[Sang Jin runs to
wherever the action is.]
[Sang Jin wants to join Sung Kyung
to go against Jin Woong.]
Got him!
[What?]
[Sung Kyun takes down Sang Jin!]
Wait, what's happening?
You and I stand about
this far apart.
Let's work together and
take off a name tag.
Push me away. Try it.
This is the best timing
for Sang Jin to come in.
Okay. Just tell me
what to do instead.
[This is how they teamed up.]
Hey.
Jin Woong. Jin Woong.
Pretend to attack me.
[Just as the script says. Action!]
['There they go!']
[The passionate rookie
runs right into the trap.]
How come he runs like that?
[So that's what happened.]
What's happening?
Please don't do this.
[Sang Jin does everything
he can to escape the trap.]
[Oh Sang Jin out.]
I had no idea it would be that easy.
- This must be the joy of fishing.
- I'll corner them in for you.
[How long will their
strategy last?]
If we keep doing this, the
only beneficiary is Jong Kook.
Let's do this then.
[Is Jin Woong sharing
the secret strategy?]
- To get Jong Kook?
- No, you... run into the building.
Jong Kook is...
Hey hey!
Kwang Soo, come here!
[Giraffe is the target now.]
[Chaos breaks out again.]
['Get Kwang Soo!']
[Yoo Hyuk avoids getting
eliminated by falling down.]
[Sung Kyung attacks
Yoo Hyuk again.]
Oh, wait a minute!
[Whoever shows his back becomes
the target in Death Bingo world.]
We need to get Jong Kook.
Come here, I should get you
because you disrespected me.
I thought you were
sending me a sign.
I'm sorry. I thought you
were sending me a sign.
I'll taking yours off.
I said I'm taking yours off.
- Please give me another chance.
- Have a seat. Stay there.
I was talking with him.
You're making him upset.
Don't do that.
He's right. We were talking...
We were in a conversation. You
should at least have some respect.
- You shouldn't do that either, Gary.
- What about?
Everyone needs a good talking to.
What day is it today?
Go on a date for a bit.
Not right now.
- I was talking with them.
- I wouldn't even...
Isn't it so much fun, Jae Suk?
[Even Jae Suk gets disciplined.]
- Kwang Soo, have a seat.
- Are you my teacher?
Let's sit. Let's sit, everyone.
Let's have a long distance talk.
- It's waste of human resources to keep this up.
- That's right.
We should take Kim Jong Kook
and Ha Ha out.
And no betraying anyone just because you
see an opening while we tag out Jong Kook.
[The person most
likely to do that.]
Everyone, while our goal is
for everyone to survive...
if we are to get Jong Kook, we should
expect one of us to be eliminated.
['Really?']
- If we don't tag out Jong Kook...
- Where are you going?
Ha Ha!
Come here.
Ha Ha, hurry.
Before we change our minds.
The first rule in surviving
long term in Running Man.
'Don't make an impulse move.'
Rule two. Before you join a gathering,
feel out the vibe before you do.
I would like one of
us to be the winner.
I hope so as well.
I hope Jong Kook doesn't win.
One, two, three.
Let's do it!
- Let's go.
- Okay.
This way.
I'll go this way.
Breaking through the front?
He might ambush us.
[They intend to surround him.]
[Nervous.]
['Are']
['You']
['Looking']
['For me?']
[Jong Kook was waiting for
his chance to move in.]
[Attacking Ha Ha.]
[Taking off his name tag
before he could react.]
[Then he disappears.]
[Blank.]
It was so scary.
- He came out of nowhere.
- It was Jong Kook.
[Everyone witnessed a
shocking hunt down.]
Our alliance is over.
[Did he really... gain
super powers last week?]
[This is how Mr. Capable
handles the alliance.]
Why can't you trust me?
['Yeah, I'm game.']
[Shocked.]
Everyone, let's mark
our cards first.
[We feel so scared but let's
do what needs to be done.]
Wow, that was so scary.
[Three players are
tagged out so far.]
I don't even have one line.
Jong Kook, you know I'm
your friend, right?
But you're too powerful.
Ah... I have nothing...
[Nobody has four complete
lines to win the game yet.]
- Sung Kyun, isn't it really scary?
- We're all that's left.
- He's so spooky.
- Where did he come from?
It's like we've been assaulted by
special forces like the Navy Seals.
Let's spread out in three
ways and look for him.
Two of you go that way and
let's meet around the back.
And what if he attacks again?
[The alliance is searching
for Mr. Capable.]
I don't think... we should
be talking as we walk.
We should be... extra cautious.
I felt like he'll jump
down from up there.
Don't you think so?
['You... think so?']
- Jong Kook might take us all out.
- We shouldn't waste human resources.
Jong Kook will end up winning again.
You were being very
disrespectful to me back there.
- You think I really wanted to do it?
- Right?
I was breaking your
fall, you know?
How did you grab my name
tag by tapping on it?
For a tiny split second you grabbed
it but didn't take it off.
What are you talking about?
You know? And you know who
our target is, right?
- Around here.
- Some place like here.
We should keep our eyes peeled.
[Yoo Hyun checks under the
vehicles just in case.]
[Mr. Capable again?]
['Jae Suk, it's me.']
['What the...']
[Betraying him 10 seconds
after promising not to.]
['Get over there!']
You'll see why.
[Jae Suk feels uncontrollable anger.]
[Because doing this gives Kwang Soo
two complete lines.]
- Jae Suk, I'm sorry.
- Hey, you call yourself human?
Please cover his mouth.
You call yourself human?
Hey, I'll...
Just the moment before...
He is...
Agh, seriously.
So mad!
So unfair!
Yoo Jae Suk out.
- Did Jong Kook do it?
- Jong Kook.
Kwang Soo!
You got to do what
you got to do.
[X's are adding up
more and more.]
So mad!
When Ji Hyo is out...
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo
tagged me out!
['I need to look for Ji Hyo.']
I think it's the most shocking thing
I came across in recent times.
It's so brutal here.
- Wow, Kwang Soo, seriously...
- How could Kwang Soo do that?
['It's time now.']
Is it possible to keep friends that way?
Very tough.
I don't hang out with him much.
[Anti-Mr. Capable Alliance
minus Kwang Soo.]
Jong Kook over there.
Don't come near.
Where is everyone?
Did you team up with Kwang Soo?
[Everyone is walking toward Jong Kook.]
[One person looks at the card.]
[Song Ji Hyo.]
['No, the Devil's talking to me.']
Are you going after Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo betrayed Jae Suk.
['Pull it, pull it, pull it, pull it.']
['Okay.']
[Going for Gary and Ji
Hyo at the same time.]
[There will be only
one winner anyway.]
[But.]
[Gary's name tag is still on?]
[Bingo Killer is not
too meticulous.]
Hey, good job. Wow.
But you didn't tag me out?
- I'm sorry.
- What happened?
- He should've tagged me out instead.
- So unbelievable.
['I am the Bingo Killer.']
- I'm sorry.
- Let's cross a name.
Let's check your cards.
[With Ji Hyo out, Sung Kyun
has two complete lines.]
Not too many of us left.
Thanks to him.
Here they are.
[Kkuk has one complete line.]
- Song Ji Hyo, out.
- Then I have two lines.
I should tag out Jin Woong for sure.
But Jong Kook...
Song Ji Hyo out.
I put Ji Hyo right
in the center.
- I have one line.
- Me too.
[A fun thing to do in jail.]
Once Jin Woong is out...
I have two.
- Me too.
- I need Sung Kyun.
Hey, let's get Jong Kook.
[But they've been
saying that for hours.]
Let's get it done at least once.
- Please stop looking at it.
- I...
to be honest... if I have
Kwang Soo and Gary's names...
- I win but...
- You're scaring me.
- However, I...
- Please look at me in a nice way.
I would like to catch a whale.
It's my dream.
I'm taking off my glasses.
OK.
['How many fingers are these?']
Let's go.
- Jin Woong, you won't tag me out by mistake?
- No, no.
- Since we're in a lion's den.
- Since we're born as men.
To catch a big one.
- Let's hold hands just in case.
- Let's hold hands.
['We're coming for you, Kim Jong Kook.']
There are a lot of cars there, right?
He's so weird.
He pretends to look over there
but his one eye looked at me.
How did he do that?
His one eye looked at me.
It's so weird.
- Awesome.
- My zodiac sign is the chameleon.
I was so scared.
[They look for Jong Kook
in the surveillance room.]
['Jong Kook, where are you?']
Oh! Oh? Over here.
[Here's Mr. Capable!]
What's the use in hiding?
Let's stand where I won't
get hurt if I fall down.
- Okay, let's go.
- Time to face off.
- Let's not hesitate.
- Here, here they are.
Time to face off.
I'll block the escape route.
Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
[But Jong Kook grabs him
instead and...]
[takes him out!]
['What just happened here?']
['He was running straight
into Jong Kook.']
[Forlorn.]
Are you alright?
- Are you alright?
- Something brushed by me.
I... looked at Jong Kook's face...
When, when did he get there?
We... we should change our plan.
[Might be easier for him to tag out
Gary and Kwang Soo at the same time.]
Now that you're out... I hate
that I'm crossing off your name.
[Sung Kyun has three lines.]
[He just needs one more
name to win the game.]
[And Kwang Soo needs to tag out
Sung Kyun or Jong Kook to win.]
[Gary also needs to tag out
[Jong Kook needs to tag
out Sung Kyun to win.]
- To be absolutely clear...
- Who tagged you out?
I resisted to the best of
my ability till the end.
- Kim Jong Kook?
- It was a fierce battle.
Did you go for Jong
Kook by yourself?
- And by myself.
- Really?
It was so fierce.
- Jong Kook was extremely surprised.
- Oh...
- Since your clothes are still clean...
- That's true.
But look at my shoe laces.
- Let's go in together.
- We were in too much of a hurry.
Alright. Going for Kim Sung Kyun.
I just need to get Kim Sung Kyun.
And it's game over.
I need Sung Kyun.
We need good team work.
He's extremely fast as well.
There he is.
[One more name to
decide the outcome.]
[Who'll be tagged out first?]
I can see what you're thinking.
I can see.
Why not walk straight?
[They were walking sideways.]
You know...
Why are you walking like this?
Why walk like this?
Let's go together,
and holding hands.
And why do you grab my
hands loosely? Why?
Let's hold tightly.
[The alliance was formed
to catch the big one.]
[But...]
[What has respect got to do
with winning?]
[Giraffe takes the
easy road to victory.]
Kim Sung Kyun out.
[Kwang Soo and Gary
have 4 complete lines!]
Am I out?
Kim Sung Kyun out.
[They are still playing a fantasy
game of bingo.]
Hey! Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
[Who will get to claim
the victory first?]
[So close!]
Oh, what's this?
Bingo!
- Bingo!
- What's this?
[How did Kkuk get here?]
There might be someone who
has to tag out Sung Kyun.
In a split second, I need
to start running toward it.
[As soon as he heard
the announcement...]
[he ran toward the end zone.]
[That's how he claimed the victory
with a walk in the park.]
You need to use your head more
than your muscles. For sure.
['Look, who's talking.']
You can't be saying that.
[The final winner is
Kim Jong Kook.]
- Hey, what is this?
- Not happy to see you at all.
Thanks to your betrayal.
It's because you tagged me out.
- No, Jae Suk.
- Hear me out. Oh, what's this?
Oh, it's a bingo card.
[A golden bingo card.]
- It should be worth about 27 million won.
- That's trophy.
- I can't trust anyone.
- Don't call me this week.
- He's the one!
- Kwang Soo!
You got what you deserve!
How many lines did you have?
- You know, it's...
- How many... one line?
The thing is I didn't
tag out anyone either.
He didn't tag out anyone and not good
at bingo either, but he kept on leading.
He was leading the charge
way in front of everyone.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Genius harpist, Oh Yeon Seo.]
[Genius pianist, Kim Ji Hoon.]
[Voice from Heaven, Jung Eun Ji.]
[Seven other geniuses.]
[But.]
[Someone kidnapped a genius.]
[A kidnapping incident.]
How could I trust you?
I knew you were the culprit.
[Find and chase down the culprit.]
The culprit is...
one of us.