[A worldwide celebration-
2014 Sochi Winter Olympics has begun.]
[Four years of tears and sweat.]
[Republic of Korea's best athletes
are getting their chance to shine.]
[2014 Running Winter Olympics-
The hell training camp starts now.]
[The hellish training that starts with the
fiercest mental training in show's history.]
[A tough journey meant for
best of the best in the country.]
I'd rather just die.
[Fierce Training Camp]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Gyunggi-Do Yangpyung.
'M' Training camp.]
[A place a little less glamorous
than Sochi...]
[2014 Winter Olympics Training Camp.]
[A place where 2014 Running Winter Olympics
will take place.]
Shouldn't we be walking in
a single file line?
Why do we have to do this?
It's not like we're athletes.
[Team Running Man makes their entrance.]
- Winter Olympics?
- We're doing the Winter Olympics?
All of the athletes from our nation are
working so hard over in Sochi right now.
- We hope that no one gets injured.
- We wish everyone a safe journey.
[Medals aside, we wish the absolute best
for all of our participating athletes.]
[It's time for the opposing team
to make their entrance.]
Who are we playing against?
- No!
[A feeling of unease
is settling over the team...]
- What if we get really strong opponents?
- Who's coming as our guests?
Who's coming that this thing is
toppling over?
[Just who will come out as their opponents?]
[It's me.]
[Captain of the All Star Team- Kkuk.]
Look at the way he's sauntering out here.
He needs to slip and fall flat on his face
for him to know any humility.
[Kkuk is the captain
of their opposing team for the day.]
Kim Jong Kook came out wearing
something around his legs.
- What is he wearing?
- Muscles.
[Kkuk is showcasing all his muscles today.]
Please allow me to introduce you
to my team.
[Who did Kkuk bring out as members
of his All Star Team?]
Come on out!
[Second member of the All Star Team is...]
[An all-around entertainer, Seo In Guk.]
[The mythical lion- Son Ho Jun]
- My team is no joke!
- There's someone else coming.
[An actor who exudes warmth and charm-
Park Seo Joon.]
[Nice entrance.]
[He is now a bonafide actor too-
B1A4's Baro.]
Jong Kook is the ugliest member
on his team right now.
[Overflowing with youth and vigor.]
- Who's the girl?
- There's a girl?
[The sole female member of
the All Star Team.]
[Always charming and unpredictable,
Actress- Kang Ye Won.]
- It's Kang Ye Won.
- I can't believe she's here.
[The All Star Team thus completes
making their entrance.]
You're in trouble now, Ji Hyo.
Her personality is nothing to mess with.
- Our Ji Hyo is no joke!
- Ji Hyo's nothing to mess with.
Ji Hyo even swears!
[Looking forward to these two fierce women
facing off with one another.]
She's only shown us a timid side of her on TV,
but in reality, she's actually quite wild.
But for once, I think we finally have a guest
who's going to fit Jong Kook better in age.
You really shouldn't say anything
about age to an actress.
Our Ji Hyo's an actress too,
and she tells us how old she is.
- How old are you?
- 34 years old.
[As always... The ever so cool Blank Ji.]
- You've got a really great team.
- Look at that. In Guk, Ho Jun...
Seo Joon and even Baro.
- You guys are a formidable team.
- That's too strong of a team.
- This is the team I'm supposed to lead.
- Seriously.
Those guys with Jong Kook as their captain
is like having a dream team of our own here.
Why did you send Jong Kook over as
the captain to a team like that?
[On top of all those members,
Muscle Boy is their captain?]
I think the only member that Jong Kook knows
of everyone on his team is In Guk.
- No, that's not true.
- Come on, be honest. You don't know Ho Jun.
- This is your first time meeting Ho Jun.
- No, I don't know him, but he's a singer.
[What?
Ho Jun started out as a singer?]
- Oh, you don't want me to say that?
- No, I don't.
[Is it a past that Ho Jun wants
to keep buried in secret?]
- Which group were you in?
- I was very briefly in a boy band group.
- What was the name of the group?
- It was called, Tachyon.
- Oh, Tachyon!
- Stop playing around!
- Don't act like you know that group!
- You were really in Tachyon?
[Tachyon-
'A particle faster than the speed of light.']
[But it was the group that disappeared
faster than the speed of light...]
[Waiting to hear Ho Jun speak in his
warm Jeonllado native dialect.]
It's so cold and nasty out here,
so let's just get this show on the road.
- That's it!
- You do know how to speak in the dialect!
This is my first time ever meeting Seo Joon.
[This is Seo Joon's first time
appearing on a variety show.]
- He's really popular with the older ladies.
- Seriously?
[Seo Joon has been known to wring some tears
on the current hit drama, 'One Warm Word'.]
He's so good looking.
Can you introduce yourself, Seo Joon?
Hello, I'm 2014's new star in the spotlight,
Park Seo Joon.
[Appraising himself strongly.]
[Stay tuned for this young man's
eye opening action on this episode.]
[Just then...]
Isn't that the Olympics?
[Wait... that screen is?]
[Running Man's resident announcer, Kim Hwan.]
They did a good job of fooling us.
This is where new categories in the
winter Olympics will be introduced.
Representatives from each country
are waiting most anxiously
to hear which new categories have been
added to this year's winter Olympics.
They all look so serious.
[Winter Olympics new sports category?]
[Just which new sports category
has been added to this year's Olympics?]
They must've added some new
sports category.
[Which new Winter Olympics sports category has
been added on for the whole world to enjoy?]
[Icy Field Name Tag Elimination.]
Icy Field Name Tag Elimination
has been added on as an official sports
category of the 2014 Winter Olympics.
[Running News-
Icy Field Name Tag Elimination.]
We hope that all the participating teams
will play with honorable showmanship
that is befitting of
the highly respected Olympics game.
I'm so envious that
Hwan gets to work indoors today.
You will be playing to determine which team
it will be that will participate in
the newly added on category of Icy Field
Name Tag Elimination at the 2014 games.
What?
Only one team?
Yes, you will have to play several
different qualifying rounds
to determine which of the two teams will
participate in this year's Winter Olympics.
Are we seriously going to the Olympics?
Can you be a little more clear?
- Are you serious? Are we going?
- Stop kidding around, and tell us the truth.
[Are we seriously going to Sochi?]
- Seriously?
- Are we really going to go?
How can he maintain such
a serious face?
[Icy Field Name Tag Elimination-
Order of the qualifying rounds.]
- Depart?
- We're going to be departing today?
[Departing for Sochi today?]
[Training camp with a definitive
set of reward and punishment.]
The winning team can rest as much as
they'd like during the rest periods
but the loser team cannot rest whatsoever
even during the rest periods.
As I'm sure you may all already know,
the team that wins the first round can rest
but the loser team has to prepare the meal
during rest period for everyone else.
The team that loses the second round
will have to do the laundry.
And the team that loses the third round
will have to chop up all the firewood.
Those are the various rounds and
punishments that are lined up for you.
- Yes, we understand.
- We will now start the first round.
- Gather at the ice field by 11:00 a.m.
- Let's go!
[2014 Winter Olympics hell training camp.]
[2. Speed Strength Training.
Loser team cooks lunch while others rest.]
[First training round for the chance at the
glory of being the national representatives.]
- Why are you guys all running?
- We have to hurry.
[Everyone must stay on their toes!]
[Gyunggi-do Yangpyung 'B' training village.]
Look at the skates over there.
[First training arena- The ice rink.]
[What kind of a training session
awaits them here?]
- Welcome everyone.
- Thank you.
We're national representatives.
You're still on reserve as standbys,
you're not the national representatives yet.
[In order to become official representatives,
they must first get through their training.]
This training session is to help
strengthen your skills in speed.
It's the short track.
- The short track?
- You will all have to skate a full round.
This round will be done in a relay.
This round will determine how quick
you're able to skate around the rink.
This is really unfair to us.
These guys are amazing runners.
[But their skating abilities are yet unknown.]
We have to take our shoes off
before we put the skates on, right?
Of course, you do.
- Yes, you have to take your shoes off first.
- I've never skated before.
I've never worn skates before in my life.
[This is Big-nose's first experience
with ice skates as well.]
[In Guk, on the other hand, is blazing around
the rink like an experienced skater.]
Why don't you try it, Seo Joon?
[Seo Joon's completely at ease as well.
Skating like a pro!]
- This is really unfair to us.
- He's a great skater.
- Seo Joon's really good.
- Hey, Ha Ha!
[Can't let them beat us!
Team RM's Ha Ha shows off his skills.]
You really are short.
You're much shorter than Seo Joon.
[Even though his stature may be short,
he's showing off some decent skills!]
Who do you think should go first?
- This is Kwang Soo's first time.
- This is my first time.
- You want to go first?
- No, I'm saying that this is my first time.
- This is my first time skating too.
- Me too.
[Team RM is full of first time skaters.]
I'm going to lose my mind.
We have no hope of winning.
What are we supposed to do now?
The winning team will leave the ice,
and rest comfortably in a nice warm room.
The loser team will have to stop by
a grocery store...
and buy the necessary grocery items for lunch,
and while the winning team is resting.
The loser team will have to cook
and prepare lunch for everyone.
[The loser team will have to cook
and prepare lunch for the winning team.]
[Lunch menu will be determined
by the winning team.]
If our team ends up winning,
our team doesn't eat things like ramen.
- So we're going to want something healthy.
- How about some stew?
[They're already listing out
what they want for lunch?]
I want some chicken stew.
- Fighting!
Good luck, Kwang Soo!
[Kwang Soo vs Ye Won.]
[First skating experience for both of them.]
[Gripping tightly onto Kwang Soo
as soon as they start off.]
[Ye Won isn't letting go of Kwang Soo
even as he falls onto the ice.]
- What is she doing?
- You can't hold onto him.
Shake her off.
[Rudolph Kwang Soo is skating full speed
on ahead with Ye Won on his back.]
[Giraffe sled is moving along
much faster than expected!]
- Let go of me!
- Good job, Ye Won!
[Suk Jin vs Baro.]
[Touching off simultaneously.]
[Immediately gets back up on his feet
to get on his way!]
[Baro catches up to Suk Jin
in the blink of an eye.]
[Middle aged Big-nose loses strength
in his legs midway through his lap.]
[Ji Hyo vs Jong Kook.]
You have to push his butt.
[Mr. Capable,
the captain of the All Star Team!]
[Mr. Capable blazes on ahead!]
[Taking the lead by more than half the rink!]
[Gary vs. Son Ho Jun]
I'm so sorry!
[Their ambition to be in the Olympics
is only getting stronger!]
Hurry, Ji Hyo!
[Team RM touches off.]
[First time skater, Gary,
catches up to Ho Jun!]
- Ho Jun.
- Ho Jun!
[Starting to cheat out of desperation.]
[But Gary quickly catches up to him again.]
[Even fails at his attempt to cheat.]
[Jae Suk vs In Guk.]
[Jae Suk quickly gets on his way.]
[But his opponent is Ace In Guk.]
- Be careful!
- No!
[Will Jae Suk get caught?
Will In Guk catch up to him?]
[Unable to predict the outcome of this race!]
[Last two skaters-
Ha Ha vs Seo Joon.]
[The last two skaters,
Ace of the two teams gets on their way!]
[The fate of victory...
lies in the hands of these two skaters!]
[Ha Ha takes the initial lead.]
[Haroro is the skating ace of Team RM!]
[A fierce battle for victory!]
[Eyes a momentary opportunity at the turn...]
[And Seo Joon takes the lead!]
[A shocking spurt of speed!]
[Full speed ahead... and bam!]
[How can this be!]
[With the finish line
right in front of his eyes...]
[Thanks to Seo Joon's mishap,
Team RM wins the battle!]
[A real life drama unfolding
right in front of their eyes.]
[Best out of three rounds-
Team RM: 1 vs Team All Star: 0.]
[What a disappointing loss...]
- Best out of three.
- We can do this!
- We can win this!
- We're Running Man!
- Yes, we're Running Man!
Kim Jong Kook, you said you don't want
ramen? We want a ramen party!
I didn't think of Seo Joon's skills.
I didn't know that he'd be this bad.
Were you trying to be funny or something?
Tell us what happened.
- I'm not good at skating.
- Seriously?
- Why are you telling us that now?
- Why didn't you tell us that earlier?
Team RM wins the first round.
[One more win, and Team RM wins the mission!]
[Figuring out the order of skaters
for the second round of the race.]
Ho Jun.
While I'm still being nice...
do a better job.
Okay, Ho Jun?
Show them what you can do.
- Yes, I understand.
- Okay? Just don't fall too far behind.
[Ho Jun's determination to win is upped
after Mr. Capable's pep talk?]
Let's just end it with this round.
- Let's not bother with a third round.
- Let's go to Sochi!
- Yeah!
- Let's go!
I'll do it right this time instead of
skating like I don't know what I'm doing.
[His mishap during the previous round
was just a show?]
- He says he'll skate normally this time.
- Really?
- I'll show them what I can do this time.
- Really? Okay.
- Let's go!
- That was all a part of our plan.
[Getting into position as if
he knows what he's doing.]
- Maybe he really is a good skater.
- He looks like he knows what he's doing.
What's he doing?
[But... something seems a little off?]
Ho Jun, shouldn't it be your front leg
that should be standing on its toes?
[Ah... that's right...]
Ho Jun, shouldn't it be your front leg
that should be standing on its toes?
[He's confused as to what he needs to do
with his front and the back leg.]
[Could this be a part of the act too?]
[Finally ready to start the second round.]
[Second Round- Start!]
[Could Ho Jun really be a good skater?]
[Just as expected...
Ho Jun is back to his walk-skate mode.]
[It's still a close call between
these two weakest skaters.]
[Ji Hyo vs Jong Kook.]
[Mr. Capable catches up
to take the lead as expected.]
[But Ji Hyo still stays hot on his heels!]
[Huh? Team All Star's next skater is...]
[Am I next?]
[While Jong Kook is busy trying to find out
who the next skater on his team is...]
[Ji Hyo touches off on
Team RM's third skater, Gary!]
[Team All Star's third skater, Ye Won,
belatedly gets on her way.]
[Mr. Gary takes a big lead.]
[A huge gap between the two skaters!]
[Team RM's fourth skater, Kwang Soo,
waits in ready for his turn.]
[Kkuk grabs onto the Giraffe's ankle
to make him trip and fall on his face.]
[Succeeds in buying
some time through cheating.]
[Giraffe gets on the way once
he gets his wherewithal back.]
[Ace In Guk of Team All Star is off!]
- Grab Kwang Soo when he comes.
- Okay.
[In Guk catches up to Kwang Soo
like a bolt of lightning.]
- Hurry, Kwang Soo!
- I'm almost there!
[Ye Won blocks Kwang Soo as planned.]
[Ace of Team All Star!
In Guk is already back at the line!]
[Rushing off to push Jae Suk off!]
[Their other ace, Seo Joon,
follows in Jae Suk's wake.]
[The two skaters are moving
full speed ahead without any hesitation.]
[But the gap between the two skaters
starts to close up...]
[And Seo Joon ultimately
catches up to Jae Suk.]
[Final skaters- Ha Ha vs Baro.]
[Just like the previous round,
the victory lies in their hands!]
[These two will determine which
of the two teams will claim victory!]
[Will it be Team RM's Ace, Haroro...]
[Or will be the Idol Muscle Boy, Baro?]
[Will he catch up to him... or not?]
[So close to the finish line!]
[Oh my God!]
[Thanks to Baro's tumble...
Team RM wins!]
[Team RM takes the victory!]
[First training round- Speed Training.
Team RM takes the win!]
[All Star Team must serve Team RM
whatever they desire for their lunch!]
Ramen!
I want ramen!
Shall we tell them to prepare a full
traditional Korean meal?
- How about some meat?
- I want boodae jjigae.
- Boodae jjigae?
- I like boodae jjigae.
Boodae jjigae?
Okay, we can do that.
We want boodae jjigae, and beef ribs...
- How about spicy pork?
- And we also want spicy chicken stew.
Will you be able to handle all that?
- I can make a really good spicy chicken stew.
- Really? Spicy chicken stew.
Why do you keep making things
worse for us?
- Why are you making all this work for us?
- Because Ho Jun needs to redeem himself.
He's trying to redeem himself
even if it's with his cooking.
Spicy chicken stew, boodae jjigae, duruchigi.
('Everything' soup, and Korean bouillabaisse.]
- Let's go and rest.
- We'll see you guys later.
[The winners skate out of there
for some R & R.]
- So this is what defeat feels like.
- I vow that we'll win the next one.
[All Star team has to do the grocery shopping
and the cooking as their penalty for losing.]
[Team RM heads off to a warm and cozy
dormitory to get some rest.]
- This is nice!
- It was all about teamwork.
- Everyone thought that we'd lose too.
- Gary and Ji Hyo skated very well too.
But... there's something that
I'm nervous about.
- Ramen is a must in boodae jjigae.
- That's a vital part of the stew.
- It's not boodae jjigae without ramen.
- Let's stop on our way and buy some ramen.
Okay.
[Preparing themselves just in case
Jong Kook doesn't buy any ramen.]
Can you stop the bus if you see any
convenience stores on the way?
[Doesn't leave anything to chance
when it comes to food.]
This is a pretty nice kitchen.
This isn't bad.
It's pretty nice.
We can't use the water in here.
The drain pipe is clogged right now.
There's a water hose outside, so that's
where you can get the water to cook.
[The youngest of the bunch are assigned
the task of washing everything.]
Chicken...
how many servings of chicken are this?
I'm only used to cooking one serving.
[Ho Jun is unsure of how to cook
this large of a serving portion.]
[Will he be able to pull it off?]
[Ye Won is in charge of the spicy pork.]
[Winner of 2014 Cooking Competition- Kkuk.]
[Having to wash the rice outside
in the midst of this cold winter weather...]
[Feels like a bucket of ice!]
[The sorrow is starting to seep in?]
I don't think it would be good
for my mother to see this.
[I miss you, Mommy...]
[Everyone who steps up to this spot
ends up screaming out in pain.]
- Let's turn it sideways.
- Want some more snacks?
Ji Hyo's really sleep deprived lately from
having to film her current drama
so we should just let her sleep.
We need her rested
if we want to win the next game.
Now that I know what it's like to win,
I want to win even more now.
If we lose the next game,
they're really going to make us pay.
That'll be the end of us.
How about we play this game,
and make the loser wake Ji Hyo up?
How about we make the loser go outside
and see how the cooking is coming along?
Okay, shall we do that?
[The person whose turn makes the doll
pop out of its spot loses the game.]
Don't think about it, and just stick it in.
[Yoo Jae Suk loses!]
- He's a born entertainer.
- Let's go, Kwang Soo.
[Recruits the youngest member as
punishment for suggesting the game.]
Go ahead.
[The remaining members go back
to their resting mode.]
- I think I want to lay down for a bit.
- How could it be the two of us?
What do you mean, the two of us?
I didn't lose that game.
- Garlic and onions.
- Give them everything that you need washed.
- Let's go.
- When will our lunch be ready?
- Is it going to be a while yet?
- Just leave us alone so that we can cook.
- Why are you mincing the garlic?
- Because I can't mince you.
- I'll go back to mincing the garlic, okay?
- Yeah... okay.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jong Kook?
- Go rinse off the chicken, Kwang Soo.
- Go rinse off the chicken.
- This needs to get rinsed off.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but Kwang Soo can't do that for you.
- What are you talking about?
- We just need these two things rinsed off.
Okay, we'll do that
if it's just those two things.
- Hurry, Kwang Soo.
- You can do that for us, can't you?
[They may have walked in on their own,
but when they can leave is up to Mr. Capable.]
We'll send Suk Jin and Ha Ha
if you'll let us go.
- Okay, then.
- Okay. That'll be funnier anyways.
- Are you letting us off the hook then?
- Just go wash the onions, Kwang Soo.
No, that's not what we meant.
I don't think you understood.
No, I heard you and I understand.
But since you're already here anyways...
[Since you're already here,
do some work before you leave.]
Then Jae Suk and I'll just go and wash
these two onions for you, okay?
[A joint effort of washing the two onions.]
[They never should've came out
to see how the cooking was going...]
[Cold water in the middle of the winter?]
I can't fathom how cold this must be.
Having to do laundry would be awful.
We have to avoid having to do the laundry.
We really have to wash it here?
- Hey, In Guk.
- Is this where you've been doing the washing?
Wow, that's cold!
[Icy cold water-
Automatically screams out in pain.]
I'll go get the bag.
[Screams out in agony.]
- What's that noise outside?
- What's that noise?
That scared me.
I thought they were slaughtering a chicken.
- You thought a chicken was being slaughtered?
- Yes.
[It's not a chicken being slaughtered,
but it's a giraffe.]
[Almost lost his voice
from having had to wash the onion.]
- Wow, that was so cold.
- That was amazing.
[Looking up spicy chicken stew recipes.]
[Ho Jun's chicken stew is
starting to take shape.]
[Adds the minced garlic to the spicy pork.]
What are you doing?
[Poured over half the bag of sugar
into the egg roll up mixture.]
[Chef Ye Won's method of measuring.]
Why did you pour in so much sugar?
[Not listening...]
Why don't you try cooking it now?
I think we need to see
how it turns out in the pan.
[Chef Ye Won's spicy pork dish
is nearing completion.]
[Bay top shell is almost ready too.]
- This is the frozen kind.
- Frozen instant boodae jjigae.
[Frozen instant boodae jjigae
is ready as well.]
- Do we have to add any water to this?
- Yes, 750ml... so we need to add 1,500ml.
Let's do better with the next game so that
we don't have to do the laundry.
- Let's not do the laundry.
- There's no way we can do the laundry.
[Spicy chicken stew and boodae jjigae
is nearing completion.]
- When are we ever going to get to eat?
- Baro.
- Baro, can we eat soon?
- We're almost done.
What's taking you guys so long?
You guys are working so hard.
- Thanks for the hard work, Baro.
- Want me to wash that for you?
- Yes.
- You do?
Okay.
[Why... did you ask that?]
- Wow, it smells really good in here.
- Wow.
[Exhausted from having to wait,
the winning team heads into the kitchen.]
- Everyone is saying how good your food is.
- It smells really good in here.
Wow, thanks for everyone's hard work.
Jae Suk, stop standing around,
and go set the table.
[Kkuk puts him back to work
as soon as he lays his eyes on him.]
- I'm sorry, but did you not make the jjigae?
- We did make it. It's simmering over here.
Don't you see it simmering over here?
- Did you forget the ramen?
- Did you not put any ramen in there?
- Where is the ramen?
- Sorry to ask, but did you not put any...
There's no ramen in there.
I don't like it. I don't like ramen,
so I didn't put any in there.
- Jae Suk.
- How can you not put any ramen in there?
We had a feeling you might do that,
so we bought some.
[Bought the ramen themselves from
the convenience store earlier.]
[Team RM was right on with their prediction.]
[It's enough to make their mouths water.]
You're all much better cooks
than I had thought you'd be.
- What are you doing?
- You have to put ramen in there.
- Take it out.
- You have to add ramen in there.
- I'm going to take it back out.
- What are you talking about?
How can you have boodae jjigae
without ramen in there?
Add more ramen in there, Jae Suk.
Do what you have to do
to get the ramen in there.
- Are we done?
- Yes, we're all done.
Here it comes.
Watch out for the boodae jjigae.
Look at that spicy chicken stew.
Thank you for the delicious meal.
[Thank you for the delicious lunch.]
This soup is amazing with the ramen in it.
[Boodae jjigae and ramen
is a match made in heaven]
The broth is really refreshing.
It almost has a seafood stew flavor to it.
You put way too much ramen in there.
Look at that mess.
- Get all the ramen out of there.
- Other people behind me want some too.
[People behind him want some ramen too...]
- Wow, this all looks so good.
- This is all so good.
- Thanks for a delicious meal!
- Thank you!
It's delicious!
It really is tasty.
- Can I get some Americano when we're done?
- You brew your own Americano!
That's a very hot tempered young man.
[This is a hot tempered
young man's restaurant.]
Who made the spicy chicken stew?
Is it pretty good?
[It seems as though Ho Jun's dish
is a huge success!]
Hey, Ho Jun. If you're this good at cooking,
I wonder how good you'll be with laundry.
- I can't wait to see your laundry skills.
- You did a great job.
[Strength training on concentration skills.]
[Arrives at the next training arena.]
[A brook still frozen over with ice.]
- Is this it?
- What are we going to be doing here?
[What kind of a training session
awaits them here?]
They want us to just go in.
We have to make sure to win this time.
[Just what... could it be?]
What is this?
What do they want us to do here?
We have to stand with our
own team members.
[Captain of the All Star Team
is standing with the Team RM members.]
- Think about what you're doing.
- I forgot that we're on separate teams.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to welcome everyone to your second
round of Hell Training Camp.
[Second round of Hell Training Camp.]
[Strength training on concentration skills.]
- Do you see the two tables behind you?
- Yes.
- You have to go into the brook...
- What?
- We have to go in there?
- Go into the stream.
You have to get a rock from the stream,
and build a six-rock tower on the table.
- This was designed to help you focus better.
- It's the middle of the winter.
- You'll be doing it while barefoot.
- How is that related to our ability to focus?
You'll find out once you start the mission.
The mission will be done as a relay course.
If the third person topples the tower over,
then do we have to start over again?
- No, the third person will have to fix it.
- Okay, start over with that person.
[If the tower topples over, then the person
responsible for toppling it must fix it.]
Please take off all your shoes and socks,
and put them in the yellow basket.
[Confiscating all their socks and shoes.]
The team that loses this round...
will have to do laundry with water
that is a bit colder than this brook water.
- There's no way I want to do that.
- We have to win this round.
I really don't want to do it.
- This is no joke.
- I know.
[Just having to be barefoot alone is
enough to make them break out in screams.]
Whatever.
[A long and arduous journey to
become the best of the best.]
- Okay, I'm all set.
- My feet are freezing!
Fighting!
No laundry for us!
[Ready]
[Frigid icy water? No problem.]
[Refreshing beyond their wildest imagination?]
[Ho Jun moves forward by avoiding the snow
by stepping on the rocks.]
[Picks out a big flat rock
easier for building.]
Don't think about getting in his way,
and just pick out a rock of your own!
[Kwang Soo chooses a rock of his own.]
[All Star team completes the first tier.]
[It's a relay race, so he
must return quickly back to his team.]
[But he doesn't have the courage
to go back.]
[The next players are anxiously waiting.]
[Ho Jun touches off with In Guk.]
[Automatically turns back around.]
That's no joke!
[Kwang Soo in the meantime
arrives back to his own teammates.]
[Touches off with Jae Suk.]
[Automatically turns back around
as soon as they step foot on the snow.]
[Must endure the pain if they want to
become the national representatives!]
[Jae Suk turns back around!]
[In Guk picks up the first rock
his hand falls on.]
[Lays down the second tier.]
That rock is too round!
You have to swap it out for a flatter one.
[Swapping out the rock
as told by captain Kkuk.]
[Team RM swaps out their players.]
[Suk Jin heads out as the second player.]
Hurry, In Guk!
I can't do it!
I really want to go back too,
but I just can't do it!
[Suk Jin forges on ahead with
a rock in his hand.]
[All Star Team completes their second tier.]
Good job.
Our tower is perfect so far.
- Hurry back!
- Just run!
[Team RM barely manages to
complete their second tier as well.]
You need to place it steadier than that!
It's all about sacrifice.
You know how it is.
[In Guk loudly makes his return.]
[Third player, Seo Joon gets on his way.]
[But...]
[His steps are so strong and steady.]
[Does Seo Joon not feel the cold?
No, doubt that!]
Hurry, Seo Joon.
[But he endures the pain,
and moves steadily on ahead.]
Is Seo Joon not even fazed?
[Ha Ha from Team RM gets on his way!]
[Calmly... completes the third tier.]
Seo Joon lost his ability to speak.
[Silent... Ice Prince.]
[The Ice Prince finally says something
at the end of his silence.]
[Shout of agony from all the pain
that he's just had to endure.]
- Is this good?
- Yeah, that's good.
- Dong Hoon!
- Hurry back, Dong Hoon.
You have to hurry back!
What kind of a rock is that?
[Team RM's third tier has zero stability.]
My turn?
[Captain Kkuk's turn.]
[Seo Joon may have started out manly,
but he returns screaming and crying.]
[Captain Kkuk's turn to head out.]
[You think you won't feel the cold
just because you're Mr. Capable?]
That's a good one.
[Finds a large flat rock at once!]
[Jae Suk finally gets on his way.]
Anything is better than
having to do the laundry.
[The All Star Team completes
their fourth tier.]
- You have to get the rock, Jae Suk!
- Hurry up and get it!
Get the rock!
Don't sit down and just come back.
[What?]
Just come back, Jong Kook.
[Captain and the teammates are all alike
in their intensity...]
Hurry up!
I don't see any rocks.
- I can't find any rocks.
- What do you mean? They're all around you!
[Rocks are all over the place...]
We've got two tiers left to go.
We've only got two left to go, right?
[All Star Team wins if they can finish
two more tiers!]
- Wow, this is no joke.
- Is it my turn?
[Ye Won's turn.]
[Ye Won is given special permission
to do the mission with her leggings on.]
Hurry, Ye Won!
[Team RM barely manages to
complete their fourth tier.]
[All Star Team is already finished
with their fifth tier.]
[One more tier, and All Star Team wins!]
[The last player of the group, Baro,
gets on his way!]
[Baro is struggling to forge ahead.]
- You go first, Gary.
- Me? You want me to go first?
- Hurry up and go, Gary!
- You want me to go first?
Don't think about anything.
Don't think about anything!
We have to win this!
[Victory must be ours!
Gary tries talking himself out of the pain.]
Okay, let's not think about anything!
- You're not in pain!
- Just think about winning the game!
[Gary is forging ahead
without any hesitation.]
- Don't' think about anything.
- You're not in any pain, Gary!
That's right.
Just think about winning, Kang Gary!
[Team RM's tower ultimately topples over.]
No!
[Even at the briefest glance,
these are not stackable rocks.]
[All Star Team on the other hand
completes building their tower.]
- How am I supposed to do this?
- We won!
[Round one- All Star Team wins!]
[Best out of three-
Team RM: 0 vs All Star Team: 1.]
[Quite a crowd of fans have gathered around.]
All Star Team won the first round.
If the All Star Team wins this round too,
then they win the game.
- Are you all very cold right now?
- Yes.
The second round will be played
with only three players.
Just three people.
- It's over if we win this round.
- That's right.
- But if we lose, then we have to play again?
- We have to finish it.
- Yes, we have to end it now.
[Team RM's players- Gary, Ji Hyo and Ha Ha.]
[All Star Team- In Guk, Jong Kook, and Baro.]
A round of applause!
[Second game of Hell Training Camp.]
[Second round- Go!]
You're doing great, Ji Hyo.
[Ace Blank Ji gets on her way
without any hesitation.]
[Baro is moving slower than
expected of him.]
[Team RM completes their first tier while
Baro is still busy searching for his rock.]
[All Star Team follows immediately behind
with the completion of their own tier.]
[That's our Ace! Leading with
a huge gap between the two teams.]
[Second player for Team RM- Ha Ha.]
Hurry.
Get back up here.
[Captain Kkuk is on his way!]
[Catches up to the other team
in the blink of an eye.]
[But while Captain Kkuk is busy
swapping out his rock...]
[The gap between the two teams
widens again.]
[Final player for Team RM- Gary.]
[Touches off with the final player, In Guk.]
[While Gary walks on precariously...]
[In Guk forges full speed ahead.]
[They both arrives at their own table
simultaneously.]
[They just need to complete the final tier.]
[Just who... will come out the winner?]
[In Guk was faster!]
[All Star Team wins two rounds in a row!]
[Final score-
Team RM: 0 vs All Star Team: 2.]
Come on, Gary!
[All Star Team has redeemed themselves from
their defeat at the short track game.]
Let's do best out of five!
- Let's do best out of five!
- No way!
[Adamantly refuses.]
Please, I beg of you!
Let's do best out of five!
- I'm sorry, but there's no way.
- Best out of five!
[Trying to convince them with
the help from the crowd.]
Enough!
[Kwang Soo... that's enough now.]
The All Star Team can go back to the basecamp
and rest in the warm room.
[It's the All Star Team's turn to rest!]
[Result of their phenomenal teamwork.]
[The two teams' situation has
turned 180 degrees.]
[Team RM must now do
the laundry as penalty for their defeat.]
Is there no hot water?
Look at that huge pile.
- I'm too scared to even start.
- Do we have to put them all in there first?
What's wrong?
- What's it like?
- Dip your hand in the water.
The water must be practically frozen over.
[The cold temperature of the water
only draws out their laughter of disbelief.]
Laughter of disbelief is all I can manage.
[Time to start the laundry.]
No, I'll do the rinsing.
No, don't do it.
I don't want you to do that.
His idea of rinsing is
just swishing it around half heartedly.
- What's wrong with how I do it?
- No, nerve mind.
Even the soap feels like a block of ice.
- I think the soap is frozen solid.
- Seriously?
- The soap feels like ice.
- Here, Gary.
This is driving me crazy.
[Their screams turn into
laughter of disbelief.]
The clothes are going to freeze into
blocks of ice if we hang them up to dry.
Why would you want us to wash these now,
and hang them up to dry this late at night?
Whose shirt is this?
Why did you leave this on here?
Wow, this is unbelievably cold.
How can they expect us to do this out here
in the middle of winter?
Can't they just put it in the washer?
- We'll give you a few more pairs of gloves.
- Yes, please!
- The gloves don't even make a difference.
- It makes no difference right now.
Suk Jin's lying to you.
It's much better.
[Four years of having to deal with
Suk Jin's devious schemes.]
It's much better.
[Just then, PD Hwan Jin comes out
carrying a basket full of laundry.]
[All the towels that they used
by the brook earlier during the game.]
You should be thankful that
you had the use of these towels.
[That was earlier...]
- We'll never finish all this.
- Hello!
- What are you guys doing?
- What's in that basket?
This is our laundry.
[All the clothes and socks that they wore
during the previous game.]
Where would you like for me
to put this?
- Just stack them over there.
- Over here?
- Thanks for doing our laundry.
- Okay.
You have to wash it and give it
back to us.
Don't be too rough with them either.
Okay, Baro.
- Make sure to wring all the water out.
- Okay, we got it.
See you later, Baro.
Don't worry about a thing.
That Baro has no fear of his older brothers.
He always says whatever's on his mind.
[He says whatever's on his mind
because he's Baro?]
I have a feeling that
he's going to make it big.
It's warm water.
[Giraffe discovers a pot of warm water.]
Is this all the hot water you have?
- Can I take this with me? Thank you.
- Sure.
You know why?
To reassure us.
- Just trying to reassure us.
- Is that a pot of warm water?
No, it's just some liquid detergent.
- That's warm water, isn't it?
- No, it's detergent.
- It's just detergent.
- Come here.
We're all cold out here,
and look at how hard Ji Hyo's working.
- I just got some detergent.
- Let me see.
[Rids the evidence now that
he's been caught in his lie.]
[The precious warm water...]
How can you be so awful?
- That precious water.
- What a waste of the precious water.
We could've warmed up our hands
whenever our hands got too cold.
- We could've used it together.
- Get out of here!
[I really must be a fool.]
[It's a karaoke party in the cozy room.]
[Perfectly in sync even when they're playing.]
[This is the ease felt by the victors.]
Everyone together!
- It's hot water!
- So warm!
[We love you, warm water!]
[Big-nose Brother rushes over
to the hot water.]
What are you doing, Suk Jin?
I guess I shouldn't have butted in there.
[Monday Couple is seen
wringing out the clothes together.]
[Playing out the scene of a clueless idiot.]
Here, let me do that.
I'm going to take the next semester off.
- These are Kim Jong Kook's pants.
- We're not washing that.
- No, we're not washing his.
- Take it.
You have to take it.
- Let's just lay them out.
- Let's lay them out without washing them.
It's already clean.
[Your sin is having met the wrong owner...]
[Slowly finishing up with the laundry.]
I wonder if we even got the clothes clean.
Even though we all did our best...
- Then they can just rewash them at home.
- Yes, you're right.
These clothes are like dried fish.
Frozen, then dried... frozen then dried again.
Jong Kook's pants are the only ones
that are still nice and fluffy.
[Of course they'd still be fluffy
since they were never even washed.]
- Look at how frozen this is.
- I can see icicles hanging off of them.
[All the laundry they just did
is already frozen.]
- This is the only thing that isn't frozen.
- Jong Kook's are nice and dry.
We're done!
- You had to do it with soap?
- We didn't even have detergent.
[The two teams are back together again.]
You can just take these back right now.
- You can take the socks back like this.
- I see my pants over there.
[Jong Kook discovers his own pants.]
Why are my pants different from
the others?
- Did you not wash my pants?
- Come on now!
- Of course, we washed them.
- You didn't wash my pants!
You didn't wash mine.
Only the part I got wet earlier is frozen.
All the other areas are still soft.
- It's because we dried them by the furnace.
- What furnace?
[What furnace...]
- You don't know what you're talking about.
- You guys are all awful.
[The rivalry between these two teams is
getting fiercer by the minute.]
[What's the next round of training
that awaits these two teams?]
[Intense Teamwork Training.]
[Evening training course for
2014 Running Winter Olympics?]
[A snow field?]
- It looks like a track field.
- What is this?
They're all fast runners.
Baro is a 12 second sprinter.
[Baro's 100m dash record is 12 seconds.]
This is going to be fun!
- Are you all rested?
- Yes.
Your next training mission is designed to see
how you work together as a team.
This training session is what our national
soccer team does in their real training camp.
All members of each team must sit in a row
and scoot along the line while holding
onto the feet of the person behind them.
You must do a lap around the field
while maintaining that position.
That training session?
You want us to do that here?
That's the same training session that our
national team does during their own training.
[Only difference here is that it's being
done on a snow field.]
This is all about survival of the fittest.
Baro's 12 second record has no use here.
Baro's record doesn't matter here.
Even Usain Bolt can't do this.
This is something Ho Jun could
be good at.
[Their black hole, Ho Jun...]
Okay, everyone sit down.
[Jumping right into coaching segment.]
Set, go!
One, two, okay?
[Practicing along Coach Kkuk's command.]
Ready, set, go.
Left, right...
Can we go a little slower?
[Kkuk's power walking.]
Right... left... right... left...
[Everyone's getting painfully dragged along
to Kkuk's pace.]
Okay, we got it.
That's a nice pace.
What are you doing?
That's a good pace.
What are you doing!
[This is Coach Kkuk's hard training
that they'd all only heard about.]
[Meanwhile...]
You can't do it like that, Suk Jin.
[Elder Big-nose is struggling
right from the get go.]
- Suk Jin can't do this.
- Set, go.
- One, two...
- Why aren't we moving?
[Making no progress.]
What are you doing, Suk Jin?
- Try getting up, Suk Jin.
- I can't do this.
[Tries it again without Suk Jin in tow.]
- One, two...
- Keep moving.
Why am I not moving?
I'm not moving!
[Gary at the tail end
isn't moving from his spot.]
Why aren't you guys moving up?
Listen... let's do this two against two.
Why do you want to keep
switching around?
He's already used up all his strength.
[Big-nose is exhausted from
having done all the laundry.]
- Suk Jin's already exhausted.
- He had to do all that laundry.
I feel like my muscles have exploded.
[All his muscles has exploded
from the load of laundry?]
How about two against two relay?
[Four representatives from each team
to do a relay of two on two.]
Okay, then we're good.
[The laundry is freezing along nicely...]
Gary, and Ha Ha!
Let's win this race!
[Gary and Ha Ha vs Baro and In Guk.]
[Jong Kook and Seo Joon vs
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.]
Why is Ho Jun sitting out?
[Excuse me?]
Ho Jun says that snow isn't his thing.
[What a unique excuse.
Snow isn't his thing?]
You and I are cut from the same cloth.
He's the race starter for your team.
- How can you say that?
- Fighting!
[I make a good cheerleader.]
This is no big deal.
This isn't hard.
So let's all do this, okay?
Let's do this!
You all know that the penalty for losing this
is to chop up all the firewood.
The winning team can go into the room,
and rest in the meantime.
We're going to win this!
[Start the race!]
[It's a neck to neck start!]
[Both teams are perfectly in sync
with their own teammate.]
[Just then...]
[All Star Team starts taking the lead.]
[Must touch off for the next players
to get on their way.]
[All Star Team is almost there!]
[But... Team RM touches off first!]
[Team RM has better timing,
and gets to start off first!]
[All Star Team rushes off in their wake.]
[They're so fast...]
[The amazing Yoo-Lee Duo.]
[Team RM wins!]
[How can this be?]
[Totally unexpected!
The All Star Team was the favored winner!]
They're so fast!
- We got this!
- You guys did great!
[Time for Coach Kkuk's
additional coaching session.]
Why are you guys practicing so much?
This is why Seo Joon's struggling
and exhausted already.
- Jong Kook... can we please stop?
- Come on, Seo Joon!
- You need to keep going, Seo Joon.
- All the strength from the earlier meal is gone.
What's so difficult about this, Seo Joon?
No one on our team can keep up
with you and your strength.
I'm not even warmed up yet!
I'm the normal one here.
- I'm the normal one of the two of us.
- Let's do better this time.
- Okay?
- You're going to kill these guys.
[Kkuk's training sessions are about to make
these 'normal' guys keel over in exhaustion.]
You're not really training for Sochi!
Here's how I honestly
feel about this situation.
Even if we do lose this game,
I think wood chopping will be good for us.
- I don't want to do this!
- This is just exercise.
[Coach Kkuk is thinking that wood chopping
could be his evening workout?]
That could be a really good
workout for us.
Look at how happy and excited Jong Kook is
about the thought of teaching you something.
You have to stop thinking
that you're the norm!
We have to raise the bar on what our people
think is the normal exercise routine.
[Does he want to send every citizen of
the nation to the Olympics?]
We have to raise the bar.
- Fighting.
[Second round- Go!]
[Their speed is noticeably faster!]
[All Star Team is pulling far ahead
of their opponents!]
[It seems as though all the nagging
by their coach is having its effect.]
[Team RM is doing their best
to catch up to the other team.]
[But the gap is already too great.]
[Second bout of players from
All Star Team gets on their way!]
[Team RM finally touches off.]
[Oh... oh?]
[Yoo-Lee Duo is doing it again!]
No!
[The gap is closing fast!]
[Please...]
[Almost caught up to them!]
[The finish line is right in
front of their eyes!]
Just a little bit more!
[Which of the two teams will cross
the finish line first?]
[Team RM's unbelievable victory!]
What are you doing, Jong Kook!
[All Star Team is relegated to
wood chopping duty.]
You exhausted him from making him
practice over and over.
I'd win the gold medal if this game was
accepted as an official game at the Olympics!
[Team RM's spirits are up high
from their thrilling victory.]
[They're all really leaving the field without
even a glance back at their opposing team.]
You should've held on tighter
to my feet.
My arms kept flailing around like this
when I was holding onto your feet.
[Unable to handle
the force of 'The Kkuk Train'.]
- All I kept hearing was your screaming.
- You're too strong for any one of us.
I'm missing my mom more and more.
Wow, seriously...
Anyways, let's not think of this as a penalty.
Let's all have fun and get some exercise.
Let's just think of it as getting a workout,
and let's go!
Let's go chop up some wood.
All that?
Is that even possible?
Why doesn't Jong Kook, as the team captain,
give everyone else a demonstration?
I can't believe how fitting
that ax looks on him.
My goodness.
He's like an expert in this.
You're not certified in it, are you?
Okay, I'll give it a try.
I don't know if I can get it in one try.
Wow, he's like a Spartan.
This is... this is pretty simple.
It's not that hard.
[Splits the wood right in half!]
This one looks tough.
I don't think I'll be able to get this.
You have to aim it just right.
[He's an expert at this!]
[Kkuk is demonstrating the task
perfectly for his teammates.]
[Baro tries his hand at the task.]
I'm not sure where to hit it.
You have to swing down strong,
and let the ax fall where it falls.
[It's his first time doing this...]
You're playing around right now,
aren't you?
[Wood chopping isn't an easy job
to pick up for newbies...]
[Kkuk to demonstrate the task again.]
[Are you really human?]
You have to follow it through.
Follow through where the ax falls.
There you go!
[Even he himself is shocked.]
Wait, let me try another one.
I have to figure this out
while I've got the feel for it.
Out of the way.
Others are waiting for their turn.
Be honest, Jong Kook.
You're having fun right now, aren't you?
- You're really excited, aren't you?
- To be honest, I really wanted to chop wood.
[The wood chopping mania finally reveals
his true desire to chop some wood.]
It's Ho Jun's turn.
At least, it's Ho Jun's turn.
[At last,
it's their Dark Horse, Ho Jun's turn.]
You want me to pick
a really easy one for you?
To be honest, I did a lot of wood chopping
when I was younger.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Then I bet you'll be really good at it.
- He knows how to chop wood?
- I can chop it down the middle, right?
- Sure, of course.
- Wow, I didn't know.
[We thought that perhaps...
but as expected...]
What's your problem?
Try it again.
- Go on and try it again.
- I don't know why that didn't work.
[Could it have been a mistake?
Giving it another try.]
[Misses his mark?]
Step back.
Step back!
How many times must you try?
How many attempts does it take?
You're hurting the wood!
You should've done it in one strike.
Hey, let's all get some rest.
We're going to get some rest
in the warm, cozy room.
Wow, that was an impressive race.
[Team RM won the right to rest
with all their hard work.]
I told you that
you don't have to do that, Ji Hyo.
[This is what heaven must feel like.]
[Everyone's passed out.]
[He and the wood pieces are now as one.]
This could help release your stress.
And it helps keep people warm too.
It's a great thing to do.
It's a great thing to do all around.
[Kkuk's wood chopping show is
mesmerizing for his team members.]
You can do it with one blow, In Guk.
[In Guk's almost got the full hang of it!]
Look at that.
Master!
- Doesn't it feel good?
- Master!
You can't be afraid of it.
- The ax and I are as one.
- Just slam it down.
All you're doing is helping the ax
go where it wants to go.
There you go!
- Next.
- My turn.
[It's a battle of the pride
in front of the wood chopping block.]
Other people are waiting for their turn!
Move!
You need to train some more.
[You need more training!
Says the ever so wise Coach Kkuk.]
[Oh... even Ye Won gets it on
her first try.]
You're even better than Ho Jun.
Okay, Ho Jun.
Believe that you can do it.
There you go!
- I think I've found my new vocation.
- Right?
[Now even Seo Joon is in love
with the wood chopping task.]
It's really discouraging for you, isn't it?
This is what life is like.
Things are not as easy as they look.
That's what real life is like.
[People do say that
life isn't as easy as it looks...]
Think of the wood as
a hurdle in your own life.
['Wood is like the hurdles in your own life.'
- Coach Kkuk.]
With conviction.
There you go!
- That's good.
- It's stuck.
I think you can just split
the rest with your hands.
Just rip it apart with your hands.
Earlier when I...
[This is the power of the woodcutter.]
- What was that?
- Come on, Ho Jun.
You can go again, Ho Jun.
['These wood pieces are representation
of your own life.' - Woodcutter Kkuk.]
[5- Icy Field Name Tag Elimination.]
[Final battle ground of
2014 Running Winter Olympics.]
What... what is all this?
[Numbered tags...
and ice hockey equipment?]
What is this?
Look at him smiling.
Look at him smiling from seeing all this.
[This seems right up my alley.]
[Time to determine the ultimate winners-
Icy Field Name Tag Elimination.]
Each team will assign a number
to each of their own members.
[Each members to be assigned
numbers from one through six.]
- I think I should be number four.
- I'll be number three.
Okay, you be number three.
Players one through four will enter
the arena together.
Players five and six can
rest along the sideline.
Each period will last five minutes.
You need to eliminate the numbered tags from
your opposing team during those five minutes.
But you have to make sure to eliminate
the tags in the numerical order.
If for example, Ji Suk Jin,
being numbered one is eliminated
then Gary, being number five
will come in to replace Suk Jin immediately.
That's how this whole game will play out.
So the first target is going to be number one.
[Number one must be eliminated first
before number two can be targeted.]
We have to eliminate their number one
while protecting our own number one.
Every time a player is eliminated...
the opposing team scores a point.
The team that eliminates the most number of
opposing players ultimately wins in the end.
[Team that eliminates the most number of
their opponent wins the game!]
Jong Kook... am I number six
because I'm the star of this team?
- No, that's not it.
- You guys didn't include me in your decision.
Don't think like that, Ho Jun.
You're our ace up our sleeve.
What are you talking about?
You know how valuable you are.
[But Ho Jun lost his star position,
and got bumped up to the fifth position.]
[Only players one through four
are taking the ice at the moment.]
[Icy Field Name Tag Elimination-
The final battle to determine the victors.]
[1. Jae Suk, Ye Won. 2. Kwang Soo, In Guk.
3. Gary, Baro. 4. Ha Ha, Jong Kook.]
We need to eliminate as many of them as
possible instead of worrying about ourselves.
[Team RM's plan- Kwang Soo with his long
arms to be on the offense.]
And keep your eye out for Kwang Soo.
He attacks from up high because he's so tall.
So if you feel that you're in danger,
then just lay down flat on the ground.
[Icy Field Name Tag Elimination- First half.
Starts now!]
I don't know what they're planning,
but I don't like it.
[Closing in on Ye Won as their target.]
[Lies down flat on the ground as
instructed by Coach Kkuk.]
[On the other hand,
Jae Suk is the target of the other team.]
[Mr. Capable makes his move!]
[Guard Gary stands as his bodyguard.]
[Offense and defense... it's two on two!]
Number one!
I got number one!
[1. Ye Won- Out!]
[2. In Guk.]
[Must touch off with the next player on the
sideline before a player can be swapped out.]
[Second target, In Guk,
quickly escapes being attacked.]
Where's In Guk?
[Ho Jun (5) rushes in to protect In Guk.]
[Mr. Capable (4) has Jae Suk (1) and
Gary (3) locked in his vise grip.]
[Someone just needs to come in
and eliminate Jae Suk's (1) tag.]
[Oh? In Guk eliminates Jae Suk's tag?]
[And Ha Ha immediately follows
and eliminates In Guk's tag!]
[Ousted players must hurry
and swap in the next players.]
[Third target for All Star Team is, Baro.]
[Swapping out the players.]
[Kwang Soo is the second target
from Team RM.]
It's total chaos, isn't it?
Someone needs to come and
rip off his tag!
[Wow... Black hole Ho Jun ousts Kwang Soo!]
- Is Kwang Soo ousted?
- Yeah.
- Kwang Soo's ousted?
- Yeah, he's ousted.
[Current target for both teams-
Number three, Baro and Gary.]
[Quick footed Baro...
and guard extraordinaire, Gary.]
[Who will be ousted first?]
This is no joke.
They're brutal out there!
[Just then, Black hole Ho Jun swoops in
again and eliminates Gary's tag!]
[Look at this!
It's next target, Ha Ha!]
[What stroke of luck is this?]
[Eliminates number three,
and number four as the cherry on top.]
[5- Ji Suk Jin.]
[Big-nose is easily taken care of
by Mr. Capable.]
[As soon as Big-nose gets ousted...
Ho Jun attacks Blank Ji!]
[He's really getting the hang of this game!]
[Team RM's players 3, 4, 5, 6
are all ousted within a blink of an eye!]
[Black hole Ho Jun is now the newly
crowned name tag eliminator!]
[Team RM: 2 vs All Star Team: 6.]
[Team RM has come a full circle,
and Jae Suk is targeted once again.]
[On the other hand, Baro (3) of All Star Team
is still alive and is targeted.]
Don't abandon me!
Seo Joon!
Please!
[Baro is surrounded by his opponents.]
[Baro sticks it out as long as he can,
but is ultimately ousted by Kwang Soo.]
[It's now time to tackle
their biggest hurdle, Kkuk.]
[While Jae Suk's busy targeting Kkuk...]
[Ho Jun appears again out of nowhere!]
[Complete chaos.]
[I'm going to sit this one out.]
[Boulder a.k.a. Mr. Capable
isn't even budging.]
[Finally gets their chance!]
[Team RM's Jae Suk gets ousted too!]
[The ever busy Eliminator Ho Jun...]
[Is ousted by Ha Ha's ambush attack!]
[If Ho Jun's ousted...]
[Then that puts Seo Joon in danger!]
[Hang in there, Seo Joon!]
[In Guk slides in...]
[And gets his hand on target Kwang Soo's tag!]
[Kwang Soo automatically flips his
body out of harm's way.]
I got number six!
[All Star Team's sixth target,
Seo Joon is ousted!]
[Cold hearted Big-nose moves in on Ye Won!]
[All Star Team's Ye Won is ousted!]
[End of the first half.]
[Current score- 7:7.]
[Complete and utter chaos
during the first half.]
How are we supposed to get them
when they're lying down on the ground?
Here, let me show you.
Lie down on the ground.
[Time for another Coach Kkuk's lesson.]
You have to lift up their back.
So ram your knee into their side.
Lift them up like this while digging
your knee into their side.
[All the students are paying close attention
to the lesson taught by Coach Kkuk.]
- There's no plan of action out there.
- It's total chaos.
[This team's plan is to attack
however they can.]
Let's go.
[Players 2-5 are in from both teams.]
[Icy Field Name Tag Elimination-
Start of the second half.]
[Current targets-
All Star Team- In Guk; Team RM- Kwang Soo.]
[Mr. Capable and Baro are on the offense.]
[Ho Jun's duty is to protect In Guk.]
Where are you going, Suk Jin?
Suk Jin!
[Suk Jin abandons Kwang Soo as soon
as Mr. Capable closes in on them?]
Someone needs to come help me!
[Gary and Ha Ha move in on In Guk.]
[All Star Team's In Guk- Out!]
[New Target- Baro.]
[Baro lies down on the ground
with Mr. Capable as his shield?]
[Utter chaos.]
This really is no joke out there.
They're all out to
rip off each other's name tags.
[Quick footed Baro shoots up
to escape their attacks.]
[With Kwang Soo getting ousted,
new target for Team RM is Gary.]
[Huh?]
[Baro is captured from foolishly
trying out his martial arts moves.]
I'm so sorry!
I won't do that ever again!
Just lay down!
[But Ace won't let this chance escape her.]
- Jong Kook! He's next!
- Who's number four?
[Yeah, it's me!]
[Mr. Capable pulls the boulder move again.]
[Even three against one isn't enough.]
Ji Hyo's amazing.
[In the midst of all that chaos,
Ho Jun ousts Gary this time!]
[They're back to being tied again.]
Do we have to oust Jong Kook?
[Of all people...]
[Ye Won takes charge of Big-nose?]
[It's a fierce and bloody one on one battle.]
[Is that how you want to play?]
[A moment later.]
[That's why you never should've
provoked me!]
What is this mess!
[Every player on Team RM is
focused on ousting Mr. Capable.]
Ji Hyo!
[As Mr. Capable holds his own...
All Star Team takes the lead.]
Ji Suk Jin.
Ji Suk Jin is next.
[Long armed Giraffe heads out!]
Number four is out!
[Long armed Kwang Soo
is pulling his weight today!]
[Number four is out?
Then I'm the next target...]
[Sticky wad of gum bodyguard?
Seo Joon lays his body over Ho Jun's.]
[Hm...]
[Target Big-nose is left all alone.]
[No one is paying him any attention
even though he's the target.]
- Number five is out.
- Five is ousted!
Number six!
We have to get six.
[In the midst of this bloody battle...
no one is paying attention to this target.]
Ye Won is next.
[Everyone goes in after
All Star Team's next target, Ye Won.]
- Why isn't anyone trying to oust me?
- Who's the next target?
Who's the next target?
[Team All Star can't even remember
who their current target is.]
[It's me.]
[Chaos... empty.]
- Ye Won's out!
- Who's our target?
It's Suk Jin.
[Finally eyes their target, Big-nose.]
I'm going to lift you up now, Father.
No!
You can't sleep out here
on this icy field.
[In Guk is outnumbered two to one.]
[Baro ousts Father Big-nose
before he falls asleep out on the ice.]
[In Guk of the All Star Team is
also ousted.]
Number two is out!
[An immediate U-turn.]
[30 seconds left in the game!]
[A player is ousted here...
and player is ousted over there.]
[It's neck and neck!]
It's Jong Kook.
We have to get Jong Kook.
[Ye Won swoops in on
the current target, Jae Suk!]
[Only ten seconds left!]
[The countdown is on!]
- No!
- Six!
Please just end it now!
[Final targets, Jae Suk and Jong Kook,
are sticking it out to the end!]
[Game over!]
[Both teams gave it their best...
a fierce and bloody battle.]
[The two teams pays their respect
to one another.]
We've gained ourselves some
new comrades.
[Patting each other on the back for their
efforts is the true spirit of the Olympics.]
The final score is, 15 to 12.
Team RM wins.
[Team RM wins the race
with the final score of 15 to 12.]
[They're just unbeatable.]
[All Star Team bestows a flower garland
around the necks of Team RM players.]
Have a nice trip to Sochi.
[The winners' prize-
A gold pin of the Korean flag!]
[Since you are the national representatives
of Icy Field Name Tag Elimination...]
- More than anything else, Sochi Olympics...
- Are we really going to Sochi?
Are you going?
[Are they seriously going?]
- We're going to head to Sochi.
- Good luck.
- Let's go to Sochi!
- Republic of Korea... fighting!
Running Man, fighting!
We'll be back!
[They did board the bus since
that's what they were told to do...]
I didn't even get to call my wife.
What am I going to do?
Have a nice trip!
I still have to film my drama.
Where are you taking us?
- I have a pretty busy schedule.
- Where are we going?
[Just then...]
[The TV on the bus suddenly flickers on.]
Here's your breaking news.
Icy Field Name Tag Elimination being passed
as the new official sport of 2014 Sochi Olympics
has just been announced as
being false information.
- Are you playing with us right now?
- Why are you doing this to us?
It has been stated that the sport will be
submitted to be accepted as an official game
of the 2018 Winter Olympics.
Until then, the players will try
even harder to improve on their skills.
And we ask that you continue to send your
cheer and support to the current athletes
who are participating in the
Winter Olympics in Sochi right now.
Here's your next news.
Good luck to all the athletes
participating in the Olympics.
Republic of Korea, fighting!
[Subtitles by DramaFever]
August 25th, 1609...
There's a record of unidentifiable
flying objects being spotted
at the same time around the land of
Joseon during the Joseon era.
Those unidentifiable flying objects...
are what brought me to the land of Joseon.
From the Joseon era to now...
I have lived for over 400 years
wandering around on this land.
And in three months' time,
I'll be able to go back to my place of home.
[He'll soon be able to go back to the
place that he calls 'home'.]
[Woman of destiny who walked
into his life.]
[The woman in danger...]
[She must be protected.]
[And the ultimate villain
who is after her...]
[What will become of their fate?]
[Running Man's 'My Love From Another Star'.]