Subtitles by DramaFever
The treasure is hidden in
Brisbane, Australia.
In Tangalooma National Park.
In order to find the treasure, you must
find the four elements of Earth.
Water, fire, wind, and fire.
These elements must come together
in order to find the treasure.
Stay tuned!
- We have to go.
- Run!
Find the treasure chest at
the ship wreck.
You won first place
in the first mission.
You may ask one question.
Is it water?
Is one of us fire?
Kangaroos!
Koala!
Balsamic.
We're trying so many things today.
Bi-Kwang-Cross!
Tomorrow morning, starting at 5:15.
The team to wake up first will
start the missions first.
5:15?
Your missions may vary.
The first team to wake up
may choose the mission.
Pick the easy ones?
More likely to pick the easier mission.
You will have the advantages
from waking up early.
We will give you two self cameras each.
- Just relax with it.
- Okay.
I'm in Gary's room right now.
Gary is ill from taking care
of Ji Suk Jin.
He's having a bad dream.
And... he is sleeping naked.
- Shh...
- Come in.
It's a secret.
The behind-the-scenes with
Kwang Soo and Ha Ha.
I will turn on the light.
I almost died.
Behind-the-scenes with
Kwang Soo and Ha Ha.
See you next time!
He scared me.
What are you doing?
Go to bed.
Go to bed!
What are you doing?
Go to bed.
Kwang Soo! Where are we?
- This is Ji Hoon's...
- Rain is here.
- You scared me.
- What are you doing here?
Everyone gets one big bed
except for them. They got twins.
And there's Marilyn Monroe in the middle.
Will you stop?
Go to bed!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
- Do you know what time it is?
- Excuse me!
Ji Hoon isn't getting involved.
We need to get everyone.
- Ji Hoon!
- Rip it!
Woo Bin is here.
Woo Bin! Come here.
Woo Bin! You want to experience
something new?
It's not like that.
Come here for a sec.
Come here Woo Bin.
This will make you sleep like a baby.
It's for circulation.
I already saw it.
Accept it Woo Bin.
Relax.
I don't even know why
we're doing this.
What are you doing?
Go to bed. We're shooting tomorrow.
Sleep inside, come on.
Set it to 4:40 AM.
Why are you arguing?
He's not doing anything!
He doesn't even want to
set the alarm.
Why are you always having fights?
- He's driving me nuts.
- Take credit for everything.
[Real big nose]
- You're so ugly.
- My nostrils are my weak point.
- How long is the dance party going to be?
- Let's have fun for about 30 minutes.
- What time is the festival going to end?
- I would have had more fun if I weren't so tired.
We can only have fun for 30 minutes.
I can't get up.
I'm tired.
This is it!
Rain come in!
It's a dance party.
Rain!
This is the dance party!
- Do I have to take a shower again?
- I think you should.
[Next morning 5:00 AM]
What?
- Gary!
- Huh?
[The ultimate combo, Jong Kook-Rain
wins first place.]
That was close.
When did you get here?
Gary!
Are they keywords about the mission?
You think they are our vehicles?
- What if we have to cross a river?
- You guys have good team chemistry.
You don't know what's ahead
of us anyway.
What? It's none of your business.
Mind your own business.
Suk Jin! Come out! Come out!
- Gary!
- Okay I'm coming.
- What are you doing?
- Gosh.
What's a Sea-plane?
Bread on the sea?
Pretzel?
- That's plain! Not plane.
- Yogurt.
What are you talking about?
- Go to the back, Jae Suk.
- Huh? We're the third place.
Suk Jin isn't here.
Isn't a Jeep the best in waters?
There may be two Jeeps because
it's the best choice.
Why are you so early?
- I think the sea-plane is the best.
- You can't let them see it.
You have to make blind picks.
Flip them and make them make
blind picks.
Let's depend on luck.
I picked it! Let's go.
- Did you pick a Jeep?
- Yeah.
I think it's the right choice.
- Be creative about it.
- We pick a Jeep too.
Give it up for me.
It's Gary's birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Give us the Jeep for my birthday.
We got second place.
Wait! Shouldn't we get to pick?
Which one do you want Jae Suk?
Sea-plane? You don't think
it spins in the air, do you?
No way.
Because I really can't do
stuff like that.
You can't do anything!
Gosh! Why did you pick me?
It was between you and Ha Ha.
I was cornered too.
I had no choice.
I would have picked Ji Hoon
or Woo Bin if they were available.
Did you have to say that?
Cornered?
You have to destroy their
team chemistry.
Like, you have to go to Team A
and bond with them first.
Then go to Team B and do
something else.
Ji Hoon did a lot yesterday,
but I gave most of the orders.
- Really.
- Really?
I have to get my revenge
on Jong Kook.
He got even bulkier.
His weakness is the pit of
his stomach.
- Hit him there?
- Hit him there.
You have to elbow it.
Just say that you're sorry.
I did it often. I really did.
[South Stradbroke Island
located in the northern Gold Coast.]
[The biggest forest in Australian Gold Coast
with wooden forests and sand hills.]
[Australian Adventure- Second Day]
[Team Running Man arrived in McLarens.]
It's really an island.
If you and your partner has more than
900 ml of water after the beach race...
- You may get out.
- What does this mean?
I think we have to drive with
a cup in our car.
So we try not to spill water.
Let's go.
Do we just go?
So we got here first right?
No?
I can't believe this.
You're always late.
It wasn't us.
The plane came late.
It was you!
- Hello.
- Good morning.
- Here's your mission.
- Mission.
The person on the boat needs to answer seven
quiz questions given by the person parasailing.
What is parasailing?
There's a big chute.
You go up in the air.
Up? The parachute?
And we have to give and answer
seven quiz questions in a minute?
Wait, so one of us has to go
on the chute?
You! It's my birthday.
- Congratulations.
- Wait.
Thank you!
Good morning.
Here's your mission.
String 15 beads while flying
on a sea-plane.
Suk Jin!
We have to string 15 beads.
We're in trouble.
[Australian Adventure McLarens.
Succeed on a sea-plane, parasail, or jeep.]
Wow.
[Deep woods.]
We're lucky that it's not too hot.
This is... wow.
There you go. Go!
Amazing!
Look at the sea.
I feel like we're on vacation.
Dang!
It's amazing.
Everyone! Australia is beautiful.
Australia is very beautiful.
I love Australia!
I love Hoju Hosu!
(Australian lake)
Ha Ha, it's seven questions per minute.
Make it quick. I will answer them.
- It's already decided?
- Of course.
It was decided at five in the morning.
Why?
My birthday.
- I will give you something else.
- No, I want this.
- It's over when we get back to Korea.
- Call.
- Happy birthday.
- Yeah!
You're a great man.
I gave the best birthday present ever.
I will get it right quickly.
Don't worry.
I think you have to string both of them.
Have the younger ones do this.
It's hard enough to escort
this old man.
The kids who need to be on this
are on the Jeeps.
This makes no sense.
Let's wake up early.
Why take forever?
And stop pretending that you're
running with your upper body.
You always do this
while you're walking.
You saw it.
He's quick.
You always make this motion
when you're really walking.
I woke up only a few hours ago.
I'll do better!
Cheer up!
I'll do better.
We're in trouble.
What should I do?
Really? Are you the driver?
- No, no, no good driver.
- No, no, no, very bad.
We're leaving!
- Oh my God!
- We're leaving.
I only saw this in the movies.
This is some 007 stuff.
- Just focus on your beads.
- Okay.
You only see this in movies.
Wait, wait.
This is impossible.
I'm almost on my back.
Why is it so fast?
Why is it skidding?
This doesn't feel good at all!
[We're adventuring in McLarens from the
land, sea, and air at the same time.]
I love Australia.
I'm becoming one with nature.
[Stay out of the shot for
a sec, Kwang Soo.]
[It's a photo shoot.]
[You're gorgeous too... or cute.]
What's going on?
How's this even possible?
The mission to the team that
woke up first is...
This is the start line and it's divided
into three sections, R1, R2, and R3.
They are connected.
- I will give you a water cup.
- Wait one sec.
Wasn't it this?
I thought it was this.
I thought it this one would be okay.
I will give you 500 ml each.
You must keep 900 ml in aggregate
after the first section, R1.
500 ml? Then 100 ml?
Yes, you cannot spill more than 100ml.
- So if we fail, we have to try again for R2?
- Correct.
- Jae Suk is going.
- It's Jae Suk!
There's water right below us.
What's he doing?
We're falling.
- We will not start the mission.
- No! No!
It started!
I knew it!
I knew this would happen.
What's up with the up and downs?
You have to tilt it in the
opposite direction of the car.
You have to tilt it.
Opposite! There you go.
Good! I think I can get it.
This is swerving way too much.
No! No!
Okay.
Wait! I'm still okay.
I'm still okay.
We're one with the car.
Don't think about it.
We have to tilt it along with the car.
That's cold.
I'm okay.
I'm still okay.
Hey! I'm good.
It's close.
- This isn't enough is it?
- Is this?
This is worse than roller coasters.
How can we string them?
This is impossible.
- I couldn't get any.
- How can you not get any?
Gosh! What were you doing?
- Do something!
- Okay.
You have to keep on working.
First hold it.
Careful! You have to be careful!
You should be laughing right now.
Don't do anything.
Don't say anything.
Let's try one by one.
It needs to exceed the line.
Let's try one first.
This won't be enough.
- I thought it'd be enough.
- It wasn't enough.
I'm sorry, Woo Bin!
It's cold.
You think we have enough?
- No cheating!
- I won't. You don't have enough anyway.
Woo Bin! You did well.
- Will this be enough?
- No way.
It's raining!
Isn't rain going to energize Rain?
Ji Hoon is getting energy.
You've failed R1.
- Is it 850 this time?- I will try it.
Let's go for 900 ml one more time.
- Just once.
- Are you out of your mind?
Why?
Trust me, I have a plan.
Let's go for 850.
Right?
And can you stop trying to be smart?
You guys won't get anywhere anyway.
Not you guys. Just him.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Kwang Soo! We have the advantage
from the rain. So let's go.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
So only Kwang Soo is doing it?
Can I have a cup of water?
Let's get going after this.
Kwang Soo!
You have something in your mouth.
I drank some water.
I got caught.
- I got caught.
- Okay, okay.
Aren't you going to talk?
We have high wakes.
How are we going to speed up
in this?
Unless you have to stand up, stay seated.
It's rough okay?
If you're feeling sick, look at the shore.
No wonder they wanted us
to take sea sick meds.
We have to get it right at once.
We have no other choice.
You're good at explaining.
I'm good at guessing.
But I'm bad at explaining.
This is really scary. Oh my God.
This is no joke!
What is this?
Can we do it here?
Are we getting on that boat?
So let's board one person at a time.
He's on the parasailing boat.
Go, go, go.
Everyone just sit down. We have a
little problem with the boat.
[Are we going to be okay?]
In the middle of the ocean. Yeah.
Okay! Sit tight.
It's very very rough.
We cannot do the parasailing.
It's too rough in the ocean today.
Maybe next time. But not today.
Too rough.
Oh my lord.
Let's go to the inside coast.
Inside.
Calm area.
- We drank it from here.
- It was tactics.
It's more than we started with.
Is it my saliva in there?
Hey! You have more water
than you started with.
He has more water!
He has more water.
- How did you get more water?
- No one gave us any.
- What the heck?
- Let's go.
Look. Look.
- No one gave us water.
- Look at the line.
- You have more water.
- It's called tactics.
I got some rain water.
Is that how you want to play?
We're not going home then.
You know I can get dirty.
Okay! We made it.
Give us an explanation.
We had water in our mouths.
Okay, we will let it go. The part with
you carrying water in your mouth.
Did you put in more water
other than the one I gave you?
40 million Koreans are watching you.
- We will do it again.
- I didn't.
I wanted to drink the water
from the cup.
Woo Bin can get dirtier than me.
He asked to drink some water.
Then he put back the water in his mouth.
Kwang Soo wanted to do it too.
But then Ji Hoon saw him.
Yeah, I swallowed it.
Since we have to save water,
we will use this water again.
It's not like I can't do it.
Do you want new water Woo Bin?
Why special treatment for Woo Bin?
I'm going to throw this on you.
What did you just say?
Pay respect to the crew.
- Give me fresh water.
- We need to conserve water.
Give me fresh water!
Why do I have to string beads
on a plane?
How do we do this?
Stop! Dropping.
What is wrong with him?
One more! One! One!
Accomplished.
Hurry up.
Why isn't this working?
- I have 15.
- Count mine.
What is this?
You need to do four more.
- Hurry up!
- Stop tugging.
[10 minutes later.]
I did it! I'm done.
[Did you have fun?]
[Oh yeah, fun enough to die.]
- You have more water.
- No. I really didn't cheat.
We got it this time.
Something is wrong if we don't get it.
The water is so hot.
We can cook ramen in this.
We got it. I think we got it.
Go!
- Did we get it?
- We got it.
Congratulations.
We got it too.
- We got it!
- Thank you!
We shared our plan.
Dolphins! Get it!
Dolphins.
Where did it go?
Over there!
Hi dolphins!
They aren't sharks are they?
- Dolphin!
- We didn't do anything.
Let's get dolphins at least.
Over there! Our friends.
Let's name our friends.
Gary and Ha Ha.
Gary and Ha Ha!
Hi dolphins!
Hi Gary!
Dolphin!
Dolphins!
Are they gone? I think they left.
You came back first.
We almost died.
We deserve first place.
It was really close.
What is it?
Do we have to do something?
- You won first place. Did you forget?
- I never got to win first place with him.
Oh yeah!
We get to ask questions.
So this is our reward.
Am I water?
Correct.
I'm water.
- Am I fire?
- Fire?
Correct.
You and I are water and fire.
I'm water and you're fire.
We are the opposite.
I knew it.
Second place?
We get to ask,
'Do we have blank in us?'
Of the four elements, is
Earth among us?
Earth is not among you.
- I'm not earth.
- That was a decisive question.
Let me tell you.
First, I won first place twice yesterday.
I had the chance to ask them twice.
I was not water or fire.
So I'm not earth either.
Then I'm likely wind.
- What again?
- Another plane?
This again?
We got last place again.
We're going to Melbourne.
We're going again.
- We're going to Melbourne?
- Again?
- Melbourne!
- I love Melbourne!
Melbourne!
I will tell you the last mission
of your Australia Adventure.
Water, fire, wind, and earth.
Collect all four elements and
put it on the final altar.
And the treasure will awaken.
The important thing is that you only need
one person on your team on the altar to win.
Okay.
We will pick starting with the first place.
Pick one.
[Take a taxi to the following address.]
Hello.
So only one of us needs to
be on the altar to win.
Let's really want it this time.
- Have you seen 'The Fifth Element'?
- I have.
It's just like that.
'The Fifth Element'.
Huh?
They put water, fire, wind, and
earth on the altar.
And the fifth element is the girl.
And it opens the door.
It's just like that.
Right?
It's 'The Fifth Element'.
You think Ji Hyo is here
as the fifth element?
We have to take Ji Hyo.
[Two hours ago at
Melbourne International Airport.]
[An agent secretly entered Australia.]
[Agent Song Ji Hyo]
[A dock near Melbourne]
Hi.
I'm here in Melbourne.
I just got here after a 13 hour flight.
I arrived in Melbourne.
I'm not groomed.
I'm sorry.
I look shaggy.
Where is the rest of the team?
I'm lonely here.
[Australia Adventure:
In the Search of Lost Treasure]
Go to the mission restaurant and
eat to obtain the Earth Card.
Collect three Earth Cards...
and become one of the four
elements of Earth, earth.
I'm human and I have to
become earth?
What does this mean? I have to
collect three Earth Cards?
The Running Men are three of the four.
Water, fire, and wind.
Remember when I said four?
They need earth.
- You're the earth.
- I am?
Only you are.
They need all four elements to
find the treasure.
You're the only earth element.
But you're incomplete earth.
So you need to go to the mission
restaurants in Melbourne.
And finish all the food there.
You will obtain your Earth Cards
from that.
- Collect the Earth Cards.
- And become complete Earth.
You have six destinations.
They are famous places in Melbourne.
You need to go to one of them.
I'm hungry.
If you run into Running Members they
may steal your card. So be careful.
I like to buy postcards overseas.
Macaron.
Entrance of Royal Arcade.
I'm hungry! Give me a meal!
[The second largest city in Australia
after Sydney.]
[Voted as the best place to
live in the world in 2013.]
[Map the staff drew for her.]
This is Royal Arcade.
I think it's here.
Look.
I can eat whatever I want.
Macaron.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Macaron is the perfect dessert
but I need coffee with it.
Green tea.
The inside is really moist.
The chocolate is really good.
It's rich and moist inside.
It's caramel inside.
It's really good.
- Okay, I'm finished.
- Thank you.
Very very good.
Finish all the food there
to obtain your Earth Card.
Thank you.
I have finished the first
step of becoming earth.
I recommend vanilla for dessert.
I recommend vanilla.
It's really good.
I need to find two more right?
I'm one third earth right now.
I want to eat something hearty.
That was too sweet.
Soup!
Center Place.
Meanwhile, Team Running Man
is on their way to Melbourne.
- Enjoy it mate.
- Yeah, have a nice day.
We went from last place
to first place.
Thank you!
This feels like a different country.
- This is... look.
- This is that.
- It's amazing here.
- Yeah.
- This would make a great set for a music video.
Should we shoot another music video?
- We have to shoot a music video here.
- Definitely.
Let's have a song that represents youth.
Let's go.
It's okay. I can do it alone.
I can't work with him.
I can't do this.
Let's go.
That was good. It was
the best music video of my life.
It had the feel.
[Been walking for 20 minutes.]
Central...
I think this is it.
Center Place!
Street musicians.
Isn't this place hot?
Song Ji Hyo!
The Soup Place.
This street is poetic.
It feels good.
Is someone here?
You have to move back.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
- Bye!
- Oh, be careful.
Where do we go?
Where are we going?
Over there. We don't know
where we're going.
Where are we going?
Oh my God! Someone is here.
I think it's this place.
They passed by her.
They didn't see me.
They just passed by.
Wait! It's here!
It's right here.
Excuse me.
It's this place.
Is this the mission?
Hear the words on the mission card
from the store employee.
I have to have her say this?
- I need to have her say this?
- We have more coming.
AIS. Hi!
AIS.
[Where Ji Hyo is.]
AIS! AIS!
They passed by again.
Who was it?
Is it a cafe? AIS?
This is the right place.
Guess the name of the K-pop song
the street singer sings.
Guess all three within a minute.
I bet he doesn't know the songs.
- This is it.
- Here?
Wow.
- Hi.
- Here's your mission.
[Bring six grown men.]
- It may take longer if we go together.
- Yeah.
Excuse me, do you have time?
We're a Korean TV show program.
Oh thank you.
Nice to meet you, Sawyer.
- How old?
- She's five and a half months.
- She's come all the way from London.
- London?
[English made easy.]
Excuse me! Do you have time?
We're Korean Running Man TV Show program.
Can you game with me?
Ignore her.
- Happy birthday.
- Oh thank you.
Happy birthday dear...
Ray.
Happy birthday to you.
[Meanwhile, Ji Hyo needs to
finish her soup to get her card.]
[The house special tomato soup.]
Oh thank you!
[Served with sour dough.]
Thank you!
It's good.
Woo Bin and Kwang Soo will
pick the person to match against.
Match?
- I thought we were teams.
- You will pick.
You need to win four in a row to
accomplish your mission.
So we're not on the same team.
The game is arm wrestle.
I can't arm wrestle.
I'm going to arm wrestle the kid.
I will go first.
I will...
I will pick him.
What is your name? Paul!
Paul!
Are you ready?
All right. Here we go.
Kim Woo Bin! Kim Woo Bin!
No! No! Please!
Just a bit more!
Thank you.
Go Kwang Soo!
Ready! Start!
Okay good! Go Kwang Soo!
Okay Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
Thank you!
I can't do it anymore.
- Isn't this Rain's 'La Song'?
- No.
Correct!
What do you mean no?
What do you mean 'no'?
Isn't it Rain's 'La Song'?
- I told you!
- Thank you.
I could tell right away.
How can you not recognize your own song?
Mission accomplished.
I know that I'm not earth.
- Fire?
[Need to pick the element that they don't have.]
- Fire.
[Jong Kook - Water
Rain - Wind]
[Ji Hyo - Earth
Mission Card - Fire]
[Meanwhile...]
Thank you! Very delicious.
I'm going to eat. Yeah?
But... how should I say this?
This is so frustrating.
Oh! I already ate.
Oh! Did you eat?
No.
- I'm hungry.
- Oh you're hungry.
- Because you didn't eat.
- That's right.
- Did you eat?
- Did you?
Not yet.
Did you eat?
Yeah! That's it. Thank you.
Yes. Melissa.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, oh.
Shouldn't we pick this one?
- Choose one?
- Choose this.
We will pick this.
[Suk Jin - Water
Jae suk - Fire]
[Ji Hyo - Earth
Mission Card - Wind]
Pass this one.
One more.
Okay!
Mission success!
You may choose one of the
elements that you need.
We have to take one we
do not have.
- This?
- Wind?
[Gary - Fire
Ha Ha- Fire]
[Ji Hyo - Earth
Mission Card - Wind]
Okay!
Lee Kwang Soo!
Thank you!
Choose one of the three.
We asked for wind.
Should we choose wind?
- Fire!
- Water or fire?
- Fire.
Let's go with fire.
Fire.
[Kwang Soo - Wind
Woo Bin - Water]
[Ji Hyo - Earth
Mission Card- Fire]
Which way should I go?
There are two teams over there.
I don't know which is which.
I saw two teams in the
restaurant and I ran out here.
I want to drink coffee in a
place like this.
[Famous street with
European cafes and restaurants.]
The point is to drink a relaxing coffee here.
But I feel like I'm being chased.
I have two Earth Cards.
I just need one more.
[Australian Americano,
long black's unique taste.]
I'm finished.
- Thank you.
The last card to make me
become Earth.
I have become earth.
First earth element of
four elements of the Earth.
Find Song Ji Hyo, the woman
of Earth, doing missions in Melbourne.
Ji Hyo is here.
You need to find her and
put her on the altar.
Find her?
- The goddess of earth is...
- We are fire.
Wind.
We need to find Ji Hyo.
She's earth.
Now that I'm complete earth,
I can walk with my head high.
We need to find Ji Hyo.
How are we going to find Ji Hyo?
Oh no.
We have the crowd coming.
Sorry!
How are we going to find Ji Hyo?
Where is she?
Do you have Ji Hyo's number?
Yeah, I need to call her.
Where are we going to find Ji Hyo?
We need to find her.
Where should we find her?
But can we shoot here?
Yeah, we don't want anyone
to get hurt.
[Due to safety issues, we
had to cancel street shooting.]
I sent a text.
If you are successful, then come
to the Royal Exhibition.
I have become complete earth.
You need to find me.
Hehe.
-  We need to find her.
- Okay.
How are we going to find Ji Hyo?
This is hard.
[The Royal Exhibition]
[Ji Hyo got here first.]
It's huge.
[This is where the treasure lies.]
What do we do now?
I'm complete.
The other members need to
find their cards.
Then I just need to wait?
Since you joined late today...
I feel like a princess today.
It's so high.
- Song Ji Hyo!
- She's over there.
Ji Hyo!
Finding me is not what's important.
It's not about finding me.
You need to find out which
elements you are.
Find your card with your
name in the Royal Exhibition.
Complete the four elements.
And step up on the altar.
We know which elements we are.
- Then go find the cards.
- We need to find the cards?
Whose side are you on?
Are you helping someone?
I have become the complete earth.
- She's the earth.
- She is.
Then...
Like I said you need to hurry up.
It's the goddess of earth.
Which cards do you have?
- Fire.
Then if Jong Kook is water,
we need to find the Water Card.
Yes.
So I need to carry all three cards
and go up on the altar with Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo!
- Hurry up!
Ji Hyo!
- Kwang Soo!
- Ji Hyo!
How are you?
- Hi.
You need the cards you won.
The person who gets up on the
altar with me wins.
I'm the earth.
Help us.
Be on our side.
I'm neutral.
So we can steal earth from Ji Hyo?
I was just wondering.
I didn't get the rules yet.
Do you know how important I am?
The mission depends on
who I go to.
I'm going to leave you out if
you don't behave.
Okay! I was just kidding.
Woo Bin is here.
You need to escort Ji Hyo to the altar.
- I'm sorry.
- You little punk!
The first thing you think about after
I got to Melbourne is ripping me off?
Find your cards first.
Watch out.
We just need to find water and fire.
We just need to find water and
fire and get up on the altar.
Not many guys know which
element they are.
- Really?
- Not many do.
Let's look in here.
Is it first floor only?
It's obviously not a place that's
too visible.
We have to find one as soon as possible.
Check the pillars.
Find them quickly.
[Found an envelope.]
It's mine.
- Did you find it?
- No.
You look like you found it.
- Is it ours?
- It's mine.
Dang!
You're so cool.
Let's hurry up.
Ji Hoon!
- Which ones did we get?
- It's fire and wind.
We just need to find water.
We have wind and fire.
Find water! It's not
in the trash can.
Everyone! This is an emergency.
Ji Hoon found his own card.
- Who did?
- Ji Hoon.
- He found his own card.
- Oh no.
We have to distract them.
Distract Team Blue.
Woo Bin! You find the cards.
I will stop Ji Hoon.
It's over when Jong Kook finds it.
We have to find it.
[This envelope is Ha Ha's.]
[Gary found one. And it's his!]
I'm going to check if it's mine.
[Gary and Ha Ha are both fire.]
[So they need to find a Water Card to win.]
- Who is it?
- We're in trouble.
- I found all of ours.
- All of them?
Really? Dang!
- We need to find water.
We just need to find water.
Then no one can beat us.
Then we can win!
This is crazy.
We just need to find water.
[So obvious]
What are you doing?
Hey this isn't coming out.
It's here, but I can't get it.
It's here. Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk!
- Woo Bin!
What? What?
Jae Suk! Stop Ji Hoon.
- How did you find this?
- I did.
You should have been discrete!
I tried to be discrete,
but it wouldn't come out.
Can you do anything right?
It keeps on going in.
It's all the way in now.
Don't we have to use a tool now?
How did you push this in?
- It's not coming out.
- Go find something else.
I'm so tired.
[Rain found an envelope behind
the camera.]
Ji Hoon! Where are you going?
[It's Kwang Soo's,
who is right behind him.]
- Did you find it?
- Stop following me.
Ji Hoon found a card!
- I said stop following me.
- I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
There is an important rule
that you cannot forget.
When you find someone else's card.
Take off the name tag of the
envelope's owner.
Then you may win the card
inside the envelope.
What are you doing?
Can I open it now?
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
Is it mine?
Woo Bin, you have to find the
rest on your own.
[Kwang Soo and Rain are both wind.]
It's someone else's wind.
Hide it.
Put it in your pocket.
[Ha Ha and Gary need water.]
I found it.
[Yoo Jae Suk]
I found one more.
I found Jae Suk's.
We have to rip the name tag.
Then we can take whatever
Jae Suk has.
He's our target now.
If you have the envelope,
then you have to rip the name tag.
- No, you have to do it.
- I have to do it?
Be my decoy.
Hey go!
He's coming. Go!
- He's coming.
- I will protect you.
Jong Kook!
I got it off.
I couldn't find any envelopes.
- Water... please water.
- Fire!
- We have all the fire cards.
You have fire, I have fire.
Woo Bin! Come here.
- Come here.
- Let me tell you something important.
Neither of you can win.
You can't win.
Then help us. And we will
share the winnings with you.
Really? Which card do you need?
We just need water.
Water? I'm water.
I'm water.
Then we just need to get yours.
But why can't he and I win?
You can't! There's no fire.
You and I need to team up.
- There is no fire.
- Then we need to take it from whoever has it.
There is no fire.
You can't take it off.
You want all three of us to team up?
I have one fire card.
Jong Kook.
- I have fire.
- How's that possible?
I got it from the mission.
Then he can win.
- You got it from the mission?
- He still has the possibility.
Then I also have a possibility.
- Jong Kook!
- Why did he reveal it?
He's too naive.
Are you stupid?
Why did you reveal it?
- I've never seen anyone like him.
- You're so cool.
You should have pretended that you have
no chance and betrayed us later.
That was a big upset in the game.
You know you just gave that up.
I couldn't even imagine.
It would have been hard for me anyway.
[He hides the fire card.]
It's Jong Kook's.
[In the right shoe this time.]
There are so many places to hide.
- Wow Running Man is no joke.
- Woo Bin.
- Which one do you need? I will help you.
- Water and wind.
Water and wind?
I have fire.
- You have water right?
- No.
I will find you wind.
- Then I find just water?
- You need to find water.
But what good is finding it?
We can't beat Jong Kook.
- I will help you.
- I can't trust you.
He trusts me. When you find the
water card, give it to me.
- Then I will just snatch it from him.
- I can't trust you.
- Woo Bin!
- I'm on my own now.
You have to use me.
- Which one do you have?
- I have nothing. That's why I'm searching.
Then I would have ripped
the name tag.
I have fire.
I bet Rain has wind.
Obviously Jong Kook needs water.
Take the wind card.
Then rip Jong Kook off.
I mean find the water card first.
Then I will share the winnings with you.
- Help me.
- Okay.
- Can you do it?
- Of course.
I have fire and you have none.
So my cut should be bigger.
You're an Heir!
Act like an Heir!
You take the trophy.
And I will take the gold.
Then let's do this.
Suk Jin...
It was 35 to 65.
But it's unlikely for us to beat Rain.
- We need all three.
- 30, 30, 30.
30, 30, 40.
You're an Heir!
No wonder you lost to Kim Tan.
We have 10 leftover.
I have an offer from them too.
- We're a team!
- So what's my cut?
I will act according to my share.
25, 25, 25, 25.
Okay, okay.
[One quarter including Gary.]
We're going to be obvious.
We have no choice.
Let's go over there.
- Did you find it?
- No.
That thing opens?
I had my arm stuck in it.
Did you find something?
No?
Why aren't you telling me?
He found it!
Woo Bin!
Wait Woo Bin!
[That means Rain has Woo Bin's envelope?]
What?
Is this right?
It's water.
We have to stop them.
They've got it all.
I found them all.
It's lost.
[Jong Kook and Rain only need Ji Hyo.]
Rain! Look at them. Oh no.
We have to stop them.
- Stick to them.
- This is like American football.
Run Ji Hyo!
Whoever wins, give me my share.
- Ji Hyo, run!
- Why is she running anyway?
What? What?
Why is she running?
I have my freedom of choice.
Did you find it or not?
Gary, what's my share?
25, 25...
What's my share?
What? What? We have to go.
Why me? I'm a nobody!
Hey! You can't stay there!
No! Gary!
Water.
Fire.
Okay! Okay!
Wind!
[Four elements complete]
[Water, fire, wind, and earth.
Four elements come together.]
[And finally awakens the hidden treasure.]
Earth!
I need my share, Rain!
What do you mean?
You worked against us.
He's not even funny.
- You were working against us.
- Keep your word.
Give me my share.
- What is that?
- Is it this?
- This is all gold.
- Is it?
Yeah. It's all gold.
Wow.
You can have this then.
- Let me see that.
- It's gold.
I'm jealous.
Your girlfriend will be happy.
You've got it all.
You even took gold.
What about me?
Anyway! Adventure Special.
The winner is...
Kim Jong Kook and Jung Ji Hoon!
We came to Brisbane first
in Australia.
And then the Gold Coast.
- And here.
- Melbourne.
It was a long trip.
We'd like to thank our special guests
and others who have helped us.
Thank you!
I love Australia.
Subtitles by DramaFever