[Ji Suk Jin]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[All of Big-nose's humiliation
in the past four years.]
[Countless number of days where victory
was the furthest thing from his grasp.]
I won!
[But his victories were
like a figment of his imagination.]
[A feeling that he'd like to
re-live once again.]
Can you... help me?
- It's getting hotter by the day.
- It's the middle of the summer.
- It truly is summer.
- It's really hot.
Jae Suk, I shouldn't admit this, but
I didn't even realize Suk Jin wasn't here.
[Suk Jin's weak existence.]
- Where's Suk Jin?
- Take a look at this first, Jae Suk.
I'm really shocked right now.
As you may have guessed, Ji Suk Jin
will appear from behind the screen.
- There must be something planned.
- Please make the announcement, Jae Suk.
This is embarrassing to read out loud.
Did Suk Jin write this?
In rain or snow, this man can always
bring bouts of laughter to the audience.
The best of the best comedian,
Republic of Korea's very own Ji Suk Jin.
Over 15 years of experience ranging from
talk shows, quiz shows, and variety shows.
From every kind of genre you can think of,
this is the man who tops all the lists!
- Why is this so long?
- Is he even going to come on?
From his on-the-spot hit songs that
he has created throughout the years...
What hit songs is he even talking about?
I'm so embarrassed for him.
And to all the victories that
he's taken home in all the years...
What?
[Big-nose did what?]
What is this?
[Finally making their appearance...]
[are Big-nose's closest friends!]
[A lively history with Suk Jin...]
[Their long history will continue
onto the muddy farm field.]
I have a bad feeling about this.
We're going to lose.
[The man of Korea's talk shows-
Nam Hee Suk.]
[And this gentleman...]
[The perfect team play over
ten years in the making.]
[He will sacrifice himself for Suk Jin.]
[The royalty of comedy- Park Soo Hong.]
[The man who never once
lost a verbal battle to Big-nose.]
[His verbal skills will become
one of Big-nose's biggest ally.]
[Verbal skills of a deity- Kim Jae Dong.]
[The young man whose first debut
was introduced by Big-nose himself.]
[The young man became a real man
and comes to Big-nose's rescue.]
[From a young man to a real man-
Kim Hee Chul.]
[Korea's biggest legends in talk shows
all come to gather in one place.]
Jae Dong?
What are you guys doing?
[And the star of today's show
finally makes his appearance.]
[A history of friendship that goes back
way farther than anyone could guess.]
[That friendship will prove to be
a huge support to Big-nose.]
[Unexpected goddess of variety world-
Lee So Yeon.]
[Today belongs to Big-nose!]
- Are you all ready?
- We are Big-nose's friends!
- Hey, let's do it one more time.
- I called them all out.
- What are they all doing here?
I invited them all out on the show.
[They look to be better friends with the
rest of the Running Man cast members?]
Hey, I invited them all out!
[His friends abandon him,
and he's now the loner of the group.]
Why are you guys on such friendly terms?
The bottom line is, they all came on
the show to win today's race.
Please give them all a big
round of applause.
I would like to introduce them,
and tell you about our friendship.
- Jae Dong and I've been with the same agency.
- That was over ten years ago, right?
Yes, that was over ten years ago.
We'd go out drinking and chat together.
- We've all been out together.
- Yes, we have.
After you left, he said some nasty things
about you behind your back.
I don't believe that.
He'd never do that to me.
You look uglier today than
you ever have.
- What about Hee Chul?
- Do you even have any hair in the front?
If this is how you were going to treat me,
then you never should've invited me on.
We didn't invite you.
Just come over to my house
where there aren't any cameras around.
I've known Hee Suk since before
I even made my debut.
- I met him through Jae Suk.
- That's when the stations were struggling.
Even though it may look like Suk Jin
and I are really good friends
this is the first time
he's called me in over four years.
I wasn't even going to answer
because I didn't recognize his number.
When I didn't answer his call,
he sent me a text instead.
His text said, 'It's me, Suk Jin.'
- Hee Suk and I are really close though.
- No, he's my good friend.
Suk Jin and I worked on the gag concert
audition together so that we could win.
- Yes, I had forgotten about that.
- Kim Gook Jin helped us plan it.
[Soo Hong played a big role in helping
Suk Jin get started in the business.]
- Hee Chul's usually not this quiet either.
- You know what he said to me earlier?
'Make Suk Jin stop this.'
Why would you say something like that?
Hee Chul didn't need to worry about that.
We thought it was funny.
It truly is an honor to be on
such an elegant show as this one.
Nice!
That was a really good comment.
Before he became a member of Super Junior,
he first made his mark by being on our show.
[Made his first debut by being on Big-nose's
show before becoming a member of SJ.]
- He was on my show for his debut.
- What about So Yeon?
- With So Yeon...
- I was on that show too.
You didn't remember that, did you?
- Wasn't it on the show, 'Hi-five'?
- No, it was on the other show.
These people are some of my closest friends.
They're like family members to me.
Then are we going to be competing against
Suk Jin and his group of friends?
Suk Jin tried for over two months to
personally invite these guests on the show.
That's why they're all on the show today.
So today's race is titled,
'Big-nose's Victory Race.'
[Big-nose's Victory Race]
We will start the race by giving everyone
one of these gold bars.
Okay, everyone may now each take one.
Running Man is awesome.
- Can I just take this?
- So Yeon really likes her gold!
[Could So Yeon be the new Gold Lady?]
Big-nose will be given slight advantages
to help him gain his victory in today's race.
You can choose one, but there are
a variety of advantages for you.
You can reuse those advantages
with each new game that you'll play today.
- Go with Lee So Yeon's card.
- Yes, that looks like a good one.
I doubt it'll be a dud.
- Double the gold!
- You chose the 'double the gold' option.
Every time your team wins a round of games,
the amount of your gold will double.
How is this going to help us win?
The more gold bars you have, the bigger the
advantage you'll have at the final competition.
- So that's a good thing.
- Can we see whose name was a dud?
Yes, you may.
[They are off to a good start,
and it's time to start the mission!]
So we got the 'double the gold' card.
Since the more gold we have, the better,
let's work really hard today.
Because this is real gold.
But what if the other team wins?
We'll just each take care of
one opponent.
Hee Chul can take care of Jong kook.
[Hee Chul in charge of the Tiger?]
I don't know what today is going to be,
but let's not be too kind to Suk Jin.
- Why would we let him win? This is our win.
- He needs to be stepped on to survive.
That's the only way to make sure that an
episode like this doesn't happen again.
We need to end it for good so that
he doesn't think of doing this again.
Okay, let's make sure of that today.
[Arrives at their first destination.]
It's a muddy farm field.
[Welcome!
It's the season of muddy farm fields.]
Look at all the water.
It's actually not that bad.
Hee Suk, you've never done anything
like this before, have you?
[First time experience for both Hee Suk
and Soo Hong in 24 years since their debut.]
[The masters of the variety world have never
experienced this before in their years.]
Let's go back to the studio.
[Comforts of a studio where it's cool
in the summers and warm in the winters.]
[Have only basked in the comforts of a studio-
Nam Hee Suk and Park Soo Hong.]
This is the first time in my life that I've
ever stepped foot in a farm field.
You know what I've always said whenever
I saw Jae Suk doing things like this?
That Jae Suk has the right to be making
the kind of money that he makes.
- He deserves to get paid his money.
- Do you know what Hee Suk texted me?
He would text me things like,
'I enjoyed watching your show today, Jae Suk.'
'Must you really do those things
on the show?'
But here he is on the show today.
[Here's your chance to experience it
for yourself today.]
We've prepared a game for you to get warmed
up and earn yourselves another gold bar.
We're already warmed up.
There's no need for this.
We felt that our guests would need
some time to get used to the field
so we're going to be playing a game of,
'Spin a circle with the woman in your arms.'
The male members will have to spin
the woman on their team once
around their waist without dropping
them in the water in a relay form.
Even if we try to drop her,
Ji Hyo won't let herself fall in the water.
[A game specifically geared
towards Ace Blank Ji.]
She's not all that light either.
[Ji Suk Jin vs Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Ace and Yoo Hyuk spin a circle
in a steady motion.]
[Big-nose and So Yeon can't even begin
to get into their spin position.]
[Yoo Hyuk finishes first and
safely passes off to Kwang Soo.]
[Big-nose is still struggling
to complete his spin.]
[Big-nose vs Kwang Soo.]
We got it!
[So Yeon is passed off to Hee Chul.]
[Team RM is already onto
their third player, Ha Ha.]
[Too heavy?]
[Ha Ha's face is about to explode.]
[Not an easy mission on the field where it's
already tough enough to find their balance.]
[Team SJ is already starting to fall behind.]
[Third player, Hee Suk vs
Fourth player, Gary.]
I'm going to spin you in one move.
[Hee Suk's shocking show of strength.]
[Unbelievable sight to behold!]
[Their only chance to catch up!]
[Team SJ catches up to their opponents
by Hee Suk's shocking play.]
[Fourth players for each team now tries
to imitate Hee Suk's method.]
[Good try- Bad try.]
[Please don't try this at home.]
My friends are doing great!
[Team SJ's final player, Jae Dong.]
[Monday Couple is still playing
hard to get with the muddy farm field.]
[Even Jae Dong successfully half spins
So Yeon around.]
[Team SJ's shocking turn of events.]
How are we so good?
[Their victory is right
in front of their eyes!]
[Jae Dong and So Yeon successfully
complete their spin.]
[Team SJ wins the game!]
[Team SJ wins their first gold bar.]
[We're Big-nose's friends!]
[Blank Ji takes a proper mud bath
in the muddy farm field.]
[Unexpected black hole, Mr. Gary.]
- We won!
- Ji Hyo, you smell like onions.
[Onion smelling actress.]
Are you all used to the farm field
a bit now?
The first game will be played
right here in the muddy field
and the name of the game is,
'Alley Leader Field Bingo.'
Do you see what's been set up
on the sides?
Assign three members to stand in front
of the bingo board on the stands.
The rest of the members will search for
numbered discs hidden out in the field.
Toss the disc to your team members
once you find it.
Connect any three numbers together to
create a bingo for the win.
Okay, we will now get started.
[Alley Leader Field Bingo]
- Get ready for the first round.
- Why do you guys look so tiny?
[The tiniest one of the bunch.]
- You just need to complete one line.
- Okay!
[They must first find the numbered discs
hidden out in the muddy farm field.]
Soo Hong!
You have to get down on the ground.
Great job, team!
[They're all desperately crawling around.]
Behind you, Jong kook!
[A numbered disc!]
[Kkuk discovers the first numbered disc.]
[Must throw the disc to their teammate.]
[Soo Hong gets his hand on the disc
by pure luck!]
[Great team play!]
[Team SJ is proving out to be
more formidable than expected.]
[While Yoo Hyuk is busy digging up onions,
Kkuk discovers another disc.]
[Eagle eyes Kkuk finds another disc!]
Get him, Jae Dong!
How can he be that fast?
[Already two discs on board.
One more for the bingo win!]
So Yeon looks so pretty from up close!
I never imagined that I'd be
crawling around like this.
You scared me!
- I thought you were a mud hopper fish!
- What did you say?
[Giraffe discovers a disc of his own!]
[If the disc is marked with number 2,
then Team RM wins the game!]
[Team SJ's aggressive block.]
[Give me that disc!
Yoo Hyuk is immediately surrounded.]
[So Yeon aggressively blocks Kwang Soo,
and Soo Hong passes the disc to his team.]
[Team SJ only needs the '9'
to win the bingo!]
[Giraffe discovers another disc,
and is immediately attacked by So Yeon.]
[The birth of a new mud warrior princess.]
[Team SJ can have a completed bingo line
if the disc is marked with number nine!]
[Did they just get a completed line?]
[Ah... it's a six.]
Right behind you!
[Even the Tiger isn't enough to scare
mud warrior, So Yeon!]
[This disc could mean victory
for either one of the teams!]
Let's just go back to the studio to film this.
Let's just do this in the studio!
Are we doing all this just so that
Ji Suk Jin could win a race for once?
[Yoo Hyuk is leisurely going for
a swim in the muddy waters.]
He deserves to get paid the big bucks.
He really deserves to get paid the money.
Jae Suk!
You deserve to get paid a lot!
You really are the nation's top MC.
Do we really need to do all this?
No matter how much effort we put into it,
it still looks like we're just playing.
He's making the rest of us look bad.
[Nation's top MC is doing
butterfly strokes in the mud.]
What is he doing?
[The muddy field is another
waterpark for this MC.]
- This is just a given.
- Look at what he's doing!
[That disc would mean an
immediate win for Team SJ!]
[They just need to catch the disc...
and it's a win for Team SJ!]
[Team SJ loses the chance!]
[Disc Nine could also mean
an immediate win for Team RM.]
[Tiger fakes everyone out!]
[Team RM's completed bingo line!]
[Team SJ unfortunately
loses their chance of winning.]
Team RM wins the first round.
- Let's help Suk Jin win.
- So Yeon did great out there.
She was a track and field athlete
throughout high school.
- Where did So Yeon go?
- You impressed me, So Yeon.
Let's help Suk Jin win!
[Round two.]
[Team RM- Disc Two.]
[Big-nose and Hee Chul each
find a disc back to back.]
[Nice catch!]
[Team SJ- Disc Four.]
[Team SJ's captain, Big-nose!]
[However...]
[Big-nose without friends by his side
is a weakling indeed.]
[That's our ace!
Team RM easily gains their second disc.]
[Big-nose's assist...
and Hee Suk's completed throw.]
[Team SJ immediately follows
with their second disc.]
[Wow! Blank Ji throws her third disc!]
Number five!
[Big-nose tries to play boomerang
with the disc he finds.]
[Throws themselves down like action stars,
and throws the disc like comedians.]
[Friendless Big-nose is like
muscleless Kim Jong Kook.]
[Team RM needs one of the following-
3, 5, 7.]
[Team SJ needs either 1 or a 5 to win.]
This towel is strangling my neck.
Suk Jin, you should always work this hard
on all your episodes.
[Even though he works hard,
doing it alone is impossible...]
Let's win this!
[Speed and nervous energy are both up!
Round two is upping the anxiety level!]
[Team SJ gains number nine.]
[Any one of these numbers means
a win for Team SJ!]
[He found disc seven?]
[Just then...]
[Blank Ji also discovers a disc of her own!]
[Will it be Hee Chul... or Blank Ji?]
[Which of the two teams
will catch the disc first?]
[Oh! He intercepts the disc!]
[Ha Ha's perfectly timed defense!]
[Blank Ji immediately makes her pass.]
[Number five.]
[Team RM completes their bingo.]
[Team RM also wins Round Two.]
[Team SJ loses another chance at a win.]
[Team RM wins three gold bars.]
You guys are dirty players.
- We're not dirty players.
- We're not letting you get away with it.
- Let's play a clean game.
- We'll show you what dirty playing really is.
- You'll be shocked at how dirty we can play.
- We're not dirty players.
We will now move onto the second location.
You may get on your way.
Can't we just finish taping it here?
This is just the first location?
[We're only just getting started.]
Soo Hong, we're really trying to win.
Do you think that we can win?
- There's no way that you'll win.
- I can't believe we lost the first game.
It's not just the first game,
but you're going to lose the rest too.
I bet my guest appearance fee,
and my phone number on you losing.
Why would you bet your phone number?
Just in case.
Suk Jin told me that So Yeon
is a really good drinker.
- Yes, she likes to drink.
- Tell us that one story again, Suk Jin.
It's a really old story. It's something
that happened a long time ago.
- She says she doesn't drink anymore.
- This happened ten years ago.
- What happened?
- We all went out to drink one night.
I knew that I should see her home just to
make sure that she got home safely.
[Suk Jin tries to get So Yeon
safely back home.]
She lives in Mokdong, so I put her in a cab,
and told the driver to take her to Mokdong.
But as soon as she gets in the cab,
she gets out the other door.
[Why is he telling all these stories?]
Since So Yeon is here, we need to play
the ideal man roulette game.
[Time to play Ideal Man Roulette!]
Okay, we're going to get this
game started!
Ugh, I miss Guk Joo!
Are you ready?
Okay, here we go with the first round!
[Fixing up his hair.]
Ji Suk Jin or Gary!
One, two, three!
Ji Suk Jin!
That's a total insult!
[How can this be?]
- You have to be serious.
- She just said that she's serious!
Okay, next round.
Kim Hee Chul or Park Soo Hong.
- One, two, three!
- I don't know!
- Kim Hee Chul!
Why do you even look surprised?
It's Kim Hee Chul.
- I have really nice legs!
- But your shorts are really short.
[Wearing his hot pants to look young and hip.]
He's pissed off for real.
[I'm not playing with you anymore.]
Next!
Kim Jae Dong or Yoo Jae Suk!
- One, two, three!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
If this is how you're going to treat me,
then why did you even invite me on the show?
You guys could've done
the show by yourselves.
This is ridiculous.
Suk Jin, Jong Kook and I
are the only ones left now?
Those three are left, but you should take
one of them off the list first.
Should we eliminate one of them?
So Yeon, you can eliminate someone.
Kim Jong Kook, Yoo Jae Suk, or Ji Suk Jin.
Eliminate one from the list.
Kim Jong Kook.
She has bad taste in men.
- Okay, then onto the next round.
- It's the final round.
Final round.
Ji Suk Jin or Yoo Jae Suk. One, two, three!
Yoo Jae Suk.
[So Yeon's Ideal Man Roulette-
Yoo Jae Suk wins!]
[Who is this game of roulette
supposed to be for?]
[A bus full of disgruntled men.]
Ji Hyo, let's play a round of
this game for you too.
[Ji Hyo's round of Ideal Man Roulette.]
Season two, Song Ji Hyo's episode!
- I really don't want to lose this round.
- Who should we pin Jae Suk up against?
I want to go up against him.
Okay, me and Gary!
Let's do this.
Yoo Jae Suk and Kang Gary.
One, two, three!
Kang Gary!
[Celebrating as if they've just won
a World Cup match.]
I did it!
[Disgruntled by her choice.]
[The riders on the bus becomes of one mind
with Jae Suk's elimination.]
Must you really react like this?
Park Soo Hong and Ha Ha.
One, two, three!
Ha Ha!
I'm getting off this bus!
Please open the door!
[What could you not like about me?
I even wore my hot pants today!]
- They look like your underwear.
- Those pants are awful!
Married men can't wear pants like these.
One of my sisters has
the same pair of shorts.
[Team SJ vs Team RM-
Arrives at their second location.]
- Are you upset?
- Bring me my pants!
- Why are you getting upset over that?
- I want to change out of these shorts.
He's upset for real right now.
Those hot shorts used to be really popular
when Soo Hong used to wear them in the past.
Soo Hong is really upset right now.
- You should just accept it for what it is.
- Those shorts are way too short!
Stop being pissed, and come over here.
I'm just going to totally go for it.
I'm going to start wearing them like this.
- I'm just going to wear them like this.
- You have no muscles in your legs.
What are you talking about?
My legs are nothing but muscle!
Look at how pretty my legs are!
[His legs could give the girls of
Girls Generation a run for their money.]
[Married man Hee Suk faces defeat
unlike his once wildly popular days.]
I don't like these girls either.
I don't get treated this badly
on any other shows I go on.
I'll come up with another game later
so stop worrying so much.
[Yoo Hyuk is working hard to
console hot pants loving Soo Hong.]
[Unsatisfied with Yoo Hyuk's efforts.]
You're off the list too.
Soo Hong used to totally disregard me
during his popular days.
- You saw that too, right, Hee Suk?
- Yeah, I did.
Your day is coming too and you'll see.
[Revenge 20 years in the making.]
Your next game is the playground loyalty game
which will test the bounds of your loyalty.
[Playground Loyalty Game]
Each member of the team will play a part
in a mission related to the number, 100.
If Ji Suk Jin's team wins,
then they will twice the amount of gold.
If Team RM wins,
then they'll just win two gold bars.
- We have to win this game.
- I've already lost my motivation.
We have to help me win this one.
I've only had two wins in four years.
What do you think we should do?
Gong-gi game?
[Team SJ has the first round of selections.]
- Drinking something may be hard.
- How about the slide?
Okay, let's go with the slide.
We'll go with the slide.
- They'll go with the slide.
- The slide is behind you to the right.
[What will they have to do on the slide?]
You have to go down the slide 100 times.
[Mission- Go down the slide 100 times.]
[What did he just say?]
[Down the slide 100 times?]
- How are we going to do that?
- Slide down 100 times?
What do you think you're doing right now?
How are we going to slide down 100 times?
Look at Soo Hong.
What's he going to do?
Sorry to ask this, but can I not do that?
It's a little embarrassing.
- It's embarrassing.
- What are you doing?
[The once popular man is trying to offer
up his sense of humor from 20 years ago.]
All six members of the team can take turns to
go down the slide a total of 100 times.
Once you go down the slide
you have to climb back up on the other slide
to slide back down on the first slide.
If you get tired, then you can
swap with another team member.
But you must slide down a total of 100 times
and the team to complete it first wins.
So this is a test of our endurance?
I haven't been working out much lately,
so this can be my workout.
- Do you all understand the rules?
- I'll just think of it as a workout session.
[Loyalty game one hundred-
One hundred times down the slide.]
[Team RM to take the first turn.]
- Misters, watch carefully on how we do it.
- Keep that up, and you'll get beat.
- What did you say?
- You won't even know who hit you.
Just like this.
Us group of 'misters' will beat you up.
I don't know if Kwang Soo can even fit
since this is a child's sized slide.
We're going to win this, aren't we?
Okay, get ready!
[Slide one hundred times- Team RM.]
[Slide challenge is proving to be
much more difficult than expected.]
This is hard.
- That was only his second slide.
- You expect us to do this 100 times?
[That's why we call it 'The loyalty game'.]
You have to do it as many
times as you can.
[Proving to be difficult
for even speedy Gary.]
[Only his fifth slide.]
How about we chat about current events
while he's running around in circles?
Okay, I'm feeling it now.
This is really hard. This is the
toughest game we could've picked.
- How many have you done? Eight?
- No, this is his tenth.
[He never slid down the slide this much
even as a kid.]
You're like a different man now
from when you first started.
[First turn- Twelfth turn.]
[The real Gary has gone and disappeared.]
I haven't seen you like this in a long time.
Four more, just do four more.
We need you to get 20.
Hurry and climb up there!
Okay, let's have the next person go
when he finishes this round.
[Depleted of his energy.]
[Gary touches off to Ha Ha after 17 slides.]
He's much quicker because he's shorter.
[Second runner- Ha Ha.
Short height means more speed.]
The way I see it, he'll probably keep
this up until his fifth slide down.
- This is only his third slide down.
- Wow, you're fast!
Okay, this is only his third slide down.
But he's going to start slowing down.
[Speedy Ha Ha is still quick on his feet.]
His eyes are slowly going to start to
roll backwards on his fourth slide down.
Then his eyes are going to roll completely
backwards on his fifth slide down.
[Will it be a different person sliding down
on this fifth slide?]
See?
He's completely different already.
[A magical slide that transforms a person from
when they first go in to when they come out.]
He looks like a suitcase that rolls out
of the conveyor belt at the airport.
Take a good look at him.
He's like a suitcase at an airport.
[Baggage claim area.]
You're still really fast.
Hey, it's okay for you to quit now.
[Sweet and tempting voice of the devil.]
- This isn't going to get you anything.
- I still haven't seen my suitcase yet.
[Tired looking Ha Ha suitcase.]
[Sixteen rounds for Ha Ha-
Touches off at round 33.]
[Young blood, Giraffe, is on the move!]
[He's stuck!]
[Sad Giraffe with his long neck...]
Seriously!
Why did you bend down your head like that?
[Finally manages to complete his first round.]
- How many is that?
- How many has he done?
[45th round...]
- So Yeon wants to say something to you.
- There's no time for that!
- So Yeon has something to say to you.
- Want to grab a cup of coffee?
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing!
- Get your head back on straight!
[Giraffe loses his head over one word
from a beautiful woman.]
Were you serious about that?
What are you doing!
Seriously!
[Slide Fairy appears to Kwang Soo again
to weave him under her spell.]
[Shaved ice... what does that mean?]
[Get over here!]
I was talking to her!
[Gets his magic hand ready.]
[Wow, the best record so far!
Kwang Soo completes 23 rounds on the slide!]
You can probably date a star now.
[A sudden burst of energy!]
Shoot her a heart!
[Shoots her a heart.]
[Total of 60 rounds down the slide-
Kwang Soo with 27 slides of his own.]
[Touches off to Blank Ji.]
[Giraffe is kicked out of the way.]
Hey, be careful.
You always make me worry about you.
Stick out your palm and slap them all
on the cheek as you slide down.
[That's our ace!
Maintaining her quick speed.]
Shouldn't you be getting married?
- That's good.
- You're doing a great job.
- Come on, Ji Hyo!
- I feel it!
- You feel it?
- Faster!
- You can do five more!
[Being considerate to a fellow member
was long lost three years ago.]
Get up there before I throw
you up there!
I can see your feet!
I can see your feet now.
Don't slow down and run!
[This is the loyalty between RM members.]
[Touches off to Yoo Hyuk.]
- How many is that now?
- You have to move faster, Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is really fast.
- He's wearing the best outfit for this.
[Best pants to be wearing for this event.]
You're doing great, Jae Suk.
[As a member of RM should,
he's maintaining his fast speed.]
- You have to do 20.
- Just keep going for as long as you can.
I never knew there would be a time
when Jae Suk would ever stop talking.
[Conceding the remaining 20 laps
over to Mr. Capable.]
[Mr. Capable's workout sessions commences.]
[Wow, he's fast...]
The slide looks like it's gotten smaller.
- It's like the slide has gotten smaller.
- He's moving so fast right now.
His dream is to get paid for working out.
- He must be happy as a clam right now.
- It's all about the frame of mind.
Mister, it's all about the frame of mind.
[Reprimanded by Yoo Hyuk's bodyguard, Kkuk.]
I want to smack him too.
- You guys are...
- Get out of my way!
[We knew that was going to happen.]
You all just saw what Jae Suk did, right?
He acted like he just didn't get smacked.
- Did you see how he just pretended that?
- What are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
Who just got smacked?
[Battle of pride between these
forty something men.]
- Who are you saying just got smacked?
- Both of you, get out of my way!
Both of you, get out of my way!
- Two more!
- I feel it!
[Seemingly impossible slide mission
is nearing its end!]
[Only two more left to go...]
[Huh?]
[Kkuk mistakes the count down the slide.]
Having to do one more when you already think
that it's over is the hardest one to do.
This is killing him right now.
[Team RM- Slide mission complete.]
We will reveal your time record once
your opponent team completes their mission.
- That's when we'll reveal your time.
- Let's just say that we lost.
[Team SJ's sneaky plan not to
even shed a drop of sweat.]
- We'll let you take the gold bars.
- We'll let you take the pride too.
- We'll let you take it all.
- Okay, we lost.
That really looks difficult.
I've never seen Jong Kook panting like that.
- In all four years of doing this show.
- I should include this in my workout routine.
[Kkuk is in love with
the slide workout routine.]
I haven't been able to workout
for the past few days.
- Hee Chul can go first.
- I had a really bad slide experience.
You have to work really hard right now.
- You're going to have to do all 100.
- You have to do a lot of it yourself.
I'll do all 100 by myself.
You have to get a lot done.
We have to win this race!
- We have to win today's race!
- I can do all 100 by myself.
That's a good idea, Suk Jin.
I was a pro on the slide
when I was still back in school.
Okay, we'll see how well you do.
- How am I going to do this?
- Get ready!
- I never workout.
- Ready!
[Slide loyalty game- Team SJ!]
[How is a once slide pro, Hee Chul doing?]
- He's already feeling it.
- Already?
[Can't be... Already?]
- It always hits me really fast.
- You told us that we were acting childish.
Keep bringing him down like that.
I'm thinking about my health right now.
This is like a health program.
- This is an elegant way of working out.
- Elegant?
[Even though you look like this?]
I look more dignified than that.
[His sense of humor is still unwavering.]
[Hee Chul is putting every ounce of
energy he has into the mission.]
I think he may be able to get
about 20 done.
Pick up the speed.
You're starting to slow down!
Hey, why are you slowing down so much?
This is really fun.
Yes!
The tiger butterfly...
[Hee Chul's never disappointing
sense of humor.]
Who else would break out into a song
like that while going down the slide?
[Amazing!
Hee Chul touches off after 20 rounds.]
[Next up-
Team SJ's very own Mr. Capable, Hee Suk!]
Hee Suk can run 100m in 12 seconds flat.
[Wow, he's flying down the slide!]
[Already three slides down
in the blink of an eye!]
There it is!
He's feeling it now!
Yeah, I'm feeling it.
[After only three slides?
That's too quick!]
- Look at how he's cringing his face.
- Nam Hee Two!
But I'm still better than Park Soo Hong.
[After only six rounds... what?]
[Shamelessly asks to be tagged out.]
He already tagged you!
No, you already tagged him out!
[Big-nose unexpectedly goes into
the mission early.]
I have no endurance.
[Useless endurance which
goes against his speed.]
[Team SJ's Captain Big-nose is
fired up with the determination to win.]
- I can't help but run around it!
- We've only done 30 rounds so far.
[Already onto their third player-
Should have at least 50 done already...]
Why are you guys just standing there talking
instead of cheering me on?
Go!
[Big-nose forcefully tags So Yeon in
regardless of the fact that she's a woman.]
- 36.
- How can we only have 36?
[Only 36 rounds between three men...]
- How many do I have to do?
- You just need to do 50.
- The vein on your forehead is popping out.
- Really?
Don't worry, you still look very pretty.
Just think back to your school athletic days.
- What was your specialty?
- Long distance jumping.
She used to come in at first place
in all her regional school competitions.
She used to be a long distance jumper?
- She's the ace on our team!
- She is an ace.
[Team SJ's Ace So Yeon.]
Lee So Yeon!
Run!
What fun would this world be
without So Yeon in it?
[So Yeon's own army of admirers?]
So Yeon is the best!
No, no, Ji Hyo's the best!
- Is that not right?
- No, that's not right to say.
[Already onto the 50th slide.]
Do at least ten more.
[So Yeon round and round all by herself...]
- She's done 18 on her own already.
- She's already completed her 18th round.
[What a sad group of men...]
- Lee So Yeon is the best!
- Can I stop now?
No, you can't stop.
Get at least two more.
I'm sorry, but we've only got
two more players left.
No, he's just lying.
He's not sorry in the least.
- The count is up to 55.
- Three more! Let's just get three more.
[Thanks to her good for nothing teammates,
she's getting her fill of the slide.]
Why are you being so inconsiderate
to So Yeon?
Would you rather do one more,
or go out on a date with me?
[What?]
[His proposal is enough to give her
another burst of energy down the slide.]
I have yet to see her move that fast.
[So Yeon completes 22 rounds-
More than even Mr. Capable!]
[Hot pants man is on the move!]
Hot pants Soo Hong.
He's so slow.
He's slow and just pathetic.
[But all of Team SJ's attention is on
their Ace So Yeon.]
80.
You've completed 80 laps.
[After 80 laps are complete,
last runner, Jae Dong, is tagged in.]
- You're doing great.
- You really are taking your time.
- Pick up your speed.
- Why are you so slow?
You look like you're done with it already.
Close your mouth when
you slide down, Jae Dong.
Stop trying to look cute,
and just concentrate on moving faster.
- We have to win today!
- Tell Suk Jin to be quiet.
- We've only got four left to go.
- You can do this, Jae Dong.
[Almost at the finishing lien!]
We are almost at the finish line!
Hurry up and pick up your speed.
[A closer competition than expected.]
- Come on, cheer him on!
- I'll buy you a cup of coffee!
[Suddenly fired up down to the core!]
Only three more left to go, right?
[He even throws the glasses off of his face!]
This looks like it may be the end...
[One final lap left to go!]
[Team SJ completes 100 laps!]
Just tell us if we won or not.
I don't care if you have to make some edits,
but can you just tell us that we won?
[Please...]
I'm down here.
[This man is left abandoned as soon as
the mission is over.]
I will start off by revealing
Team SJ's record.
[Team SJ's record to be revealed first.]
Your record is... 15 minutes and 23 seconds.
- We've been doing this for 15 minutes?
- You filmed this for 15 whole minutes?
- Running Man really is something else.
- Can you speed up my process then?
We've just been used.
If you don't play out the whole thing,
then I'm going to sue you guys.
[Wanting to relay to the viewers just
how hard they've worked and sweated.]
Do you think that you should maybe
edit my portion of it?
- He really is something.
- Make sure that my legs are showcased.
[Time to reveal Team RM's record.]
[In the 15 minute mark just like Team SJ.]
15 minutes and 12 seconds.
[Team RM wins with only
a ten second difference!]
This is all because of you guys!
- You guys didn't even do anything!
- Do you think that we can win today?
[The glasses he threw off are now broken...]
Can you do something about the 11 seconds?
This is what those 11 seconds did.
- How did that happen?
- While coming down the slide.
It's because we were doing
what you told us to do.
[Doing everything they can to help
Big-nose win today's race.]
- We're not asking you to fake anything.
- We're just asking for 11 seconds.
It's just one game.
You can beat them at the next game.
[There are more games to be played!
Best out of three for playground mission.]
Let's win the next one.
Stop begging.
I'll just go to a nearby optometrist.
Forget this.
- I'm not even going to watch this episode.
- Please edit it so I look good.
- Where did you throw it?
- Did you just randomly throw it off?
[Time to look for Jae Dong's glasses.]
- I think it's around here somewhere.
- You should carry around a spare pair.
Looking for these glasses is
like a challenge on its own.
But... this isn't a joke,
but this is actually really touching.
I think I'm about to start tearing up.
Look at how beautiful this sight is.
[A beautiful sight to help ease
his earlier sense of loneliness.]
- How about we stop? This is exhausting.
- Yes, we've definitely played our part!
One, two, three.
Slate!
[This touching moment is now over
with the snap of the slate.]
[Next game- Score 100 points with Gong-gi.]
Your next mission is, gong-gi.
This is another mission which is
related to the number, 100.
All six members will each take turns
like you just did
and catch the gong-gi pieces
to score 100 points.
If you either miss catching the piece
or drop the piece,
then it's onto the next player.
[Miss catching the piece,
then it's onto the next player.]
If both teams succeed the mission,
then the team with the fastest time wins.
But if we fail, then we automatically lose?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Okay, then I'm going to dump all the pieces.
[Team RM to take the first turn.]
- Make sure you assume the correct position.
- Are there different colors?
Don't dump it while standing,
but lower your stance when you dump it.
How old were you when you first
started playing gong-gi?
What does that even matter?
This is just a scientific fact.
Just lower your stance
because that'll be better when dumping it.
Stop doing that!
- Why are you even doing that?
- How does it feel to be scolded by him?
How does it feel to be scolded
by someone younger than you?
[Older Hyuk is used to having to listen
to his young brother.]
- Yes, that's good.
- You have to toss them around like this.
- Wow!
- Wow, that was a total failure.
What the heck is this?
This is like an amateur pocket ball player.
[Acting like a pocket ball newbie.]
- No, you can't do that.
- What the heck is this!
[Gong-gi scheming duo.]
You guys are such dirty players.
- What are you guys doing?
- What do you think you're doing?
- Can you pass that over to me?
- Maybe they're trying to help us out.
[Courteous enough to stack the five pieces
together to help them grab better.]
- Then should we just go down the line?
- Yes.
That's probably better, right?
Okay, then I'm going to get started.
[Team RM's Yoo Hyuk takes the first turn.]
If you do it like that, then you're
going to lose your sense of balance.
- Don't lean off to the side.
- I'll just do it while sitting down.
Okay, you're doing great.
- Why are you blocking me from the camera?
- Sorry.
This is just the way I like to sit.
- You can do it one at a time too.
- Move it over to the other hand!
- You're taking a lot of time.
- Do you always get scolded by him like that?
It's okay.
It's because we're really close.
Good, you're doing really great.
[Very steady hand movements.]
- Yes, you're doing great!
- You really are doing really great.
- You're doing so well!
- Drop it.
- Let's move out of his way.
- Grab that group of three stones.
[Successfully grabs three all at once!]
[But...]
[He unexpectedly ousts himself
while moving over the gong-gi pieces.]
Then is his turn over?
Are you serious?
[16 pieces and the time keeps on ticking...]
Get out of the way.
[Jae Suk now gets spanked from
his older friends.]
[Kkuk is already onto his eighth piece.]
- Look at how he's catching his pieces.
- You are so dainty!
Have you been working out your arms
just so that you could do this?
We're on the same team!
Get your head on straight.
Yes, I forgot.
We are on the same team.
Catch both those pieces at the same time.
[Already a huge mound of pieces in his hand.]
No, you have to put that back down!
[Extremely sensitive down to the smallest
piece of gong-gi.]
Wouldn't it be better for you to
sit down and do it, Ji Hyo?
- Why did you go for such a huge piece?
- Because someone has to do it!
- But you have smaller hands.
- Just be quiet!
[Blank Ji is the only member of the team
whom Mr. Capable will back down to.]
[Blank Ji ousts herself while moving
the gong-gi piece.]
- Get out of the way.
- No, put that back down!
You have to put that back down!
That piece bounced out of my hand.
[Next player- Calm and peaceful Gary.]
- What is he doing right now?
- I have to move it over, don't I?
- Look at his eyes.
- My eyes are very blurry right now.
[His eyes are blurring for some reason.]
[Wow, catches the difficult group of three.]
- I've got my focus now.
- How is he going to hold onto all that?
You're doing great.
- You're done. Put that back down.
- Fine, I got it!
How am I going to do this?
You can do it.
[He moved the neighboring piece!]
[Everyone's overly excited!]
[No way!]
Okay, fine!
[Ha Ha is disqualified before
he can even get started.]
This is absurd!
How can I do all this on my own?
[Remaining 29 pieces are all
on Kwang Soo's shoulders.]
These guys stacked up all these pieces.
You have to allow for us to move these.
Come on, just let Suk Jin win for once!
- Please, just let him win.
- I don't know how to reply to that.
If we can't do this,
then we have no chance of winning.
[A very pitiful man indeed...]
Okay, your turn is now over.
[Fails to catch 100 pieces-
21 pieces still left to go.]
- What is this?
- He needs to drop them all at once!
[It's like he's watering a plant garden.]
Isn't he supposed to spread it out
all at once?
Come on, just let Suk Jin win.
- You can't play the game like this!
- Just let Suk Jin win.
[Even with all this scheming,
they've yet to win a game today.]
- Let him get another winning star.
- Do you think we can win this?
Even though we're all fighting,
it's still nice to be with others.
- Yes, it's very nice.
- No reason not to be happy.
[Hee Chul is out as soon as he starts.]
[How can this be?]
We have to win today!
[Hot pants lover is tagged in next.]
- What is his deal?
- Hey, take your time.
- Hurry up!
- There's no reason to rush it.
There's no need to hurry.
Why are you in such a rush?
His stance right now is really
fitting with his hot pants right now.
You're really good at gong-gi.
- I thought you were So Yeon for a second.
- You look so delicate right now.
[So Yeon's older sister?]
Soo Hong, you should've been
born a woman.
Take your time.
Look at his mouth.
He keeps opening his mouth too.
[Just then...]
[But Soo Hong alone takes care of 24 pieces.]
[So Yeon is up next.]
Is Soo Hong going again?
We're okay on time, so take it slow.
[Ace So Yeon is good
with even gong-gi playing.]
If you succeed,
then you win automatically.
[A total of 36 pieces
including So Yeon's turn.]
[Now only three players left to go.]
[Just need to get over 79 pieces,
and they win regardless of the time.]
I think we'll be able to win this.
[Has lost every game so far-
But isn't letting that stop him.]
One win every two years,
so that's two wins in every four years.
[That's sad...]
Yeah, that's like the World Cup.
[Along the same time frame as
the World cup and the Olympics.]
I know I shouldn't say this, but you shouldn't
have called us if you wanted to win.
I wish we could start over
from the farm field.
- I want to start over from the farm field.
- No, he should've called other people.
I have to move over a little.
[He passes the danger...
but crumbles from the other hand.]
[38 pieces left out of a total of 100 pieces-
Jae Dong is tagged in for the win.]
- Okay, we'll let you keep that one.
- He caught it with his left hand.
- My glasses are broken, that's why.
- Don't use that as an excuse.
If you keep saying things like that,
then we have plenty of excuses of our own.
[Gets distracted by all the talking
and ends up dropping the piece.]
I want to forgo my turn.
I hate being pressured like this.
[Final player, Hee Suk,
doesn't like feeling pressured.]
- We're going to lose again.
- Those are really sexy socks.
Are those your wife's socks?
- Take your time.
- I feel like I'm going to start laughing.
He says his younger daughter watches
our show three times a day.
[Hee Suk's daughter is
a fervent fan of Running Man.]
She really wants to come on as a guest.
[His never wavering sense of humor.]
[Team RM's record is 79.
Team SJ is hot on their trail!]
I really don't like being pressured like this.
Okay, good!
Don't drop it.
- This is a very important role you have.
- Just don't drop it. Move it over.
Wait, aren't you older than him?
No, move it over to the other hand.
It's weird hearing him talk to him like that.
Grab the smaller piece in front of you.
[Currently at 77.
Three more pieces to win the game.]
[Now down to two.]
[Two pieces all at once?
If caught successfully, then Team SJ wins!]
[Team SJ wins the game with 80 pieces.]
Team SJ wins this round of games!
[Team SJ wins this round of games!]
You did really good.
[Next Loyalty Game 100:
Endure 100 seconds of Arm Wrestling]
Endure 100 seconds of Arm Wrestling.
100 seconds?
Six members will go up against one member
of the other team in an arm-wrestling relay.
As a team, you must collectively
endure 100 seconds.
We've won.
I think if they put Jong Kook...
If they put Jong Kook last...
- Put Jong Kook last, Jae Suk.
- My shoulder's not great.
- Put Jong Kook last.
- He's really not feeling well.
- Why are you putting him up to it then!
Why are you putting him up to it!
Does he have a chronic disease?
He has a chronic disease?
He has a constant cold!
[Just take out Jong Kook.]
- Bring out Kwang Soo!
Do you have to do it like that?
Don't you want to see me win once?
I'll whisper it to you.
Jong Kook is going to do it.
- Jong Kook is going to do it.
- Relay it to the others.
- Get ready.
- Hee Suk is pretty strong.
Nam Hee Suk is actually quite strong.
Get ready!
[First Round, Team SJ's
Mr. Capable Hee Suk]
[Won't Lose Easily]
- Start!
[Match Start!]
[Everyone's nervous]
- He's strong.
- He's really strong
[Ringing right away]
Next, next.
- Start!
- Hey, you punk!
- Hey, punk! Punk!
- Just push down!
[As expected, ends right away]
All right, we'll start right away.
Start.
[One second...]
Next, next.
He's really strong.
Four seconds have passed
since the start of the match.
[Three people in four seconds]
- Is this a game?
- This is unfair!
You said you would
make sure I would win!
- You said that I would!
[I waited two years for today...]
You told me that I'd win!
Let's finish this quickly. Start!
Ow, ow.
- Why did you do that?
- Why me? Why me?
[We haven't heard castanets
for a while now...]
I thought you were playing castanets!
You see those happen in animations!
Even if you win a game, you shouldn't
stomp over someone's character!
- Let's hurry up.
- Let's hurry.
I told you about him, right?
The 'deungshin' (fool) who boasts
about exercise.
He's really great at back exercises.
[Back muscles god]
A back muscles god!
'Deungshin'!
'Deungshin.' 'Deungshin.'
Back muscles are good. They are.
You'll be surprised if you saw them.
Beat him, beat him.
I don't know! I don't know!
- I loosened up.
- Think about your image. So Yeon's watching.
I don't know. I don't know.
If you lift this up,
then all of this is tanned.
But you can see the t-shirt line here.
[A bold t-shirt tanning line]
Get ready.
- Think of changing your image.
- You've got muscles, too. Look at your arm.
Start...
[Our team's humiliation,
I'll repay the favor in kind]
Start.
[It won't work]
Don't overdo it.
[A sorrowful ringing siren.]
[Totally Embarrassed]
What are you doing?
Stomping all over his image.
You're really amazing.
I keep getting hit here,
but it hurts here.
but it hurts here instead.
If you were going to do this,
then you shouldn't have invited us.
If I were home alone, I'd be known
as 'a healthy person.'
I came out here and look at me.
It's a total of 6.36 seconds.
So Yeon, it hurts there, right?
It'll hurt if you put it there, right?
[So Yeon has to endure 94 seconds!]
Just finish it quickly.
What meaning does this have?
Finish it quickly and it'll make
So Yeon comfortable, too.
- Kim Jong Kook on three. One, two, three!
- Ah, Kim Jong Kook!
[Ack! What's the meaning of that lament?]
He feels even worse!
You were so worried when
I was up against Kim Jae Dong?
It's already over.
Get ready.
- Let's go.
- You can use two hands.
Wow, Jong Kook's hand is bigger
than both of hers.
- Start.
- I'm so scared! What do I do?
Sit, sit!
[So Yeon grabbing on with both hands]
Good job!
He's your family's enemy!
What's wrong with you?
Grab him!
[No way, already 20 seconds?]
Don't be like that.
Hurry up!
[The entire house is in an uproar]
Are you going to date her?
What are you doing?
- Lee So Yeon!
- End it already!
My arm won't work!
[End of Game]
- But really...
Even though they're my team,
they're still a sight from the back.
The four guys in the back
are chanting, 'Lee So Yeon!'
These people...
Ji Hyo and Ha Ha were angry before!
- Seriously what were you doing?
- 'Are you going to date her'?
How could you talk to
your sister-in-law like that!
Who is?
Lee So Yeon endured for 36 seconds,
and for a total of 42 seconds.
Will I be able to win like this?
We're going to lose anyhow,
so how would you guys like to win?
Give us some ideas.
How do you want to win?
- Seriously..
- We'll lose for you...
We'll just lose the way you want us to!
It's gold everyone!
[Two Gold bars from winning
the Playground Loyalty Game]
Take one for yourself.
[Team SJ gets one gold bar]
I hope you can send the message
that we aren't unhealthy people.
I'll beg of you.
[Will they be able to win?]
[Team SJ: 11 Gold Bars,
Team RM: 8 Gold Bars]
[N Theme Park in Goyang]
[Team SJ and Team RM arrive
at their third location.]
What's this?
[Above the field, there are
these cute animal masks.]
Please wear the animal mask
of your choice.
I'll be the impala.
[So Yeon is a cute chick]
[A cat]
My little brother Grasshopper!
It's been a long time!
[Yoo Hyuk Grasshopper
finding his usual self.]
[Cute Rabbit]
Doesn't Gary look like a real monkey?
- Why did you pick that?
- Because I'm a giraffe...
Why did you pick a tiger then?
Try putting on a grasshopper.
You'd pull it off.
- You already wore a mask.
- I did.
[A mask that falls short]
- Really.
- Seriously.
I bought a house with this.
This is the last game, everyone.
We said that Team SJ would get
twice the gold if they win, right?
- That would make it six.
- I don't understand it at all.
[Winning team wins three gold bars,
losing team wins two gold bars.]
- I'm going to win
-You have to win.
Our last mission is Target Dodgeball,
'You're Alive, Impala.'
Thank you for that.
We're going to be playing animal dodgeball
because of your love for animals.
But we're going to have a king
in each team to protect.
While you protect the king on your team
you must oust the other team's king
in order to win.
The last person protecting the king
cannot be eliminated.
Since that person is necessary
to protect the king.
- Are you out if it hits your mask?
- Yes.
Guess we can't choose the giraffe
because it's too long.
I'd be out if it hits here?
You can assign the opposing team's king.
- Giraffe!
- We choose the giraffe!
[Giraffe is chosen as king]
We choose Soo Hong!
- Me?
- No, we choose...
Hey, let me be king once!
All right, we choose Soo Hong.
Let me do it once!
If I came out here, you should
at least protect me once!
Soo Hong, just to be clear,
it wasn't about your shorts.
[An animal king wearing
short shorts.]
Who's going to go after the ball?
If the tiger pounces,
then go and grab him.
Hey guys, let's go after the tiger!
Do you think we can win today?
You guys can't run.
You, you, you.
Block Soo Hong.
I just have to be the last one alive.
Start!
[Hee Suk versus Jong Kook]
- Hey!
[No!]
[This is a chance!]
Ah...
[Tiger who evaded the attack
with his instincts.]
[Hee Suk, who missed the chance.]
[Fiery hot at the start.]
[It's game over as soon
as the ball hits the king.]
Come back some more.
[Hee Chul Mouse is out!]
That long, that long neck over there!
[Definitely looks like a giraffe]
That won't work.
[Jae Dong...]
I can definitely see the giraffe.
You can't take that?
[A heading from the animal king.]
[An easy Round 1 win.]
How could you do that!
- What was that?
- You should have blocked it!
What have you done?
What?
[The animal king was killed
in one minute.]
What were you doing?
[A steal thanks to the giraffe?]
A nomination. Nomination.
It's too impossible with him.
- We'll nominate again.
- Calm down please.
- Nomination: Giraffe!
- Giraffe!
[Unanimous Vote: Giraffe]
Soo Hong. Soo Hong.
- Okay!
- We'll just eliminate him.
Let's do a cheer.
What a pity for Jong Kook.
You're going to make sure
I win, right?
- One, two, three!
- One team!
What do we do about him?
He's so useless.
Try shaking your head.
You have to shake it a lot like this.
[Giraffe Smartphone Antenna]
- He's like an antenna!
I told you to hold your mask on like this.
- That's important.
- What's important is winning.
- Let's win!
- Go the reversal.
You just stay there.
[Second Round, protect the king.
Soo Hong versus Kwang Soo]
[Again, it's Hee Suk versus Jong Kook.]
[This time, the Tiger wins.]
[Hee Chul Mouse is ousted first again!]
- Sit down next to Jong Kook.
- He's out.
- I'll sit down like this.
- Good.
Should we surround Jong Kook like this?
Let's surround him like this.
And block it.
Hey, he sat down this time.
He sat down.
Hee Chul, you're the most important!
- Go and try.
- Stand still.
[Hee Suk and Hee Chul
are already eliminated.]
- What do I do?
- We have to protect you.
Wait.
- An out.
- [Cat Ha Ha is ousted.]
- Me too!
- [Rabbit Ji Hyo is ousted too.]
You're not going to protect him?
What is this?
- I see him!
I see him.
[Jae Suk Grasshopper is out!]
- Jae Suk...
- I see him!
I see his head!
His head!
Save me! Save me!
[Gary Monkey is out!]
[A tiger protecting the king
cannot be ousted.]
You're going to block this one, right?
Jong Kook hasn't been eliminated yet.
He's getting hit.
Good good.
[Must hide!]
Pass it around!
[The impala caught it with his face.]
Seriously!
[The impala is energetic to win.]
I'm holding back!
I see Kwang Soo's head.
Stop any attacks from above.
His head, his head, his head!
[Attack Missed!]
Good, good!
- Isn't that So Yeon?
- [So Yeon chick out!]
I didn't know that you'd get hit!
Okay, pass it.
[The ball went beneath their legs]
[Soo Hong is in grave danger!]
All right.
What the? How annoying!
Seriously. You fox!
Our king should run like this!
You keep doing this!
Do I have to?
[The giraffe is stuck to
the tiger's back like glue.]
He's hesitating!
Center it!
How could the tiger be left
out of everyone?
You have to pass it! Pass!
You have to keep passing it around.
Hey Gary. Good.
[Soo Hong avoided it like a fox!]
Pass it, pass it!
[Gae Monkey Showtime]
This really makes you look like a fool
because you can't aim with your head.
You have to catch it.
Giraffe!
[Within range]
[Moment of change]
[Target hit]
- Hooray!
- Wow!
[Team SJ wins Target Dodgeball.]
[Kwang Soo, why did you do that?]
Why would you go there?
Did we win? Did we?
- Why did you do that?
- Why did you go over there?
I'm sorry.
Why did you move?
We can win today!
This is a game we would
have definitely won!
- Take your gold.
[Team SJ gets six gold bars]
Gary should have caught it.
This is the start of our win.
I think we're going to win.
Please count how much gold you have.
I think we'll be about the same or lose.
[The team who has the most gold wins.]
- What will be the last game?
- I'll announce the results.
Team RM has 13 gold bars,
and Team SJ has 14 gold bars.
The final winning team is Team SJ.
We won? Really?
- This isn't it.
- Really?
The last game...
Only the winning team, Team SJ,
can participate in the final mission.
- We can't participate?
- No, you can't.
We only lost once!
- It's because of Kwang Soo!
- Really?
It's the end for us?
I only stayed like this
for the entire game!
[The true winners are the ones
laughing in the end.]
We just lost once.
Big Nose! Big Nose!
- What happens now?
- This is what happens.
How could you do that? Giraffe?
Hurry and take them away!
[Guards to take them to the final mission.]
- What is this?
- What's going on?
We have to go somewhere?
[The guards are taking Team SJ somewhere.]
- My hat.
- I didn't bring my bag.
Where are we going?
- There's a reversal to this.
[What on earth is this?]
Why does it feel like this
even though we won?
- This isn't supposed to happen!
- We won!
Where are we going?
You won't say.
Where are you all going?
Where you taking them?
- Hey!
- Why are you following him?
Hey this is some kind of prison!
- What, what is this?
[You'll find out once you're there]
What are you doing? What?
I have to win today, though.
I don't know what's going on.
What is this?
There's a phone here too.
[There's a pen here,
so maybe writing something?]
What is this?
[Team SJ have all been separated
into different rooms.]
Your final mission is
a friendship telepathy test.
- A friendship telepathy test.
[Telepathy?]
Starting now, you'll choose either
gold or money and write it down.
If your telepathy works and everyone
choose either gold or money
we'll give you an enormous prize.
If your telepathy doesn't work
and one person writes a different answer
You'll lose all of the gold
you've acquired.
Even one person's answer
can't be different?
- Wow.
[The friends who spent a lot
of time together.]
So it's six people who feel the same.
Probability-wise, this is impossible.
How could six people say the same thing?
Then I have to think about
the other people right now.
This is awful.
Wow, Running Man is awesome.
It'd be great if we could
all be the same.
I made my decision.
[Gold? Money?]
Soo Hong would need cash
to hit the clubs...
He can't go to the clubs
with gold. Isn't that right?
My nickname is
'Shaman Nam Hee Suk.'
Try searching 'Shaman Nam Hee Suk'
on the internet.
I'm positive.
Two people will have a different answer.
We're six people, but four will have
the same answer, and two will be different.
I'll send a wave.
I'll change it.
[An order through his nostrils.]
[A charged telepathy.]
Let's do this.
- Let's do this!
[Everyone, do you hear my voice?]
[Big Nose's friends who
have to think of each other.]
[Those who don't need a stare-off.]
This is Kim Hee Chul.
[You know my heart... right?]
- So Yeon, are you ready?
- Yes, I'm ready.
We're Big Nose's friends!
[Has only won twice in 206 episodes.]
[We have to change that sorrow!]
[Our only goal is to make sure
Big Nose wins.]
Let's make sure Suk Jin wins!
Big Nose! Big Nose! Fighting!
[If that sorrow disappears,
there's a huge prize at stake.]
[Telepathy over]
[Will they all have gotten
through to one another?]
[Ta-da]
[The final mission stage
to test their telepathy.]
What is this? Wow.
We really only lost once
and this is what happens?
- It's too much.
- Isn't that all in vain?
- JSJ was too much today.
- I think they're going to drop.
- I think this is good for us.
- Do they drop if they're wrong?
As you know, Team SJ has won
in a reversal today.
They only won once.
There is a chance for you
to take home the gold.
- What is this?
- Just wait and see.
You see the final mission is
a friendship telepathy test.
Everyone is in separate rooms
and they were given a choice.
Is it gold or money?
- Wow.
- Gold or money?
- We want to try it, too.
- Let's try it.
- Gary stand over there.
- Gold stands, and money sits.
One, two, three!
- Huh?
- Of course it's money!
- What are you going to do with money?
[Zero Telepathy]
You can't even exchange it.
If we're this bad, then that team
has no chance.
He's coming. Suk Jin's coming.
- Don't I look like a swimmer?
- Please go up!
Ah, this is a drop. How scary.
His shorts really are too short.
- Why are his clothes so short?
- Huh? Can't hear you.
[Team SJ has written down
either gold or money]
- What is this?
- You can't hear anything, right?
This is what the winning team does?
Jae Dong's coming. He's coming.
He's coming.
[What did Jae Dong choose
between gold and money?]
Come over here, Jae Dong.
[He's still energetic.
Will he be in a bit...]
Is this what it feels like
to see a celebrity on stage?
He looks really young.
[All of Team SJ is now on stage.]
- Take your headphones off!
- Take them off.
Take them off.
I'm sure everyone wrote down
the same thing.
It's a miracle if we get this.
A miracle.
Today's winning team is Team SJ.
Congratulations.
Thanks, you guys!
Why do we have to be uneasy
and stand up here?
Team SJ, who has received
14 gold bars.
You must all have written the same answer
to acquire this prize.
That doesn't make any sense!
Do the majority!
If your telepathy works,
we'll give you double your winnings
for a total of 28 gold bars.
- 28 gold bars?
- Really? Really?
- That's awesome.
- We'll really give that to you.
I really need it.
Getting gold teeth for my wife
is very expensive...
[A chance to melt gold bars
into gold teeth.]
However, if even one of you writes
a different answer and fails...
you'll fall into the pit, and we'll take
back the 14 gold bars
and give them to Team RM.
- Hooray!
- What's the meaning of that?
You can't do that!
We'll test everyone's telepathy results
one by one.
- What is this?
- That isn't fair!
It's double the gold though!
- This isn't easy.
- I feel like I'm being punished.
You planned for this!
But I'm trusting you guys!
Let's go!
- We'll proceed.
- This won't work.
Starting with Suk Jin, please open
what you've written on your chest.
But none of you can see.
You cannot see. Even with one answer
the platform will drop.
Really?
We're of one heart!
One heart!
[They'll stay in these seats
if their telepathy works.]
We'll take a look one at a time
starting with Ji Suk Jin.
One, two, three!
[Gold or Money]
[Big Nose chose Gold]
- You can't see.
- Don't look.
[If the rest of Team SJ chooses gold
then they get double the gold.]
- Next.
- Then we can drop here, too?
- Wait!
- If Soo Hong wrote a different answer...
Then all of them will drop.
- This is my style.
- SBS, really.
One, two, three!
Suk Jin!
Suk Jin, it was this, right?
[Will Suk Jin's Gold telepathy
have worked?]
It was this, right?
[Gold]
[The Gold telepathy worked!]
[They didn't fall!]
It's okay! It's okay!
I can't do this!
I'll give up! I'll give up!
I'll give up! Seriously!
Nam Hee Suk remain standing.
Just take it, you guys.
You must remain standing.
Next!
- Jae Dong!
- One, two, three!
One, two, three!
[Save us...]
Three!
[Telepathy... worked!]
[Gold]
[They didn't fall!]
- It was right!
[Feels good]
[Three out of six people's
telepathy worked.]
- It was right!
- It's right!
Give me an okay sign.
Let's go, Hee Chul!
[Hee Chul's shoulders
are getting heavier.]
I'm the leading role
of today's victory, everyone!
Victory Icon, Kim Hee Chul!
[Will he really be the Victory Icon...]
[Will that faith block their ousting...]
Keep showing them.
- Let's go!
- One, two, three!
Victory!
[Telepathy worked?]
[Gold]
[They didn't fall!]
[We can do it!]
How awesome.
[Bending down for the third time.]
[Legs are shaking]
- What's going on?
- This is really hard.
[Has the Gold telepathy
really worked...]
[Is this impossible task really
possible for these friends?]
- Hee Suk!
- Two left!
- Hee Suk please!
- One, two...
I'm trusting you!
- I trust you, Hee Suk!
- Please!
[What answer will the trusting
Hee Suk have?]
[Gold or Money]
[You must work, telepathy!]
[We're dreaming of 28 gold bars!]
[This is right, right?]
[Telepathy...]
[Money]
[Drop]
[Skydiving from the stage]
I knew Hee Suk would write
down 'Money'!
[They watch the other team drop
and are happy to get gold.]
[They drop into a plastic ball pit]
Hey you idiot!
Hey, you idiot! Hey!
- Hey!
- You wrote down gold?
We ran around getting gold until now!
It was me? Me?
[They've won but this feeling
isn't great.]
- How could you have done that?
- That was you?
How frustrating.
[A gold smell all around outside.]
I knew that 'Gold' would come up.
- This is what you call a reversal.
- This is thrilling.
How thrilling!
It's amazing that they got that far.
Hey, one of those two were me.
I was part of my own prediction.
We spent all day hunting for gold!
Why would you write down 'Money'?
Do you have any loyalty?
- What did you write?
- 'Money.'
- Why did you?
- I thought that all of you would write that.
We really hate money!
For So Yeon, this isn't 'Money'
but 'Good.'
- It's good.
- She wrote it down wrong.
Good, I wrote it down wrong.
Running Man is really 'Good'.
With that, our team wins 14 gold bars.
That could have been ours!
Of course it's gold!
We may have gotten the gold,
but the victory...
- is Team SJ!
[A gold-less win]
Why did we win?
Why couldn't we have won?
[Dejected and in vain]
We won 14, but we have two
left over because we're six people.
Share this among your team.
I can take it, right?
[Gold over Friends]
- Suk Jin, you're the best.
- Take them.
In any case, we're adding one more
victory star for Suk Jin.
Congratulations Team SJ!
[Anyhow, thanks to Suk Jin's friends,
a third win!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Hallyu's goddess: Suzy]
Suzy!
It's been a long time
since I've ridden a bus.
Three years?
I'm your paparazzi.
You have to take pictures
of the other team.
I'm taking one now!
Then hold a Hallyu star fan meeting.
Suzy!
[2014 Hallyu Star: A Day for Suzy]