[Young blood- Get up on your feet!]
[2014 Running Man University Competition.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[In a few moments...]
[A gigantic scaled project will
take place on the Han River.]
[7 AM-
Coffee shop near Dong-kuk University.]
- Why isn't anyone else clapping?
- We don't clap when we start.
[Even clapping gets Kwang Soo in trouble.]
There could be people who may not be
in the best mood when we start filming.
- Some people may not be in a good mood.
- Why wouldn't they be in a good mood?
We need to make sure to put people in a good
mood as we start filming throughout the day.
How can I already be in trouble
when I haven't even said anything yet?
Let's all cheers together for a good day.
[This is what you call 'timing'.]
It's okay.
You're still learning.
Just eat some patbingsoo
and be quiet.
- Can I just eat then?
- Is this patbingsoo?
This really is a delicious cup of coffee.
[Cake and patbingsoo...
their morning brunch.]
[He's not even touching anything?]
I already had breakfast before I came.
I got up at 5AM this morning, so
what time did you get up for breakfast?
I got up at 4 AM.
- You got up that early?
- I always make sure to have my breakfast.
- That's a late night snack.
- I always eat my breakfast.
That's not breakfast.
That's more like a really late night snack.
Did you stay up all night
just to have breakfast?
[Is he that obsessed with breakfast?]
I've been hearing some shocking
news lately.
I know that you're trying to keep it a secret,
but we know you've been busy setting up.
[Are they sensing something?]
- We've been hearing some things.
- We were trying to keep everything a secret.
We'll start off by telling you what
your final mission is going to be.
[Revealing what
the final mission is going to be.]
You have to cross a river.
- Are you serious?
- So it's true!
[Today's final mission...]
[Crossing the Han River.]
You've already crossed the Han River by
building your own boat
so I'm sure you'll all be very good at it.
What do you mean, we're good at it?
Have you not seen our boat capsizing?
- We were stuck in the water for 40 minutes.
- I've never experienced anything like that.
[Their Han River incident is still fresh
in their minds as if it happened yesterday.]
[Their freezing cold Han River experience.]
- Do you know how cold the river is right now?
- We did a great job with that.
[This time, they won't be
crossing in a paper boat.]
[The boat must be made with various
different materials.]
How about giving us a huge basin?
- What about cotton candy?
- Probably cotton candy and bread.
Is there a huge basin?
Seriously?
- What did you say?
- A basin. A huge basin.
- What did he say? A prawn?
- We have to cross with a prawn?
[How are you going to cross the river
on a prawn?]
- We have to ride on a prawn?
- Tie up a thousand prawns together.
And this time, you'll be building the boats
together with some special guests.
- Who are our guests?
- Please come on in.
What's it going to be?
[Several pictures are brought in on a table.]
[The country's biggest female stars!]
- You all must pick a picture that you like.
- Seriously?
- Each of you must pick a picture.
- Does it matter which one we pick?
- Each of you must choose a picture.
- You go first, Kwang Soo.
- Should I go first?
- Yeah.
- I want Lee Hyung Yi.
- I want Yang Hee Eun.
- No, I want Yang Hee Eun.
I have a good feeling about Yang Hee Eun.
I'm going with Yang Hee Eun.
[I'm going to go with the one
that the others wants.]
- He really is gullible.
- You can't change your mind now.
Okay, you go next.
I don't know who to pick.
[It's now Gary's turn.]
I need to choose the person who has the
biggest chance of actually being on the show.
[What kind of a mission is this going to be?]
- Go with Yeon Hee.
- That's who Jong Kook wants.
You can't worry about that.
You get to pick first.
[Finders keepers.]
- Go with Yeon Hee.
- I'm going to pick Goo Ha Ra.
[After careful consideration,
Gary chooses Goo Ha Ra.]
I don't know anyone else
with that name.
Wow, Yeon Hee is like a sister to me.
Ji Hyun...
I didn't make it to her wedding.
That's because you weren't even invited!
[Have you even met her before?]
You need to wake up from your
daydreaming.
- Then Jong Kook can have Yeon Hee.
- I want Kim Yeon Ah.
- What?
I once played a character by that name
in a drama a long time ago
- and I feel like I'm meant to pick her.
- Really?
Then I'll pick Kim Yeon Ah.
[Always chooses the one
that someone else wants.]
[Four pictures to choose from.]
- Ah! You should pick Hyuna.
- You should pick Hyuna.
I'll go with Hyuna.
[Ji Hyo chooses Hyuna of 4Minute.]
If this is what I think it is,
then I think Lee Hyun Yi is right for me.
- Then I think...
- I think I want Han Ga In.
[Who says?]
Then you get Han Ga In,
and I get Jeon Ji Hyun.
[Han Ga In for Suk Jin,
and Jeon Ji Hyun for Ha Ha.]
[Everyone completes their selection
of their top stars.]
Everyone's finished making their selections.
[What is their picture mission?]
As mentioned before, you have to make a boat
with various different materials.
Starting with Kwang Soo, please take
the sticker off the back of the picture.
Seo-Gang University?
- That's a university.
- Seriously?
[The alma mater of the star in the picture!]
[Korea University]
[Chung-Ang University]
Not that, but the back of the picture.
[Are you trying to take the picture?]
[On the back of Han Ga In's picture...]
[Kyung Hee University]
Dong-kuk University!
That's right out front!
[Dong-kuk University]
[Kun-Kuk  University]
Yes!
Seong-Shin Women's University!
[Seong-Shin Women's University]
I didn't know that's where Ha Ra went.
[Everyone's envious of Gary's selection.]
Is mine the only all women's university?
The only place I get any warm reception
is at an all-women's university.
You must now go to the university that
you have each chosen
and choose a male and a female student
whom you'll complete your mission with.
You must choose two teammates
and bring them back with you.
Man and a woman?
In Song Ji Hyo's case,
she'll have to bring back two males.
Then as for me,
I'll have to bring back two females?
- Yes, Gary will have to bring back two women.
- Is there a boat making class?
- Try an architecture class.
- Ah, architecture class?
Then will these students have to cross
the river with us in the boat?
[Must cross the river with the students
that they choose as their teammates.]
Then I'll have to choose
students who'll listen to me well.
[Must you really worry about that?]
I think anyone you pick
will listen to you well.
The broadcast date
of this episode will be March 2nd.
Today's the start of a new semester.
That's why we're calling this episode,
'2014 Running Man New Semester Race.'
[New Semester Special-
2014 Running Man University Competition.]
[Most infamous universities of Korea.]
[Team up with smart, and passionate
students of local universities!]
[Build a boat out of
various different materials.]
[Three people per team.]
[The team that crosses the river
quickest will win the race.]
Ideas, skills, and teamwork.
You need all three elements to win the race.
Find your teammates that possess
all three of these attributes
and bring them back with you to join you
on this mission as your teammates.
Go.
Okay, let's go!
I need to get there quickly and
find the best teammates that I can find.
The most important thing is
their creativity.
Their passion and ambition is what I need.
If I could have my choice,
I'd want a male student like Kwang Soo.
And a female student who's like Ji Hyo.
As for the male...
I want someone who'll follow my lead well.
A guy who's good at following orders.
Someone who's quick on their feet.
As for the girl...
I would like for her to be...
Someone who can listen, and be cooperative.
A girl who's sweet and cute.
[We told them to find their teammates,
not describe their ideal type in a mate.]
I want to be able to get along with them
like I would with my family members.
Maybe we can meet up on the weekends
and build boats to ride on the Han River.
Yes!
[No further words are necessary...]
[Everyone is headed to their respective
universities with excited hearts.]
We're here.
[Jae Suk arrives at Korea University.]
I've been here so many times in the past.
[Current time- 8:40 AM.
Korea University Campus.]
I actually used to be a part
of the cheerleading squad here.
I was a part of the cheerleading squad.
I wonder if anyone I know is still here.
I don't know
what kind of a person I should pick.
[Must be careful when choosing
their teammates.]
[But the campus is very quiet this morning
with many the students still on break.]
Kyung Hee University!
I think I should go this way.
How can the campus be so empty?
You didn't tell them I was coming, did you?
[That wouldn't have made a difference...]
There aren't any students on campus.
I haven't seen anyone around.
I can't believe how empty the campus is.
I feel like I'm back in college.
[This campus is
also devoid of any students...]
It's still too early in the morning.
But I don't have much time.
- Hello.
- Hello!
[Discovers some students!]
- We did a Tug-of-war race here before.
- I participated in that.
- I was a part of the team.
- So many students were out cheering for us.
- But it's so empty here today.
- We love you!
- I have to find someone to help me out.
- Me!
- Pick me!
What major are you?
We have to build a boat today.
That's great.
We have to build a boat.
[A... boat?]
- I'm good at building boats.
- I can build it too.
[Anything is cool with them!
This is what youthful passion is like!]
I don't know which one of you to pick.
I personally like someone
with long straight hair.
[They all have long straight hair!]
I didn't know there would be so many of you
with long straight hair!
[Who would've ever dreamt that
a day like this would come to him?]
All women's university.
I hope I can find some students.
What if I don't find any students on campus?
[And the happiest person of the day.]
All beautiful women are sleepyheads.
[Gary enters the library.]
I'm feeling a bit bashful now
that I'm here.
Hello.
Are you studying right now?
[A beautiful student studying
in the library.]
Is this university full of
beautiful women like yourself?
I actually...
[Getting up the courage to
tell her about his mission...]
I have a mission that I need to complete
with the help of university students.
And I have to choose two students who can
do the mission with me all day today.
- By any chance...
- Sure, I'd love to.
No, I'm not saying that you can
be on my team.
I have to choose my teammates.
But in order to do so,
I have to test them on a few things.
- Can you help me out with that? Thank you.
- Sure.
You look very beautiful this morning.
Then can you wait for me right here?
I'm going to go find a few more people.
- Is that okay with you?
- Yes.
I wish I could pick all of you.
I don't know what to do.
Do I have to pick just two people?
[Wishing that he could build a large ship
and put all the girls on the ship...]
Why is your face suddenly so red?
[You know why...]
In this case... why don't
you all just come with me for now?
[Impossible to choose.
Taking everyone with him for now.]
I can't take all of them with me?
Or how about I just
stay out of the race today?
Do I really have to participate today?
I just want to stay here.
- Hello.
- We heard that you were here.
[Other students heard of him being here,
and they all came out to see him.]
Wait a minute,
I'm feeling really bashful.
[Mr. Gary feels as though he woke up from
a nap in the field of flowers.]
[At the same time...]
[Jae Suk still hasn't run into
a single student on his campus.]
[He discovers a male student
leaving the library!]
Excuse me!
Where are you going?
- Where are you headed right now?
- I was heading off to study.
Excuse me?
Wow, look at that calculator.
- What major are you?
- I'm studying Business Administration.
Really?
What year are you right now?
- I'm in my fourth year.
- You must be busy with your exams.
- Did you stay up all night last night?
- No, but I had some things going on.
- What kind of things?
- I got some bad news from my family.
- Bad news from your family?
- Yes, well...
- Is everything okay now?
- Yes, everything's fine now.
- What happened to your family?
- Our house got broken into last night.
[On my goodness...]
- I'm serious.
- So what happened?
- Everything turned out fine.
- Did you catch the thief?
No, we weren't able to catch him,
but we did report the robbery to the police.
I guess this won't do then.
How can I ask him to come build a boat
with me with his current situation?
No, it's okay.
I can come with you.
But your house was broken into last night.
- But your house was broken into.
- But it wasn't anything too serious.
That's a relief to hear.
It really is a relief to hear
that there wasn't too much damage.
It's good to do something uplifting
when something bad happens to you in life.
I can understand what you're saying,
but you can't think of this as being fun.
- This is going to be a warzone.
- You're going to build a boat?
- Yes, that's what I'm saying.
- A boat?
I think what happened to your house, and
your exhaustion is confusing you right now.
You must've not heard me right.
I'm not saying that you should come
on a boat ride with me on Han river.
- Build a boat?
- We have to build it. This is no joke.
I'm really good at building things.
- Really?
- I'm really athletic too.
- How are you athletic?
- I used to be a basketball player.
How long ago?
I know that I'm a bit short,
but I played all through middle school.
- I used to box too.
- Can you show me some boxing moves?
[Then how about showing us some
shadowboxing skills?]
Just a few moves.
[Huh?]
[Something is a bit...]
It's because you caught me off-guard.
- I caught you off-guard?
- Yes.
Seeing your boxing skills,
it doesn't look like you did that very long.
Not very long right?
How long did you box for?
- Two months.
- Two months?
Why are you doing this to me?
You're really overselling yourself right now.
[Just as he wanted, he found a male student
who seems to be similar to Kwang Soo.]
- Can I use one of these sheets?
- Yes, of course.
I know that this is pretty irrelevant,
but can you make me a paper boat?
- A paper boat?
- A paper boat.
- I'm not sure if I remember how.
- You don't remember how?
Show me some of your skills.
Since you study accounting and things,
you're probably good with figures.
- I'm killer with all that.
- I bet it's no joke.
Can you just show me what
you can do?
- Okay, I'll give it a try.
- Yes, we have to try to win this.
This is still a flat sheet of paper.
[His unidentifiable skills?]
The paper is still the same.
You haven't folded anything at all.
- You're supposed to make a paper boat.
- The calculations for it have to be exact.
- Yes, the calculations have to be exact.
- We have to be exact about it.
The designing phase is crucial.
[Starting to use technical terms.]
90% of the success rate
is in the designing phase.
Yes, you're right.
That's exactly what I mean.
- You're saying you can design it?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
- Of course.
Even though I've never
actually done it before.
- Do you have some free time today?
- Yes, I've got some free time.
If you and I become a team,
we need to recruit a female student too.
- I can go bring anyone you'd like.
- Do you have any friends you could bring?
- I do have a friend that I study with.
- Really?
What kind of a person is she?
Is she good at building things like this?
No, I don't think so.
But even if it's not her...
This isn't a situation where I'm here to
introduce you to other girls.
I think that you're...
What is your nickname?
- 'Mi Young' back in middle school.
- Why were you called 'Mi Young'?
It stood for, 'Crazy Young Taek'.
[Resembling Kwang Soo more and more...]
That's not the way
that I want you to resemble Kwang Soo.
Then can you come with me right now?
- Can you give me five minutes?
- Five minutes? Yes, that's fine.
[Needs five minutes to get his things
from the library.]
I have decided to take Young Taek with me
for my male teammate.
Have you explained to him exactly
what he'll be doing with you today?
But from what I see,
Young Taek here...
- I can even build a house if I need to.
- Exactly my point.
[He's 'Taek-Guyver'.]
- Don't worry about him.
- Water.
- Han river.
- Don't worry.
I recently learned how to windsurf too.
[Okay, you win...]
If I told him that I want him to go to
outer space right now, he totally would.
Young Taek would fly up to the sky,
or dive to the ground if I asked him to.
He would do anything he's asked of right now
because he needs to do something uplifting.
What Young Taek needs right now
is to do something uplifting.
- You could fall into the Han river.
- That's okay.
- Why would you tell him that?
- As long as I have a life jacket on.
- Of course, we'd be giving that to you.
- Then I'm fine.
- What about extra underwear?
- Men can go without it from time to time.
That's the right frame of mind.
That's the right way to think about it.
This is the type of guy Young Taek is.
He'll just go along with the flow.
He'll go without underwear if need be.
Okay, Young Taek, come with me.
- Go get your stuff, Young Taek.
- Okay.
- I'll wait for you out here.
Okay, I've found a male student.
The thing I'm worried about right now is
that Young Taek is trying to meet a girl.
That's what kind of worries me,
but other than that, I really like him.
[Will Young Taek be able to find
the girl of his dreams on the show today?]
I've finally arrived at Dong-Guk University.
I think the best place for me to go
is the library.
I see a lot of students here.
But I want someone fit and strong.
You okay?
[Just then...]
- Don't I look like Kim Jong Kook?
- Wow!
You do look like him!
He looks just like Kim Jong Kook!
[Kim Jong Kook of Team Dong-Guk!]
Kim Jong Kook!
You and that temper too!
Dong-Guk University's Kim Jong Kook.
- What's your major?
- Korean language.
Korean language major?
Do you have any free time today?
- I'm working right now.
- What kind of work?
I'm fixing computers.
[How disappointing...
He's working right now.]
Yes, you do have to work.
Study and work.
You're working so hard.
Right now...
who's that couple over there?
Look at that couple.
Wow!
Wow, look at that couple.
Are you a couple?
- Are you two a couple?
- Yes, we're a couple.
Wow, look at you two.
Sorry, but have a good day.
Goodbye.
- Sorry, it ripped.
- You really are short.
Wow, listen to him.
He's so sassy.
First... come here, let's sit down.
[What luck to be rolling in!
Sitting down together to talk.]
- I watch Running Man every week.
- How about a brief self-introduction first?
Introduce yourself.
My name is Kim Sun Eun,
and I'm a Business Administration Major.
- Classroom 13? Then how old are you?
- Yes, classroom 13.
- I'm 22 years old right now.
- 22 years old?
That's a good age.
Your turn to introduce yourself.
My name is Lee Ji Eun, and
I'm also a Business Administration Major.
- Then you guys are a 'CC' (Campus Couple)?
- Yes.
The most important thing is,
are you two free today?
- Just skip it.
- I think I can do that.
You could build memories together today.
[Memories of crossing the Han river
together as a couple?]
And he looks like he belongs on our team.
I need to do a simple physical test.
Okay?
- Do you see those elephant statues?
- Yes.
The one who comes back to the finish line
first after touching the nose wins.
- I'll be right back, okay?
- Okay. Fighting.
[Sweet as pie couple.]
Go!
[Running race- Go!]
[Wow... he's fast!]
[Sun Eun lost his shoe!]
[But he doesn't hesitate,
and just keeps on going!]
[Sun Eun wins with ease.]
[His ambition to win doesn't stop him
even as he loses his shoe.]
- I really like you.
- Okay.
I like the way you look too.
I really think that you guys may be
a part of my team.
Go to the cafeteria and grab some breakfast,
and I'll call you after I look around a bit.
I really hope that you guys
become members of my team.
We'll start from right here,
and whoever touch that first wins, okay?
[Another team, and another physical test.]
Ready.
A round of applause!
[Asking for a round of applause
out of the blue.]
A round of applause!
Ji Suk Jin!
[A fierce round of cheer from
excited group of high school students.]
Okay, we're going to run.
Ready, set, go.
[Sprint!]
I won!
[Beats the student by cheating.]
How could you have lost to me?
Ji Suk Jin!
- Where's Yoo Jae Suk?
- Yoo Jae Suk went to Korea University.
- Where's Gary?
- Gary's at another university.
Why?
Aren't you guys glad to see me?
- Aren't you glad to see me?
- Ji Suk Jin!
[Kind young girls trying to make
the elder feel better.]
- Have a nice day!
- Bye!
Ji Suk Jin!
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- Come on, there's no need for that.
Lee Kwang Soo!
[These students are working so hard...]
You know what this feels like?
You know those really popular senior guys
at a university campus?
Wait, this is really embarrassing.
[But this senior is even more popular.]
Ladies...
[If this isn't heaven...
then I don't know what is.]
I don't want to go anywhere!
I want to stay here forever!
I just want to live here!
[And is Kkuk shooting a school promo video?]
Ji Suk Jin!
- Senior...
- Can you all do something for me?
[Wants to act out a scenario of being
the most popular senior at school.]
- Take my pictures, and giving me love notes?
- Okay, we'll do that for you.
I've always really wanted to do that.
- Can you do that for me?
- Sure!
I've always wanted to do that
ever since I was in elementary school.
[Scene 1- Seo-Gang University's legend.
Everyone's out waiting for Lee Kwang Soo.]
[This student is acting in awe.]
Hang on, you guys.
[Gross!]
[That's going one step too far.]
[Scene 2- That 'senior' who disappears off
into the distance with girls behind him.]
Thank you everyone!
I've been wanting to do that for so long!
You guys are all really great.
You guys all have such warm hearts.
Jong-Ang University.
[Kkuk is busy taking in the scenic
atmosphere of the university campus.]
- Are you all students at this university?
- Yes!
[So many university students are gathered
even at this early hour.]
Are you on vacation from the army?
[Even a student out
on vacation from the army.]
Excuse me, you there with the hat on?
- Me?
- Yes. Are you a student here?
- Yes.
- What's your major?
- I'm a math major.
- Would you be interested in building a boat?
- A boat?
- Yes, a boat.
- This 'bae'? (Belly)
No, a boat that you ride on.
[No, not that 'bae'.]
[He without a doubt thinks it's working on abs
since it's Coach Kkuk asking the question.]
[Feels like death warmed over.]
Wow, you're pretty strong.
[Even testing out a fit looking
Portuguese student.]
[But he's flimsy when up against Mr. Capable.]
[Okay, physical test may not
work here...]
Okay, then let's go with smarts.
[At the same time, at Kun-Kuk University.]
[Blank Ji is testing out the physical strength
of Business Industry Major students.]
His legs are about to give out on him.
- She's really light.
- One.
[This student looks like he can do
about a hundred of this exercise.]
I really like doing this.
[And Yoo Jae Suk on the other hand...]
It's been quite a while since
Young Taek went in there.
[No sight of Young Taek,
who went in to get his backpack...]
I don't know about him.
I wonder if Young Taek...
There's Young Taek right now!
[Young Taek finally steps out.]
You said you only needed five minutes,
but you took longer than that.
It's okay.
What took you so long?
- I had a lot of books to gather up.
- You had a lot of things?
Okay, let's go.
By any chance, are any of them your friends?
- I know a lot of their faces.
- Really?
By any chance, do you know Young Taek?
Are you a friend of his?
- Young Taek!
- Can you tell me what Young Taek is like?
No, there's no need to be shy.
What kind of a guy is Young Taek?
- Is Young Taek pretty fit? Really?
- Yes.
- He says he boxes too.
- Yes, he's a good boxer.
[What? He's a good boxer?]
I saw his boxing skills.
- He's a good boxer? Seriously?
- Yes, he's good.
Thank you for taking
the time out to talk to me.
Young Taek is on my team,
and if my team wins first place
Young Taek will take you guys all out
to celebrate.
Yes, give Young Taek a round of applause.
[Off on his way with a crowd of his
fellow students cheering him on.]
He'll be back.
Don't worry about Young Taek.
He'll come back a winner.
I promise that Young Taek will come
back a winner. You all just wait and see.
Have a good day.
Thank you!
You saw that, right?
All those people back there now have
huge expectations of you.
You have to come back a winner.
- You have to come back as a winner.
- I vow to come in at first place.
- Wait, we still need a girl student.
- A girl student...
What do you think is the most important
quality we need to look for in a girl student?
Long black hair?
What are you talking about?
Come here.
What does her hair have to do
with anything?
[It seems as though Young Taek has a
different kind of mission in his mind.]
Seriously.
- Young Taek.
- Yes?
Okay... I'll accept that.
Long black hair?
Okay, long black hair.
- Okay, what else other than the hair?
- I think she should be about 163-164cm tall.
[Unbelievable...]
- Why?
- If she's to fit my height...
Why does she have to fit
your height?
- Why does her height have to fit yours?
- Our team...
- Because we're a team?
- Yes.
- What else?
- Other than that...
- You're okay with everything else?
- Yes, I'm okay.
Don't you think that it would be good to find
someone who's a bit brash and forward?
- Yes, I agree with that.
- Right? Someone a bit competitive?
- Yes.
- Somewhat, right?
- Have you ever rowed oars before?
- Yes, I have.
I know how to windsurf.
He says he's done it before.
Young Taek has done it all.
[Young Taek has experience in every skill!]
- This past summer... you know those canoes?
- Yes, canoes.
I rowed a banana boat across Han river.
[Rowed a banana boat?]
Don't ask him so many questions.
Don't try to examine him like that.
Didn't you just hear him say that he rowed
a banana boat across the river?
It's okay, Young Taek.
Let's just go. I have faith in you.
[Discovers two female students
waving at them enthusiastically.]
- Are you students at this school?
- No.
Then did you just come here for a visit?
- We're from Kyung Hee University.
- That's where Ji Suk Jin is.
We just saw him.
He told us that you were here,
so we took a bus over here to see you.
- Where's Yoo Jae Suk?
- Yoo Jae Suk's at Korea University.
[It's these two students!]
[They raced over here to see Jae Suk!]
- What's Ji Suk Jin doing?
- He keeps cheering himself on.
- That's what he's doing over there?
- Yes.
[That's what he's still doing...]
[At the same time, Ha Ha is...]
[He hears someone singing
inside the room!]
[He opens the door to see a female student
playing the piano as she sings along.]
[Could this be fate?]
[Haroro is mesmerized by her singing.]
I can't believe that just happened.
It was like something out of a drama.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm here from Running Man.
Yes, I'm here from Running Man.
What are you practicing right now?
- I'm practicing my singing.
- Singing practice?
- Are you a music major?
- Yes.
Can you play some more?
I loved hearing you sing.
['A Farewell For Me' by Kim Hye Rim.]
[Sun Min's clear and singing voice...]
May I join you in this song?
[What an awful duet...]
- Are you here for a class?
- No, I'm here to practice on my own.
[Park Sun Min, who came to school early in
the morning to get some lone practice time.]
Why don't you come with me over there?
Then do you have some free time today?
Are you free?
- Yes.
- You're just here to practice, right?
- I purely came in here by coincidence.
This really is something that would
only happen in a drama or a movie.
I can't even believe
that this is happening right now.
I feel that this is fate.
I don't even know who you are.
But I just loved the way you looked from
behind when I walked in this room.
There's a huge competition
that's about to take place.
If we win that race...
then we can show the whole country that
this truly is the best university around.
Do you have the confidence to go out there
and give it the best you've got today?
- Yes.
- Fighting!
[He recruits a musical girl.]
In that case, let's get you changed into
my team uniform and come along with me.
Who was that guy from earlier?
The guy from that couple from earlier?
[He completes his team by recruiting
ambitious Sun Eun from earlier.]
Even though skills are important too...
the soul that screams passion
from your heart...
that's what I'm going to be looking for.
- Do you want me to pose in any specific way?
- How about a sexy pose?
[I wish that I could stop time.]
You've got ten minutes.
[Ten minutes-
Must draw a portrait of Gary.]
Think of yourself as being in France.
Think of me as some French model.
[The very first student that he met
this morning to show her work first.]
The peaceful expression on your face,
the thick, masculine eyebrows
and the high prominent nose...
Thank you.
I drew you as you are while part
of the Monday Couple.
[Next student drew Kang Gary in his
Monday Couple phase.]
- I drew a very calm picture of you.
- That's a picture of a monkey.
[ET Gary?]
I wrote the phrase, 'I want Kang Gary',
and I drew a small figure of Ji Hyo too.
- I drew you as a flower boy.
- Are we a Tuesday Couple now?
- You drew me like a nice cartoon character.
- Your eyes are shooting hearts.
How about reciting a poem with my name?
'Kang'.
- Kang Gary.
- Yes?
- Sorry. 'Gae'
- I can't help but to keep looking at you.
Is that how my name is spelled?
Well, 'Ga' and 'Gae' is pretty much
the same.
- I can't help but to keep looking at you.
- Me too.
- 'Ri'.
- Come here.
Come where?
[A very unique way of reciting
the poem.]
- 'Kang'.
- In Kang-nam...
- 'Gae'
- If I was to see Gary...
These ladies are really
making my heart flutter.
- 'Ri'.
- I'm going to tie him up and take him home.
You were all so good, and
I feel like I've gotten close to all of you.
It's so hard to pick just one of you.
But the student who wanted to
tie me up in a ribbon...
[Makeup artist major, Lee Ye Na is chosen!]
Can you put your phone on vibrate?
This is a very important moment right now.
[Jae Suk and Young Taek are busy trying to
recruit a female student of their own.]
His name is Young Taek.
- He's a business major.
- I see. Hello.
Did you hear her say, 'I see'?
It means she's not interested in you.
I'm really sorry to be asking this...
but do you have any free time?
Not all day, but until about 6 PM?
- Until 6 PM? I have a meeting later.
- What kind of a meeting?
I have to go and help some students
who are in need.
Then that's not going to work.
You have to go help take care of them.
- In that case... maybe next time?
- See you next time?
Okay, I'll see you next time.
You're really cool.
That's too bad that you two have
other things going on and have to get going.
By any chance...
Can you think about it some more?
Maybe we can ask you about it again later?
- Yes, thank you.
- Bye.
That's too bad.
She doesn't have the time.
- How do you feel about that, Young Taek?
- How do you feel?
I think that they both...
will be very good at building boats.
[Young Taek is hiding his true feelings behind
the veil of their potential building skills?]
Well...
listening to the way she was speaking...
I saw you.
I saw the way you were looking at them.
[The way Young Taek was looking at them
was totally caught by Jae Suk.]
- But they don't have the time for it.
- And being a psychology major...
- What about being a psychology major?
- I think they'd be really good at it.
You think they'd be good workers
because they're psychology majors?
[It's almost time for them to head out...]
I think the girl in the white pants
looks pretty competitive.
What are you doing?
- I think that she'd be very good at it.
- He keeps pointing out his ideal type to me.
[He's outright telling Jae Suk
about his ideal type now.]
[Just then, a female student
boldly raises her hand.]
You're a student here?
What is your major?
- Psychology major.
- Psychology major?
[She's also a psychology major.]
Are you a friend of hers?
Are you good at building things?
- I'm actually pretty strong.
- Really?
- You're strong?
- Yes.
- You want me to grip it harder?
- Wow.
- You're strong.
- I like how bold and forward she is.
[Now that we think about it, it seems
Young Taek likes psychology majors.]
- Young Taek.
- Yes?
What kind of sports are you good at?
- I know how to do shooting, but others...
- You know how to shoot?
[Young Taek and this student alike...
They're not very meek students...]
- Do you have some free time today?
- Yes, I can take the day off.
- You can take the day off? Seriously?
- Yes.
She's very forward.
She's really... she's really forward.
[Young Taek and Bo Yoon make up
Team Korea.]
Bo Yoon, come right back, okay?
Then Young Taek and I will go as a team and
we promise to return as victors of the race.
Thank you.
Yoo Jae Suk!
Thank you for all your cheer
and encouragement!
[Team Korea is now off to the competition!]
Cham, cham, cham!
[Gary completes picking out
teammates as well.]
[Kkuk is also in the phase of
picking out his final teammates.]
- 'Jong'.
- Kim Jong Kook is really...
- 'Kook'.
- The handsomest man in this country.
- Chung-Ang University!
- Fighting!
[All seven university teams are now complete!]
Let's go and show them
what your university is made of!
- Go!
- Okay, let's go.
[Park Sun Min- 25. Theater major.
Kim Sun Eun- 22. Business Admin major.]
Is there anyone whom you've always wanted
to meet from the cast of Running Man?
You know you can imagine whom you'd
want to be teamed up with in a game?
Who would you pick?
- Ji Hyo.
- I'd pick Gary.
[He's asking the same question.]
I like Jae Suk.
- What about you, Yoo Kyung?
- I like Gary.
Do you both want to get out of the car?
- How do you expect to win like this?
- Lee Kwang Soo!
- I'm sure we'll win somehow.
- Yes.
- Should we come up with a battle cry?
- A battle cry?
[That's our forward Young Taek.]
Why are you thinking
of a battle cry already?
- Are you a third year student, Bo Yoon?
- Yes.
- And Young Taek is a fourth year student?
- I have one semester left.
- You only have one semester left?
I'm so grateful that you're allowing me to
finish out my last year like this.
What are you talking about?
We have to win before you can say that.
[You have to cross the river
without sinking first...]
- I think I'll be happy no matter what.
- It's good to think so positively like that.
- You're prepared too, Bo Yoon?
- Yes.
[Start of 2014
Han River University Competition.]
What is this?
What the heck is this?
[Team Korea is the first team to arrive.]
I thought we were building a boat.
[Why are there balloons, hoola hoops,
and chips on this field?]
- These are my two students.
- Okay.
[Team Chung-Ang also arrives.]
- You're very bright.
- Yes, she's a very bright person.
She's much brighter than I expected.
I didn't think she'd make it here with me.
These two are my teammates.
They're both very positive people.
- You told them about how we fell in, right?
- Yes, I told them.
He called his mother and she told him that
she had a weird dream last night.
- She said she dreamed about water.
- And he's going to be on a boat today.
- Yes, her dream was right.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Look at her two male teammates.
- I have the perfect team for boat building.
[The best of the best teammates are
all arriving one by one.]
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
You brought two very adorable
people with you.
[Tiny]
- What is your major?
- I'm an economics major.
- And what about you?
- He just got accepted.
[Does this mean that he's still
a high school student?]
- No, he's 20 years old.
- He's about to start his first year?
- That means he's still a high school student.
- There wasn't anyone else to choose from.
- But he's still a high school student.
- No, I just graduated today.
You just graduated today?
[Crossing the Han river is his
graduation gift?]
Everyone's here now.
Why are you holding their hands?
- Why are you holding their hands?
- We're building our teamwork.
- We're trying to build teamwork.
I heard that he held an audition for them.
- You held an audition?
- It was my version of Kpop Star.
Kang Gary.
This is my teammate, Sang Bum.
- Sang Bum's nickname is, Kang Gary.
- Why?
- He says he gets compared to you a lot.
- Is that why you chose him?
[Is that why?]
- He wants to stand next to you and see.
- Song Ji Hyo's mine.
Song Ji Hyo's mine.
[You better stay on your toes
today, Gary.]
Do you know how I met her today?
I was about to give up when I heard
someone playing the piano in one of the rooms.
[Sound of the piano that he heard
playing in a room...]
She was playing the farewell song
all by herself early this morning.
- Why?
- She was singing while playing the piano.
I'm sure it's because she had
something happen to her.
- Look here!
- That's why she was playing that song.
You say something happened to her?
His house was broken into last night.
[A breakup is nothing compared to me...]
He still came on the show today even after
what happened to lift his spirits up.
[All of the strongest students are
together all in one place today!]
We were all so happy to meet each other.
- Okay, we now have everyone here.
- Ji Suk Jin's not here yet.
[Why are you disregarding Big-nosed Brother?]
- He's here.
There he is.
[Team Kyung Hee finally arrives as if
they knew others were talking about them.]
Let's all welcome them
with a round of applause.
Ji Suk Jin!
[A pity welcome party?]
The rumor's spread to even Korea University.
I heard you've been cheering yourself on?
- Seriously?
- That's right.
Can you all introduce yourselves?
Hello, my name is Hong Sung Yong,
and I'm a philosophy major.
- Nice to meet you.
- What a great personality.
She belongs to a group at school,
and they're called, 'The Employment Group'.
[We hope that you find a job soon!]
Hello, my name is Yoon Ye Ji, and
I recently graduated with a business degree.
[That completes all seven teams!]
Welcome to all the students who are here to
participate in Running University Challenge.
[Welcome]
- You all know what you're doing today?
- Yes.
Did you tell them
they could fall in the water?
- Yes, of course.
- Did they say that it was okay?
He said he wouldn't even care if
the bungee cord snapped on him.
Running Man members have experienced
crossing the Han river before.
Then you're all aware how important it is
to build a good boat
and how important the material you
build that boat with is, correct?
- Yes.
- You're not building your boat with paper.
- Then what are we building it with?
- We have seven other material here for you.
We will first play a round of games to
determine which material each team will win.
Do you all see the field behind you?
It's a three person relay game.
[Game to determine which boat building
material you win.]
First course- Pop the balloon with your butt
before you can move onto second course.
In the second course, all three of you must
go through the same hoola hoop as one.
For the third course, you have to eat
a ring of cookie together.
Then you all have to cross
the finish line together.
- Are you all ready?
- Yes.
[Everyone's lined up against the fence.]
- We'll just naturally win this, okay?
- Yes.
Wrap your arm around my waist.
Yes, there you go.
[Everyone's coming up with
plans of their own.]
- Ready.
- Let's do this.
[Teamwork is the most important
element in this game.]
[This one game will determine which material
will be given to them to build their boats.]
One, two...
[First course- Pop the balloon.]
What are you guys doing!
[Team Dong-kuk is the first to arrive.]
[Most people are breezing through
the first course with ease.]
[Quickly heads onto the second course-
Hoola hoop.]
[In last place...]
[Pops the balloon with her whole body!]
- You have to pop it with your butt.
- Your butt! Use your butt!
You did it!
Get up!
[It's tough being with Kwang Soo, isn't it?]
[Second course- Hoola hoops.]
[Team Dong-kuk and
Team Kyung Hee are in the lead.]
[Easily passes the hoola hoop from the top.]
[This team passes the hoop from the bottom.]
[Easily succeeds the second course.]
[Still in the last place...]
Right foot on two!
Just leave it!
[Non-stop screaming Giraffe.]
- Lift it up!
- We're ruined.
[Third course- Eat the cracker.]
[Come on, cracker... where are you going?]
[These crackers are placed up pretty high.]
[High level of concentration.]
[Big-nosed Brother succeeds in
eating his cracker!]
[First place- Team Kyung Hee.]
[Second place- Team Dong-kuk.]
[Breaking out in celebration of joy.]
[Aren't you going to eat your crackers?]
[Team Korea comes in at third place.]
[These three are in a league of their own...]
[Not easy for this team with
the cracker placed up so high.]
[Just then, these guys in the last place
comes in to participate in the last course.]
[That's our Giraffe.]
[Gets that cracker in his first attempt.]
[Succeeds in catching up to the others
and comes in at fifth place.]
[Gary is exhausted from having
lifted up one of the students.]
[Team Kun-Kuk succeeds the mission.]
What do we do?
We're in last place.
Hey!
What is this!
What's wrong with you girls!
[Enraged at coming in at last place.]
[Off to pick the materials first.]
[Off to the next location
in the order of their win.]
[This is the boat building grounds.]
Don't come in yet, and stand in a line.
[Plastic bottles, balls, and even blankets?]
Those blankets.
Gary, I think you're going to get those.
[Even from a brief glance,
they're predicting that Gary will get it?]
For the students that come in at first place,
they will win financial scholarships.
[Immediately feels their ambitions rising.]
We will start by having Suk Jin's team
choose their materials.
Choose your material
and go stand in front of it.
[Goes to stand in front of the water bottles
without any hesitation.]
We're going to go with the water basin.
[Second place-
Team Dong-kuk chooses the water basin.]
- We want the cans.
- Okay, go stand in front of the cans.
[Team Korea chooses the cans.]
- We're going with the balls.
- The balls.
[Team Chung-Ang chooses the balls.]
- Balloons!
[Team Seo-Gang chooses the balloons.]
[The only thing left are blankets
and plastic bags...]
- We want the blankets.
- Okay, blankets.
In that case, you have the plastic bags.
It's the plastic bags life.
Don't worry.
We can still make it float.
[Material selection process complete.]
[Time to build the boats!]
This is going to be right.
You have to go with your gut instinct.
We first build the boat,
and do you see those large bottles back there?
- We'll attach the big ones like this.
- On both sides?
I'm positive that this won't sink.
We have to come in at first place
because we have the best material.
We have to admit
that we have the best material.
- We can't sink with this material.
- We can't lose with this material.
If we lose with this...
no, that can't happen!
I really want to help you guys
win the scholarships, okay?
[Big-nose wants to get them
their scholarships.]
Maybe we should tie them up like this.
- What are you doing?
- I'm sorry.
- I didn't do that on purpose.
- Seriously.
She's so demur when she gets angry.
'Oh my goodness'.
[Serious about bottle boat building.]
There's nothing we can say if we lose
with this material.
We really can't say anything then.
[Meanwhile...]
I'm sorry.
Why did it pop?
[The balloons are popping left and right.]
[Pops... and pops again.]
- Putting tape on it is making it pop.
- Right?
[Not easy to tape the balloons together.]
They're all going to pop.
Please stop popping them!
Be more careful!
[Taking his anger out on Chun Yi.]
How do we stop it from popping?
What are we going to do?
We're ruined!
[Their hopes are popping
along with the balloons.]
We're ruined!
We're going to fall into the Han river!
- Let's just swim across.
- You want to swim across?
- Are those sandbags on the sides?
- No, it's air in the plastic bags.
- Is that the large plastic bags?
- Yes, and there's air inside of that too.
- All with plastic bags?
- With air inside.
- So the most important thing for us is...
- Getting air in the plastic bags.
[Getting air in the plastic bags
is the key to their success.]
Even though we chose a difficult road...
we overcame our obstacle.
- Are these not popping?
- I don't know, so don't touch them.
- Are these okay?
- I told you not to touch them!
[Giraffe is pressing all the air
out of the plastic bags.]
I told you not to do that!
- The air is leaking!
- That's none of your business!
Here's the way I think we should do this.
[This team is trying to decide
how to build their can boat.]
I think we should attach all the cans together
and wrap the whole thing in plastic bags.
We don't have the time to wrap
these up individually.
[Jae Suk's experienced Han river
crossing know-how.]
I don't know if it was because
the bottom portion was too tall or what.
But our boat just flipped over
while we were rowing the boat across.
So make the bottom portion small?
So that we don't flip over?
But having a bigger portion of the boat under
the water ensures that we won't flip over.
We have to have a good part of the boat
submerged in order to make it more stable.
- To make that submerged part deeper?
- Yes, that gives is more stability.
- There are some cans that are still full.
- Then we'll put those on the bottom.
Once the rest of the boat is built,
we can put a few of these on the bottom.
Having some weight on the bottom
ensures that the boat won't flip over.
Being able to go fast is important too,
but we have to be able to float above all.
[Speed is crucial, but being able to float
is first and foremost.]
- I think it'll be easier to build too.
- Doing it this way?
Yes, because it's more stable.
[Chatty Young Taek is practically building
the boat with his talking alone.]
- We can build it wide like this.
- Didn't you say you're good at calculations?
- Excuse me? Yes, I can do that.
- He's good at lip service calculations.
This material is so unexpected.
[Meanwhile, Team Kun-Kuk is struggling
with their blankets.]
You with your love for sleep is
what got you those blankets.
Jae Suk, I'm going to try sleeping
on the Han river.
Yeah, that sounds good.
[Are they building a boat, or a bed?]
- And lastly, this will go on top.
- Folded in half?
[Briefly shapes the boat...]
[And tape all the blankets together.]
[Will this boat be able to float on water?]
[These three have already become close enough
to start joking around with each other.]
[Meanwhile,
there's Team Chung-Ang with their balls.]
We picked a really tedious material.
- I'm just glad we didn't get the balloons.
- Me too.
[Even though the balls are a lot of work,
the balloons are even more work.]
No!
[These balls looks so sturdy
compared to the balloons.]
- I think these are going to float well.
- I feel like we're on a science program.
[But in actuality...
it's more of an athletic program?]
- Are you recycling right now?
- Can't you see what we're doing?
- Are you organizing your recyclables?
- This boat is going to whiz past yours.
Today must be recycling day.
- Keep that up, and I'll include you in it.
- What did you say?
Do you want me to tape you along to your cans
and recycle you along with them?
[Bit Na comes to get Kkuk
to stop the two from bickering any further.]
I have to get back to work.
[Takes Kkuk back to their work station
with one simple glare from her eyes.]
[Team Dong-kuk is busy building
their basin boat.]
- Let me give it a try.
- This is really hard work.
- It's okay.
- Be careful not to bust it.
This is too tough for a girl.
[She's good.]
She's much better than us.
[Musical girl's angry burst of saw action.]
[Even the hammer...
and the drill is no problem!]
[These boys are just her helpers.]
[Musical girl, Sun Min, all of a sudden
is the lead builder of this team.]
[They're picking up the speed
with Sun Min's lead.]
I feel so nervous.
I can't sink again.
[Building the boat with these basins
doesn't seem like easy work.]
If we sink,
there's nothing we can do about it.
[Cross the Han River...
Their second attempt.]
[Seven boats built with
seven different materials.]
[Just which of these boats will succeed?]
[And which one of these boats
will be the fastest?]
[Only ten minutes left on the clock.
There's still so much left to do.]
[Recruits another helper to
help them finish building their boat.]
[The balloon boat is starting to take shape.]
- Is it okay?
- Not bad.
Yeah, it's okay.
I think this is going to be okay.
[Attach all the balloons together lengthwise...
to make it the same length of the boat.]
If we fall in the water, let's get all
these balloons out and have a party.
[Chan Yi's graduation balloon party?]
She's really good.
[Blank Ji's speedy taping job leaves
the male students' jaws dropped in awe.]
How is she so good?
[Even the blanket boat is
getting close to completion.]
That looks good.
- Where are you from?
- I'm from Running Man Moving Center.
[A boat made out of blankets...
will it float on water?]
That blanket boat is pretty good.
[Team Korea's can boat is nearing
its completion as well.]
Three people can fit on this, right?
Let me try and see how we fit.
[In case they crush the cans,
he only imitates sitting down on it.]
I think it's going to work.
[Always positive thinking Young Taek.]
You're so positive.
Okay, we're good.
Let's wrap it up.
[Final wrapping job
is all they have left to do.]
[Wrap it... and wrap it some more.]
[Wrapping it up without leaving
any room for any water to leak in.]
[Even puts some cute
decorative finishing touches.]
[Smile]
I hope this doesn't sink.
I don't know how this is going to do.
The only thing left for us to do
is finish this race in first place.
I want you both to go back to your school with
the scholarship and a smile on your faces.
[We hope that Young Taek doesn't lose that
self-assured confidence of his on the water.]
[The plastic boat is barely starting
to take shape of a boat.]
This is better than
I thought it was going to be.
Can we just roll it around?
[Thanks to her brilliant idea,
they're able to do the wrap job quickly.]
You want to make a handle?
[Even making a handle for the boat?]
['Ye- Sisters', Ye Na and Ye Ji,
showing amazing teamwork skills.]
[Even a cute smiley face
to finish off the boat.]
Do you think that's going to float?
Of course, it'll float.
Why wouldn't it float?
- You made this with just plastic bags?
- Yes.
[100% plastic bag boat.]
[How long will the air in the plastic bags
hold out for them?]
I think we'll be okay.
[Team Dong-kuk is putting the final touches
to their boat too.]
We didn't have enough time, so we didn't
get to finish making our side floats.
[Unable to finish building as planned
due to the lack of time.]
[But they're still doing their absolute best
to finish building as best as they can.]
[The basin boat is now complete!]
- We have to wrap it all together.
- Saran wrap or tape?
We have to use saran wrap.
[Team Chung-Ang just needs to finish
wrapping up their boat.]
It's pretty bouncy.
We're going to win and
you're going to win the scholarship.
How about splitting the scholarship
three ways?
Okay, fine.
You know I wouldn't do that.
Yes, he would do that.
I'm sure you'll get a phone call from him
a couple days after the show.
I'll send you my bank deposit number.
[The water bottle boat is nearing
its completion as well.]
- Is it finished?
- Let is down gently.
Gently.
We're done!
We built this whole thing
with plastic bottles.
[From water bottle boat to plastic bag boat-
All seven boats are now complete.]
[Lift up the boats that they had built...
and off to Han river they go.]
- I hope we don't sink.
- We're not going to sink.
[Seven boats all made from
seven different materials.]
We can't drop it.
[Will they be able to cross the river safely?]
[On their way to Han river.]
You know how the students build their own sets
when they put on plays in theater class?
She was able to do everything
on her own.
She did the hammering and the sawing herself.
I was so shocked when I saw that.
We have what's called 'Theater Set Building'
class in school.
We learn how to hammer things,
and build stairs and bookcases.
Do you want to see
my girl teammate's hand?
[Bit Na has no ounce of shyness
about her.]
- I had a great time today.
- Me too, Gary.
Even better times are waiting
for us ahead.
The question is, whether that blanket boat
is going to float or not.
- Will that boat float?
- I guarantee that the blanket will float.
That blanket boat looked really nice.
As for Ye Na and Ye Ji...
you should just study hard at school
and win your own scholarships.
[The plastic bag girls will just have to
earn their scholarships on their own.]
- You should just work hard.
- I think we're here.
[A round of applause for everyone
and for the hard work they've put in.]
I'm starting to feel nervous.
[Finally arrives at Han river.]
[What nice weather for a boat ride.]
[Team Korea approaches the water with
their can boat held high above their heads.]
Here we are again.
You know where you have to go, right?
The fountain you see on the other side...
I know that.
How can I forget about this place?
Put your boat down on the ground.
To keep everyone safe,
please put on your life jackets.
Can we start from that side over there?
From where?
Sure, you can do that if you'd like.
The reason being, this is the spot
where we got started the last time.
[That day's trauma is still fresh in his mind
now that he's back on the banks of Han river.]
[All the other teams are arriving one by one
with their own respective boats.]
Do you think that other people would even
guess that this is made out of blankets?
I bet you can carry this by yourself.
What if we get swept down by the current?
[They're already worried about being swept
down the river before the race even starts.]
- Are you alright?
- Be careful.
I'm fine.
Watch your step, okay?
[All seven boats are now gathered
together at the starting line.]
[All the teams are busy practicing
how to row their boats.]
Kim Jong Kook and Chung-Ang University.
Ji Suk Jin and Kyung Hee University.
Ha Ha and Dong-Guk University.
Lee Kwang Soo and Seo-Gang University.
Song Ji Hyo and Kun-Kuk University.
Gary and Seong-Shin University.
Yoo Jae Suk and Korea University.
This is how I fell in the water
the last time.
[At last...
it's time to head out into the water.]
[With the boats that they made themselves...
they have to cross Han river.]
Everyone must cross to the other side.
Everyone rally up and we'll get started.
[Even though this looks to be
an impossible challenge...]
[It's the passion of these youths
that may get the job done.]
[But will all these boats float on water?]
Are you all ready?
We're sinking!
I think we're going to sink!
[The balloon boat is in danger of sinking
right off the bat?]
[On the other hand,
the bottle boat seems quite sturdy.]
[Safety first!
The rescue boat stays nearby.]
[They're about to start.]
[Even though they all just met
for the first time today...]
[They've somehow all become comrades
with the same goal and mission.]
We wish you all a safe journey
across the river.
- Ready!
- Fighting!
[Half trepidation, and half excitement-
Off they go with their passionate hearts!]
[Off to the Han river without
any hesitation.]
[Wow! All the boats are afloat!]
[But none of the boats
are really moving forward!]
Don't bump into us.
[Not easy to find their direction.]
[The bottle boat, ball boat, and basin boat
are all just spinning in place.]
[On the other hand, the other four boats
are gliding off towards their finish line.]
[Not only that...
but the blanket boat is in the lead!]
[And the weakest plastic bag boat
is in second place.]
[The fact that they're even
afloat is amazing enough...]
[Even the balloon boat is starting
to pull ahead.]
[Jae Suk and Team Korea are starting to
pull ahead on their can boat.]
[They're all starting to get on their way!]
[Current Rankings]
We can do it!
- What's our goal?
- To win!
- What did you say!
[Their goal is to win...
but their boat isn't moving.]
[What's going on here?]
[Their boat definitely is made
with the best of the best material.]
[So why isn't their boat even moving?]
[Even the ball boat
is just spinning in its place.]
[Even the boat made with second best material,
the basin boat, isn't moving very far.]
[The back portion of their boat is starting to
sink lower and lower into the water.]
- We have to cross the finish line.
- One, two!
[They're putting everything they have
into rowing their boat across...]
[But the boat isn't moving from its place.]
[These two are aggressively
taking the lead.]
[Plastic bag boat,
with the worst material of the lot.]
[And with the most number of girls
on the team...]
[But they're pulling strongly
as second in lead.]
You're doing great!
I'm not even cold!
I'm actually hot!
[Could this be these girls'
hidden superpower?]
[They're fast!]
[No one could've even guessed that these
two worst teams could be in the lead!]
[Taking the time to check the finish line.]
[And the blanket boat is off again!]
[And the balloon boat
is closely on their tail!]
[Some balloons floating by on the water.]
That's our crown!
Bye!
Why are our balloons starting
to shrink?
[Will their balloons
get them to the finish line?]
[They must hurry before all the air
escapes from their balloons.]
[However...]
[Team Korea is right on their tail!]
[Still catching up to them even with
their feet submerged in the water.]
[They may catch up to them
at any moment!]
[The can boat is right on their tail.]
[Even the chatty Jae Suk and Young Taek
are just rowing without any talking...]
[Will they catch up to the others?]
[Meanwhile...]
[The blanket boat is still in the lead.]
[Amazing teamwork!]
We just crossed the Han river on
a stack of blankets!
[We crossed the Han river on blankets!]
We can do it!
Blankets! Blankets!
[A world record!
Crossing the Han river on blankets.]
[Feeling totally at ease.]
[Almost to the finish line-
And these three are giving it their best.]
[A huge gap in their lead.]
[To cross the Han river on some blankets...]
[Still unable to believe what we're seeing.]
[Even their record is hard to believe.]
His socks are all soaked.
[These two men's passion shining
all the way through to the end.]
[Ji Hyo and Team Kun-Kuk
arrive in first place.]
[Taking their precious blanket boat
with the help of one another...]
[Heads towards the victory flag
with an ease in their steps.]
This should've been
a documentary of some sorts.
[Ji Hyo and Team Kun-Kuk wins.]
- Kun-Kuk University, fighting!
- Fighting!
[Kun-Kuk University and Song Ji Hyo!]
We won!
We're going to float that blanket boat
in the university's pond in commemoration.
[In the university's pond?]
Please allow the students to be able to ride
the blanket boat for exercise purposes!
- Fighting!
[Gary and Team Seong-Shin are almost
to the finish line as well.]
Don't stop!
We can't stop now!
[Brother Gae is giving encouragement
to the two younger girls.]
We're almost there!
Another 100m!
Talking is going to exhaust you even more.
Just row!
Seong-Shin University, fighting!
[Screaming along
with their final burst of energy.]
The two teams that were in last place are
the only ones at the finish line right now.
The two teams with the worst selections are
- Kang Gary, fighting!
- Seong-Shin University, fighting!
[With the worst plastic bag material...]
[And with two girls on their team...]
[They finish in second place!]
You're almost at the finish line!
Just a little bit more!
Come on, soldiers!
Row! there you go!
We did it!
We did it.
We actually did it!
[Gary and Team Seong-Shin
finishes in second place.]
[The agony comes to find them
the moment they get off the boat.]
[You can handle the pain.
You came in at second place!]
Come here!
Come here, my soldiers!
[A hug of joy with his teammates.]
You both did great.
Because of all your hard work, we'll give out
scholarships down to third place winners.
[Congratulations on winning the scholarship!
Time for another hug!]
The two teams with the worst materials
came in at first and second place.
- You all did great!
- Yay!
I never would've guessed that the blankets
and the plastic bags would even succeed!
But we did it!
[But...]
[The competition isn't over yet.]
[The battle for third place
is starting to heat up even more.]
[And...]
[These three teams still aren't moving,
but they're all still giving it their best.]
[The gap is closing in even more.]
They might catch up to them.
[The can boat is right on
the balloon boat's tail.]
[They're about to catch up to them!]
They're really catching up to us!
[Those two boats are neck and neck!]
No!
[They've surpassed the balloon boat!
Jae Suk and Team Korea are in third place!]
[The team that gets to the finish flag first
will be declared third place winners!]
[The scholarship will be given out to
the third place winners as well.]
Down to the third place winners!
[Jae Suk and Team Korea are almost
to the finish line!]
[Just then...]
[Desperate Giraffe
throws himself in the water.]
[All three members of the team must
pull the flag out together for it to count.]
All three members have to pull
the flag out together.
All three members must be together.
No!
[Jae Suk and Team Korea wins third place.]
I'm so cold!
So cold!
[Team Seo-Gang comes in at fourth place.]
This is amazing.
Did you start to sweat towards the end?
Yes, I got so hot that I just
wanted to jump in the water.
Fighting!
[Even though winning
may have been their goal...]
[That has no place in their ultimate goal
of crossing the finishing line.]
[Right in this moment, everyone is a winner.]
You're almost at the finish line,
Dong Hoon!
Fighting!
[One voice and one heart-
Cheering them on to the very end.]
Ji Suk Jin!
[And the beautiful last place holders...
getting the hottest cheer of them all.]
[Giraffe is in the mood and
is attempting to ride the wave.]
[But he's criticized immediately.]
Hurry, Suk Jin!
I'm cold!
Ji Suk Jin!
[The final team crosses the finish line
in the midst of their enthusiastic cheer.]
[A huge round of applause for finishing
the race without ever giving up.]
[All seven teams complete the race.]
Thank you to all the students,
and the Running Man members.
Every single one of the seven teams
succeeded in completing the race.
[All seven teams completed the race!]
The blanket boat was amazing.
Every single plastic bag
could make a huge difference!
The two teams with the worst material
selection came in at first and second place.
That's what life is like.
[Scholarship is passed out to
Kun-Kuk University winners.]
[Ji Hyo and her team break the record
with 16 minutes and 47 seconds.]
[A word from the winning team.]
[Even though they started off with a
huge disadvantage in sixth place...]
[But that spurred them on to work even harder
and thus were able to come in at first place.]
This has taught me that hard work will always
make me a winner in whatever I do.
[Hard work can make anything possible!]
We started off in third place,
and we finished in third place.
I think studying is easier than this.
No way!
How can you say that studying
is easy?
[Gary can't understand her logic.]
[And lastly, a word from their eldest.]
You think you're in first place,
but you're actually in last place.
And you think you're in last place,
but you're actually a winner.
You can always catch up and win in life.
Fighting!
[Thank you to all the university students
who graciously participated in our episode.]
[Here's to all the passionate youths and
to their brand new beginnings.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Are you ready in Australia?]
You have to go find your lost treasure.
[Things...]
[That you could never have
even imagined...]
[Are about to happen right now.]
[Tangalooma]
What is all that?
[Currumbin Sanctuary]
Isn't that a real kangaroo?
My baby had a baby of its own!
[Gold Coast]
[Palm Beach]
[Melbourne]
I'll go in the water myself.
[Next Week's Running Man-
Adventure in Australia.]