Subtitles by DramaFever
[Triangle (Noun)- A plane figure with
three straight sides and three angles.]
[Triangular Mystery]
[A cursed beauty created by
three straight lines.]
[You're no exception from
its curse!]
[I'm so mad!]
[Why did Jae Suk have to be
covered in mud?]
What is that?
[Large TV?]
What is this?
[Running Men are going with the flow
without knowing what's going on.]
[Flying as a phantom thief!]
[The man who flew from a TV.]
Isn't that Tae Min?
[The Nation's Younger Brother!]
[Tae Min of SHINee!]
[Jump!]
[Elegance]
[The Singing Goddess]
[Soyou of Sistar!]
[The best dancer of our generation!]
[Kai of EXO!]
[Dangerously Charming Idol!]
[Se Hoon of EXO!]
[Presentation of the best idols
of our time!]
[Only one more stage to go]
[The kid of our time]
[Ha Ha]
[Serious]
[We are the new idols!]
[Not fast forwarding]
[Haroro's frivolous dance]
What the hell is he doing?
[He's in his own world,
with his own song.]
[Finally, Tae Min's magical time!]
[Powerful popping!]
[Bad copycats]
[Even the ending is perfect!]
[Kai and Se Hoon's perfect teamwork.]
[Burdensome dance]
[Soyou's turn!]
[Her uncle fans are happy!]
[Her fellow idols are having fun.]
[She is as radiating as
the midsummer sun!]
- What fun!
[Ending with a hand heart.]
You guys are awesome!
[Bowing deeply]
Go away!
Old farts!
What the hell was this?
What were you doing up there?
Look at them.
You're the worst one here!
You don't take care of yourselves, do you?
You need to put in some effort to look good!
How did you do that up there, Tae Min?
How do you shake like that?
It's just like the feeling of
getting startled.
Startled!
[Shake the body as if you're startled.]
[Giraffe's electric shock popping.]
[Popping is not hard!]
Let's introduce our next team!
Please come out!
[Another team to oppose
these new idols!]
[A man emerges from the large TV.]
[The charisma that doesn't require jumping!]
[The original princely idol!]
[Eun Ji Won of Sechs Kies!]
It's Ji Won!
[A bit of a heavy jump.]
[The legend of first generation idols!]
[Moon Hee Jun of HOT!]
[The man who is a sculpture himself]
[Danny Ahn of g.o.d!]
He got so scared!
[Frozen]
[Is it obvious?]
[The father of all frivolous idols]
[Cheon Myung Hoon of NRG]
Are you wearing pajamas?
[The pajamas fashion that is
hard to understand.]
[What?]
[Is that... Kkuk?]
[Formerly a turbo engine,
Kim Jong Kook!]
What is he wearing?
[We are the original idols!]
[Wow, this song is...]
[Kkuk's hit song in his Turbo years!]
[Black Cat (1995)]
[His group, Turbo, was the
number one singing duo in mid-1990s]
[His body remembers the old dance!]
[A Grandstand Play by Sechs Kies (1997)]
[Taekwondo dance by Sechs Kies?]
[Ji Won could jump to
touch the sky back then...]
[The time when he was the leader of
six crystals...]
[The memory still shines
as bright as crystal!]
[Finally, H.O.T.'s national anthem!]
[Candy by H.O.T. (1996)]
[Automatic response]
[Do you remember?]
[The time when this song gave you
butterflies in your stomach?]
[Everyone is in unison as they
remember those days together.]
[The Power Racer Dance comes out!]
[This is my song!]
[The song that gave hope to everyone!]
[You Can Do It by NRG (1997)]
[Giving his everything in his pajamas]
[NRG's performances were always
known for their energy.]
[Evolved from a quiet, pretty boy...]
[Into a frivolous uncle!]
[The trendy dance of the time!]
[g.o.d.'s driving dance!]
[Observation by g.o.d. (1998)]
[They used to sweep the top of music charts
every time they released a new song!]
[Everyone remembers the dance
as if they practiced together!]
[This is the power of the original idols!]
[H.O.T., Sechs Kies, g.o.d., NRG]
[HotsechgodRG + Kkuk!]
I'm so tired!
[Panting]
Because you were dancing so much!
[Original idols are discharged]
Why are you all so tired?
I'm so tired.
You're drenched in sweat!
Ma'am!
You look like an old woman!
Anyway...
All these young kids were so good
with their jumping...
But how come all your jumps were
so erratic?
Some of you were too forward,
some were too back...
In the 90s, it was customary
to jump and land forward.
That's right!
We had to jump and land forward!
Then every one of you
should've landed forward.
How come only a few of you landed forward
and the others landed backward?
And what is this Jikiri dude doing here?
[Jikiri: Ha Ha's former group of three men]
And a dude from X-Teen is here too!
That's a false accusation!
My popularity is a recent development!
[Gary used to be X-Teen's Guest Performer]
I'm still considered
as a new singer!
We have so much history!
Hee Jun is still cute.
Is that so?
You did get a bit shorter.
But it's okay.
Everyone's pants got tighter, right?
- We used to use pins to hold them up!
- Right! And rubber bands!
I used to wear size 40 pants.
They don't sell those pants anymore,
so I had to patch some things up last night.
My fashion coordinator did
a lot of work last night.
I couldn't refuse the result of her hard work,
so I had to wear these.
And I couldn't find real goggles,
so I just pasted something here.
What are these?
Do you think SM Entertainment
couldn't afford a pair of goggles back then?
Ji Won isn't wearing his
real costume either!
- This is my real costume!
- Really?
Don't you think this is too new?
To be honest, I made this from
a regular dress shirt.
So you can see my undershirt.
This needs more work...
That's fine! We'll be running on Running Man,
so your undershirt is fine...
I'm sorry...
Because they had me dressed like this,
even my jokes are from the 90s!
Damn it!
That joke would've worked in the 90s!
Take a good look, you guys.
You should save some of your costumes just in
case you go on a variety show decades later!
[Learn from Hee Jun's mistake!]
Every team has a girl.
How come my team doesn't have one?
Your team has you!
[He looks like an old lady
who came out to take a stroll]
You are definitely the old lady
of the team!
Fine, just wait and see what it feels like
to be killed by an old lady.
Say what?
Just wait and see?
So why are we divided into
three teams?
So we have
Team Running Idol...
Team Original Idol...
And Team New Idol.
Three teams.
Then what is he doing there?
[We'll treat him as the manager
of Team New Idol.]
So the theme of today's games
will be the number three.
It's called the Triangular Mystery Race.
[Triangular Mystery Race.]
The team which solves the mystery
related to a triangle will be the final winner.
Each team will get different hints according
to how successful it was after each round.
The team that solves the triangular mystery
in the end with all the hints will be the winner.
Just like a triangular sushi.
[Was that a joke?]
I'm helping you guys out!
Even we don't say such bad jokes!
What triangular sushi?
Definitely the 90s...
Such a bad joke!
That can end your tenure on this program!
You might get kicked out
of this program forever!
Look at Soyou's face.
She got dumbfounded by Ha Ha's joke...
[What...]
[What is he saying...]
She could neither open
her mouth nor close it!
- Soyou! Come to our team!
- Let her speak!
- Am I stuck with him until the end?
- Yes!
- I don't get to choose?
- No!
You should be nice to me
while I'm nice to you.
Before we end up eating dinner
at Samgakji!
Today...
Only the team that solves the triangular
mystery shall escape through these doors...
No!
I want to leave here alive!
[I can't lose!]
No!
I need to continue my career!
[To the first stage]
What is Jong Kook doing?
[Now Playing: Light by H.O.T. (1998)]
He's too cool for us.
- Are you abandoning us?
- We're the guests!
I'm sorry, guys!
Please take care of us!
We'll show them who the bosses are!
The power of the 90s!
[All of us used to be friends and rivals
back in the 90s...]
[Back then, the whole world
belonged to us with our fans.]
[We'll revive the passion
from our past together!]
Things were not kind to us
back in the day.
- And we've made it so far!
- That's right.
Just look how he turned out.
He must have gone through a lot...
I'm still swollen from the fatigue
from my heyday.
My body won't go back!
Pumpkin can help with swelling.
Pumpkin?
I should eat more?
You want to eat even more?
- Pumpkin is good for you.
- Really?
- Where are we going?
- It's a pool!
[First Stage]
[Their first triangular mystery]
[What could be in this?]
Come around, everyone.
You came with your goggles?
My coordinator says she had no idea
the opening segment would be that short.
She says I should use them more.
She did spend the
whole night making them!
She told me to not waste them!
So I put them on here.
It was inconceivable to see you all
together back in the 90s.
How could you all be here together?
Jong Kook is our focal point.
[Everyone under me!]
Let's take it easy, okay?
[Intimidated]
Look at Hee Jun. He'll forever
be a junior in front of Jong Kook!
When I was changing with Gary...
I saw that on Ji Won's knee.
So I asked him why he has it on.
He said, "Old age."
- You have other health problems too.
- My shoulders.
Because of too much popping...
Be careful of this, Tae Min.
This will be your future!
[You're my past, and I'm your future!]
One more thing to be careful.
You might become round like me
in 18 years!
[Despair]
[V-line to U-line in 18 years.]
Everyone's so pale!
We'll get you tanned to maximum!
Have you not gone
outside this summer, Hee Jun?
I'm so happy to be outside!
It's been forever!
So, welcome to the first stage.
This is going to be
Triangular Water Basketball.
First...
We got this.
- We're really bad at basketball.
- That's fine.
- Do you know how to play?
- Yes...
Did you see how he was befuddled?
As soon as he started talking about basketball,
the whole team said they're bad at it!
Soyou was the best.
She closed by saying
"Do you know how to play?"
That was probably unexpected.
Every team will send one member
on the yellow pad.
Each team will get one of the pads and
try to send the ball to their teammate on the yellow pad.
Only the shots from the team's own
pad will be counted.
And no matter who the shooter is, a point
will be given to the team that catches the ball.
For example, even if Kim Jong Kook
shoots the ball towards his teammate...
if the other team's member catches it,
the point will be given to the other team.
- So the goalie is the most important one.
- That's right.
The goalie doesn't matter for you.
Just do what Jong Kook tells you.
Running Man is all about
dishonor, slyness, and deception.
Just like how soccer players foul
when the referee isn't looking.
[That's the spirit!]
- Let's at least pretend like we're discussing.
- Okay.
- Why are you spying on us?
- Look.
Everyone is exchanging their thoughts
freely. But here...
Kook is dictating over everyone.
What is he telling you to do?
He can just tell us nicely,
but he continues to talk like this!
I told you already!
Because I'm wearing these,
I must be clear with my directions!
I'm scared that your finger
might poke my eye!
He hasn't changed a bit!
[Entering the arena]
You can't get wet today, Ji Hyo!
Okay?
I'm getting wet because of you, honey!
Did you just call me honey?
You guys are too obvious...
Come on in, gentlemen!
My heart isn't so good these days...
[The water is still a bit cold for us...]
[Not cold at all!]
It's so cold!
Hurry up and get in!
I did my hair at a salon today!
It's so cold!
Why is it so deep?
I never knew I'm this short!
It's so deep!
[Just like a huge tuna from the Pacific.]
We're ready.
- We're next to the pad!
- Pushing is also important.
Remember to hold onto the ball!
Don't forget to hold
onto the ball, Hee Jun!
[Sliding]
Hey! New Idols!
Go back to your flag!
[Waging a nerve war]
They're just kids!
[All ready for Triangular Basketball]
Go! Run!
Get it!
[They need to get the ball first]
[The ball has to be thrown from the pad.]
[Kai's critical pass]
[Team New Idol's chance
right in front of the goal!]
[Whoever catches the ball will score
no matter which teams shoots it!]
[Ha Ha shoots!]
[The catcher of this ball
would be the winner of the first round!]
[Fails after bouncing off of Soyou's arm]
[Giraffe's rebound]
Kwang Soo!
Just take it away from him, Myung Hoon!
[Giraffe's long pass]
[Jae Suk gets it then passes to Suk Jin.]
[All he needs to do
is to shoot at Ji Hyo.]
[Splash!]
[Great strategy of pad flipping.]
Jong Kook!
[Tight]
Flip it!
Right here!
My ball!
[Total Chaos]
This isn't basketball!
This is rugby!
Don't take my pants off!
The cameras won't show it!
[The cameras are showing it!]
We're here, Jong Kook!
[Floats]
[Se Hoon intercepts]
[The ball has to be thrown from the pad.]
[He got it!]
[Great chance in front of the goal.]
[The ball slips out of his hands.]
Let's not push each other!
I'm so scared!
I won't push you, sisters.
So please don't push me!
I'm right here, Myung Hoon!
I want to touch the ball too!
I want to touch the ball!
[Giraffe is screaming for the ball.]
[Kkuk's accurate back pass!]
[The goal is a bit too far.]
You must come closer!
Flip the damn pad!
[Splash!]
[Got kicked out of the pad by Blank Ji.]
What just happened?
Hurry up and get up there!
[Fishing for a giant tuna once again.]
[Nice passing between
Kkuk-Ji Won-Myung Hoon.]
[Great chance for Team Original Idol!]
No...
[Splash!]
[His arms and legs are too short...]
[Great tuna fishing continues.]
[Coming back on the pad itself
is a great mission for him.]
Hey!
Get up there now!
[Team Original Idol removes
the Giraffe who occupied their pad.]
[Kkuk is not letting the ball go
against three opponents!]
[Team Original Idol regroups in the meantime.]
[Great Chaos]
[Jae Suk's pass...]
[Bounces off of Gary]
[Danny's rebound goes straight
to Myung Hoon!]
[Perfect Chance for Myung Hoon.]
[Get it, Hee Jun!]
[The team that catches this ball
would be the winner of the first round!]
[Soyou's perfect catch]
What was that?
Point to Team New Idol!
[Team New Idol wins the first round!]
[Whoever catches the ball gets the point.]
[I demand an answer!]
I thought the catcher doesn't matter!
I thought I just had to throw it!
[It's been a while, Myung Hoon...]
[You've always been silly
from the first time I met you...]
[And always quite dim-witted.]
[After so many years...]
[How can you still be the same?]
[Wake up, Myung Hoon!]
You gave it directly to Soyou!
You should've pushed her!
Get down here, fattie!
[Fattie]
Fattie?
You little...
You're just a jacked old woman!
Get down here!
Fattie?
My mom is watching this
show right now!
This is too much!
This isn't Yo-yo!
Fattie?
Come down!
I refuse!
A fattie can't go down!
He's been very sensitive lately.
I'd rather be called Yo-yo...
It was a term of endearment!
Hey!
I won't even look at you!
He's upset!
You should apologize!
Hey!
Just do it right!
You're very endearing, fattie!
I don't need to be endearing!
Stop calling me that!
Be the bigger person, Moon Yo Yo!
[Cheers for Moon Yo Yo!]
Please get ready for the second round.
The score is 1:0:0.
Your glasses are broken, Hee Jun.
My glasses!
Just toss them away!
I can't!
My coordinator made them for me!
This is fun!
Give us the ball!
We must score at any cost.
Get ready...
[This could be the last round]
[There's nowhere to back out to!]
[Tae Min gets the ball]
Grab him!
[Forced Washing]
Stop it!
Why is he tickling me?
[Kai has been tickling underwater.]
What's wrong with him?
[Se Hoon passes to Tae Min.]
[Tae Min shoots!]
[Soyou is the only one on the pad!]
[But the ball curves...]
[This close!]
[Kkuk's interception!]
This way, Jong Kook!
[Danny is right in front of him.]
[But the goal disappears right before
the shot...]
[Giraffe's iron defense]
[Blocking Ha Ha with his own pad.]
Stop spinning!
[From Kai to Tae Min to Ha Ha.]
[Accurate passes, amazing teamwork]
[Team Original Idol isn't afraid to foul!]
He bit my butt!
We have our own Suarez here!
[Moon Yo Yo and his nuclear teeth!]
Nicely done!
I apologize.
I'm sorry!
Grab my foot to come up!
[Kkuk mans the goal for Team Original Idol.]
It's too far!
We caught him!
[Big Nosed Brother gets the ball...]
[Then passes to Ji Hyo!]
[Ji Hyo shoots!]
Awesome!
[Soyou's hustle play]
[Team New Idol wins Triangular Basketball!]
[Confused and lost]
I'm so sorry.
[Disappointed]
- She means serious business!
- I didn't push him!
She's no joke!
I didn't push him!
How dare you throw a tantrum?
Jong Kook pushed him.
We admit.
With Myung Hoon's admittance,
Team New Idol wins!
Who are you to admit anything?
[Myung Hoon...
What's your true identity?]
[We won!]
I meant it was a foul!
[We got it, but the game is over...]
[Soyou's shining performance]
Team New Idol wins the first stage.
One more round!
Please!
We need to decide the second place!
Then let's do this.
Team New Idol can take a break, and
we'll have a match between the other teams.
This will be decided by a single match.
Let's have a gentlemen's game!
We had some dirty players in past rounds.
I had no idea that kids these days
played so dirty!
[You mean, us?]
Here's the match to decide
the second place.
[Tae Min's throw will start the game.]
I'm right here, Tae Min!
Kang Ta is like my brother!
Your boss!
He's like my brother!
I'll call him to make sure
you get paid on time!
Just throw the ball to me.
Trust me!
[Danny's straight pass!]
[Directly to Ji Won
right in front of the goal.]
[It's considered a shot
as it touched Ji Won's hand!]
[Team Running Idol wins by catching it!]
[The game was over in a split second.]
[Denying the reality]
What the hell were you doing?
How could I catch that?
[We've lost, right?]
Team Running Idol takes
second place!
Just one more round, please!
We can go on and on
if this is how it's going to go!
[Enjoying the water]
Team New Idol gets two points,
and Team Running Idol gets one point.
And Team Original Idol gets no points.
Not even a point?
[Five dots]
[The Triangular Mystery...]
[What is it?]
[Second stage]
What is this?
I don't feel good about this.
- It's covered.
- What is this?
Please don't look.
Come together in front of the flag.
Please tell him to go with his own team!
Why does he keep following us?
I'm not following you!
Move quickly! I'm getting
yelled at because you're slow!
[Singers with 20+ years of experience
are getting yelled at by Kkuk.]
Hee Jun got cuter ever since
Jong Kook called him a fattie!
I forgot about it...
It'd be nice to establish
that as his character!
He even blowdried his hair!
[He blowdried his hair using
the plug at the snack stand.]
He's a true idol!
I just blowdried my hair after washing it.
[Maintaining his mystique as an idol.]
I just wanted to look better
because he called me a fattie!
Where did you blowdry your hair?
Team New Idol is quite competitive!
You need to talk the talk and
walk the walk!
What?
Talk the talk?
- You would've lost without Soyou!
- That was our whole strategy!
Soyou did very well!
Team Original Idol used to be
very energetic like that...
Let's stop talking about our past.
We're still alive and well!
We're still here, making this show!
We're not dead yet!
I'm still alive!
[How dare you!]
He just made us laugh out so hard!
You know we have those
sunscreen sprays, right?
My coordinator brought me one.
So...
Suk Jin closed his eyes
and asked me to spray it on him.
So I went like this with my mouth...
Then he went...
[Maintaining his skin with
Yoo Hyuk's saliva!]
I was totally fooled!
[Embarrassed]
I couldn't feel anything!
But he kept going like this!
Hold on.
Why are there thigh bands?
- Perhaps...
- Could it be that...
I said number three would
be the theme of today.
This is Triangular Wrestling!
The second stage will be Korean Wrestling.
We have three different rings
as it'll be Triangular Wrestling.
One is just a regular sand ring.
But there is something special
about the other two rings.
We'll do the wrestling in one of
these rings picked by you.
Since we have three teams, we need to
pick a team that will skip to the final round.
You'll play at the corresponding ring
after choosing one of these blocks.
The objective would be to
take the name tag.
[Which ring would be their fighting ground?]
[Ring Number Two!]
Let's reveal the rings!
Please reveal!
[What kind of special rings are they?]
[Ring Number One is a water ring]
[Ring Number Three is a regular sand ring]
The Ring Number Two must be the weird one!
[Ring Number Two is making everyone scream.]
[A mud ring]
Is it mud or cement?
If it's real cement,
the loser won't be able to get out!
[Full of mud that's good for skin!]
We brought 2.4 tons of mud from
Boryeong Mud Festival.
This is good for your skin!
Please send a person to
represent your team.
Come on, Hee Jun!
I just dried my hair!
I can't put mud on myself
in front of these young guys!
I can't be a dirty fattie!
- Just do it!
- You shouldn't have dried your hair!
We'll send Kai!
Come, Kai.
Go, Kai.
I'll let it slide because
he's SHINee.
Such a joke will not work
in ten years!
You have to keep working hard!
Tae Min only learned from you!
- Suk Jin should do it.
- Why me?
Unless they're going to pick a girl,
Suk Jin is a good choice.
What are you talking about?
He's the next best thing
to facing a girl.
Kai, Suk Jin, and Hee Jun will fight to decide
which team advances to the final directly.
I'll show you
what tag ripping is all about.
There'll be a moment
when you'll be facing someone directly.
That's when you just need to go in!
- How handsome...
- Just go in!
You need to go in more than you think.
Also...
He won't be able to use
what Jong Kook tells him.
His skills are only for
those with a lot of power.
Don't waste your energy!
[Ha Ha's prediction is correct...]
I think you're just too strong.
If you worry about your inside,
the tag will be gone.
So don't worry about your tag.
Just focus on ripping the other tags!
Go inside when the opponent
is putting his guard down.
Make it as dirty, evil, and
deceitful as possible.
Remember our motto.
We have to do them too.
Representatives, please enter the ring.
Players, please go in!
- Are you going to wear them?
- Should I go barefoot?
I think they'll come off.
You're wearing shoes that look like you!
Very round!
My mom got them for me!
The winning team will
advance to the finals directly!
[Mismatched]
Roar!
[Their inharmonious cheer
is not helping...]
Please get ready.
Only one match!
Kai, think carefully!
Stop talking and just go in!
Give Hee Jun a nice mud bath!
No thanks!
Quit talking and just come at me!
Don't provoke them!
Step aside, Kai.
- Why are you doing this?
- Don't say things like that!
[He must be out of his mind.]
I love EXO!
Don't do things like that!
- Don't do this!
- Ji Suk Jin!
Defense!
I'll get rid of this old man first!
Who are you calling an old man?
You fattie!
Fattie!
[Cutesy]
Remember what Jong Kook taught you!
[Hee Jun charges forward!]
[He got it!]
[Can he do it?]
[What?]
[Big Nosed Brother grabbed the tag too.]
[Big Nosed Brother was quicker!]
He's out.
Get him out of here!
Go away!
Wow, Suk Jin!
I couldn't even see it!
Suk Jin was so quick!
Let's win!
He's done this quite often.
[Using deceitful tricks
just as Haroro taught him.]
Don't cut him any slack
because he's EXO!
EXO is dead to me!
[Getting started]
You've been doing this
for four years!
- You need to lose your shoes!
- It's fine! Just continue!
[Kai is pushing forward]
Rip it!
No!
[They both grabbed each other's
name tags!]
[Who'll rip it first?]
[Kai was faster!]
[Kai ripped it first...]
[Then Big Nosed Brother!]
Kai did it first!
[Great performance by Kai!]
We're going to be killed
by Jong Kook!
Look how angry he is!
- Great job!
- Well done!
Very cute!
[Posing as if nothing happened]
He just danced.
[EXO's new mud step dance.]
[Semi-final between
Team Running Idol and Team Original Idol]
For your semi-final,
you'll pick your ring once again.
Let's just do it in mud!
I liked playing in mud.
You may pick.
Mud!
We need a ring that
might cause Jong Kook to slip!
I'll put your face in it
and slide it up and down.
Team Running Idol
and Team Original Idol...
[This round will be
a last-man-standing round!]
[First volunteer for Team Original Idol?]
[You?
That'd be easy...]
[No, it's me!]
[But...]
[He slips!]
[He deserves it!]
That was just a performance
from him!
Jong Kook is so angry right now!
He's become quite spiteful!
It's too dangerous to fight a person
like him!
We need to do something for him!
[Worried for his safety]
[The reverse massage to
make him more tense.]
Give it back to him!
[That feels good!]
How cheeky!
[He's having so much fun.]
Why are you laughing?
Do you want to forfeit?
Damn all of you!
- Why, what's wrong?
- Too scared?
Without Jong Kook,
they'd be nothing!
It's fine!
Just win it!
Show him the power of the 90s,
Jong Kook!
I shall!
Cheers!
Cheers for the 90s!
My claps are causing dust!
The floor is slippery and uneven.
The player whose back
touches the floor first loses.
I think our whole body will touch the floor.
First round of the semi-finals!
[A competition of pride
between two team leaders.]
[A human windmill?]
Are you really going to be like this?
Look at Jae Suk's face!
[Splash!]
[Mud]
[Shampoo]
[A shocking visual]
[Mud conditioner this time!]
[Annihilation]
Is he making a piece of art?
Perhaps a sculpture?
Just finish!
Please!
Let go of me!
I'll get you!
[A nice face pack to finish up.]
That's enough!
[Kkuk Wins!]
[Sad...]
I'm so angry!
[So enraging...]
[The life of the weak...]
So angry!
[I will avenge this disgrace!]
[Sure! Be my guest!]
So he just stays in the game?
[Mother...]
Jae Suk, you can wash up down there...
What?
He can't hear well because
his ears are stuffed with mud!
The mud got hard in his ears!
You can hose yourself down there...
That doesn't mean anything!
My heart...
Who will wipe off the mud
on my heart?
Such disgrace!
I'll avenge him!
I'm so mad!
So mad!
[Mud Washing of Rage]
I'm so mad!
[Dying of laughter]
My heart!
He really sacrificed himself.
His performance was so good.
[As he's about to wash up...]
There's no water!
Not a single drop of water!
[Never-ending parade of rage]
Second round, please!
Fine!
It'd be easier to die first!
I'm scared...
Don't grab my band!
Get set!
[Should I just go home?]
[Goodbye]
[Not in this world]
Is this the floor?
Where is Gary?
- Where is he?
- I can't see him!
Where is my home?
[Kkuk is scaring everyone off.]
Give me some water!
I can't see!
Where is my home?
[Big Nosed Brother brings water.]
You can't take water away from me!
His situation is more urgent!
[Team Running Idol is in need of water
every time they play.]
Two nothing, everyone.
Three players remaining.
Suk Jin is going in!
[Big Nosed Brother slips
as he enters the ring.]
[Kneeling down even before
the match begins.]
Why did you kneel down?
Why?
My legs are shot.
I didn't mean to kneel down.
So, how do you want it?
Nonsense.
I'm going to beat you.
I'm going to beat you!
I will!
You look like a grandfather!
I don't know...
Dude.
For how long are you going to
just play with me?
Answer my question!
Jong Kook!
You should just nail him down like this.
That's exactly what I'm thinking.
Grab his ankles first!
Then like this!
You should write his name out
with his hair!
Where's the band?
Get set!
What are you going to do?
It's back!
[This pose is quite familiar]
[The winner of the
calligraphy performance.]
What are you doing?
[Writing in one stroke...]
[Kkuk the Mud Calligrapher]
[No upset there,
Kkuk the Mud Artist wins!]
This is too much!
This is so enraging!
I'll get you some water...
[Multi-purpose Yoo Hyuk Spray]
This is nice!
So nice!
Get set!
It's three-nothing right now.
It'll be five-nothing soon!
Jong Kook should diversify
his method of winning.
He's different.
I'll give my everything!
For how long?
You're our only hope!
[No such thing as an upset.]
Are you here to work out?
[But Giraffe regains his balance
with his long legs.]
[Surprised]
[Giraffe's counterattack!]
[Could it be?]
[Only his front side touches the floor!]
[The back must touch to lose.]
I'm fine as long as my back
doesn't touch the floor, right?
As long as your back doesn't touch!
- I can't find his band!
- Just grab his underwear!
- Right above!
Don't do it!
You have to disgrace him!
[A very sneaky and intimate attack.]
Disgrace him!
You can lose!
But just disgrace him as much as possible!
His back didn't touch!
[As long as the back doesn't touch!]
[Let's continue then!]
His desire to survive
is stronger than a cockroach!
[High praise]
[Tattered]
You've become a zombie, Kwang Soo!
You can do this all night long!
Do it all night long!
[A mud zombie!]
Fine, let's do it!
Just last five hours!
I shall not flip!
Some water for your face!
Just give up, Kwang Soo!
Time!
No stopping.
[Then...]
I lost.
[The Mud Zombie gives up his back.]
[Kkuk wins after giving his all.]
I don't think Jong Kook
can perform in the final.
This is it!
Our plan worked!
I'm fine.
My energy will come back soon.
So, who's next?
[Team Running Idol's last hope]
[Blank Ji]
[For woman competitors, the
one whose back touches the floor wins!]
I shall revenge the disgrace
of my teammates.
Let's go, Kim Jong Kook!
That's the spirit!
[Burping]
I'm sorry but...
Are you baptizing?
[Desperation]
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what I was thinking.
The mud wrestling!
Hang onto him, Ji Hyo!
[Blank Ji hangs onto Kkuk]
[She bites him!]
[Blank Ji wins!]
[Blank-arez defeats Mr. Capable!]
You did it!
You did so well!
Give her water!
We can win!
You can beat all the other four!
You never know!
She meant business!
[Blank Ji is their only hope.]
Just four more to go!
Come out here, Moon Hee Jun!
[Shaking]
Do I have to?
- Get out there, Hee Jun!
- Can I bite people too?
I want to bite people too!
Remember, with women competitors,
your back must touch first to win!
[The fate of Team Running Idol
is entirely in the hands of Blank Ji.]
Don't be afraid to mess your hair up!
You can always dry it again!
Don't mind too much!
Do I look pretty?
Mr. Director?
I need to know these things.
A bit of mud on your face
will make you more sexy.
I got it.
Why are you shaking your butt?
[This might be the last game!]
[Hee Jun stops Blank Ji's attack]
How pretty!
[What?]
[Hee Jun pulls back
when she lets her guard down!]
What do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry!
I won't do it again!
[How dare you!]
[Team Original Idol advances
thanks to Hee Jun!]
How come his hair is still the same?
[His hair is still clean!]
I tried this area before
to see if I can fall here!
This part was the shallow part!
So the final round would be between
Team Original Idol and Team New Idol!
[Final]
This is the final round. Are you ready?
[Finals will happen on the sand ring per lottery]
Even until early 2000s,
Korean wrestling was very common.
But unfortunately many wrestling matches
have disappeared from TV...
The weather is great today!
[Competition in live broadcasting]
Which network are you from?
We're from SBS.
Where are you from?
- We're from SBS.
- No, we're from SBS!
Are you airing from
the Deungchon Office?
No, we're from the Mokdong Office.
Let's go, Danny!
[First Round]
[Danny vs. Kai]
All my teammates wanted to
go against Danny!
Danny showed some great performance in
other programs such as Let's Go Dream Team.
But he kind of looks like a toothpick.
[So slim]
Kai and Danny!
Korean Wrestling is also about
the men's pride!
That's why my pride has been
hurt so badly.
Kai is also very slim,
but he can be very fast.
You really can't tell this round!
Danny's form is very solid!
[Aggressive from the beginning]
[Danny pushes, yet
Kai pushes back.]
[Then!]
[Kai's inside attack!]
[What will happen?]
[Danny's outside counterattack!]
[Danny used his technique
in a split second!]
Kai was more powerful than Danny.
But Danny won with his experience!
This is what Korean Wrestling is all about!
Korean Wrestling is only fun
when it's more than just power.
But you made everything so boring!
It's all your fault
for making it so boring!
As you probably saw,
Kai had more power.
But Danny used Kai's pulling power
and pushed him onto the ground!
What a technique!
I did not expect Danny to be
such a skilled wrestler!
But I kind of knew it all along.
Is that so?
You never did!
Tae Min is the most slim one
among all of us.
Have you ever done Korean
Wrestling before?
I did it a couple times for fun
with my friends.
There's another microphone
up there.
Kids these days don't really get to
play Korean Wrestling.
When I was in school, that's all we did.
At every chance we got...
You probably did it because
it was very fun for you!
Because he can win!
[Korean Wrestling was the easiest...]
Danny Ahn might sweep the round!
Some people are just naturally strong.
Are they commentating also?
[Competition returns]
If you have a microphone,
you can commentate!
[Tae Min's form is very stable]
You never know with Tae Min!
[An unexpectedly even game.]
He watched and learned
from Kai's performance!
He's being very careful.
[Danny's ambush!]
[Team Original Idol will win points
if Tae Min loses!]
[But Tae Min endures!]
This is no joke!
One good thing that Danny is doing
is lowering his center.
Danny just pushed Tae Min because
he is smaller.
Tae Min still has some energy left in him!
You never know!
For a guy like Tae Min,
the right leg should go behind.
Are you still awake, Danny?
[Tae Min switches his feet.]
[Satisfied]
[Danny tries flipping!]
[But Tae Min stands again!]
I think they must be pretty
tired by now!
Let's give them a round of applause!
[Danny continues with an outside attack.]
[Tae Min defends with an inside flip.]
[It's hard to believe that
Tae Min is new to this!]
Tae Min managed to defend
two critical attacks.
Danny might need to use
more energy...
[Danny's critical attack!]
[Quick infiltration!]
[Concluding with a
combination of techniques!]
[Tae Min put up a good fight...]
[But Danny's experience wins!]
[Danny the Wrestling King!]
His experience triumphs!
Team Original Idol gets two points!
[Team New Idol gets one point
as second place!]
[Getting closer to
the Triangular Mystery.]
[Five dots...]
[Using five dots and seven lines...]
- Did you wash your hair again?
- You blowdried it again?
Your hair is indeed nice!
[His hair is his life.]
[Going to the next stage
to solve the Triangular Mystery!]
- What is it this time?
- It's a pool again.
The flying chairs...
[Is everyone ready to fly?]
Why did you even give us a break?
You really dragged everything
out of storage!
[Welcome to Flying World]
[Scared]
Make Hee Jun more comfortable!
I'm already taking good care of him!
He doesn't look like it at all!
You should look more at ease!
Your arm is so heavy...
I love seeing my boys!
You're the only one
who loves it!
You love seeing anyone,
no matter how old they are.
Everyone is exhausted by your presence.
[To Kkuk, they're just cute brothers.]
When Myung Hoon saw you down there,
he took a detour!
Tae Min is about to release
his first solo single!
Can we get a small taste of
his new song?
The song is called "Phantom Thief."
It'll be his first single.
It has to do well!
[Powerful!]
[Sharp dancing]
[Bad copycat]
[It'll be a hit!]
In the 90s, we had a dance move
per beat.
But he has managed to put
many moves into one beat.
As the senior of his
former management company...
I'm just very glad that
your first single isn't a rock song.
You can't change your identity
too quickly.
[I like rock!]
He's finally back!
How have you been managing?
It drove me crazy.
And Kai and Tae Min got very close
over eating chicken soup for lunch.
Tae Min used to be in the
same year as Kai.
But SHINee ended up debuting first,
then EXO started later...
It was such a sad story!
My tears made my chicken soup salty!
A bowl of teary chicken soup!
It was such a sad story!
But I assume he was at least
well fed.
Their lot is better than ours!
When these guys first started out,
they didn't even have enough food to eat!
That's why you need to let go of them!
I ate a bit too much!
Because you're pushing my shoulder,
the pressure can be felt all the way.
Why do you only pick on these two?
You don't really pick on them!
I'm about to move onto these guys.
[Kkuk is spreading his love]
You should've lasted a bit longer!
I love these guys!
I love this feeling!
My shoulder!
They haven't changed a bit ever since
when I met them when they were young!
How did you manage to keep your mystique
when H.O.T. was so popular?
All I had to do was this.
[All his mystique came from
hiding one eye.]
My shoulder!
That's why your hair is so
important to you!
If wind ever puts my hair down...
[Rocker instinct]
But if it goes like this...
[His hair can be used for comic relief!]
So what's the game?
The third stage of the Triangular Mystery...
[Wait for the epilogue to see why they're wet!]
The Flying Chair of Three Men!
This is about a pebble game
that was played by ancient Europeans.
I'll give a pebble to each team.
Decide if you want to put the pebble in
your right hand or not, then put it forward.
Then each team leader must guess how
many pebbles were put forward altogether.
The members of the teams that
say incorrect answers will be catapulted.
You're our hope, Ji Hyo!
[A lot of psychology is involved!]
Fighting!
[Player: Ji Hyo]
[Chair: Jae Suk]
[Player: Ji Won]
[Chair: Jong Kook]
[Player: Ha Ha]
[Chair: Kai]
Please play rock paper scissors
to decide who'll guess first.
Let's go around like this.
- Counter-clockwise?
- Yes.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Okay!
I can decide first!
[Ha Ha - Ji Won - Ji Hyo]
[Anxious]
[First Round of Psychology Warfare
with Pebbles!]
Get your right hand ready.
[Will they put the pebble in their
right hand or not?]
Please straighten your back.
One, two, three!
[It can be anywhere from zero to three.]
[The only thing they know is
what's in their own hand!]
[They must guess how many pebbles
are in their hands!]
His fist is pretty tight.
Two!
Is it me? [Rule: You can't repeat
the number that's already chosen.]
It's frustrating because
he called two first!
Very frustrating, indeed!
- It's between 0,1,3!
- It can't be zero!
- One!
- I'm feeling good about one!
[Only zero and three left]
What if no one gets it right?
They all might go into the water!
It can't be three.
Go with zero.
Don't say zero!
Do I have it or not?
Do you think I have it or not?
Only zero and three left...
Zero!
Please open your fist
on three.
I'm going to get sick...
- One!
- Is it zero?
Two!
Three!
[Ji Hyo wins!]
[And the teams that got it wrong...]
[Goodbye!]
[A goddess of fortune!]
[He survives]
I thought it was one.
[Each of their teams lost a member.]
Let's keep ourselves dry today!
Let's keep it dry today!
We'll keep ourselves dry today!
Next players, please.
[Danny and Tae Min]
The order is very important.
I'm going first now.
Let's make a miracle, Ji Hyo!
[Moving their hands to
confuse others.]
Can I get a blanket too?
[She decides if we get dumped into
the water or not!]
Are you turning her into a mummy?
I'm panicking...
One, two, three!
It's heavy.
[The shape of their fists
might be a hint!]
Ha Ha has only air
in his fist!
I can see it!
[Is Ha Ha faking it?]
[What would be the sum of
their pebbles?]
I'm going first.
Two.
She has one.
Definitely has one.
Ji Hyo must have it.
Three.
Really?
[It's certain that Ji Won has one.]
Then, one!
- Two, three, one.
- He doesn't have it!
I'm right!
[The front is guessing...]
[While the back is being nervous.]
Please!
We're losing our minds!
Hurry up!
If the sum is zero,
all three of you will fly!
I wanted to go into the water
a long time ago!
Please, one!
One, two, three!
[Ji Hyo wins!]
[Team New Idol and Team Original Idol
lose two players in a row!]
[Ji Hyo the Ace has done it again!]
Let's keep ourselves dry today!
She's too good at things like this!
She's amazing!
[You're great, Blank Ji!]
This is too nerve-racking.
Next players, please.
[Those teams only have two players left.]
[Just you wait]
Take it easy!
[These guys can tell whether
Ha Ha has it or not in one look!]
Try to guess it this time!
Since we've made it this far,
just win the whole thing!
[Pressured]
One, two, three!
Ha Ha has it this time.
His fist is way too tight!
He's too simple!
Ha Ha doesn't have one!
One.
She doesn't have one!
Are you sure?
Think again!
[Dilemma]
She said one?
[There's a larger possibility that she
said one because she doesn't have it.]
She said one without holding it.
Then I say two!
He has one!
I really was going to say zero.
One, two, and zero for me!
She doesn't have one,
and he's just wishing that both of us have them.
It might be one!
One, two, three!
[Ji Hyo Wins!]
[Blank Ji's miraculous winning streak!]
[Idols are flying together!]
[Team Original Idol and Team New Idol
lose three players in a row!]
[She's a scary woman...]
[Awesomeness!]
[Goosebumps!]
Can you read my fortune?
Will I be lucky next year?
[Blank Ji the Mind reader]
This is no joke!
[Ji Hyo is one victory away from a sweep.]
She may be my enemy,
but she's so great.
[A new fandom is arising.]
- Who is she?
- She has something.
We'll win if you get this!
[Soyou and Hee Jun are the last players]
She won't know if I hold it like this.
Or maybe like this.
I tried to guess from
Ji Hyo's perspective.
I got them all wrong.
[Fourth Round of Psychological Warfare]
- One, two, three!
- Keep helping me, Suk Jin!
This is crazy..
Oops.
Ha Ha has one.
[Winner goes first]
You need to become a fortune teller
if you get this one right!
Where are you looking at right now?
Can you tell by looking?
Where is she looking at?
Does Ha Ha have one?
Can you tell if I have one?
[Will Ji Hyo sweep?]
I think she's more sure about you.
Just say it!
Three.
What's with this girl?
[The probability of three is 12.5%...]
- What if it's three?
- I don't think it is!
If it's three, I'll kneel down!
It can't be three.
That means she has one.
- Ji Won?
- So she has one?
Think carefully!
Ji Won!
At least one!
[Thank you for stating the obvious.]
[Ha Ha keeps shaking his hand.]
Is it one?
Ha Ha is shaking because
he has one.
Two!
Good!
He has one!
This is crazy.
Just tell me if I'm flying or not!
Ji Hyo is a ghost!
Do you have one?
One!
I have no choice!
Wow, look!
Ji Hyo!
It'd be total nonsense
if it's three.
I'll have so much respect for you
Two...
Three!
[Ji Won Wins!]
- Ji Won won!
- I don't have to go?
[Hooray!]
He had one!
[What? He had one?]
- You dropped it!
- Dropped it where?
It's right here?
How would I drop it?
I don't know what you're talking about.
[What happened?]
Review the video!
Where did it go?
[Under review]
[Gary saw something!]
[The result of the video review is...]
[Moments ago...]
[A pebble!]
[He stretched his hand out
after throwing his pebble away!]
Ji Won won!
[Great chaos]
[Ji Won tried his best for this team.]
Everyone!
Hands can be quicker than eyes!
- Nonsense!
- No?
- We have to do it again!
- Void this round!
I opened my palm as requested!
How dare you second deal the pebble!
It's just a pebble!
Help me, Jong Kook!
But Ji Hyo is great.
She guessed them all!
[The mysterious woman who guess them all.]
I guessed them all!
For this round...
Team Running Idol wins!
Song Ji Hyo!
Let's keep ourselves dry today!
She really got them all right...
You're the best!
[The Mind Reader]
Kwang Soo is the only one
who guessed it right.
My own kind understands me!
As I said before, the only thing
left now is solving the actual mystery.
We'll give you different hints
depending on your points.
You can go ahead.
- Okay!
- How did she guess three?
Song Ji Hyo!
Can you believe this?
She's definitely weird!
This is the final mission of today.
[A walled castle]
Today's final mission is
solving the Triangular Mystery.
The doors through which you can
leave this castle are blocked right now.
The door will open automatically
once you solve the mystery.
The team that escapes the castle first
will be the winner.
As promised, I'll give different hints
depending on your points so far.
We're last.
The final score is three points
each for Running Idols and New Idols...
And two points for Original Idols.
[Hints are given in envelopes]
I'll tell you the mission now.
What if it's something math-related?
[Using five dots and seven lines...]
[Using five dots and seven lines,
make nine triangles.]
I hate things like this!
My head already hurts!
Please go ahead!
[Entering each team's room]
- Don't touch the dots.
- This was like this.
Like this?
[The two-point hint for
Team Original Idol.]
[Team Original Idol is making a W
per the hint.]
What's the hint?
[The three-point hint for
Team Running Idol.]
[W and a triangle]
[Team New Idol got the same hint
with their three points.]
I think I got it!
This is it.
[Enthusiastic]
[Tae Min is solving it without hindrance.]
- Make a triangle here...
- And here?
We have three triangles,
with seven sides.
We have to have nine triangles.
[Only three triangles...]
Nine? Really?
It'll be quicker to calculate it.
We only need to put three lines.
Just complete three lines.
Diagonally here...
That's too long.
And like this.
We have one, two, three,
four triangles.
With one more line here...
We can have seven...
Let's put it on first.
We have seven!
We need nine...
[The middle one is a rectangle...]
[Mr. Moon the Mysterious]
- So maybe one horizontally?
- Let's put one up here.
That gives us two.
Then what if...
How many are these?
One, two, three, four, five.
We must think simply.
You don't need this here.
If you put it down, you'll get an extra triangle.
[Giraffe sounding smart!]
By putting it there,
you'll get an extra triangle.
- Here's one.
- One, two, three...
[Five triangles with
one line to go.]
Six...
That's not a triangle.
[Yoo Hyuk's last stroke.]
That's not a triangle...
[Close! Eight triangles!]
Can we curve one of those lines?
- It can't be so complicated.
- I think it's probably very simple.
- I don't think this is it.
- It's not.
There's a clue in this.
This is the point.
This, right here.
So let's make this W first.
Should I go spy on other teams?
Don't move the magnets.
Look at this way...
[Soyou is going to spy on
other teams.]
[A mysterious shape for Team Running Idol.]
They made it like this.
With a line here.
With a line here,
and here.
So this line goes here...
They put two more lines
down here.
Wait a minute.
That's right!
Didn't we do this before?
Is this it?
Are we making a star inside?
[Is a star the key to this mystery?]
- Then we can just do this!
- That's right!
- But this isn't a triangle.
- Then take it out!
We can take it out!
That's right!
- Wait...
- This is not a triangle.
We got it!
We have nine triangles!
[Team New Idol has the answer!]
- This isn't a triangle...
- No, that's right.
[Only seven triangles]
I think it's related to the star.
This is empty.
We have nine triangles!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine!
No, this isn't a triangle!
[Frustration is causing them to see
a rectangle as a triangle.]
You startled me!
I thought you might be a genius!
Let's try it with here.
How many do we have?
We have eight!
Almost!
It might be similar to this...
Make an X here!
They're making an X here.
[Everyone's cheating off of each other]
How many do we have?
We have nine!
[Fails with eight triangles
and a rectangle.]
Just a moment, please.
Put it right here.
Right here!
- This will solve it.
- But this is still a rectangle.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine!
[Mysteriously, they all think
a rectangle is a triangle.]
I hate rectangles!
I'm sick of rectangles...
- That's good!
- No, this isn't it.
- One, two, three...
- Another triangle right here!
But these are not triangles.
This is driving me crazy.
[If you're stuck, take a sneak peak
at the room next door.]
They're behind us.
[Brain overload]
[And schizophrenia]
If we do this,
this still is a rectangle.
Why are you laughing?
You should try it!
It's not easy!
Do you know the answer?
Let's take some steps back.
Here...
- I think it's a star.
- Let's make it again.
This is a star.
My wife.
This isn't it.
This is driving me nuts!
[Schizophrenia is happening.]
Let's start from here.
We have three...
Let's think again...
- Let's think again.
- We can have three lines.
We only need three lines.
I think the longest one
should go up here.
It should go.
[These guys only need two more lines...]
[They have four triangles
with six lines.]
This way...
We had nine before!
No, we didn't.
[Big Nosed Brother puts the last line on.]
This isn't a triangle...
We have eight.
We need one more.
Can they give us
one more line?
It can happen with what we have...
Right here...
- In the middle...
- What if...
What'll happen if we move this?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight...
Nine!
We have nine!
We got it!
[Will they be able to escape the castle
by solving the mystery?]
We have nine!
[Nine triangles, completed!]
[The door is open!]
[They've escaped after solving the problem!]
[No way]
[Congratulations on your escape!]
- It's similar to ours!
- That's a rectangle!
Goodbye!
It's very similar to ours!
[We still have seven lines...]
[Tae Min is utilizing the beauty of curves.]
Since they opened the door,
let's all leave!
[I'm going to freeload!]
Goodbye!
How can they close it right here?
[Why were they wet before?]
[Soyou's Type World Cup!]
There'll no such thing as an interview.
You just fly!
Cheon Myung Hoon vs. Kang Gary!
Kang Gary!
[Kang Gary wins!]
[Awesome!]
- Ji Suk Jin vs. Kai!
- Kai!
[Kai wins!]
[Sorry, Big Nosed Brother!]
[Lee Kwang Soo Wins!]
[Hee Jun beat his rival, Ji Won!]
[Ha Ha wins!]
[What an upset!]
[The Turbo's power is still there!]
[Jong Kook wins!]
We have six people now.
Jong Kook vs. Hee Jun!
[Jong Kook wins!]
[Kwang Soo wins!]
[Ha Ha wins!]
And her final choice is...
[Well?]
Kim Jong Kook.
[Kim Jong Kook is Soyou's type!]
Shall I get Soyou's phone number?
Subtitles by DramaFever
The condition of the day and luck,
along with mental power and focus...
- You have to give everything.
- I'll bet everything I have!
[Putting the effort in to getting
the best talent of the industry.]
They're trying to find
the best closer of the country!
[From idols to
national athletes...]
[One grand scheme to
get their help!]
[The final round begins now!]
[The World's Largest Alkkagi Competition]
[Forget about everything you know
about alkkagi so far!]
[Drama that unfolds on top of
the Go table!]
[Black and White]
[The Life of One Game]
Subtitles by DramaFever