[Republic of Korea in the 21st century.
A self-portrait of a workers' life.]
[A morning commute's battle, and
the deal with the foreign buyers!]
[But an event of a lifetime
comes to find these workers...]
[Coming to you soon.]
[Living as a corporate employee
in the Republic of Korea means...]
[the bright morning sun comes to
find them every morning.]
[Which brings about another morning
commute into the office.]
[The battle of the morning commute.]
[A random Monday, Autumn 2014.]
[A new employee of 'R' Group,
Yoo Jae Suk- 43 years old.]
[Even though the same path
is traveled every morning...]
[Each morning commute brings on
new adventures for the day.]
I don't know what to expect.
[Morning commute train arrives at
Noksapyeong Station.]
What's this?
[Greeting the new employee on
the first day of his new job is...]
[a mission messenger machine?]
Click on the screen?
The morning commute is almost over,
but how are you handling it?
Although the morning commute can be brutal,
you know that being late isn't acceptable?
Managing to escape faster than other
new hires will give you a huge advantage at
the promotion review, so escape
the crowd as soon as possible!
Come out exit number four,
and press the touch button to win.
Exit number four?
[Mission start.]
[Morning commute is a battle against time-
Must start running.]
[Currently on sub terrain level five-
Must get up onto the fourth floor.]
Wait a minute.
[A huge crowd of young college students
rush down the stairs out of nowhere.]
Excuse me.
[First mission- Fight through the crowd of
college students to climb up the stairs.]
[The never-ending crowd of
college students.]
Excuse me.
[The usual morning and
evening commuting scene.]
[A physical battle at the train station
that gets repeated every single day.]
[In danger of being late to work already!]
What the heck is this!
[You've all been through
this experience, right?]
[What is this now?]
[Countless cleaners taking up
the whole hallway.]
[Second mission- Walk around the
cleaners to get through the hallway.]
Excuse me.
[All the sweeping and mopping doesn't
leave much room to get around.]
Why are you doing this to me?
[Rushing through the hallway
results in a big wipeout.]
- You should be more careful.
- Excuse me.
[Morning tap dancing around
the numerous brooms and mops.]
[Finally fights his way through the crowd.]
[Only to battle up the 70 flight of stairs.]
[Climb and climb again up the stairs.]
[Thank you for the cooperation of everyone
to enable safe taping of this segment.]
[Catching a sigh of relief?]
- Hi, you must be exhausted.
- Yes, I am.
[Is there some sort of an event going on?]
[Third mission- Your health is most important!
Gulp down a hot health drink in one shot.]
[The bitter tea!]
[The bitterness attacks!]
What are you doing to me!
[Why so many obstacles during
my busy morning commute?]
[Say goodbye to the case of the Mondays.]
- Chul Soo, is that you?
- Excuse me?
- Chul Soo, right?
- No, I'm not Chul Soo.
[Fourth mission- Evade the people who
mistake you for someone else.]
- Chul Soo, it's great to see you!
- I'm not Chul Soo.
[Why must I look like someone else
during my busy morning commute?]
[Gets through the numerous obstacles
and is one step closer to the exit.]
[But...]
[Oh my goodness!]
[Fifth mission- Pick up all the bottles that
the worker spills onto the floor.]
We need you to help us.
We're running late.
[One hectic morning commute.]
[If every morning commute was like this,
then going into work would be a real pain!]
Ugh, so bitter!
Do you have any water?
Ugh, that tea was so bitter.
[No water, just a bunch of empty bottles.]
- You should be more careful.
- Thank you for your help.
[Finally sees the exit.]
[One more level, and he
succeeds his morning mission.]
[Discovers exit number four.]
[Another huge flight of stairs.]
[A serious morning workout.]
[A shocking, but common reality for
Korea's morning commuters.]
[Worker Yoo's morning commute,
complete.]
[Unbelievably difficult
first morning commute.]
[And to think that it's only Monday...]
The train is pulling in right now.
[Who's the second new hire that's about
to experience their morning commute?]
[Second new hire-
Lee Kwang Soo, 30 years old.]
Hey, 'R' Group new hire!
[Kwang Soo also receives
the same mission.]
Although the morning commute can be brutal,
you know that being late isn't acceptable?
Late?
Managing to escape faster than other
new hires will give you a huge advantage at
the promotion review, so escape
the crowd as soon as possible!
It's an individual mission?
[Start!]
[The crowd of college students
begin to fill up the stairs.]
What is this?
[Gets flustered at the sight of
the oncoming crowd.]
Go to the right!
You have to go to the right!
[The once peaceful platform is immediately
transformed into absolute chaos.]
Where did you all suddenly come from?
[Worker Kwang successfully
passes his first mission.]
[Then immediately falls into
the second mission.]
[Fights his way through the crowd as
if jumping through the hurdles.]
Do you really need to go this far?
[Only the beginning of the second mission,
and Worker Kwang is feeling anxious already.]
I'm sorry.
Ma'am, please let me pass!
[Barely manages to pass the
second mission.]
[Time to climb up the 70 flights of stairs.]
I've never seen such
a tall flight of stairs before.
[An automatic sigh of distress.]
- Hello.
You must be tired.
Enjoy a nice cup of healthy drink.
Drink it all up.
- It's very good for your health.
- It should really revive your energy.
It's an herbal tonic.
[A shocking wake up call to his senses.]
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
[Entering the fourth mission.]
- Chul Soo.
- Excuse me?
- Aren't you Chul Soo?
- No, my name is Kwang Soo.
[What is it this time?]
[Completely befuddled from the realistic
acting from the man in the hiking gear.]
- Aren't you Chul Soo?
- No, I'm Kwang Soo.
My name is Kwang Soo!
[Just when he thinks he's
in the clear...]
[Don't ever let your guard down
during the morning commute.]
[Fifth mission starts in the midst
of his confusion.]
What is this?
You guys should've been
more careful!
I'll just be going now.
[Picks up the last bottle,
and clears the fifth mission.]
How many missions are there?
[A dead run towards exit number four.]
[Even though it may seem
like it's over...]
[The darned stairs!]
[Is this a morning commute or
a hiking adventure?]
[His workday hasn't even started,
and he already looks beat.]
[Worker Kwang's morning commute
is complete.]
[Extremely exhausting morning commute.]
That's the worst bitter tea
I've ever had to drink before.
[Third new hire, Ha Ha, recently
completed his own morning commute.]
[The three workers are left sitting
side-by-side while waiting for others.]
- Ha Ha's most curious about Suk Jin.
- I'm so curious to see how Suk Jin does.
- I wish I were Suk Jin.
- You're a fan of Suk Jin, aren't you?
- I'm also a fan of his.
- I'm a total fan of his.
I really filled up those tea cups
before I left.
Good job. You got it
ready for the next player?
[A few minutes prior.]
I don't think that was enough bitter tea.
Can you really fill up the cup
for the next person?
[A full cup of the bitter tea
for the next person.]
Are you aware that the cooler the tea
gets, more bitter it becomes?
- How about another cup of tea for the road?
- No, I'm fine.
No, I'm fine.
- That's so you.
- You're the dirtiest player I know.
[This man would definitely survive
the tough corporate world.]
[The arrival of the next new hire.]
[Who will it be?]
[Could it be the person
that they've all been waiting for?]
[Fourth new hire, Ji Suk Jin.]
- I'm a new hire at 'R' Group.
- Suk Jin!
[It's Suk Jin!]
[Dreams do come true!]
Ji Suk Jin.
It's Big-nose time!
It's finally starting!
I have to start now?
Where's exit number four?
Wow, as soon as the mission starts...
[Worker Big-nose also gets barraged
by the mob of college students.]
[Swept away by the mob and
climbs back down the stairs.]
He's being pushed back down!
[Big-nose Brother never
disappoints his fan club.]
Why are you coming down
the steps this way?
Wow, this morning commute is no joke!
This is what morning commute is like?
[First mission clear.
Time to enter the second mission.]
Why are you putting so much
effort into cleaning?
He got smacked on the shins.
[Like an Impala
prancing through the pastures.]
Where's exit number four?
Suk Jin is moving faster
than I thought he would.
I think the tea mission
is going to take some time.
Wait, where did my scarf go?
[Taking forever just to get
to the tea mission...]
Wow, this is exhausting.
[Finally arrives at the tea mission.]
No, I don't want any.
I don't want any!
[Who says you have a choice?]
- Have a cup of tea before you go.
- Drink this, and you'll feel much better.
[I filled up the cup before I left.]
Ouch, that's hot!
- I really filled up that cup.
- Here it comes.
Wow, morning commute is exhausting.
- This is good for my health?
- Yes, it is.
[Benefits of the bitter tea- Improves
lung functions and helps clear up the skin.]
[Gulps it down in one shot after
hearing that it's good for his health.]
- He's feeling it now.
- It's worse when you're out of breath.
- I couldn't believe how bitter it was.
- It was the most bitter thing I've ever had.
I thought I was going to die, too.
- This part really annoyed me.
- This mission was annoying for me, too.
Having to tell them that I'm not Chul Soo
when my mouth tasted so bitter...
- Chul Soo, what are you doing here?
- I'm not Chul Soo.
- Where are you going?
- I have to get to work.
- No, I'm not Chul Soo.
- Wait, you're not Chul Soo?
No, I'm not Chul Soo.
Great to see you, Chul Soo!
Don't you recognize me, old friend?
- You look much older than me.
- Don't you remember me?
This is great!
Those ladies are doing great!
They're doing great!
My name is Ji Suk Jin!
[Worker Big-nose clears his fourth mission,
and enters the fifth mission.]
What are you doing?
What are you guys doing?
Why are you spilling everything?
- I'm so busy right now.
- We're busy, too.
Wow, look at his acting
in front of the cameras.
He's not acting like himself.
[Big-nose is disappointing his fan club
with his show of kindness.]
You guys can pick up the rest.
[Where do you think you're going?]
[Barely manages to clear his fifth mission,
and now heads towards exit number four.]
My mic is falling off.
Here's the exit.
I'll finally be able to make it to work.
[As predicted... taking
forever to climb up the stairs.]
[Stays on his course with the
determination to make it into work.]
This is it.
[Worker Big-nose completes
his morning commute.]
[The heart of a new hire, and
the physique of a senior manager.]
[New hire's legs gives up on him
on his way into the office.]
Come on, hurry!
Excuse me, ladies.
[The three are in a sudden rush.]
Come on, let's go together.
Let's all go together.
Kim Jong Kook's coming, so be prepared.
- Kim Jong Kook's coming.
- Grab him, pull him, do whatever you must.
[The sudden onset of nervous energy.]
[At last, he's on his way...]
[Worker Kkuk also receives
the same mission.]
[Start the mission!]
- Don't be afraid.
- If we crumble now, then it's all over.
- Everyone has to stay on their toes.
- Everyone, link your arms together!
[Operation 'Obstruct Worker Kkuk's
morning commute' begins.]
[Army of backpacking college students
and the three man army heads out.]
Exit number four?
Okay, up these stairs.
[What is this?]
[An onslaught of hurried college students.]
No, this way.
Everyone to the left.
Why are you doing this?
What is this!
[It's three against one-
Focused on detaining Worker Kkuk.]
Wait, this isn't over yet?
[Worker Kkuk- First mission, clear.]
What's the use of going down there
when he'll just barrage his way through?
Thank you for your hard work.
[Takes off to obstruct the next mission.]
- I'm so sorry.
- No, not us.
No, it's not us.
[The three man army is also being
put through the second mission again.]
[Worker Ha shoves the trash can.]
[Worker Kwang bodily pushes the trash can
into Worker Kkuk's path.]
[Worker Yoo directs all the ladies into
Worker Kkuk's pathway.]
No, it's not me.
The other way, not me.
Sorry, Ma'am.
Where's exit number four?
[In the midst of all this, Worker Kkuk calmly
works his way through the second mission.]
[The three-man army successfully
delays Worker Kkuk's mission time.]
- We've delayed him at least ten seconds.
- We did good.
If we hadn't done anything, he
would've just shoved his way through.
I'm sorry, excuse me!
[Sixth new hire-
Song Ji Hyo, 34 years old.]
Please excuse me.
[Quickly passes through the first mission.]
[And jumps right into second mission
without any hesitation.]
[Fast footwork allows her to quickly
avoid all the cleaning tools in her path.]
I'm sorry!
[Worker Kkuk downs his shot
of the bitter tea... and succeeds.]
- I can feel myself getting stronger!
- Ugh, I'm so sick and tired of him.
[Worker Blank also takes on
the bitter tea challenge.]
It's the bitter tea!
I'm so out of breath and thirsty,
and bitter tea is what I get?
- Ugh, that was so bitter!
- Good luck!
- Chul Soo, is that you?
- No, I'm not Chul Soo.
- No, it is you!
- I'm going to go out of my mind!
- I'm not Chul Soo!
- Have you changed your looks?
No, I haven't.
- Young Hee, where are you going?
- Excuse me? My name is Ji Hyo.
- Ma'am, my name is Ji Hyo.
- Chul Soo, what are you doing here?
I told you that my name isn't Chul Soo.
Chul Soo and I must look alike.
[Worker Blank is already
onto her fifth mission.]
What is this?
Ugh, what is this?
You, youngsters...
why are you so bad at your jobs?
Hurry up and pick them up!
Hurry!
[Mr. Capable and Ace fly through
their missions, as predicted.]
Why couldn't some of those bottles
roll down the stairs?
- They should've beat him up with those.
- Good luck!
[All missions cleared.
Blank Ji rushes towards exit number four.]
Why is the morning commute so difficult?
[Kkuk power in full mode! Flies up
the flight of stairs in one breath.]
Hello.
[The polite new hire manages to greet
the elders even in the midst of her commute.]
[Worker Kkuk's morning commute, complete.]
[The morning commute proves difficult
for even Mr. Capable and Ace.]
[Worker Blank soon follows suit,
and completes her own morning commute.]
- Here she is.
- There you are.
- Did you all finish it?
- Yes, of course.
- My legs are shaking.
- My legs were shaking, too.
- There he is.
- There's Gary.
Isn't that Eung-Sam?
[What does Gary look like
in his transformation?]
[The final new hire-
'Eung-Sam' Kang Gary, 37 years old.]
[So awkward looking.]
[Oh... is this a mission?]
Don't click the mouse,
and just touch the screen.
How the world has changed.
The morning commute is almost over,
but how are you handling it?
I hope we get to see Gary
in his focused mode.
- I can see Gary in that mode.
- Where, exit number four? Do I start now?
Do I start now?
[Run full speed ahead
without any hesitation.]
[Steadily works his way through
the army of college students.]
Wait, I have to get to work!
Where did all you people come from?
[Worker Gae clears the first mission.]
[Flies into his second mission.]
I have to get to work!
Please!
[Gets through the crowd
in record breaking time!]
- Wow, he's really fast.
- How is he so fast?
- He squeezed through the corner.
- He's moving really fast.
[Even climbs up the 70 flights of stairs
in the blink of an eye.]
I have no strength left in my legs.
- Hello.
- You must be so tired.
- Why don't you have a cup of this tea?
- No, I have to get going.
[Since he's told to drink it,
he tries to gulp it down in a rush.]
- You have to finish it.
- It's so bitter! What is this?
[It's a healthy cup of bitter tea.]
- I'm already healthy.
- You have to finish the tea.
[Even those watching the scene can
relieve the bitter taste of the tea.]
Gary's still much quicker
than I thought he'd be.
- I think Gary has the best time.
- I think he's the fastest one of us all.
- It's me, So Hyun.
- No, you've got the wrong person!
[Making it to work on time
is all I care about right now!]
No, I'm Gary!
I'm just Gary!
[Worker Gae flies through
his fourth mission.]
Why is the morning commute
so exhausting?
[Okay, here we come!]
[Time for the fifth mission.]
[Attempts to ignore and just run past it.]
[Crushed by reality.]
[Attempts his second escape.]
[But forcefully gets detained
for the second time.]
- He's trying to run away.
- He's running away.
[Worker Gae's single minded determination
brings a huge round of laughter.]
[Let me just get to work!]
Okay, I'm leaving!
Good day!
[After a polite saying of farewell,
heads straight towards exit number four.]
[Please let there be an escalator...]
Ugh, more stairs!
[Still starts to climb
without any hesitation.]
[Worker Gae completes his morning commute.]
[Worker Gae completes his
commute faster than others.]
Wow, that was really exhausting.
I don't think I can do this job.
I don't think I'm cut out
for this commuting thing.
[Your first morning commute is your last?]
Thanks for the effort you all
put into your morning commute.
Morning commute is a battlefield.
I have so much respect for all those
who make the commute every morning.
Today's race will allow you to experience
the lives of Korea's office workers
in a race called,
The Workers' Super Race.
The member with the best results from
each round of missions
will be given a promotion mission, which will
allow them to go onto the final mission.
For the final promotion mission...
bets will be made on the member whom the
real employees will be cheering on to win.
[Employees will bet on Running Man members.]
The final winner and those who cheered for
the winner will win an exceptional prize.
You will also be given the chance
to advance yourselves.
Ha Ha's commuting time
will be announced first.
- Okay, what's his record?
- Everyone was too aggressive for my turn.
- What was his time?
- Ha Ha's time was, 4 minutes and 46 seconds.
[Worker Ha-
Four minutes and 46 seconds.]
We don't know who had the best time yet.
- Worker Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yes.
- Four minutes...
- I thought he was faster!
and 11 seconds.
- That's not much of a difference.
- He's currently in first place.
For Worker Lee Kwang Soo,
his time was, four minutes...
- Wow, he's that close?
- And 14 seconds.
[Worker Kwang-
Four minutes and 14 seconds.]
[Worker Yoo maintains his first place spot
by a mere three second difference.]
- That's funny, I won.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Only a three second difference.
- Worker Ji Suk Jin...
[Worker Big-nose...
Five minutes and 25 seconds.]
[The unchallenged last place.]
Everyone seriously worked really
hard to obstruct my way.
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Four minutes...
- He's in the four minute mark, too?
- Four minutes 48 seconds.
- You're still in first place!
[Worker Yoo is in the current lead with
the time of four minutes and 11 seconds.]
- Our plan worked!
- It's because you guys interfered.
- Coming in at first place is what matters.
- Yes, it doesn't matter otherwise.
Worker Song Ji Hyo.
- Four minutes...
- Ji Hyo's in the four minute range, too?
- Four minutes and 47 seconds.
- What is this!
- What the heck?
- What if I really win first place?
- Ji Hyo was fast though.
- Were you really that fast?
- I don't know about Gary though.
- Worker Gary...
- He took too long at the last mission.
- He wasted time with those bottles.
- He was really fast though.
- Was he faster than Jae Suk?
- Four minutes...
- Wait, did Jae Suk have 11 seconds?
Tell us what the last number is.
Just the final ending number.
- Two.
- If it's 12 seconds, then I'll win.
[Unless it's two seconds,
Worker Yoo wins regardless.]
Worker Gary's time was four minutes...
[What is Gary's record?]
Four minutes and two seconds.
[Four minutes and two seconds.]
- Can you guys be happy for me?
- Why are you shouting?
I feel like I'm the only one
happy about this.
[Worker Gae wins the morning commute
mission and thus gets promoted.]
- Let's just get going.
- There's a bus for our commute.
[A commuting bus will be used as
their means of transportation.]
- We're all coworkers.
- Are you sure you're not my senior?
No, we're not seniors or
juniors to each other yet.
[Gary is given a chance at a promotion at the
final mission for winning the first round.]
Where are we going now?
- Off to another mission, I'm sure.
- People who have to do that commute...
- They really need to be commended.
- That's what most people do every morning.
Just climbing up those stairs
exhausted me.
That's why we slept
in the classroom every morning.
I bet it's exhausting for them.
[Second mission- The art of flattery]
'I love you, Director.'
What is this?
Welcome to your second mission,
A flattery convention.
- Flattery?
- It's a welcoming rally for the new director.
You have to participate in the game
according to how the director wants it.
[The new director of 'R' Group-
Choi Hyun Ho.]
[A former national handball player.]
[Have made appearances on variety shows,
dramas, and even movies and now, in RM.]
- Welcome, Director.
- Hello, Director.
- Hyun Ho?
- Yes, hello.
[It's been a while, Worker Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Let's see how well you do!
Calling all workers to attention!]
Director!
- I started the chant.
- He has a way of making me feel awkward.
- I was born in 1985, so don't feel that way.
- Congratulations, Director!
[Worker Kwang bows down in determination
not to lose out to anyone.]
- I like him the best.
- Is that the sort of thing you like?
- That's what you like, huh?
- I'll give it my best effort.
I was recently brought onto this position
and there seems to be some negative talk
about the fact that I'm still so young
and was a former athlete.
- No, not at all. Who's saying that?
- I won't let them get away with it!
You're only here because you've proven
you had the skills for the position.
- We won't stand for this slander.
- Someone got you this position, right?
[What? He got the job
through connections?]
- What are you talking about?
- He's the one who started the rumors.
That mouth of his!
That's how we all got in here!
[Worker Yoo's big word stumble.]
Let's move past the fact that you're my
subordinates and that I'm your superior
- and just have a great time together.
- Sounds great! I'm ready for some fun!
- Wow, you're so handsome.
- He's so cool, too.
[Rally prizes- Kimchi fridge, digital camera,
and mixed coffee set.]
A real kimchi fridge?
Your first category is, sit-ups.
The winner will be determined by who does
the most amount of sit-ups in 30 seconds.
- Sit-ups?
- Something I'd like to mention...
is the fact that I actually have my eyes
on the third place winner's prize.
[The prize that the Director
has his eyes on.]
- I don't have a very refined taste buds.
- We need the director to come in third.
We can't come in at first place,
but need to come in at third place.
I really want to come in at third place.
- I hope you're not burdened by this.
- Yes, I understand.
[Feeling extremely burdened.]
I feel like the Director is
going to be really good at this.
I'll just buy you the mixed coffee set.
I really don't like flattery.
You can't try to help me on this, okay?
How can we do this and
not make it look obvious?
- Okay, I'm going to get started.
- Okay.
- I'll hold onto your legs for you.
- Wow, you really are the best.
- Thank you.
- I knew I liked you for a reason.
- Ugh, seriously.
- Don't forget about third place, Kwang Soo.
- Seriously... Just take your time.
- Okay.
- 30 seconds.
- Get ready... start!
- One, two, three...
- Take it easy.
You should take it easy.
You said you wanted the third place.
[Sit-ups at full speed.]
- Eight, nine...
- At this rate, you'll come in at first place!
- We're in trouble.
- Why are you doing it so fast?
- You don't have to do it like this.
- I have a bad back already.
- 18, 19...
- My back isn't at its best right now.
- Do you have something against us?
- Why are you doing it to this extent?
[We're ruined.]
- 28, 29, 30, 31...
- What is this!
- He's doing more than one sit-up per second?
- He's not slowing down one bit!
- 35, 36...
- Stop. He has 36.
[Director Choi Hyun Ho succeeds
in getting 36 sit-ups.]
How are you going to get third place
when you do it like that?
Then how many do we have to do?
37 of them?
[There needs to be two people who
can beat the Director's record.]
You do it, Gary.
You should go first.
- We have to succeed right away.
- You're not planning something, are you?
We have to succeed right away, and
not make it look obvious when we fail.
[Worker Kwang's idea- Succeed right away,
then fail without making it look obvious.]
- You have to do a good job.
- Worker Gae, do a good job, okay?
- You have to do your best.
- You need to do 37 sit-ups.
Even if your stomach rips,
you still have to do it.
- Do it no matter what it takes.
- Even if my stomach rips, I'll still do it.
- Worker Gae, you need to get 37.
- It's been a while since I've done this.
He's good at this.
- My shirt feels tight around here.
- Why would you say it like that?
[Director Choi seems to be in a good mood
and breaks out into a big smile.]
Set, go!
[Speedy!]
Gary's seriously so ugly.
[I don't care if this makes me look ugly
as long as it makes Director Choi happy.]
You need to do it faster!
- You have to do this!
- Faster!
[At this rate... he might actually beat him!]
[Current standing.
Choi Hyun Ho- 36. Gary- 34.]
[Even though I did it until
I felt I was lit on fire...]
He did a great job.
I don't think Director Choi
will get third place.
I don't think Director Choi is
going to come in at third place.
We need to get Director Choi
his coffee mix!
Ji Hyo, why don't you try it?
Ji Hyo's really fast.
[Worker Blank is more trustworthy than
this group of male workers?]
- Hi Hyo, we need 37.
- We're in trouble if Ji Hyo can't do this.
- Ji Hyo, you have to do this.
- I will do my best.
- Give it your best.
- Start!
[Worker Blank's woodpecker imitation.]
[May be cheating a bit, but still
attempts to surpass the 36 mark.]
- She looks like a woodpecker.
- She may even surpass the 100 mark.
[The victory is right in front of her eyes!]
- 38, 39, 40!
- You did it!
[Worker Blank succeeds with 39 sit-ups.]
Even though it's a bit embarrassing,
we still did it.
[Current standing:  Song Ji Hyo- 39.
Choi Hyun Ho- 36, Gary- 34.]
Yes, very impressive.
- Yes, that was a great job.
- She gave it her best effort.
[Just one more person to surpass the 36
mark to get Director Choi his coffee mix.]
- Wow, this could be embarrassing.
- You have a shorter distance to go up.
- You might be able to do it.
- Good.
Good, ready... go!
[Worker Ha is giving it his best.]
[I will sacrifice my body for
Director Choi's happiness.]
Is he being fast with this?
[Exhaustion sets in.]
[Already at the end of his wits...]
[Just a little bit more!]
It's not over yet.
34!
[Worker Ha succeeds in getting
33 sit-ups.]
- It's because he got too excited.
- That's his show of excitement.
[Whatever the case,
Director Choi is still in second place.]
You must've liked doing sit-ups.
- He really likes it.
- I never knew he liked it so much.
[Worker Ha can liven up
any atmosphere.]
[Worker Ha is the best!]
[Worker Yoo succeeds in getting 30.]
- Worker Kim Jong Kook's in great shape.
- Yes, he is.
Worker Kim Jong Kook is our last hope.
- Come and help support us!
- Okay, ready!
- Don't be shy to cheer him on!
- You have to get 37.
- Set, go!
[Speedy as predicted!]
Wow, he's so fast!
[Nice, Worker Kkuk!]
[Worker Kkuk's lightning fast pace!]
[We can do this!]
Just seven more!
1, 2, 3, 4...
[I vow to succeed!]
[Worker Kkuk succeeds in getting 38!]
[Task complete-
Director Choi comes in at third place.]
[Current standing: Song Ji Hyo- 39.
Kkuk- 38, Director Choi- 36.]
[Mr. Capable even in the corporate world!]
- I can't even move my neck.
- Who cares? Director Choi got third place.
- Get him out of the way.
- Good job!
The game is over, so get up. How dare
you sprawl out in front of the director?
[Cruel corporate world-
Worker Kkuk is met with hostility already.]
- Worker Kwang, it's your turn.
- No need to get 40 now.
- Why don't you try going for 37?
- I don't like effortless attempts.
- No, I'd never do that.
- None of us in here would do that.
- I will give it my best.
- Fighting, Kwang Soo.
[Just needs to get less than 36.]
Director Choi doesn't like
effortless attempts.
- Wow, look at how handsome he looks.
- That's a nice look on his face.
[Worker Kwang, you can slow down now...]
- Slow down or you'll do 30.
- You're approaching 30.
That's enough.
[A warning to Worker Kwang to
stop working so hard at it.]
[Enough, dummy!]
Grab his head!
- Let me go, I'm going to do this!
- Grab his head!
[Giraffe, on the verge of an explosion.]
[Director Choi is so happy to
win his mixed coffee set.]
[Worker Kwang succeeds in getting 35.]
[All my co-workers did such a great job.]
Great job everyone.
[Succeeds in having Director Choi
coming in at third place.]
Here's your next category-
Ball tossing.
You have to throw the ball to knock down
the most number of bottles to win.
- Director Choi used to be a handball player.
- This is too greatly in his favor.
[This puts us at a huge disadvantage.]
[1st- Overseas vacation, 2nd- Coffee machine,
3rd- Napa cabbage kimchi.]
- No, can't be...
- You all know what I want, right?
- Yes.
- We have tons of kimchi at home for you.
My family is into farming napa cabbages.
I had a feeling you'd like kimchi,
so I have a whole box of it out in the car.
But I still want the kimchi prize.
- Why is he being like this?
- Seriously... why is he like this?
The kimchi smells so delicious right now.
Is this what stress is really like?
- Work stress?
- It just smells so good.
[Does the former national handball
player still have his skills?]
[Only ten balls-
How many bottles will he get?]
- That was...
- He hit that right on.
- He was dead on with his accuracy.
- You have to leave us a chance.
[A bulls eye on two out of the ten bottles.]
- Why don't you take it easy?
- Excuse me?
Sorry, that was my mistake.
[Four bottles in a row.]
Just take it easy!
[This won't do!
We need to disrupt him.]
No, Director Choi!
[Plans to disrupt succeeds.]
[Four bottles down, and fails one.]
[Re-focuses on task at hand.]
[Fails to break his focus, and he
succeeds in knocking down his 7th.]
You're having too much fun with this.
It's been awhile since I've held a ball,
and this is making me so happy right now.
You should've just worked harder
when you had the chance.
[Final count- Director Choi succeeds
in knocking down seven out of the ten.]
- Director Choi, we'll take our turn now.
- Fighting.
Come on, Jae Suk.
[Worker Yoo fails first of the ten.]
No need to throw it too hard.
[Knocks one down and fails one.]
There you go!
[Knocks two down and fails one.]
- Jae Suk, I knew you could do it.
- You're doing great.
Worker Yoo has the feel for it.
[Knocks two down and fails three.]
I need to kill two birds with one stone.
[In order to knock down more than seven,
he needs to knock two down with one throw.]
Put a little spin in your throw.
[Please hit the bottle!]
[Fail]
Don't get angry at it!
- Just have fun with it.
- What's wrong with you?
[Worker Yoo explodes.]
What's wrong with you?
Stop it!
I'm going to quit this job!
I'm so angry right now!
I'm too angry to keep working here!
- I'm going to quit this company!
- What are you doing in front of the Director?
I need to just quit this job!
Why are we just playing games
instead of working?
- Worker Yoo's got a temper.
- He's trying to calm down.
I'm here to work, not play games!
[Director Choi is on the move.]
- Yes, I understand what you're feeling.
- I'm so sorry for my outburst.
- I'm just so angry.
- I'm sorry.
- Get yourself some water.
- I'm going to keep working for this company.
Thank you for that.
- I'll go this time.
- Okay!
[All-around sportsman,
Worker Kkuk, to the challenge.]
- Okay.
- Concentrate.
[But fails.]
- Throw it harder, Jong Kook.
- What's wrong with this guy?
- You have to throw it harder.
- This is stressing me out again.
Wow, he's really awful at it.
This is so aggravating!
[Worker Yoo's on a rampage.]
- Ugh, this is so aggravating!
- Director Choi is watching!
[The rally turns into an utter chaos.]
[I don't even care about this
job anymore!]
[Director Choi is just
coolly enjoying the show.]
- I'm sorry, Director Choi.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
[Current standing: Choi Hyun Ho- 7,
Yoo Jae Suk- 2; Kim Jong Kook- 0.]
- I was just angry at myself.
- Okay, I can do this!
[Only Worker Blank succeeds in getting 8,
and Director Choi is still in second place.]
- You can do this.
- Ready...
[Worker Big-nose is their last hope.]
- I don't think what he's doing is right.
- That doesn't look right to me.
[A direct hit!]
I think he's got the feel for this.
[Worker Big-nose's surprising start.]
I think I can do this.
- That has to appear larger to you.
- Don't talk to me right now.
Are you getting annoyed
with us right now?
[Knocks down his second bottle
in a row!]
I guess that actually works.
[Big-nosed Brother's lucky day.]
This is Suk Jin's day to shine this year.
- He's got the feel for it now.
- He looks good.
- Look at how focused he is.
- Maybe he really will get it.
[The ball misses its mark...]
- No, you've still got it.
- We're still good, let's keep it up.
- We've still got a chance, right?
- We're still good. You can do this.
You can do this!
[Perfect]
['R' Group's very own Wilhelm Tell.]
- You're doing great.
- Looking good.
- That bottle has to look larger in size.
- Can you just stop talking?
[Sorry...]
Don't talk when I'm about to
take my shot.
[Knocks down three and fails two.]
- He still has a chance.
- He can do this.
[Big-nose's sixth ball.]
[Fails again.]
[No more room left to fail!]
- Try throwing it from an angle.
- I think throwing it from an angle can do it.
[Knocks down four and fails three.]
- Wow, this is...
- Please!
[Knocks down his fifth target in a row.]
[A day like this comes to find Big-nose
about once  a year.]
[Let's take this all the way today!]
I can't believe this.
Suk Jin's actually good at something.
[Big-nose's ninth ball.]
Try knocking all those three down
at once. You never know.
- Okay.
- It may work.
[He's on a roll, so a
miracle may actually happen...]
No, just do it like this and
knock them all down.
- I have a feeling you may get it.
- I think you can get it, too.
Will the god of variety shows
smile down on you today?
- Will he have luck on his side?
- He will be saving all of us.
Please.
[Three birds with one stone...]
[Please let there be a miracle.]
[Only manages to get one, thus
a total of six hits and four misses.]
[Director Choi fails to win
his third place prize of the kimchi.]
- This has been so fun.
- I had a real great time.
- This was a great time.
- I'm so happy to be here at this company.
- But what did you say earlier?
- I couldn't control my emotions earlier.
Since I did come in at third place once,
I would like to reward you for it.
[Director Choi's reward!]
Director Choi!
I have prepared seven envelopes
and the one with the biggest cash prize
in the envelope wins first place.
Is it totally random then?
You're so fun!
[One step above flattery.]
On the count of three, you can all go up
there and grab the envelope you want.
- This is a competition in itself.
- I'm going to get promoted!
One, two, three!
[Worker Big-nose takes a nose dive
in any sort of competition.]
- Don't you think you're being too harsh?
- Don't you think that you're too harsh?
- You can't grab it and set it back down.
- Seriously.
Give it to me.
[In the face of a promotion,
everyone's your enemy.]
- What do you have?
- 20,000 Won.
[Worker Big-nose has 20,000 Won.]
It's not much of a difference.
- I have 30,000 Won.
- 30,000 Won?
- So yours was more?
- How much do you have?
- I have 40,000 Won.
- I have 10,000 Won.
- 70,000 Won must be the winner.
- I have three.
Four, five, six, seven!
[Worker Ha with 70,000 Won.]
- Okay, we got it.
- Six, seven!
I only have 60,000 Won.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
[Worker Ha wins a chance
at a promotion.]
I will become a helpful
addition to this company.
All I feel is aggravated ever since
I started with this company.
I'm just going to go into broadcasting.
[What is their next mission?]
[In just a few...]
[Something completely unimagined...]
[The final promotion mission will
soon be revealed.]
Two, one!
[The shocking twist of events
will soon come your way!]
[Third mission- Negotiation battle.]
[Off to the next mission without
even a moment of breather.]
Where are we now?
Here's your brief announcement.
The negotiation meeting with
the buyers will soon take place.
All employees must report to
the conference room on the first floor.
A meeting with the buyers?
- Is it a real meeting?
- It looks like a real meeting.
[Feels as though a real meeting
is about to take place.]
Please get a hold of your temper and do
your best to win a chance at a promotion.
[Who are the buyers that they'll
have to go up against?]
[Formidable physique and exotic appearance.]
[The formidable buyers are on their way.]
- Are the buyers about to come in?
- Who are the buyers?
Oh my.
[Foreigners!]
Brad?
[Familiar faces from TV?]
- You guys know how to speak Korean, right?
- No.
I know Fabien can understand me.
What is he saying?
[These are the foreign buyers.]
- We're here to make business.
- Business.
We're here to sign the contract,
and no dropping the honorifics.
[The formidable looking foreign buyers.]
These men are all famous and
are familiar faces on TV.
To introduce these men,
first we have, Jake.
[An entertaining young man who is a
familiar face already in the variety world.]
- He's been in Korea for four years.
- My name is Jake, and I'm from England.
[Buyer from England, Jake.]
You're on the show, 'Hi honey', aren't you?
[Elite son-in-law, on the show,
'One hundred year's guest', Husband Ma.]
He's Husband Ma.
[American buyer, Mark Taylor.]
- You're a fitness trainer?
- Yes.
[Behind the gentle smile
is the body of a steel.]
As you may all know, Chris is
a well-known commercial actor.
[American buyer, Chris Jones.]
- What's your background?
- I'm a homemaker.
You're a homemaker?
I make various appearances on TV,
and I'm also taking some classes.
- You graduated from a military school?
- He's the best arm wrestler of his class.
[A man with immense strength.]
- John, can you introduce yourself?
- John is so good looking.
Hello.
[German buyer, John Rosenthal.]
- Are you mixed?
- Yes, my parents are German and Korean.
[Handsome, John, with parents from
both Korean and German background.]
- He was born in Germany.
- Yes, I was. Where were you born?
Schulte Garte?
What did you say?
- What is he saying?
- I mean, Stuttgart.
I'm sorry, but your
pronunciation is really strange.
He's second level Taekwondo.
I won second place
in a Taekwondo competition.
Fabien also practices Taekwondo.
[Fitness trainer, National Taekwondo athlete,
Military arm wrestler, Taekwondo.]
And as for Craig, he's quite the singer.
[Soulful singer who's singing talents have
been recognized on various stages.]
- I really want to hear him sing.
- Can you sing something real quick?
[Sings the famed, 'I miss you',
with a twist of R&B.]
[American buyer, Craig Priester.]
As for Brad, I think everyone's
already pretty familiar with who he is.
- He's a drummer, isn't he?
- Hello.
[Busker Busker's charismatic drummer.]
[American buyer, Brad.]
- Your wife is Korean, isn't she?
- No, she's American.
Don't speak if you don't even
know what you're talking about.
[Don't make such silly mistakes in
front of an important buyer like him!]
We're already familiar with Fabien,
who hails from France.
[A foreigner with a previous
experience of being on Running Man.]
[A French buyer, Fabien.]
The sole reason for me coming here today
is to eliminate Lee Kwang Soo.
- I've already apologized to you for that.
- That doesn't matter.
[The painful experience of having been
betrayed by the Giraffe.]
Here's your brief announcement.
A negotiation game of name tag elimination
will now start with the foreign buyers
over the grave matters of determining just
who will win the next chance at a promotion.
- That is just absurd!
- This is unfair, he's a fitness trainer!
The employees must eliminate
the foreign buyers' name tags
and sign their eliminated name tags
to successfully conclude the negotiation.
Only when all the foreign buyers' name
tags are eliminated and signed
will the negotiation
be successfully concluded.
The surviving employee with the most
signed name tags in the end wins this mission.
- Are they serious?
- This is too unfair.
Mark is a fitness trainer,
and Fabien also practices Taekwondo.
There are also Chris,
and John to consider, too.
[Most formidable foreign buyers
they've yet to encounter.]
Name tag elimination with the negotiation for
the final promotional chance will now begin.
['R' Group employees vs Foreign buyers.]
[Negotiation name tag elimination game-
Start.]
[Running Man employees
have stepped out of the room.]
There are no rules. You just
have to rip their name tags off.
[Full of confidence.]
[Buyers, go!]
- Buyers, go!
- Fighting!
[Buyers are on the move,
full of confidence.]
We can ambush them and oust
at least two members, can't we?
- Should I lure them in to you guys?
- Okay, sounds good.
- Lure them over to me.
- Okay, good luck to you guys.
[Buyers are on the prowl
for the 'R' Group employees.]
Fighting!
Since you're bigger,
you should go first.
It's Mark!
[Mark looks ready to face a battle.]
[Without even a moment of hesitation.]
[Eliminates Gary's name tag
in the blink of an eye.]
Why am I having such hard time with
name tag elimination these days?
[Worker Gae breaks the negotiation.]
[Just then, Worker Blank faces off with
Taekwondo Master, John.]
[Sorry, but there's nothing
I can do for you.]
[Got it... no, he's got her!]
[Worker Blank breaks the negotiation.]
He's just so big that I couldn't
even get my arm around him.
[Brad and Craig also discover
their targets.]
[Workers Yoo and Kwang flee
the scene for now.]
[Brad runs around the other way.]
[Craig takes off after Kwang Soo.]
[Where did Kkuk suddenly fly in from?]
[Kwang Soo lures in the buyers...]
[Kkuk runs out from his hiding spot
and launches a surprise attack.]
[Worker Kkuk eliminates Craig's name tag.]
[Brad runs out of there
in lightning fast speed.]
You have to get Brad!
[A nicely carried out plan that
even Craig is impressed by.]
[All he has to do now is
to sign Craig's eliminated name tag.]
[But Kwang Soo snatches away
the name tag.]
[No matter who eliminates the name tag,
the one who signs it first, gets it.]
Then why are we even helping you?
You were only able to get that
because we helped lure him in.
Then just go your own separate way!
[It is the fate of these salaryman to
become enemies in the face of a promotion.]
- Ugh, this is so aggravating.
- We were all in on this together.
[Big-nose is busy getting
chased after by Fabien.]
[Just then!]
[Worker Ha runs out from his hiding
to launch an ambush attack.]
[Five years of experience is
on Running Man employees' side.]
[Wait, Mark is on his way!]
Wow, Mark!
I got Fabien's name tag.
I got Fabien.
[Worker Ha gets his first name tag.]
Fabien, out!
[Did they get that on camera?]
What are you going to do about
your grudge against Kwang Soo?
[Fabien will just have to wait for
his next chance to get his revenge.]
These are all in ancient Korean?
[Chris is leisurely perusing
through the showcased items.]
I'm learning the ancient Korean language
while attending a catholic parish.
But this is really hard.
Suk Jin, over there.
I saw someone going in there.
[This time, I will succeed!]
[I will get you!]
[Workers Yoo and Kwang catch onto
the scent of the prey and joins in!]
[Who will be the one to get the prey?]
- Let's make a deal.
- What kind of a deal?
- Since it's all of you...
- We have to get him before others come.
- Mark isn't out yet.
- Let's all catch our breath.
[We can catch our breath later.
Let's just eliminate you first.]
Here he comes!
I see him!
[Worker Kkuk also joins in.]
[The battle over the prey becomes even more
desperate with Worker Kkuk on the scene.]
[Worker Big-nose gets Chris' name tag.]
[Worker Big-nose signs his
first name tag.]
Chris, out.
- Who?
- Chris.
Chris.
Dummy.
[Buyers who failed at their deal
returns to the conference room.]
[Just before, John also had his deal
shattered by Worker Yoo.]
- Who eliminated you?
- Mr. Yoo.
Then... the man with the big nose...
The man with the big nose!
Chris, even you think that
his nose is big?
It's a bit on the larger side.
[Big-nose's nose is acknowledged
by people everywhere.]
It's okay, let's go slow.
[Jake's plan is to lure the others in
while Brad waits in hiding.]
Either I get eliminated,
or I eliminate them.
[Just then...
Mark faces them head on?]
- You have to eliminate Jake.
- Come here, Jake.
- Come on.
- No.
[No... this is the plan.]
Mark, just come back in here.
[Mark is already battling two against one.]
Now's our chance!
[Worker Ha gets his second name tag.]
[Darn...]
Jake!
[Jake lures them in...]
[And Brad rushes out to eliminate.]
[But he fails to eliminate!]
Jake, come out!
- Jake, come out!
- Got it!
[A wailing end,
right out of a Hollywood movie.]
Brad, out.
[Worker Kwang gets his first name tag.]
- Run, Jake is the only one left.
- Really?
Jake is the only one left?
[The war isn't over yet.]
[Jake flies into the air to avoid the attack.]
[Jake turns around and
starts his counterattack.]
[Worker Big-nose breaks the negotiation.]
[Workers Yoo and Kkuk
enter the lecture hall.]
You're ousted?
[I have to eliminate Jake
before the others get here.]
Okay, good.
[If he can just eliminate Jake, then
Worker Kwang may get his chance.]
[If left alone, Worker Kwang might
get his chance at a promotion!]
[Let me just get my promotion!]
- No!
- Jake is out!
[Another Hollywood ending.]
[Worker Kwang gets his
second name tag.]
[Worker Kwang's final spurt
in a show of performance.]
[The end of negotiation.]
Team Running Man wins.
[Team Running Man succeeds in
their deal with the foreign buyers.]
[But the chance at a promotion
goes to only one person.]
Ha Ha eliminated Fabien and Mark.
[Worker Ha signs both Fabien
and Mark's name tags.]
Lee Kwang Soo eliminated both
Jake and Brad's name tags.
He also has two, so they will both
be given the chance at a promotion.
[The win is tied between
Workers Ha and Kwang.]
- Kwang Soo got both in the end.
- It's all thanks to you.
[Worker Kwang also earns his chance
at a promotion.]
[Thanks to the seven special guests for their
appearance and for their love for Korea.]
[It all now boils down to
the final promotion exam.]
[Final round-
A chance to turn their lives around.]
[Returning to the office, where the lights
still burn bright even this late at night.]
[But...]
Hello.
[Who is Worker Yoo greeting?]
[A crowd of 300 workers are here to give
the Running workers a warm greeting.]
[Utter state of confusion.]
[Speechless at the unexpected
greeting from the crowd.]
[And the Running Workers, who are enjoying
this unexpected crowd of eager fans.]
We were in the middle of filming
and we came here because we were told
that this is the next mission site.
But we had no idea that
so many people would be here.
Thank you all for being here.
[A polite bow of greeting
to the eager crowd of fans.]
[The final panel of judges will be
this crowd of 300 people.]
[Just what is the final promotion mission
that awaits our workers?]
[Worker Yoo is handed a stack of cue
cards to MC the rest of the mission.]
Three of our members currently have
a chance at receiving a promotion.
That would be Ha Ha, Gary,
and Lee Kwang Soo.
[Only one of these three
can receive the promotion.]
[The one who shows up at the office
early will win the boss' favor.]
[Gary wins the morning commute mission
with a single minded determination.]
[First candidate- Gary.]
[Maintaining a keen eye is
crucial in the world of business.]
[Treat the boss as you would your father-
Brown-noser, Worker Ha.]
[Second candidate- Ha Ha.]
[Even though I might not have a keen eye,
the contract will get signed!]
[Come on, foreign buyers!
Contract signer, Worker Kwang.]
[Third candidate- Lee Kwang Soo.]
[The three candidates up for a promotion.]
[Just which one of these three
will receive the promotion?]
[But what are these 300 people
doing here?]
But there's a term that exists
in the business world, which is 'Line'.
Like the namesake of this race,
one of these three will receive a promotion.
And all of you out there will choose the one
you think will get it and get in their line.
[Choose one of the three candidates,
and get in their line.]
[They have to choose the most likely
candidate and get in their line...]
I will bet my whole
fortune on this promotion!
Lee Kwang Soo!
[As any other day, Worker Kwang,
once again bets his whole fortune.]
This will be my fifth year of being
a regular cast member of Running Man.
But today has been the luckiest day
that I've had of being on this show so far.
Do you want 2015 to be
the best year you've had so far?
- Yes!
- Then choose me!
Ha Dong Hoon!
[And last but not least, Worker Gae.]
Make some noise!
I hope that you choose me, and
I'll make sure that you all become winners.
Fighting!
Great, it's now time for the members
to make your selection.
- I don't even know what this is about.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- I'm going to think about it.
- There's no time, so make your selection.
Five, four, three, two, one!
Okay, Lee Kwang Soo.
[Worker Kwang chooses
to get in Kwang Soo's line.]
Why!
Okay, next.
What about you, Song Ji Hyo?
Kang Gary!
[Monday couple]
[Follows everyone's chanting,
and chooses Gary's line.]
- I'll go with my little brother.
- Okay, Ha Ha.
[Worker Kkuk chooses Ha Ha's line.]
Okay, I will now make my selection.
In the history of Running Man, whenever
Gary and Ji Hyo partner up together
it's rare for them not to win.
[Monday Couple as a team is
almost a guarantee at victory?]
I choose to stand with Gary and Ji Hyo!
[Worker Yoo joins Gary's line.]
Okay, all the members
have now made their selection.
It is time for the rest of you
to make your own selection.
Please move over by the team
whom you think will win the mission.
Once the time is up, we will clearly
outline the lines of the each team.
Does everyone understand?
[The floor becomes chaotic as the crowd
moves around to make their selection.]
Let's all countdown together.
Ten, nine, eight, seven... one!
[Line selection is now complete.]
Happy new year!
I'd like to wish everyone
a happy new year in advance.
[Greetings for the new year
after the countdown is over.]
Now it's time...
[Just then, the writer comes up on
stage to hand something over.]
[What could it be?]
[Wait... that's gold!]
- To ten people?
[After the final mission is over, ten people
from the winning team will win the gold.]
[Fervently chanting on their team.]
[Shouting until their throats burst.]
[The crowd fervently cheers on.]
[The pressure builds on.]
Wait a minute.
[Can't hear you!]
If I can just tell you real quick,
this isn't all pure gold.
Do you see this round mark over here?
[Only this portion is real gold.]
[Hope you're not too disappointed.]
[Time to start the final mission.]
[Nervous energy...]
I have been given the final mission.
[What is their final mission?]
The game that you all will be participating
in for the chance at a promotion is...
[The final battle with the chance at
a promotion hanging on the line.]
What does life all boil down to?
Life's greatest gamble, Rock-paper-scissors!
[Life's greatest gamble-
Final mission- Rock, paper, scissors.]
[What the heck...]
- That's just all about luck!
- That's no way to get a promotion!
Life is all just a random gamble,
and thus, this will be the final mission.
- My promotion is riding on the line.
- If you're not playing, then leave!
I'm going to play no matter what!
The first of the three to get three wins
will receive the promotion.
[One point per win.
First person to win three points wins.]
[Team Gary's line.]
[Team Kwang's line.]
[Team Ha's line.]
[Battle of the lines vs
Rock, Paper, Scissors.]
Please stand back-to-back.
[I vow to win the battle and
gift my line with the gold.]
- Kwang Soo, you've got this.
- What kind of a promotion is this?
[No matter how they view this, this doesn't
seem like a logical way to a promotion.]
- What have we been doing all this?
- This is the company policy.
- This is what it all comes down to?
- Tell me what you're thinking, Ji Hyo.
She told me that she loves me.
[Worker Gae's charming sense of humor.]
Life is all just a random gamble,
as this mission is about to show us.
- Okay, get ready!
- I'm so nervous!
- You can do this!
- I got this!
[Will it be the lucky Worker Ha...]
[Or Random Mr. Capable,
Worker Gae...]
[Or Worker Kwang, who's luck
may be starting to turn?]
[A tie- They all threw out a
different sign.]
[Their hearts are at their throats.]
Okay, you'll do it again.
[Even the crowd of on-lookers are
showing an extreme state of nervousness.]
Rock, paper...
[Gary and Kwang Soo, win.
Ha Ha, loses.]
[Who knew that a round of rock-paper-scissors
would elicit such a fervent response?]
[Worker Ha loses the first round,
and his line cheers him on to comfort him.]
[A passionate round of cheer from
having won a round of rock-paper-scissors.]
Lee Kwang Soo and Kang Gary.
[Rule- Only one winner per round.
A rematch between Gary and Kwang Soo.]
[Who will this round's victory go to?]
[Worker Gae wins!]
[Gary's line wins
their first of three points.]
[Team Kwang- 0, Team Gary- 1,
Team Ha- 0.]
Please get back up on your feet.
Let's win the next round, too.
[The Traitors' Club at work. Up to
something after losing the first round.]
Ha Ha, do you really trust
Lee Kwang Soo?
- Excuse me?
- Kwang Soo, do you trust Ha Ha?
- What are you doing?
- Why are you doing this?
[Worker Yoo tries planting seeds of doubt in
an effort to help his own team, Team Gary.]
- Okay, let's go.
- Don't do it.
They're up to something!
[Let's both throw out a scissors.]
You guys have to be careful.
You might end up hurting yourselves.
Rock-paper-scissors!
[All three throw out rock.]
[Huh? I thought you were
throwing out a scissors.]
[As expected.]
[Throws out a rock after agreeing
to throw out a scissors.]
This is what they're always like.
- I knew you'd do something like this.
- You just can't be trusted, can you?
[Pot calling the kettle black.]
- I wasn't wrong about this.
- They'd both agreed to throw out scissors.
Okay, once again!
[Another round of rock-paper-scissors.]
[Worker Ha wins.]
[Team Ha wins the first of
the three points.]
[Meanwhile, Team Kwang is...]
[Worker Kwang feels bad
for having lost again.]
It's okay, you can do it.
[Team Kwang- 0, Team Gary- 1, Team Ha- 1.]
- Get ready.
- Wow, I'm seriously so nervous!
[Extreme state of nervousness over
a simple game of rock-paper-scissors.]
- You must be feeling so nervous.
- Will Kwang Soo even out the score?
[His nervousness has him
muttering to himself.]
- Rock-paper-scissors!
- It's just a game of rock-paper-scissors.
[Both Workers Gary and Ha
throws out a rock...]
[What did Worker Kwang throw out?]
[Paper-win, Scissors-lose.]
[It's a scissors!]
[Feeling crushed...]
[No!]
[Gary and Ha Ha, win.
Kwang Soo, loses.]
[Only this section is silenced.]
[Looking for a rat's hole to crawl into.]
[Grave expression Team Kwang.]
[A tie breaker between
Worker Gary and Worker Ha.]
With their second point on the line,
a rematch of rock-paper-scissors.
It's time for a rematch.
Are you both ready?
Okay, rock...
[300 pairs of eyes are transfixed
on their hands.]
[Worker Ha wins!]
[Team Ha is the first to
win two points.]
Everyone on Team Lee Kwang Soo
has a sour look on their faces.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Yes.
- Do you think that your team could win?
- I definitely...
Answer the question with
your honor on the line.
I don't think it'll be easy.
But we still have our faith
in Lee Kwang Soo!
How are you feeling right
at this moment?
I really have crappy luck.
I'm sorry.
[It's okay.]
[Back to another fateful round of
rock-paper-scissors.]
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
[Please...]
You all laughed when the final
mission was revealed.
But you're now watching with your hands
clasped together in nervous energy.
Kwang Soo, make everyone on
our team shout out in joy.
[Everyone on Team Kwang Soo's one wish
is to be able to shout out in joy even once.]
[Please, I pray...]
Keep your mind sharp, Kwang Soo!
[Everyone on Team Kwang Soo,
I will make you all shout out in joy!]
[Rock-paper-scissors.
Round four.]
[At last... we get to shout out in joy!]
[Worker Ha will now face
a rematch with Worker Kwang.]
[Worker Gary is disqualified.]
[Shouting out Kwang Soo's name
with all their might!]
[Thank goodness!]
As mentioned earlier,
if Lee Kwang Soo wins this rematch...
[Come at me!]
Please listen carefully,
if Lee Kwang Soo wins this round...
then he'll be able to stop Ha Ha
from winning this round.
And as he himself said earlier,
he will change the course of this game.
But if Kwang Soo loses this round,
then Ha Ha wins the whole mission.
Right at this moment, even Gary and Ji Hyo
must cheer Kwang Soo on for their own sake.
Kwang Soo, you don't want Ha Ha
to win, do you?
Our team will swap out our cheer.
We'll now cheer out, 'Let's go home.'
Let's go home!
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Both Team Kwang Soo and Team Gary
fervently starts cheering for Kwang Soo.]
[Extreme state of pressure.]
- Stop him Kwang Soo!
- We will not get started.
[The fate of the victory could rest
on this round of rock-paper-scissors.]
Keep your mind sharp, Kwang Soo.
[Being promoted... sure is difficult.]
Rock, paper...
[Please...]
[Worker Ha, wins!]
[We won!]
[Team Ha wins the mission!]
[Worker Ha receives the promotion!]
[So disappointed...]
[Feeling sorry to his team for
having lost the mission.]
Let's go home!
Today's final winner is... Ha Ha!
[Final winner- Team Ha.]
[The prize of a gold bar to everyone
who helped cheer him on.]
[Dragging their exhausted body off
to another day at the office...]
[To all those who exhaust themselves through
hard work and tip-toeing around your boss...]
[Exhausted as you may be,
let's remain strong.]
[Even through the hardship, a good day
will come when you can find your smile.]
[Let's walk through this
journey of life together.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Han Goo Roo]
[Jeon So Min]
[Kyung Soo Jin]
[Lee Sung Kyung]
[Song Ga Yeon]
[Five angels, who'll set our
hearts aflutter.]
[Our moment of happiness that
I thought would last forever.]
You seem to know how to party.
[But their true selves will
come to surface.]
[Gentle demeanor gets transformed
into a frosty inner steel.]
[Next week on Running Man-
Two Faces of an Angel.]