[Running Man 2014 World Cup Special]
[The little boy with two hearts.]
[The soccer ball becomes his dreams.]
[The Cinderella of the 2002 World Cup.]
[First time in Asian soccer game history,
he scores three goals in a row!]
[An official member of 'The Century Club'.]
['No other words for a player like him.
Ji Sung is the best player I've ever coached']
[Becomes an official player for England's
Manchester United in 2005.]
[The first premier leaguer in all of
Korea's soccer history.]
[The best of the best in Asian soccer!]
[The first Asian soccer player to ever play
in the European champion league.]
['He is the ultimate professional athlete.'-
Coach Alex Ferguson.]
[Wins the championship league in 2008.]
[Running Man members are awaiting his
entrance with excitement and anticipation.]
[Retires from the professional league,
but he will forever remain our captain.]
- What is that?
- You actually put that up there?
Did you actually have to
put that up there?
[Makes an appearance on Running Man
in 2012, and 2013.]
[The pride of Korean soccer.]
[The Eternal Captain- Park Ji Sung.]
[The return of the legend.]
[Captain Park is dressed up in
a sleek black suit.]
Look at how he's all dressed up!
Please welcome Captain Park Ji Sung!
[Welcome back, Park Ji Sung!]
Ji Sung!
[Everyone wants a piece of Ji Sung.]
[Everyone's fighting over for their chance
to greet the Captain.]
Ji Sung is wearing a ring on his finger!
- Is that a wedding ring?
- Did you get married?
- He announced that he's getting married.
- Is he getting married on here today?
- No, he's not.
Is it diamond studded?
What are you doing?
- You really are something else.
- Why would you ask him about a diamond?
How many studs do you
have on the ring?
- He has once again returned to Running Man.
- He's a part of the RM family!
Let's give him a round of applause!
[Making his return after a year-
Our eternal captain, Park Ji Sung.]
Can you say a word to our
viewers at home?
It is that time of the year again
for me to return to the show.
Thanks for making me a semi-permanent
guest on the show, my name is Park Ji Sung.
[Never failing sense of humor
from our MC Park.]
Our Park Ji Sung has made his return
after being away for this past year.
He had his farewell ceremony back in May, and
he is now officially retired from the games.
I want to be his knees.
I want to be Park Ji Sung's knees.
But I don't want that.
[That's our MC Park!]
- Gary, just stick to your own knees.
- Okay, I'll just use my own knees.
[We'll just have Gary stick to
using his own knees.]
What will we be doing today with our
eternal captain, Park Ji Sung?
As I'm sure you may have guessed after seeing
that Park Ji Sung is our guest for the day
following the tradition of 2012 and 2013
Running Man has been given the chance to
participate in the 2014 Dream Cup again.
Can we just not do that?
[The reason why Captain Park is
waving his hand in refusal is...]
[Running Man's shockingly bad performance
at the games last year and the year before.]
[Even Captain Park was shocked to see
how bad they played during the games.]
The past two years were embarrassing
enough that even Park Ji Sung
is hesitant to let you play
again this year.
- But we'll be much better this year.
- But Ji Sung knows us better now.
Now that he knows us better, I think he'll
choose the players differently this year.
- But that doesn't really mean much.
- He even grabbed Jong Kook by his collar.
[Kkuk showed that he's not very skilled in
soccer with his playing last year.]
- I couldn't see the goal without my glasses.
- Let's all just be honest here.
- Did anyone else try a heading shot?
- What did you say?
- You didn't do it either.
- You can't call what you did a heading shot.
[Not really much of a heading,
but more like a ball to the face shot.]
- Has anyone else kicked a penalty ball?
- You didn't even make the goal!
- Who cares when you didn't even make it!
[Jae Suk's golden opportunity to score
a point during last year's game.]
[But he didn't make the goal...]
You were 'Hollow Leg Yoo Jae Suk',
and 'Crap Ball Kim Jong Kook'.
Are they right, Ji Sung?
Was it really a bad kick?
Missing the penalty kick is purely
the fault of the player kicking the ball.
[Nice!]
He's saying this now after a whole year?
He knows how to hold a grudge.
So you've been holding that grudge
against me for the past year?
We will be preparing ourselves this year for
the Dream Cup game being held in Indonesia.
Today's mission is called, 'Boot Camp
Training Race' with Ji Sung in charge.
[Mission- Dream Cup Boot Camp Training.]
Today's mission will be a mixture of missions
from Running Man and from your captain.
[Separate Running Man missions,
and Captain missions.]
[Depending how whether or not they succeed
the Running Man mission...]
[the difficulty level of
the Captain's mission will vary.]
Also, depending on whether or not Ji Sung
succeeds the Captain's mission or not
you will be given a certificate that you'll
be able to use during the final mission.
In the event that Team Running Man wins
the final mission at the end of the day
the team will be given an extreme advantage
that can be utilized at the game in Indonesia.
We're not going to be given any psychic powers
on the soccer field or something, are we?
I can definitely use the Roll-Roll power.
[Flying through the air and move the goal post
at an international soccer game?]
- What the heck is this!
- What are you doing!
That would be an embarrassment
to the whole country.
- We can't do that.
- I'm not using any of those powers.
[I bet you're going to want to wear
a face hiding mask to do that...]
Don't you think that we're going to need
someone else to help with the training?
- That's right, we had others come last year.
- How about Evra?
- Let's ask another legend to join us.
- That sounds good. Do you know someone?
- Why, do you know anyone?
- No, but just think about it.
- How about Cha Bum Geun?
- It would be amazing if Cha Bum Geun came.
- Isn't he a legend himself?
- Yes, he's totally a legend.
[If they can only get the soccer legend and
SBS sports commentator, Cha Bum Geun...]
I don't know Cha Bum Geun's number,
but I know his wife's number.
[Kkuk knows Cha Bum Geun's wife,
Oh Eun Mi's number...]
- How about we try some real tough training?
- What do you mean, try?
- Why don't you do it yourself?
- Why don't you try giving him a call?
It would be awesome if he came
because he's the best forward ever!
He and Ji Sung would be amazing together.
[Calling Cha Bum Geun's wife.]
[Passes the phone off to Captain Park
after initiating the call.]
- Hello?
- Hi!
[She answered the phone!]
Yes, hello...
This is Park Ji Sung.
Okay, hang on a second.
Coach Cha is doing something right now.
- Hang on just a moment.
- Yes, of course.
- She must be with him right now.
- I can't believe she answered!
Maybe Coach Cha is filming something.
- Hello?
- Hello, Sir.
- That's his voice!
- This is Park Ji Sung.
- That's the voice!
- Hello, this is Park Ji Sung.
- 'Oh, okay. Hi.'
- Hello, Sir.
That was a lot of great work
you did all these years.
Yes, thank you for your kind words.
I'm actually on the set of RM right now.
Sports Commentator Cha Bum Geun,
I love you!
I have nothing but the utmost
respect for you!
- Where are you filming right now?
- We're filming in Samahmdong right now.
- 'Samahmdong?'
- Yes, Sir.
- 'I'm doing something in Ilsan right now.'
- He's right by us.
Ask him if he's free at all today.
Coach Cha, we were wondering if you're
free at all later on today?
I've never seen you acting
so nervous before.
- 'Why?'
- Tell him why we want him here.
It's just that Running Man members are
such poor soccer players...
so I was hoping that you could come and...
- 'You're asking me to coach them?'
- Yes, Sir.
- Please help us, Coach Cha.
- We love you, Coach Cha.
It's been a while since
I've quit coaching anyone.
But there's no one else I know who could
even begin to help these guys unless it's you.
- We're total newbies.
- You're a legend to our country!
Please come and help us!
Okay then.
Is he really coming?
[Soccer legend, Park Ji Sung... and
another legend comes to join the team...]
[SBS Sports Commentator, Cha Bum Geun at
a photo-shoot for the Brazilian World Cup.]
[Cast of Running Man calls
during his photo-shoot!]
Hello?
[First words shared between
one legend to another.]
[With a heartfelt gratitude...
'Thanks for all your hard work'.]
[Sports commentator, Cha Bum Geun,
and his fellow announcer, Park Sung Jae.]
- I was just thinking that you could...
- He's really hesitating right now.
- Why are you hesitating so much?
- You really seem to be hesitating.
[Can't help but laugh at the sudden request.]
You should try and help them.
I think they need it.
[Hard to refuse Captain Park's request.]
You don't need to use that
when you're talking on the phone.
Okay.
I think he said okay.
- Tell him that you'll do it.
- Okay.
[Coach Cha agrees!]
- 'Once I finish up here...'
- Okay.
- 'I'll see you then.'
- Yes, thank you.
[We'll be waiting for you!]
But we're not sure if
he'll really come or not, right?
- He says he's in Samahmdong right now.
- That's really close.
I'll stop by there when I'm done here.
We have prepared your first mission to
determine who you'll be teamed up with.
- Yes, let's get started.
- Let's go!
[Dream Cup Boot Camp Training- Start!]
[Will the near hopelessness of RM's
soccer skills be improved in one day?]
- Ji Sung's getting married in July.
- That's right around the corner.
I bet your fiancée is really accommodating
to you right now, isn't she?
Yes, of course.
- Yes, I'm sure she is.
- I hope that she'll stay that way.
[The married men club's
unanimous understanding.]
- Do you want a daughter or a son?
- It doesn't matter to me at all.
[Captain Park doesn't care if
they have a boy or a girl in the future.]
- If your son wants to be a soccer player?
- He should be encouraged.
If that's what my son wants,
then I'll encourage it.
- What if your daughter wants it?
- Then I'll encourage her too.
[Captain Park will encourage whatever
his children will want to pursue.]
- You're a very open-minded dad.
- Ji Sung will be a supportive dad.
His children will be capable of doing anything
with Park Ji Sung as their father.
- What if your son wants to be an MC?
- Then I'll tell him to rethink his decision.
- You're so stifling.
- You're a strict dad.
- He's already pretty strict.
- He's the boss of his family.
What if Hyun Woo says he wants to
become a Ddakji King?
As long as he can make money
from doing it.
But that wouldn't really earn him
any money.
[Boot Camp Training- Course one.
Mental Reinforcement Training.]
[First training session location-
SBS headquarters in Mokdong.]
[What is that?]
They're training uniforms.
[Nervous energy...]
Are they drawstring pants?
[With the exception of the captain,
everyone else is changed into their uniforms.]
- You look so funny right now.
- I didn't know we'd have to wear this.
Gary's legs are too long for his pants.
[Drawstring fashionista.]
- Can't you warn us of things like this first?
- How far do we pull up these pants?
[Kwang Soo's first time ever
in a pair of drawstring pants!]
- Okay, here's your mission.
- What kind of a mission is it?
In order to train your mentality to avoid
getting flustered no matter what happens...
we are going to be playing,
Drawstring Telepathy Game.
Running Man members will disperse
separately on their own
to successfully complete each of the missions
on their own and come back to this spot.
There will be a time limit to
complete these missions.
While you're each completing
missions of your own
Park Ji Sung will be doing
a mission of his own right here.
But no matter how well you're doing
at your own mission
as soon as Park Ji Sung fails the mission
that he'll be doing on his own
then everyone as a whole
will fail the mission.
[Everyone must return to the starting line
before Captain Park completes his mission.]
- You have to make sure to do well.
- This is our first game.
Don't mess this up for us.
You will get a total of five chances
and if you succeed just even once,
then the mission is successfully completed.
[Successfully complete the mission within
five chances to pass the mission.]
[Captain missions' level of difficulty will vary
depending on the success of RM missions.]
Everyone understand the rules?
Then we will now start the missions.
- So it's an individual mission?
- Do a good job, Ji Sung.
[Everyone to their positions.]
So the members don't know what kind
of a mission I'll be doing?
This is making me feel nervous.
[Drawstring Army set - in position!]
Is only my face showing right now?
Doesn't it look like my face is floating
in midair right now?
[Park Ji Sung will draw to determine which
mission the members will be performing.]
While Park Ji Sung carries out his mission
each of the seven members must find costumes
of seven different colors
and come back to the starting point
dressed in the borrowed costumes.
- So no one can be in the same color?
- Yes, that's correct.
Here's the mission that you'll have to
carry out in the meantime.
You have to do the beanie toss (hacky sack)
without dropping the beanie on the ground.
[Hacky sack until all the members
make it back to the starting point.]
If you drop the beanie on the ground,
then everyone fails the mission.
- Do you understand?
- Can I catch it with my hand?
You will have two chances to
catch it with your hand.
I've never played hacky sack before.
Can I have a practice round first?
This is a really nice gym.
Here's your mission.
[Time to hand out the mission
to the Drawstring Army.]
We have to borrow the costumes
from other people?
[All seven members must borrow costumes
of different colors from other people.]
Can it be just any type of clothing?
We don't have to lend our clothes
out to those people, right?
We will now start
Captain Park Ji Sung's mission.
You have two chances.
Different colors, different colors.
[Drawstring telepathy- Go!]
[Must hold out until all the members
make their return!]
I'll just wear the gym clothes here.
Look at all the clothes in the gym here.
I should choose a color that most people
don't usually wear often.
[Concentrate]
What unique color can I find?
Wow, Ji Sung.
You're really good!
[Clueless Giraffe breaks Captain Park's
concentration with his comment.]
[One hand catching chance is used.]
[Giraffe almost killed
Drawstring Army's chance!]
- Ji Sung.
- Get out of here!
- Wow, you're really good.
- Just get out of here!
There's nothing you can't do, is there?
Park Ji Sung!
Okay, I'm leaving.
- You have to get back to hacky sack.
- What color can I find?
You've used up one of your two chances
to catch it in your hand.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Don't talk to me!
- What are you doing?
- Don't talk to me right now!
[Now, it's Drawstring Big-nose.]
What?
[No thanks to the Drawstring Easy,
Ji Sung used up all his catching chances.]
[Next mistake is the end of this round!]
[Must continue the mission until all
seven members makes it back.]
- I have to keep going until everyone's back.
- Until everyone's back?
How are you going to do that?
- You just interrupted him.
- I know.
But I didn't know.
I'm sorry, Ji Sung. Hurry back!
Hey, we fail the mission if he stops.
I'm sorry to be asking for this,
but can I borrow your shirt?
I'm so sorry to ask you for this
but can I borrow your coat?
[There's no time!
This is not the time to be shy!]
[Ji Sung is starting to show his fatigue.]
Hurry up!
Why can't you find it?
I'm good!
I found mine!
[Hold out just a little bit longer!]
[Hurry back!]
Just for a little while.
Thank you so much!
What's taking you so long?
[Captain Park Ji Sung fails the mission.]
[Falls down in exhaustion.]
- What's so hard about this?
- What did you just do!
It's not his fault.
We just took too long.
I have to keep kicking the beanie
until everyone makes it back here.
- Until everyone makes it back.
- You have to keep kicking it?
- You can't drop it at all?
- Until everyone makes it back here.
He had two chances to catch the beanie.
Kwang Soo came around
to interrupt me the first time...
[Captain's lonely battle...]
- What happened?
- We failed the first round.
- We failed?
- Yes, we failed.
- Why did we fail the mission?
- We should've been quicker.
[Everyone's acting so cocky
after having taken their sweet old time.]
- I was in the gym.
- You got that from the gym?
[That's our Drawstring Fashionista!]
- Where did you even find that?
- Where were you?
I found this.
I could've accepted everyone's colors since
they were all different in style and color.
- But since the Captain failed his mission...
- Ji Sung!
- Can't you do better?
- You have to do a better job.
Hey, this is all your fault!
Come on, Ji Sung, let's concentrate.
I'm telling you that it isn't my fault.
Wow, seriously.
- Let's all work better.
- You need to work faster.
- We're just starting out.
- Don't forget this.
Don't forget the fact that I get to decide
who gets to play in the World Cup.
I was just joking, Ji Sung.
Yes, we know how difficult
this must be for you.
We did pretty well in the first round,
and I know that we can do this.
[Second attempt-
Everyone back to their positions.]
Hey, Park Ji Sung.
Let's get it done this time.
Okay, let's get it done.
[What will their mission be this time?]
While Park Ji Sung carries out his mission
While Park Ji Sung carries out his mission...
You have to go find an item that starts with
these two characters and return to the line.
Find these items and get back to
your starting point on the first floor.
- Okay, those two characters?
- Yes.
All seven members must each bring back
a different item in order to succeed.
What could I get?
[They all must be different items.]
Here's your mission.
It's jump roping.
If you trip and fall before all the members
return, then you fail the mission.
We will let you choose which jump rope
you'd like to use.
We have two different ones.
[Compares the two different jump ropes.]
I'll go with this one.
When's the last time you've
jump roped?
Middle school, I think.
I haven't jump roped since
I was in middle school.
Okay, Park Ji Sung,
you may start your mission.
What are some items that start
with those two characters?
A hat!
I've got a hat!
[Blank Ji is the first to arrive
with a hat as her item.]
Just a little bit longer.
What the heck?
Did you bring back a hat?
- Yeah, I have the hat.
- Darn!
- Hey, what did you bring back?
- A hat!
No, you can't be tired yet.
I'm sorry, but can you lend me
a water glass?
I'll bring it right back.
A water glass!
[But this guy is also going
after a water glass...]
By any chance, is there anyone here
by the name of, Myung Ja?
Is there a Myung Ja here?
- Mi Joo?
- No, it's not.
That's not your name?
A beer!
Thank you!
But where am I going to get a beer?
Concentrate.
- Ugh, I'm starting to get really tired.
- No, you can't.
You can't get tired.
A hat... what else is there
besides a hat?
Dust?
There's a lot of dust around here.
How about a marker?
Do you have a magic marker?
- What's taking everyone so long?
- Come on, hurry!
- Water glass. I got water glass.
- Water glass!
Get out of his way.
[Oxygen tank, Park Ji Sung,
is still going even after all this time!]
- What's taking everyone so long?
- I'm here!
- I got it!
- What did you bring back?
[What? He brought back a person?]
[Just then...]
[Oh... my... God...]
[Park Ji Sung fails the mission.]
- No!
- A magic marker!
I have a magic marker!
[How can this be...]
- You couldn't even do that?
- Jump roping is easy.
[Ah, I feel so alone...]
Foot fungus.
He says he has foot fungus.
- I'm serious! That's what he said.
- But still! Foot fungus?
- Foot fungus starts with those characters.
- What are you thinking?
He really said he has foot fungus.
I'm so sorry for this.
I'm sorry for asking this,
but do you by any chance have foot fungus?
- Do you have foot fungus?
- Yes, I do.
Can you come with me for a moment?
Thank you.
Thank you so much!
Come on!
We need to hurry!
Thank you so much.
Would you have had to confirm
that he really has foot fungus?
- We failed the mission anyway.
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you though.
- Here comes Gary.
- What is it?
- What did you bring back, Gary?
Blank Ji!
[Only thing Gary sees that begin with
those characters is, Blank Ji.]
- I couldn't think of anything else.
- There are ton of stuff like this beer.
But the real problem here is that
Ji Sung keeps failing his missions.
[Blaming everything on the Captain?]
When I saw him jump roping,
I thought we were going to succeed for sure.
- I haven't jump roped since middle school.
- Seriously?
You should've done it more.
[As expected, Big-nose doesn't care about
mincing his words even to a living legend.]
Are you being all harsh to Ji Sung
now that he's retired from the game?
You know that Ji Sung will be the one
to pick who gets to play at the game, right?
Okay, we will now start your third
out of five chances to pull off this mission.
- Everyone back to your positions.
- Do better this time, Ji Sung.
- Okay, let's get this done.
- Fighting!
I feel like the missions are
getting easier though.
[They all seem to be pretty comfortable
in their drawstring uniforms now.]
- Good luck, Ji Sung.
- Choose your mission.
[The next mission for the members is...]
While Park Ji Sung carries out his mission
seven RM members must bring someone back
from each of the different age groups.
Bring someone back
[Example- Teens, 20s, 30s... etc.]
- Yes, of each different age groups.
- Okay, I got it.
I wonder how I need to do it
so it's different than anyone else's.
Your next personal mission is...
to use your whole body to bounce a ball
without ever dropping it on the ground.
If the ball even grazes the ground,
then you fail the mission.
Okay, here's your ball.
You have to bounce it around.
[Carefully compares the two balls again.]
If I fail this too...
Then we'll be in big trouble.
Ready, set, go!
[Drawstring telepathy- Go!]
Ma'am!
Ma'am, how old are you?
Excuse me, but can I take the baby?
I mean, can you and the baby come with me?
Yes, please come with me.
Excuse me,
but can you please keep it down?
How old are you?
Twelve? Okay, come with me.
- Come on, hurry!
- How old are you?
- I feel so nervous.
- Your baby is eleven months old?
- This baby is eleven months old.
- He's twelve years old.
Hello.
Ma'am, who's the oldest person
in this room?
- She's in her sixties.
- In her sixties?
- Where? Where is she?
[Big-nose is trying to convince a
coffee shop worker to come with him.]
How old are you?
[Mr. Gary chooses
a foreigner in her twenties.]
She's in her twenties!
[Steady and confident ball bouncing.]
[That's our Park Ji Sung!]
She's in her twenties!
Ji Young!
[Wait, that's...]
[The Queen of Ballads, Baek Ji Young.]
[Catch Baek Ji Young!]
- What?
- Come with me.
[A chance run-in with Ji Young, who
was waiting for the radio show to start.]
- You're in your late thirties, right?
- Yes.
- She's in her twenties.
- What?
She's in her twenties, so you have to go back.
[Double of twenties.]
- Mrs. Baek.
- Aren't you in your forties yet?
I've still got another year to go for that.
[Over five minutes have passed.
Park Ji Sung's skills are amazing!]
Is there anyone here who is
in their forties?
[The remaining members must now bring
someone back over the age of 40.]
- Anyone in their twenties here?
- Yes, there is.
- How about in their thirties?
- Go get someone in their fifties!
- Go back and get someone!
- We already have someone in their 30s here.
Director, I need you to
help me out for a minute.
You're the oldest one here right now.
Help me out for a minute.
[Then who's going to film the show?]
[Captain Park is slowly
starting to feel the fatigue.]
- Who is that?
- She's not a celebrity.
Why does that guy keep kicking the ball?
Wait, is that Park Ji Sung?
[Ji Young finally recognizes Park Ji Sung.]
- I just need you for three minutes.
- Is there anyone in their fifties here?
- She needs to get back to work.
- How old are you?
- I'm in my sixties.
- She's in her sixties.
We've verified her age,
so she can go back to work.
[Kkuk's guest in her sixties rushes back
to work after having her age verified.]
Get someone in their fifties!
[Eight minutes have now passed.]
[They'll succeed the mission if Kwang Soo
can bring back someone in their fifties.]
[They just need to verify
everyone's age now.]
[What?
You mean it wasn't over yet?]
[Will they fail the mission?]
[He saves the ball!]
[What amazing talent!
So dangerously close to having lost it!]
- He's eleven months old!
- He's in his teens!
- Who's in their twenties?
- She's in her twenties!
- Thirties over here!
- he's in his forties.
- Fifties here.
- The grandmother earlier was in her sixties.
- Is he in his fifties?
- You're in your fifties, right?
No, I'm in my sixties.
[Kwang Soo!]
Hold on just a little bit longer, Ji Sung!
[Will Captain Park Ji Sung be able to
hold out much longer?]
[Find a guest in their fifties!]
[Another dangerous moment!]
Oh no!
[The Queen of Ballads freaks out!]
Ji Young is freaking out over here.
[Drawstring Kwang Soo must find
someone in their fifties!]
- I'm over fifty years old.
- Really?
Then can you come with me for a moment?
[Now past the ten minute mark!]
[Even though he may be Captain Park,
even he has his limits...]
I'm on my way!
Wait just a little bit longer!
I've got sweat in my eyes,
and I can't even see the ball right now.
[Will he be able to stick it out...
or will he flail down to the ground?]
- Here he comes!
- Just hold on a bit longer.
- Just a little bit longer.
- Hold on, Ji Sung.
[Will Kwang Soo touch ground first...
or will the ball touch ground first?]
[Captain Park!
Just a little bit longer...]
- Eleven months!
- Teens!
- Twenties!
- Thirties!
- Forties!
- Fifties!
The grandmother from earlier
was in her sixties.
[Mission success!]
Thank you!
[Thank you to all those who participated
in helping out our Drawstring Army.]
Thank you.
[Thank you to Baek Ji Young for joining us
even with the radio show looming ahead.]
- Bye!
- I'll see you later.
- You have a new song out?
- It's titled, 'Still hot as ever'.
- Tell the viewers about your new song.
- 'Still hot as ever' is now out.
[Makes her exit after briefly
promoting her new song.]
[Captain Park kept up the bouncing
of the ball for over ten minutes!]
[The amazing Park Ji Sung!]
I thought that I had it the first time.
Because all of you succeeded
this mission
the difficulty level of the Captain's missions
have now been lowered.
If you succeed the next mission
you will be given a great advantage which
you will be able to use at your final mission.
[Mission One- Mental Reinforcement Training.
Success!]
I will now reveal your next mission.
[Time to reveal the Captain's mission.]
Does he have to pull the car
with the rest of us in it?
- But this is supposed to be an easy mission.
- This is something that I should be doing.
Captain's mission.
Shoot the ball through the car window.
You're saying this is the easy mission?
Then what's the hard mission?
If Park Ji Sung succeeds this mission
then you will be given a huge advantage
which will be of great use at the final mission.
The difficult mission you almost had was
you would've had to kick the ball
through the window
and make it come out through
the window on the other side.
- Thank you.
- This is definitely easier.
The way I see it,
today's your boot camp training day.
The way I see it, I don't think this is bad,
and you should be able to do it all.
There are no practice shots.
This isn't even a soccer field,
and I don't even have soccer shoes on.
You have to say whether you're going to put it
through the front or the back window.
- That's going over the line.
- Please decide which window you want.
- I think the front window will be better.
- I'll kick it through the front.
The front window?
Okay, I understand.
[Then it's time to roll up the back window.]
But he could've been aiming for the front,
and had it end up going through the back.
- Okay, we're ready.
- Let's do this.
He doesn't even have soccer shoes on,
so this may be tough.
- Park Ji Sung, fighting!
- Fighting.
I have no strength left in my legs.
[He only has three chances to
shoot the ball through the front window.]
Challenge.
[Even after 20 years of playing pro soccer,
this is the first experience of its kind.]
Challenge.
This is making me feel really nervous.
[First attempt]
[The ball is directed perfectly!]
[Will it make the goal?]
[A clean goal without any hesitation.]
[Celebrating along to
Park Ji Sung's official cheer song.]
He's still got it.
- How did he do that?
- That's just unbelievable.
Then can we have the Captain come
forward and accept the certificate?
[Thanks to Captain Park Ji Sung,
the team wins the special certificate.]
- Would you like to try the difficult one?
- No thanks.
Seriously, Park Ji Sung.
That was amazing.
- Can I open this?
- Yes, you may open it.
- That was a clean shot.
- What is it?
A chance certificate?
This is going to be
advantageous for us, isn't it?
We will now head off to your second mission,
Crisis Management Training location.
[Dream Cup- Boot camp Training.
Crisis Management Training.]
[Headed off to somewhere quite remote...]
I'm getting a weird feeling about this.
We're going off to a very rural area.
- They're not going to...
- What do you think this is going to be about?
If we're to be honest, other than the farmers
who actually work the fields or marshes
we probably go in those places
more than anyone else we know.
- I see a goal post over there.
- What?
What's that?
[Boot camp Training Mission Two-
Crisis Management Training.]
[Specially built soccer field
on the farm field.]
I'm sure the goal post is for us
to shoot the ball through, right?
What is all this?
This is a soccer field.
This isn't a soccer field,
this is a farm field.
It may look like a farm field,
but it's actually a soccer field.
Who's that?
[Top world soccer stars are aligned
alongside the soccer field.]
Look at all those stars.
- Wow, I can't believe all this.
- Wow.
Kwang Soo is the water boy.
If anyone needs any water, just let me know.
This mission is to help you train
for crisis management.
For this mission, Captain Park Ji Sung
will also be participating with you.
[Captain Park Ji Sung to participate
along with the rest of the members.]
If you look on the field
R1 will drop the ball on the blue 'R' mark
in the middle of the field
then R2 will dribble the ball down the field
with their arms held out to the side
and zig zag through all the star players
as quickly as they can.
- Ji Sung has to do that.
- Yeah, Ji Sung has to do that.
Yeah, that will be Ji Sung's job.
You will use the soccer ball as your baton.
Once you get through the player course
you will then throw
the water balloon with your foot.
That's going to be tough.
Even if the balloon pops, as long as it makes
it into the basket, we'll count it as good.
Then the person with the balloon basket
will dribble the ball over to R5.
Then the scarecrow in R5 position will lean
to the side to fill up the water bottle.
[Fill up the water bottle while
standing in a scarecrow stance.]
- That would be perfect for Kwang Soo.
- That's Kwang Soo all the way.
Then the person in R6 position
will get doused with the water
will ceremoniously bring the ball
to the person in R7 position.
Then the final person at the goal post
will use their feet to catch the ball.
[Five chances to complete the mission-
90 second time limit.]
[An unbelievably difficult mission.]
If you fail somewhere along the mission,
then you will have to start over.
If you succeed the mission, then
the Captain will have an easier mission.
- Ji Sung will dribble through the obstacle.
- Yeah, Ji Sung will do that.
- Should I do this one?
- Yeah, you do that one.
But my shoulder aches.
[Kwang Soo is chosen to do
the scarecrow portion.]
[Captain Park's first scarecrow experience.]
You look really funny with that thing on.
- You think it's funny too?
- Yeah, it's funny to me too.
So I just dribble the ball
through this course?
[Captain Park's practice dribble.]
I just need to do it like this.
I'll be fine doing it like this.
- Ready!
- This is really high up.
- Fighting!
- We can do this!
[Fighting!
We can do this!]
Fighting!
[Crisis Management Training- First attempt.]
Wow, this is really fast!
[R1 must drop the ball precisely
on the 'R' mark.]
[Successfully drops the ball.]
[Returned to original starting position
in preparation for second attempt.]
[In a scarecrow stance
on top of the uneven farm field...]
[But he still dribbles the ball
at an amazing speed.]
- Here he comes.
- Okay, good.
[Arrives at R3 in no time at all.]
Okay, throw it.
[Throw the ball with the foot
into the basket in R4's head.]
[Succeeds at first attempt!]
Hurry!
- Good! You caught it!
- Hurry!
What am I supposed to do?
What do I do now?
The ball!
Bring the ball over to me!
[Dribble the ball down to R5 with
the basket on his head.]
Pass it over to me.
[Fill the cup with water while
remaining in the scarecrow stance.]
Kwang Soo,
you're pouring it all over your face.
You're just pouring it on your face.
[Is he doing the mission,
or is he just washing his hair?]
- Stop pouring it on your face.
- Get your face out of the way.
Hurry up!
- To where?
- You have to move your face out of the way.
- Hurry up!
- There you go.
- You got it! Hurry over to me!
[Scarecrow water pour.]
He wasted all our time.
[Finally manages to fill the cup...
But time over!]
We can definitely do this.
- You have to lean your face away.
- Try it again.
Instead of you looking where you're pouring,
Ji Hyo should just tell you where to pour.
Try doing it with your head lifted away.
[Even with his head lifted,
he still gets soaked...]
[Even with his head bent,
- Kwang Soo can't do it right.
- Then how else am I supposed to do it?
- Why can't you do it, stupid?
- How many times am I washing my hair?
- Ji Sung, switch spots with me.
- No, I don't want to do that.
No, you do it.
- No, you do it.
- Yeah, you just do it.
What did I ever do wrong!
Come on, Ji Sung!
Switch with me!
Just look at the state I'm in right now!
[Kwang-crow explodes after his shower.]
Come on, switch with me!
Are you not listening to me?
[Kkuk swaps positions with Captain Park,
and practices his dribbling.]
[This isn't too bad.]
- Okay, let's do this!
- We can do this!
- Yes, we can do this!
- Let's get this done!
Let's think of this as our one last chance!
Kwang Soo, you and I have to
work together on this.
- I'll show you how it's done.
- Okay.
Tell me when to stop.
[Second attempt- Start.]
Drop it!
You got it!
[Ji Hyo drops the ball precisely
in the center of the 'R' mark.]
[Ji Sung, take a good look at
the Tiger's dribble skills.]
Where are you going!
- What are you doing?
- What's he doing!
Jong Kook!
Kim Jong Kook!
[Brawling with the life-sized boards.]
[Gary and Suk Jin combo who previously
succeeded their attempt on the first try.]
Once you're ready,
then just throw it to me.
[Succeeds on their first try
for the second time in a row.]
The ball!
[The water bomb explodes in the basket
on top of his head.]
[Finally arrives at their biggest hurdle, R5.]
What's wrong with you?
Are your arms too short?
[Nice plan! Spit the water out
from his mouth into the cup.]
[Giraffe speeds up the process,
and quickly succeeds the mission!]
I'm going to throw this in your face.
[Jae Suk gets hit in the face with the water
that Giraffe had spit out from his mouth.]
[Runs over to Ji Sung in R7 to
do the goal ceremony with him.]
We're doing great on time!
[R8 must catch the penalty kick ball
with his feet.]
[Checks and locks in the goal...]
[The ball is kicked
directly in Ha Ha's path...]
[He just needs to catch the ball
with his feet!]
[So close, yet fails the mission.]
[20 seconds still left on the clock!]
You should've kicked it harder.
Okay, I got it.
- We're out of time anyways.
- Let's try it though.
[Tiger's awkward dribbling-
The Tiger Butterfly's dance.]
- Kim Soccer!
- What? I got it done quickly!
- What are you doing over there?
- I made good time!
- How was that fast?
- That was pretty fast.
- I was weaving through it like this.
- You're so much slower than Ji Sung!
Out of my way!
[Takes out his anger on Jae Suk.]
- Wow, look at him lashing out.
- You really have a nasty personality.
Seriously.
- Wow, look at him.
- Don't talk to me.
- What did you say?
- You're really awful at that.
But I'm not the problem here.
The final part is the problem.
But you take up the most amount
of time!
- Why are you taking so long?
- What?
- You can't even do it right.
- I told you not to talk to me!
- I'm working really hard right now.
- Park Ji Sung, let's you and I fight too!
- Why can't you kick it to me better?
- Why can't you catch the ball?
- Okay, this is our last chance.
- Up or down?
- Let's decide which way to go.
- Let's go down.
Fighting!
- Okay, let's do it right this time.
- Let's do this.
This is our one last chance.
[Only one final chance is left.]
Let's please just end this game.
Let's go!
[There are no more chances!]
[We will succeed this mission,
and come out even stronger!]
[Their final fifth attempt- Start.]
Nice.
[Ji Hyo's steady ball drop.]
Kim Jong Kook.
[Tiger's bulldozing tactics.]
[This is American football style.]
[Arrives at R3 in lightning speed.]
Okay, that's good.
[Gary and Suk Jin combo never misses!]
Okay, let's succeed this mission!
Suk Jin is doing great.
[Kwang Soo's new method-
Dump it with the lid wide open.]
Okay, there you go.
[Time sucking Kwang Soo-crow]
You did it!
Okay, you got it, go!
[Full speed ahead!]
- Come on Ji Sung.
- This is our last chance!
This is our last chance.
- Take your time, Ji Sung.
- Calm down and stay steady.
[There are no more chances.]
This is our last chance.
[They succeed through all the courses!]
[The mission will be a total success
if they made it within 90 seconds.]
[Scarecrow shoulder battles.]
Stand straight in a line.
Okay, come in under my arms.
[Standing nicely shoulder to shoulder.]
Your final time is...
[Their final time is...]
Two minutes and 24 seconds.
[Final time- Two minutes and 24 seconds.
Mission fail.]
Just mix up all the parts that
we succeeded from the other attempts.
[When have we ever done that?]
Now that we're in this situation,
the Captain has a different mission to do.
- We just need the Captain to succeed.
- Right?
- He just needs to succeed his mission.
- Yeah, we'll be fine then.
We could even say that Ji Sung is
the reason why we failed this mission.
- Because he didn't take it seriously.
- What did you say?
Since the last mission was about his skills,
it'll be about his luck this time.
[It's time to test the Captain's luck.]
Captain's mission is, random chance draw.
- What's going to happen?
- You have to pick the right one.
- You just need to pick the right one.
- Why is that thing so long?
- What is that?
- Is it an anaconda?
How many things are there?
- It's not an anaconda or something.
- Why is that thing so long?
- What's this?
- Open it.
You want us to open it?
- One, two, three.
- I hope it's something to drink.
It's a chance game.
If you guys had succeeded in your mission,
it would've been a choice between two dishes.
- See, that's what I thought.
- But now your chances have been lowered.
It's only in one of those dishes.
There is only one chance card.
You have to choose the dish which you think
has the chance card under it.
Otherwise, you'll find a healthy herbal drink
which you'll have to down in one shot.
- If it's healthy, then I'll drink it.
- It's probably the bitter tea.
I bet it's something very bitter.
The staff member is unwrapping the candy.
- What's that candy for?
- Okay, get yourself ready.
- I think it's the one in the middle.
- No, I don't think that's it.
I think it's the one at the end.
- No, I think it's either this or this.
- I think it's this one.
- I think it's that one over there.
- You don't think it's the one in the middle?
- No, it's that one.
- This one?
No, don't listen to anyone,
and you just go with the one you want.
[The decision is Captain Park's to make.]
- Just go with whichever one you want.
- But it's not that one.
- No, it's not that one!
- No, just go with that one.
- Just do it.
- Open the lid.
[He opens the dish.]
[Only a 20% chance,
and he picks the chance card!]
[Not only is he skilled,
but he also has luck on his side!]
[The rest are bitter teas,
and steeped root teas.]
The rest are teas that are very bitter,
but also very good for your health.
- Is it really good for your health?
- Yeah, it's very good for you.
- It's extremely good for your health.
- Seriously?
As I've mentioned it to everyone before,
I've had the bitter tea before.
But there are a lot of other teas
that are just as good for you.
- He's drinking the whole thing.
- Give him a piece of candy.
- I'm going to have one too.
- Wow, that's nice.
You like it?
- I'm sure it's good for you.
- Then drink this one too.
- The aftertaste is even more bitter.
- I think it's good.
- The aftertaste is so bitter.
- Are they all the same thing?
- Wow, you really are something else.
- Drink it, it's good for you. It's okay.
[Captain Park downs his drink too.]
- It's good.
- That was good.
I'd take this over a piece of candy.
- Wow, seriously.
- I'd take this over candy any day.
[Dream Cup Boot Camp Training-
Off to their final location.]
[Dream Cup Boot camp Training-
Goal Precision Training.]
What's this?
- What are we doing here?
- You've completed your first two missions.
- Yes.
- This is your third and final training.
You've gained chance cards from
your first two races.
- Yes.
- Unbelievable, wasn't it?
- It was unbelievable.
- There's nothing he can't do.
The next training is the most important aspect
when it comes to scoring points in the game.
It's a training that helps you hone your
precision skills in scoring goals.
It's the one thing I'm very confident in.
- Why would you have any confidence in that?
- You've never scored a goal before.
Even though you've had the chance to run
out on the field these past two years
none of you has yet to score a goal except
for Yoo Jae Suk who almost had his chance.
I guarantee that I'll score a goal this year
if you'll only give me the chance to do so.
Me too.
What's that over there?
- It's a limousine.
- Who's in there?
Is someone going to get out?
Is it an actress?
[Who will alight from the limousine?]
It's really him!
[He's here.]
[Korean soccer legend, Cha Bum Geun.]
[Caster- 'Cha Bum Geun is Germany's
top number one player.']
[At the time, he was the best player
the league has ever seen.]
[1979- Frankfurt.
1983- Leverkusen.]
[Played in a total of 308 games.
Scored 98 goals.]
[But he never once kicked a penalty goal.]
[Dubbed by the Germans as
'Brown Fire Bomber.']
[Twice won the UEFA Cup from the league.
In Frankfurt in 1980, Leverkusen in 1988.]
[Jürgen Klinsmann-
Germany's legendary forward.]
[Won the World Cup in 1990
and led to victory of Euro Cup on 1996.]
['Even though I'm acknowledged as a pretty
good forward, but I'm no Cha Bum Geun.']
['There's the living legend in the stands.
He's Korea's Cha Bum Geun.']
[He rewrote the history of Korean soccer,
and he's here on Running Man.]
[He really came!]
[Flustered at seeing his most
respected senior here in person.]
Is this the car that you normally
ride around in?
[No, but we sent the car to him
when he graciously agreed to come here.]
[A visit from the living legend.]
[And a meeting with his former pupil.]
- Thanks for all your hard work.
- Thank you.
I really had no idea that he'd actually come
after our sudden call earlier this morning.
I came for Ji Sung.
['I came here for Ji Sung.']
[The man who made history in soccer...]
[And the one who followed in his footsteps.]
[Now... a legend meets another legend.]
When Ji Sung called for my help earlier...
I realized that I haven't seen him in a while,
and I really wanted to see him.
I didn't even get the chance to go
to his retirement ceremony either.
And I wanted to thank him for
all the hard work that he's done.
- Wow, that's amazing.
- That's so kind.
But since you're already here,
can you teach us a few things?
But you've got this top star
here right now.
- But this is different.
- Your teaching is different.
Ji Sung is good, but
learning directly from you is different.
Would you be able to gauge our skills
if you see how we kick the ball?
I'll be able to tell somewhat
once I see you guys out there.
When you either pass or shoot the ball
during crucial moments
then the eyes have to be kept
directly on the ball.
Whether you kick the ball with the top
of the side of your foot...
[A bad kicking stance.]
If you would've just kicked out your foot
like this, then it would've went straight out.
- The way he's explaining it is much better.
- Ji Sung never explained it like this.
- He just wants to be the only good player.
- He only cares about his own plays.
- He only cares about looking good himself.
- They still don't improve even if I do.
You can't be that mean.
- I think what he's saying is important.
- Yes, I agree.
Should we take turns kicking the ball?
- Since we have Coach Cha here...
- Should we all take turns kicking?
It's a real honor to have Coach Cha here
to coach us like this.
I know that it's too late
but when he used to teach soccer,
I really wanted to take a lesson.
I feel like I'm getting to live out
one of my dreams.
Let's have Ji Sung show us a demonstration.
[Park Ji Sung to show everyone
a demonstration of how it's done.]
For amateurs, it's important for them to get
the right foot stance next to the ball.
That's right, make a firm stance.
Just think of it as swinging your leg out
directly forward from the back.
Let's have Park Ji Sung show us all
a demonstration of how to do it.
- Shoot your leg out straight.
- Don't hurt yourself while doing it.
[Make a firm stance next to the ball...]
[And swing out the other foot
straight ahead.]
Don't move that foot on the side of the ball
until you've finished swinging your kick.
No, don't move that other foot.
No, don't move that foot
and just swing it out straight.
- No, just leave that foot alone.
- We can't move the foot.
[An explosion of practices.]
You have to have a firm footing.
Make a firm stance with that foot.
Think of standing up tall with
a slight lean off to the side.
[Lean the body weight slightly off
to the side when kicking the ball.]
[No matter what Coach Cha says,
they immediately fall into practice mode.]
- That's the way to do it.
- Coach Cha, I'd like to try it as well.
- Okay, give it a try, Ji Hyo.
- I'd like to give it a try as well.
Be careful with your foot
so that you don't hurt yourself.
[Blank Ji takes her turn with the kick.]
[Even though her kick may have been weak,
her direction was precise.]
It actually went towards the goal.
That was good.
- It went towards the goal.
- Coach Cha just said that it was good.
[A model student-
A firm stance and footing.]
It's different now that
we've had proper training.
You have to have a steady stance,
and find your balance.
[Coach Cha demonstrates the kick himself.]
[Steady stance... and a clean swing.]
- He's a hundred times better than us.
- He's on a whole different level.
[He's that good while wearing dress shoes.]
Go!
- He keeps interfering.
- He keeps playing around.
You can't kick if you're that sensitive.
Don't pay him any attention and just do it.
- Don't pay him any attention and just do it.
- No, then you won't be able to do it.
You have to forget about everything else.
[I love you, Coach Cha.]
[Mentality is just as important as skills
when playing out on the field.]
You have to keep going even if
he were to spit at you.
I'll just endure it.
Okay, here I go.
I'm really going.
[Ha Ha's kick.]
- That was too much.
- Not what you had intended.
- It wasn't totally bad.
- Thank you!
- Just need more practice. You have potential.
[Haroro is showing some potential!]
Okay, Gary's going to go.
[Decent stance and a strong kick.]
Good, that was a good kick.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, I'll kick this time.
[Last up is Kwang Soo.]
Knees bent, body forward,
and leg straight out.
- Yes, that's correct.
- He's a model student.
Wow, let's see this.
[Knees bent, body forward,
and leg straight out.]
[Huh? Something looks funny...]
[He did everything that he just said,
but something looks a little off.]
The stance was pretty good.
But your footing was
too far behind the ball.
[The problem was that his footing was
too far behind the actual ball.]
The footing should be more forward,
okay, I think I got it.
But your form wasn't bad.
[One point kicking lesson-
Don't cower the body, but kick naturally.]
- Okay, I got it.
- Can you show me, Jae Suk?
- There you go.
- I get it now.
- The way you use your shoulder is...
- You swing out your arms.
Stretch your arm out, and swing.
You didn't tell us anything about
stretching the arm out at first.
I'll try it again in that position.
Thank you.
Stretch out your arm.
There you go!
[His kick improves drastically with
one piece of advice from Coach Cha.]
- This is how you coach.
- This is how you do it.
[The effects of a one point lesson
that could be felt with their whole body.]
[Amazing- The only thing he did differently
was to stretch out his arm in front of him.]
Stretch out your arm.
Can you tell us who you thought
did the best job of kicking the ball?
- I'm your loyal pupil.
- Coach Cha, I'm your apt pupil.
- I didn't get to do that at first.
- Can you tell us some more pointers?
Him over there and this one.
[He chooses Kwang Soo and Gary.]
- I love you!
- Thank you!
[A kissing ceremony.]
Thank you so much!
- No, you didn't do that.
- Yes, I did.
If you're this good during your first lesson,
then you guys are really good.
I'm starting to feel the passion for soccer
bubbling up inside me right now.
- I really want to play now.
- Me too.
Coach Cha will be staying to watch
your mission to the end.
I will now reveal your next mission.
It's a kicking related mission.
You will all take turns
kicking the penalty kick.
But instead of a goal keeper
there will be two baseball players with
a baseball bat standing in front of the goal.
Those two players will bat the balls which
you'll try to kick into the net.
[If four out of the eight kickers can kick
the ball in, then the mission is a success.]
They're both currently baseball players
at a local university.
- Please take good care of us.
- Take good care of us.
Fighting!
[Kicker number one- Kim Jong Kook.]
Keep your eye on the ball.
- Kim Jong Kook, fighting!
- Fighting!
If you kick it just like that, then
they won't be able to stop the ball.
Okay, here I go.
[Locking in on where
he'll be kicking the ball.]
[Homerun]
[Jong Kook fails.]
- You're way too good.
- You really must be a baseball player.
- They're no joke.
- No, this is no joke.
[Kicker number two- Yoo Jae Suk.]
There's no reason why
we even need to have Ji Sung kick.
[Now only seven kickers are left.
Still has four goals to make.]
But it was a good kick.
[Nice kick, but still fails.]
[Jae Suk and Jong Kook have both failed.]
The penalty zone is too far.
[There you go, time to protest.]
The penalty kick is only eleven meters.
[Huh?]
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven.
[Checking to make sure it's only 11 ft.
to help out his pupils.]
- I think it's pretty much the same.
- It's not much of a difference.
[No kidding...]
- That's a little bit closer.
- But that's not much of a difference.
[The only way for them to repay his kindness
is to make the goal.]
Thank you, Sir!
We vow to succeed the mission.
We will make sure to repay you
for all your kindness and grace.
[Don't just try to fill it with words.]
Please... God of Ddakji!
Why are you talking about ddakji
when we're playing soccer?
[Kicker number three is praying to
the god of ddakji on a soccer field.]
[Team Running Man's first goal!]
[It's a miracle!
Big-nose scores a goal after his lesson!]
[God of ddakji... thank you!]
I can't believe that just happened!
[Only five chances now remain,
and three more goals must be made.]
[Kicker number four- Gary.]
- Come on, Gary!
- Gary!
[Gary, with an approval from Coach Cha...]
[Will he be able to live up to
the expectation as a star pupil?]
[A direct kick right through the center.]
[A great kick befitting of a star pupil.]
Thank you for your teachings!
Wow, that was amazing.
We only need two more, Ha Ha.
[The ball didn't even get close...]
That was almost insulting.
He was almost insulting with
the way he hit the ball out of there.
[Only three kickers left,
and they still need two more goals.]
Be careful and keep your eye on the ball.
[Kicker number six- Song Ji Hyo.]
[My foot...]
- That has to hurt.
- I bet that hurts.
- No, you did good.
- It's okay.
[The only kickers left remaining now are
Park Ji Sung...]
[... and Giraffe.]
[This isn't good.]
[Kicker number seven- Park Ji Sung.]
If Ji Sung doesn't make it in,
then we're in big trouble.
[Captain Park, with a high probability
of succeeding, but the problem is...]
[...him.]
[A precisely clean kick.]
[That's our Eternal Captain!]
[One more goal is needed in order
for them to succeed the mission.]
[Final kicker- Lee Kwang Soo.]
- You saw where to kick, right?
- Yes, I saw.
Knees bent, body forward,
and leg straight out.
- Fighting!
- Find the right footing.
[The footing... the footing...]
[Kwang Soo has shown that he's a good
follower of Coach Cha's instructions.]
[He was even chosen to be one
of the best kickers of the team.]
[Just do... as I've been taught.]
[Fail or succeed...
Everything rides on the Giraffe's kick.]
[Giraffe actually did it!]
[It's all thanks to your teachings!]
[Team Running Man improves their
kicking precision after just one lesson!]
Let's give a big round of applause to the two
players who came out to help us today.
[Thank you for your participation.]
More than anything else, let's give a huge
round of thanks to our Coach Cha.
[A heartfelt gratitude to Coach Cha.]
- With just one lesson from Coach Cha...
- Our skills have greatly improved.
[The miraculous effects of
the one pointer lesson.]
Since you've succeeded this mission,
there's an easier Captain's mission for you.
- Okay, bring it in.
- What's that now?
[A ring of fire?]
- This is the easier mission?
- Then what's the difficult mission?
The difficult mission was with a smaller
and a taller ring of fire.
Wow, that's not going to be easy.
To score a goal through that...
Even Coach Cha is saying that
making that goal isn't going to be easy.
[Captain's mission-
Kick the ball through the ring of fire.]
- For an amateur to make that goal...
- No, Ji Sung will be doing it.
Coach Cha, would you like to
give it a try?
- How about you give it a try?
- What do you do it with?
- Kick the ball through the ring.
- That's going to be tough.
Cha Bum Geun.
Only someone as good as
Park Ji Sung can do this.
- Wow, that's really high up there.
- Coach Cha! Coach Cha!
[For a living legend... it may be possible.]
- Let me practice first.
- Okay.
Coach Cha!
[Legendary Coach Cha
will do this mission himself!]
Then Coach Cha will do this mission himself,
and he'll have three chances to get it done.
[Kick the ball through the ring of fire
to succeed the mission.]
The last time I really kicked a ball...
I think it's been over ten years
since I've last kicked a soccer ball.
[Legendary Cha Bum Geun...
meets the ball for the first time in 10 years.]
[First attempt.]
I don't know about these dress shoes.
[No matter how difficult, if it's him...]
[Bounces off the rim!]
[How can this be!]
[Fails the first out of his three chances.]
[He truly is a legend! Almost
makes it in on his very first attempt!]
It's because I have these dress shoes on
and the ground is uneven.
See?
Did you see that?
It was the uneven ground...
- Can you try it one more time?
- Let me change into my soccer shoes first.
- Soccer shoes.
- Hand me a pair of soccer shoes.
Wow, Coach Cha is putting on
the soccer shoes.
[His competitive streak
is starting to peek out.]
[Legendary Cha Bum Geun...
He puts on the soccer shoes.]
[Cha Bum Geun's second attempt
after changing into his soccer shoes.]
- I think you've got this now.
- Let's give him some space.
Can you guys even out the
ground for me?
[Everyone jumps in to follow his wishes.]
Now that I've got the soccer shoes on...
Okay.
I'm starting to feel
my competitive streak coming out.
[Second attempt.]
[Will it... make it in this time?]
[Bounces off the ring again!]
[Precise direction! Everyone
thought that it was going to make it!]
[Fails the second out of three chances.]
[If it had been just a little bit lower...]
[His one last chance.]
[Throws the ball with his hands...]
[The ball with
everyone's hope riding on it...]
[He shoots it through!]
[Even though 25 years have passed
since his retirement...]
[His skills haven't diminished one bit.]
[A clean shot for the joy
of all his juniors and pupils.]
[The level of a legend's skills has been shown
right in front of everyone's eyes.]
This is the first time he's touched
a soccer ball in over ten years.
[A cheer of respect that bubbles up
from the bottom of their hearts.]
Let's give our Coach Cha another
big round of applause.
I guess Coach Cha was happy about it too
because he threw his hands up in cheer.
- He was so excited about it.
- That was a hard shot.
Since you succeeded the mission,
you win another chance card.
[Another chance card is won thanks to
the legend succeeding their mission for them.]
[Dream Cup Boot Camp Training ends.]
The only thing we have left to go
is the final competition.
[Only final competition remains-
A soccer match with the top idol athletes.]
[The bloody battle is about to start.]
I had a wonderful time today.
And to our beloved Park Ji Sung,
who has brought all of us in this country...
so much joy.
It truly has been the greatest gift.
It's a bit disappointing that we won't get to
see him play anymore now that he's retired
but I wish that our soccer fans will continue
to give their love and support to Ji Sung.
Thank you.
Please give another huge round
of applause to Coach Cha Bum Geun.
[Representative of Korean soccer,
Coach Cha- Thank you so very much!]
[Dream Cup Boot camp Training- Course Four.
Match against the top idol athletes.]
[Incheon soccer field.]
Thank you to everyone for all
your hard work.
This is your final mission of the day.
It's a soccer match against all the top
idol athletes.
[Soccer match against the top idol athletes.]
These are the idols who are rumored to be
quite good at playing soccer.
We carefully selected each player to
put together a formidable soccer team.
Please look off to the side to see
who your opponents are.
- Who is it?
- Look at the size of their shoulders.
[They don't look nervous in the least
even with Captain Park out on the field.]
[Chang Min, Dong Jun, Doo Joon, Ki Kwang,
Yoseob, Min Hyuk, Leo, and Baro.]
[It's nice to see you all!
A fierce battle waits for them ahead.]
- Wow, these guys are really good.
- These guys are great runners.
[Team Park Ji Sung is feeling the pressure.]
Doo Joon is a really good soccer player!
[Doo Joon and Leo
actually used to be soccer players.]
The star of 2002 World Cup who will
lead the Idol Team is...
Who is it?
[The star of 2002 World Cup?]
[His charismatic walk...]
The star of 2002 World Cup...
He's nicknamed The Sniper,
his name is Seol Ki Hyun!
[The Sniper, Seol Ki Hyun.]
[Can still remember
the excitement of the match.]
[The 2002 World Cup game against Italy-
The star of that miraculous moment.]
[Swept through all of Europe
including England and Belgium.]
[The real sniper, Seol Ki Hyun.]
Sniper Seol Ki Hyun is here
to coach the Idol Team!
But he's not going to
actually play in the game.
[Sniper Seol Ki Hyun...
reunites with Park Ji Sung.]
It's good to see you.
He looks like a model.
Hello, my name is Seol Ki Hyun,
and I'll be coaching the Idol Team.
He's so cool.
If you're going to be tall,
that's the right way to be tall.
Just being tall like Kwang Soo is no good.
- That's the way to be tall.
- We just have different styles.
[Even though your styles may be different,
we vote for Seol Ki Hyun's style.]
The main reason that I'm here is because
I haven't seen Ji Sung in so long.
It's been so long since I've had the chance
to see Ji Sung in person myself.
- Go stand next to him.
- Go stand over there.
Why are you being so shy?
[Former co-players who are finally reunited.]
I'm reminded of 2002 again.
The combo play between you two...
How is this game going to be played?
I will explain the rules of the games to you.
Running Man Dream Cup Idol Match.
First and second half of the game will
last 15 minutes each.
You can swap out the players anytime
you'd like at any given time.
How many chance cards have you won?
- Three.
- We have three of them.
The chance cards you have in your hands...
can be used to buy play time for
Park Ji Sung during this game tonight.
Each chance card will buy him
five minutes.
[Five minutes per card,
hence a total of 15 play time for Ji Sung.]
[His soccer uniform is at the dry cleaners.]
We will now start the first half!
[Team Seol Ki Hyun's Idol- Forward.]
Bring it down!
Bring it down here!
Let's take it easy!
[Coach Seol takes his coaching very seriously
as soon as the game starts.]
Ki Hyun, why are you taking this so seriously?
- Why are you taking it so seriously?
- Because you're going to be playing too.
It's because you'll be playing too.
We have to score as many goals
as we can before you get in the game.
Go, go!
[Baro's impressive footwork.]
Wow, they're so fast.
Why are there so many of them out here?
[Ki Kwang's solo play that requires
two players in an attempt to block him.]
[Attempts to kick in a goal
as soon as the game starts.]
[Much more formidable than
Team RM had ever imagined.]
Just hang out here, and don't move.
Just leave him.
He's no joke.
[A clean kick straight over to Ki Kwang.]
Get on him!
[Ki Kwang scores the first goal!]
[Team Park Ji Sung: 0
Team Seol Ki Hyun's Idols: 1]
[Even Coach Seol is impressed
with the goal.]
Score another one.
Let's score ten more before
Park Ji Sung gets out here.
[Score as many as they can
before Captain Park comes out to play?]
[Oh no... you'll be able
to help them out, right?]
[Team Ji Sung is on the offense for once,
and they're immediately intercepted.]
[Blank Ji's ball is stolen from her.]
[Giraffe's hands are kept frantically busy.]
[Min Hyuk scores another goal
for Team Seol's Idols.]
[Team Park Ji Sung is getting beaten!]
[Team Park Ji Sung: 0
Team Seol Ki Hyun's Idols: 2]
[Captain's wasted boot camp training.]
Should we bring Ji Sung in?
I don't think it'll make much difference
even if I were to go in the game.
Why do they all look so fresh
and cheerful?
[Fresh Idols- Singing is their hobby,
and soccer is their specialty.]
Should we make a switch?
[Is Captain about to go in?]
[The Idols are feeling the pressure.]
No, it's just me.
[We have to be more sparing
with the Captain.]
[Player swap-
Gary- in, Ji Hyo- out.]
Center.
You have to block the center.
[Will they be able to turn the game around
with the player swap?]
[Gary's long center kick.]
[A direct pass straight over to the Tiger.]
[This is our chance!]
[But Tiger is immediately surrounded
by the opponent's defense.]
[It's Big-nose Brother's crucial chance!]
Suk Jin!
[One on one against the goal keeper.]
[Kicks only the air in front of him.]
[It may be hard to believe,
but that's what really happened.]
[Just as I heard...]
[King of ddakji takes his frustration
out on the grass.]
Come down here, ddakji king!
Wow, what a waste.
[The striker's dream is lost within a second.]
[How will Idol Team's Ki Kwang fare?]
[Wow, what impressive footwork!]
[But he's my junior...]
[Without any hesitation... he shoots!]
[Please miss... please miss!]
[Idol Team's amazing shooting accuracy.]
[Team Park Ji Sung: 0
Team Seol Ki Hyun's Idols: 3.]
They've already scored three goals.
Suk Jin, should we switch?
[He's going to come out
during the first half?]
What do we do now?
[They don't seem to be ready
to face the Captain just yet.]
[Five minutes left in the first half...
Captain Park steps out onto the field.]
[Will he be able to turn the current score
of 3:0 around?]
He's in the game!
I'm so scared!
[What do we do now?]
Don't kick the ball towards Park Ji Sung!
[Attempts to pass the ball over to Ji Sung.
His attempt fails.]
We can do this!
[Coach Seol directs an order.]
[Become Captain Park's shadow.]
[Shadows Ji Sung's back.]
[Gary kicks the ball.]
[Like a bolt of lightning!]
[A shot like a bullet!]
[Unfortunately misses the goal!]
[Coach Seol's anxious coaching.]
We can still do this.
He's so fast!
That was unbelievable.
[An example how not to kick the ball.]
[Baro gets ready to accept the ball.]
[Definitely a man of two hearts.]
[Passes the ball over to Gary,
who's standing in front of the goal.]
[Will this finally score their first goal?]
[So close!]
[Ten years are shaved off their lives.]
The whole atmosphere of the team
is totally different now.
[Park Ji Sung's turn to drive the ball.]
Look at the guys just floundering around.
[A whopping total of four defensive players.]
[Just amazed at his footwork!]
When Park Ji Sung runs out there,
I feel like a rampant bull is running.
[The ball is passed back to Ji Sung.]
Go back!
Go back and catch him!
[Lets the ball fly toward the goal keeper?]
[Passes the ball directly over to Gary!]
[Ji Sung's assist!
Gary's goal!]
[Team Park Ji Sung finally
scores their first goal!]
[Fanatic bench ceremony!]
[Team Park Ji Sung: 1
Team Seol Ki Hyun's Idols: 3]
- This is good!
- It's okay, it's just one.
It was just one.
Can you count that as two points for us?
[First half is now over.]
The problem is...
we're not playing offense at all.
We have to play offense too.
The other team has a lot of guys who know
how to kick the ball around.
Let's think about the lesson
we received earlier.
- They're all real soccer players.
- We're so sorry, Coach Cha.
We really didn't want to disappoint you.
I don't know if I can use
the teaching that I was taught today.
[Please watch over us, Coach Cha.]
- We don't have much time.
- We have to keep running hard.
I think I can put myself on one person
and just stay on that person like glue.
- Just bite him down.
- Stick to him like a wad of gum.
Even if you end up kicking your opponent,
it's not a foul if the referee doesn't see it.
[He's slowly starting to think like
a true Running Man member.]
It's just that he's never been
caught yet.
Let's all do this.
[Second half- Start.]
Get out there.
Everyone get out there.
[Coach Seol is getting even more
serious about his coaching.]
[Oh my gosh- He gets greedy
about scoring on his own team.]
What in the world is the matter with you!
[Immediately surrenders to
his own mistake.]
[Do you like comedic soccer?]
You can't lose the ball.
[Team Seo Ki Hyun and Idol's
relentless attack.]
[Easily scores a goal
even from a difficult spot.]
[Lee Ki Kwang's impressive skills.]
Ki Kwang.
[Two chance cards are still left.
A total of ten play minutes for Ji Sung.]
[Team Ji Sung can't get the ball
past the center line.]
[Is he playing 'alkkaggi'
with the soccer ball?]
[Team Park Ji Sung: 1
Team Seol Ki Hyun's Idols: 5]
- Take it easy.
- Good job.
Wow, these guys are way too good.
[A thoughtful expression on his face.]
[Only ten minutes left in the game.]
I think I'm going to have to
take this off.
[Park Ji Sung decides to enter the game!]
[With only ten minutes left in the game,
will he be able to turn the game around?]
- He took his jacket off.
- This is crazy!
[Does it mean that Captain Park
is really going to bring it?]
We made him take off his jacket.
Wow, this is crazy!
Wait, how about we make
Park Ji Sung keep his jacket on?
[Idols are shaking in their shoes
at the sight of Ji Sung out on the field.]
Please don't scare them
too much, Ji Sung.
I'm sure they'll get out of my way
if they get scared.
['Kim-Enthusiastic' is already
wanting to escape.]
- Get out of his way if you're scared.
- Get ready to play defense!
[Should I get this game started?]
[Here he comes!]
[We're in big trouble now!]
[Shoots the bullet shot!]
[How will Captain Park's first shoot fare?]
[A goal post earthquake.]
He's starting to get worked up.
Any mistakes are going to
put me in a tough spot.
Don't make any mistakes.
You guys should know that
Ji Sung is fired up right now.
You guys had better take it easy!
Ji Sung is all fired up.
[Atmosphere of the whole team changes
whenever Captain Park gets near.]
[But Baro pulls forward through
the crowd.]
[Mommy!]
[He blocked it?]
[When did Captain Park get here?]
[Like a bolt of lightning!]
[An unbelievable level of focus
on the ball!]
Ji Sung is doing everything by himself.
Dong Jun and Chang Min.
Do it!
That was our chance!
[Competing against Coach Seol
in the coaching seat.]
Pass the ball!
Where did you learn moves like that?
[Tiger's long pass.]
[Passes it straight over to Captain Park.]
[A true work of art.]
[The ball unfortunately gets
cut off the Team Idol's defense.]
[The man with two hearts... Plays both
defense and offense simultaneously.]
[After trapping the ball with his chest,
he drives the ball across the field!]
[Captain Park- Finally explodes in fire!]
[Scores a goal within four seconds
of having the ball stolen away from him!]
Park Ji Sung!
[Team Park Ji Sung: 2
Team Seol Ki Hyun's Idols: 5]
[Even Coach Seol cheers for Ji Sung.]
- He truly is my brother!
- Get back here.
That's my brother!
[Captain Park doesn't disappoint!]
Republic of Korea!
Why am I so happy about him
scoring on us?
He's already dribbling the ball away.
[Even the opposing team
is in awe of his skills.]
[The amazing Park Ji Sung!]
[Dribbles the ball quickly, yet
scores the goal with calm and ease.]
[Good work, Ji Sung!]
[Game over]
[Team Park Ji Sung: 3
Team Seol Ki Hyun's Idols: 5- Wins.]
I know that Ji Sung is busy
with his retirement these days
but I'm so glad that I got to see him
like this tonight.
Even though it wasn't an official game
I'm so glad to have played this
one last game with him tonight.
All the players on the team played hard
and gave it their best tonight
and I'm grateful for their efforts.
I'd like to thank everyone for
their hard work and effort.
[Boot camp training in preparation
for 2014 Dream Cup...]
[All the preparations are now over.]
[There are no more practices.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[This is reality.]
[Set their feet down once again
on the field of dreams...]
[Dream Cup in Indonesia.]
[The toughest team they've ever
gone up against.]
[But we will persevere
with our fighting spirit.]
- What do you want from me?
- This is very dangerous.
[But fighting spirit alone
cannot help you survive in this place.]
[Indonesia- Survival in the wild.]
I really don't think that I can do this.
[Next Week's Running Man-
Dream Cup in Indonesia.]
Subtitles by DramaFever