Subtitles by DramaFever
[My Love from a Running Star]
[First record]
[From a galaxy far far away, an unidentifiable
object was seen flying across the sky.]
[August 25th, 1609.]
[A round disk-like unidentifiable object
was seen fleeing across the sky.]
[And...]
[Do Min Joon,
a man from an unknown world.]
[What is the fate that awaits him?]
[Hanyang- 400 years ago.]
What are we doing today that you
would have us dressed like this?
Do you remember your life
from back in the 1600's?
- Yes, I do remember.
- Oh, wow.
Why?
Why do you ask?
- Why do you look so surprised?
- You don't think this question is odd?
Yes, I know it's a bit odd...
but yes, I do remember.
Then is Seonjo... is he our current king?
[Year 1614-
King Gwanghae is currently in reign.]
No, Seonjo is not in reign.
Yes, I think I know the year we're in.
I can sense that Spring is near.
Even though Spring is near,
but my heart...
My heart is still feels cold
like a block of ice.
Where could my love be right now?
Could my love be shivering from the coldness
in her heart like I am right now?
I will not...
I will not take her into my bed!
[What are you doing?]
Everyone...
did I shock you with my performance?
That was just my acting.
You can stop your acting now.
I'm just getting started.
We have to do all this stuff.
[We hope... that you'll get a role in a
good historical drama in the near future.]
What is this?
[Scholar Kkuk- Resembling more of a General
with his big stature.]
Find the jade hairpin.
- Find the jade hairpin.
- Jade hairpin?
I have found someone...
whom I never want to forget.
[The jade hairpin that became symbolic of
Do Min Joon and Cheon Song Yi's fateful love?]
Find the jade hairpin.
But if your identity tag gets taken away
from you, you'll have to come to a cease?
This tag?
That is your identity tag.
[Name tag of the Joseon era.]
Is there something back there?
Is this the identity tag?
We have to come to a halt if this is taken
away from us before we find the jade pin?
I have a feeling that a game similar to this
is going to become popular in the future.
[Then could this be where the name tag
elimination game originated from?]
Is the jade hairpin in this
village somewhere?
[Find the jade hairpin that's hidden
somewhere within this village.]
Come hither!
Is no one out there?
Where has everyone gone off to?
Let's see here.
Where is that jade hairpin hidden?
[Just as it was stated...
they must find the hairpin in Hanyang.]
A noble gentleman is supposed to stately walk
around with his hands behind his back.
[Must say goodbye to his gentle disposition
for the sake of accomplishing the mission.]
The size of these face cutouts are
perfect for Ji Hyo and I.
Don't you think that this cutout is
the perfect size for my face?
See?
My face fits perfectly in here.
[A perfect fit.]
If we had met 400 years ago...
we really could've been something special.
Isn't that a jade hairpin?
Excuse me.
[But... the jade hairpin must have
the letter 'R' engraved on it.]
Isn't this a jade hairpin?
- It's a cheap knockoff.
- A cheap knockoff?
[That's not the jade hairpin you want...]
[Now that they take a closer look,
jade hairpins are seen all over the place!]
Wait.
I'm just a passerby,
but can I check your hairpin?
Wait.
Can I check out your hairpin?
[Gentle nobleman or not,
main priority is to find the jade hairpin.]
No, it's not it.
I apologize.
I won't ever forget you.
Ahoy there, Scholar Blank.
Why are you laying your hands on a
delicate woman's body like that?
- What are you talking about?
- You're a total scoundrel.
[Scholar Blank is chastising Scholar Yoo
for laying his hand on a woman's body.]
What kind of a noble scholar are you to walk
around with your hair so red like that?
- This is my personal style.
- Are you out of your mind?
Do not cast an amorous glance
at just any women.
- How dare you.
- How dare you!
Do you think that every women out here
likes you or something?
- What are you talking about?
- You're walking around smiling at everyone.
- This is what you're walking around doing.
- When did I ever do that with my eyes?
- Look at you. You're nothing but trouble.
- You need to be more careful with your words.
- You are a troublemaker!
- You watch yourself!
- Don't even act like you know me.
- All you women, be aware!
- You need to watch yourself.
- Yoo Jae Suk is on the loose!
I really feel like I'm back in
the Joseon era.
What's 'Ok-bineoh'? (Jade hairpin).
Who has an ok-bineoh'?
How can that be?
There's a yellow haired person over there.
Excuse me...
but where do you hail from?
- He's asking where you're from.
- Australia.
Australia?
I love Australia.
This is so fascinating?
Are those things to keep your ears warm?
Yes, they are.
Fantastic.
I'm sorry, Jong Kook!
Jong Kook, I'm so sorry!
- Just hold still.
- Yes, I'll just hold still.
[Even though the times may have changed,
the order in the food chain never changes.]
- Let's go find the jade hairpin.
- Yes, I understand.
I dedicate my life to you in servitude!
- Where shall we go?
- I think that it's on a person.
- Quick, aren't I?
- Yes, you're very quick.
- Okay, let's go start looking.
- Yes, but if you'll let go of me...
No, I have this odd feeling that you and I
are somehow meant to be together like this.
- No, we're not.
- Look, there's a hairpin.
[Just then, they see a jade hairpin!]
- We need to walk in a more leisurely fashion.
- Excuse me.
- Is that a jade hairpin?
- My lady!
- Please excuse me.
- Hello.
I never knew that such a fine lady
lived in this village.
- I had no idea.
- Can we take a look at your hairpin?
Is that a real jade hairpin?
- Allow me to take out your hairpin.
- Is this hairpin made of jade?
[Scholar Kkuk pulls out the Lady's hairpin
as if pulling off a name tag.]
- Please excuse me.
- Allow me to apologize in his place.
[Please excuse Scholar Kkuk's rudeness.]
[No marking of the letter 'R'.]
It's a village celebration!
Watch yourself!
Join me in the celebration!
[His dance moves are about 400 years
ahead of their time.]
Come on, join me!
This is a celebration!
[It... fell off...]
Why did you have to dance like that?
- What are you doing?
- It's because you moved!
- But that was...
- That pulled off real easily.
- I can't believe it snapped off like that.
- What are you doing? Put it back!
- I didn't mean to do that.
- Jong Kook!
- I'm serious.
- How could you do this to me?
[So things were exactly the same
even 400 years ago...]
I really didn't mean to do that.
I was just holding it, and it broke off.
I didn't know it was that flimsy.
Am I really out?
Is it really over for me now?
I'm going to get my revenge!
Even though it may be over for me
like this in this lifetime...
I vow...
I vow to get my revenge
against that lowlife scoundrel!
[Thus, Scholar Kwang Soo's story
comes to an end...]
[Meanwhile]
Pardon me, but I need to check
your hairpin.
Will you please allow me to do that?
Come hither.
I need to check your hairpin.
No, this one isn't marked.
I'm sorry for the intrusion.
Please excuse me.
I must hurry and find the
jade hairpin.
[Elegant stature.]
No, I don't think this is it.
Wait, you're...
[Wait, this young woman is...]
Are you...
the Grim Reaper?
[Even though she captured the heart of
Do Min Joon 400 years ago...]
[She tragically had to say
her goodbye in the end.]
Come here.
[Quickly pulls her away in hiding to keep her
from being discovered by the others.]
Song Yi!
What are you doing here, Song Yi?
I can't believe that it's you!
Do you know how much I love you
in the drama?
- Are you cold? Here, wear this.
- I feel cold.
You have no idea how much I enjoyed
watching you in the drama.
- I bet you're cold. I'm a huge fan of yours.
- Thank you.
Please find a palanquin for me to hide in
so that I may escape out of here.
You need a palanquin?
[Escape? A palanquin?]
I will...
protect you.
[I will protect you.]
We need to find a palanquin.
Where shall we go?
Come on, let's go.
I'm such a huge fan. Let's take a picture.
Can I take a picture of us together?
Yes, you may.
- Where's the palanquin?
- I do not know that either.
[Could Scholar Ha be her protector
like Do Min Joon was?]
[Or... is he like an older fan of hers?]
Okay, we need to stay cautious.
Over there.
I see someone.
Can you keep an eye on Song Yi for me?
Stay back here.
Stay here, and stay hidden.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, I understand.
Camera team.
All of you get back there too.
Come on, and get back there.
Hurry up and get back there.
You're going to get us caught.
Don't you know what's going on here?
This is a special situation.
[Once in a lifetime chance for Scholar Ha?]
- I will return once I've found the palanquin.
- Okay, I understand.
Do you have any money?
This is a variety show!
You take credit cards?
That's amazing.
Get money from your VJ,
and get yourself a snack.
[Even though he may not have any money,
he's still trying to take care of Song Yi.]
I will return soon with the palanquin.
Just wait here for a moment.
[Now that the jade hairpin has been found...
he has to find the 'R' marked palanquin.]
Isn't that a palanquin?
What is that thing over there?
This looks similar to a palanquin.
Isn't this it?
I would appreciate it if you would
pull the coat down for a moment.
I need to check your hairpin.
If you go that way...
wait, they're over there.
That's Song Ji Hyo.
Come on, let's get away from here.
[Discovers Scholar Blank and
Scholar Kkuk off in the distance.]
[Runs away as soon as he sees them.]
How is it that we keep running into
each other like this?
[No matter where he escapes to,
he's still within Scholar Kkuk's grasp.]
- We must be destined to be together.
- I have some business to tend to.
- Master Ji.
- Please hold on.
- Yes?
- Wait a moment.
- There you are, Master Ji.
[Scholar Blank is now on the scene too.]
- Master Ji.
- You two have me surrounded.
[Big-nose is caught between
a rock and a hard place.]
- I have some information for you.
- Information?
I just saw Yoo Jae Suk pass by this area.
[Attempts to avoid danger by selling
Scholar Yoo out... and he fails.]
I have a bad feeling about this.
Wait a minute.
[Already predicting his own outcome.]
How can I make this look most entertaining?
Would it be better for me to
attempt an escape
or would it be better for me to give
you easy access to my back?
Okay, then I'll see you later.
I feel like something like this
may happen in the future too.
[Scenes like this...
are going to happen often.]
You scoundrel!
How dare you approach me?
- You scoundrel.
- Scholar Song.
How dare you try to oust me in front
of this row of drying corn?
[There's just no way of escaping from
Scholar Kkuk and Scholar Blank Duo.]
- I'm sorry.
- In front of all these drying corn?
I'm sorry.
- You pulled it off?
- You pulled it off already?
- It just broke off.
- That's so flimsy.
- I noticed that it's very flimsy.
- My goodness.
I think I need to get this checked out.
[I'm going to get this checked out,
and I will see you in 400 years.]
Young Master Gae!
- Young Master Ha!
- Ahoy there!
Young Master Kim and Young Master Song
are in cahoots.
- Who and who?
- Let's go and eliminate them together.
- We need to join our forces.
- Who did you say is working together?
- It was Young Master Kim.
- Young Master Kim?
Yes, that's right.
I can't believe he used Song Ji Hyo
to get to me like that.
[Lovesick Scholar Gae... Out!]
Where is this jade hairpin?
[Scholar Yoo is still in search
for the jade hairpin.]
Hold on a moment.
[He discovers Song Yi in hiding.]
Is it... Eun Hye?
[Unable to recognize her right away
with her face hidden behind her coat.]
I thought she was Eun Hye.
I thought that we were finally getting...
am I wrong?
Is that not Eun Hye over there?
Excuse me, Maiden.
May I take a look at your hairpin?
By any chance...
[Wait, this young maiden is...]
[In that case...]
By any chance...
is that the jade hairpin?
- Am I right or wrong?
- You're right.
- What do I need to do?
- Find the palanquin for me to ride in.
Isn't it over once I take the jade hairpin?
What is it that you're doing?
[Unable to hold back her laughter from seeing
Scholar Grasshopper standing before her.]
You're aware of the danger luring outside,
aren't you?
So that I'm able to make my escape...
please find the palanquin for me to ride in.
- Is that what I need to do?
- Yes.
- Yep.
- Yep?
[Alien language for the 1600's.]
Do you know what year this is?
This is the 1600's. What do you mean, 'Yep'?
'Heol', 'Daebak', 'Uh-jjeol'.
('Wow', 'Awesome', 'What the...')
[Scholar Yoo has already decoded
the foreign alien speech.]
[Trying to regain her composure.]
The palanquin...
What are you doing right now?
What is it that you're doing?
- Do I need to bring the palanquin back here?
- You need to give me a ride.
Yep.
- Okay, I understand. Stay here, okay?
- Yes, I understand.
Then I will see you momentarily.
Nice to meet you.
- Please hurry.
- I understand.
[Wow... awesome.]
Find the jade hairpin,
and now, find the palanquin?
[Scholar Yoo sets out in a search
for the palanquin.]
[Some magical way of traveling
over water?]
Servant!
[Servant Gwon Yeol is rushing to keep up
with Scholar Yoo in his wake.]
Watch where you're walking.
- I'm sorry.
- Watch where you aim that thing.
[Servant Gwon Yeol's legs are about to give up
on him from having followed Jae Suk's path.]
Wow, I thought that was
the palanquin for a moment.
Look at this.
What could this be?
It's a palanquin!
I see a palanquin over there!
[Scholar Yoo finds the palanquin at last!]
- You can either bring her here...
- What are you even saying right now?
I found the palanquin because
I was told to find the palanquin.
I found the hairpin you wanted me to find,
and then you say to find the palanquin.
Now that I've found the palanquin,
you want me to bring the maiden with the pin?
- You're telling me to bring her here?
- You should've brought her with you.
[Master... please come back to me.]
So I need to bring her back to the palanquin?
[Now he must bring Maiden Song Yi
back to where the palanquin awaits...]
I'm getting a bad feeling.
Wait... where did...
where did the young maiden go?
[The maiden... is gone?]
[Just moments ago...]
Just remain a little bit more patient.
I've searched all over the place.
- But I haven't been able to find anything.
- Master Yoo has been here.
No! Come here.
You need to come with me.
Here, grab my hand.
[Took the maiden away to hide her somewhere
else so that Master Yoo can't find her.]
Master Yoo has been by to see you?
[Scholar Yoo was one step too late.]
Wait... where did the maiden go?
- She left.
- When did she leave?
Ha Ha came and took her away.
How could this be?
Young maiden.
I know that it's cold,
but stay here for just a bit, okay?
- Okay, I understand.
- I'll go and figure out what's going on.
Our secret code is going to be... 'Sorry'.
Sorry, okay?
Give it a try.
- Sorry.
- Okay, sorry.
Sorry.
- Sorry.
- Okay, sorry.
Come out when you hear me say the code.
I'll go find it real quick.
Please return quickly.
- Sorry.
[Scholar Ha is desperately
seeking the palanquin.]
[Now that he thinks about it, how
is he going to bring the palanquin back?]
I wonder if I should bring her with me?
[Maybe it would be better if he brought
Maiden Song Yi with him?]
Sorry.
[Scholar Kkuk]
Scholar Ha?
[How did he know that she was here?]
- Who told you such lies?
- Master, I need to escape out of here.
- Please find me a palanquin...
- Why are you telling him such odd lies?
- Shut your mouth!
- Shut my mouth?
- Maiden...
- Maybe I should eliminate him.
- Find me a palanquin so that I may escape...
- Maiden, please stop talking.
You need to come with me.
- Wait, I'm sorry, but we love each other!
- Come here.
[Renders Scholar Ha helpless
in the blink of an eye.]
- Stop it!
- You scoundrel! Do you know who I am?
- What?
- You scoundrel!
- Okay, just wait.
- Wait for what?
Where did my fists go?
Maiden.
I'm sorry, but please help me out.
We're supposed to be in love.
I'm trying to save you.
You can't just ignore my plight.
[Scholar Ha is trying to weasel himself
out of the predicament.]
Just hold on a minute!
Let go of me.
We're all done here.
You really are something else.
- Where did my arms go?
- This is a nice hanbok.
- I'll see you in 400 years.
- See you in 400 years.
I need to find Ha Ha.
Ha Ha.
[Another huge boulder to cross...]
[He thought she was with Scholar Ha,
but she's with Scholar Kkuk instead...]
Look who it is.
Scholar Blank!
Scholar Yoo!
I'm on my way out!
Have you found anything?
Who is that?
What do you mean?
You know what that is.
Haven't you already met the maiden?
Well... I have seen her on the drama,
'My Love From Another Star'.
I've already told him.
- Why did you tell him that?
- She already told me.
- Why are you acting like you don't know?
- I think there's a misunderstanding.
Where are you planning on
taking her?
I'm not taking her anywhere,
but we're going to escape together.
Just give me a moment.
I need to ask the maiden something.
- Just a moment.
- Okay.
Maiden.
- Why must I do that?
- Listen to me.
- Please help me out.
- Master Yoo wants me to go to your back...
- and wants me to pull off your tag.
- What are you doing!
- Why are you...
- What are you telling her to do?
- Why are you telling her to do that?
- It's just a misunderstanding.
- What are you doing?
- Why are you telling the maiden to do that?
I'm not on anyone's side.
My priority is to make my escape out of here.
I just need to find my palanquin and
get out of here.
I get the feeling that you know
where it is.
I'm not quite sure where it is.
What does that mean?
You either know, or don't know.
What kind of an answer is that?
It means that I don't know,
and I'm not sure about anything else.
- Don't you know what I'm saying?
- Lead the way.
Lead the way,
or I will take this as a challenge.
- Don't you think that you're being too harsh?
- No, I'm not being harsh.
- Come with us.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
[Agreeing to go together.]
Maiden... why did you tell him that?
I like everything else about you,
but you're too light of the mouth.
Why are you trying to
get her to do bad things?
- How is that a bad thing?
- That is a bad thing.
[With the maiden in between...
their mouths never take a rest.]
- See? You knew where it was.
- That's why I'm taking you there.
- See? You knew where it is.
- Wait just a moment.
Be careful.
[Maiden Song Yi's skirts gets caught
on the steps.]
That's why you should've been
more cautious.
You should've been more cautious.
- I knew that you'd do something like that.
- Scholar Kim.
You should've been more careful.
- I was concerned about the maiden's skirt.
[The Grim Reaper appears as
Scholar KKuk's guide.]
- Why am I getting the Grim Reapers?
- Goodbye!
- Why am I getting these two?
- If the maiden's skirt hadn't been caught...
- You just wait and see.
- Wait and see what?
- I will get my revenge.
- Just get out of here.
- Goodbye!
Let's go, Maiden.
You stepped on your skirt
at the right moment.
- Did you do that on purpose?
- No, it wasn't done on purpose.
- It wasn't done on purpose?
- Yep.
[No matter what the case,
all thanks to the help of her skirt...]
I can't tell you how hard I've worked
to find this palanquin for you.
There it is.
Watch your step.
Thanks for all your hard work.
There it is.
Take your seat.
- I can't express how thankful I am.
- No, not at all.
Even though I almost fell into danger
because of your light mouth...
I'm just glad that we were still able to
get to where we are now.
No matter who, or what you are,
you are still my savior.
- No, not at all.
- As a sign of my gratitude...
- I'd like to give you this book as a gift.
- What is this?
Please read the book and prepare yourself
for what may happen to you in the future.
Does this contain secrets of the future?
Master.
- There is something that I must tell you.
- What is it?
The truth is...
I... really like you.
I...
really like you.
[Same Master...
but a totally different feeling...]
[Trying her best to maintain her composure.]
My late grandmother told me that
farewells must be said in advance.
That when the real time comes to say your
farewells, you won't get your chance to do so.
Master, thank you for everything
you've done.
No, please don't mention it.
Other than the fact that you like to
spill all the secrets...
I won't ever forget you.
I'll never be able to forget you.
Yes, then I wish you all the luck with school
since school is back in session.
Safe travels.
Please be careful.
Then do I keep this book in
my possession?
- Goodbye.
- Safe travels.
Will we meet again in the future?
I don't know!
Are you angry?
- Good luck back in school.
- Thank you.
[Part two will start in 30 seconds.]
Just what is the identity of this book?
This book is a book of prophecy that will
predict the future events of this nation?
Future forecast.
In 2002, the whole nation will be swept up
in an uproar in a celebratory mode.
Is this talking about the 2002 World Cup?
How would you know about that?
I just get the feeling that it is.
Second day of 2002.
The longest numbers on this day are,
16, 18, 24, 42, 44, and 45.
Is this talking about the lottery drawing?
How would you know about that?
[Go where the horses run free, and the
berries flow like water to find your answer.]
What place is this talking about?
No matter who or what you are,
you are still my savior.
[A book of prophecy handed to him
by Maiden Song Yi.]
[It definitely sounds like something that
may happen 400 years in the future...]
[Just what is the fate that awaits him?]
[My Love From a Running Star-
Second Record.]
This is the period of enlightenment.
[Period of enlightenment- Seoul.]
Have you seen this movie?
'Love Announcer and the Mother'?
Of course, I have seen it.
[Full of history and memories.]
This is what you call, a telephone.
- You can talk to someone from afar.
- Is this what you're talking about?
[A cellphone from the future?
Could Gary be from another star?]
This is the place where I used to fight
when I was in my twenties.
[Running Man members are transported
to Korea's period of enlightenment.]
No, I won first place.
Aren't you the one who had your tag ripped
off by me in the past?
I've already got my eyes on you,
so you better watch out.
- What is it that we have to do?
- What is that in your hand?
[Welcome, Running Envoy.]
[A special mission that requires
some emergency planning.]
We have put five yang in each of your pockets
without your knowledge.
- In here?
- What do you mean? You handed it to us.
[Five yangs were handed out
to each of the members.]
We are going to start a special mission
which will allow you to earn more funds.
A person who decides to take on the mission
can bet money on themselves.
- Is that right?
- I see.
And should you succeed your mission,
you'll earn twice the amount of the bet.
But should you fail the mission...
the money will be confiscated.
The first person to earn ten yangs will be
given a huge bonus compensation.
[A huge bonus compensation to the first
member who earns ten yangs.]
Okay, Ha Ha can start.
[Determine who will do the mission
by drawing straws.]
- It's not me either.
- Not me.
- It's not me.
- It's one of those two.
[Ji Hyo and Kkuk are it.]
[Scholar Kkuk and Scholar Blank
worked together even in the past...]
[The competition is... 'Book Slamming'.]
- Jong Kook's not very good at this.
- You'll take turns with the book slamming.
[Will take turns with the book slamming,
and the person who fails to flip loses.]
- I don't know about this.
- Then going first may not be good.
- I think who goes first may be important.
- I'm betting on Ji Hyo.
I bet one on myself.
- In that case...
- It's not that I'm awful at this game...
- But I get very nervous.
- I bet four on Jong Kook.
[Jae Suk bets four yangs on Jong Kook!]
[And the nagging is just a bonus?]
- Four?
- Okay, I bet four.
I bet two on myself.
I bet everything I have on Jong Kook.
[Going all in!
Bets everything on Jong Kook.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
I hope that you win.
[Rock, paper, scissors to determine
who will get to go first.]
[Ji Hyo wins.]
- Song Ji Hyo!
- I won.
- Tell him to go first.
- Okay, I want Jong Kook to go first.
[Kkuk to go first.]
[Is Mr. Capable nervous?
Muttering to himself over and over.]
I'm not even nervous right now.
See the smile on my face?
[So please don't get too nervous...]
- You won't be able to do it.
- This is no big deal.
- Here I go.
- Okay, do it.
Come on and do it!
You can do it!
This is all ready to get flipped over already.
- I'm nervous to death!
- Stop being so nervous.
[The divine Mr. Capable is nervous
in front of the Book Slamming game?]
- I'm nervous to death.
- That coin is ready to get flipped over.
It wants to get slammed.
It's ready to get flipped over.
Look at how it's ready for you already.
- Just do it.
- It's ready to flip over, isn't it?
- You've done it, it's no big deal.
- Just do it already.
[Finally goes for it.]
- Get ready to win.
- You know where to hit it, right?
[Kkuk succeeds.]
[Elated as if he just won the World Cup
all by himself.]
- No, that counts.
- But you didn't say, 'Challenge'.
- Ji Hyo's turn.
[It's now Ji Hyo's turn.]
Here I go.
[Goes for it immediately without
any fanfare?]
[So very easily succeeds.]
- Song Ji Hyo!
- You did great.
[Deserving of her 'Ace' reputation!]
[Kkuk's turn once again.]
He's nervous, he's nervous.
You're so nervous right now.
We won!
- We did it.
- Let's go with best out of three.
Let's go with best out of three.
I went first, right?
And since I failed this last round...
we'll say that we play another round
and if Ji Hyo wins again, then that's that.
- What are you talking about?
- She already won.
Don't you know what era we're in?
This is the time of enlightenment.
[Time of enlightenment... what about it?]
- Do you even know what that means?
- This is the time of enlightenment.
- We have a condition.
- What's your condition?
Kim Jong Kook has to drink
a bottle of cola.
[Kim Jong Kook to drink a bottle
in one shot.]
- What kind of a condition is that?
- Okay. We accept your condition.
- We accept.
- Okay, deal.
[One shot of cola.
Deal is made without his approval.]
- Do you want to lose?
- I bet five yangs on you!
I bet everything I have on you!
- You only bet one yang!
- Give me back my money then!
We bet everything we have on you.
- What are you doing?
- You can't drink a bottle of cola for us?
What do you think you're doing?
Just drink the cola! We've bet everything!
- Just drink a bottle of cola!
- Let's do this!
You can't say anything else after this.
[A scene that can't be missed.
Kim Jong Kook drinking a bottle of cola.]
I'll drink all this in one shot.
So let's go for best out of three.
- Come on.
- But it doesn't count if he burps.
- But if he doesn't burp...
- Deal. He can't burp for five seconds.
[Can't burp for five seconds after
chugging the bottle in one shot.]
[The negotiation is over again
without his consent.]
We bet all our money on you.
We bet everything we had,
and it's just one bottle of cola.
- Just don't burp!
- Don't burp for five seconds.
Set, go.
Just open up your throat.
You've seen it done before.
There's no time limit, so take your time.
- Even the way he drinks is frightening.
- If you have to burp, then do it now.
- Even his throat has muscles.
- It's like shooting a commercial.
- He actually looks sexy.
- You should take off your shirt.
[It's a cola fountain.]
- What the heck!
- You failed.
[Book Slamming Game-  Ji Hyo wins!]
Let's just play one more round.
Let's do what we've agreed to.
We need to admit that you lost.
You're a sore loser, aren't you?
- You need to accept the inevitable.
- Accept that you lost.
- You need to accept your defeat.
- You're on his side, aren't you?
- Of course, we are!
- We're totally on the same team!
[How can you even question that?
Of course, we are!]
I'm a penniless beggar now
because of Jong Kook.
Song Ji Hyo wins.
[Two yangs in the first round,
and three yangs in the second-  Ji Hyo wins!]
A special book of prophecy will be given to
Ji Hyo for being the first to win ten yangs.
- Nostradamus?
- A Nostradamus book?
- You can't show anyone else.
- Then you must've gotten something earlier.
- You must've got something too earlier.
- Why did you give that to her in front of us?
[Just what... could this be?]
I guess this is all going to come down to
the use of my physical strength later on.
Let's go.
Let's just go for now.
[Off to the next era.]
[The mystic prophet, Nostradamus.]
[First prophecy.]
[In the Eastern Peninsula of the five colors,
people of the world will gather hand in hand.]
After two thousand years have passed,
and on the seventh moon...
the moon will swallow up the sun and
plunge the world into darkness.
That's the eclipse.
[And... the third prophecy.]
[Could this be?]
[Part three will start in 30 seconds.]
[The Book Slamming Game from
a moment ago.]
[The time... came to a stop?]
[And some mystical power took control of
the coin to ensure it didn't flip over.]
[Just... how did that happen?]
[Earlier this morning.]
Mr. Do Min Joon.
Mr. Do Min Joon?
[Do... Min... Joon?]
[Do Min Joon of Running Star- Ha Ha.]
[Ha Ha is Do Min Joon?]
Why are you laughing?
You left your home, Gold Planet, and crash
landed on earth in your UFO 400 years ago.
And since then, you have been living here
on this earth for the past 400 years.
- Cheon Song Yi, whom you met 400 years ago...
- Song Yi.
Song Yi!
You still miss and long for Song Yi,
whom you met 400 years ago, right?
Yes, you're right.
Of the members that are here today...
your soul mate, Cheon Song Yi,
is in presence within one of them.
- She's here? Song Yi is here?
- Yes, she is here.
- And since you're an alien...
- That is correct.
What is the special power that
Do Min Joon possesses?
Ability to travel through time,
ability to pause time, and to teleport.
- Yes, he does have all those powers.
- Yes, he does.
- You really must love the drama.
- Yes, I've seen all the episodes.
- No need to explain the powers to you then?
- I will not let Jae Kyung get away with it.
Jae Kyung is so frightening.
He's scary even when he smiles.
Ha Ha from another star...
[My Love From a Running Star...]
[You must rescue your soul mate,
Song Yi, from danger...]
[And return home to Gold Planet,
to live happily ever after with all the gold.]
May I go to the opening in my own style?
- Yes, you may.
- Teletransportation.
[Haroro is the best when it comes to
the usage of his supernatural powers?]
[When the time came to a standstill...]
[It was Ha Ha's usage of his superpowers!]
We won!
[See the strength of Ha Ha's powers!]
- We won.
- Let's go for best out of three.
- What's your condition?
- Jong Kook drinks a bottle of cola.
[And even made Jong Kook drink
a bottle of cola.]
[My Love From a Running Star-
Final Record.]
[I, Do Min Joon...
have waited 400 years for this day.]
[The day that I get to return to Gold Planet
with my love, Cheon Song Yi.]
400 years.
400 years ago...
I never got to seat my Song Yi
on that palanquin.
[Even though fate brought them together
before anyone else 400 years ago...]
[Their tragic fate tore them apart before he
could seat her on top of her palanquin.]
[Just wait a little bit longer, Song Yi.]
[You from another star, Ha Min Joon-
Board the UFO with your Song Yi to win.]
The UFO's door will open in two hours.
You must stay on the run and escape from
being captured for those two hours.
If I miss my chance this time, then I'll have
to live here for another 400 years.
You must first reunite with Cheon Song Yi,
who's desperately waiting for you.
Is Cheon Song Yi back again?
- Of course, she is.
- But the young version of her left already.
[If you're saying that it's Cheon Song Yi...]
[Could it be her?]
Why are you making me all nervous now?
Wait a minute.
No way.
Then is there another guest on the show
other than our regular members?
You won't be disappointed.
This is driving me crazy.
[Could this be the day?]
[Who could our Cheon Song Yi be?]
Could you be the one from another star?
[Am I Do Min Joon?]
If you want to check and see if you are
Do Min Joon from another star
then you must reunite with Cheon Song Yi.
Ways to reunite with Song Yi-
Find the drama script,
and reenact a scene from the show.
If you are Do Min Joon,
then you will hear a bell in the distance
when you're finished reenacting the scene.
Even if you are not Do Min Joon
you can still win by boarding the UFO
once you find the gold key to it.
So we can still win
even if we aren't Do Min Joon.
- Do you understand it?
- Yes, I do, but let me look at it again.
The UFO door will open in two hours,
and only one human can board the ship.
So it's one of the two.
Either Do Min Joon, or board the UFO.
Am I right?
Gold planet?
So the prize... must be gold?
In two hours?
So the time is already predetermined?
[In order to board the ship,
you must remain alive for two hours.]
I have to find the script
and reenact a scene.
I've already received my book of prophecy.
[Jae Suk received a book of prophecy from
the younger version of Song Yi earlier.]
Go to where the horses run free, and the
berries flow like water to find your answer.
So this is where the script must be.
I need to figure out if
I'm Do Min Joon or not first.
But if it's Cheon Song Yi...
then is Jeon Ji Hyun coming?
I've never seen her in person before.
I can't help but feel excited.
Cheon Song Yi?
[Everyone is hoping for Jeon Ji Hyun.]
In that case, that Nostradamus book
that I received earlier...
it mentioned something about
a flock of evil.
Ultimate evil will come forth in darkness
to throw the world into a state of chaos.
Which means that one of us is
the ultimate force of evil.
[An ultimate force of evil is
hiding amongst them!]
So we don't know who the evil is,
nor who Cheon Song Yi or Do Min Joon is?
- It's possible that you could be Do Min Joon.
- So be sure not to get eliminated, right?
[Who could be the force of evil
that's threatening everyone's happiness?]
Where's the script?
[First things first- Find the script
and see if you are Do Min Joon.]
[Cellphone with an 'R' sticker?]
[A cellphone in hiding with
the 'R' sticker on it!]
Here's something.
[My Love From Another Star's script is
saved onto the phone!]
Stop doing everything and don't move.
Or I will kick you out of here.
Who knew that I'd find it this quickly?
[Ace Blank Ji is the first
to find the script!]
Okay, I found the script now.
So who's Cheon Song Yi?
Could it be?
Could it be that young girl from earlier?
[Who could the mysterious Cheon Song Yi be?]
[The time is getting closer for the
UFO to depart...]
[Unidentifiably mysterious...
our woman of the hour.]
[Goddess of the Hallyu wave,
Cheon Song Yi...]
[Is she here with us right now?]
[Her name alone is enough to make
any man's heart beat flutter.]
[Who could she be?]
- What the heck is this?
- Sorry.
- Don't you know who I am?
- What are you doing?
[I'm Cheon Song Yi.]
I thought Jeon Ji Hyun was going to be on.
Don't you know who I am?
I'm Cheon Song Yi.
You're Cheon Song Yi, the Goddess of Hallyu
from 'My Love From Another Star'.
I am?
[400 years ago.]
[Young Cheon Song Yi, who was able to find
her palanquin with the help of Jae Suk...]
[Chooses to be reincarnated with
Jae Suk's looks 400 years later.]
Find the gold key to the UFO that you
and Do Min Joon will take to make your escape
and you will win the race if you
board the ship with the key.
You're telling me that I'm Song Yi?
[Even he himself can't believe his own fate.]
[Anyways, this person is Cheon Song Yi,
the Goddess of the Hallyu wave.]
- Why am I turned down?
- What do you mean? I just turned you down.
- Why are you turning me down?
- I just did. I'm Cheon Song Yi.
I just turned you down.
Seriously.
You can't be Do Min Joon.
- I am Do Min Joon. Don't you remember?
- What did you say?
I just turned you down.
- What are you doing?
- Why are you turning me down?
I guess words may not be enough.
- What kind of a Cheon Song Yi are you?
- Who do you think you are?
What a joke.
What a joke?
What kind of a Cheon Song Yi are you?
You're telling me that you're Cheon Song Yi?
- No way.
- I don't want you, so you can just leave.
- I don't want you.
- You're telling me that you're Song Yi?
That's absolutely ridiculous.
How can you be Cheon Song Yi?
[Muscle boy, Kkuk, barges in out of nowhere
to take Cheon Song Yi by the arms.]
This is driving me crazy. This is the most
absurd thing I have ever heard.
- Song Yi.
- Wait a minute.
- Let me go for a minute.
- What kind of a ridiculous joke is this?
Muscle boy, and Big-nose...
I'm turning you both down.
- You really are very cocky.
- I'm Cheon Song Yi.
[And... there's one being who's still
unaware of this turn of events.]
[After 400 years of waiting,
my soul mate, Cheon Song Yi...]
[I'm coming, Cheon Song Yi.]
So this is no joke?
He's Cheon Song Yi?
- I'm Cheon Song Yi.
- Song Yi!
[My love... Cheon Song Yi.]
[Did you call out my name?]
[You are... Cheon Song Yi?]
[Oh My God.]
[My Lord... why have you abandoned me?]
I thought it was going to be Jeon Ji Hyun.
- I thought it was going to be Jeon Ji Hyun.
- Then just leave.
- I'm turning him down too. Leave.
- Why would she be on the show?
- I really thought that it would be her.
- That would make no sense.
Go tell your managers
that I turned you all down.
Go tell your managers that I, Cheon Song Yi,
just turned you all down.
[This has to be a nightmare.]
- Why do you all look so disappointed?
- No, that's not it.
Don't you think that you guys crossed
the line way too much?
I turned you all down.
I, Cheon Song Yi, turned you all down.
[Cheon Song Yi and Do Min Joon
are busy putting each other down.]
- Can we reenact the scene?
- Sure, we can reenact it right now.
How can you as a Song Yi lick spit
onto your thumb like that?
[Song Yi, without any inhibitions.]
- I'm Cheon Song Yi.
- No, I don't think so. Say, 'sorry'.
- Sorry.
- No, he's Song Yi.
- He's Cheon Song Yi.
- That's absurd.
- Hey, Gary.
[Everyone is opposed to
Jae Suk being Song Yi.]
- Why do you keep shedding?
- Because this is a cheap knockoff.
- Are you really 'Song Yi'?
- He really is.
I wanted Jeon Ji Hyun!
- Seriously.
- Cheon Song Yi!
[Giraffe rushes in with his greed
to take the spotlight for himself.]
How does that even make any sense?
- That doesn't work.
- Don't do this!
[Do Min Joon hopeful gets knocked down
with a knee kick to the stomach.]
- Look at who it is up there.
- Cheon Song Yim!
- That's my little brother.
- She does look like Cheon Song Yim.
- I really thought Jeon Ji Hyun was coming.
- I'm Cheon Song Yi.
Cheon Song Yi!
How is that even possible?
I need everyone's attention right here.
I don't know who Do Min Joon is...
but we just need to work together to get
the gold, and then go our own separate ways.
What kind of a Cheon Song Yi are you?
- Who's Do Min Joon?
- It's me.
- No, it's me.
- I'm Do Min Joon.
- I saved you 400 years ago.
- No, I saved you.
[Everyone is using their own methods to
insist that they are Do Min Joon.]
There's not much time.
You know what happens in two hours, right?
- What are you, a cheerleader?
- The ship leaves in two hours.
[The UFO door will
open in an hour and a half.]
Even if you were to find the key,
I'd still turn you down.
- I'm Cheon Song Yi. I'd turn you down.
- I'd be the one to turn you down!
[Cheon Song Yi vs Do Min Joon-
A battle of their dislike for each other.]
[These two are supposedly
a match made in heaven...]
- I just turned you down.
- You sure are weird looking!
Ugh, seriously.
How unlucky am I?
Yeah, we're cool.
We can work together to get the gold...
and go our own separate ways after.
[Changing his code from 'love' to 'gold'.]
- I'm telling you that I'm Cheon Song Yi.
- Why don't you go take a rest?
Go get it right now.
Go find the script, Gary.
Okay, I understand.
I need to keep my focus on the gold.
I have the script.
[Blank Ji approached Song Yi with
the script that she found.]
- Where is the script?
- It's in my pocket.
- You have the script right now?
- Yes.
- I need to know if I'm Do Min Joon or not.
- You're Do Min Joon?
- I need to find out if I am or not.
- Let's go where no one can hear us.
- You have the script?
- I have it with me.
Why did Cheon Song Yi's pretty clothes
have to get wasted on you?
Is that the scene?
It is the scene!
[The scene that Jae Suk and
Ji Hyo must reenact.]
I'm really good at cleaning.
[A parody of a scene from
'My Love From Another Star'.]
Let me clean this up first.
[Do Min Joon and Cheon Song Yi's
back hug scene!]
So I can kick this off?
[My Love From Another Star-
Back hug scene- Take one.]
- I want you to always treasure this.
- Okay.
Sorry.
Stop moving, and don't do anything
before I end up kicking you out.
I got it.
[Blank Ji's like- NG.]
[Even though the bell didn't sound since
she isn't Do Min Joon...]
[But they decide to give it another try.
So, it's Take Two.]
- I want you to always treasure this.
- Okay.
Sorry.
Stop moving, and don't do anything
before I end up kicking you out.
- I think I got it wrong.
- Seriously, Ji Hyo! What's wrong with you!
[Somehow... it's Take Five.]
[Fifth one to be smashed over her head.]
Stop moving, and don't do anything
before I end up kicking you out.
I got it.
[If she really was Do Min Joon,
then the bell should've sounded by now.]
- I don't think it's me.
- I don't think it's you.
- No, I don't think it's me.
- You got the lines right this time, right?
Yes, I got my lines right.
[Blank Ji is off the list of
Do Min Joon possibilities.]
Bye, and sorry.
- Sorry?
- Yeah, sorry.
It's not her.
It's not Ji Hyo.
- Then what do you have to do now?
- I have to go find the key to the UFO.
- You just need to find the key to the UFO?
- Find out where the key is hidden.
And find out where the UFO is?
That's much better than what I have to do.
I have to find out who Do Min Joon is.
[In two thousand years, during the second
moon after the passing of 14 seasons...]
[a force of evil will come shroud in darkness
to threaten the happiness of all mankind.]
[Who's the ultimate evil that the
book of prophecy is speaking of?]
Cheon Song Yi.
I will be by your side soon.
Mister, why don't you just go home?
I'm sorry to tell you this, but have yourself
a nice bowl of soup, and just go home.
Come on, come with me.
I found the script, so come with me.
[Big-nose found the script.]
- I'm telling you that I'm Do Min Joon.
- Really?
[Old man Big-nose, is fully convinced
that he is Do Min Joon.]
- Let's go somewhere a little dim.
- Why are you trying to take me to a dim place?
We can't have anyone catch us
doing this.
- What are you doing?
- Come with me.
[Big-nose and Jae Suk's reenactment scene.]
You need to pay close attention to
what he's doing with his fingers.
[Wait... this scene is...]
[These two have to reenact this scene?]
- This is the scene we have to reenact?
- Are you serious?
[Big-nose and Jae Suk have to reenact
this beautiful and romantic scene?]
You're not supposed to talk...
when you're in someone else's dream.
So I'm supposed to be forward, right?
- She's so pretty, isn't she?
- Yes, unlike you.
[Must reenact this scene
just as it happened...]
How do you expect us to do this?
[Totally against the idea of
reenacting the scene.]
How about I carry you and lay you down...
let me finish talking!
Let me take a look too.
Just go away!
- You're not Do Min Joon.
- Yes, I am.
[In the meantime, the real Do Min Joon...]
How did you end up like that?
[Upset at how Song Yi ended up...]
[Just what could have happened to you
in the past 400 years?]
Since we're stuck in this situation,
let's remain cool like you said we should.
You and I will go our separate ways
after we win our gold.
I'll save you.
[Song Yi and Do Joon's love has
transformed into greed for gold.]
- Come here, I'll protect you.
- Seriously!
Do Min Joon can't look like you.
I'm about to run away from you.
- You should look in the mirror.
- What are you talking about?
How can you be Song Yi?
Seriously... I'm about to lose it.
[They must maintain their composure
to reenact the scene.]
[Bed kissing scene- Take one.]
- You have to hang onto me.
- Why are you struggling so much?
[Only blaming one another.]
- You have to hold onto Do Min Joon.
- Didn't you see what he did earlier?
I make my move when you're about to
pull your arm out.
Why did you wait so long though?
Let's just start over.
Why is Do Min Joon struggling so much?
[Weakest Do Min Joon hopeful
of the bunch.]
What are you doing?
I only weight 67kg.
- You're grossing me out as Song Yi.
- I find you even more disgusting.
Seriously... your wife needs to be praised.
[Arguing about who's better looking?]
- Your wife is amazing. Be good to her.
- You better be good to your wife.
[Bed kissing scene- Take two.]
- You have to grab onto me!
- Why are you sniffling?
[Sniffly alien, Big-nose?]
What was that all about?
I don't think it's you.
I'm dumping you.
[No way that Big-nose could be
Do Min Joon?]
- I have to try the scene with Gary.
- Gary.
[Gary is waiting for his turn with
his copy of the script in hand?]
- What's taking you so long?
- Do Min Joon is so weak.
- I'm telling you that it isn't you.
- How do you know? Go away.
I'm sick and tired of waiting,
so let's speed it up.
Okay, we got it.
[I can't believe that I have to wait
around for that Cheon Song Yi...]
[If they don't succeed at once,
they're going to have to do this again...]
Cheon Song Yi, I was just...
You can't shove your ugly face
into someone else's dream.
[I can't do this for the second time!
Grit down, and finish the scene!]
[Bed kissing scene- Take three- Done.]
I have to go brush my teeth
like 300 times.
[The bell has to sound
if he really is Do Min Joon...]
- Lets go our own separate ways.
- I knew it.
[Going their own separate ways
after that hot kiss.]
I knew that it couldn't be you.
- Hey.
- How many people must I do this with?
- Did you find anything?
- What?
- Why haven't you found anything yet?
- The script?
- I did find it.
- What?
- But it's not you?
- No, I'm not.
[It's been found that Blank Ji
isn't Do Min Joon.]
[And Kkuk still hasn't found his script?]
Didn't you get your mission?
- I know that there's a key to the UFO.
- Then find the key and board the UFO.
- You have to be Do Min Joon to get on it.
- No, you don't have to be Do Min Joon.
- Is that the hint?
- The hint said...
I'm just going to tell you this.
I haven't told anyone this yet.
- There's Cheon Song Yi and Do Mi Joon.
- Yeah, tell me.
But the book that I received...
I was told that there's an evil force.
[An evil force?]
There's an evil force,
but I don't know who that evil force is.
[Blank Ji reveals that there's an
evil force amongst them.]
I was told that we need to find out
who that evil force is.
- Seriously.
- Do you get what I'm saying?
[In that case...]
- Are you sure?
- I haven't found any scripts yet.
Okay, I got it.
Let's go.
[Just then!]
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
[Why did Mr. Capable do that?]
[Wait, that's...]
[The ring symbolic of the evil force?]
[In that case...]
[Mr. Capable is the evil force!]
[Be quiet, Ji Hyo...]
You are the evil force from
'My Love From Another Star'.
The ultimate Mr. Capable with the looks,
skills and every other power that you need.
But you are the ultimate evil with two sides
that are as different as night and day.
Find the nail ring with a member's name
engraved on it
and rid that person's name tag
one by one.
You must oust all the members.
You can win the race by finding the gold key
and boarding the ship all by yourself.
[Oust all the members,
and board the ship with the gold key!]
Then I should pretend to be Do Min Joon like
everyone else, and get close to Cheon Song Yi?
[The ultimate evil with a hidden evil side.]
So I just need to board the UFO
all by myself?
That doesn't sound difficult.
How dare they try to leave for
Planet Gold by themselves?
I don't need Cheon Song Yi either.
[The ultimate evil,
without any pity for anyone.]
Song Ji Hyo?
[Goodbye, my friend...]
Song Yi.
[Ha Min Joon finally finds a
script of his own.]
I told you that it's me.
[But Cheon Song Yi still doesn't
recognize him for who he is.]
If it's not you, then it means
that Jong Kook is Do Min Joon.
- I guarantee that it's not him.
- I rather that you were Min Joon than him.
Even if I were to leave for some planet,
there's no way that I can go with Jong Kook.
I've been watching you from afar,
and I've started to grow feelings for you.
I'm the woman of the hour.
[This Song Yi is getting cockier
by the minute.]
Sorry.
- Excuse me?
- I got it.
[The scene that will solidify these two
as the real Song Yi and Min Joon is...]
[The heartbreaking scene where Min Joon
has to hide his true feelings for Song Yi.]
[The scene where he freezes the time
to come up to her and kiss her.]
You're going to hear the bell ring.
I have no other hope if you're not Min Joon.
[These two are really hoping that
Ha Ha is the real Min Joon.]
But why do I feel like you're
lying to me?
[Snowy kiss scene- Take one.]
'I don't like you.'
'So... what do you want me to do?'
'I want you to disappear from my sight.'
'But...'
'Why does it feel like
you're lying to me right now?'
[Song Yi has to heartbreakingly turn away
from the one that she loves.]
[And Min Joon is unable to grab onto her.]
[And...]
[Time comes to a halt.]
[A movement frozen in time...]
[Has to remain completely frozen.]
[Even though she may never know...]
[Do Min Joon wraps his arms
tightly around her.]
[Just then...]
[The bell sounds to grant permission
for Min Joon and Song Yi's love.]
[The sound of the bell could be heard
throughout the building.]
Then who's Do Min Joon?
I'm Do Min Joon.
I'm Do Min Joon!
I'm Manager Do!
What is this?
[Even the evil Mr. Capable is feeling
the pressure with the ringing bell sound.]
[But Cheon Song Yi is still feeling
unsure of what's going on.]
See?
I look like him.
I have so many powers right now.
I can teleport, stop time, and move time.
- I can teleport, stop time and...
- Stop time?
But I can't eliminate any name tags
by freezing time.
[But he can't use his powers to
eliminate anyone's name tag.]
[But he possesses the great power to escape
from the danger of being eliminated.]
- Then it's game over.
- But only I can use the powers.
- Song Yi can't use the powers.
- Then did I just get dumped?
[Already wondering about the strength of
their love three minutes later?]
Let's make a clean break after
we get our hands on the gold.
- Okay, gold, and it's over.
- We're just in this for the gold.
We're different from the drama,
because this is a variety show.
[A little bit of a different feel
than the actual drama.]
We'll take one picture as proof,
and we'll go our own separate ways.
[It's goodbye as soon as they get
the gold in their hands.]
I will protect you.
- I won't leave you for a second.
- Sorry to tell you this...
But I'm the feisty type.
- I'm not the lovey dovey type.
- We have to get the gold first.
- I got it.
- You got it?
[This is an extremely incompatible
Cheon Song Yi and Do Min Joon.]
I have to find it quickly.
[Evil Mr. Capable is on the search for
the rings in order to oust the members.]
I have to find them quickly.
I have to find the rings.
[He can only oust the person who's name
is engraved on the ring he finds.]
[Bingo!]
Wow, I can't believe how well
you hid this.
[The ultimate evil finds another ring box!]
[Who's name will he find on the ring?]
Who is it?
Who could it be?
Cheon Song Yi!
[Cheon Song Yi!]
[Evil Mr. Capable is given the chance
to oust Cheon Song Yi!]
I've been given the chance to catch you.
[Cheon Song Yi from 400 years ago who
ripped off my identity tag...]
Wait for me, Cheon Song Yi.
I'm coming for you.
[Meanwhile, Song Yi and Min Joon
come across Min Joon wannabe, Giraffe.]
- Manager Do. Manager Do!
- Jae Suk.
[Their plan is to keep
Ha Ha's identity a secret.]
- Aren't you Manager Do?
- Who else besides me is Manager Do?
- Where are you going?
- I'm running away because I'm nervous.
[Ha Min Joon is keeping his ears to the ground
to be alerted to any sign of danger.]
Wait, listen to me.
Kwang Soo.
[Nervous Kwang Soo keeps retreating
from an uneasy feeling that he's getting.]
Where's the UFO?
Song Yi!
Please don't do this to me.
Don't close in on me so suddenly like this.
I'm just asking where the spaceship is.
Who is it?
Is it Jong Kook or Ha Ha?
[Just then, evil Mr. Capable
walks onto the scene.]
- It's Ha Ha, isn't it?
- It's not you?
No, it's not me.
It's Ha Ha, isn't it?
[Ha Min Joon, afraid of Song Yi getting
ousted joins the fray as well.]
Wait, I know that he's Do Min Joon.
It's not me.
- I swear it isn't me, Kwang Soo.
- It's one of you two.
- I don't want anyone getting close to me!
- Kwang Soo.
Trust me, Kwang Soo.
I'm not Do Min Joon.
I swear that I'm not Do Min Joon.
Kwang Soo... which of these two
do you think is Do Min Joon?
[Cheon Song Yi and Ha Min Joon are trying to
argue that Mr. Capable is Do Min Joon.]
[To keep Jong Kook and Kwang Soo
from joining their forces together.]
- You know you're lying!
- Where are Ji Hyo and Suk Jin?
Where did everyone go?
Where are Ji Hyo and Suk Jin?
- Why are you asking us that?
- What do you mean, 'us'?
- I was just asking you.
- No, you asked that of Kwang Soo and I.
No, I wasn't asking Kwang Soo.
I was just asking you.
Come on, Kwang Soo.
[Jae Suk is doing whatever he can to get
Kwang Soo to be suspicious of Jong Kook.]
- I have no idea what to do.
- Kwang Soo.
Do Min Joon.
Why without any permission from me...
did you oust Gary, Ji Hyo and Suk Jin?
- What is it that you're after?
- Ji Hyo and Suk Jin are ousted?
- Just what is it that you're after?
[Cheon Song Yi is trying to paint Mr. Capable
as the traitorous Do Min Joon.]
Take a good look.
What do you think is going on right now?
What do you think that he is doing?
He's trying to get you to think
that I'm Do Min Joon.
- No, I'm not.
- And he'll oust us with the real Min Joon.
[Evil Mr. Capable is figuring out
what Jae Suk is really planning.]
- Dot' you think that I'm right?
- Have you found the key?
No, I haven't found the key.
These two could already have the key.
Gary and I talked earlier.
We thought that the key could be hidden under
Song Yi or Min Joon's name tag.
Then how about I see
what's under your name tag?
- Why do I have to show you my back?
- Did you see his reaction?
If I'm Do Min Joon,
why would he be so afraid of me?
Because I could be ousted even if
Do Min Joon is the one eliminating it.
But Cheon Song Yi had to board
the ship with Do Min Joon.
[Just then, Mr. Capable comes down
one step closer towards Song Yi.]
[Evil Mr. Capable already has
Song Yi's ring in his possession.]
[Thus, he is able to oust Song Yi!]
Song Yi or Min Joon can board
the ship by themselves.
Anyone can board the ship by themselves
if they want to keep the gold for themselves.
[Mr. Capable's hand is slowly...]
[No... Song Yi...]
Stop the time.
[Do Min Joon activates his
time stopping power.]
[Ha Min Joon stops time to
protect Song Yi.]
[Rescues Song Yi from danger
while the time has come to a halt.]
[Time halt... over!]
See?
Ha Ha is Do Min Joon!
- Cheon Song Yi!
- Stop looking for Song Yi!
- Where did you go, Song Yi?
- What are you doing?
[But Evil Mr. Capable is now aware of
Do Min Joon's superpowers.]
[Do Min Joon... must be eliminated.]
[One minute ago- What really happened.]
Stop the time.
- Why do you keep...
- What's going on here?
[The board team is on the move!
Min Joon's power is activated!]
Come on.
Get on my back.
- Why didn't you oust him?
- Why are you being so outspoken?
- Why aren't you ousting him?
- Why do you keep butting in like that?
- I don't think he would've ousted me.
- He almost had you.
- I won't die.
- You will die!
If it hadn't been for me,
you would be ousted by now.
- I'm telling you that I won't die.
- Yes, you can die.
- There's nothing for me to be afraid of.
- Why won't you be afraid of anything?
I thought that this was a part of the coat,
but this is just a scarf.
[It's a cheap knockoff...]
What are you going to do?
Tell me.
[Nothing about this couple is compatible.]
What we have is
a business relationship, not love.
Let's just do what we need to do,
and go our separate ways.
That's a given.
And I'm pretty offended right now.
Do you know how old I am?
- How old are you?
- I'm 401 years old.
Let's just get on the UFO, and go our
separate ways after we get the gold.
[They no longer even
want to be around each other.]
Where are you going by yourself again?
[It's almost time for the door to open...]
[Evil Mr. Capable is starting to
feel really anxious.]
[Must find Do Min Joon's nail ring
as quickly as possible.]
[Could it be?]
[Nail ring with Ha Ha's name on it!]
Do Min Joon.
The only reason why you're still alive...
is because I let you live until now.
[You'd better watch yourself, Do Min Joon.]
[Unable to trust anyone else,
but they're going into hiding for now.]
Here's what I think.
I searched everywhere
for over an hour earlier.
But I couldn't find anything.
Even the hairpin was found on a person.
Remember the hairpin
during our first mission of the day?
[The jade hairpin that the younger version
of Song Yi was wearing in her hair.]
I think it's on us somewhere.
You could have it, or I could have it.
The hairpin?
No, the key.
- The key?
- The key could be on our person.
So let's just search through
our own clothing.
[Where are you, Do Min Joon?]
It's not there.
I looked everywhere.
Here it is.
We have to rip it.
[There's something inside Song Yi's coat...]
This is it.
[A USB key for the door to the UFO!]
How did you expect us to find this?
[Did you think that it would be that easy
to fly into outer space?]
Since we now have the key...
all we have to do is find the UFO.
[Find the UFO,
and they can return to Planet Gold!]
- We're going to be together.
- I know we are, but...
[The foundation of their love is being
shaken in front of the UFO key?]
You have to listen to me from
now on, okay?
[Ha Min Joon is feeling mighty cocky
after having found the key.]
You are such an impish little woman.
Stop running around recklessly.
You're driving me crazy.
It's over once we get the gold.
I have no reason to see you anymore
once I get the gold.
[All they need to do now is find
the UFO that's outside the building.]
Why don't you come here?
You ousted Gary, Ji Hyo and even Suk Jin,
didn't you?
- What are you talking about?
- What am I talking about?
I was with you most of the day.
[What luck is this?]
It's because you want to keep the gold,
and the UFO for yourself.
[Suspecting Kwang Soo of everything.]
[That's why you should be
nicer all the time...]
[Alien Ha Min Joon is getting ready to
activate one of his superpowers.]
You dare antagonize my lady, Cheon Song Yi?
I will not let you get away with it.
[Superpower- Activated!]
What is all this?
What is this?
What are you doing?
[This is none other than,
rubber ball thunder!]
Wait!
What is this?
What are you doing?
You can't do this!
I just got hit.
[Taking advantage of the chaos to
attack Kwang Soo to eliminate him.]
[A full force attack on the lonely Giraffe.]
- There's no time, Jong Kook!
- Stop the time!
[This won't do... Stop the time!]
[Flow of time... come to a halt.]
[While everyone comes to a stop...
only Ha Ha is able to make a move.]
[Comes to stop right behind Kwang Soo.]
[Kwang Soo is ousted the moment
that time starts to flow again.]
Cheon Song Yi?
Cheon Song Yi, my butt.
- Just let it go, Song Yi.
- Let go of me.
[Song Yi, the fighter?]
[Puts up a good fight to the end,
and Kwang Soo is out!]
Any mistake, and both of us
could've been out.
- If you hadn't done that...
- There's Jong Kook.
[Discovers Mr. Capable in hiding!]
[The final face-off,
Song Yi and Min Joon vs Evil Mr. Capable.]
Mr. Capable coming down the stairs
to corner the two.]
[What is that chill in the air?]
[The three face off with one another!]
- Where did Kwang Soo go?
- Isn't Kwang Soo playing Jae Kyung?
What did you say?
There's a bad guy?
[What he pulls out of his jacket...
are the two rings with their names on it.]
[That's right...]
[I'm... the ultimate force of evil.]
- I will send you off into your eternal rest.
- Why are you talking in such a scary way?
Why are you wearing a nail around your finger?
You're wearing that as a ring?
The reason why you're both still alive...
is because I let you live up to now.
- Yes, I don't doubt your words.
- Did you oust Gary and everyone else?
I ousted everyone.
[Goodbye, Gary.]
- What about Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin too.
- You're so frightening.
- You can't do that.
[Time for you to go
and get some rest, Suk Jin.]
- What about Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo was first.
[As soon as she told me about the evil...]
[Do you remember, Song Yi?]
[The promise I made you 400 years ago?]
You can't kill me.
[Song Yi's protector, Min Joon vs
Force of evil trying to rid of Song Yi.]
- Because you can't kill me.
- Why not?
Stop the time!
[The time stopping agents are on the move!]
Sorry.
I thought that my jaw was going to break.
Teleportation!
[One more- Teleportation.]
[Everyone moves at an incredibly slow speed
with the exception of Ha Min Joon.]
[But he still continues to protect Song Yi.]
- Song Yi.
- What are you doing? You have to oust him.
I told you that I can't oust anyone
while the time is at a standstill.
I just need to get Do Min Joon's mouth shut.
We've only got three minutes left.
[Only three minutes left until
the UFO door opens.]
- You'll never be able to kill me.
- He's really angry.
[The ultimate force of evil is on the move!]
Use your power!
[But this beast doesn't even blink an eye!]
[Are you done with your tricks now?]
[UFO is activated.]
[The final battle they must fight!]
[Will Song Yi and Min Joon be able to hold on
to their love 400 years in the making?]
[Just then]
[Ha Min Joon... is ousted.]
I was so close... so close!
Song Yi!
[I'm sorry that I wasn't able to
protect you.]
[I've waited 400 years for this UFO.
Must I wait another 400 years?]
[The final battle-
Cheon Song Yi vs Ultimate force of evil.]
I should've finished you off 400 years ago
when I had the chance!
[Their fate 400 years in the making...]
[It's time to end it now!]
I didn't know that you were Jae Kyung.
- I had no idea that you were Jae Kyung.
- You need to put the wig back on.
[Even in this current situation,
comments about his ugliness must be made.]
[Wig headed Cheon Song Yi vs
Ultimate Force of Evil Mr. Capable.]
Song Yi!
[A bloody battle]
[Time... to... end this now.]
[Totally unexpected!]
[Cheon Song Yi eliminates Mr. Capable's
name tag first!]
[History repeats itself 400 years later!]
[Mr. Capable's energy is depleted
after the two against one battle.]
You worked hard, Jae Kyung.
You worked hard...
but you just got dumped.
[Sorry, Mr. Capable.]
[In the end, Song Yi heads off to
board the UFO by herself.]
I can't believe that just happened.
It would've been so nice if
Min Joon could've been here with me.
Do Min Joon... I'm sorry.
And Kwang Soo, what were you playing today?
What role were you playing?
Anyways, I'm so happy with the outcome.
[He only has to fit the key
in the lock of the door.]
Why isn't the door opening?
[The door is opening!]
What a miracle!
[Cheon Song Yi boards the UFO.]
[His long awaited gold prize inside the UFO.]
[My Love From a Running Star...
Sequel in 400 years.]
Song Yi!
- Song Yi!
- I'm coming!
- What is this?
- Thanks!
Why are you closing the door?
Why are you leaving me?
Why would you take this back
to my planet?
- Min Joon!
- You're an earthling!
- I'm sorry, Min Joon.
- I should be the one leaving!
You should find yourself another woman.
[Chung Song Yi is leaving Do Min Joon behind
to leave for outer space herself.]
Cheon Song Yi is wrapping,
mem mem mem...
[How can this be?]
Let's go.
Where are you going, Song Yi?
No, I should be the one leaving!
Song Yi!
Cheon Song Yi!
Subtitles by DramaFever