Running Man
Bro...
I hear... that a huge business
deal is going down tonight.
Want to hear what it is?
I heard that an ancient noble script
will be revealed tonight.
But without any other members finding out,
I want just us two to get it.
What do you think?
Want to do it with me?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, can we do that again?
I've never seen an
expression like that before.
[Working with a five star rated actor.]
I'll explain it to you.
We'll be eliminating them
in a very unique way today.
Instead of ripping off their name tags,
we'll be writing their names on the tags.
- Write it?
- Yes, write it.
It's a very simple method.
We're going to search for blank
name tags.
- And if we write the member's name on it...
- Write the name on the tag?
Once we write their name on the tag,
then they'll be ousted.
- Then they'll wonder why they're ousted.
- They won't even know why they're ousted.
They won't even know that there
are spies, and we'll just...
We'll find...
It's no joke, is it? I didn't
know Running Man was this cool.
They're always surprising me
with each new episode.
We don't need to rip it off anymore.
That's too brutal of a method.
There are more dignified and
easier ways to do it, such as this.
- Look at how simple this is.
- That's right.
- There's no need to exert all our strength.
- And ripping people's clothing, too!
- All that was unnecessary.
- No, it's not necessary.
If we can win the mission
then we'll be given a tool which will
help us oust the other members.
- And we'll...
- A tool?
- I heard it's a very important tool.
- Is it a pen?
I have a feeling it's something similar,
and we have to...
I could hear the producers muttering
something as soon as I said, 'pen.'
I was going to pretend that
I didn't hear any of it.
But they're talking about how smart I am.
I'm going to shatter it today.
- The image that I've always had...
- Today's the day.
- I'm going to shatter their perception of me.
- Show them what the Asian Prince can do.
I'm really smart.
I'm a college graduate.
- Really? I had no idea.
- Yeah.
- I'm going to show them.
- Today's the day.
Let's do this.
[Brain Kwang Soo and Woo Bin's spy plans.]
I've got some information on the experts
of each category whom we'll be facing today.
Yoo Jae Suk, who can open any doors
and locks with the use of flour.
[There isn't a door that I can't open!]
[Human opener, Yoo Jae Suk.]
Ji Suk Jin, who can open the locks with
the use of a special eye retina scan.
[Eye retina master, Ji Suk Jin.]
[Kim Jong Kook, a man who can break
through anything with his strength.]
[Human tank, Kim Jong Kook.]
A human tank?
So, Jong Kook doesn't
have any special powers.
[Kkuk is just his usual Kkuk self.]
[Monday couple, Gary and Ji Hyo,
who can climb anything with compressors.]
[Moonlight Monday Couple, Gary and Ji Hyo.]
Gary, we made it!
- We've made it!
- Grab my hand.
Ha Ha, who has the ability to manipulate
and diffuse any sort of bombs.
[Bomb expert, Ha Ha.]
Five, four, three, two...
Oh my goodness!
[Slightly less than perfect experts.]
Lastly, the expert who can camouflage himself
in any sort of surrounding, Lee Kwang Soo.
That would be me.
That would be you.
The master of concealment.
[The master of concealing himself
from sight.]
[Master of the disappearing act,
Lee Kwang Soo.]
[His disappearing act!]
[His presence cannot be
detected by anyone.]
What do you think?
[Kwang Soo disappears in front of
Woo Bin's very own eyes.]
I'm right here.
[The true master of the disappearing act.]
- The members thinks of me as an airhead.
- Yes, you're very misunderstood.
- They think you're stupid.
- You know that it's all an act, right?
The last three times that I've been on
the show was in preparation for today.
Are you aware that it's all been an act
just to build up to this episode?
My stupidity that you saw for the past
five years has all been an act, too.
- It was all for this moment.
- I knew it.
Let's do this.
[Two 'pretend' airheads'
passionate embrace.]
You and I are the only ones
who are aware of today's real mission.
Okay.
[Woo Bin and Kwang Soo's oath of secrecy.]
Where do we go now?
[What fate awaits these two
clumsy airheaded spy brothers?]
We're totally ruined.
[One hour later.]
[Seoul Museum of Art.]
- Did everyone get their secret number?
- Yes.
- I wonder if they're all the same?
- Should we all open it together?
I think we need to open it together.
- One.
- Six.
[Configuring the numbers together for this
group of experts is like a walk in the park.]
- It's opening!
- It's unlocked!
The safe is finally opening!
What is it?
What the heck is this?
- What the heck?
- Is it Woo Bin?
[The safe contains human beings?]
[Enigmatic man of masculinity,
Kim Woo Bin.]
Long time no see!
[And standing next to him is...]
[The Nation's favorite youth,
Lee Hyun Woo.]
It's been so long!
[Two men, who are more precious
than any other gemstone.]
[While others are enthusiastically
greeting the two guests...]
'Kwang Soo, you and I are the only
ones who know of this.'
[The hidden meaning behind their hug.]
[To escape others' suspicion,
Woo Bin moves onto hug Gary.]
- Hyun Woo looks like a man now.
- He was like a kid when he was last here.
- How old are you now?
- I'm 22 years old.
- You're a man now.
- He's taller, too.
Kwang Soo looks like a guest
standing next to Woo Bin.
- We should greet you, too.
- Woo Bin knows how to carry his height.
Everyone has their own style.
We all have our own style.
- You really look like a squid.
- We need to trade spots!
I don't want to switch spots either!
[Everyone's too frightened to
stand next to Woo Bin.]
Before I explain the rules of the race,
allow me to announce the teams.
[Time to announce the teams.]
- Kim Woo Bin.
- Yes.
You're teamed up with Yoo Jae Suk
and Lee Kwang Soo.
All the good looking men
are teamed up together.
This is why people always say
that similar people hang out together.
- All the good looking ones are together.
- Two squids are teamed up with Woo Bin.
[Looks genuinely happy.]
Woo Bin looks especially
good looking right now.
[The squid effect of making a good looking
man appear even better looking?]
[He seriously...
does look even more handsome.]
The next team will be Lee Hyun Woo
with Kim Jong Kook and Song Ji Hyo.
[Lee Hyun Woo, Kim Jong Kook
and Song Ji Hyo.]
The rest are like a bomb squad.
[The rest- Ha Ha, Big-nose and Gary.
The bomb squad.]
[Ha Ha, Big-nose and Gary.]
I'm still going to have to
stand in the middle.
Why would you stand in the middle?
- Just take a look at us.
- Here are the rules.
Today's race is, The Technician Race.
- Have you all been to the National Museum?
- Yes.
An ancient script, which all the legendary
thieves are searching for is in the museum.
The person who gets the ancient script
will become today's winner.
Each time you win a mission
an item will be given to you which will
be critical to your win at the final mission.
Thus, you will have to give it your
best efforts to win the missions.
[That will be ours.]
[There are no safety zones!]
[You're already ousted!]
[The operation order:
Signature Technique Elimination.]
- Is it an individual race?
- Only the last mission.
But the rest of the game will be played
with three people per team.
- The two of you are a team.
- I see.
- Two people per team?
- No, three per team.
- I see.
- It'll be announced at the opening.
Wow, the other person on our team
will end up looking like a fool.
Jae Suk, we're going to win
the first game, right?
Why would you even ask such a thing?
Isn't that a given?
Of course, we'll have to win
the first game.
You're a spy, aren't you?
- Kwang Soo, are you a spy?
- Are you?
How do you get to me being a spy
from me asking you that question?
Why would you suddenly ask such a thing
if you're not a spy?
- Kwang Soo, you're really something else.
- Let's just win all the games today.
- Of course.
- For real.
[Seriously, Kwang Soo!]
[Sorry...]
[The first snowfall of 2014.]
[The heart of Seoul- Myungdong.]
[This is the first mission site of the day.]
- Okay, let's get out.
- Okay.
Wow, it's been so long
since I've been to Myungdong.
Wow, I really love Myungdong.
[The center of Myungdong is bustling
with holiday shoppers.]
[What is the first mission
that awaits them here?]
Wow, I don't even remember
the last time I was here.
[Team Black is excited to take in
the sights of Myungdong streets.]
[A horizontal bar awaits their arrival.]
- Is that a horizontal bar?
- It's in the middle of the street!
What is this?
- Jong Kook, I think we need to hurry.
- Already?
- They're already here.
[Team Red arrives soon thereafter.]
- Come on, hurry!
- What is this?
[What is their first mission that's to take
place in the middle of Myungdong streets?]
- Gae!
- Married-Men-Cross!
- Why do you do that all the time?
- We're determined to win.
Okay, here's your mission.
This is a mission to help solidify
your teamwork skills.
Technician's teamwork mission.
[At last... it's begun.]
One member from each team will
hang from the horizontal bar.
While the person is hanging from the bar
the other two members will have to
successfully complete a task
they're given and return to the bar.
You'll have to return and ring the bell before
your teammate falls in order to succeed.
But if your teammate falls off before then,
you fail the mission immediately.
I just heard something really frightening
from this team right now.
Suk Jin asked if he should do it.
[Surreal to hear Suk Jin ask
if he should hang from the bar.]
[Suk Jin offers to hang from the bar
due to the younger member's hurt shoulder.]
- What a team, you are!
- It's all in the frame of mind!
[Even though their bodies may be frail,
their voices sound stronger than ever!]
The team that wins this mission will earn
a very important clue to the final mission
and the advantage to leave first
for the next site.
[Okay, mission accepted.]
They look like a couple of athletes
in training with their trainer.
- They're trainees.
- I'll work very hard!
[Kwang Soo and Woo Bin are exchanging
secret looks with the mission ahead.]
- Woo Bin!
- Yes?
[Have we been caught?]
- Let's win this.
- Let's do this!
We'll be really fast, so don't worry.
Kwang Soo and I are lightning fast.
[These worrisome guys...
will they be able to succeed?]
First mission. While your teammates are
hanging from the horizontal bar...
- We're in trouble. He's going to be good.
- No, I'm wearing too many layers.
[Bring back the food items on the menu
before their teammate falls off.]
- You need to stay back.
- Hey!
[You have to be back before I fall off!]
One, two, pick!
[Choose the menu.]
You can't leave yet.
- What's this?
- What is this?
[Complicated drink menus are given
to all three teams.]
- What is this?
- Memorize the items instead of complaining.
[Must memorize the full menu.]
Do you think you can do it?
Is it hard or easy?
Ji Hyo and Hyun Woo,
you have to do a good job.
[Iced caramel macchiato with
extra chocolate syrup and cinnamon...]
[A confusing menu
that's difficult to even comprehend.]
Ready, set, go!
[Must deliver the items on the menu
before their teammate falls off.]
[Repeating the menu to themselves
to deter from forgetting it.]
- Where's a coffee shop?
- Do you know?
- There it is!
- I see it! It's over there.
There it is!
Let's go!
[Must speed up! Running
through the streets of Myungdong.]
Kwang Soo, if we win
the missions along the way
we'll be given a tool which will be critical
in helping us oust the other members.
I think it's going to be a necessary tool
in order for us to oust them.
[We must win the mission in order to
earn the tool to oust the other members.]
Hey!
[Breaks out the cheating moves.]
- Seriously!
- Wow, Woo Bin.
- Kim Woo Bin, seriously!
- This is so comfortable.
You fail the mission the moment you fall off
unless your teammates are back.
- Hey!
- Let me rest my legs, too.
Hey!
[I'm sorry, Suk Jin,
but I really have to win.]
- Where's the coffee shop?
- There it is!
[Team Black discovers a coffee shop.]
Will they have what we need?
[Will they have remembered their menu?]
- Hello.
- Do you have caramel macchiato?
- There it is.
- Cinnamon powder and chocolate powder...
- Chocolate.
[What are they trying to order?]
[Iced caramel macchiato with extra chocolate
and cinnamon powder, minus whip, with soy.]
With soy, and minus the whipped cream.
- I'm sorry, but it's a mission.
- Do you want it iced?
Yes, iced!
Is it not?
- No, hot.
- Is it hot?
[Repeating their drink order.]
- With soymilk!
- Yes, soymilk.
- Wow, you can actually order it like that?
- I didn't know that you could.
Do people normally order
the chocolate powder?
They don't?
[Team Blue and Team Red
run into the same coffee shop.]
[Tall English breakfast tea latte with
fat free milk, and with drink sleeve.]
- Tea latte.
- English breakfast tea latte?
No, they want iced cafe mocha.
English breakfast tea latte
with fat free milk.
- What size?
- Tall.
- With a drink sleeve.
- They want a Grande size.
- No, a tall.
- Tall, please.
I'm sorry for all the rushing.
We're not finished yet!
We're not finished yet.
We have to pay first!
[Team Red shouts out their order.]
[Grande iced cafe mocha with a drizzle of
chocolate and caramel syrup with whip.]
- Drizzle it.
- Drizzle the sauce on it.
Are you listening to us?
Thank you so much.
Whipped cream with a drizzle of
caramel and chocolate sauce on top.
Drizzle the sauce on top.
Please give us our order first.
- Please help us out.
- Would you like a receipt?
- No, it's okay.
- Please make ours first.
Barista!
Will the cafe mocha be out first?
No, I don't think so.
Can you both work on the drinks?
Is that drink going to be any good?
It's not, is it?
Why are they making us get something
that isn't even good?
- Can I ask for a glass of water?
- It's done.
- We don't need the water, thank you.
- I need some water.
- Woo Bin is waiting for us. Thank you!
- Just a glass of water? Thank you!
[No time to waste,
back to the judging table!]
Is this ours?
[Team Blue's drink is also ready.]
Thank you.
Let's go, Hyun Woo.
[Team Blue also sprints back
to the judging table.]
Thank you.
Grab a straw.
[Team Red is also on their way.]
[Heads back without knowing what's
going on at the horizontal bar.]
- Hey, Woo Bin!
- Excuse me!
[Team Blue is the first to arrive
back at the judging table.]
We're the first ones back!
Close the rope.
[Huh?]
Tall English breakfast tea latte with
fat free milk, and with drink sleeve.
Jong Kook, why did you fall off?
What are you doing?
[Drink is correct, but fails because
Kkuk fell off from the horizontal bar.]
[Just then, Team Red arrives.]
Hurry!
[Team Red also gets their drink correct.]
[Team Black is the last to arrive.]
- What took you guys so long?
- Why did you fall off already?
Caramel macchiato with extra chocolate
and cinnamon powder, minus whip, with soy.
You were told to get iced,
but you got it hot.
[Team Black fails to
bring back the correct drink.]
All three members fell off the bar,
so all three teams fails the mission.
[All three teams fails
the first attempt at the mission.]
[Then what was Big-nose doing
back on the bar?]
[Woo Bin easily eliminates Big-nose
from the bar.]
[And goes onto eliminating
Mr. Capable, as well.]
[But falls off the bar from exhaustion.]
Hey, how about I hang from the bar
by myself when they return?
Let's see how they react
when they see it.
Excuse me!
[Big-nosed Brother fools
everyone with his prank.]
They said what you ordered isn't even
any good, so why did you order it like that?
- Is that what they said?
- Yes, they said it's really awful.
[Everyone has different tastes.]
You have to be three times faster
than what you were before.
If you can't do that,
then we'll all fail again.
- You have to be back quicker.
- Our barista was so fast though.
[Kwang Soo and Woo Bin exchange
yet another secret glance.]
- Want me to do it again? I think I can.
- No, we have to take turns.
Fighting!
[We vow to win this time.]
- Take your places under the bar.
- Can we switch places?
[A feisty battle for their spots.]
Your second mission-
While your teammates are hanging from the bar
you have to bring back a foreigner who's here
from a country that's more than 3 syllables.
Bangladesh!
Any foreigners out here?
- Any foreigners!
- Where are you from?
Where are you from!
[As soon as they get on the bar,
Kkuk starts his attack on Big-nose.]
[Jae Suk joins in on the attack.]
You guys are seriously driving me crazy.
[Big-nose is already in danger!]
[The only way to rescue Big-nose from danger
is to complete the mission quickly.]
- Singapore!
- Where are you from?
Singapore?
Where are you from?
- Singapore!
- Is that more than three syllables?
[Singapore is more than three syllables
in Korean language.]
[Team Red successfully finds
their foreigner in the blink of an eye!]
- Excuse me, where are you from?
- Thailand.
- But that's 'Taegook' in Korean.
Sorry!
I love Thailand!
- Where are you from?
- Taiwan.
[Taiwan is 'Dae-Mon' in Korean,
thus, unacceptable.]
Woo Bin, we have to win this no matter what.
You know that we have to
come in at first place, right?
- Hello, where are you from?
- Where are you from?
- China.
Okay, I love China.
[Peaceful Giraffe loves the entire world.]
Excuse me!
Excuse me, where are you from?
- England.
- Did you ask what his name was?
- No, his country.
- The country?
[Drags him back to the judging table.]
[Team Red arrives back
almost at the same time.]
[All three are still hanging from the bar.]
[Team Blue and Team Red are almost there.]
[Team Red arrives first
by the split of a hair.]
Where did Woo Bin and Kwang Soo go?
- What's your name?
- Michael.
Michael is from Bazaar.
[Bazaar?]
I love Bazaar.
[Which country is Bazaar?]
Look at how huge Kwang Soo's face looks.
- Did you already fall off?
- Of course! What took you guys so long?
- Where is he from?
- Bazaar?
- What? Bazaar?
- Bazaar.
[Just where in the world is Bazaar?]
- Where are you from?
- Belgium.
Belgium!
[It wasn't Bazaar?]
- He's from Belgium.
- How did you get 'Bazaar' from that?
Even though it is three syllables,
you failed because Jae Suk fell off.
[Team Black fails because
Jae Suk fell off the bar.]
[England is 'Young-Gook' in Korean,
thus, Team Blue also fails.]
In Korean, England is 'Young-Gook.'
- Where is she from?
- Singapore.
- The country of chili crabs.
- But he fell off from the bar.
Even though it is three syllables,
you fail because Suk Jin fell off.
[A strong denial.]
[Video replay.]
[Team Red returns after Suk Jin
has already fallen off the bar.]
Ugh, that was so close!
[Five minutes after having said that...]
- I fell off the bar?
- Yes, you did.
[Fails the argument.]
- Thank you, it was nice to meet you.
- Thank you, I love Belgium.
[Thanks the foreigners for their
participation in the game.]
[Even takes a picture.]
How did you mistake Belgium for Bazaar?
- He should've been more clear.
- He said, Belgium.
- How did you get Bazaar out of that?
- That's what he told me.
- Decide who'll hang on the bar this time.
- It'll be Ji Suk Jin.
- I can't do it.
- You guys need to switch up.
- I'm not lying, it really hurts.
- What do you mean, it's not a lie?
[Hyun Woo takes a turn for Team Blue.]
[Woo Bin takes another turn
for Team Black.]
- I can't run because of my painful knee.
- Stop lying.
[Woo Bin is already pulling out the lies.]
- Have you all decided?
- Let's go, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, we have to be quick.
We have to win this time.
[Woo Bin, I'll be right back.]
[Kwang Soo, I'll hold on until
you get back.]
While your teammates
are hanging from the bar
buy and bring back an item with
the consonants, D, S, and an R!
Go!
Don't do it!
[Big-nose immediately eliminates
himself from the game.]
[Meanwhile, Woo Bin launches
his attack on Woo Bin.]
Don't do it!
No, don't do it!
Jong Kook!
[Jong Kook is busy carrying out his mission.]
D, S, R...
- Do-Shi-Rak!
- That's it! Doshirak!
[Mr. Capable and Ace do it again!
Off to find a doshirak.]
- We need to find a convenience store!
- What else is there besides doshirak?
[Team Red have also figured out
Doshirak as a possibility...]
[But they're probably unaware that
Big-nose has already eliminated himself?]
Darimi?
- That's not D, S, R.
- How does 'D, S, R' fit into that?
- Okay, you're right.
- Dodari?
- I said, it's 'D, S, R!'
[Yoo-Lee Brothers
can't seem to figure it out.]
[Meanwhile, Woo Bin is getting
quite used to the horizontal bar.]
- You can't be sitting up on the bar.
- I never realized how scary he is.
[It's impressive that Hyun Woo
is able to withstand the attack.]
- I'm sorry.
- Hyun Woo is impressive.
[I'm sorry, but I really have to win.]
- Are you sure you're friends?
- I really am sorry.
[Once again,
Woo Bin is the lone survivor.]
- When did you fall off?
- I never even made it up.
- I didn't even see you fall off.
- I never made it up.
- You should've helped me.
- But I never even made it up there.
Where is it?
Where's Doshirak!
[Must find a doshirak!]
There's a convenience store!
There it is!
[Hurry back!]
Do you have any ideas on
how we can make him fall off?
- What do you think?
- Let's take off his shoes and tickle him.
[Woo Bin in danger!]
- Just come down here, Woo Bin.
- I've hung on this long.
- I can't even see anyone right now.
- You're just exhausting yourself.
[Team Black searches for their Doshirak
at the convenience store.]
Why are you even searching through?
Just pick whatever.
[Chooses the chicken doshirak,
of his own preference.]
[Must rush back to the judging table!]
- I hope he's still hanging on.
- Just bring back a doshirak!
[Team Blue and Team Red give up
and make their way back.]
- You can find them at convenience stores.
- What about a Dok-Su-Ri? (An eagle)
[Where are they going to find an eagle
in Myungdong?]
[I'm going to hold on
no matter what it takes.]
Woo Bin, you're just wasting
your efforts.
[Just then...]
[Woo Bin, we're coming for you!]
[Rushes back with a doshirak in hand.]
- What's this?
- It's a doshirak.
- This isn't a doshirak.
- You guys be the judge.
- That's not a doshirak.
- It's not even written on there.
[Leaving it to the producer to judge.]
Jae Suk said the chicken one is tasty.
[Woo Bin comes back down after
seeing the doshirak in their hands.]
Yoo Jae Suk, Lee Kwang Soo,
and Kim Woo Bin...
you succeeded your mission.
[Team Black succeeds their mission.]
[A victory won from Woo Bin's power,
and Jae Suk and Kwang Soo's speed.]
As mentioned, you've earned yourselves
an important item for the final mission.
This is for you,
and your next mission site.
- Here.
- Thank you.
[This is the clue to the final mission,
and the tool for ousting other members.]
He's really merciless.
He was just ruthless.
[Shakes his fans' hands
as a service.]
- Wow, how did you last up there?
- It wasn't easy.
[Amazed that Woo Bin held on
until they returned.]
- Wow, it's Kim Woo Bin!
- Yes, I'm Yoo Jae Suk.
[Unsolicited greeting to Woo Bin's fans.]
They were shouting out
Woo Bin's name.
Yes, I'm Yoo Jae Suk.
[Okay, we've got one under our belt.]
[Off to the next mission site.]
- What's the clue?
- Kwang Soo, let's take a look at the hint.
[Pens!]
- What is it?
- What are these pens for?
[The bag is full of a variety of pens.]
- This must be the hint.
- Why are there so many pens?
[Pens...]
Kwang Soo, if we win
the missions along the way
they'll give us the tools that we'll need
to oust the other members.
Pens or something of the like?
I can hear the producers muttering
as soon as I said the word, 'pen.'
[Kwang Soo's guess that took
the producers by surprise.]
They're going on and on
about how smart I am.
[Could he... really be that smart?]
- Why are there so many pens?
- There are about a hundred in here.
[Over a hundred pens are in the bag.]
Why are there so many pens?
[What is the hidden meaning of these pens?]
['K' cafe in Hannamdong.]
What is this?
[What is the meaning of this setup?]
- What is this?
- Sorry, but Woo Bin goes in the middle.
- What does that even matter?
- Woo Bin goes in the middle.
[Woo Bin belongs in the center
of this team.]
- I'm older than him.
- But he still belongs in the middle.
Since you're the first to arrive,
you automatically move onto the final round.
[Team Black moves onto the final round
for being the first to arrive.]
[Team Red arrives behind them
by the split of a hair.]
- We arrived at the same time.
- This is great!
[Things are going well as planned.]
- What is this?
- What is this for?
- Is it the cookie eating game?
- Second mission is, the staring game.
- Okay, I know this one.
- It requires skills.
- I'm really good at this.
- You are?
- I'm good at the staring game.
These two have never lost a single game
when it comes to the staring game.
I haven't once blinked my eyes
in the past twelve years.
[That's a very easy
twelve year record to break.]
- You just made him break his 12 year record.
- I just broke his 12 year record.
[How about Woo Bin's skills?]
This game is very advantageous
for Jong Kook.
You really have to look closely when checking
to see whether his eyes are open or shut.
How would you know that?
He was watching a movie on the plane and
a stewardess covered him up with a blanket.
- No, that really happened.
- Because it was dark in there.
- You have to look at him closely.
[Installing the boards to hide their faces
from their opponents.]
[Break through these boards and
start the staring game simultaneously.]
- I blink all the time as a habit.
- He's not good at this game.
[First round-
Ha Ha vs Kim Jong Kook.]
Wow, you really are so ugly.
[Ha Ha's specialty,
Rolling his eyes backwards.]
- How did you get so ugly?
- You're ugly, too.
- You've gotten even uglier.
- You look like a beltfish.
- You're seriously really ugly.
- You're no joke either.
- Kwang Soo, say something to him.
- You're both ugly.
- Don't talk about your looks.
- You're all squids in front of Woo Bin.
I'm being serious when I say that I'm one
of the two best looking on this show.
What a joke!
- What a joke!
- What is he saying?
[Where in the world did his sense
of self-confidence come from?]
You should just be quiet about your
ugliness like Gary is being.
Why are you bringing me
into this conversation?
- He's not even saying anything.
- I didn't say anything.
- Get ready.
- Don't forget to make that face.
Set...
[Staring game- Ha Ha vs Kim Jong Kook.]
[Eyes rolled back vs Sleepy eyes.]
[A battle between the small eyes.]
[An example of a soundless scream.]
- Wow, he's seriously so ugly.
- Jong Kook's eyes are starting to tear up.
[Jong Kook's small eyes are in danger!]
Do you like Yoon Eun Hye better,
or Moon Geun Young better?
Wow, my eyes are stinging.
[Ha Ha's in danger!]
[He's holding on!]
[Kim Jong Kook wins the first round!]
- Wow, my eyes are really stinging.
- Did you lose?
[What was it that you said earlier?]
- I was just curious.
- Why would you ask that?
[Staring Game-
Team Red: 0 vs Team Blue: 1.]
Do something with my hair
to make me look ugly.
- No, you're fine as you are.
- You know that puzzle?
The squid puzzle?
- What is that?
- You don't know it?
You put pictures of all the good looking
guys like Woo Bin around the edges
and whomever you put in the middle
becomes the squid.
Can you pull that up on screen?
These guys need to be put up there.
You look like a squid even
when you're just standing there.
Put Ha Ha in the puzzle, too.
- Dried cuttlefish shouldn't talk.
- I thought he was an alien.
- Dried cuttlefish?
- Or like a baby squid.
- King squid, say something.
- Why am I getting pulled into this?
- I don't want to get pulled into this!
- The King Squid should say something.
Why aren't you saying anything?
[Round Two- Gary vs. Jong Kook.]
Gary, you're already funny
even without having to do all that.
Ready, go!
Roll your eyes back.
There you go.
Ouch, my eyes are already stinging!
They're stinging already!
I can't do this!
- I can't do this!
- You have to endure it.
[You have to endure it!]
Yoon Eun Hye!
No!
[Team Red's Gary wins!]
- You won!
- I won?
Yoon Eun Hye!
[Yoon Eun Hye attack worked!
Team Red: 1 vs Team Blue: 1.]
[Kkuk's eternal Achilles' Heel...]
Gary's seriously so ugly.
Wow, my eyes are really stinging.
Isn't he awesome?
Isn't my Gary so ugly?
[At last... it's time for
the Monday Couple's battle.]
[The final round that will determine
who will go on to the playoff round.]
- Okay, next.
- Ji Hyo.
[Practicing.]
- Okay, ready!
- We have to win this.
- I don't know about Ji Hyo.
- Win the game, and win the love.
- Just know that she likes you.
- Set, go!
[Blank Ji will never back down!]
I don't think I can even look at her.
What are you two doing?
Don't fall for it!
[This is child's play.]
[This isn't a game for me.]
[Blank Ji breaks out the big guns.]
[On the brink of losing his sanity.]
[Gary is about to break
through his screen!]
[Strong kissing tactic on her part.]
- Do it back to her!
- Do it!
- You just closed your eyes.
- We won!
[By a mistake on Blank Ji's part,
Gary wins!]
[Team Red moves onto the final round.]
That doesn't count.
Come on, Jae Suk.
[Flutters her eyes shut
without even realizing it.]
That's because Ji Hyo really likes Gary.
- Things are heating up again.
- Ji Hyo, is this our beginning?
- Clear things up for me.
- Four years of teasing is enough.
[Four years of teasing and
still counting for the Monday Couple.]
- It's our turn.
- Okay.
[First round of the playoffs-
Suk Jin vs Jae Suk.]
We should paint something on.
Do you have the pen on you?
[The pens that they received in the bag
after having won the first mission.]
A mole on my nose?
[Plans to make the opponent shut
their eyes in laughter.]
[Jae Suk is going through
a transformation.]
- They can't put things on their face!
- What are we supposed to do?
[We're going to have to do
something, too...]
Hand me some tape.
- Let's see who wins.
- Fine.
[Becoming extremely competitive.]
Yeah, go for the clippers.
Don't go too overboard.
I think they're doing something.
I was going to do that, too.
[The breathtaking behind.]
[We can't let them win!
Jae Suk also goes for the tape.]
- Are you sure about taping the hair?
- It's okay.
- Wait!
- Kwang Soo, this is how you do it.
- Why are you going this far?
- Because this is what I need to do.
Big-nose is breaking out the big guns.
[Big-nose's counterattack vs
Jae Suk's forestallment.]
[Suk Jin vs Jae Suk.]
[A shocking visual.]
[Pretty close.]
I thought this was just a
staring contest!
[A slapstick comedy that's disguised
as being a staring contest.]
[I vow to win this!]
Kwang Soo, pull it back even more.
- Pull it back more.
- Tape it more.
[Ji Suk Jin wins the first round.]
- Why did you pull that hard!
- You told me to do it!
[A painful loss.]
[Big-nose sacrifices his dignity
for the win.]
Woo Bin is up next.
- I feel burdened by it.
- Do you think you can do it?
- You need to protect Woo Bin.
- I think he's eager to win.
[I have to win to earn the next clue.]
You can use the tape on me.
Put it back really hard.
[Handsome Woo Bin said
he wants to do it.]
That's enough.
[Turn my mouth to the side, too.]
- Don't do it!
- No, that's good.
[Woo Bin, we have to
win this no matter what.]
[Team Red is convinced that they'll win
with Gary's transformation.]
- That's awesome, Gary.
- Ready.
[Round two- Gary vs Woo Bin.]
[Where did your eyebrows go?]
[Where did Woo Bin go?]
What is this!
[He even flips his eyes around.]
[Woo Bin is determined to win!]
Endure it.
You're ugly and you can win this.
My eyes hurt!
[Kim Woo Bin wins the second round.]
[Shocked at Woo Bin's performance.]
[Woo Bin dedicates himself
to the win.]
This team is very strong.
They've got too big of an advantage.
[Team Black wins the second mission.]
- We're confident that we'll win it all!
- This is my favorite game!
- That's right.
- My family played it just this morning.
- Who won this morning?
- My mother won.
My parents are still laughing
about it.
[Mission two, clear!]
[Let's put our strengths together
and win the last mission, too!]
You've won yourselves another hint for
having won the second mission.
- Thank you.
- I'll carry it.
Let's go.
[Kwang Soo and Woo Bin
take both the hints.]
I haven't been here in a long time.
[Seoul's National Museum.]
[The members enter the treasure filled
museum with trepidation in their hearts.]
[Scatters about as soon as
they enter the museum.]
Isn't this what we wore during
the opening?
[The black shirts they wore during
the opening are scattered about.]
Are you going to film me
changing my shirt?
What are we going to do
after we change?
[Sound for an announcement.]
Here's your final mission of the day.
Find the ancient script.
[Final mission-
Find the ancient script.]
From this moment on,
it'll be an individual game.
Piece together the parchment papers hidden
throughout this place and find the script.
Only one name can be written into the script,
and whoever writes their name in it
will win the whole race.
A great secret is hidden behind the clues
that were earned after each previous mission
so take good care of
the clues earned.
What the heck?
My other teammates took the hints.
[I'm in trouble.]
Keep in mind that the hint items earned
can be taken from one another.
We will now start the final mission.
[Ancient script mission- Start.]
What the heck?
I thought we were all on the same team.
[The method of elimination is
still shrouded in a cloud of mystery.]
What's in the second bag?
I need to meet up with
Kwang Soo and Woo Bin.
[Jae Suk's plan is to meet up with
Kwang Soo and Woo Bin first.]
[But those two are already
in the know.]
There's information that an ancient
script will be revealed tonight.
[The two men have been working towards
a secret mission since this morning.]
[The secret deal to eliminate the others
to take the ancient script for themselves.]
[And...]
[The reasons for them having given
their best to the missions all day...]
[Is because of the mysterious item that
is hidden in this bag.]
[A secret mission is handed to these two only
after the rules of the game are announced.]
You're a spy.
[You're a spy.]
[And the method of elimination that
only these two spies are privy to.]
[Name tag writing.]
[Oust the members by finding blank name tags
and writing their names on it.]
- We don't need to do that anymore.
- That was always so barbaric.
This method is so much easier
and dignified.
[Will it be as simple as they thought
and will it be how it'll be carried on?]
[Spies- Oust the seven members by writing
their names onto the blank name tags.]
[But there is a condition.]
[But it must be written on a designated tag
with the corresponding pen for it to work.]
[Designated name tag?]
[Write it on the wrong name tag, and
you'll be the one to get ousted instead.]
The location of the script will be revealed to
you letter by letter after each elimination.
[The location of the script will be revealed
letter by letter after each elimination.]
[These countless pens are
all designated to a certain tag?]
There's an extra 'R' sticker
on this one.
Wait, why is the word, 'pen'...
This one is written differently.
I wonder if it was written with
a paintbrush.
Okay, so we can't use just
any pen for this.
[Must use the correct pen for
the elimination to take effect.]
I've already taken out a few pens.
I wonder if it's this one.
[This brush pen...]
[Is the correct pen!]
I just need to keep this one out.
[He didn't think that pen was special
when he originally took it out!]
I just took it out
because I liked how it wrote.
I write really well with these pens.
I wasn't even thinking anything of it.
[That was the pen used to transform
Jae Suk's face earlier.]
This is why that word
was written in differently.
[The brush pen is the only effective
one out of this whole lot.]
[Let's hide the pen and
get this started!]
Take it!
We have to take it from them!
- Let's take their hints away from them!
- We have to take it from them.
- Can we do it together?
- Who was on that team again?
- Woo Bin, Jae Suk, and Kwang Soo.
- That's right.
I need to find Kwang Soo
and Woo Bin first.
[Kwang Soo's plan is to entice
Mr. Capable over to his side first.]
[Secretly approaches Jong Kook with
an offer to show him what's inside the bag.]
[Opens the bag to show him all the pens.]
I think we're supposed to use these
and do something with them.
[But the effective pen is hidden
inside Kwang Soo's sock.]
Ugh, you startled me.
[Hyun Woo finds them, and
joins the group.]
- I smelled something.
- Smell what?
I could smell you guys.
[Young Hyun Woo sniffed out the hint.]
You really startled me.
- Can I be included in this?
- Have you found anything?
- I just found it right here.
- This is what I earned earlier.
The reason why I told you this was to ask
that you don't try to overpower me.
Then I promise not to overpower you
with my strength either.
Do you want to die?
[Hyun Woo's adorable antics.]
- You know that this is an individual race?
- Of course, I know.
[Kwang Soo is in need of allies, and
gains Hyun Woo and Kkuk on his side.]
- Us three are the right amount.
- Yes, four would be too many.
- You have to get in the right line.
- Yes, I know. The right line.
- Are you getting in this line, too?
- No, you're both getting in my line.
- Just for today. That's right.
- Like this?
[Let's just win this thing and
take care of the consequences later.]
- I think he's acting too cocky.
- Maybe I should snap the rope off.
Why would you do such a thing?
I feel something here.
We just have to look for
the blank name tags.
[Woo Bin searches for the blank name tags
while others search for the parchment paper.]
[Oust the other members by writing down
their names onto the designated name tags.]
[Oust all the other members in order to
find out where the script is being kept!]
[Just then.]
[A name tag is discovered.]
[But... who's name should he write?]
- Kwang Soo, where are you?
- Between the second and the third floor.
[The two spies meet up away
from other members' eyes.]
[Woo Bin shows Kwang Soo
the name tag he found.]
[Whose name should they
write on the tag?]
We'll be the ones to get ousted unless
we write down the correct name on here.
Yes, but who?
Just write down whomever on it first.
- This is all you found? No clues?
- That's right.
We have like a hundred pens,
so can we just use whatever?
No, you need to use the right pen.
[Kwang Soo is already aware that
only the brush pen can be used.]
- Tell me.
- I can't figure that part out.
You... why is it that I can't even
tell my own partner about it?
[Remains competitive with his
own teammate.]
Give me some time.
Give me about three seconds.
Keep this up, and
I'll write down your name.
I'll just try every one of these pens.
Here's the right pen.
- I have one, too.
- Pull the cap off.
That's the one.
- Is this the only one that works?
- Yes, why?
When we first received the mission...
Must I teach you everything?
We're on the same team!
[The dumb and dumber spies are wasting
precious time with their conversation.]
Only this word is written
with a different writing utensil.
Smarter than what you expected,
aren't I?
[Cocky...]
[You sure are a smart cookie...]
- You really got lucky with your partner.
- Do you feel how sweaty my palm is?
[The Spy Brothers are back in the game.]
Pull out all the right pens
and hide them in your clothes.
[Woo Bin pulls out all the pens
and sticks them in his pockets.]
[And places eye catching pens
in their back pockets.]
[But... wo's name will go on
this name tag?]
- Jong Kook, he was trying to steal my pens.
- Seriously?
- He was seriously going to take it.
[Kwang Soo is telling his recent partner,
Jae Suk, on Jong Kook.]
- He was seriously trying to take it.
- What are you doing?
- Were you trying to take it?
- You're stealing from your own teammate?
- Seriously...
- Did you see how he was talking to me?
He's pointing his finger in my face.
Please watch yourself.
[The young bodyguard tries
to act tough.]
- We're over.
- You have to go through these two first.
[Kwang Soo is relying on
Kkuk's shield.]
- Can I say something to him?
- Sure, go ahead.
- Don't step too close to him.
- Okay, just one word.
[Gets Kkuk's permission
to slap him in the face.]
That's all I wanted to say to him.
I understood what you're saying.
Where are the parchment papers?
[Ji Hyo is searching
for the parchment papers.]
[Searching through every
nook and cranny.]
[Discovers an 'R' marked parchment paper.]
Wow, that wasn't easy to find.
[What information is hidden
in this piece of parchment?]
[There's a spy hidden amongst you.]
Unbelievable.
[Blank Ji finds out that there's a spy!]
[But their identities
still remain a mystery.]
Who could it be?
[Who could it be?]
Have you found anything?
- What are you doing?
- Have you found anything?
[What's wrong with Ji Hyo?]
I don't have anything to share with you.
- I did find something.
- You did?
You're lying.
Really?
What have you found?
I really have it here.
[What could that be?
It can't be...]
Let's trade.
- You have to find these, too.
- That's true.
- This is very important.
- Okay.
[Woo Bin already took out
what he needs from the bag.]
Push it towards each other
on the count of three.
One, two, three.
[Trades the bag of pens for
the parchment.]
[Ugh, why are there so many?]
[Woo Bin gets the parchment in his hands.]
[A hint alluding to his presence.]
I'm going to have to hurry.
Where could it be?
[Rushing to find more blank name tags.]
[That is...]
[The first was outlined in red,
but this one is outlined in light purple.]
[There must be a reason why
they're colored differently.]
[Steps outside to solve the riddle of
the different colored name tags.]
- Why did you take out some of the pens?
- I only took out a few.
Let me see.
I'm just going to take a look at it.
- Wait.
- Wow... is that it?
Right?
Don't you think that they're
related to our different characters?
[Could it be?]
I think these means something...
I'll share them with you.
Okay.
[Woo Bin offers up the pens in an
attempt to walk away from them.]
We have to let each other know
if we find anything out, okay?
[The members are still left
in a state of confusion.]
[Just what is it that he discovered?]
I got it.
I think I figured it out.
It's the color of their buttons.
[The color of their buttons?]
[Just a moment ago...]
[When he saw the members...]
[Ha Ha's buttons are yellow.]
[Blank Ji's buttons are light purple.]
[All the members'
button colors are different.]
[The different colored outlines are
indicating to the different colored buttons.]
[Woo Bin's keen eyes solve the mystery
of the blank name tags.]
Running Man seriously is no joke.
Have you found anything?
Would I be walking around
aimlessly like this if I had?
Woo Bin, have you found anything?
[Jae Suk's buttons... are green!]
I did find one parchment paper.
- Okay, wait here.
- Come here. What do you have?
[Jong Kook is...]
[Wait, that's...]
[The first name tag I found...
The red buttons!]
[The owner of the name tag
has been found!]
[While Kwang Soo diverts
their attention...]
[Woo Bin disappears out of
their eyesight.]
[Writes down red button wearing
Jong Kook's name onto the red name tag.]
[Will it work?]
This means someone's been ousted.
Someone's been ousted.
- Kim Jong Kook, out.
- What? Already?
Kim Jong Kook, out.
- What did it say?
- I knew this was going to happen.
I told you.
I knew this was going to happen.
[Mr. Capable is the first one
to get ousted!]
Wait, I shouldn't be cheering.
- What? Kim Jong Kook is ousted?
- I told you!
- Why? Who ousted you?
- What happened?
[Jong Kook is ousted before
their own disbelieving eyes.]
This is great!
[Unsure of what just happened,
but still breaks out in a dance.]
[It's time to celebrate!
Jong Kook's just been ousted.]
[The location of the ancient script-
First piece of the puzzle.]
[Byul]
- Kim Jong Kook, out.
- See?
He got ousted from being with
Kwang Soo.
[Ha Ha suspects Kwang Soo.]
But look what I just found.
[Ha Ha finds a piece of the
parchment paper.]
[Oust the spy to find out the location.
The way to do that is...]
[There's a spy?]
What's the method to do that?
[I can win the race if I oust the spy.]
- Can I trust you? Keep this a secret.
- Of course, I will.
Take it off, Suk Jin.
- I knew it.
- You really haven't found anything?
- There's a spy amongst us.
- Seriously?
I'm just going to show
this to you.
[Sharing what he discovered
with Jae Suk.]
Oust the spy to find out the location.
The way to do that is...
- How do you do it?
- That was it.
We have to find a way to
oust the spy.
- You're not a spy, are you?
- No, I'm not.
- I trusted you when I showed this to you.
- Of course.
I didn't show this to you just so
that you could call others to alert them.
There's no one around us, is there?
Why are you acting like this?
I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
[Yoo Hyuk attempts to play a prank
and pretends to be the spy.]
You think I'd actually fall for that?
I'm not stupid.
[Even though he may talk tough,
he continues to stop Jae Suk from writing.]
[Suk Jin pulls out a pen of his own.]
- Ji Suk Jin, out.
- Yoo Jae Suk, out.
[Immature behavior of a 46 year old.]
- The star can't be eliminated that easily.
- What? I'm the star here.
You think that a star can be
so easily eliminated?
I even found the parchment paper.
Stop being so ridiculous.
[Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is...]
[Writes down Ji Hyo's name on the
purple name tag he got from Woo Bin.]
[He's writing down Ji Hyo's name!]
You don't think it's me, do you?
Song Ji Hyo, out.
- What is this?
- What's going on here?
Where's Jae Suk?
Why did Song Ji Hyo get ousted?
What's written on
the parchment that you have?
[Ignores his question.]
Come on, Woo Bin.
Fine, I'll find one on my own.
Hey, I'll just find one on my own.
[How sad for anyone who hasn't
found a parchment paper of their own.]
- Ugh, seriously.
- I'll give this to you.
And don't forget what I told you.
- What? About the spy?
- Yeah. If I leave like this...
Don't just walk around aimlessly
and find something!
- Ugh, seriously.
- I'll go look for a gift for you.
- Don't get yourself ousted, okay?
- Why would I get myself ousted?
['Byul' 'Yi'...]
[Earns the second piece of the puzzle
to where the script is kept.]
How am I going to eliminate them?
Everyone knows that there's a spy.
[They must now find out
how to eliminate the spy.]
Hey!
[Jae Suk actually finds something.]
[Find the designated name tags
and write down their names.]
What does this mean?
It must mean that there are
some name tags.
But where are these name tags?
It's one and the same.
The culprits are searching
for the name tags, too.
The culprits are writing down
the names on the name tags.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo got ousted when they
wrote down their names on those name tags.
[Ha Ha discovers a name tag!]
[The blue name tag...
belongs to blue button wearing Gary.]
[But Ha Ha is still unaware of the secret
behind the blank name tags.]
[It must be one of these pens...]
I have to find it.
I need to find out how to do it.
[Must find out the method of elimination.]
Suk Jin is the spy.
- Woo Bin, I need to talk to you.
- Let's talk in private.
- Who do you think is the spy?
- Who do I think?
I have no idea.
- I found one.
- What?
- I found one of the name tags.
- Seriously?
Let me see.
- You haven't found any?
- I don't even know what it looks like.
[Bragging about his name tag to the spy.]
[This sky blue name tag is his own!]
[What do I do?]
Wait.
Wait here.
Stay there.
[Sunny and cheery as ever.]
[Pretends to be on the lookout,
and quietly calls Kwang Soo over.]
Kwang Soo and I have been talking
about it, and I don't think this is it.
What else could it be?
Try writing down my name.
[Writes down Hyun Woo's name
as he sits right next to them.]
[Sorry, Hyun Woo.]
Lee Hyun Woo, out.
See?
[Jae Suk witnesses the scene.]
- Lee Hyun Woo was the spy.
- What just happened?
Kim Woo Bin!
[Even his cries of despair sound cheery.]
- He wrote down his own name.
- Who just wrote that down?
He wrote down his own name.
[Turns it around and says that
Hyun Woo wrote down his own name.]
This doesn't look like Hyun Woo wrote it.
Look at the handwriting.
The handwriting is different.
[Awkward expression on his face.]
[And immediately changes their story.]
I have no idea what's going on here.
Why did Hyun Woo get ousted?
Why did they leave that happy Hyun Woo
to write down his own name?
Woo Bin.
We need to find the green tag.
We have to find the green one
right now.
[This won't do. We need to
eliminate Jae Suk immediately.]
The colored outlines on the name tags...
I just figured it out.
It's the buttons.
[Ha Ha solves the mystery
of the buttons.]
Someone's buttons are red.
Kwang Soo's buttons are white.
They're all different.
I forgot what color Jong Kook's was.
We all have different colored buttons.
The name tag with the yellow outline...
is mine.
[Ha Ha accurately solves the
button mystery.]
Writing down my name on the yellow
name tag would mean that I get ousted.
I have to find the other colored tags,
and write down the matching name on it.
Okay, I've figured it out.
[The problem now is to find
the correct pen to use!]
[The net is starting to close in
on the spies!]
What is it?
[Just then...]
Ji Suk Jin, out.
[Spies' fourth victim, Big-nose.]
['Byul' 'Yi' 'Seo' 'Do'.]
- Good job.
- Did it work?
[Kwang Soo finds and eliminates Suk Jin
without anyone even knowing about it.]
We need to find out how much
the others know.
[Worried about what the
others may know.]
- Do you have any more name tags?
- No, I don't.
Are there name tags for us, too?
No, there can't be.
[Of course... there is.]
- Do you have mine?
- No, we're on the same team.
[Suspicions are back in place.]
I can't eliminate you
when you're my partner.
And I don't think the same rules
apply to us.
Ugh, what could it be?
[Ha Ha is the closest to figuring out
who the spies are at the moment.]
[Discovers another parchment paper!]
[Kiddo is taking care of
some business today.]
[Clue to the spy identity-
Baduk.]
[This hint indicates to
the identity of the spies!]
[Baduk?]
[The black and white pieces of baduk are
indicating to the spies' button colors.]
Someone already took them
out of here.
How am I going to
get that pen away from them?
The pen that Kwang Soo has
is the real one.
I have to find the name tags.
Ugh, this is so scary!
I'm suddenly getting scared
of Woo Bin.
[Find their own name tag and hide it,
or find the spies' name tag and oust them!]
Kwang Soo, you're really scary.
[Ha Ha makes contact with Kwang Soo
in order to get the pen in his hands.]
What else do you have?
[Searching through all of Kwang Soo's pens.]
[That's the real brush pen!]
I'm just going to borrow these, and be back.
I'll be right back with these.
- What is it?
- Dong Hoon.
- I'll seriously give them right back to you.
- Just give me one.
- Which one?
- I'll pick.
Okay.
- Give me one more.
- Why? Why are you being like this?
[Can't ask for the brush pen,
as that will just ignite his suspicion.]
Okay, here.
- Satisfied?
- Give me one more.
[Ha Ha still has the brush pen
in his hands.]
- Okay, we're good.
- Ha Ha.
[Gary picks up the abandoned case.]
Come on, Ha Ha.
[Ha Ha picks up on the clues,
and runs away from Kwang Soo.]
I think it's this one.
[Finds out which pen is the right one
from Kwang Soo's reaction.]
[Jae Suk joins the chase
while remaining clueless.]
Dong Hoon is the culprit!
- What did you say? Seriously?
- Dong Hoon is the culprit!
[Kwang Soo attempts to frame
Ha Ha of being the spy.]
- No, it's Kwang Soo.
- Jae Suk, we have to catch Ha Ha.
[Jae Suk doesn't know who to believe.]
- Kwang Soo is trying to frame me.
- Wow, you're such a liar.
[Ha Ha gets the brush pen
in his hands...]
[Just then, the announcement
bell sounds.]
Yoo Jae Suk, out.
[Woo Bin find the green name tag and
ousts Jae Suk in the midst of the confusion.]
Yoo Jae Suk.
[Earns the fifth piece of the puzzle.]
['Byul' 'Yi' 'Seo' 'So' 'Gwan'.]
Byul Gwan?
[One step closer to the location.]
[Now, it's Kwang Soo and Woo Bin
vs Ha Ha and Gary.]
Dong Hoon took my pen.
It's over if he ousts us first.
[The Spy Brothers are in danger of
being ousted by Ha Ha.]
I found another piece of the puzzle,
but we have to oust the other two first.
The spy can't rip off your
name tag, can he?
It's not about ripping off the name tag,
but it's about writing down the name.
- Then can't you write down the name now?
- I don't have any name tags.
- You don't have the name tag?
- We have to find his white name tag.
[Must find either the white or the black
name tag and oust the spies!]
If he finds our name tags first,
then it's all over for us.
- Hey, Dong Hoon.
- Yeah?
- What about this color?
- What is it?
Do you need this one?
[Wait, that's Ha Ha's yellow
name tag!]
Gary, this would be big trouble.
That name tag would eliminate you, right?
- Did I do a good job?
- Totally.
- Let me give you a kiss.
- No, don't do it.
- We'll split the prize if we win.
- Really?
[Who knew that Gary would have
Ha Ha's name tag!]
I was going to keep it to myself.
- I'm going to give you this as a gift.
- What is it?
[Huh?]
I almost killed you myself.
[Ha Ha pulls out Gary's
name tag out of his pants!]
No, not there.
Put it down your pants.
- What if your hat falls off?
- No, it's okay.
[They each had each other's lives
in the grasp of their hands.]
One of those two could have
their own name tags on them.
I have no doubt.
[Can't find any more name tags and
guesses that they must have it on them.]
[The Spy Brothers prepares to
faceoff with Gary and Ha Ha.]
Have you found anything?
[Walks towards them...]
Why are you following us?
[Attempts to surround them.]
- What are you looking for?
- We don't have anything.
[Gary and Ha Ha are in possession
of their own name tags.]
[Ha Ha senses the danger and
attempts to flee.]
What are you looking for?
I don't have anything.
[Gary puts on a dumb act.]
Come here, Dong Hoon!
What are they looking for?
[The spies aren't backing off.]
I'm going to have to hide it.
[Ha Ha successfully escapes with
his pen and name tag still intact.]
I really don't have anything, Kwang Soo.
[Gary is receiving a full body search.]
I told you that I don't have anything!
Kwang Soo, here it is.
Why are you doing this to me!
[The hat boy fails to protect
the name tag lamb.]
I didn't even get to do anything!
No, what are you doing!
[Kwang Soo stops in the midst of writing.]
What are you doing!
No, don't do this!
[Forcing him to finish writing out
his own name. How cruel...]
We got it!
Gary, out.
[Discovers the sixth piece
of the puzzle.]
Dong Hoon almost has you two,
so you'd better watch out.
[Seriously?]
- It's all over for you two.
- Does he know our button colors?
What?
He knows about the button colors?
[Left remaining-
Two spies vs Ha Ha.]
[Eliminate the last remaining person
to find out the location!]
I'm sure that he has his own name tag.
Gary just said that
he traded his own name tag.
[Kwang Soo and Woo Bin are in
full search mode for Ha Ha.]
I don't think I can find it.
Have you found it?
[Kwang Soo discovers Ha Ha.]
If you've found it, then I'm sure you
would've already written it down.
[Mind game to feel each other out.]
[It all comes down to who'll be first
to get the name tag in their hands.]
[Each thinks that they have their own
name tags and starts to search.]
Ha Ha, did you hide it somewhere?
- Lee Kwang Soo, out.
- What the heck!
[What?]
Ha Ha, did you write down my
name somewhere?
[How can Kwang Soo be ousted
when Ha Ha's standing right here?]
[That can only mean...]
[Woo Bin ousted Kwang Soo!]
[Completely unexpected!]
[Why would he eliminate his
own spy partner?]
[A while ago... Woo Bin discovers
Kwang Soo's white name tag.]
This is Kwang Soo's name tag.
[Just in case, he keeps it
a secret from Kwang Soo.]
[After ousting Gary, six of the
seven puzzle pieces are found.]
[Only one more puzzle piece is needed!
Must eliminate just one more person.]
[Just then...
he remembers the other name tag.]
This was all learned from you.
I'm sorry.
I had no other choice.
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
[Thus, Kwang Soo is ousted.]
[What just happened!]
What is this all about?
- Did you just oust me?
- No, I didn't. What color is Woo Bin?
[Goodbye, Kwang Soo.]
Woo Bin, I've been eliminated!
I think Dong Hoon knows
everything!
[The Giraffe still doesn't
understand what's just happened.]
[Finally earns the last piece
of the puzzle.]
The library annex on the second floor?
Second floor library annex?
['Byul' 'Yi' 'Seo' 'So'
'Gwan' 'Gwan' 'Cheung']
[Second floor library annex.]
[Second floor library annex-
Just need to get to the location to win!]
The spy is amongst you.
You're seriously no joke.
What do you mean?
Write down the names onto
the designated blank name tags.
- What is it?
- I have something for you.
Why are you giving me so many?
The spy...
is amongst you!
That's why you'll never make it.
I'm... the spy!
What is this?
Cheung?
Second floor library annex.
[Woo Bin is getting closer
to the ancient script.]
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
[The ancient script is mine!]
[Follows the clues and
makes it up to the library annex.]
[The legendary ancient script
is right in front of his eyes.]
[Only one name can be added
to the script.]
The ancient script.
[The owner of the script... Kim Woo Bin.]
You didn't find anything out?
[If they had all worked together,
then they could've easily figured it out.]
This was all because you kept
everything to yourself.
You knew that Woo Bin was behind it all?
Seriously, Woo Bin.
This is the one thing that I've learned
from being on Running Man four times.
[What he learned was knowing
how to betray.]
Hyun Woo never found anything out,
but kept that cheerful smile on his face.
Anyway, today's winner is,
Kim Woo Bin!
[Last Business-
Final winner- Kim Woo Bin.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
- Merry Christmas!
- Okay, I'll be a permanent fixture.
- Our nation's representative mother!
- She is a mother to everyone!
- Mom!
[The famed actress fully immerses
herself into the variety world.]
[The hottest Christmas to date!]
This is really fun.
[The unexpected surprise gift!]
- Kim Hye Jung!
- Please!
Yes, this is what it's all about.
[Next week on Running Man-
Take care of our mother.]