[Gyunggi-do: Running Man Dormitory]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[All the students at the dormitory
are in a great mood this morning.]
We're playing like a group of old people.
- Are you all paying your rent on time?
- Make sure to pay your bills on time.
I'm the landlord's son, so be careful
unless you want to get evicted.
I've been here the longest
out of everyone here.
No, that's me.
[How dare he say something of the like
in front of Big-nosed Brother.]
I was born in 1993.
- You were born in 1993?
- Of course, I was.
- I was born in early 1993.
- Early 1993? How early?
Very early.
I know that you've all been students of
this dormitory for years
- but we've got some new students.
- Please let it be girls!
- They're about to come in from over there.
- Please let it be girl students.
It's a group of female students.
[Get ready...]
[Because they are headed your way.]
[A group of fierce and ferocious girls.]
[This group of new students will
rule the Running Man male students.]
[Running University's Visual Design Major-
Lee Gook Joo.]
We have to get rid Kim Jong Kook first!
Get the easy ones out of the way first!
Do you know what
her social security number is?
[Female Tiger- Baek Ji Young.
Running University's Home Econ Major.]
[You can't find anyone who knows
how to party better than her.]
Should we play the game over here,
and party over there?
[Nonstop energizer bunny- Hong Jin Young.
Running University's Dancing Major.]
[This isn't the same Fei that
we're used to seeing on Miss A.]
[Two faced idol- Miss A's Fei.
Dance sports exchange student.]
[A commendable comedic sense.]
[The infamous model- Kang Seung Hyun.
Running University's Model Major.]
[A formidable group of female students.]
Kick with the front leg,
and kick with the hind leg!
Hello.
[An impressive group of
Running University students.]
Hello, my name is Baek Ji Young of
classroom 12. It's nice to be here.
- What's your major?
- Me? I'm a Home Economics Major.
- I'm a Home Economics Major.
- You are?
Shouldn't you be a
Domestic Marriage Major?
I've never seen anyone do that
to Jong Kook.
I can't believe I just saw her
do that to Jong Kook.
[Ji Young shows that
she isn't afraid of the Tiger.]
Hello! Ppuing ppuing!
(Common "cute" gesture)
- I was born in 1995. Ppuing Ppuing!
- What year?
I was born in 1995. Ppuing Ppuing!
[Even she can't seem to believe
her own actions.]
She was born in the year that
I made my debut.
Hello, my name is Lee Gook Joo,
and I'm really glad to be here.
What's your major?
I'm a Visual Designs Major.
[Gook Joo must be very detail-oriented.]
- Gook Joo.
- Yes?
Why are you so sweaty already?
We haven't even done anything yet.
We haven't even done anything.
We seriously have yet to do anything.
I'm full and luxurious.
A luxurious waistline and legs.
Full-figured and luxurious!
[An infamous person in the dormitory.]
- You should've put on a fake mustache.
- I wanted to look more girly on the show.
So I left my fake mustache at home.
Hello, I'm your favorite energizer battery,
Hong Jin Young.
Hello everyone,
my name is Hong Jin Young.
Jin Young's putting on an act.
She's not normally like that.
Me?
What about me?
- I'm sure you'll change.
- I bet she really loves to party.
She's the perfect type of girl
to party with.
I bet Ji Young and Jin Young would've been
really good friends back in school.
Don't worry about me.
I'm just trying to cool down a bit.
I thought you were snapping off the leaves
so you could eat them like lettuce wraps.
- Leaves for the lettuce wraps?
- No, I'm fine back here.
Hello.
She is so pretty.
My name is Kang Seung Hyun, and
my dream is to become a famous model.
[Placed first in a worldwide
Asian model search.]
- She's already a famous model.
- Can you show us your catwalk?
- Why would you ask her to do that?
- I can't see you from that far away.
- You can't see me? You want me to do it here?
- Yes, show us your catwalk.
- Show us your catwalk.
- But I don't have any heels on.
[A rare catwalk demonstration by a top model.]
[A top model student.]
[Luxurious Gook Joo will show off
her own style of catwalk.]
Next, our very own Fei!
[Miss A's very own Fei.]
Hello everyone.
How's Ji Hyo going to follow that act?
[Dance major exchange student, Fei.]
- Fei has changed a lot.
- Yes, I have.
She used to be so shy in the past,
and would never do stuff like that.
[Our Fei has changed.]
- How did you change so much?
- It's from all the dancing I do.
It's from all the dancing I do.
I'm so embarrassed!
Don't you think you're
reacting too differently?
- What did you say?
- Your reaction to her.
It's okay because that's all she has.
That's all she has to offer unlike us.
[You've only seen a fraction
of what she has to offer.]
Are you looking for your lettuce
wraps again?
[Maybe she's hungry for food?]
- All of you are students at the moment.
- Okay.
Your rent money that you have saved up
is slowly starting to dwindle.
That's why you will all be participating
in summer part-time job missions.
As a prize for winning each of the missions
you can choose what you would need as
a struggling college student as your prize.
Maybe we can get a washing machine.
- I don't have a washing machine.
- The team that wins the final mission...
will be given the chance to take
home all the prizes that have been won.
We just have to win the final mission.
But you can't win just at the end because
you have to collect the prizes along the way.
- So you have to work the whole time.
- We've got two big fighters right now.
[The formidable Tiger siblings.]
[Off to their first part-time job location.]
[Separate buses for the two teams.]
- See you later, Mrs. Baek.
- See you later.
- Gook Joo, do you have a boyfriend?
- We broke up pretty recently.
- But why do you look so happy?
- You are such a liar!
- You're such a liar!
- What do you think of Kwang Soo?
- Do you think he's cute?
- I like skinny guys.
I like chubby girls too.
You're the first person
to ever tell me that I'm chubby.
Why are you telling me that
I'm chubby?
- I just meant that you're cute.
- I guarantee that you two won't ever work.
- Why not?
- Kwang Soo isn't Gook Joo's style.
- There's nothing wrong with me.
- I'm right, aren't I?
You think Kwang Soo wouldn't like her?
No, it's Gook Joo who won't like him.
What are you saying is wrong
with my face?
Gook Joo will never go for
Kwang Soo's looks.
I think Jin Young has a really cute voice.
But the expression on your face
says that you're lying.
- I'm always pretty expressionless.
- Gary's just like that.
I really like your music.
I just like you.
[Just then, a bee flies in
through the bus window.]
[Jin Young very naturally jumps over
to sit down next to Gary.]
Can I ask you what this means?
Jin Young, 'what mean'?
My body just felt pulled over here.
I've never felt so at a loss
for words before.
[While everyone is enjoying
conversing with their teammates...]
[They arrive at their first
part-time job location.]
- It's an amusement park.
- This is great!
[Make your rent money mission-
First part-time job location: Amusement Park]
You've all been told that this race is to
help you earn your rent money.
Your first part-time job will be...
to work at an amusement park.
[Welcome your Amusement Park Job.]
[Everyone's in high spirits
for being at the amusement park.]
There are a variety of jobs you can do
at an amusement park.
That's why we've prepared
a job scramble.
What do we have to do?
- Do you all see the bungalow behind you?
- Yes.
- You all have to go in there.
- I bet it's really hot in there.
- Is it air conditioned?
- No, it's not.
[Fei really has changed a lot.]
She never used to ask any questions,
but she's totally different now.
I will announce through the mic what
your job will be once you're in the bungalow.
Then only the first person to come out of
the bungalow will get to do that job.
- Only one person?
- If that person succeeds the job...
then the team that person is on
will be given a point.
But if the person fails the job, then
a point will be given to the other team.
[Fail the job, and the point will be
given to the opposing team.]
[It won't always be an advantage to be
the first one out of the bungalow.]
The first team to gain a total of five points
will get to win this mission.
It looks so hot in there.
[Everyone steps into the bungalow.]
- You have to use your strength, Gook Joo.
- Okay, I understand.
- Okay, to all the students...
- Yes?
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes.
I will now announce
what your first job is going to be.
Your first job will be...
catching the water balloons.
[First job- Catch the water balloons.]
You have to throw the water balloon
into the air and spin a full circle in place.
Then you have to catch the water balloon in
the basket placed on the top of your head.
You have to catch at least three out of
five balloons to pass this mission.
[A total of five chances-
Must catch three to succeed.]
[Confident Big-nose gets ready
to dash out the door.]
[Muscle boy holds fast to the doorknob.]
Everyone get out of the way.
[Gook Joo is on the move.]
[Out of my way!]
[But... the game hasn't even started yet.]
- We haven't started yet.
- It's a total battlefield in here.
Everyone needs to calm down
and wait for the sound of my whistle.
- He's blocking the door.
- I never did that.
[All the girls are engaged
in a verbal battle.]
[Starting over until the sound of
the whistle is heard.]
[Total chaos]
[People wanting to get out vs
people wanting to block.]
Fine, I'll just do it!
[Kkuk takes an attempt at
the water balloon job.]
[Gary is feeling bewildered after having
experienced Gook Joo's power firsthand.]
I think he'll be able to do it.
We have to hope that he fails.
Whether Jong Kook succeeds or fails the job,
he will not be returning to the bungalow.
[Once a person steps out of the bungalow,
that person can't go back in the bungalow.]
Yes!
[A Kkuk-less bungalow is a great
piece of news to the Red Team.]
Let's do it over.
[Angry Kkuk is out of control.]
Even if Jong Kook succeeds and gets his point
him being out of the bungalow
is worth so much more than that to us.
Okay, let's get the game started.
Jong Kook, crouch down a bit
when you're trying to catch the balloon.
You have to crouch down.
Was that Fei just talking? She
never used to talk so much in the past.
Wow, she's become quite the talker now.
I can't believe how Fei has changed.
She's learned to talk quite a bit.
[Now that things have turned out this way,
Kkuk really needs to succeed his job at hand.]
The sun is really bright.
Can I wear my sunglasses?
[Worker Kkuk may get in trouble in
his attempt to look cool at the job.]
The sun is really hot and bright out there.
[Water balloon challenge.]
[First attempt- Will he succeed?]
[A total of five chances.
Fails at his first attempt.]
- Don't throw it up too high!
- Just throw it midway into the air.
Crouch down a bit.
Okay.
[Frightening group of female students are
nagging the ever invincible Mr. Capable.]
Kim Jong Kook!
[Did he catch it?]
[No, he fails to catch it.]
[Drops the balloon from the back.]
[Two attempts are already wasted.
Must succeed the rest of the three chances.]
[Ha Ha steps out to scold him as
a representative for the whole team.]
Get back in there!
[I can't do it.]
Whatever!
Challenge!
[No, not even a chance...]
[Red Team gains their first point
without even having lifted a finger.]
How could you not have gotten
a single one?
[Blue Team fails to gain their point,
and even loses Kkuk from their team...]
I'm going to do it myself!
I'm going to get rid of Gook Joo!
[MC Kkuk will carry on the show-
Time for the second round.]
Instead of doing the Ring Around the Rosy,
I'll just play a song while you wait.
[It's freestyle dance time
until the whistle is blown.]
You can step out the door
once the music stops playing.
[What's that expression on his face?]
Okay, I will announce your next job.
[Fei succeeds her job.
Current score- 1:1.]
Next game is, 'Stick the watermelon seed.'
[Stick the watermelon seed.]
I'm really good at this game.
There will be 30 seconds on the clock.
You have to stick five watermelon seeds
on your face within those 30 seconds.
This game may be to Gook Joo's advantage.
[Why does Ha Ha look so anxious?]
Ha Ha just told me that he has to poop.
What are we going to do?
I don't want to concede to him
because I really want some watermelon.
- He just told me that he has to poop.
- Why would you tell her that?
I just whispered to her and
asked if she could let me out.
[He seems to have asked Gook Joo to let him
leave so that he could go to the bathroom.]
Excuse me, can someone
get us a diaper?
I don't know if he'll make it,
so can someone get us a diaper?
[With the watermelon challenge on the line...
Start the music!]
[Wait, this song is...]
['Dash' by Baek Ji Young.]
[The original singer of this song is
excited to dance along to her own song.]
[Make way...]
[A halfhearted dance.]
[In the midst of the chaos...
the whistle blows!]
I have to get out of here!
I really have to get out of here!
[I have to get out of here!]
[Haroro- A man who really needs to get out.]
[Ji Young has made Gook Joo
her own personal mark.]
I'm a man with a mission!
[In the midst of all this desperate chaos...
Gook Joo makes her move.]
[She's on the move!]
[I will get out of here!
I will get to my watermelon!]
[Gook Joo makes her touchdown!]
[Gook Joo's determined focus on the watermelon
which no one could keep her away from.]
You ultimately made it out here.
She's freakishly strong.
Even though she's a member
of my opposing team
I will still judge
her performance very fairly.
Just swallow all the seeds
along with the watermelon.
- I'll just chomp it all down.
- Get ready!
- Yes, I will judge it very fairly.
- How many seconds on the clock?
How many seconds?
How many seconds on the clock?
- How many seconds? 30 seconds, right?
- Who just asked that question?
Who's voice was that?
Who just asked that question?
- That voice was just ear shattering.
- All my team members were one time partiers.
You know how Jin Young started off
all cute and soft spoken earlier?
But look at her now.
Gook Joo, just swallow down
the seeds too!
Why are you crouching down so
demurely all of a sudden now?
[There's only one person who doesn't seem to
find any of this funny at the moment.]
[Please make it quick.]
I really am sorry, Ha Ha. But I
was so thirsty that I had no choice.
[Aside from the desire to win the game,
quenching her thirst is her top priority.]
- Gook Joo, you have to win this.
- I'm just so thirsty. Don't come any closer.
You have to spit it out and
make it stick.
You can't spit out food.
You'd be punished for being so wasteful.
Slurp down all the watermelon seeds!
I'm just going to slurp it all down!
- We shouldn't have let her out.
- Are you ready?
The watermelon looks so good.
Okay, get ready...
[Watermelon seed challenge- Go!]
- Spit out the seeds.
- Just swallow it.
Don't worry about the seeds
and just eat.
Gook Joo, just eat.
- She's only eating the seeds.
- She's getting all the seeds.
[Now that she's gotten her fill,
she focuses on the mission at hand.]
I swallowed all the seeds.
Why would you swallow the seeds?
What are you doing?
Gook Joo is still eating.
Only ten seconds left on the clock.
[Ten seconds left on the clock.
Must start spitting out the seeds!]
[But no seeds, and only watermelon...]
[Time over- mission fail.]
I have one right here.
[No, it's all watermelon.]
[Blue Team gains a point with
Gook Joo's failure. Blue Team 2: Red Team 1.]
[Just then, Jin Young flies in from out of
nowhere to steal some of the watermelon.]
[Throws her on the ground?]
[You dare lay a hand on my watermelon?]
All the women on the show today are weird.
They're not how you're led to think they are.
Let's just do this!
It's hot in here, so let's just do this.
- See?
- She says it's hot in there.
[The oldest girl of the bunch
doesn't like things to be dragged out.]
- Seriously.
- Being hot can make you feel annoyed.
Ji Hyo's the calmest one in there.
- Ji Hyo's a total sweetie in there.
- She's like an angel in here.
- Save some for us.
- Then you'd better hurry up.
- Okay, let's all get back inside.
- Let's get this started again.
- Let's get this going.
- I think we need to speed this along.
Okay, here's the next job category.
The next part-time job is...
a gourd breaker.
- Gourd breaker?
- Breaking the gourd on your head?
- Gourd breaker? I'm good at that game.
- Smash the gourd on your head
and break it in one single attempt.
[Break three gourds in a row on your head.]
- I'll go for this one.
- Okay, you go for this one.
[The Red Team puts their faith in Jae Suk...]
[Blue Team will be led by Haroro
due to the current state that he's in.]
- Get ready!
- Okay!
Go!
[Music starts again.]
[Battery of love- Hong Jin Young.]
[He really is so ugly.]
[It's not time yet...]
[Hands the mic over to the watermelon eater.]
[Gook Joo gets into the music.]
[You can't get out of here that easily!]
[A cluster of chaos.]
[Doing everything they can to
deter their opponents from getting out.]
[Oh?]
[Isn't this the man with an urgent need?]
[Eyes for the right opening...]
[And jumps out of the melee.]
[The man with an urgent need's
desperate attempt to get out.]
What the heck was that!
Who was it that tried to pull
my pants down?
[We have no idea what you're
talking about...]
I have a reason for
needing to finish this game.
I vow to complete this mission
so that I can take care of my own needs.
The man with an urgent need
will make an attempt at this challenge.
[Man with an urgent need-
Gourd breaking challenge.]
Break all the easy ones first!
- Okay, let's get ready.
- Whose voice is that?
- Her voice is so weird!
- Your voice is distracting to the show.
[A middle aged woman's voice?]
That's not the type of voice that
a popular singer should have.
Look at Hong Jin Young's stance.
- What about it?
- The girls on my team are all so weird!
- All the women on our team are a bit weird.
- Let's just do this!
Let's just do this!
[Please...]
- How do you think you'll do?
- Stop talking and just get it started.
Okay, let's just get started.
[Ha Ha's attempt to break
three gourds in a row.]
[With his teeth tightly gritted...]
[Off like a bullet to take care of his needs.]
Wow, that was just...
That was something else.
- I don't even know what to say to that.
- Just doing this hurts my head.
[These hard gourds have become
nothing but shards on the ground.]
[This is the power of what
an urgent matter can do.]
The next job category
is a very entertaining one.
- We need to get out there.
- Your next job category is...
It's a female arm wrestling match.
I'm really awful at arm wrestling.
[Music is back on!]
[This song is our very own MC Kkuk's song!]
['How lovely' by Kim Jong Kook.]
Why do you keep playing all
the old songs?
[Everyone seems to be having fun!]
[But he still sings along.]
[This lady is getting her groove on
after her watermelon snack.]
[Dancing queen from the 90's
is totally getting into it.]
[Even Yoo Hyuk, the complainer,
is having a great time.]
I don't want to stop singing the song.
[Representative for the Red Team-
Top model, Seung Hyun.]
[Red Team seemed confident
about this challenge...]
[But the Blue Team, on the other hand,
is forcefully dragged out of the bungalow.]
[Jin Young attempts to go out,
and Ji Young tries to stay in.]
[In the midst of all this chaos,
down they come.]
[What a sight...]
[Sporting orange underwear...]
You're about to scalp me right now.
[What a mouth on the woman!]
She just said,
'You're about to scalp me right now!'
Okay, Jin Young is out.
She's our contender for the Blue Team.
[Just as the Blue Team had wanted,
Jin Young makes it out as the contender.]
[Just then...]
I feel so much better now.
What a great day this is!
- Are you alright?
- All's right in the world.
- Have fun with the game.
- You did a great job earlier.
That was nothing. You must
be getting ready to arm wrestle?
Have you ever arm wrestled before?
- Yes, I've arm wrestled before.
- You have?
- She says she's good at everything.
- Really?
- She says she really is good at it.
- Beat her, Jin Young!
You'll be wrestling with your right hand,
and grab onto the handle with your left.
Yes, grab onto your handle.
Yes, there you go.
Look at how she's standing.
Look at how Jin Young
has her legs spread open.
- She knows what she's doing.
- She looks pretty strong.
- She must have very strong legs.
- You look very arrogant from the back.
Okay, here we go.
Relax your hands.
[If Jin Young wins this game, then
the Blue Team might win the mission.]
Ready!
Get ready...
[Come and get me.]
[Go easy on me, Jin Young.]
[Very confident Jin Young...
could this be the end for her?]
[Unbelievable!
Seung Hyun wins!]
[A hero for the Red Team!
Seung Hyun!]
Don't mess with me.
[You just wait and see.]
Not many players left.
Two members left on the Blue Team?
What the heck?
Gary and I are the only ones left?
- Unbelievable.
- The score is now 3:2.
- We need to get two more points.
- Your next job category is...
Gulp down a bottle of cola in one shot.
[Gulp down a bottle of cola in one shot.]
[This is Kwang Soo's specialty.]
You must gulp down this bottle of cola in
one shot within 15 seconds.
[Gulp it down within 15 seconds,
and abstain from burping for five seconds.]
I can't drink any carbonated drinks.
Ready, set, go!
[Time for another dance session.]
[Ji Young's 'My sweet candy.']
Play some recent songs!
[This old man keeps asking for some
more of the recent songs to be played.]
[The knee kick dance.]
[The spectators are also
getting into the groove.]
[Ha-Gook's candy dance.]
These guys are much more entertaining!
[Ha-Gook couple is the spotlight of the show.]
[Even the original singer of the song
is impressed by their performance.]
We can't let them show us up like that.
[Upset at having their spotlight
stolen from them.]
[Like this?]
[Ha-Gook candy.]
[Just then...]
What are you doing, Ji Young?
[Kwang Soo attempts to leave
to take on the cola challenge.]
[But he's stopped by Ji Young's
forceful defensive move.]
Why are you doing this?
[Gary uses this chance to
push Jae Suk out the door.]
[In the midst of all this chaos,
Jae Suk is shoved out the door.]
[Flame-broiled Grasshopper.]
Welcome, welcome.
- Why didn't you make it out there?
- You were supposed to do this one!
- We're glad to have you out here, Jae Suk.
- It could've been really big trouble.
[Ji Young looks beyond excited from
having screwed Kwang Soo over.]
That's why I told you to get
Ji Young out the door earlier.
[No matter what the case, it's now
up to Jae Suk to take on the task.]
The most important thing to note
is that the cola is very warm right now.
[Cola is now very warm
from having been out in the sun.]
- This needs to be cold.
- Yes, that's how it should be.
- I bet that will taste very sweet.
- Here's a cold bottle right here.
[Cold 500 ml bottle vs warm 350 ml bottle-
The choice is up to Jae Suk to make.]
Go for the cold bottle.
[Tempted by the devil- The feel
of the ice cold bottle on his neck.]
- Cold one will sting more.
- Your body's needs don't matter.
[But the undeniable draw of
the ice cold bottle.]
- Go for the cold one!
- This cola is like a femme fatale.
[Deadly bottle of femme fatale.]
- Go for the cold one!
- 350ml!
Go for the cold one!
Cold drinks are better in the heat!
[Will it be the cold bottle of 500ml,
or the warm bottle of 350ml?]
[That is the real question.]
Okay, I'll go with the cold bottle!
- Cola needs to be cold.
- Yes, that's right!
[Femme fatale tempts Jae Suk into
falling for its devilish draw.]
[Ends up choosing a bottle that's
150ml more in volume.]
Start the countdown from opening
the bottle.
- What's wrong with that lady?
- Just get this lady out of here.
No, that's a very good point.
[The ever entertaining voice show.]
Are you ready?
You only have 15 seconds,
and you can't stop at all.
You can't spill any either,
and should drink before it gets warm.
[Wait five seconds after downing
the whole bottle within 15 seconds.]
[Makes your own throat burn in pain
just from looking at what he's doing.]
He's almost done with it.
[The amount of cola
is very clearly diminishing.]
[He succeeds in finishing
the bottle within 15 seconds.]
[Now must hold off from burping
for five full seconds.]
[A satisfying burping ceremony.]
You definitely know how to eat!
You succeeded with the time
of 14.78 seconds.
[With Jae Suk's success,
the score is now tied at 3:3.]
[Only two more points left to score
by either one of the teams.]
We will play the last game for two points.
For the Read Team, we still have
Ji Suk Jin, Blank Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo.
For the Blue Team,
we still have Gary and Ji Young left.
Since this last game is worth two points,
we'll have a special competition mission.
It's a competition mission,
which means only one player per team.
For the mission...
Split the apple in half with your
bare hands.
- Ji Young!
As you may have already guessed,
both players will do it on the count of three.
The first person who can break it
in half will win the game.
You need to have skills for this,
and Gary will be good at it.
- I don't know who can do it on our team.
- Ji Hyo will probably be the best bet.
[These two men are less trustworthy
than Blank Ji.]
Okay, here comes the music.
Play the music!
[Cue the final song!]
[Sad Salsa- Baek Ji Young.]
[Hair pulling same aged friends.]
[Fancy footwork!]
Gook Joo has nice footwork.
I lost 8kg by dancing.
[Fei's engine gets started.]
[Dancing mania, Yoo Hyuk, gets
the honor of being her dance partner.]
Just hold still, Jae Suk!
[Shakes in unison.]
Why don't you all come out for
a little dance break?
[Games all having been forgotten,
the day turns into a sudden dance party.]
[Amusement Park Dance Club opens.]
[Hot dance time.]
[The original dancing queen
takes over the dance floor.]
[Heavy head banging dance.]
[Next dancer...]
[Unexpected dance skills!]
[Dance king, Mr. Gary,
is now a fan of Gook Joo's dancing.]
[Top model Seung Hyun's turn.]
[This is also totally unexpected.]
Let's dance with our friend, Se Young.
[Seung Hyun's long time best friend,
Se Young PD is invited to join their dance.]
Are you just going to sit there as
your friend is humiliating herself out there?
DJ Yoo Hyuk is in the groove
and pulls other onto the dance floor.
[The PD doesn't even have her shoes on.]
[Okay, whatever!]
It's a party!
[Party chaos!]
- What about the game?
- Let's just do the game!
You guys are all so weird!
Call the police!
Okay, that's enough.
I finished wiping down the table.
Come on, let's play the game.
Want to switch?
- Switch what?
- Switch the music and dance again.
Please, that's enough!
One more time?
Don't you want to dance some more?
Ever since that impromptu dance party,
Gary won't leave me alone now.
- Look at him.
- I didn't know it would be like this either.
- Are you the new Monday Couple?
- Maybe he really is attracted to her.
- This is no joke.
- But Ji Young looks really annoyed.
She looks annoyed because
she wants to party some more.
- She does look annoyed.
- Should we go home with all these girls?
[Gook Joo is trying to gauge
Ji Young's mood.]
Just let me know whenever
you're ready to go.
You girls just stay still.
Ji Young says that she's tired.
- And what's this guy's deal?
- Gary is still sitting next to her.
[I like you.]
One final two point game, right?
[One last final showdown with
two points for the win on the line.]
- Man against man.
- Ji Suk Jin and Gary!
[Split the apple open in half with bare hands-
Red Team's Red Nose vs Blue Team's Gary.]
- Ready!
- Let me wipe my hands first.
[The game with the winner
of the first game on the line.]
Fighting, Gary!
- Fighting, Suk Jin!
- Fighting!
[Which team has the better cheerleaders?
Time to start the game!]
[Just who will win the game?]
[Oh my goodness!
Completely unexpected!]
[Big-nose wins the game!]
[Celebratory dance time.]
[Apple love shot.]
[Final score- 3:5.
Red Team wins!]
It's time for your prize.
There are seven cake boxes in front of you.
Five of the most popular items of what
all college students wants are in the boxes
- but two boxes are duds.
- Good! That's so great.
The winner team will come forward and
choose five out of the seven boxes.
The loser team will get to choose
one of the two leftover boxes.
[Blue Team only gets to choose
one of the two leftovers.]
[Red Team's carefully makes their selection.]
You can't change your mind
once you choose.
Okay, Kwang Soo will start.
One, two, three.
[First selection- A bike.
Good selection.]
[A real bike awaits for the winner
in the final location.]
[Second box- Digital camera.]
- Are they really getting that?
- These are real nice cameras.
Okay, Blank Ji.
On the count of three.
[Third box- A dud.]
[One of the two duds are chosen.]
Gook Joo, on the count of three.
[Fourth box- A pair of headphones.]
Okay, Seung Hyun is up next.
[Last box- A box of ramen.]
[Wait, that's...]
[Gook Joo can't believe what
she's seeing.]
- Let's swap places.
- She likes the ramen better.
[Headphones and ramen.
Swaps out her spot with Seung Hyun.]
- No, you pick.
- Have Ji Young pick.
[Blue Team's turn to pick.]
One is a dud, and I'll
tell you what the other prize is.
- What is it?
- It's a laptop computer.
[One is a dud, and the other is a laptop.]
[Two completely different outcomes.]
It's okay, Ji Young.
Fighting!
[Ji Young seems to have had
made up her mind.]
- Oh my God.
- Come on, Mrs. Baek.
[Blue Teams wins the laptop
with their one and only chance.]
The Blue Team won the laptop computer
and the Red Team won the bicycle, digital camera,
headphones and the box of ramen.
We still took the biggest prize
even after having lost the game.
- Gook Joo, ramen or the laptop?
- Ramen!
Slurp down all the ramen!
- Is everyone hungry?
- Yes!
- We'll move onto our next location.
- Okay, let's go!
[Off to their next job location
to help satisfy their hunger.]
I can have my ramen even
without kimchi.
You know that song?
I thought that Seung Hyun
would be the better dancer
but it was Gook Joo who was
the better and sexier dancer.
I thought Seung Hyun would be a sexy dancer,
but she was a horrible dancer instead.
It's been about 28 years since I've seen
a woman dance the crab dance like she did.
Gook Joo was a really great dancer.
I used to be a better dancer, but
became clumsy as I gained more weight.
I used to be so swift on my feet.
I realized it once again today,
but Ji Hyo really isn't all that tough.
[Ji Hyo isn't all that tough- Showing
off a much gentler side to her today.]
- I'm a very sweet person, Jae Suk.
- I was so shocked, Ji Hyo.
- Jin Young and Ji Young though...
- They're both something else.
[Jin Young and Ji Young...
Frightening Young Sisters.]
[What about me?]
- What are you craving the most?
- Me?
I want a really cold bowl of noodles.
Bean noodles.
- I like it sweet with some sugar in it.
- You can't do that! You need salt!
- We use sugar in Jeollado.
- No, you need to be using salt.
[Is it salt or the sugar?]
Sugar is so good in it.
My blood sugar level is really low.
[Students arrive at their next job location.]
I bet the ribs here are really amazing.
Let's work hard so we get to eat it too.
[What kind of a job will they be doing
at this rib restaurant?]
Your next job has been especially prepared for
all of you whom I know are hot and hungry.
It's everyone's beloved rib restaurant.
- Part-time meat job.
- I'll show you how much I can slurp it down.
[One of their job locations-
A barbeque restaurant!]
Only one representative from
each team will play the game.
Do you see the five metal pots
on the tables in front of you?
The two players will take turns
lifting up the lids from the pots.
But if you choose a bad pot lid
where only the handle is lifted up
then a member of that team will get soaked
by the water dumper staged in the back.
And that person will be ousted.
Then the person who made the bad choice
will be swapped out for a new player.
[Can choose the order of the player themselves
and keep playing until a member is ousted.]
I think Ji Young has the magic touch today.
[Ji Young with the lucky touch of the laptop
is chosen to represent her team.]
Sine Ji Young is stepping up,
our Miss Blank will represent our team.
- She's so lucky with things like this.
- Ji Hyo's always good at things like this.
[Round one- Baek Ji Young vs Song Ji Hyo.]
- But I picked a dud earlier.
- No, that was just a fluke.
- You can do this. Fighting.
- We now have to pick the other person?
We're going to pick Suk Jin to go first.
[Chooses Suk Jin to stand under
the water dumper without even a hesitation.]
- Why don't you go stand back there?
- Okay.
[Water dumper-
Hong Jin Young vs Ji Suk Jin.]
[If their teammate selects
the defective pot lid...]
[Then it's an immediate cold shower.]
You can decide amongst yourselves
as to who's going to go first.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Ji Hyo wins-
Ji Hyo gets to make the first selection.]
- Fighting!
- Our newest sweet and gentle girl!
- You're an angel!
- You're a sweet and gentle girl!
Challenge!
[One of the five lids is a defective one.]
[Success- A perfect lid.]
- It's okay.
- You're going to get soaked!
It's okay, don't worry.
You can do it.
[Baek Ji Young's turn.]
- Challenge!
- She's got the feel for it.
[Success- Ji Young also selects
a perfectly fine lid.]
[Now the risks are even higher!]
[Ji Hyo succeeds.]
[Blank Ji definitely is one lucky lady.]
You can do it, Ji Young.
- It's a fifty percent chance!
- I know you can do it!
[One of the two is defective...
and one of the two will get soaked.]
Ji Young will make her selection first,
and Ji Hyo will get the other one.
You can't touch it yet.
Okay, lift it up on the count of three.
One of you two will definitely get soaked.
One...
One.
Two!
[Who will the lady of luck smile down upon?]
[Ji Young ends up with the defective lid.]
[A deluge of water dumps down on Jin Young.]
[What just happened?]
[A soaked dance time.]
[Blank Ji Hyo,
with the lady of luck on her side.]
No, it's okay.
[Jin Young is now soaked to the bone without
even having tasted any of the tasty rib meat.]
- Okay, Jong kook will go next.
- It's Jong Kook's turn next.
[Jong Kook of the Blue Team will now
go stand under the water dumper.]
Since I went first earlier,
I'll let the other team go first this time.
Don't be like that and just go for it!
Challenge.
[Lady of luck... please smile down upon me.]
[Huh?]
[Seriously?]
[Baek Ji Young selects the defective lid.]
[Ji Young, new icon of misfortune.]
[Lucky lady, Blank Ji, wins twice in a row.]
I told you that I have rotten luck!
Ji Young is the best.
[The icon of misfortune is drawn to
all the defective lids on the table.]
Okay, Kang Gary will go up next.
[Gary is sent in to take the next shower.]
I'll just be prepared to get soaked.
Gary is already preparing his heart
for the deluge of cold water.
Even though he says he's tough,
he's a major pampered city boy.
Okay, let's go!
- Do it first.
- Okay, I'll go first.
[Blank Ji makes the first selection.]
- Just pick the one you like.
- This one!
Let's go home nice and dry.
- She really is amazing.
- Okay, I know which one.
[One of the four is defective.]
I feel so nervous!
[Ji Young also succeeds.]
She got it?
You're going to win.
You're too lucky to lose.
Challenge.
[Ji Hyo gives Big-nose a shower
by picking the defective lid.]
[Prepares himself for the deluge of water.]
[What? Where's the water?]
- I can't stand to watch anymore.
- Just put him out of his misery.
We have a slight malfunction,
so go stand under the other dumper.
[Moves over to the other dumper
to receive his water shower.]
Please.
What is this?
[It's just a regular shower for Big-nose.]
[Unlucky Big-nose employee...]
What the heck is this!
Why are you giving him a shower?
[Even a machine malfunction
is a cause for laughter.]
Okay, we'll switch.
I'll swap Kwang Soo out.
[Kwang Soo is swapped out for Ji Hyo.]
[Under the water dumper-
Ha Ha vs Kang Seung Hyun.]
Kwang Soo and I are awful
at things like this.
The Red Team is already looking deflated.
Now that he's in that seat, it's all over now.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Off to a good start!]
Challenge!
- Fighting.
- Her voice is already different.
[Oh my goodness!]
[Definitely the new icon of misfortune.]
[Goodbye, Ha Ha.]
[A frightening level of misfortune.]
[Even this unlucky man admits
to her misfortune.]
[The little kiddo explodes.]
[Then I'll go stand under the dumper...]
I don't think I can trust Kwang Soo.
- It's okay.
- I'll be fine.
Show us a wave if you get soaked.
Do you know the scene in that movie when
Ye Jin throws her head back as she gets wet?
[Sohn Ye Jin in Art of Seduction.]
[The sexy water shower scene.]
She truly is a goddess.
[This?]
[Toss of the hair and
extending out the leg is key.]
[Fails to imitate Sohn Ye Jin.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
Yes!
I'll go second!
- That's a very good plan, Kwang Soo.
- You've got luck on your side, Kwang Soo.
That's a very good plan.
[Selects a normal lid.]
- She's better than me.
- Don't even think about it, Kwang Soo.
[25% chance of choosing the defective lid.]
[Kwang Soo miraculously succeeds.]
It's okay.
Relax and just pick one.
- You'll be fine.
- They all look the same.
[An uneasy feeling...]
[Lucky Fei!]
[I'm so going to pick the defective one...]
Once he makes the selection,
you will both have to lift up the lid.
[Nervous Gook Joo can't do
anything else but laugh.]
- I'll go with this one.
- Okay.
Okay, you both have to lift it up
on the count of three.
[Lift it up simultaneously.]
One.
[Which of the two will end up getting soaked?]
I won't let you down, Gook Joo!
[Lady of luck, please smile down upon me...]
[Kwang Soo has the luck on his side!]
[The defective lid!]
[Ji Young immediately falls into
Sohn Ye Jin's pose.]
[A sexy new goddess at the rib restaurant.]
[Seaweed hair.]
[The ever still sexy Mrs. Baek.]
- Only one person left on the Blue Team.
- Yes.
Okay, here we go.
Choose the order by playing
rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I'll go second.
That's a good plan, Kwang Soo.
[Jin Young goes first.]
Just pick whichever one you want.
[Feeling the energy from each of the lids.]
[Hong Ji Young succeeds.]
- You have to be confident when you do it.
- You look pretty with the reflected light.
[Like this?]
- Do you like her or something?
- She is my ideal type.
- Who is? Jin Young?
- Yes, I like her style.
Wait, then we're going to
have to do this.
[MC Love-Line makes a quick appearance.]
- So this is what you've been waiting for?
- No, Jae Suk.
Seriously, you should've told me sooner.
We're going to do this seriously.
- Kwang Soo likes cute girls like Jin Young.
- Yes, he really does.
- I know that much about Kwang Soo.
- I'm so weak at things like this.
We won't end here, but you can exchange
your numbers right here and right now.
[Agreement to exchange
personal phone numbers.]
Let's not waste any time here.
- This isn't just for fun right now.
- We have to get your mothers to meet.
Look at how it's done.
Gary and Ji Young will give a demonstration.
[Look at each other if there's mutual liking,
or look away if there isn't.]
Three.
This is how you do it.
[If you don't like the other person,
then completely disregard the person.]
This is how you do it.
- May I ask how old you are?
- We're the same age.
[Both born in '85.]
One, two...
Three.
[Disregards her?]
Fine, let's just be friends.
You totally made me feel bad!
I would normally let this go,
but can't let it go this time.
[But how can they let this one go
when she just got dissed by Giraffe?]
No, that wasn't what I meant.
I just meant that we could be friends.
- Hey!
- Stop hanging all over me.
She's the obsessive type,
and I'd get sick of that.
I have never seen anyone
get dumped by Kwang Soo before.
- Come on, Jin Young.
- I'm so embarrassed right now.
Did you hear what she said earlier?
She says, 'Fine, let's just be friends!'
[Haroro is having too much fun
teasing her while she's down.]
Ready.
- You'll get punished for this.
- No, I won't. Challenge!
[Will Giraffe pick
the defective one this time?]
Yes, go for that one.
[If they win this round,
then the Red Team wins the game.]
Just go with the one you feel
good about.
[There's his punishment.]
[That was a lot of water.]
[A very forceful impact.]
What was that? Why did
you have to dump so much water?
[It was the same amount of water,
but a different effect on Gook Joo.]
- I'm sorry, Gook Joo.
- The force totally knocked your head back.
Gook Joo, are you okay?
[Interviews the victim of the water splash.]
- You think that was funny?
- Look at her face!
Is it funny to totally make
a joke out of a woman like this?
I bet this restaurant is making
a lot of money from all this.
How much water did you just
dump on her?
I like a lot of water.
[Still able to maintain her humor
even after all that.]
Wow, that was amazing.
No, that was fun.
I enjoyed that.
- Get her another towel.
- I hope you all enjoyed that.
[People still left remaining are-
Blue Team 1 vs Red Team 2.]
- We're all friends here.
- This could be the final round.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I'll go second.
[Giraffe still sticks to his original plan.]
- You'll be fine with Ji Hyo up there.
- Ji Hyo will give you her lucky energy.
Challenge.
[Easily succeeds her turn.]
[A celebratory ceremony.]
Let's go, Kwang Soo.
[Giraffe also picks a normal lid.]
It's all because of Ji Hyo's luck.
Okay, just pick one.
[Success!
Another lid dance.]
Okay, it's Kwang Soo's turn to choose.
[Only two lids to choose from.
It's a fifty-fifty chance.]
[A fifty-fifty chance of winning.
Will the Red Team win the game?]
[Last chance for this one unlucky man!]
[Kwang Soo's unbelievable turn!
Red Team wins!]
- Ji Hyo seriously has all the luck.
- This wasn't your luck, but it was Ji Hyo's.
- This was all Ji Hyo's luck.
- Seriously, Ji Hyo...
Red Teams wins the restaurant
mission as well.
[Red Team wins again
at the restaurant mission.]
Your prize for winning this game...
is the prize of a backpack trip that
all college students dream of.
[All college students' fantasy-
a backpack trip.]
[A total of two duds. Choose four of the six,
and the Blue Team will choose one of two.]
- What's in it?
- A car rental coupon!
[Seung Hyun chooses the rental car coupon.]
[Big-nose's selection is... a dud!]
We never told Suk Jin
that he could choose one.
Come on, Rambo!
Make your selection.
[Lucky shot for her prize.]
[Another dud!]
Plane tickets!
[The ever lucky Blank Ji!
This is just plain amazing!]
This is amazing.
Her luck is just unbelievable.
- We can't even get the zipper to work.
- Hope it's not anything good.
- A meal ticket.
- Ugh, I want that!
[Genuinely seems disappointed.]
- Want to swap it for the plane ticket?
- No, we'll swap Ji Suk Jin for it.
No, thank you.
[Prizes won so far...]
[Off to the next location on the same bus.]
- But why are we taking the same bus?
- I like taking the same bus.
- Why?
- Why do you like it?
- Is it because of Kwang Soo?
- Come on, don't be like that.
[Could it be because of this one man?]
- Let's just clear this up right now.
- Tell them, Kwang Soo.
Your husband at SBS is Kwang Soo.
- But she really is my ideal personal type.
- You don't have to lie about that.
- Who wouldn't like Jin Young?
- Yes, that's very true.
Okay, then let's just play
the dating roulette.
- Okay, just go for it then.
- I'll even put Ji Young in there.
[Lee Kwang Soo's ideal type
dating roulette.]
- You have to say whatever comes to mind.
- Okay.
This is where we're going to determine it.
Song Ji Hyo and Baek Ji Young.
One, two, three.
- Baek Ji Young!
- Yes!
[Blank Ji is eliminated right off the bat.]
Saw that?
Even though Ji Hyo has absolutely
no interest in Kwang Soo
but I bet she's still feeling a little
disappointed by his selection.
Congratulations to Baek Ji Young,
and let's go on with the game.
Baek Ji Young is moved up on the list.
Okay, onto the next pairing.
We'll go with Fei.
- Don't be surprised, Fei. Okay?
- Okay.
[Miss A's resident entertainer, Fei vs
Worldwide top model, Kang Seung Hyun.]
Wait, wait!
I need a moment.
It's Fei against Seung Hyun.
One, two, three!
Seung Hyun!
- Why would you drop Fei?
- Don't ask him why.
- There's no reason to discuss his reasons.
- Why do you look so disappointed?
As you can plainly see,
these two women in this row over here...
You need to watch out for these two.
Okay, we'll go with Ms. Hong this time.
Jin Young vs Gook Joo.
Is it Gook Joo or Jin Young.
One, two, three!
- Is it Gook Joo or Jin Young?
- Gook Joo!
Gook Joo!
You get over here right now.
Do something with him!
He says he'll get sick of you,
so just sit back down in your seat.
- I didn't take you to be like this.
- No, you need to sit back down.
I'm really disappointed in you.
Jin Young is a bit of an obsessive type.
So I've beat an actress,
a singer, and a model?
You've already moved onto the semi-finals.
- You've moved up to the semi-finals.
- I don't think I'm going to lose.
It's Baek Ji Young vs Seung Hyun.
Ji Young or Seung Hyun?
One, two, three!
Seung Hyun!
[Mrs. Baek's one final word.]
You can just have him.
[Seung Hyun moves onto the final round.]
Let me remind everyone of who didn't
make the cut.
That would be Jin Young, Fei, Blank Ji Hyo
and even Ji Young now.
- What are you basing your decisions on?
- Don't ask him questions like that.
The only thing Kwang Soo is basing his
decisions on is that it isn't Jin Young.
How can you even say that?
- No, he didn't mean that. Sit down.
- Kwang Soo normally isn't so blunt about it.
It's now Seung Hyun vs Gook Joo.
Will it be Gook Joo or Seung Hyun?
[Final round of ideal type roulette.]
- One, two, three!
- Seung Hyun!
[Seung Hyun wins the roulette!]
- You were just using Gook Joo.
- No, I wasn't.
- How did I use her?
- You are an awful jerk!
I didn't use her.
[Sadly disappointed by his selection.]
- Swap seats with Gary.
- Why?
[Jin Young tries to seat Seung Hyun
next to Kwang Soo.]
That's not something for you
to worry about.
Don't worry about what Kwang Soo does.
Why are you girls fighting over me?
[Arrives at the next job location.]
What is this place?
[What kind of work awaits them here?]
This is an old school part-time job.
Newspaper delivery.
Like I told you earlier,
this is a newspaper delivery center.
You'll be playing newspaper basketball
with these bundles of newspaper.
[Basketball nets are brought out.]
- Wow, that's awesome.
- They're real basketball nets.
- They really bounce.
- Balls made out of newspapers.
This will be a bit different than
your regular basketball games.
I told you that this is
a mercy basketball game, right?
[Everything goes!]
You can lift up your teammates for the goal,
and basically anything goes in this game.
- Two points for dunk shots.
- We have Kwang Soo on our team.
[Kwang Soo's height will be to his advantage.]
[An easy dunk shot.]
- Since dunk shots are worth two points...
- We've got Kwang Soo and Seung Hyun.
We can lift her up together
and let her dunk it.
There's no need to do all that, Suk Jin.
With Kwang Soo on outside,
we're guaranteed to score some goals.
[Kwang Soo and Seung Hyun-
Their own goliath.]
[Plan is to have Kwang Soo lift Seung Hyun
on his shoulders for dunk shots.]
[Meanwhile, the men on the Blue Team
do some light warmup moves.]
[Every ball that they throw
makes it into the goal.]
[Those guys are no joke...]
Ready!
[Mercy newspaper basketball- Start.]
[A giant goliath is born
at the sound of the whistle.]
[How are we going to stop those giants?]
[Playing defense so that the goliath
can't get their hands on the ball.]
[Catches the ball!]
There you go.
Just keep going.
Get in there!
[The ball just floats midair
like a full moon.]
[Gook Joo bulldozer clears the path
for the Goliath.]
[Makes it to the goal net.]
[A successful dunk!]
[The Blue Team makes an offense move.]
[Kkuk makes a slam dunk.]
[Even though they might have the height,
Goliath is lacking in speed.]
[Speed isn't on their side.]
Go to the middle, Kwang Soo.
You don't have to dribble the ball.
Pass it to Gook Joo.
Pass the ball to Gook Joo.
[Nice pass, Kwang Soo!]
[Nice shot!
Makes the goal on a rebound.]
[Giraffe is pulling his weight
as the center player.]
You have to block their offense moves.
That's right.
Suk Jin can move off to the side.
[Tiny Haroro vs Giant Giraffe.]
[Evades his block... and misses the goal.]
[Kkuk misses the ball.]
You missed the ball!
[Embarrassed]
[Whenever something bad
happens to Kwang Soo...]
[Gook Joo runs over to his rescue.]
[Forceful removal.]
Run, Ji Hyo!
[Anyone who gets in Ace Ji Hyo's way...
Gook Joo will punish.]
[Gook Joo clears the path...
and Blank Ji scores the goal.]
[Blank Ji and Gook Joo-
A fantastic combo play.]
Stay right there, Gook Joo.
Don't move.
[Gook Joo's energy starts to deplete-
Must conserve her energy.]
- Get in there, Seung Hyun.
- Seriously!
Why is the net so low?
You can't have the net hanging so low.
Nice steal!
[Bravo, Giraffe!]
Give it to Jin Young.
[Midair blocking.]
Ugh, he's so annoying!
[Fairy Fei is brought in
to save the Blue Team.]
Gook Joo!
Run!
Out of my way!
Pass the ball to Kwang Soo!
- Please stop!
- Steal the ball!
This isn't basketball!
[What do you mean, how is this basketball?
It's mercy basketball.]
[Kkuk-Joo personally blocks Kkuk.]
How is this even basketball?
- Gook Joo won't even let me play!
- Gook Joo!
[The terror on the basketball court-
Kkuk Joo.]
[A pro stealer... and an amateur shooter.]
[Blue Team on the offense.]
[There's the long arm block again!]
[Nice defense!]
[Red Team is on the offense this time.]
[Gary's defensive move
might have ulterior motives.]
Seung Hyun!
What is this!
[Smacked down by Gook Joo...
and undressed by Fei.]
[Ha Ha takes advantage of his chance
and makes the goal with ease.]
Nice!
The score is now tied!
[The end of the first half.]
What the heck is this!
- Kwang Soo, are you okay?
- This is a total battlefield.
It's a complete battlefield.
- How is this even basketball?
- This is too much!
[Rest time on the bench.]
- That was a good game though.
- It's so hot out there.
They're so much faster than us.
Kwang Soo, are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not okay!
I didn't undress you on purpose.
- Who took your shirt off?
- Why are you doing this to me, Fei?
It's seriously so hot.
- It's unbelievably hot.
- What kind of a move was that earlier?
You can't make moves like that.
[They're all arguing with each other
on the dirty methods used during the game.]
You guys did a lot to us too!
Don't get discouraged when they score on us
and just start running to the other side.
[Game plan for the second half
is to keep running offensive plays.]
The girls can grab the ball and
stand in front of the goal.
Can you please take me out of the game?
- No, you're our most valuable player.
- Please, I don't think I can take it anymore.
[Game or not,
I need to survive the day first.]
Okay, let's get out there.
I don't think the ladies on our team will be
able to get any rest today.
You just have to keep running.
We have no other choice right now.
We will now start the second half.
Current score is tied at 4:4.
[Second half- Start.]
- Block her!
- Let's do this!
[A very rough start to the second half.]
[Ha Ha Iverson-
Scores a point with his impressive skills.]
- Dong Hoon!
- You're such a good basketball player.
[Sisters Blank Ji, Gook Joo, and Seung Hyun
advance with the ball hidden behind them.]
Where's the ball?
[Kkuk Joo takes charge of blocking Kkuk.]
[And Seung Hyun uses her chance
to score a point for their team.]
[Blue Teams' offense.]
[The moment the ball is grabbed,
then the person with the ball is attacked.]
[Sisters Blank Ji, Seung Hyun and Gook Joo
are on the offense again.]
Move, Jong Kook!
Gook Joo's making me so hot!
Go and score the goal.
[You are my destiny!]
[Score!]
You guys are doing great!
[Four points already!
Seung Hyun is a goal scoring machine!]
We have to save our Dong Hoon!
[Red Team has their Seung Hyun,
but the Blue Team has their Dong Hoon.]
Run!
[Give me the ball!]
- You have to stop her!
- No!
Do you want to die!
[These two are having a full out brawl
on the basketball court.]
[Two overly passionate and
fiery female students.]
Let's swap Gook Joo out for a minute.
Gook Joo needs to get some rest.
- Go get some rest, Gook Joo.
- Do you need to rest too, Jin Young?
[The two fiery players are
benched for some rest time.]
I think you may need to stop by
at the salon.
No, I'm fine.
- This is fun.
- Gook Joo.
This is fun.
[Even after all the tussle and fighting,
they're best friends in the end.]
Kang Gary keeps getting in my way!
Kwang Soo!
I love you, Lee Kwang Soo!
Boo, Kim Jong Kook!
Boo, Ha Ha!
[Screams out to whomever gets the ball.]
[The ball is back in Seung Hyun's hands.]
[Nice shot!]
[Five points scored in the game!
The reigned queen of mercy basketball!]
[While everyone's still focused on Seung Hyun,
Kkuk uses this chance to score two points.]
That was a dunk, right?
[Red Team's rebirth of the Goliath.]
[Blue Team is now aware of
the power of the Goliath.]
[Just then...]
[Big-nose makes an unbelievable pass.]
[And Jae Suk's breakthrough offensive play.]
[Air Grasshopper!]
[Yoo Hyuk evens out the score
with only 30 seconds left on the clock!]
[A very tight game!]
I'd like to swap Suk Jin out
and bring Gook Joo in.
[With only 20 seconds left on the clock,
Bulldozer is brought into the game.]
Gook Joo is mine.
[What are you talking about?
I belong to Kkuk.]
[Taking their position in front of the net.]
One more point, and we win.
[Catch the ball, Kwang Soo!]
[Yoo Hyuk's perfect ball pass.]
[Current score- 8:8.
One more point for the win.]
[The one who scores the next goal
will determine the victor.]
[Giraffe misses his crucial chance!]
[Blue Team moves into immediate offense.]
[Ha Ha's no look pass.]
[Slam dunk!]
[An NBA worthy combo play!]
[Final score- Blue Team wins!]
[Blue Team for the win.]
[If only I hadn't missed that goal...]
[Victory ceremony!]
[Why did I do that!]
There are six gift boxes on the table.
Four of the six boxes contains
money for your rent.
[Four of the six boxes contains money!]
Two boxes containing 500,000 won.
One box containing 300,000 won.
One box containing 100,000 won,
and the rest are duds.
Let's go for the 300,000 won.
Ji Young shouldn't even touch anything.
No, I'm not choosing anything.
That's the one I was going to go for.
- Seriously?
- I was seriously going to go for that one.
Once I put my hand on it,
I have to pick it?
This was Baek Ji Young's choice.
One, two, three.
[An empty envelope!]
[Icon of misfortune!
She picks a dud!]
[Congratulations]
I'll go next.
[Fei's selection.]
[Expectations are high!
A pretty thick envelope.]
This is no joke.
- Is it 500,000?
- I think we got 500,000 won.
[500,000 won for the rent!]
[Jin Young's selection.]
Our team is so awesome.
[Jin Young also selects the 500,000 won box.]
Let's just pick whichever for our last one.
[Gary makes the final selection for the team.]
[Another thick envelope!]
1,300,000 won!
[A total of 1.3 million won for the rent!]
Even though we won the first two rounds,
they got the laptop computer too.
How about we go with the opposite
of Kwang Soo's choosing?
[Icon of misfortune, Kwang Soo,
makes his selection.]
You can't get a dud.
We need something at least.
[A dud?
A very thin envelope.]
[Opposite of whatever Kwang Soo feels
is usually the way to go.]
- I told you to pick that one.
- I said we should go against his choice.
- We at least should've gotten 100,000 won.
- Kwang Soo really is so unlucky.
I'm so sorry!
[Apologizes to his teammates.]
[Arrives at the final location.]
What is this?
Is that a stage?
[What is their final mission to be?]
[A special stage under
all the glittery lights.]
[And a pole?]
All the prizes that you've won so far
are laid out on the table behind you.
[All their prizes!]
Let's take the money and go
out to dinner.
All the prizes that you've worked hard
to win today will be put on the line
for one final mission.
So the winner takes all?
Every member of the team will take a turn
to throw a ring onto the pole you see in front
and if you can get all six rings
on the pole, then you win the mission.
- We have to get all six rings around it?
- Oh my gosh!
- All of us?
- In a single try?
If even a single person fails,
then you can't take home the prize.
- Then we could lose everything?
- Yes, that's right.
- We can't take anything home?
- Look here, what do you think you're doing?
That's way too harsh.
So if neither one of our teams win,
then this is all just over?
- Yes, that's correct.
- What the heck is this!
[But win the mission,
and it's really time to celebrate!]
You can decide amongst yourselves
as to which team will get to go first.
[They're actually given a chance
to do a practice round.]
- It's not easy doing it with one hand.
- That wasn't bad.
[The ring toss is proving to be
much more difficult than it looks.]
[All six members of the team must succeed.]
We have to do it like this,
and toss it harder than I just did.
- That is much better.
- Then let's just throw it like that.
[Much more accurate
than tossing it with one hand.]
[Timing and the correct amount
of strength is key.]
[This mission requires a precise stance
and correct usage of their strength.]
[That's our Ace!
Gets it right on the first try!]
- What was that?
- That's a fail.
[If the ring bounces back out,
then it's a fail.]
[Practice time is over!]
This is now the real thing.
[With two wins under their belt,
Red Team is given a total of two chances.]
[But with only one win under their belt,
Blue Team only has one chance to succeed.]
You have to say, 'challenge' first.
[Lee Gook Joo to start the game.]
- Don't get too nervous about it, Gook Joo.
- Challenge.
[The pressure of being the first to go.]
[Will she be able to rise above
the pressure?]
[Lee Gook Joo succeeds!]
[Bulldozer, Lee Gook Joo!]
[Second player for the Red Team-
Kang Seung Hyun.]
If I can do it,
then the rest of you can do it.
[Kang Seung Hyun succeeds!]
[Red Team makes two goals in a row!]
[Third player for the Red Team-
Song Ji Hyo.]
Song Ji Hyo, fighting!
[Ace throws the ring!]
[Ace Ji Hyo fails!]
[Red Team has one more chance left.]
No, Gook Joo can go first.
[With the added pressure and nervousness,
the difficulty level is on the rise.]
[Red Team's second attempt.]
[First up- Yoo Jae Suk.]
[All the focus is on Yoo Hyuk.]
[I have to make this goal!]
[Yoo Hyuk succeeds!]
[Up next- Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Everyone watching
feels just as nervous.]
[Lee Kwang Soo succeeds.]
[Up next- Song Ji Hyo.]
- Song Ji Hyo, fighting!
- Challenge.
[There's no failing for the second time
for Ace Ji Hyo.]
[Ace Blank Ji succeeds!]
[Up next- Lee Gook Joo.]
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
No need to feel pressured.
[About ready to start crying
from the pressure of it all.]
Just think about your ramen.
[An unbelievable amount of pressure.]
She's so cute.
She really is so cute.
I want to carry her around in my pocket.
[That had better be one big pocket!]
[Will be she able to rise above
this unbelievable amount of pressure?]
[Lee Gook Joo fails.]
- I'm sorry.
- I feel as nervous as she does.
- No, it's alright.
- This is a lot of pressure.
- We have to be positive about this.
[Pressure is their biggest enemy.]
[They only have one chance to succeed!]
- Let's just do this.
- Challenge.
[First up- Kkuk.]
Just step forward and toss!
[Kkuk easily succeeds.]
Okay, challenge.
[Next up- Gary.]
- Okay, here I go.
- Take a slight step forward.
Just like this!
[Very easily succeeds in making the goal.]
[Blue Team is keeping their nervousness
at bay with all their cheers.]
[Next up- Fei.]
Think about having played this in China
when you were little.
[Tosses the ring without any hesitation.]
[Caught on the pole!]
[Hits the pole, but still makes it in!]
[Up next- Baek Ji Young.]
You can do this, Ji Young!
[Baek Ji Young succeeds!]
[Only two more to go!]
You have to own this, Jin Young!
- You miss this, and it's all over.
- Don't put too much strength on the legs.
[Red Team freely rags on the Blue Team
since they've already lost their chance.]
One, two, three, challenge!
[Up next- Hong Jin Young.]
[No amount of pressure will be
able to stop me.]
[Hong Jin Young succeeds!]
[Only one person left!]
[The final player, Ha Ha.]
You can do this!
- You can do this!
- Think about your daughter!
[Bigger cheers and even more pressure.]
[Fighting!]
[A celebratory dance to help keep
the nervousness at bay.]
I can do this!
I'll going to make this in!
[Final challenge of today's race.]
[The fate of the day's race
all rides on this one final toss.]
[Will it make it in?]
[Please...]
[Success!]
[Everyone on the Blue Team succeeds!]
[Blue Team is the final winner!]
[An enthusiastic victory ceremony!]
[Blue Team gets to take home all the prizes.]
- I hope that you'll come back on the show.
- Can we all come back on the same team?
- Let's have another rematch.
- I'm sorry, but this is too hard for me.
We will be back again next week
to run for our viewers!
- Yes, that's right!
- Thank you everyone!
Subtitles by DramaFever
The freedom of early morning
when no one else is awake yet.
[Beautiful man, Joo Won.]
[Beautiful man wanna-be,
Hong Suk Chun.]
[Making new memories with these two men...]
[But these won't be your average
memories.]
[A challenge for this city dwellers-
A DIY cooking battle.]
[And the panel of judges.]
[Next week's Running Man-
DIY Cooking Battle.]