Subtitles by DramaFever
[With all the luck and concentration...]
[Bet everything on this one moment.]
[Their lives hangs on the fate
of this one Baduk table.]
[The one who controls the Baduk piece
will control the fate of victory.]
[Black and White-
The life of one game.]
[R Group office.]
[All the R Group employees are gathered
in the office early in the morning.]
[What do I need to do?]
Yes, President, I understand.
- Good morning.
- What is he doing?
We haven't seen you in so long!
[FD Dong Wan is their manager?]
He started working here after me,
but he's already the manager.
- Is everyone here?
- Yes, Sir.
Glad to see that everyone's here.
Can someone get me a cup of coffee?
- Me!
- I'll go get it for you.
Suk Jin, let me have that.
[Jae Suk is trying to steal
Big-nose's drink for the boss?]
[I was going to give this drink
to Manager Go...]
I'm a much better worker though.
- I have the upper hand here.
- Do you?
- You want your vacation, don't you?
- Yes, I do.
[Immediate submission when faced
with an opportunity for a vacation.]
- What did you do this past weekend, Ji Hyo?
- I slept in preparation for Monday.
Why did you sleep all weekend
in preparation for Monday?
In order to be at your best for work,
you have to get plenty of rest.
I've heard some rumors that you spent
your weekend with Kang Gary?
- With who?
- No, that's not true. I wasn't with Ji Hyo.
I was with another woman.
- So it wasn't Ji Hyo?
- I only see Ji Hyo on Mondays.
[Ji Hyo is only for Mondays.]
You guys are so carefree
like other Hollywood couples.
[This is Gary's Hollywood style.]
- Doesn't that constitute as cheating?
- Hello?
Yes, President!
Yes.
[Everyone freezes at the President's call.]
- Yes, I understand.
- You can be an actor.
His acting has gotten so much better.
- We just received an important assignment.
- What is it?
In celebration of our five year anniversary,
an alkkaggi match...
[Alkkaggi?]
We will be playing Big Seven,
Alkkaggi challenge.
So we're going to play an alkkaggi match?
- Like a ddakjji match?
- It'll be two against one.
- You'll even have a surprising guest.
- We're going to have a guest?
The problem is, we have a place
and the time already set
but we haven't been able
to get the guest yet.
- We have to get the guest?
- Yes.
So it is your duty to find the guest
whom you'd like to have on the show.
- Really?
- Is this for real?
You have to go and find your own guests.
The competition will take place at
SBS Headquarters ay 5pm tonight.
Suk Jin already used up all my friends.
[A fiery competition
over their list of clientele.]
That's why you should always be nice to
them and treat them with kindness.
You will each be given your own location,
so good luck finding your guests.
- First, here's one for Employee Yoo.
- Where am I going?
- He's going to CoKo Entertainment?
- That place is full of women!
[CoKo Entertainment]
[Kim Won Hyo]
[Kim Joo Hyun]
[Lee Gook Joo.
Yang Sang Gook.]
[An entertainment firm with the largest
roster of comedians in the nation.]
[Where over 40 of the most popular
comedians are signed on as clients.]
- That's a nice place.
- This is my company!
- No, you're with KBS!
You're doing a show with KBS, aren't you?
- SBS is my only company!
- SBS is the only company I work for!
SBS is the best!
[A Team of SBS news announcers.]
[The best of the best when it comes to
looks ad talents.]
There's a huge list of female announcers.
[Out of consideration for
the old time bachelor, Kkuk.]
Big-nose, this is for you.
[Big-nose's location.]
Isn't that where Yong Hwa,
from CNBlue is signed?
[FNC Entertainment]
[An entertainment company with a variety of
singers, bands, TV actors, and movie actors.]
[A huge roster of actor and
singers on the list of clients.]
I have a feeling that this is the one.
I just have a feeling...
No Brain!
[Roxta Muzik]
[The company known for their
list of Indie Rock bands and musicians.]
[A place where three of the hottest
indie rock bands are signed on as clients.]
[Employee Kwang is headed to... JYP.]
[JYP Entertainment]
[The latest and the hottest
trends in music are made here.]
[If you want to become a star,
then start knocking on JYP's door.]
[Where will Employee Ha be heading to?]
[Seoul's very own SK Knights-
A professional basketball team.]
[With the legendary Coach Moon Kyung Eun!]
[The victors of 2012-2013 KBL Season!
A record breaking tie of 11 wins!]
[The best of the best in pro basketball.]
- I'm going to a modeling agency.
- What?
- Where are you going, Gary?
- I'm going to a modeling agency.
Don't be too happy about it.
They're all going to be taller than you are.
- Where are you going?
- Don't even bother celebrating.
[ESteem- Fashion Show Production
and Model Management.]
[An agency with the hottest fashion models.]
[The start and the end for all
the hottest models in the nation!]
- Let's go win!
- Let's win this one!
[Time to get to work.]
Don't forget to each take a box
of nourishing refreshments.
- Yes, thank you.
- Let's go!
[With a box of nourishing refreshments to
help convince their potential guests.]
[Time to get to work!]
Let me think about this.
Everyone at CoKo Entertainment
are my juniors.
Ji Min, Won Hyo... Joon Hyun,
and our recent guest, Gook Joo.
My position with those guys are
different than anyone else would be.
Going there is like a homecoming for me.
Alkkaggi game aside, there are people
who just have luck on their side.
My thought is to figure out who that may be
and recruit that person for my team.
First rule in business.
Smile and be kind.
As long as you smile
and treat them with kindness
then anything is possible.
Those models are usually
very strong spirited.
Even though I've strolled down
the runway myself a time or two
I really do like that about them.
Their strong and fiery spirit is what's
going to help us win in the alkkaggi match.
I need to make sure to win.
But I'm not very good at alkkaggi.
[Must recruit an alkkaggi pro
from SBS headquarters.]
Okay, basketball players.
Even though you may all laugh at this
becoming a basketball player
used to be my dream when I was little.
But I had to give up on that dream
when I couldn't grow any taller.
One of my favorites,
Iverson once made this statement...
'Basketball isn't played with height,
but it's played with your heart.'
Even though he made that statement,
he himself was over 180cm in height.
I think it's around here somewhere.
That's the building.
Wow, that's a huge office.
[A place of business where over 45 people
are signed on as their clients.]
[It's time for Employee Yoo to get to work.]
- It's very nice to meet you.
- Yes, you too.
I'm here on some official business.
Here's my business card.
[Employee Yoo's business skills-
Hand out the card after a polite greeting.]
Yes, the company was created today, but
today's our first and last day of business.
It's like a ghost company,
so please don't try that number.
But you can just keep it as a souvenir.
[Business skill number two-
Honesty is best policy.]
Won Hyo?
[Enter the office space with confidence.]
[Kim Won Hyo is discovered.]
[Even comedian Lee Kwang Sup
is bewildered to see Jae Suk.]
- What are you doing here?
- What are you doing?
[Business skill number three-
Make yourself at home at a friend's desk.]
- Is this a letter from your fan?
- It's from Min Sang.
- What are you doing here?
- I need to talk to you about something.
Wait, I want to talk to you too.
Is anyone else here?
- Tell us what you're doing here.
- I'm here for work.
I see there are more people in here.
Mr. Yang Sang Gook!
Hello!
No, you can lay back down.
There's no need to get up.
[Interrupts Yang Sang Gook's massage
to start chattering away to him.]
I need to talk to you too.
- You're a part of CoKo Entertainment, right?
- Yes.
[Business skill- Thorough background check
to know your clients.]
Can everyone please take a seat?
The reason why I'm here today...
it's because I'm facing
an alkkaggi challenge later on today.
[Alkkaggi?
That's what all this is about?]
[Seriously?]
Maybe I should give Ji Min a call.
- Why are you doing that?
- Just use one of us here!
- There's a gag concert rehearsal going on.
- Then what are you all doing here?
[Business skill-
Make your clients feel desperate.]
- You three are the only ones here right now?
- Are you not happy with us?
- No, it's not that.
- Stop beating around the bush and be honest.
- Just get to the point here.
- You guys are misunderstanding my point.
- Wait a second, you guys.
- Are you feeling flustered?
Wait, just take this.
[Flustered Employee Yoo hands out
his business card to the group.]
- Why did you give me two business cards?
- Wait!
I only need one,
but why did you give me two?
- He's trying to push himself on us.
- I'm not that type of a person!
Don't misunderstand my intentions.
- In case you don't have any work...
- I thought you were a good senior.
I'm not being picky with people,
so I don't want you to think that.
Where's Ji Min right now?
- I told you that he's at gag concert!
- Oh, I forgot you told me that.
Kwang Sup hasn't eaten yet, right?
Although I'm here on business...
Don't try to buy yourself more time by
feeding us so you can wait for more people.
- Just pick one of us now!
- Wow, you're really quick witted!
How did you know that was my plan?
I was debating whether I should
do the alkkaggi challenge or not
but I'm going to do it for sure.
- You've wounded my pride too much now.
- Don't you know me at all?
It took me years before I was able to
find my success too.
I can't stand it when people try to get
their job done through connections.
Where's Ji Min?
[While Employee Yoo's busy wrestling
with his people connections...]
[Employee Kkuk arrives at SBS Building
with the spirit of the Tiger.]
Is this my battleground for the day?
Isn't that Tuna?
Tuna!
[He runs into Sa Yeon at the front
of the SBS building!]
- It's so great running into you!
- I didn't even do my hair today!
Is something going on here today?
[A surprise visit even from former
R Group shareholder, Jung Chan Woo.]
- I'll see you later.
- Sun Hee's over there too!
[Running into so many familiar faces
even before he enters the building.]
It's around here somewhere.
There it is!
[Employee Gae arrives at ESteem office.]
Is that who I think it is?
[Discovers some models shopping
at the clothing store on the first floor.]
I should walk on my tippy toes.
I should just walk like this.
I'm an employee of Running Man's
R Group for the day.
[Employee Gae gets to work
on these two beauties.]
[Models, Jin Jung Sun and
Jung Ho Yeon.]
- You ladies are so beautiful.
- Thank you.
[Employee Gae's skills-
Be very complimentary.]
[Employee Giraffe arrives at
JYP Entertainment.]
So this is where it's at.
[Front of JYP Entertainment is always full of
fans waiting for a glimpse of a celebrity.]
[But they're not here to see you...]
[Wonder Girls, 2PM, Miss A, Sun Mi etc...
JYP is full of the hottest stars.]
I vow to succeed my mission!
[Employee Giraffe looks to be very nervous.]
Hello, Jia!
[Full of sexy charisma- Miss A's Jia.]
- I've been wanting to meet you.
- I'm a huge fan of yours.
Thank you so much.
[Jia reveals that she's a fan of
Employee Giraffe.]
Have you eaten yet?
I wish I had something to give you.
- You're a company employee?
- Yes, I'm an employee.
- So I'm here for work.
- Seriously?
Is that why you look so handsome today?
I don't think anyone's told me that
in over 20 years.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
[Ye Eun and Sun Mi, too!]
We're having an alkkaggi challenge today,
and I was hoping that you could help me.
Alkkaggi?
Are you really playing that game?
I'm not quite sure of it myself
since I didn't find anything out myself.
[Who cares about alkkaggi...
Just as long as you'll be with me.]
[This is my idea of heaven.]
[Employee Big-nose arrives
at FNC Entertainment.]
Hello, how are you?
[Big-nose's business skills-
Being polite is the way to go.]
[CNBlue's Lee Jung Shin!]
Hello!
Even though I may not be the best,
I always dream of being the best.
My name is Ji Suk Jin,
and it's nice to meet you.
I saw you on TV when you
were in New York.
You two are an item, aren't you?
[Jung Shin and So Young-
An item on the new drama, 'Temptation'.]
- I'm a company employee today.
- Seriously?
I know your name!
Wait, give me a minute.
I have to know all your names.
Your name is So Young!
I'm right, aren't I?
[A hot new star, Kim So Young.]
What are you doing here?
You gave me two business cards.
Here's a nutritional drink for you.
There's even a picture of me on it.
Our company, R Group,
is having an alkkaggi competition today.
[These two are taken aback by the
announcement of the alkkaggi competition]
- We have the alkkaggi competition.
- I see.
If you have the time...
Were you practicing your lines?
- Yes, we were.
- We have to get to the shoot in a few.
- You have to go too?
- Yes, we're filming today.
- Can you push it back?
- How about I...
Come with me for a minute.
[When things don't go his way,
he transforms into a pesky employee.]
- I'll introduce you to some other people.
- Really?
- There's Min Hyuk, and AOA members...
- Okay, let's go.
[CNBlue's Min Hyuk and AOA members
are also in the office.]
[While Big-nose greeds after his guests
at FNC Entertainment...]
[Employee Blank Ji is almost to
her destination at Roxta Muzik.]
I wonder where it could be.
[But the navigation system leads her
to a residential area?]
You're telling me that the rock stars
are in this residential area?
Seriously?
In this residential area?
[That's so strange...
But they're rock stars?]
[Shouldn't it be a building full of
screaming fan girls out front?]
[This peaceful residential area...
is where I can find my rock stars?]
[Welcome to Roxta Muzik.]
Kindness and smile.
[Employee Blank enters the building.]
[A bookshelf full of trophies for
the musicians signed on with their label.]
A building full of
these great musical artists.
[Heads up to the second floor
in search of her rock stars.]
Hello.
- Hello.
- Wow!
[Greeted with a loud cheer by
all the males.]
[Roxta family- No Brain, Janmi Yeogwan.]
Song Ji Hyo!
[Beautiful Employee Blank is met
with fervent enthusiasm.]
- I'll wait for you to finish eating first.
- Why don't you sit down and join us?
[The group of males are offering for
Blank Ji to join them for lunch.]
- You are so beautiful.
- Thank you.
[Yook Joong Wan of Jangmi Yeogwan
is full of compliments.]
- I'm here as an employee from my company.
- Is that for us?
Thank you so much.
[Joong Wan seems to be a quite
the fan of Employee Blank.]
- I need to take you back with me.
- What for?
There's a very important matter in which
I need some of you to help me with.
It's for the five year anniversary
for our show, Running Man.
We're having an alkkaggi competition.
[You're here for an alkkaggi competition?]
Wow, but she really is so very pretty.
[One hundred percent sincere!
Amazed by Employee Blank's beauty.]
I've never seen anyone so beautiful
as you before in my life.
You have to bet your band's honor on the line
and win the game as well as a prize.
This is a very crucial event.
Every one of us plays the guitar,
so we're very good at using our fingers.
[That's so true!]
Your guitar playing does make you more skilled
in the way you manipulate your fingers.
It's not just a play thing,
but it's almost scientific for you.
[While our anticipation for these guitarists
alkkaggi skills are on the rise...]
[While others are busy recruiting,
Employee Ha is still driving on the road.]
SK Knights professional basketball team!
[Finally arrives at the location.]
Can't you feel their energy?
Okay, let's put the nervous energy aside
and go into the building.
[Steps out of the car with his once dream of
being a basketball star in his heart.]
This is so great.
So this is the place.
[2012-2013 season's winning trophy.]
These are the handprints of
all the great players.
[A wall plaque of
all the players' handprints.]
His hand isn't that big.
His three point shooters
are like works of art.
[Heads toward the office with
excitement and anticipation.]
[The legendary Coach Moon Kyung Eun
is standing right in front of his eyes!]
[The pioneer of Korean basketball
with his explosive three point shooters.]
[The legendary Rambo shooter,
Moon Kyung Eun.]
I'm such a huge fan of yours,
and I greatly respect your work.
You're still pro ball player,
Moon Kyung Eun to me.
- Can I drink this?
- Yes, of course.
- You didn't put anything in here, did you?
- No, I didn't.
What would I have put in there?
I just put some of my love in there.
I really love you, Brother!
I was such a huge fan of yours!
[Back to CoKo Entertainment.]
I'm here to do my job, but I
feel like you're auditioning for me.
You guys are so forward.
Where's Joon Hyun?
I was just asking because I don't know
which one of you are good at alkkaggi.
The three of us are the best at that
of everyone here at CoKo.
We play alkkaggi all the time because
we don't have any other gigs to get to.
It's not like we're professionals
when it comes to alkkaggi either
and I'm sure that everyone else
is pretty much the same.
That's why your day to day
condition is most important.
So can I see how your luck is today?
Let's read up on our horoscope.
I'm the sign of the rat.
Luck is shining down on you today
and there's a good chance
to earn great fortune.
- Today's the day.
- See? Today's fortune looks great for me.
- Management of people is crucial.
- See? I knew it!
Don't be anxious at heart because
what you need the most is already beside you.
See? It says that what you need
is already right beside you.
What you need is already
right beside you...
But, this is what's important.
Here's the sign of the rat for 1972.
Someone in your surroundings may try to
entice you into an undesirable result.
[Someone in your surroundings may try to
entice you into an undesirable result.]
See?
It's written right here!
- But we're not trying to do any of the sort.
- Why don't we read our fortune?
Okay, let's read yours.
What year were you born?
I was born in '81.
Everything starts by being in isolation.
Then you should be in isolation today.
- What about you, Kwang Sup?
- I'm the sign of a monkey.
The sign of the monkey?
That's a good sign.
- Here it is?
- Really?
Listen to this carefully.
Harder and tougher things get,
don't try to face the challenges head on.
Instead, learn ways to
go around your challenges.
- This doesn't sound very good.
- Maybe you should go around this.
Even though this is just a mere baduk board
and baduk pieces that you're facing...
What you'll soon be joining me for in
Sangahmdong isn't just a mere alkkaggi game.
But we will be heading towards a dream...
towards a common goal...
But I am in search of a companion who will
help me bring home the dream and victory.
- A companion...
- Everyone, tell me where Ji Min is.
[Meanwhile, this building is filling up
with sounds of laughter and music.]
[Everyone's so full of cheer and excitement.]
[This impromptu concert's next song is...]
['You're just my style' by
Jangmi Yeogwan.]
[May I have this dance?]
I'm sorry, but you're not my style.
[Yes, I see...]
You're not my style.
[This rock star office is so full of
high spirited energy and excitement.]
[Time to choose the alkkaggi player.]
[Representative for Garlixx-
Jun Kyung Joon.]
[Very close to the finish line!]
[No Brain's Hwang Hyun Sung
is disqualified.]
Okay, let's go!
[Last but not least-
Jangmi Yeogwan's Yook Joong Wan!]
[Roxta Muzik's attic room
is overflowing with love and laughter.]
[Almost in the same line as
Garlixx's Kyung Joon's cap!]
[Time for some serious judging.]
I don't have a ruler,
but I do have a line we can use.
[That's the best he has?
A cord from a hairdryer?]
[First measures Jangmi Yeogwan
Joong Wan's distance.]
Okay.
[Compares that distance to that of
Kyung Joon's cap from Garlixx?]
[It's a bit further off!]
[Jangmi Yeogwan wins!]
Okay, we got it.
Joong Wan from Jangmi Yeogwan.
[Roxta Muzik's representative is,
Yook Joong Wan of Jangmi Yeogwan.]
Let's go.
[Blank Ji and Yook Joong Wan-
Team Roxta Muzik.]
[While Employee Blank is the first
to recruit her partner...]
Coach, I'm heading out.
[Yay, it's Haroro!]
[Employee Ha is in player Sims' uniform-
Like a kid wearing his daddy's clothing...]
[All the other players are bursting out in
laughter over Ha Ha's fashion statement.]
I'm looking for a volunteer
or an applicant.
A player who's willing to participate in
an alkkaggi competition with the honor
of SK Knights' name on the line
in a race for victory.
I would like to see who would
be interested in volunteering.
[SK Knights' forward position,
Choi Bu Kyung.]
Why don't you step forward too?
Your hands are so large.
I was only going to choose one player...
But I would like to nominate
Coach Moon Kyung Eun as well.
Let's give him a huge round of applause.
I have some say in this matter as well.
We're going to play a round of
free-throw game.
[A free-throw game where the penalty
is to get snapped in the forehead.]
[Coach Moon and the players to throw
3 pointers, and Ha Ha with the free throws.]
[Coach Moon makes his attempt
at his first three pointer.]
- How old are you?
- 25.
25?
I'm 36 years old.
I'm brother,
and you're my younger brother.
[Bragging about being older while
staring way up at him.]
[He shoots...]
[And scores!]
[Choi Bu Kyung shoots from the side.]
Yes, that's great.
[I think he's going to get
smacked on the forehead.]
[Kiddo Ha attempts to make
his free-throw shot.]
That's going in.
[It's going in?]
[So close!
It bounces off the rim!]
He's just like you, Jung Sung Ji.
Hold still.
[A forehead smack from his childhood hero.
A resounding smack of honor.]
Scratch under, okay?
His smack was harder
than I expected it would be.
[Much harder than expected!]
I'm sorry, but this is going to hurt a lot.
I'm afraid that your neck
might snap backwards.
Grab onto the back of my head
so that I don't run away.
Grab onto the back of my neck
because I may end up running away.
[The smacking sound is enough
to echo through the court.]
[Bu Kyung's unbelievable power.]
[With the power of those fingers...
let's rule the alkkaggi competition!]
[SK Knights' Choi Bu Kyung to
represent in the alkkaggi competition.]
[Ha Ha and Choi Bu Kyung-
Team SK Knights.]
[One by one, they're each recruiting
their own partners for the competition...]
Can you please help me?
[Employee Kwang has tracked down
Woo Young and Chan Sung of 2PM.]
We're going to play a game to determine
who will come with me to the competition.
[Playing the cola-cider game to
determine who will play in the competition.]
[Amazing!]
[Unbelievable!
Woo Young's pebble stops on the line!]
That was amazing, Woo Young.
- Woo Young, are you free today?
- I'll have to check.
[I'm just kidding.
Of course, I'll come.]
[Kwang Soo and Woo Young- Team JYP]
[It's getting closer to the deadline...]
[Employee Big-nose has yet to
recruit anyone as his partner.]
Please help me. I want to
be my company's best employee.
I want to become the best,
and I need AOA's help.
I want to become the best.
Thank you.
My name is Ji Suk Jin.
[CNBlue's Min Hyuk is also
a possible contestant.]
Kwang Soo wanted me to tell you
that he'd really love to meet you.
But I'm sorry that it's Kwang Soo.
- Are you free at all today?
- My schedule is open.
- Really?
- Yes, I don't have any other plans.
- Seriously? You can come with me?
- Yes, I can.
In that case, I will decide
whether it'll be Min Hyuk or Sul Hyun.
If it's Sul Hyun, then can it be of help
when you play against Kwang Soo?
Yes, that could be very possible.
- We should try for that.
- He's very cold when it comes to winning.
I have decided who will be joining me
for the R Group competition.
Contestant for alkkaggi competition
will be... Sul Hyun!
[Without a doubt, it's Sul Hyun of AOA.]
- Ugh, I'm just going to play ddakjji!
- Let's play a ddakjji competition together.
- Let's play together then.
- I have an audition to get to then.
[Big-nose and Sul Hyun of AOA-
Team FNC.]
[Employee Gary is also stepping up the game
at the modeling agency.]
[Playing a game of cham-cham-cham
to test their luck.]
[A round of pushups to test their endurance.]
[And 'push the cap' game to test
their alkkaggi skills.]
[Model Lee Hye Jung shows some
surprising skills.]
- Have you ever played alkkaggi before?
- Yes, when I was little.
With baduk pieces?
[Immediately wins at the game of thumb war.]
What kind of a mindset do you need
when you're modeling?
- You have to think that you're the best.
- Yes, that's how you need to think.
[Must tell yourself that you're the best
when you're modeling.]
[Top model, Lee Hye Jung-
Contestant for the alkkaggi competition.]
[Gary and Hye Jung- Team ESteem.]
[Employee Kkuk at SBS...]
[Marks Running Man's announcer, Kim Hwan,
as one of the possible contestants.]
I have to choose the best contestant
that I can find for the competition.
[Earn the approval from
the department chief first.]
- This is for the honor of SBS.
- All those guys are good.
[Polite Kkuk is first seeking the approval
from Team Leader Kim Tae Wook.]
This game will be played for
the honor of SBS announcer team.
Announcer Kim Hwan has always been
a great supporter of our show.
[Kim Hwan is recruited for always being
such a great supporter of the show.]
[Team Leader is gratefully adjusting the
schedule to accommodate Kkuk's recruitment.]
- Do you think he can actually do it?
- I will definitely give it my best.
Once he gets some practice,
he'll be very good at it.
- With him being so athletic already...
- You two look good standing together.
Thank you.
Then are you giving us your approval?
[The ultimate pairing
with the two workout maniacs.]
[Kkuk and Kim Hwan- Team SBS.]
We're in love with Song Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo, fighting!
- FNC, fighting!
- ESteem, fighting!
- SK Knights!
- Running Man, fighting!
[Time to head off to the final location!]
[But...]
How long is it going to take for me
to be able to recruit someone?
Why is this taking so long?
Let's just do it like this.
This is all about luck.
Since I can't really choose anyone,
let's let luck decide for us.
- This is the last time, right?
- Yes, let's make a promise to each other.
This is it.
- You just need to pick one.
- It doesn't matter if I go first, right?
[The person to choose the piece that's been
marked with the pen wins the draw.]
At the count of three, check
to see if you have the marked piece.
One, two, three.
[Won Hyo is chosen.]
Let's go.
[But Won Hyo was the worst during
their alkkaggi competition.]
Wow, he really is the worst.
You go, Won Hyo.
You're the most popular of all of us.
[That darned popularity issue!]
Okay, then let's all go.
Are we going to be on the show?
We want to be on the show.
Are you going to cheer him on,
or just to be on the show?
- I've never been on SBS before.
- Are you serious?
Then Won Hyo will be the contestant,
but you can come along too.
Okay, let's go.
[Won Hyo is ultimately chosen
to be the contestant in the competition.]
- We promised to be happy for each other.
- Be happy for him, will you?
[Fake and forced cheering.]
[Big 7 Alkkaggi Competition-
Player recruitment is now over.]
[It's now time to
head over to the competition!]
Before we head over to the competition,
order whatever you'd like to eat.
- Seriously? Whatever I'd like?
- Of course.
- You seem hesitant about that.
- No, not at all.
Order whatever you'd like to eat.
Won't the cost of this meal be
just a drop in the bucket if we win?
[In that case... Beef sirloin!]
No, it's okay.
[Off to SBS Sangahm building!]
[5pm- SBS Sangahm Prism Tower.]
Let's go!
- Won Hyo!
- Yes?
[Employees and their partners are
starting to gather at the final location.]
It's Joong Wan!
Look at the size of his hands!
[Big Seven Alkkaggi Competition-
40 minutes before the competition.]
[Each team enters their own waiting room.]
I'll show you, so watch closely.
- Should I beat you or not?
- No, don't do it.
- Should I really hit you or not.
- Don't hit me, but hit the piece.
I never knew that
he could be so focused like that.
No wonder he became an announcer
and had to quit playing sports.
He seriously is very impressive.
[Big-nose Brother wins seven times
in a row in practice alkkaggi game!]
[He already is the ddakji king,
and now the alkkaggi king, too?]
I really shouldn't play it like that.
I thought you were
making pancakes over there.
You can't over-think it.
Just go for it.
You have to do it like you do it every day.
Like it's no big deal, like this.
[Woo Young is practicing
shooting with his pinky.]
Do you just want to come back
when we do a ddakjji competition?
[Team practice time is now over.]
[It's finally time for the competition.]
[The arena is suddenly filled with
unexpected crowd of fans.]
[And the baduk board of destiny.]
[Team Roxta Muzik-
Song Ji Hyo and Yook Joong Wan.]
[An excited cheer from
his record label family.]
Yook Joong Wan!
Wow, that startled me!
[Team ESteem- Lee Hye Jung and Gary.]
[A team of ESteem models.]
[Team SBS- Kim Hwan and Kim Jong Kook.]
[Where am I going?]
[Come over here.]
[Team SK Knights-
Choi Bu Kyung and Ha Ha.]
[SK Knights' cheerleaders.]
[Team FNC- Suk Jin and AOA's Sul Hyun.]
[Team JYP-
2PM's Woo Young and Kwang Soo.]
- Awesome!
- You guys came!
[Sun Mi, Ye Eun and Jia came
to cheer Woo Young on.]
[Team CoKo-
Jae Suk and Kim Won Hyo.]
Yoo Jae Suk!
Why is it just the three of you?
You should've brought more people with you!
How can it just be the three of you?
- Couldn't you have brought more with you?
- The three of us are more than enough.
We weren't even going to come,
and we had to force ourselves to come.
- Seriously.
- Where's Ji Min?
Today is Running Man's first ever
alkkaggi competition.
To all seven guests who came to participate
in our first ever alkkaggi competition
and to everyone who came to cheer us on,
we'd like to sincerely thank you once again.
[A huge round of applause to all those
who came to cheer them on.]
Why is Team SBS' cheerleading team so small?
What do you mean, it's small?
This is a big group of people.
It's just that they're sitting in two rows,
but you only have one more than us.
- You act like you have quite a few.
- This is more than plenty enough for us!
- It's just the way we're sitting
- But this is completely different.
We all work in an office,
and they're probably still working.
We've prepared a small event for our fans
who came to cheer us on.
Wouldn't that make this competition
more fun?
[Gwak Dong Yeon of FNC.]
[Roxta Muzik-
Jangmi Yeogwan, No Brain, and Garlixx.]
The game you'll all be playing is,
guess the winning team.
[Cheerleading squad's event-
Guess the winning team.]
You have to guess
which team you think will win.
If you correctly end up guessing
who the winning team is
then those who guessed correctly
will be given a special prize.
[They're free to choose whichever team
they'd like to choose.]
[Name: Jun Kyung Joon.
Prediction- JYP's Kwang Soo and Woo Young.]
I chose these guys.
Kwang Soo is the best.
- You've all made your selection already?
- Yes.
- You've already cast your votes, correct?
- You already did it?
- Who did you vote for?
- Who's in the lead?
The team that's in the lead...
is leading with a total of six votes.
Six votes?
Which team is it?
[The leading team has a total of six votes.]
[CoKo Entertainment.]
Which means that three other people
voted for us!
Please note that we've had other people
vote for our team.
It's possible that six people from
other teams have voted for you.
No, it couldn't have been six people.
But the prediction can be
very different from the actual reality.
No one can guess just who will
come out the winner of this competition.
[Team Roxta Muzik moved up to
the playoff round through an earlier game.]
The goddess of alkkaggi will be joining us
to announce the game for us.
Please welcome announcer, Jang Ye Won!
[The goddess of alkkaggi, Jang Ye Won.]
[Enters the arena with a fervent
cheering from the male crowd.]
- Wow, Jang Ye Won is no joke.
- You're on our side, aren't you?
- She didn't hesitate to take his hand.
- Hello, my name is Jang Ye Won.
It's nice to meet all of you.
- Can you please tell us how old you are?
- I'm 25 years old.
- Jong Kook is eliminated!
- Why?
Kim Jong Kook is eliminated!
You're too old.
Without any regard to the age,
Yang Sang Kook is also eliminated!
[Yang Sang Kook is also eliminated
with no regards to his age.]
We will now get started with the first round.
Team CoKo and Team SK Knights!
[Big Seven's first round-
Team CoKo and Team SK Knights.]
We will now get started with the first round.
Jang Ye Eun will now commence
with the first round proceedings.
We will now get started with
the alkkaggi competition.
Please give a huge round of applause.
[Big Seven's first round-
Yoo Jae Suk vs Ha Ha.]
It's tough to predict who'll win just
by seeing how they start off the game.
Just take a look at how player Ha Ha
is lining up his pieces.
[Yoo Jae Suk's line formation
vs Ha Ha's 'W' formation.]
[A fierce mental game
is already in the works.]
The way I see it, one of the pieces
will be knocked out right away.
This will be a very fierce game
of alkkaggi.
They will each have five pieces.
Ha Ha will make the first move.
- This will be an interesting game.
- Yes, I agree.
Please commence the game.
[Start the competition.]
[The baduk board...]
[The unavoidable match...]
Fighting, Jae Suk!
You are all welcome to cheer for them.
[Yoo Hyuk starts off with a sliding move.]
He started off with a sliding move.
[Haroro responds with a scattering move.]
[Each showing off their own unique moves.]
Please watch carefully.
This is where it all starts.
Is he really going to attack?
[Yoo Hyuk's piece barely manages
to stop at the board's ledge.]
[Unbelievable!]
[Haroro's chance.]
[Just the slightest tap,
and Yoo Hyuk's piece is off the board.]
[Please...]
[Too strong- His own piece is eliminated.]
[CoKo Entertainment advances
without even lifting their finger.]
[Remaining number of pieces.
Jae Suk- Four vs Ha Ha- Four.]
Is that the best Ha Ha can do?
[Ha Ha's grave mistake.]
It's now back to Yoo Jae Suk.
[Lures Ha Ha by tapping the piece.]
- What's 'tapping'?
- Don't you know that move?
- How many different moves are there?
- There are a total of 240 moves.
[Ha Ha looks to be getting ready for
a forward attack move.]
You're making me nervous!
He doesn't seem to be too sure of himself.
- He's not playing around right now.
- He learned his moves in Germany.
[Ha Ha studied his moves in Germany?]
If he succeeds with his attack,
then it'll put him at an advantage.
He missed very slightly with his attack.
He should've been a bit more forceful.
[Jae Suk also assumes an attack position.]
Will Yoo Jae Suk be able to
succeed this time?
[A clean successful attack.]
This puts Yoo Jae Suk's team
at an advantage.
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Remaining number of pieces.
Jae Suk- Four vs Ha Ha- Three.]
- All the black pieces are in a group.
- Black pieces aren't in a good position.
White pieces are scattered about
which puts it in an advantage.
When the pieces are grouped together,
it makes it tough to attack as well.
[Two pieces at once!]
[Remaining number of pieces.
Jae Suk- Four vs Ha Ha- One.]
That move just put CoKo Entertainment
at a great advantage.
- But the outcome is still unknown.
- Fighting!
Ha Ha is still in the game.
He needs to knock this piece out.
[Succeeds the attack with a perfect aim.]
The outcome is still unknown.
[The game isn't over yet!]
[Remaining number of pieces.
Jae Suk- Three vs Ha Ha- One.]
But Ha Ha is still at a great disadvantage.
- This is extremely disadvantageous to Ha Ha.
- I agree.
This is similar to a game of soccer.
[No need to drag this out any further...]
[I'll finish it with this one move.]
Remember the game when the France scored
four goals in the second half of the match?
[Jae Suk succeeds his attack and wins.]
[Final score-
Jae Suk- Two vs Ha Ha- Zero.]
[CoKo Entertainment wins the first game.]
CoKo Entertainment wins the first round.
The first team to win two games
will move onto the next round.
[Big Seven Alkkaggi- Second game:
Kim Won Hyo vs Choi Bu Kyung.]
- That was really...
- Choi Bu Kyung, fighting!
No, cheer for Kim Won Hyo.
- Kim Won Hyo.
- We will now start the game.
What kind of a formation is this?
[Even the formation is taken
with a serious level of concentration.]
How about putting one of the pieces
up front to make the attack easier?
- What kind of a formation is this?
- I would've put a piece up front.
- It's too bad that they didn't do that.
- It's almost like a basketball positioning.
- You must not know much about basketball?
- That's correct, I don't know.
That's not what they do in basketball.
[Won Hyo's cautious tap.]
What is he doing?
What is that move?
[Huh?]
[What is this move?]
[What is this?]
[A forceful sweep move!]
[A forceful power befitting
that of the size of his hand.]
What was that move?
He only used one finger.
- Sure, we'll allow that.
- Formal name for that move, one hand sweep.
[I will sweep it all off the board.]
[The white piece is swept off the board
with one monstrous sweep.]
[An unbelievable turn!
Kim Won Hyo is easily taken down.]
[Next game-
Yoo Jae Suk vs Choi Bu Kyung.]
[Jae Suk isn't going down without a fight!]
Yoo Jae Suk!
[However...]
[The giant's advances cannot be stopped.]
[Jae Suk ultimately ousts himself.]
[With two wins in a row,
Team SK Knights moves onto the next round.]
Team SK Knights wins!
[How are we going to stop that giant?]
Team Choi Bu Kyung will move on
to the next round.
[Team SK Knights to
move on to the next round.]
- You're awful, Won Hyo!
- What are you doing?
[First round of Big Seven Alkkaggi-
Team SK Knights wins.]
[Team FNC- Suk Jin and Sul Hyun.]
[Team ESteem- Gary and Hye Jung.]
- Let's start the game.
- We will now start the game.
[Big Seven Alkkaggi- Round Two.
FNC's Sul Hyun vs ESteem's Hye Jung.]
Sul Hyun is in the 'M' formation,
and Hye Jung is in the 'W' formation.
They have assumed opposite formations.
You can't lose.
You lose and it's over for us.
- Then it's the end for AOA as well.
- Suk Jin is threatening his own partner.
Why would it be the end for AOA?
If Sul Hyun loses this game,
then it's the end for their team.
That's a nice formation for an attack.
She has to win this game.
- Sul Hyun is about to make her move.
- I'm so nervous!
- Will it be a forward attack?
- She has no other choice.
She has to remain calm.
- She can't be feeling nervous.
- Do it when you're no longer nervous.
This move is...
[Bu Kyung's sweep move.]
[Not a bad attack for Sul Hyun.]
The closer the pieces are together,
more cautious one must remain.
[Controlling the force of the attack
is key in this situation.]
It's very easy to oust yourself
along with the opponent's piece.
It would be very easy
to oust herself as well.
[Team ESteem plays it safe.]
Eliminate the one you want.
[Using all the proper
terminology for this game.]
I'm just telling her to do
what she feels comfortable with.
If she wants to remain defensive too,
then she needs to start eliminating.
Nine, eight, seven, six...
[Team ESteem's plan of defense worked!]
[Hye Jung follows it up
with a successful attack.]
[Remaining number of pieces.
Jae Sul Hyun- Three vs Hye Jung- Five.]
We've already lost, so just remain calm.
- We've already lost, so just be calm.
- That's a lie, don't you think?
[Sul Hyun makes a huge mistake
in such a crucial moment!]
She's sacrificing herself for their win.
It can't get any worse for them right now.
- Will this be the end for them?
- She's making it easy for their win.
- All five of their pieces are still left.
- But you still don't know what'll happen.
Since Hye Jung is at an advantage,
her moves look to be very much at ease.
Think back to when you were struggling.
She's struggling right now as is.
Think back to your training days.
It's like her father is reprimanding her.
Have you forgotten what took you to
get here? How can you not beat this?
[Yes, I can do this...]
[The battle isn't over yet.]
[A clean sweep of the attack!]
[Remaining number of pieces.
Jae Sul Hyun- Two vs Hye Jung- Four.]
- She's showing some improvement.
- In a competition like this...
This isn't to show your experience,
but it's to showcase your skills.
Why are you doing that?
Why are you copying my words?
You just copied my own words!
- Wow, you're so shameless.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
[Succeeds in two attack moves in a row.]
[Remaining number of pieces.
Jae Sul Hyun- Two vs Hye Jung- Three.]
You can't predict the end result.
[Sul Hyun is in the groove.]
[Sul Hyun successfully sweeps
three pieces out in a row.]
[Team FNC, fighting!]
She's now getting used to her move.
- That's amazing.
- It truly is amazing.
[Now it's down to one on one.]
[Team ESteem is now on the defense.]
- The outcome is unknown!
- It's down to this one last move!
- It's down to this move!
- She needs to be more aggressive!
- She is being told to eliminate Sul Hyun.
[How can this be...]
[Sul Hyun's complete game changer!]
[Big Seven Alkkaggi- Game Two.
FNC:1 vs Esteem 1.]
It's a miraculous win for Team FNC!
It's okay.
AOA's Sul Hyun saves her team
from the danger of elimination!
[Big Seven Alkkaggi-
FNC's Suk Jin vs ESteem's Gary.]
Are you finished?
Jang Ye Won isn't normally like that.
Big-nose is starting to listen to
Coach Sul Hyun's instructions.
Sul Hyun, Hye Jung and
Ye Won are all so beautiful.
They're all such beauties.
Suk Jin and Gary are making the beauties
look even more beautiful in comparison.
[You ladies are like roses,
and we are like babies breath.]
And Yook Joong Wan is supporting
my statement as well.
Yes, he is fiercely supporting
your statement.
Ji Hyo looks even more beautiful
than usual.
Actually, his company as a whole is
making Ji Hyo look so much more beautiful.
[Roxta Muzik will do whatever we can to
make your beauty shine even more brightly.]
[Team ESteem Gary's attack.]
This game really grabs your attention.
[A precise and powerful attack.]
Gary is one hundred percent in his zone.
Gary really enjoys shooting pool
in his spare time.
Yes, that could be helpful in this game.
Suk Jin is really good at bluffing.
[Ah...]
Maybe my statement had an effect?
Did my statement influence the outcome?
- Is he about to reveal a new move?
- What is Ji Suk Jin doing?
Ji Suk Jin is showing a new move.
[Succeeds in the one finger sweep attack.]
[Big-nose successfully attacks
Gary's piece with the sweep.]
Ji Suk Jin and Gary both usually
attacks with the thumb flick.
- Can he get it done?
- Let's see if he can eliminate the piece.
[Gary successfully eliminates
another piece!]
Gary is one hundred percent in the zone!
Yes, he is very much in the zone.
It's absolutely unbelievable.
Three, two, one!
[I won't let you win! Big-nose
eliminates before the buzzer sounds!]
[A very tight competition.]
[Remaining number of pieces.
Suk Jin- Two vs Gary- Three.]
[Gary is a professional alkkaggi player!]
- He is one hundred percent in the zone!
- He is truly unbelievable.
Sul Hyun, forgive me if I lose.
[Why are you apologizing now?]
Maybe it would've been better for
Sul Hyun to play this game too.
[Big Seven Alkkaggi- Game Two.
Team ESteem wins!]
I'm sorry.
Team ESteem will move up to semi-finals!
[Gary and Lee Hye Jung-
Team ESteem into the semi-finals!]
They're very focused about their formation.
[Round three-
JYP's Woo Young vs SBS' Kim Jong Kook.]
[The winner of this game will move on
to the semi-finals round.]
[Woo Young's pinky attack.]
This is Woo Young's promise finger move.
Don't you think that your names
for these moves are too much?
Maybe you should be more selective
about the words you choose to use.
I hope that Ms. Ok Joo Hyun doesn't
take offense to your comments.
[Ok Joo Hyun move to Pinky promise move?]
[Woo Young is feeding off the
'Pinky promise move' statements.]
[Wow, two pieces with one flick!]
[Perfect speed and aim!]
[Team JYP moves onto the semi-finals.]
We will now immediately  move
onto the semi-finals round.
[Big Seven alkkaggi competition-
Semi-finals.]
- It is the semi-finals round.
- Yes, that's correct.
It's Choi Bu Kyung vs Gary!
[First round of semi-finals:
Choi Bu Kyung vs Gary.]
[The strong vs The strong!
A formidable match!]
I know this since I've competed
against Kang Gary myself.
As you all already know,
Gary has been 100% accurate.
Choi Bu Kyung on the other hand is
the pioneer of the sweeping moves.
- It's in a straight line formation.
- It's a push move.
No, don't do that!
That's way too aggressive.
He's moving the pieces back further
hopping that Gary will make a mistake.
We'll see who will make
the first aggressive attack.
I know from first hand
that he is very highly skilled.
[Perfect aim!]
[Random Mr. Capable is drawing
a loud cheer from the crowd.]
- The crowd can't help but cheer for him.
- He can be a national representatives.
[Choi Bu Kyung's sweep move.]
[He loses his own piece as well
in the process!]
He still boasts a 100%
success rate.
[Zero mistakes!]
Kang Gary!
- Wow, he really is remarkable.
- Amazing!
I wonder if he's aware of just how good
he is at the game himself.
[Choi Bu Kyung succeeds.]
[Remaining number of pieces.
Choi Bu Kyung- Two vs Gary- Three.]
This truly is a great game.
[Player Gae unfortunately loses
his own piece as well in the process.]
Choi Bu Kyung must successfully
eliminate one of the black pieces.
If he doesn't,
then Team SK Knights will be in danger.
Just lightly tap it.
[Chooses to go with a defensive move.]
In my opinion, I think an
attack would've been a better move.
If he fails his attack...
[How can this be!]
[Precise Gary's missed shot!]
[He seems to be on edge from having
to compete against Choi Bu Kyung.]
That could've been a detrimental mistake.
[Trying to lure Gary into another attack,
Choi Bu Kyung makes another defensive move.]
[Only one piece left for both players.]
- This could be the move.
- Will he be able to get it done?
[Will he be able to make
a successful attack?]
He's getting ready to make his attack.
[Another missed shot!]
[Team SK Knights wins the semi-finals!]
- Choi Bu Kyung!
- Ha Ha and Choi Bu Kyung!
[Team SK Knights moves onto the finals!]
[SK Knights moves onto the finals
in the Big Seven Alkkaggi Competition!]
[Second semi-finals game.]
Please welcome Song Ji Hyo
and Yook Joong Wan!
[Roxta Muzik finally
makes their entrance!]
[Team JYP is their opposing team.]
It's Lee Kwang Soo and Yoo Young
vs Song Ji Hyo and Yook Joong Wan.
How Yook Joong Wan-like of him.
- That's very like him.
- Very befitting of his own name.
- Can we sing our cheer?
- Sure, go ahead.
Let's hear a cheer from Roxta Muzik.
Jang Woo Young!
Sorry, but you're not our style.
[Attack on the opponent under
the disguise of it being a cheer.]
- Yes, this is great.
- Please make your formation.
- They could be at an advantage.
- This is something new!
[Yook Joong Wan's mountain formation.]
- What is this?
- What kind of a formation is that?
What is this?
[Woo Young's unbalanced formation.]
What kind of an obscure
alkkaggi move is that?
- What is he doing?
- I have no idea what that is.
[Right from the formation,
this is a very unusual game.]
[Joong Wan's skills are still unknown.]
Yook Joong Wan's first move.
[First move will show
the level of his skillset.]
It almost became two birds with one stone!
[Skillset befitting of being
moved up to the semi-finals.]
- It could've been two with one move.
- His impressive skills are unveiled.
Yook Joong Wan showed some impressive
skills during the earlier game as well.
One of the white pieces
are hanging on the ledge.
[Idol, Woo Young, shows impressive
targeting and shooting skills.]
Yes, he is very good.
- Yes, that was very good.
- Impressive skills.
Yook Joong Wan seems to favor
the sweeping move.
No, it's okay.
- It's okay.
- Three white and three black pieces left.
The important thing to realize is that
even though the white piece is on the ledge
that position could actually prove to be
advantageous in the end.
Yes, it can definitely lure in the enemy.
- What, 'the enemy'?
- This isn't a war.
What kind of a term is that?
How is he the enemy?
- It means to lure in the opponent.
- Go easy with your comments.
Your skills are really lacking
compared to theirs.
[Quiet hackling from the back.]
[The seriousness of the move can be felt
through his fingertip.]
[Unfortunately misses ousting
both pieces with one shot!]
[A fierce competition befitting
of the semi-finals round.]
This is very nerve-wrecking,
and very aggressive attacks.
[Tries to lure Woo Young into attacking.]
Yes, that move wasn't actually half bad.
If we had to compare
Joong Wan to a soccer player
then he'd resemble Rooney very closely.
Yes, Rooney of Manchester.
- They each have two pieces left.
- Will it be an attack or defense?
- The positioning is very important.
- Which of the two will he do?
It looks as though he's on the defense.
[Defense?]
[A very successful attack!]
[TKO!]
[Please give me your strength!]
He has the quickest speed
of everyone else I've seen.
[Ceremonial dance.]
The speed he puts into his moves
are the quickest I've seen.
Even though I haven't measured it,
his speed is at about 130km.
[Piece speed racer.]
Yes, the speed of how he attacks
could be very important.
[Yook Joong Wan is down to his final piece.]
You can't predict what he can do
with his one final piece.
[Succeeds the attack.]
[Yook Joong Wan's
responsive ceremonial dance.]
This is a very skilled competition.
- This is a highly skilled competition.
- Yes, the best we've seen so far.
- That's a very difficult position.
- Jang Woo Young!
[Speed racer butts his white piece
right up against the black piece.]
This is a very skilled move.
Being too close to the opponent's piece
could actually be even more difficult.
Yes, you can never guess
what could result.
[His explanations needs a rest.]
Move out of that spot.
[Yook Joong body checks Woo Young
to take his spot.]
- Woo Young just got pushed out of his spot.
- Yook Joong Wan body checked him.
He shows strength when it comes to
bodily moves.
[A worrisome distance and moves.]
Will he succeed or terminate himself?
[Too close of a distance is proving
difficult for elimination.]
[This is my chance.]
That could've been a detrimental mistake.
- This could be his chance.
- Woo Young and his lightning speed.
This could be the final attack.
What is that sound?
[Player Yook starts to chant.]
Yes, that is allowed.
[Starts to chant to fluster his opponent.]
[All his friends runs over
to join in on his chant.]
[Please...
we pray for you to make a mistake.]
[A group chant and prayer.]
It's almost like a chanting of a spell.
[Please miss... please miss...]
[Player Yook is praying for
Woo Young to make a mistake.]
'Please miss?'
[First time anyone has ever chanted
a spell during an alkkaggi game.]
No, don't listen to him!
Just do it!
You need to stay focused!
Stay focused!
It's okay, you can do it.
[Everyone's caught up in the chanting.]
Will our Speed Racer be able to succeed?
Speed is very important,
but precision is just as important.
- Will he make it?
- Put your life on the line.
[This is one very serious game!]
Okay, he bets his life on the line.
This move will determine whether
he lives or dies.
[The fierce look of determination-
Scanning of the board now complete.]
[It's a tie!]
[Ji Hyo vs Kwang Soo.
This game will determine the winner.]
- What a fierce competition!
- We're in love with Song Ji Hyo!
[What great atmosphere!]
Thinking of you, Kwang Soo!
What are you talking about?
Lee Kwang Soo is very well known for
his streak of misfortune.
- He's the icon of betrayal, isn't he?
- Yes, he is.
When he was deep into his traitorous days,
he said he'd betray even his own parents.
[Kwang Soo moves out of his seat
right from the start?]
- Why do you think he's doing that?
- Do you really need to do that?
[The ease of knowing that
they're already in the finals.]
You are such a dirty player.
[Giraffe moves over to the opposite side.]
No, he can't do it.
I can almost guarantee that he'll fail.
We can safely assume that he
can't do it.
[Blank Ji's attack.]
[Attempting to squeeze in between
her own pieces.]
[A difficult move
due to the very narrow space.]
- Concentrate!
- She's going for it.
She could very well oust herself
in the process.
[She does it!]
She's better than most men.
[An ace at anything that she does!]
- There's nothing she can't do.
- Can she win this?
[Grazes Ji Hyo's piece,
but ultimately ousts himself.]
He's losing out in every single category.
[Remaining number of pieces-
Ji Hyo- Four vs Kwang Soo- Three.]
[Precise aim and strength.]
Yes, it's all about the sweep
when it comes to alkkaggi.
Now that the competition is getting fierce,
Team JYP is starting to look grim.
[Fighting, Giraffe.]
Lee Kwang Soo is also attempting
to make the sweeping move.
[Giraffe gets his finger in position.]
This is his chance to show off his skills.
He eliminates his own piece!
Lee Kwang Soo!
[This is the first time that an opposing team
has shown a sign of gratefulness.]
Sum Mi is actually pouting right now.
- As mentioned before, he has no chance.
- No, he really is awful.
[Remaining number of pieces-
Ji Hyo- Four vs Kwang Soo- One.]
I hope that she'll show us something
grand for this one final move.
The final move by Ji Hyo!
[Ace's clean finish!]
[Song Ji Hyo and Yook Joong Wan
move onto the final round.]
[I'm sorry for losing...]
A female player wins the game!
It's the final round!
Ha Ha and Choi Bu Kyung...
vs Song Ji Hyo and Yoo Joong Wan!
[Big Seven Alkkaggi Competition-
The final competition!]
[Song Ji Hyo and Yook Joong Wan
vs Ha Ha and Choi Bu Kyung.]
[Only one final round
to determine the victor.]
[The key is to choose the right player
to lead the team into victory.]
For this final round,
we will be playing with seven pieces.
Players may now enter the arena.
[Time for the players to enter.]
[Yook Joong Wan for Team Rock stars.]
[vs Choi Bu Kyung of SK Knights.]
[Face-off between two strongest players.]
[Will it be the pioneer of the sweep move,
Choi Bu Kyung...]
[Or the pupil of the sweep move,
Yook Joong Wan.]
[Eliminate the anxiety...]
Look at how many new fans of
alkkaggi we're gaining.
[Time to assume the formation.]
- Are you finished with the formation?
- The formations are very similar.
- It's a very safe looking formation.
- Maybe push it towards the edge a bit.
[Joong Wan to make the first move.]
[Plans to eliminate two pieces
with his first shot.]
[Even though he misses eliminating two,
he succeeds in eliminating one.]
[Bu Kyung's turn to make a sweep attack.]
Sweep it off the board!
[A clean sweep.]
This leaves the black piece with a chance
to eliminate two whites pieces at once.
Is he not going for that?
[Succeeds the attack.]
It's a very clean game, isn't it?
[The target piece.]
[Perfect aim, but too weak of a shot.]
[Now it's back to Yook Joong Wan.]
[Follows it up... and ousts his own piece.]
[Remaining number of pieces-
Joong Wan- Five vs Bu Kyung- Four.]
[Time for Choi Bu Kyung to turn the tide.]
[Remaining number of pieces-
Joong Wan- Four vs Bu Kyung- Four.]
Any mistakes can be deadly.
[Team Roxta is back in the lead.]
Yes, he needs to hit it
a little off to the left.
[A chance to eliminate two pieces at once.]
[But he fortunately succeeds in
eliminating one of the pieces.]
[Joong Wan switches his position.]
[Choi Bu Kyung follows along
to run interference to Joong Wan.]
[Basketball player's alkkaggi defense moves.]
- It's down to the physical blocks.
- Joong Wan isn't easy to block physically.
He's screening Joong Wan
just like a basketball player would.
[Joong Wan overcomes the block
and succeeds in his attack.]
[Remaining number of pieces-
Joong Wan- Three vs Bu Kyung- Two.]
- This isn't an easy position to attack.
- What kind of a move will he make?
[A move that he enjoyed making
during the semi-finals round.]
- He had fun with those moves earlier.
- I don't know what to do here.
- This is an easy time to make mistakes.
- Joong Wan needs to be cautious.
If he's able to eliminate both with one move,
then it'll be a game changer.
[Attempting a two in one move.]
[If he succeeds,
then he'll turn the game around.]
[Ousts one piece!]
[Very closely misses ousting both pieces!]
- He's so good!
- That was so close!
[A single mistake can turn into defeat.]
[Yook Joong Wan successfully attacks.]
It could be down to this one final move!
[A serious playoff game!]
- Choi Bu Kyung, fighting!
- If he misses, then it could be the end!
This could determine
whether the game will end or go on.
They're betting on Choi Bu Kyung right now.
I can start to see the end.
[Fails! A soft shot
in fear of self destruction.]
[Remaining number of pieces-
Joong Wan- Two vs Bu Kyung- One.]
If Yook Joong Wan succeeds,
then that's the end of the battle.
[Success of this attack would
mean their victory!]
[Will this attack mean their victory?]
This really could be the final attack.
[Complete focus.]
[Everything is riding on this one attack.]
Song Ji Hyo really is amazing.
Okay, he's about to make his move.
[Putting all his energy into this one sweep.]
[If he fails at this attack...
then the other team still has a chance.]
[Succeeds in his attack!]
[Team Roxta wins
the Big Seven Competition!]
Song Ji Hyo and Yook Joong Wan wins!
[Blank Ji and Yook Joong Wan...
and their crowd of fans wins the game!]
[Team SK Knights comes in at second place.]
- You guys were amazing.
- I can't believe we won!
[A huge round of applause to
all the teams.]
Ye Won will now present a prize
to the winning team.
[A prize for the winning team.]
Who guessed that this team
would win the competition?
[FNC's Juniel get a prize for predicting
the win for this team.]
Who else?
Please step forward.
[Two people from Team ESteem.]
No one from this team?
[We had no idea that they'd win...]
[Only one member from their team
predicted the win.]
[A gold bar to the seven people
who guessed correctly.]
Let's check and see what the prize
for the winning team is.
[Time to reveal the prize.]
[A baduk board.]
So that you can play this game at home.
That's why you're getting this prize,
and congratulations again for winning!
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is an amusement park.
[A place full of love and hope.]
[An exciting date with their partner.]
This is what an amusement park
is supposed to be like.
[Like this?]
[A terrorizing experience
to close off the summer.]
[Must do whatever they have to in
order to succeed these extreme missions.]
[Must succeed the missions to avoid
the worst imaginable punishments.]
[Just who will be invited
to experience this terror?]
[Next week on Running Man- 1470.]