Subtitles by DramaFever
There's a floorless amusement
ride in Taiwan.
[August 2015- 8:15AM]
[This is where...]
[You'll face your
worst terrorizing nightmare.]
[The one who's unable to solve
the riddle of the number, 1470...]
[This is where you'll have to face
the climax of your fears.]
[Witness the most extreme punishment
Running Man has yet to face.]
[You will get to experience it.]
[The end of all fears where
heaven meets earth.]
[Someone will face the skies of Taiwan.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One day earlier.]
[Each couple gathers in Incheon.]
This is a numbers race.
[Early morning, in an amusement park...]
[1470 Numbers Race-
Turn the number, 1470, into a zero.]
- I really love them.
- You like these rides?
[Earn the number cards by succeeding
a variety of amusement park missions.]
[Jae Suk's partner-
Amusement ride maniac, Lee Sung Jae.]
[Jae Suk and Sung Jae-
A thrilling rollercoaster.]
[Photo taking mission doesn't seem
all that difficult for Sung Jae.]
[Lee Sung Jae-
The terrorizing shutter mission.]
[Kwang Soo's partner-
The latest 'It' actor, Ji Chang Wook.]
[Midair 'Eat the dried persimmon' mission.]
[Chang Wook gives his all to the mission...]
My persimmon disappeared!
[The persimmon disappears on him!]
[Desperate attempts to earn
their number cards.]
[Sweet Chang Wook's desperate
attempts continue on.]
[Gary's partner- Soul Diva, Ailee.]
[Rollercoaster karaoke bar mission.]
[Ailee is now dubbed,
'The high frequency diva.']
I forgot all the lyrics!
[Ha Ha's partner-
Korea's top reggae artist, Skull.]
[Suk Jin's partner- The queen
of the comedy world, Song Eun Yi.]
[It has been verified that she's been
spun and twisted around all day.]
[Mission- Guess the words written
on the bottoms of their feet.]
[Big-nose twists his own partner's
legs around to pass the mission.]
People who are shorter than 140cm
may not even get on the ride.
- I barely made the mark.
- Me too.
- I wasn't sure if I could even do it.
- Which ride were you on?
[What was Ha Ha and Skull's mission?]
[Save the water in a 360 degree twist.]
[Skull gets a water bath on the ride.]
[Mission- Save the water balloons.]
[Jong Kook's partner-
g.o.d's Kim Tae Woo.]
[Ji Hyo's partner-
2AM's velvety voice, Seulong.]
[Unlock the padlock by counting the
number of items on the colored mats.]
[Ace Ji Hyo unlocks the padlock
only on their second try.]
[Each team earns their own numbered cards
once the mission has been won.]
- You have to turn it into a zero.
- One, two, four...
[The key to help them turn the number,
1470, into a zero.]
[Once their cards have been earned,
they all gather together in Incheon.]
What do we do now?
- I've been hearing a lot of rumors.
- You have no idea what's being said.
Everyone's talking
when the cameras are turned off.
- I've heard so many different things.
- You know what I've heard?
Some are saying that this whole race
is a hidden camera race.
- I even heard something about Taiwan.
- I'll tell you what's going on.
- You've all been told about 1470, correct?
- Yes.
As you've all been told,
you have to form a zero out of 1470.
The meaning behind the number,
1470 is...
The secret behind the number is...
it represents 1470km.
It's the distance from Incheon
to the airport in Taiwan.
[The distance from Incheon to
Taiwan airport- 1470km.]
[Someone out of this group will travel to
Taiwan to face a terrifying punishment.]
You won't have to leave Seoul if you're
able to form a zero out of 1470
so that's why you've been asked
to form a zero out of the number.
So if we're able to form a '23' out of it,
then do we stop 23km into the trip?
If you're able to form a zero,
then you get to go home right away.
Then do we get the day off tomorrow?
[Face the punishment in Taiwan,
or enjoy a relaxing day off.]
You've all earned your share of
numbers after your missions, correct?
I'm sure there are some of you
who are in need of some more numbers
and some of you are probably wishing
that you had more numbers in your hands.
You will be given just one additional chance
to earn more numbers.
[Last chance to earn more numbers.]
[Mission- A piggyback run.]
One member from each couple will go
stand behind the numbered curtain.
Then the other person standing in front
of the curtain will stand facing forward
and assume a piggyback stance.
[Won't know who they'll have on their back
and will run blindly forward.]
[Who will be the lucky person to
get Tae Woo on their back?]
[And one grateful person who ends up
with Eun Yi on their back.]
Eun Yi doesn't know how light she is.
People behind the curtain will dance along
to the music and swap their positions around.
Once it's time,
the curtain will drop to the ground.
As soon as the curtain drops
the person in the back will go on the
back of the person in front of them.
[No choice in who's back they'll jump on.]
[To some, it'll just be another mission,
to others, it'll be a nightmare come true.]
If you're lucky enough
to have your own partner
then you have to run over
to the finish line.
Does it look like we're lucky right now?
[Tae Woo is more than just a simple
mission even to the Tiger.]
Even if you end up with someone else,
you still have to run over to the finish line.
First team that crosses the finish line
will win the mission.
- Being disruptive will have to be my plan.
- I'm confident that I'll be very disruptive.
The team that wins the mission will be
given any number of their choosing.
- Any number we want?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Does everyone understand the rules?
- This is not an easy mission.
You never know
who's going to win this mission.
[The runners assumes their positions
in front of the curtain.]
As soon as I get on someone's back,
I'm going to make that person drop.
[The riders assumes their positions
behind the curtain.]
- I can hear them.
- We're not in position yet.
[That's why the music has been prepared.]
[The runners won't know who they'll
end up with on their backs.]
[Seulong and Suk Jin swap spots.]
[Suk Jin swaps spots again
with Chang Wook.]
Did you guys plan this?
[Even the riders move around
to swap out their spots.]
[Utter chaos]
I don't know where to stand.
[Sung Jae attempts to sniff out
Jae Suk's position.]
[Immediately changes spots
when the feeling isn't there.]
- Chang Wook, want to switch spots?
- Yes.
[Getting a good feeling
about someone else's spot.]
I got a real bad feeling over there.
[I feel very good about this spot.]
[Everyone is now in position.
Must run as soon the curtain comes down.]
[Tiger- Yoo Hyuk.]
[Sung Jae- Blank Ji.]
[Seulong- Giraffe.]
[Chang Wook after his final swap...]
[The heavy load.]
[Bear, Tae Woo, does a full body shake.]
[Ace Blank Ji's
'You're not going anywhere!' move.]
[Giraffe kidnaps Seulong.]
[Kiddo vs Kiddo.]
[I need to cross the finish line
no matter what I have to do!]
[Defensive moves are Yoo Hyuk's specialty.]
[Gary's partner is...
what unbelievable luck!]
Hurry, Gary!
[Total chaos.]
[Ha Ha, with light Eun Yi on his back.]
[Kidnapped Idol, muscle boy, Seulong.]
[We're the Green Couple!]
[Gary and Ailee break ahead of the pack.]
[What luck!
Gary and Ailee win!]
Oh my God!
Ailee!
[Chang Wook, is in the
midst of his physical training.]
What are you doing?
What are you doing over there?
Chang Wook, what are you doing?
Kwang Soo, Tae Woo was...
[Chang Wook gets a full workout
thanks to Tae Woo.]
I could tell when I got on his back
that he's actually quite strong.
It was actually harder on me.
Want to give it a try?
I thought I heard you over there,
so that's why I switched spots.
I was two spots over from you.
I switched spots at the very last minute.
[Gary swaps out his spot with Chang Wook
at the very last moment.]
I had a very bad feeling about that spot.
I got a very bad feeling over there.
[This is what he was feeling.]
Gary and Ailee got it right?
[Gary and Ailee were the only couple
who actually found each other.]
What the heck, Song Ji Hyo?
You made him fall down to the ground!
- Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo made him fall.
[Extremely determined not to travel to
Taiwan to face the punishment.]
Would you like to play another round
if you want to earn some more numbers?
One more time!
But if Gary and Ailee win again,
then they'll end up earning two numbers.
[Everyone unanimously agrees
to play one more round.]
[The winning couple of this round
will also earn a number card.]
[Please let it be my own partner...]
[Everyone in position.]
[Must be fate.]
[Bye, Gary.]
[You can't go, Ailee!
Seulong drops down to the ground.]
[I'm glad it's you!]
[This time, Giraffe kidnaps Big-nose.]
[Yes!
It's lightweight Ji Hyo!]
[It's the Iron Man!]
[Lucky!]
[Running at top speed to avoid
having to face the Taiwan punishment.]
[No matter what she does...
his strength takes over.]
[Chang Wook does his best
to withstand it...]
[But ultimately ends up falling down
to the ground once again.]
What do you think you're doing!
[We're not facing the punishment!]
[Currently in the lead-
Tiger with Eun Yi on his back.]
[Running as if his life is on the line.]
[Jae Suk and Sung Jae win.]
[Song Eun Yi ends up getting her Tiger.]
What luck is this!
- Where were you?
- In the fifth spot. Where were you?
- I switched out of that spot!
- What did you do that for!
Why couldn't you get it done?
She's really good at interfering.
I was really shocked at how
good she was.
This round's victory goes to
Lee Sung Jae and Yoo Jae Suk.
[Winners-
Jae Suk, Sung Jae, Gary, Ailee.]
[Able to choose any number of their liking.]
- He just clung himself onto my back.
- I shouldn't have switched spots.
We came in at second place both times.
That's too bad, but there's
nothing we can do about it.
[Here's to hoping that
you win next time around.]
[The two teams are now trying to decide
which number to pick.]
[Each number that they possess will play
a very crucial role in the race.]
There's not much time left
until the flight.
What's so important about this race that
you're making all the guests feel so anxious?
[1470 Race...
You'll feel even more anxious later on.]
- I think we really are going.
- The final mission could be over quickly.
Yes, I'm sure that it won't
take long.
[Gary and Ailee are very cautious
about their number selection.]
Okay, the numbers have been selected.
Now that the numbers have been selected,
it's time to start your final mission.
[Time to reveal the final mission.]
The building we will be going into
is Incheon's Children's Museum.
Within that building, you will find a variety
of numerical symbols and numbers.
You will either have to find the symbols
or steal them from other teams
to form a zero out of the numbers
that your team has in possession.
[Transform 1470 into a zero through
the usage of different numerical symbols.]
Once the time limit is up, the
door leading to the outside will open.
Which means that even though you're able
to transform your number into a zero
within the time limit of five minutes
it has no meaning until those doors
leading to the outside are opened.
You will have to either protect your numbers
or stay hidden until the doors are opened.
[A final battle of wits, brains,
and physical strength.]
[Which couples will get lucky
and escape the punishment?]
[The final numbers mission.]
[The final destination of where the
mission will take place.]
[Each team will be given their numbers
and symbols before entering the building.]
[Gary and Ailee have chosen the number,
one, from having won the previous mission.]
- That's the number we chose.
- What is this?
[Jae Suk and Sung Jae have chosen the number,
'three' from the previous mission.]
Let's see if you'll be having your dinner
in Taiwan or in your own home.
Do you have it?
[Time to start the final race.]
[Time given- 30 minutes.]
[The doors to the building
will now be padlocked.]
[Only those who successfully transform
their number into a zero...]
[Will be able to escape
this terrifying punishment.]
[Current standing of the teams.]
[The countdown has begun.]
[A variety of numerical symbols are
hidden throughout the building.]
[Must protect the numbers and symbols in hand
and find other needed numbers and symbols.]
Shove them down your pants so that
no one can take them away from you.
[Shoving them down his pants.]
I thought you said liked amusement rides,
but I guess you don't want to go to Taiwan?
[This amusement ride maniac seems to
have a change of heart in half a day.]
We have to go find more symbols.
Shove them down my pants?
What if it falls out?
Inside my pants?
[Even the Giraffe starts to shove the numbers
down his pants without any hesitation.]
[And eager Chang Wook follows
Kwang Soo's lead in anything he does.]
- Not down front, but in the back.
- But what if it falls out?
[Always such a hard worker.]
Just make sure not to have it taken away.
We need two minus signs,
and one and a five.
It would be awesome if I can find
a multiplication sign.
[Ha Ha is determined to win the race.]
[Ha Ha plans on locking his numbers
away in the lockers.]
Does anyone have any change?
[But he doesn't have
100 Won for the locker...]
[Plan is to formulate a zero,
then finding a multiplication sign.]
Do I need to search in the
trash cans, too?
- Do I need to search in the trash cans, too?
- No.
[With such a scary punishment on the line,
all their pride goes out the window.]
[Hides their numbers away in a trash can.]
- This could be our ticket.
- Ugh, that stinks.
[But the punishment they may have to face
is even more frightening than the smell.]
- No one saw that, right?
- Let's keep quiet.
[Gary and Ailee only need to find
a couple of signs in order to win.]
Here is what we need.
If we divide 1470 by 245,
then we're left with six.
Then we subtract it by six,
and we get our zero.
- So we just need the division sign.
- Really?
And we can also just use a minus sign, too.
Diving those numbers will give us a two.
Then we just need to subtract two
from it to get our zero.
Like you just said, we need
either a division or a minus sign.
To avoid confusing ourselves, let's
talk it out after we find more numbers.
I think that would be our best bet.
We won't get our taken away,
so let's just keep them in our pants.
[Plan- Let's just find as much
as we can.]
[Must form a zero no matter what-
Time to start searching.]
You want to do this?
What is it that you need?
- Let's help each other out.
- We need a one, a five, and a minus.
[We've got it all!]
We don't have any of those.
- What do you guys have?
- We can give you our addition sign.
- You have something you don't need?
- You don't need your addition sign?
- Anything else?
- A seven.
[Such a lie!]
- We don't have a seven.
- Keep quiet!
Keep quiet!
Your elder is talking!
- Let's go. Negotiation is over.
- What's the matter with you!
[Innocent Chang Wook
doesn't know how to lie.]
- Suk Jin!
- Go away!
[Ah, that was just your plan?]
- We have something you need.
- You almost had me fooled!
[Pure of heart, Ji Chang Wook.]
Chang Wook is so innocent.
I'll give you what you need later.
[Kwang Soo loses his prey
no thanks to Chang Wook.]
What are you going to do about this now?
- What are you going to do about this?
- So this is how you play it?
I'm learning from you.
- I'm starting to learn how to play it.
- I may end up smacking you across the face.
We need to find a division sign.
- The division sign is all we need.
- He said there's nothing in here.
We've already searched everywhere in here.
[Scheming Kwang Soo and his pupil
follows Ji Hyo into the room.]
What do you need?
We have something we don't need.
- We need a certain symbol.
- We have one that we don't need.
- What do you have?
- A divide, a root, and a plus symbol.
A divide, a root, and a plus symbol.
[Nervous and awkward.]
[Seriously?
You have a divide symbol?]
- Let's see your divide symbol.
- You seriously have one?
Yes, I have it.
I hid it away.
[The pupil is visibly nervous
at Kwang Soo's scheme.]
If you don't need the divide symbol,
then why did you hide it away?
[Diverts his gaze away.]
I don't believe you, Lee Kwang Soo.
[Second prey smells something foul
and escapes away.]
- I don't like the look on your face.
- Hear me out.
No, I won't fall for your lies.
Hey, Ji Chang Wook.
Are you going to be like this?
[Sorry, Teacher.]
- I really don't think I can lie.
- You have to.
- Then show some reaction, at least.
- How?
At least nod or head or something
instead of that blank look on your face.
- Okay.
- She caught onto us because of you.
- Got it?
- Okay.
- Next time, you're going to get a spanking.
- 'Yes, we do have that symbol.'
If I say that I have a certain symbol,
then hold it up like this, as if this is it.
- What if they ask to see it?
- Don't show it to them.
I'm going to have to teach you how to lie.
Think of this as your first lesson.
[How will this pupil fare his lessons?]
[Huh?]
[Stops in the middle of his search
to make an imprint of his face?]
[What does Jae Suk's face look like?]
[It's a grasshopper!]
How can this even be possible?
[Even he's amazed at his own likeness.]
[The time keeps on ticking,
and the terror creeps in closer...]
Skull, go check over there.
We have to keep on running.
[Ha Ha and Skull are in need of
'X', '( )' and '-' symbols.]
Since the staff members are human beings too,
I'm sure they probably thought similarly.
[Thinking like a hider would.]
I have a feeling that it's
around here somewhere.
See?
I knew I'd find something.
[Finds the '( )' symbol that he needs!]
Most people tend to think alike.
[His level of confidence shoots up
after finding his first symbol.]
I bet there's something here, too.
See?
[The 'X' symbol!]
[Amazing! Skull is finding
all the symbols that he needs!]
Ha Ha!
Wait, I can't lose this one.
I can't lose this one
even if I lose other symbols.
[Must protect his 'X' symbol.]
Maybe I can avoid having to
go to Taiwan.
I just need to work a little harder.
[Ha Ha and Skull are off to a good start.]
[Ha Ha is also having good luck
finding his symbols.]
[But what is he going to use
the 'root' symbol for?]
- Dong Hoon!
- Where are you?
- Come here, amazing.
- Me, too!
I found the multiplication sign.
['X' and '( )' symbols are found.]
[These two best friends are in
perfect sync with one another.]
Do you have a five?
I have the four and the seven.
We need to find a minus sign
and another same number.
We need to stick together because
we can't have anything stolen away.
Wait, do you have 100 Won?
- Why?
- Hurry up and give me the change.
Do you have it?
Okay.
Okay, I'll pay you back.
Come with me.
[Finally borrows the change he needs.]
Let's put these in a locker.
[Rushing off to the lockers
that he saw earlier.]
[The key is to protect all the numbers
and the symbols they have on hand.]
Put them all in there.
[Only locking up the ones they need to keep.]
Remember, locker number 96.
[All they need to find now are
a '-' symbol and either 4, 7, or an 8.]
We have to find it.
[We can... escape having
to go to Taiwan, right?]
- Tae Woo?
- Yes, Jong Kook?
Search over there,
and I'll search over here.
[Jong Kook and Tae Woo are
on the search.]
[What they still need to find.]
[Wow!
Finds the 'X' symbol!]
This is awesome.
[Even Mr. Capable is amazed at
his own find.]
[Tae Woo finds a plus symbol!]
[And a parenthesis symbol!]
[Amazing! Finding all
the symbols that they need!]
[They now just need to find
the number one!]
Coming!
[Here's another lucky team-
Ha Ha and Skull.]
- Are you having luck finding things?
- What else do you need?
- Us?
- Yes, what do you need?
We don't need any help.
We have everything we need already.
- We have a lot of numbers.
- We'll give you what you need.
We have a lot of numbers.
[Muscle consumed Sung Jae succeeds
in stealing something!]
You're allowed to do that?
Are you allowed to do that?
[But... it's a root symbol.]
Hey, Jae Suk.
- I stole one.
- What did you steal?
But it's not something very useful.
It's a root symbol.
- There are too many root symbols around.
- I know.
- People are trying to get them taken away.
- Really?
Just because you stole something,
they're going to come after you now.
- Come with me.
- Okay, let's stick together.
[Darn...]
They're going to be mad now, so
they're going to come after you with help.
Do you know what happens then?
You're going to end up losing five just
because you took one away from them.
Don't go around making them angry.
Don't antagonize them.
- You have to stay away from them.
- I didn't know that.
- You can't anger them.
- I didn't think he'd be like that.
[They're already angry.]
Tell us what you need,
and we'll give it to you.
- We have them all hidden away.
- We wouldn't be offering it otherwise.
We have a lot of numbers.
Tell us what you want, and it's yours.
Just give us one number.
Do you have any extras?
- Any numbers that you don't need?
- Do you have an eight?
- Eight...
- We don't need an eight.
- Then do you want a four?
- No, we have a four.
You can subtract a four from a four
to get a zero.
[They're going to find us a four?]
See? You could get a zero.
We'll give you a four.
- You have a four?
- We'll give you a four.
- But give us either a 5, 7 or an 8.
- If they give us a four...
[Jong Kook and Tae Woo would get
their zero with a four.]
- Four minus four is a zero.
- Then we can get our zero.
- Multiplying that would give us a zero.
- Okay, deal.
[But we want either a seven
or an eight in exchange!]
- We'll give them all to you.
- Do you have an eight?
We can give those to them.
[If the exchange is made, then all
Ha Ha and Skull would need is a '-'!]
[It's a win-win situation!]
Go stand over there so that
no one else can come in.
[Both teams are excited at the thought
of escaping the scary punishment!]
Okay, we'll see you in a bit.
This is awesome.
- It's over.
- We got it.
We can escape having to go to Taiwan
if we play this right.
[Will these two be able to escape
the terrorizing punishment?]
If we divide it by four,
then do we get 70?
If we divide it by four...
then it's... I don't know.
What if we divide it by seven?
That's... 210.
How about if we subtract 213?
- Subtract four?
- Yes, subtract it by four.
Subtract it by nine?
We need a plus sign.
We need to steal it from someone.
[Must steal a '+' symbol!]
We need to steal it.
Ouch, my legs.
Dong Hoon, just give me one.
Just give me one number.
Suk Jin has a lot of numbers.
Suk Jin, just give me one.
Can you just give me one number
that you don't need?
- You have yours hidden away somewhere?
- No, Kwang Soo took them away from me.
To Kwang Soo?
You really are something else.
How can I win against two guys?
[Gary and Ailee's plan- Beg.]
[Ha Ha ultimately hands one over
out of pity for Gary's begging.]
Sung Jae took something from us earlier.
[While no one else is looking...
Hides it all in the trash can.]
People don't search through
filthy trash cans.
I got a parenthesis sign,
and I hid it in the trash can.
I just got a parenthesis sign.
[All they need now are a '-' and
a 'X' symbol in order to get their zero.]
[Gary, you're the best!]
This isn't a trade,
but we're outright begging.
[Please]
No, don't pay attention
to what they're doing!
[What is such a big deal
about the amusement ride?]
[Their pride has been cast aside
a long time ago already...]
[I can't get on that ride
even if my life depended on it.]
[A life and death situation for
Ha Ha and Skull.]
[The truth is, Jong Kook and Tae Woo
already have everything that they need.]
[But trading in their eight for the four
will still make it easier for them.]
[Trade has been made!]
[Ha Ha attempts to escape
from the attacking hyenas.]
Give me the four.
[Jong Kook and Tae Woo succeed
in their mission!]
Give me the parenthesis sign.
You take the 'x' symbol,
and I'll take the '( )' symbol.
[Will they be able to hold on
to everything until the end?]
Bear and the Tiger.
[Prison break?
This team is being attacked!]
[Checking on the other numbers and
symbols that they kept hidden away.]
Don't be so nervous.
[Both of them are full of nervous energy
like a couple of sinners.]
[You really don't want to
get on the ride, do you?]
You're too visible right now.
[They successfully have their zero!
Hiding away what they need under the desk.]
Don't film that!
What are you thinking?
- I don't want to go to Taiwan.
- Here they come.
[Okay, we're all set...]
[On the other hand...]
Ji Chang Wook!
[Giraffe is being attacked!]
[Ailee eyes her chance and
steals something from Big-nose!]
[Everyone's the enemy!]
You fool!
How could you have it taken away!
- You don't have anything?
- That's just my body!
[Kind of looks like there's something...]
Make your escape!
Kwang Soo!
[Save me!]
[Seulong joins in on the tussle
from out of nowhere.]
I think this team needs the symbol!
[Brain Seulong, steals the '+' symbol.]
[Ji Hyo and Seulong stow away to
a quiet place to get organized.]
[Seulong puts everything that they have
together to calculate what they have.]
With these numbers,
we are able to get 1468.
When we add two to that number,
then we get our 1470.
Then we subtract the sum of 1468 and
two, which leaves us with our zero.
Okay, we got it.
[Ji Hyo and Seulong get their zero!]
You're smart.
[Will these two be able to escape
the Taiwan punishment?]
[Only five minutes left on the clock.]
Hey, let's make an exchange.
- Come on, let's make an exchange.
- What do you have?
You can have either three, seven,
or a nine.
We're being very serious.
You can have any of those numbers.
- But we don't need any of them.
- Wouldn't it be better to have more numbers?
Then we'll give you our '+' symbol
for two of your numbers.
[Pupil Chang Wook's shocking transformation.]
[Ji Chang Wook-
Graduating as a top pupil.]
[Actually, both teams can avoid Taiwan
if they each give up what they don't need.]
[But it is not Running Man's way to give
something up even if they don't need it.]
- Wait.
- Let's just make the trade.
Don't just put it down because
they'll just take it.
[That's why he's the master of scheming.]
[Seriously...]
[This is war!]
[Did you think that I wouldn't be
able to find you?]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I wasn't thinking clearly.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you out of your mind?
- I'll never do it again, please forgive me.
- Bring me a '+' sign.
- I'm sorry.
- I told you to bring me a '+' sign.
[Like a student called into
the principal's office.]
Ji Chang Wook, bring me a '+' sign!
Chang Wook!
- How much for the '+' symbol?
- Where are you hiding your things?
- Where are you keeping yours hidden?
- You have to carry them around with you.
- This is all we have.
- We already have a nine.
Kwang Soo, this is it.
[The hyenas exchange glances.]
[Everyone attacks Jae Suk and
Sung Jae together.]
[This is what happens in Running World if you
let down your guard even for a second.]
[Jae Suk is having everything
taken away from him.]
[But they end up fighting
amongst themselves as well.]
[Ailee succeeds in stealing something.]
[Meanwhile, Chang Wook is separated
from his scheming partner.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
Save me!
[Chang Wook is being attacked by
Suk Jin and Eun Yi.]
Kwang Soo!
You have to hold on!
[Only three minutes left on the clock!]
[No more time left to waste!]
[Time for a real battle.]
[Gary and Ailee only needs
the '-' symbol in order to succeed.]
[But there's no mercy when faced
with the Taiwan punishment.]
[But the symbol that falls on Ailee's lap...
The '-' symbol!]
[As if dropped from heaven!]
[As closing time draws near,
all the couples gets more frantic.]
Put it all together.
[All they need is the '-' symbol that
they just lost to Ailee in order to succeed.]
If we play this right,
we may not have to go to Taiwan.
We may be able to escape
having to go on the ride.
- You said you wanted to go earlier.
- No, I don't want to go.
[I changed my mind about that
a long time ago...]
I really don't want to go on the ride.
I don't want to go to Taiwan
and get on that ride.
I just want to go for the sightseeing.
What's the point of us
standing around here like this?
[Did Jong Kook and Tae Woo
go off for a leisurely stroll?]
If anyone comes near us, I'm going to
spray them down with the fire extinguisher.
Hey, Skull!
Let's go find Jong Kook.
[After Giraffe gets everyone to agree
to look for Jong Kook and Tae Woo...]
[Chang Wook goes off on his own
to calculate what they have.]
[Lucky Ailee gets the '-' symbol.]
- How many ones do we have?
- Here's the parenthesis.
We have two right now.
We need that one.
[As long as they can keep these safe,
they can go home once they get out.]
[Suk Jin and Eun Yi are also busy
calculating what they've got.]
[They've got quite a few numbers...]
- Where did our six go?
- Didn't we have it?
I thought we had another six.
[They have their zero!]
[But they don't even know it!]
[The answer is right in front of them,
but they're not even aware of it.]
- We're in trouble.
- Wait.
- What are we going to do?
- Should we take this out?
[Will they be able to figure it out
before their time is up?]
[Meanwhile, Ha Ha and Skull already have
had their answer figured out a while ago.]
[Ha Ha comes back for the numbers
that he had hidden away.]
They're all gone.
What are we going to do?
[What in the world happened?]
[A little while ago, while everyone went off
searching for Jong Kook and Tae Woo...]
[Chang Wook happens to go to the desk
in order to make his own calculations.]
[Then...]
What is this?
[What is this!]
[Happens across Ha Ha's buried treasure!]
- Amazing!
- What is it?
I found three!
I think someone had them hidden here.
[The scheming pupil pulls one off!]
[A great chance of succeeding the mission!]
[A total nightmare for this team.]
Skull.
Someone took everything.
- Stop kidding around.
- I'm totally serious.
[We're ruined!]
[Only one minute left on the clock!]
[Wow, that's where you kept
them hidden?]
[The final minute left on the clock to
avoid having to go to Taiwan!]
[This is their last chance!]
Gary.
- I really don't have anything.
- Do you have a '-' symbol?
- Don't lie to me!
[Ailee has it in her hands
and is staying hidden in the room.]
I couldn't believe it when I found these.
I just went to calculate our own stuff.
[Oh!
Did they succeed?]
[But they're unaware of it...]
[Please...]
[Please let me go home instead
of having to face the punishment...]
[Time is over.]
[The doors are opened.]
[Once they walk out those doors,
they're in the safe.]
[Ji Hyo and Seulong grab their hidden bag
and are the first ones out the door!]
Run!
Give me just one!
[Suk Jin and Eun Yi are desperate
to find a five.]
[But they find a five
that Blank Ji threw away!]
[Just who will be the ones to get
on this hellish ride?]
[Solve the 1470 riddle.]
[Get the answer to the riddle on the board
to be able to go home!]
Open the bag!
Open the bag and get them all on there.
[Gary and Ailee- Zero is complete!]
[We're going home!]
- We're finished!
- We're done!
[Ji Hyo and Seulong- Mission cleared.]
We're not going to Taiwan!
[We get to live!]
[It's a real celebration for the survivors.]
We did it!
[Jong Kook and Tae Woo- Mission cleared!]
[Suk Jin and Eun Yi?]
Doesn't this work?
- No, it has to be plus five.
- Plus five?
[How can this be?]
[Oh my gosh!
Mistakes a '+' for a '-'?]
[Have everything they need,
but still can't figure it out...]
How about we fix this symbol?
[Have Kwang Soo and Chang Wook
figured it out?]
[They still haven't figured it out...]
[Just then, Chang Wook seems to
have figured something out.]
Where did our '( )' symbol go?
- We just gave that away.
- Ah!
[They gave the '( )' symbol away?]
[Final trade made by all the teams
right before the time ran out.]
No, we don't need that.
[Just gave the '( )' away,
thinking they wouldn't need it.]
We couldn't figure this out when
we had the '( )' symbol in hand.
We just gave the symbol away  to Dong Hoon
thinking that we wouldn't need it.
[It's already water under the bridge...]
- This is all I was thinking about.
- We didn't think of that earlier.
[The scheming brothers' unfortunate mistake.]
- We just needed a '-' symbol.
- We don't need any of this.
[If they only had the '-' symbol...]
[Too bad...]
Dong Hoon.
[A '-' symbol is needed,
so attempts to transform '=' into a '-'.]
Let's just go.
[Escapes punishment- Gary and Ailee;
Ji Hyo and Seulong; Jong Kook and Tae Woo.]
[Envious...]
Those of you standing on stage are
free to go home right now.
[Gets to go home right away!]
- Tae Woo, you can go home.
- Are they really going home?
[And... we're going to Taiwan?]
[Mommy, don't wait up for me...]
Sorry, Jae Suk!
[The winners leave to go home with
a bounce in their steps.]
Then I'll be heading home early.
[What a sweet ending it is...]
At times, moments like this is what
determines the outcome of one's life.
[Goodbye.]
It's been a while since the jail-timers
have gathered around like this.
- We're the original regulars in jail.
- I don't feel so alone.
As for the rest of you,
please be on your way.
Stop looking at it, Chang Wook!
It's all over!
[Do I really have to go on the ride?]
That's just absurd.
[The terrifying punishment
they now have to face.]
[Terror of unimaginable proportions
and the hidden secret behind it.]
[And also...]
[A trial that Running Man members
will now have to face.]
You only think of yourself, don't you?
[Six actresses and their harsh fate...]
- You've hurt me even worse, you jerk!
- You make me feel filthy!
[Where is this all headed?]
- Can't be!
- Stop obsessing over Song Ji Hyo!
I want you to love me!
[Coming soon.]
[Off to Taiwan to face their punishment.]
[Incheon International Airport.]
[The seven members, who
have failed to succeed their mission.]
[Off to face their frightening punishment
with a cheer from their fans.]
I'll be back.
I love you, Taiwan.
[Taiwan- Size of Taipei- 35.980km with
the population of 23.36 million people.]
[A food lovers' paradise where the culture
coexists side by side with nature.]
[August 2014- Taiwan's 'L' Resort.]
[The fateful day is here.]
Is it recording?
[Skull's self-cam.]
Good morning from Taiwan.
What am I doing in Taiwan right now?
I just came to guest on Running Man,
but here I am in Taiwan this morning.
Isn't this room...
so messy?
This is my room.
Oh my goodness,
what a mess from my shower.
Let's go check out other members' rooms.
Let's start with Ha Ha's room.
[Off to his best friend, Ha Ha's room.]
Ha Ha went to bed late last night
and his room is still locked.
- Hello.
- Let's go have breakfast.
[Good morning, Big-nose
and good morning, Kwang Soo.]
[Haroro doesn't seem to be
quite awake yet.]
Turn on the lights.
Let's see what you look like.
- Yeah, Kwang Soo.
- I woke up about three hours ago.
I read the paper with a cup of coffee
after my morning run.
You look like you just woke up.
Dong Hoon.
I'm still half asleep.
[Kwang Soo's morning raspberry.]
I said, knock it off.
Wow, this is a zoo!
[Outside their room window...
is a real zoo!]
[Right in front of the lawn are giraffes,
rhinos, and a variety of other wild beasts!]
- Good morning, Sung Jae.
- Did you sleep well last night?
What time did you get up?
Are you all ready to go?
[Sung Jae is ready to go and already
enjoying his morning cup of coffee.]
[Giving Sung Jae the tour
of the zoo out in the front lawn.]
The world really is a fascinating place.
- What is that, a rhino?
- This is a zoo!
Isn't this amazing?
There are a total of three
Kwang Soo's here.
It's like a real safari.
[Giraffe from Namyang... is trying to
communicate with giraffe from Taiwan.]
Come here.
Come here, it's me.
[What a weird Giraffe.]
[Feels that it needs to avoid
the weird Giraffe.]
Don't go!
No!
Don't go back to him!
I vow that I'll get my revenge!
I think the zebra's legs are too short.
I've seen some dwarf horses before,
but I've never seen a dwarf zebra before.
I think it's a cross breed between
a dwarf horse and a zebra.
It's because of the global warming,
and the pollution issue.
- That is?
- Yeah.
It's a degradation of the ecosystem.
You got 'degradation of the ecosystem'
just from seeing that zebra?
I'm not the one being weird, but
you're saying all sorts of weird things.
It's because you're nervous, isn't it?
You lied about liking those rides, didn't you?
- Yes, I do like my rides.
- If you do, then why are you being so weird?
[Now that we think about it,
the reason why we're even here...]
[is to face our terrorizing punishment.]
[That is the ultimate climax
of the 1470 Race.]
Are we really getting on that scary ride?
I heard that the punishment that we're
going to have to face is just unreal.
[The rumor can't even begin to describe
the extent of the terror.]
[The absolute terror of the punishment
that they will soon have to face.]
[And what is the secret hidden
behind the punishment?]
[The squad gathers together to get
ready to face their punishment.]
- Is that it?
- Good morning.
[They just can't seem to
tear their eyes away.]
- I think you it goes up and down.
- Is it connected?
It's those two tips over there.
It's perpendicular.
It's totally perpendicular to each other.
[A deep sigh...]
Welcome to Taiwan.
- Why did we have to come to Taiwan for this?
- Is this really worth the trip?
I thought that was an apartment tower
off in the distance.
That's the kind of thing you see
when an apartment is being built.
- That's an amusement ride?
- That's the ride.
- You'll see once you get there.
- I'm sorry I couldn't make the zero.
I had no idea that it was going to
warrant such a huge punishment.
- I'll make the zero from now on.
- I will make sure to make the zero.
[An unimaginable level of tragedy from
having failed the 1470 Race?]
What if I can't ride it?
Then can I sit it out?
Or we can play another game amongst ourselves
and have the loser ride it for everyone?
No!
- Wow, that's really scary.
- Let's go.
[Off to where the punishment will take place
with heavy steps.]
It's been a real long time since the bus
has been this quiet with the cameras rolling.
Everyone has this
ambiguous look on their faces
because they're unable to smile,
but they don't want to frown either.
See?
That's the ride.
- That's just absurd!
- Is that really one ride?
[Why is it that we've never been wrong
when it comes to things like this?]
Lee Sung Jae looks the most relaxed
out of all of us here right now.
He thought he wanted to come here,
but he said he's changed his mind.
- Do you like rides like this?
- Yes, I do.
But I've noticed that many actors
like to put up a false front.
I know that he says he's okay with it,
but let's see what he looks like later on.
- You saw me on the ride yesterday, right?
- Of course, I did.
You were cursing out loud.
- You were totally cursing out loud.
- You looked really scared yesterday.
[Actor, Sung Jae... his expression was
enough to express the fear he felt.]
I was just showing my respect
to the ride I was on.
I really can't tell if he's
telling the truth or not.
[Such a realistic sounding bluff.]
Sung Jae, just admit that you're scared.
All our members will be the first
to admit when we're scared.
- Chang Wook, you're scared too, aren't you?
- Yes.
I can tell that he's scared because
he just took a deep breath.
- What about you?
- My mind is just blank right now.
- Just be honest with us.
- He's not good on rides either.
[Finally arrives at the site
of their punishment.]
[Very heavy footsteps.]
[The fear keeps on closing in.]
I want to run away from here.
I want to make everyone faint
and just go back home.
If we would've just helped each other,
then none of us would've had to come here.
[Had we known this was going to happen,
we would've just helped each other...]
If we had just exchanged
whatever we didn't need.
- Why is a king acting so nervous?
- I'm really bad on these rides.
You really are so honest about
everything.
- That's the way to be.
- So I'm the only one who's good with rides?
You're not good on rides!
You're just pretending like you are
when in fact, you're not.
I can finally see it up close.
[Time to face their fears.]
Oh my, I can't go!
- What are you doing?
- Over my dead body!
- Just walk over me!
- I can't go any further.
[Seeing it up close
is paralyzing them with fear.]
This really is unbelievable.
I already feel sick to my stomach.
[A warning signal starts to go off.]
[1470 Race- The final punishment.]
[Screaming Condor- Terrorizing rollercoaster
that is known all around the world.]
- Why didn't you make the zero?
- You're the one who lost it for us!
[The moment where they resent each
other for having to come here.]
Wow, I've never had to go down to
the basement to go on a ride before.
[This is the final and ultimate punishment
that the losers of 1470 Race must face.]
- I bet the front seat is the scariest.
- Are we all riding it together?
We're not, are we?
[Half their sanity
is already out the window.]
As you all are already aware,
this is the most famous ride in Taiwan.
With the height of 56m,
and the speed of 105km per hour.
You will have a group mission to complete,
rather than just a team mission.
You will have a group mission to complete.
[What?
A mission?]
There's another mission?
If you succeed on your first try,
then you get to go home right away.
[Absolutely ridiculous!]
Let's just go home!
- They tricked us!
- Are you kidding me!
- It's a very simple mission.
- Riding it just once is hard enough.
Do you see the two 'R' flags on
the posts on either side?
You just need to look at the flags
on those two posts.
All you have to do is correctly guess
the number written below the flags.
- It's another number mission.
- You like these rides, don't you?
Okay, I'll do it.
- Chang Wook, you can sit up front.
- I can't believe there's a mission.
You didn't tell us that
there was going to be a mission!
- Suk Jin is seriously angry.
- Seriously!
[Big-nose explodes in rage.]
First, you must decide
where you're going to sit.
It's two people per row.
- Want to sit up front with me?
- Yes, go sit.
[Jae Suk is shoved forward to
be chosen to sit in the front row.]
- Why did you shove me?
- You'll be safe with me.
[Extreme state of nervousness
right from the moment of seat selection.]
- Let's get this done in first try.
- Think of your parents and your children.
- Let's get this done.
- Get it done on our first try!
[Let's get this done!]
[We'll get it done on our first try!
We are united as one!]
- Chang Wook, get yourself together!
- You have to pull yourself together.
You can't lose your
sanity right now, Chang Wook.
- Chang Wook, pull yourself together.
- We have to work together as one.
I suggest that for this mission,
we forget our formalities.
Yoo Jae Suk, pull yourself together!
- Okay, I will.
- Everyone pull yourselves together!
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Pull yourself together!
You'd better seriously
pull yourself together.
- Do you hear me?
- You dare to shake me?
Lee Sung Jae.
Pull yourself together.
[This time, it's time to tell Sung Jae
to pull himself together.]
Chang Wook, you do it too.
Do it to me.
- Jae Suk...
- Do it.
Pull yourself together.
Listen to me, Yoo Jae Suk!
Ji Suk Jin!
Pull yourself together right now.
[Dropping formalities isn't an easy feat
for this polite and sweet young actor.]
Tell Lee Sung Jae to pull
himself together.
[But this is my senior, Lee Sung Jae...]
[But no one is exempt from this moment.]
Lee Sung Jae, pull yourself together!
[Lee Sung Jae, pull yourself together!]
[Okay, I'll pull myself together...]
You bastard! You'd better
do a good job, you bastard!
Do you hear me!
How do you think this makes me feel,
you bastard!
[A passionate round of cheers
for everyone in the group.]
- I can't believe...
- Lee Sung Jae.
Lee Sung Jae,
stop bluffing and take a good look.
- Stop bluffing, do you hear me?
- Wow, he's such a good actor.
[This actor truly is a master
when it comes to acting.]
Donte afraid.
If you're feeling afraid, then
start slapping each other like this.
[A cheerful round of slapping to
help alleviate some of their fear.]
Lee Sung Jae, pull yourself together.
[If they could only transform
their fear into courage...]
[Cheer going a bit overboard.]
[Transforming their fear into rage.]
I'm not afraid!
[These guys are so weird...]
Pull yourself together!
Is everyone ready?
- You can get it done on your first try.
- We'll get it done on our first try!
Yes, you really can do that.
[His bravery is crumbled
by a tiny little bee.]
- You guys are driving me crazy.
- Let's get it done on our first try.
[Will this cowardly group of men be able to
successfully complete the mission?]
[Time to board the ride.]
[This portion of show was safely filmed thanks
to the help and cooperation from Taiwan.]
[First row- Jae Suk and Sung Jae.]
[Second row- Chang Wook and Kwang Soo.]
My legs are just dangling.
Is there a footrest?
[Third row- Skull and Ha Ha.]
[Fourth row- Big nose.]
No, no, no!
[It's okay, it's automatically
going to tighten up.]
Please.
I'm sweating bullets.
[Already soaked down with sweat
before the ride even starts.]
- We only have one chance!
- Think of this as our final chance!
Pull yourself together, Ji Suk Jin!
Pull yourself together, Lee Sung Jae!
Pull yourself together, Ji Chang Wook!
Pull yourself together, Ha Dong Hoon!
Pull yourself together, Skull!
Pull yourself together, Yoo Jae Suk!
[At the speed of 105km per hour.]
[And the height of 56m.]
[Conquer all your fears...]
[And check the number beneath the flags.]
Please!
Concentrate!
[Will they be able to conquer their fears
to successfully complete the mission?]
[1470 Race- The final mission.]
[Go!]
[Starts off at an unbelievable speed!]
[As soon as the ride takes off,
the numbers are attached to the posts.]
[Mission numbers- Nine and Five.]
[Off to a fast start.]
[A 90 degree climb.]
[A complete out of body experience.]
[Giraffe's fear has been transformed
into feelings of rage.]
I can't do this.
[Skyrockets into the sky.]
[At zero gravity.]
[What... a perfect day to be riding on
a rollercoaster.]
[And a dead drop back down
to the ground.]
What the hell is this!
[Sucked back down backwards!]
[Passes by the mission numbers
at top speed.]
[Father Big-nose is asleep
with his mouth hanging wide open.]
[This time, they're pulled back up
backwards at a 90 degree angle.]
[Seven octaves of screaming.]
[Facing the ground while hanging in midair.]
[Pulled backwards as if pulled back
by a taut bow.]
[And falls back down
to the ground at top speed.]
[Falling at the speed of 105km per hour.]
[Will they even be able to see the numbers?]
[Even with their eyes wide open, the
numbers are flashing by at 105km an hour.]
[Big-nose is in the REM cycle of his sleep.]
[Sung Jae screams out
at the top of his lungs.]
[But still manages to keep
his eyes wide open.]
[Has Skull passed out with
his eyes wide open?]
Mommy!
How are we going to do the mission!
[Comes to a sudden and an abrupt stop.]
[Father, it's all over now.
It's time to wake up.]
Did you see the numbers?
[The Giraffe is dry heaving.]
We can't do this!
[I... survived...]
[Unable to stop
the frantic beating of their hearts.]
Is everyone okay?
- Are you okay?
- I thought...
I thought we were slowly going to go
back and fall back down like this.
I really can't go back on that thing.
This is over.
Okay, it's time to verify the answer.
Did you get to see the numbers?
We'll start with Kwang Soo.
Please step forward.
[Starts with Kwang Soo to verify
the answer.]
- Here's your question.
- Okay.
What do you get when you
multiply the two numbers?
[What do you get when you
multiply the two numbers?]
[Nine and Five.
The answer is, 45.]
45.
[Kwang Soo saw the numbers!
Succeeds the mission.]
Kwang Soo, please don't share your answer.
[Chang Wook's turn.]
What do you get when you
multiply the two numbers?
45.
[Chang Wook saw it too!
Succeeds the mission.]
What do you get when you
multiply the two numbers?
45.
[Sung Jae also succeeds the mission.]
What do you get when you
multiply the two numbers?
[Nervous...]
45.
Okay, Yoo Jae Suk.
[Big-brother manages to see what he
needs even through his REM cycle.]
What do you get when you
multiply the two numbers?
45.
What do you get when you
multiply the two numbers?
45.
[Jae Suk and Skull
also succeeds the mission.]
[Ha Ha is the only one left remaining.]
What do you get when you
multiply the two numbers?
[If Ha Ha correctly guesses the answer,
then it's a mission success.]
I seriously couldn't even open my eyes
because I was so scared.
[Ha Ha kept his eyes tightly closed
during the whole ride.]
I just heard about the five, but I
don't know what the other number is.
I just heard about the five,
but I don't know what the other number is.
[What?
You didn't hear?]
[What? Then do we
have to go back on that thing?]
In that case...
[They fail the mission because of
Ha Ha having kept his eyes closed.]
Since Ha Ha didn't see the numbers,
you'll have to get back on the ride.
[It's back on the ride for everyone.]
Look!
I really think that the front row
is the scariest spot to be sitting.
Shout out loud what the numbers are.
When you first start,
this is what it sounds like.
[How it sounds on the way up,
and how it sounds on the way down.]
[How are they going to scream out the number
when they're too busy screaming?]
The rest of us all got it right!
- Then let's just live here!
- What did you say?
[What else can I do about it
when I can't even open my eyes!]
- Okay, select where you're going to sit.
- Chang Wook, was it tolerable for you?
- What?
- Was it tolerable for you?
- I seriously couldn't open my eyes.
- I didn't open my eyes once either.
I thought it would be worse to close my eyes,
so I couldn't even blink my eyes.
Then sit up front.
You can sit up front, right?
[How can you even say such a thing to me?]
Then sit up front.
You can sit up front, right?
Why are you soaked in sweat?
- Maybe he was really scared.
- I think he was really scared.
But you know what he said to me
the moment we got off?
'That wasn't even that scary.'
[He can't stop his bluffing
even through all that sweat.]
- It's because you're scared.
- This ride is terrifying!
- Why am I the only person sweating?
- You're covered in cold sweat.
[No kidding.]
Lee Sung Jae,
just admit it if you're scared.
Stop breaking out in cold sweats like that.
- I'm not scared.
- Look at all the sweat covering your arms!
Wow, he is like the master of bluffing.
He sweated more than any one of us
but he keeps insisting that he's not scared.
I'm not scared.
That's why I rode in the front row.
You look to the left,
and you look to the right, okay?
[Look to the right... okay!]
Okay, please get back on the ride.
[Punishment mission- Second attempt.]
Why am I the only one sweating like this?
Sung Jae, that's cold sweat
because you're nervous and scared.
- This is fun.
- You think this is fun?
Yes, it's fun.
Wow, we have to get it done
no matter what.
I'll try to keep my eyes open.
I seriously can't do this again.
Over my dead body!
[Punishment mission- Second attempt.]
Fighting!
Wow, this is so scary.
[Front row- Once again,
Jae Suk and Sung Jae.]
[Second row- Ha Ha and Kwang Soo.]
[Third row- Skull and Chang Wook.]
[Fourth row- Father Big nose.]
[Loosening up his mouth to
prepare himself for all the screaming.]
[Punishment mission- Second attempt.]
[There will not be another failure!]
[It's just as fast the second time around!]
[But their expressions are
looking even more stiff!]
[This time around,
the number are, four and seven.]
[Kwang Soo's owl-eyed plan fails.]
[Father Big-nose is talking in his sleep.]
Please!
Look at the numbers!
[Will everyone see the numbers
this time around?]
[Ha Ha's hawk like gaze.]
[I'm going to see the numbers
even if it kills me!]
It's four and seven!
Four!
[Four!
Chang Wook's desperate shout out.]
[But the front row is too busy
screaming to hear Chang Woo's pleas.]
[At the maximum speed.]
Seven!
[Current speed- Over 105km an hour.]
[But they seemed to have seen the numbers
the second time around.]
[Everyone's shouting out the numbers that
they saw at the top of their lungs.]
[But unable to comprehend due
to all the blood curdling screams.]
Four!
[Even father's eyes are wide open.]
Seven times four is twenty-eight!
I saw it!
[An amazing transformation
compared to their first attempt.]
- I saw it!
- I saw it.
Mission... success!
[Completely soaked in sweat.]
[I can't get back on this ride again.]
I feel a little nauseous.
I can't ride that for the third time.
Riding it two times in a row
has me feeling nauseous.
Just admit that you were scared.
- No, it's not that.
- He keeps expressing his fear in other ways.
- He's now saying that he's feeling queasy.
- What's wrong with you?
- You're sweatier than any one of us.
- Just admit that you're scared.
Riding it two times in a row
has me feeling nauseous.
You all know what the numbers are, right?
- I saw it.
- I saw it with both my eyes.
- I saw both the numbers.
- I didn't see the one on the right.
[What the hell... is he saying?]
- You have to look at both the numbers.
- I couldn't see the one on the right.
- You have to look at both!
- You told me to look at the one on the left!
- So I just looked at the one on the left.
- You have to look at both the numbers!
[Oh my God!]
[Sung Jae... are you serious?]
Did you see how Chang Wook
was glaring at him?
Lee Sung Jae, pull yourself together!
I can't ride that for the third time.
[Ah... what are we going to
do about this?]
[Time to check Kwang Soo's answer.]
- He's lying.
- He screamed out the answer.
How was I supposed to hear him
when I was busy screaming myself?
How could you not have heard him?
[Please let it be a lie...]
Here's your question.
What do you get
when you add up the two numbers?
Eleven.
I'll ask Lee Sung Jae last.
Okay, Ha Ha's turn.
What do you get
when you add up the two numbers?
The question is different.
It's a different question?
[Even the question is different?]
Eleven.
[Oh no...]
[What were the numbers?]
Eleven.
[The can succeed the mission only if
Sung Jae can correctly answer the question.]
- Please don't lie to us.
- Seriously, don't lie to us.
[Their fate lies in Sung Jae's answer.]
[If Sung Jae can't answer the question,
then they have to get back on the ride.]
[Please...]
[Please answer the question correctly.]
[What was Sung Jae's answer?]
[If Sung Jae fails, then they
must all get back on the ride.]
I just guessed the other number.
- What were the two numbers?
- Four and seven.
- Four and what?
- Seven.
[He's smiling?]
[What is the result of their mission?]
Everyone answered the question
correctly.
[Correct answer]
[We survived!]
[Sung Jae's acting had everyone fooled!]
What do you get
when you add up the two numbers?
Eleven.
[Correct answer]
I really couldn't get back on that ride.
I seriously can't get back on that thing.
- I guessed and I got it right.
- You're such a liar!
[What will Running Man
have to face this time?]
Since you successfully
completed your mission...
You have four hours to pack up
before we leave.
We can't just leave like this
when this is our trip to Taiwan.
[Their love for Taiwan hasn't even
been explored yet.]
Are we seriously just going
to go home?
Because we were all so consumed by
our fear for this ride
we didn't even get to enjoy ourselves
since having arrived here.
But aren't we all so happy now
to be here?
He may never have been afraid of rides,
but he is definitely fearful of this one.
[First time being fearful of amusement
park rides in the 45 years of his life.]
You're the only one who didn't see
both the numbers the second time around.
We'd like to thank everyone in Taiwan for
welcoming us and allowing us to film the show.
- Thank you!
- I love Taiwan!
[First ever international punishment
now comes to a close...]
[They thought everything was going to
go back to peace and ease...]
[Incheon Songdo 'O' Hotel.]
[Heir to G Constructions, Lee Kwang Soo.]
[The eldest son of K Hospital,
Kim Jong Kook.]
[Second generation CEO of
'D' Stocks and Bonds, Ha Ha.]
[The big man of
the hospitality industry, Gary.]
[Second generation to
a wine conglomerate, Ji Suk Jin.]
[Second generation real estate mogul
in Gangnam, Yoo Jae Suk.]
[A twisted fate that these six men
have come to face.]
- This is so good.
- What do you think you're doing right now?
[The queen of weekend dramas,
Lee Yoo Ri.]
All you ever care about is eating!
Is food all you ever need to survive on?
Are you a pig or a cow?
How are you any different than an animal?
This is all your fault.
Ever since you came into my life,
my life became a filthy mess!
No... you can't be thinking...
- Don't do this.
- You brought this upon yourself.
Is this what you were thinking?
[Just what in the world is happening!]
Every morning... I start
the day with a game of pocket ball.
With a hot cup of coffee
over a foreign newspaper.
And also...
[A whack to the head the
moment she flies into the room.]
[What the heck?]
Did that hurt?
[A dynamic actress, Choi Yeo Jin.]
- Does that hurt?
- Why are you doing this?
- Tell me how much it hurts!
- What's wrong with her!
- Does that hurt?
- She just hit me for real! What is this!
You hurt me for real, too, you bastard!
[It's only been five seconds
since their meeting.]
[Totally confused.]
What do you mean, who am I?
I'm your girlfriend!
- Let's just die together. Come with me.
- Wait!
Why would I die?
- Why are you doing this?
- Eat it.
- Said, eat it!
- What is wrong with her!
[Kwang Soo, I can't ever forgive you...]
Who is it?
[The epitome of a character actress,
Seo Woo.]
[What is this?]
Did you think that you could threaten me
with a measly file like that?
Excuse me?
A man like you...
I can bring to an end in one blow!
You know that I can do whatever
I set my mind to doing, don't you?
- Don't you?
- What is going on here?
Quiet.
Because I'm already...
- What's wrong?
- My appendix...
What's wrong with you?
[You seriously don't know
why I'm being like this?]
11,026... 11,027...
11,028...
[The queen of all ice queens,
Yoo In Young.]
- 11,029.
- Hey.
Move to another gym.
I've never... even met her before.
Not only is he ugly,
but he's dumb, too.
Why are you saying that to me?
I feel so filthy and dirty
whenever I see you!
Get out of here!
[Frozen in place.]
[I got you now, little kiddo...]
Jong Kook.
Do you even care for me?
[Huge acting skills in a tiny package,
Kim Min Seo.]
Do you even know what I've been
reduced to doing for you?
You only care about yourself, don't you?
I even stopped all the hospital sponsors
just so you could become the next director!
I even fired some of the doctors!
- What are you going to do now?
- Please stop this.
What?
Stop what?
I can do much worse than this!
You fool!
So that no one can lay their
finger on you!
That's a really nice wine glass.
Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo?
- Aren't you Ji Hyo?
- Do you know me?
- You're Song Ji Hyo.
- My name is Min So Hee.
['Temptation of a wife' returns-
Blank So Hee.]
[What...]
I'm going to lose it.
- Min So Hee.
- You put a mole on your face!
- How dare you touch me?
- I thought that was a pimple.
Jung Gyo Min sent you, didn't he?
[Trying really hard to
maintain his straight face.]
That's right, Jung Gyo Min sent me.
He sent me here to kill you.
Jung Gyo Min sent me here to kill you!
Did you just confess that
Jung Gyo Min sent you?
Yeah, that's right.
I took the job for 50,000 Won!
I came here to kill you for 50,000 Won!
I'm here to kill you, Min So Hee!
[I'm the actor!]
What are you going to do about it?
I vow to oust this despicable human being
and go to the depths of hell myself.
Just go to hell by yourself.
Just go by yourself.
You really do have a mole on your face.
You put a mole on your face.
Wow, Song Ji Hyo...
This is nothing compared to
the pain that you gave me!
- Here, take this!
- How is this nothing?
- I asked if it hurts!
- It totally hurts!
Whenever I see you...
I get so pissed and angry!
Enough!
I'm so sick and tired of this.
Seeing you sickens me to my stomach.
- Pick it up.
- Tell me what wrong have I done?
Stop blaming me...
and blame yourself for being
so damned attractive!
Stop being so obsessed with Song Ji Hyo.
I want you to love me, too!
[Money, love, betrayal, and revenge...]
Why are you taking so many pills?
- I'm going to end everything.
- What are you taking?
What is this?
They're just vitamins.
Jong Kook.
Why can't you understand
how I feel for you?
I really love you.
I even love the goop in your eyes.
I loved you with all I had.
Leave.
This is my studio, and I've
never once hid my feelings from you.
- Why are you doing this!
- Bastard.
Please recognize the love
that I have for you!
[These six women with
likely reasons of their own...]
[How will this drama end?]
You can only love me!
I'm the real thing!
[SBS Running Series,
It's Okay, It's Heirs.]
Subtitles by DramaFever