[A whisper of a breeze at
the mouth of Seomjingang River.]
[A small village on the outskirts
of Jiri Mountain.]
[Jeollanam-do Province's
Gokseong-eup Daepyeong-ri.]
- Hello.
- You've come a long way.
Yes, I've been wanting to come
visit Jiri Mountain for a long time.
Wow, look at all the beautiful
fall leaves.
What's going on here?
Are we the only ones here?
What is this? You can't team up two
of the weakest members together.
This place is really nice.
Where is this place?
Look at the beautiful mountain.
That's not Jiri Mountain, is it?
- It's Jiri Mountain?
So the car brought us to
Jiri Mountain?
What are we doing here?
We're at Jiri Mountain.
- What are we doing here?
- Take a look behind you.
- Look behind us?
- It's a senior citizen center!
- Isn't that a senior citizen center?
- Why are we at a senior citizen center?
Me?
I think I'm supposed to go into
the barbershop.
What's going on here?
[Blank Ji arrives at a gas station.]
Hello.
With the arrival of all the members
at Jiri Mountain for a visit
we will now commence the
2014 Running Man Event Race.
We came all the way to Jiri Mountain
to do an event?
For the first event, the owner of this
gas station himself sent out the invitation.
[Blank Ji's first event is at the
invitation of the gas station owner.]
- I'm the Village Head.
- Hello, Sir.
Hello, Sir.
[A grand bow greeting
to the village head.]
You have to give me a heads up
before you do that.
Market's 40th anniversary?
[Jae Suk has been summoned
by the market owner.]
Jae Suk!
It's so nice to meet you!
- It's really nice to meet you.
- Hello.
[A warm greeting from all the neighbors.]
- Is today the market's 40th anniversary?
- Yeah.
Even though it's been more than 40 years,
we're just going to say that it's our 40th.
- What did you write on your hand?
- 40th anniversary.
[A cheat note to remind herself
that it's the 40th anniversary.]
- Take good care of it for us, Jae Suk.
- Do not worry, Ma'am.
Leave it to me,
and I will take great care to
ensure your 40th anniversary event
goes perfectly without any glitches.
Yes, okay.
- Gary, you're here.
- Yes, Sir.
[Gary has been summoned by
the owner of the barbershop.]
I've been operating my barbershop
for over 30 years now.
- Really?
- I need your help getting more customers.
Should I stand out here and do this?
Ah, you want me to promote
your gas station?
This place is famous for the dogwood fruit?
[Big-nose and Ha Ha to help promote
Dogwood Fruit Celebration Event.]
[Running Man Event Race- Start.]
[However...]
I'm supposed to stand here
by myself...
and promote this gas station?
I want all the staff members to
fill up their gas tanks right now.
- Hello, Ji Hyo.
- Oh my goodness!
Oh my goodness!
[Someone's here?]
[The idol who took all of Asia by storm,
Super Junior's Leeteuk and Kyu Hyun.]
[The golden idol boys, Super Junior,
are here at Jiri Mountain gas station.]
I can't believe this! Are you
guys going to be doing this with me?
- We came here to help you.
- Really?
- Can you pretend you're happy to see me too?
- Kyu Hyun! So glad to see you!
- Wow, I can't believe this.
- Let's go over here.
[But what's on the wheelbarrow?]
[A must for any event-
A karaoke machine.]
[Singers- Song Ji Hyo, Leeteuk, Kyu Hyun.
Will sing any requested songs!]
[Then who could be the
barbershop helper?]
Bobby! Jung In!
[Groove-filled event singers!]
[Soul daddy, Bobby Kim.]
[Soul queen, Jung In.]
[The top soul musicians to help out
at the barbershop event.]
I think this is a karaoke machine...
- Wait a minute.
- Did you not get any sleep last night?
What's this karaoke machine for?
We're going to promote by singing?
But... Bobby doesn't really know
any Korean songs.
- I know a few.
- He only knows pop music.
Am I not allowed to sing
pop music?
- Wow, dogwood fruit extracts.
- You and I both need it.
Is anyone here?
- Excuse me!
- Is someone headed this way?
- You!
- Hello!
[The sexy performance queen, Narsha.]
- Wow, it's Narsha!
- This is so heavy.
- What are you dragging over?
- Why are they making a guest do this!
- Move, and I'll help you.
- What is this?
- I wanted to make a grand entrance.
- 'Sexy red dogwood fruit celebration.'
Event facilitators are Ji Suk Jin,
Ha Ha and Narsha?
This is one very fierce girl.
Okay, we're good!
We're all set now.
- Today's the day! We're going to win.
- Why did they team me up with you two?
Our ages combined is way over
a hundred years old.
- Don't worry about a thing.
- Let's come up with a name for our team.
- How about 'Yittagu'?
- Okay, let's go with that.
Yittagu... we are Yittagu.
(Meaning, 'We are here.')
- It's be a new sating of sorts.
- We are still Yittagu... (We still got it.)
- We are Yittagu.
- Dogwood fruit is Yittagu.
Yittagu Cross!
('Yittagu'- Almost a state of being.)
Push harder.
It's suddenly getting very heavy.
- Is it getting heavy?
- There you are!
[Singers for the supermarket's
40th anniversary are...]
[The heart of Korea's rock scene-
Kim Kyung Ho.]
[Impressive vocalist, Kim Yeon Woo.]
Okay, that's good.
That's far enough.
Come say hello to all the
grandmothers.
- She's the supermarket owner.
- Hello.
- Take good care of it for me, Kim Yeon Woo.
- He's Kim Yeon Woo.
- Yes, and I'm Kim Kyung Ho.
- Kim Kyung Ho!
- Take good care of me, okay?
- Thank you, and of course.
- Help me promote my store, okay?
- Ma'am, do you know what this man does?
- He sings... he's a singer.
- Yes, he is.
[She knows that they're singers!]
- Do you know what Kim Kyung Ho sings?
- I don't know any of his songs.
I'd be more surprised if you knew
my songs.
Ma'am I'm going to do the promotional event
with Kim Kyung Ho and Kim Yeon Woo
- so don't worry about a thing.
- A promotional event?
- It's her market's 40th anniversary.
- It's her 40th anniversary?
To celebrate the market's
40th anniversary
you just need to accept the villagers'
requests and sing songs for them.
That shouldn't be a problem
with these two singers here.
But we will only accept the songs
if you score 70 points or above.
Seventy points.
You have to sing for ten people.
[Must sing a total of ten requested songs
in order to succeed the mission.]
But if the songs are being requested by
elders, we may not know a lot of the songs
so what do we do then?
There may be a lot of songs
that we may not be familiar with.
[This team is worried about
the same issue.]
[Must sing the songs that are
requested by the villagers.]
- You can only sing the requested songs.
- Bobby's here to promote his new album.
[While they're all worried about the songs
that will be requested of them to sing...]
[But there's one team that
doesn't seem to be worried...]
[The star of that voice is...]
[She's here!]
[Trot music's newest human battery,
Hong Jin Young.]
I'm a woman who needs no introduction.
The goddess of events, Hong Jin Young!
I can't do things like this,
but Jin Young's so good at it!
- I wish I could learn from her.
- We totally lucked out.
We got so lucky with Jin Young
for this event!
[Kkuk and Kwang Soo hit the jackpot.]
We're here all the way from Seoul.
Hong-Kook-Soo is here from Seoul.
That's a good name.
[The new group name, Hong-Kook-Soo.]
[Lead singer, Jin Young's brilliant idea.]
[What an odd girl...]
- Ma'am, we wish you great health!
- Happy new lunar year!
Let's just keep going.
[Sorry, young man.]
Jin Young really is great.
[The event goddess leans back
in a relaxed pose on the dolly.]
Who else but Hong Jin Young
would do something like this?
You're a tad bit embarrassed, aren't you?
- Maybe we should turn down the volume.
- Let's turn it down a little bit.
Hong-Kook-Soo is here.
We're here to sing our songs for you.
Put some muscle into it!
[Jin Young's singing voice rings
loud and clear throughout the village.]
[The event goddess has come
to Jiri Mountain.]
[Running Man Event Race.]
[The event singers are ready... but
there aren't any audiences to be found.]
Come and gas up your cars!
- We'll sing your requested songs!
- Come and gas up your cars!
The gas is really cheap here!
- Come this way!
- Stop hesitating and come here!
Sir, come this way!
Sir, we'll even sing for you!
This is trouble.
[When are they ever going to
get to sing their ten songs?]
[Just then... a car
pulls up at the gas station.]
- Sir, where are you going?
- Hello.
- If you're not busy, we can sing for you.
- We're taking song requests right now.
- Then will you sing me a song?
- Yes, that sounds great!
[Their first customer!]
- I'll help you.
- Be careful getting out of the car.
Yes, please come this way.
Ma'am, what song would you
like to hear?
- Tell me what song you'd like to hear.
- 'What's wrong with my age.'
We have all the songs here.
What would you like to hear?
-  'What's wrong with my age.'
- That's the title of the song.
['What's wrong with my age.'
is the title of the song!]
- She wasn't talking about her age.
- Okay, 'What's wrong with my age.'
Let's find the song.
- Ma'am, 'What's wrong with my age.'
[Team Super Blank Ji.
First request- 'What's wrong with my age.']
Ma'am, this song's for you!
[The song's starting...]
[They don't know the song,
so making it up as they go.]
[No regards to the beat...
and no regards to the rhythm.]
- Is that right?
- Yeah, I think you're good.
[Just then, the grandmother
starts to leave!]
- Ma'am, don't go!
- I don't think she likes it!
[She can't seem to handle
listening to their singing anymore.]
[Just get in the car.]
[Grandmother...]
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Ma'am.
[But she still leaves behind a kind word.]
[Dogwood fruit event-
Still advertising their singing event.]
- Hello!
- We're here! Team Yittagu is here!
No, you can't just leave!
- Sir!
- The ultimate singing trio.
[Finding an audience is really hard...]
- We are Yittagu!
- Dogwood fruit is Yittagu!
Ji Suk Jin's comeback
after 22 years is Yittagu!
We are here.
We have come to see you.
We are here from Seoul.
[Jin Young continues to sing out
to promote their event.]
- They're all over there.
- We're here from Seoul.
- They're doing something with persimmons.
- Hello, Ma'am.
- Hello.
- Hello, I see you're hard at work already.
- You're singer, Hong Jin Young!
- Yes, I sing 'Love's battery'!
[These ladies recognizes Jin Young
for her trot music.]
- We're Team Hong-Kook-Soo.
- What is your favorite type of Kook-Soo?
- Hong Kook Soo!
- Your favorite type is 'Hong-Kook-Soo'!
[Jin Young gets the ladies excited
with her sweet charm.]
Request a song you like,
and we'll sing it for you.
- We like that song by Lee Mi Ja.
- Lee Mi Ja? Then 'Camellia Lady'?
- Yes, that's the song I want to hear.
- Okay, we'll sing 'Camellia Lady' for you.
Should we sing the disco version?
How about we sing the livelier version
and move our bodies a bit?
[Event goddess' know-how:
Disco version to liven up the mood.]
[Team Hong-Kook-Soo.
First request- Camellia Lady by Lee Mi Ja.]
[Spin and spin around.]
[A song to help alleviate the exhaustion
from persimmon picking.]
[The ladies seem to be happy
with the unexpected gift of song.]
[Jin Young's voice helps to
up the excitement ante.]
[A successful score of 82 points.]
Grandmother, we got 82 points!
Grandmother seems to know the beat.
Wasn't that a nice song?
[While Team Hong-Kook-Soo already
succeeds at their first song...]
[One team is still working on
coming up with their team name.]
How about 'Sum-Jin-Kang'?
- Sum-Jin-Kang.
- That is so simple.
There's no need to think too hard about it.
Let's go with Sum-Jin-Kang.
Today's market day, so many people
will be coming in by the bus.
- So you'll get a lot of audience members.
- All these ladies are here already though.
[Quite a few ladies are already here
with it being market day in the village.]
We're Team Sum-Jin-Kang.
We're going to sing your requested songs to
help celebrate the market's 40th anniversary.
There's no need to look so frightened.
Ladies, there's no need to be so afraid.
These two men are really great singers.
- Which song would you like to hear?
- 'Andong Station.'
- Andong Station?
- I've never even heard of the song.
I've never heard of such a song.
Are you sure it's not 'Home Station'?
[All the ladies seem to be familiar
with the requested song.]
- Let's see if we can find it.
- I've never heard of such a song before.
There it is!
It is 'Andong Station.'
- Ma'am, is it 'From Andong Station'?
- Yes.
They all shout out, 'Yes'.
[All the ladies agrees in unison.]
Okay, ma'am.
- What are you doing?
- I'm just taking a look.
[Kyung Ho searches the song on
the internet to practice.]
Ugh, seriously.
- It's a traditional trot song.
- Right?
[The rocker with over 20 years of experience
looks more serious than ever before.]
Ma'am, is this the correct song?
- They don't seem to know Jin Sung's song.
- Excuse me?
We're really sorry, but we
don't know who Jin Sung is.
- This song is really popular lately.
- This song is?
Sis... I can't believe I
called her 'Sis'.
- Good, I like it when I get called that.
- Yes, of course.
Then Sis... Team Sum-Jin-Kang
will sing it for you.
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang.
First request- 'From Andong Station.']
[The grandmothers start clapping
along to the song's melody.]
There you go!
I think you're doing it right.
That's good.
- Isn't he good?
- Just follow the beat and sing along.
Isn't 11 o'clock in the morning
too early to be dancing?
[Who cares about the time?
Let's just have some fun!]
[Kyung Ho is encouraged by
the grandmothers' excitement.]
[He was doing so well...
then he stumbles.]
[Hm...]
- He's good, right?
- No, he's bad!
- He's going to ruin my hearing.
- He's bad?
[Kyung Ho remains oblivious to their
opinion, and just keeps on singing.]
Wait, you're doing okay,
but she just said, 'He's bad!'
[Grandmother's blunt comment,
'He's bad!']
[Even these top musicians can't escape
the panel of judges' sharp comments.]
- Yes, I'm so sorry.
- Her one line comment, 'He's bad!'
- I'm breaking out into a cold sweat.
- Can't you even sing that?
[While the god of rock and legendary
vocalist breaks out in a cold sweat...]
[Team Yittagu has already
succeeded two of their ten songs.]
- Welcome, Ma'am.
- Ma'am!
Hello, Ma'am.
Can you please stay for a song?
- Please come this way.
- What for?
We're taking song requests right now,
so can you request a song?
You can request any song you'd like.
How about 'Oh my' by Jang Yoon Jung?
- That's sounds good.
- Okay!
Grandmother, have a bite of
the dogwood fruit.
[A bite of the dogwood fruit first.]
- Let us sing you a song before you go.
- Okay, let me hear it.
- I'm here on vacation from Suwon.
- You're here from Suwon?
We'll sing you a song
to help you enjoy your trip here.
- Thank you.
- Yes, here we go!
Team Yittagu, let's hear it!
[Team Yittagu- Third request:
'Oh my' by Jang Yoon Jung.]
- Ma'am, what is your name?
- My name is Lee Teuk Shil.
Grandmother Lee Teuk Shil,
wishing you a lifetime of health!
[The adorable grandmother responds to
the song with a bright smile on her face.]
[Team Yittagu's main vocalist, Narsha,
and the backup chorus, Big-nose and Ha Ha.]
[A special performance for the sole
enjoyment of this grandmother.]
- What's our score?
- Please stay healthy, Grandmother!
- 93 points!
- Okay, 93 points!
[Three successful songs in a row
thanks to the grandmother from Suwon.]
Would you like to sing the song,
Abracadabra, with us before you go?
Allow me to sing a fun song
just for you before you go.
- Mother, you're going to like this song.
- You just need to cross your arms like this.
[Narsha's glint in her eyes transforms.]
[The dance that took Korea by storm...
Is it about to happen right here?]
[There she goes!]
[If her looks could kill...]
[Narsha's hot Jiri Mountain performance
is about to bring the place down in flames.]
Grandmother, just follow my moves.
[Is she about to do the dance?]
[Grandmother is feeling the groove!]
- Make it more sexy!
- You're doing great!
Look at me like you want to eat me up.
[Grandmother isn't falling too far
behind Narsha's sexy moves.]
A little sexier!
[While Team Yittagu is burning up the place
with Grandmother's sexy moves...]
[Hong Jin Young's battery
is still going strong.]
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi's fourth request.
'Everyone cha cha cha.' by Seol Woon Do.]
[Barbershop, hip-hop and
trot music's newest harmony.]
We wanted to know if you had a song
request that we can sing for you.
'That human being.'
- Are you talking about Bobby Kim's song?
- Yes.
- Then I mean, 'That love.'
- Yes!
Okay, then can you step outside?
Let's all step outside and hear him sing.
Excuse me, did you say,
'That love'?
Don't you even know your own song?
What's with this guy?
Okay.
Bobby, since this is your own song,
you have to get a perfect score.
[Perfect score singing his own song?]
That's me on the screen.
- I'm that man on the screen.
- Just sing.
[The original singer of the song misses
the beat while in the midst of self bragging.]
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi's fifth song.
'That love' by Bobby Kim.]
[What kind of a song is this?]
[Singing the requested song
with all their might.]
- That was beautiful.
- Let's see the score.
Please let it be 100 points.
- 88 points.
- 88 points!
- You should've gotten a perfect score!
- We just need 70 points or above.
- Even if we succeeded, you still...
- I still did my best!
You're a really great singer.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
[Team Super Blank Ji's sixth song-
'Me and the 18 year old' by Baek Nan Ah.]
Wow, she's so embarrassing.
[But tone deaf Blank Ji is still
giving it everything she has.]
[Kyu Hyun may need to give CPR after
Blank Ji is finished singing this simple song.]
[Lucky for them, these kind ladies
seems to have enjoyed their singing.]
95 points!
[Unbelievable!
95 points!]
[How unbelievable!]
[Team Super Blank Ji successfully
sings their sixth song!]
We've enjoyed listening to you sing,
and we'll fill up our gas tank before we go.
Thank you, you're the best!
You're the best!
Please come this way.
[Successfully sings their song, and also drum
up some business- Two birds with one stone!]
- What is all this so early in the morning.
- He wants to know what we're doing.
He wants to know what
this is all about.
[While tone deaf Blank Ji's mission
successfully carries on...]
[The legendary vocalist is...]
Am I singing this right?
No, he's wrong!
[He's singing it all wrong.]
I'm literally re-composing this song.
- 94 points.
- Oh my!
[What? 94 points?]
How are you getting those high points?
When you sang like crap?
You think our score is too high
for having sang like crap?
[These panel of judges can't seem to
comprehend how they got their high score.]
Then we'll sing you
a proper trot song this time.
[This won't do anymore.
Time to sing a real trot song.]
The overall sense at this time is that
they don't trust your singing abilities.
- They don't seem too happy right now.
- I think we need to sing an upbeat tune.
- I think that's what we need to do.
- Most trot songs...
- But 'Unconditional' is overdone.
- No, 'Unconditional' is good.
- Let's do that. You can sing that, right?
- Okay, let's sing that one.
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang's seventh request.
'Unconditional' by Park Sang Chul.]
[Legendary vocalist and the rock god
attempt to recover their honor.]
Grandmothers, sing along with us.
[The veteran musicians are putting
their all into singing each lyric.]
[The grandmothers are slowly
getting into the beat.]
[Grandmothers are slowly starting to
get more and more into the groove.]
[Even getting into the harmony.]
[The grandmothers finally seem to
approve of their singing.]
They're finally getting into it!
[They actually seem to know
how to sing a song.]
[Whew, we made it...]
I think we need to move elsewhere.
Please remain healthy.
- Thank you.
Jae Suk, are you the lackey?
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang's youngest member,
Jae Suk, takes charge of the cart.]
Goodbye, Grandmothers.
- Goodbye.
[Thanks for all the songs.]
I bet it's been a long time since you've
been told that you're not good singers.
I bet it's the first time
you've ever been told that.
Not even just 'bad',
but we were 'awfully bad.'
I bet you've never heard that before.
But for what those elders are used to,
I bet our singing isn't that exciting.
How about you guys try singing
'Andong Station' again?
Please come this way.
Come this way.
No, please come this way.
- What is your name, Miss?
- Her name is Ji Soo.
- What would you like to hear, Ji Soo?
- I'm actually a fan of Kim Yeon Woo's.
So I'd like to hear, 'Still beautiful.'
- Kim Yeon Woo's 'Still Beautiful'?
- Yes, there's even been a remake of it.
- So I'd like to request that song.
- First time a new song's been requested.
[Even though the song's 15 years old, it's
the newest song that's been requested.]
Okay, let's sing Ji Soo's requested song,
'Still Beautiful' by Kim Yeon Woo.
This is nice.
[Team Sun-Jin-Kang's eighth request.
'Still Beautiful' by Kim Yeon Woo.]
[Farm field concert for Ji Soo
at Daepyeong-ri, pyeonga.]
That's nice.
I'll film Ji Soo like
she's the heroine in a movie.
[A music video of a young woman,
'Still Beautiful.']
That's nice.
She's doing a great job.
[Daepyong-ri's bundle of fun, Ji Soo.]
Ji Soo, come sing the highlight!
[Ji Soo joins in on
the highlight of the song.]
[That's the legendary vocalist
we know and love!]
[So touching...]
- I'm about to start tearing up.
- Great job!
[Thanks to Ji Soo's great personality,
Team Sum-Jin-Kang succeeds another song.]
One, two, three.
Help us!
- Help us!
- Pull us up!
[Calls out for help to the little boy
who just requested a song by Turbo.]
One, two, three.
[Finally able to pull up the cart
thanks to the little boy's help.]
Bye, kiddo.
Thanks!
Let's get going and sing something
upbeat for the last two songs.
Okay.
She just hops back on there without
any sense of shame or guilt.
It's actually quite amazing.
Okay, one, two, three.
- Has the cart always been this heavy?
- Why does it feel so heavy on a downhill?
- What happened?
- Has it always been this heavy?
Hey!
[My mic.]
I put that mic out of
her reach on purpose.
- Your voice sounds hoarse.
- You sound off.
Your voice sounds really off.
On the backside of our event cart are two
very handsome men here to sing for you.
Please do not hesitate and
come join us in a song!
Please call out for Hong-Kook-Soo!
[This song is an anthem of any events,
'Southbound Train.']
[Have succeeded eight songs so far.]
[Have succeeded nine songs so far.]
[A national even anthem for a reason.
A song that's been requested of every team.]
[Have succeeded eight songs so far.]
[Have succeeded nine songs so far.]
[With the singing of 'Southbound Train',
the mission slowly draws to an end.]
Thank you very much.
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi's score
for the tenth song is?]
98!
98 points!
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi succeeds singing
their Ten Request Song mission!]
- Bobby, we succeeded. Are we done?
- We succeeded!
You're done with your mission, and
the barbershop owner has a prize for you.
- He has a prize for us?
- Yes, head back to the barbershop.
[While Team Gae-Jung-Bi wraps up
the mission in first place...]
[Team Yittagu is partying it up
for their final song of the mission.]
A round of applause for 95 points!
[Team Yittagu also succeeds
with their Ten Request Song mission.]
[Right at the same time, Team Hong-Kook-Soo
also succeeds their first mission.]
Thank you for all your hard work.
[Village head comes to thank them
for a job well done.]
- Thank you so much.
- You have your next event to get to.
- Who should I give this to?
- I can take that.
- No, I'll take it.
- You can give it to any one of us.
- Please give it to me.
- Just give it to him.
- I like being given things.
- I bet we have a good one.
[What is their second event mission?]
A campaign celebration.
This is where we go for our
second mission?
[Next mission is an old custom
campaign celebration event.]
You must find your own way
to the next event location.
The faster we get there,
better advantage we'll have.
- How are we going to get there?
- Since we made money, let's take a taxi.
- Sir, is this place far?
- It'll take you about 30 minutes.
- Sorry to ask, but are you busy right now?
- No, not really.
- Then can you give us a ride?
- But I only have a truck.
- No, it's okay!
- Is that okay with you guys?
[They luck out! Village head
is actually headed that way.]
Put that money away. He's helping us
out of the goodness of his heart.
[Now the question is,
who'll be the first to get there?]
[Yeon Woo is still belting out the tunes
for their team's final song.]
[Their last audience member
is an adorable baby.]
[The baby quietly listens to the song
within the comfort of his mother's arms.]
How is he so calm and attentive?
[He's a pretty good singer.]
[Yeon Woo sings more earnestly now
than he ever has before.]
[Explosion of adlibbing.]
[An amazing singer who always gives
his all no matter how small the stage.]
We don't know when we'd be back,
but please always remain healthy.
[To everyone who joined us today,
wishing you all a lifetime of joy and health.]
[A beautiful and heartwarming
performance.]
- That was great.
- I can't believe how sweet this baby is!
- He didn't even get scared at all.
- He didn't get scared, and remained so calm.
- Did everyone enjoy the song?
- Yes, we loved it.
- This is Seo Yeon.
- His name is Seo Yeon?
- This is my grandson.
- He's your grandson?
No, she's your granddaughter.
She's actually his granddaughter,
but he called her his 'grandson.'
[Mistakes his own granddaughter
as his grandson.]
How sweet are you!
You are such a sweet baby.
[Hope you grow healthy and
strong, Seo Yeon.]
- Sir, thank you so much.
- Thank you for the ride.
[Everyone hurries to
their second mission site.]
[Advantages will be given out to the teams
depending on the order of their arrival.]
We can't start getting tired
after the opening game we just had.
- My back is starting to ache already.
- No, that's not allowed.
Bobby, have you ever been to
Jiri Mountain before?
- Jiri Mountain?
- Yes.
- Yes, I've been here before.
- You've been to Jiri Mountain before?
To see the gam-poongi.
(A word slip on Dam-poonghi= Autumn leaves.]
- Gam-poongi?
- I mean, dam-poongi.
Bobby, what's wrong with you!
You can't even speak Korean or English.
[Not good with either Korean
or the English language.]
- Jung In got married in Jiri Mountain.
- Seriously?
[Jiri Mountain has a very special
meaning for Jung In.]
[Instead of a wedding ceremony, Jung In and
Jung Chi started their marriage with a hike.]
[Wanting to do something meaningful,
they took a picture at the mountain summit.]
So you started your lives together
as a married couple in Jiri Mountain.
- Yes, that's right.
- Life as a married couple.
[Old Customs Campaign Celebrations.]
Thank you.
Have a great day.
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang is the
first to arrive.]
Hello.
[On the beautiful outskirts of Jiri Mountain,
a field of ripe persimmon trees.]
[What kind of an event awaits
our teams here?]
Are we going to roll around here?
[You'll soon find out.]
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi arrives in second place.]
- Look who's here!
- It's an honor see my seniors here.
[A happy greeting between
the musician juniors and seniors.]
- Bobby!
- He's getting married.
- He's getting married this Saturday.
- This upcoming Saturday?
[I'm getting married!]
Kyung Ho's getting married
this weekend.
[Married on November 9th.
A married rocker from this point on.]
Then you're going to have to
be careful today.
- Who is Kwang Soo with?
- It's Hong Jin Young.
And Kim Jong Kook?
Jin Young!
[Team Hong-Kook-Soo arrives in third place.]
[Jin Young makes her moves
the moment she arrives.]
Did you all know that Bobby was the
rapper for our song, 'The Twist King'?
- Seriously?
- Yes, for the rapping portion of it.
- Bobby was the rapper for that.
- Seriously?
- Back then, Bobby...
- 'Come on people, on your feet!'
[That's the voice!]
[An instant replay even after
all these years have passed.]
[Team Yittagu arrives in fourth place.]
[Welcome!]
[The country's top singers are finally
gathered together in one place.]
- What's this all about?
- Today's race is 'Running Man Event Race'.
To the winning team of each of these
missions for the race here at Jiri Mountain
a hint will be given out in the order of
their win regarding the final mission.
[Team Sun-Jin-Kang arrived in first place.]
[First place clue- Agricultural product
that is cultivated on our own soil.]
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi arrived
in second place.]
[Second place clue-
Feel the energy of Jiri Mountain.]
[Team Hong-Kook-Soo arrived in third place.]
[Third place clue- Texture of this food
is more unique than anything else.]
The winning team will get to stand on stage
at the upcoming Jiri Mountain concert event.
A simple mission to help determine which
one of the teams will stand on that stage.
- We have to win this no matter what.
- Here's your second event mission.
Your second mission is, 'Our old
custom is better' campaign celebration.
- Ours is better.
- Is that right?
Then this mission is a
battle of the moles.
One member from each team will step
forward to compete against one another.
Do you see the wooden blocks
in front of the start line?
You have to dig a tunnel in the dirt
to pass through under the wooden blocks.
- Are you serious?
- Then...
- That's just absurd.
- That's crazy.
[We told you that it's a 'mole' game.]
- You expect us to dig in the dirt?
- Past that, you'll find some shovels.
Step on the shovel to fling the rubber shoe
in the air and catch it in your basket.
Then run and pull the radish out of the dirt
to lift it above your head to win the game.
- Yes, one person will do it all.
- How can one person do it alone?
The more you win, the better
clues you'll be able to earn.
- It's crucial that you pick the right person.
- Narsha is our ace.
On the count of three, announce the
first contestant from each of your teams.
[Suk Jin, Kwang Soo, Yeon Woo,
Bobby and Teuk.]
[Not bad!
I can handle these opponents!]
[They all feel a surge of confidence
after seeing who their opponents are.]
- I can do this.
- This isn't bad.
[Who'll be the last one laughing?]
[Mole game- Round one.]
- Yeon Woo!
- Team Yittagu!
[Each team representative is
brimming with confidence.]
- Team Yittagu!
- Fighting!
[And an even more fervent cheering section.]
- Jiri Mountain!
- Yeon Woo, you can do this!
- Gary, let's win this and go see Dam-poongi!
- Yes, Dam-poongi, fighting!
- Dam-poongi!
[Looking at ease as if standing in
the fruit garden of his own home.]
Don't you think that Yeon Woo's
pants are hiked up too high?
- He can't help it.
- He looks good from the side.
[The perfect size to dig his way
through the dirt hole.]
He's a human mole!
- How is he such a good digger?
- I'm not kidding when I say they're a mess.
- You guys are a hot mess!
- You really are a hot mess.
Teuk only looks young here because of us,
but he's actually ancient in the idol world.
Everyone, get ready!
[Mole game- Round one.]
[A dead sprint towards their first obstacle.]
You have to dig really fast.
[Some serious digging in the dirt.]
- Kim Bobby!
- You're too slow!
[Fighting!]
- You have to get right up there.
- Leeteuk!
[Teuk's amazing dirt digging speed.]
- Teuk is really fast.
- Wow, Teuk is no joke.
[I wonder if this will be enough.]
- Yeon Woo, dig in front of you!
- You're too slow!
Kwang Soo, get out from under there!
We've already lost this game.
[Already done digging deep enough
to squeeze his head through.]
[Fighting, Teuk!]
[Yeon Woo also succeeds in
sticking his head through.]
Yeon Woo, you're getting through.
[Teuk also succeeds in getting
his shoulders through the hole.]
[Time to start cheating.]
Kwang Soo!
Bobby's getting through!
- Bobby's getting through!
- Bobby, not yet!
Don't do it, Bobby!
- Kwang Soo!
- Suk Jin, over there!
- Suk Jin!
- My shoulders are stuck.
I'm older than you...
I'm older than you!
[Yeon Woo's almost through
the opening.]
- Yeon Woo's almost through.
- Bobby!
[I'm more frustrated than you are!]
[Just then... Teuk makes his escape!]
[Teuk is first to make his way
to the second course.]
Hurry, Yeon Woo!
[Yeon Woo makes his escape
soon thereafter.]
Yeon Woo, you have to hurry!
He won't get it on his first try.
[Barely manages to escape, and it's
one hurdle after another.]
[Yeon Woo succeeds on his first try!]
[How did he get so lucky?]
What luck is this?
[Leeteuk is hot on Yeon Woo's tail.]
[Teuk is hot on his trail...
but the radish isn't so easy to pull.]
[The real physical battle begins.]
[Kwang Soo successfully makes his escape.]
Put the basket on your head.
Are you out of your mind?
[Big-nose also makes his escape
soon after Kwang Soo.]
Move it, Mister!
[Almost depleted of energy after
the hole he had had to crawl through.]
Hey, Kim Bobby!
[Meanwhile...]
[This one man is still sharing
some quality time with the dirt.]
Bobby!
[How did everyone else do this?]
[Still digging a hole all by himself.]
[It's now a battle against himself.]
[Kwang Soo rushes over for the radish.]
[Suk Jin also succeeds soon thereafter.]
Run!
[The radish still shows no intention
of going anywhere...]
[And there's still Bobby...]
[Finally succeeds in making his escape.]
Okay!
[It's a battle against himself anyway.]
Do it right!
[Bobby's hilarious!]
Don't give up, Bobby!
- Bobby, don't give up.
- Narsha, are you okay?
- Bobby, you're almost there.
- Narsha can't stop laughing.
[This eager fan is happier for him
than his own teammates are.]
Narsha is now a huge fan of Bobby's.
What are they doing over there?
[Frustrated onlookers at the lack of
progress their partners are making.]
[Bursts out laughing whenever
she sees Bobby.]
They're all prominent figures
of this country on their own...
[But this radish is all we see right now...]
[A fiery battle begins as soon as
the radish gets pulled out of the ground.]
It's like they're playing rugby.
[The battle of the radish
starts to get very fierce.]
- You have to lift it above your head!
- Don't give up, Suk Jin!
Yeon Woo, eye for your chance!
- Suk Jin already gave up a long time ago.
- It's like a game of rugby.
[Succeeds at nabbing the radish after
having stayed with the radish all along.]
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang wins the first round.]
[His follow-plan succeeds.]
Narsha is a fan of Bobby's.
[An enthused fan cracks up
at Bobby's every move.]
[Even though he lost his radish,
he gains himself a new fan.]
She laughs at everything he does.
[As part of his fan service,
offer his fan a hug.]
Not a single person here
respects me right now.
Marsha here at least...
[Who's Marsha?]
[Thanks, Narsha.]
He's so cute.
Okay, time for the final contestants.
[Team Hong-Kook-Soo wins the second round,
and it's now time for the final round.]
On the count of three,
final contestants, step forward.
[Jung In, Jin Young, Ji Hyo,
Kyung Ho, Ha Ha.]
It's all women.
You're all women, okay?
It's like a girl group
with the exception of you.
[With Ha Ha out, it's like
a four member girl group.]
Look from the back.
It's a total girl group.
[Very deceptive from the back.]
All the contestants move over
to the starting line.
[Final round of the mole game.]
[A fierce battle between the women
is estimated.]
- Kyung Ho, you can't go easy on them.
- I'm ready to be decimated!
Kyung Ho, if you lose,
I'm not going to like you anymore!
I'll do my best!
You just wait!
I'll bring back the radish!
Jin Young loves doing things like that.
[Jin Young's never-ending charm.]
Jung In, you should give it a try, too.
- Show us what you've got.
- You do it too, Jung In.
Radish, you're mine!
Enough!
That's enough!
Kyung Ho!
You give it a try.
- What do I say?
- Say, 'Radish, you're mine.'
Radish, you're mine!
[That was good!]
- His was the best!
- That was so cute!
Third round contestants, get ready!
[Current score- Team Sum-Jin-Kang:1
vs Team Hong-Kook-Soo:1.]
- Fighting!
[This round could determine
who'll win first place.]
Kyung Ho, what are you doing?
[First obstacle-
Dig a hole and crawl through the dirt.]
[As if they've been studying, they
start their own method of dirt digging.]
You have to dig up front, too.
There you go.
- You have to dig front and back.
- Kyung Ho.
[Kyung Ho calmly digs front and back.]
A little bit more.
[Kyung Ho attempts to make his escape.]
Kyung Ho, you can't make it through yet.
[Extremely slim body! Crawls his
way through the tiny opening!]
[I can't let you get through that fast.]
[If I can just grab his feet...]
[Kyung Ho makes his escape
at top speed.]
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang
is one step closer to a win.]
[Our Ace Blank Ji escapes
hot on Kyung Ho's heels.]
- You have to do it again.
- Song Ji Hyo!
[Ace blazes her trail.]
- Song Ji Hyo, fighting!
Song Ji Hyo!
[Even succeeds at catching
the rubber shoe on his second attempt.]
Just start digging around the radish first!
[At a speed we've yet been
able to see.]
[Will he be able to end the
game right here?]
[No!]
[Pulls the radish out of the dirt!]
[Put everything back in the basket
and lifts it above his head!]
[Kyung Ho's amazing performance lands
Team Sum-Jin-Kang in first place.]
- We won!
- Already?
[Even all the losing teams are
flabbergasted at Kyung Ho's win.]
[Everyone's shocked at
the groom-to-be's performance.]
[I got dirt in my eye.]
- Jung In, you were too slow.
- What are they doing?
What was that?
What are you doing?
[No, it was nothing...]
- What are you two doing?
- Is it a new romance?
- Kim Jong Kook!
- She said she got dirt in her eye.
I'm asking because I'm curious
but do you start kissing on these shows
now if you're attracted to someone?
- Is that what you do now?
- Knock it off.
- Nice going!
- It's been awhile since I've done this.
Jong Kook, you've got something
in your eye.
- There's nothing!
- You've got something in your eye!
[First place: Team Sum-Jin-Kang.
Second Place: Team Hong-Kook-Soo.]
[Team Super Blank Ji wins
the tiebreaker round.]
[Come visit Jiri Mountain's orchard grove.]
But you were still funny.
[Second place winners:
Team Hong-Kook-Soo.]
[While you're in Jiri Mountain, you
have to try these foods before you go.]
I have no idea what the
previous clue meant.
[First place winner:
Team Sum-Jin-Kang.]
[Like the charm of a peacock!
Both the green and the red are delicious.]
I don't know what that means either.
[Distribution of clues are now complete.]
[What is the secret hidden
behind these clues?]
Do you have a mudpack
on your face?
Your skin tone looks much better now.
[The benefits of organic soil.]
- Your skin tone against the shirt...
- He finally looks like a live human being.
Teuk seems to find everything funny because
he hasn't been on a variety show in so long.
He's so intrigued and amused
by everything.
I find it fascinating because
I feel like I'm amongst celebrities.
It's really fascinating.
Kyu Hyun, who do you keep looking
at Teuk with such look of disdain?
I just want to take off these pants.
- He has his own reasons.
- No kidding.
Kyu Hyun's not like he used to be
from having been around Goo Ra.
He keeps looking disgruntled.
[Off to the next event mission site.]
[As long as you're in Jiri Mountain,
try these foods before you go.]
- Try these foods.
- Jiri Mountain must have good foods, right?
- Maybe seven different side dishes?
- Yes, maybe you're right.
- No, it's seven different genres.
- Then maybe seven different categories?
Maybe it's seven different foods
from all different categories.
- What is it?
- I hear sanyoosu fruit is famous here.
- Yes, you're right.
- Are you sure it's not dogwood fruit?
- No, it's sanyoosu.
- 'Sanyoosu'? You sure it's not 'Sansooyu'?
Isn't 'Sansooyu' a name of a village?
No, I think 'Sansooyu' is right.
Sanyoosu.
[Is it... or isn't it?]
What's the other clue?
[The texture of this is
more unique than anything else.]
- An agricultural crop?
- Agricultural crop.
What agricultural crops are there?
There are lots.
There are a countless number of them.
One of our clues said something
about an agricultural crop.
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang is also
trying to decipher their clues.]
What does it say?
We have to guess what it is?
[Agricultural crop that is produced
from our own soil.]
Agricultural crop that is produced
from our own soil... what's the next one?
[Like the charming peacock,
both the red and the green are delicious.
If it's produce...
then how about peppers?
[Could it be peppers?]
But apples can also be either
red or green.
- Depends on whether it's ripe or not...
- It could also be bell peppers.
- So we need another hint, don't we?
- Yes, we do.
[Just what is it that these clues
are indicating to?]
[Jiri Mountain's seven
item celebration event.]
- Ugh, I'm so hungry.
- I bet loser team doesn't get to eat.
- Then does this mean we don't get to eat?
- I don't think we'll be eating.
- All because of Suk Jin?
- Narsha, you got put on the wrong team.
Why did I have to be teamed up like this?
Who's responsible for this?
[But you've got some
very positive teammates.]
- Hello.
- Wow, what's that?
[The best southern delicacies-
Jiri Mountain's 20 dish feasting table.]
[This is the taste of the south.]
Everything looks so good!
- What's that?
- It's a loach stew.
[Delicious loach stew!]
- Is this whole loach stew?
- This is amazing.
Kim Kyung Ho,
you have to come this way.
You can't go to the bathroom right now.
[Jiri Mountain's infamous red bean porridge.]
This is amazing.
[A feast just for us.]
- Wow, everything looks so delicious.
- It looks so good.
[A delicious and generous feast
of Jiri Mountain's 20 dish meal table.]
[Did you all get a good look?]
- I'm so hungry right now.
- Remember the placement of the dishes.
[Oh no!]
[What's this?]
[Hurry up and memorize it.]
[It's mission time!]
[What... is this?]
[In the blink of an eye, all 20
dishes get covered by a huge bowl!]
Doraji, bibim...
- Do not touch the table.
- Just let us eat.
Suk Jin keeps peeking under
the covers!
Suk Jin just forfeited one
of his chances.
[Suk Jin's naughty hand.]
- Suk Jin's needs to compensate for it!
- I like this rule!
- Stop being so dramatic.
- I seriously got the chills.
[Rocker groom-to be remains oblivious to
everything as he returns from the bathroom.]
- This is what I really hate.
- Hate what?
- He can't do anything right.
- You have to support your teammate.
I have nowhere else to go
if you guys turn on me, too.
- Are you all hungry?
- Yes.
Did you all get to see the dishes
that were laid out on the table?
Kyung Ho didn't get to see anything
because he was in the bathroom.
That's why I told him
not to go to the bathroom.
[What happened while I've
been gone?]
He doesn't listen very well to others.
As the banner behind you states, this is
Jiri Mountain's feasting table memory game.
[Jiri Mountain's 20 dish feasting table
memory game.]
- That's what I thought.
- We have to use our brains.
Ugh, this is a thinking game.
[Take another good look!]
Of the numerous dishes laid out
on the table
we will choose just one dish,
and present it to all of you.
[Correctly guess where the presented
dish is placed on the table.]
[The team that correctly guesses the most
number of dishes wins the game.]
[Only the winning team of the game
can enjoy the taste of Jiri Mountain feast.]
If the dish you choose matches the dish
presented, only then can you enjoy the dish.
- I don't remember anything.
- Kyung Ho didn't even get to see anything.
But if our opposing team gets it wrong,
we still get to check where a certain dish is?
[Figuring out the placement of the dishes
by other team's mistakes is advantageous.]
- Will they give us a chance to look first?
- No.
Why did you go to the bathroom earlier
when he told you not to go?
Kyung Ho, you have to learn to hold it
when you're on a variety show.
Do I have to take this kind of abuse for
having gone to the bathroom for 3 minutes?
All this happened within
the three minutes you were gone.
I can't stand this kind of
dirty playing and abuse.
You're forbidden from further
bathroom use.
But look at how engrossed
Teuk is with everything.
[Teuk's engrossed position from having
been away from variety for so long.]
From what I'm seeing over here,
I don't think anyone here is quite sane.
It's because doing this
variety show made us this way.
Kyu Hyun used to smile all the time,
and I don't know what's happened to him.
It's not that...
but I want to make an example for
the young viewers
and in order to do that,
I think I need to bring Suk Jin down.
You're starting to act like Goo Ra.
You're close to Goo Ra these days, right?
I'm just trying to set an
example for all our young viewers.
Here's your first dish.
Your first question is a dish made with
a certain shellfish from Seomjin River.
A dish made with a certain shellfish
from Seomjin River.
It's a noodle dish made
with a certain type of shellfish.
- I think I know where it is.
- A noodle dish made with this shellfish.
[Where is this noodle dish located?]
Where was the noodle dish?
- I know. Just trust me.
- You know?
- Okay, I'm trusting you.
- You can trust me.
[Jin Young attempts to sniff it out!]
If you get it wrong, then you must close it
to prevent the other teams from seeing it.
[Time to check the location
of the noodle dish!]
[Correct]
[Team Yittagu and
Team Gae-Jung-Bi succeeds.]
[Earns themselves a bowl of
the shellfish noodle soup.]
- Gae Jung Bi!
- See, I got it right.
Three!
[Red bean porridge, Grilled fish,
and Stir-fried pork.]
[Too bad- The other
three teams fail their attempt.]
[He does it again!]
[Totally caught!]
Ji Suk Jin peeked again.
Ji Suk Jin, one more, and you lose
your chance to pick the next one.
[Big-nose receives a yellow warning card.]
[Big-nose's cowardly excuse.]
- What's wrong with this man!
- Seriously! Come on.
- Just kick him off our team.
- I can't work with him anymore!
[Team Yittagu's fission.]
Can you swap him out with Bobby?
[Me?]
I want Bobby on our team instead.
- Ready!
- Here's your next dish.
It's a famous vegetable dish made of
a vegetable that grows in Jiri Mountain.
Find the spicy doraji muchim!
- The doraji muchim?
- Find the doraji muchim!
- Yes, the doraji muchim.
- Is there anything that you do remember?
- Are you sure?
- I'm telling you that I'm right about this.
- You have ten seconds.
- I'm right about this!
[A divide within the team?]
- I'm right, but he says that I'm not.
- No, you're not!
One, two...
[Jin Young actually got it right?]
No, that's deoduk.
[Jin Young mistakes deoduk for
the similar looking doraji dish.]
- That's not right.
- That's deoduk.
- How could you think that was doraji?
- Three!
Wow, we got it right!
[Team Super Blank Ji and Team Yittagu
successfully earns the doraji muchim.]
[What a relief that they didn't
listen to Big-nose brother.]
This is really confusing.
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang has yet to
get anything correct.]
I got my dishes confused.
Bobby doesn't even know the names
of these side dishes.
He doesn't know anything
but pizza and hamburgers.
[Only familiar with pizza and
hamburgers.]
How are we getting everything wrong?
I can't believe we haven't gotten anything.
[Team Hong-Kook-Soo and
Team Sum-Jin-Kang have yet to get anything.]
- We still have an ace up our sleeves.
- Like what?
- What is it that we remember?
- There's that dish we remember.
Wow, they've got something
going on there.
That's what I'm saying.
[A love line between
Jin Young and Kkuk?]
- It's like a romantic comedy.
- I agree.
Kwang Soo, why are you looking
so old all of a sudden?
[Giraffe's exhausted from all
the dirt digging from earlier.]
Here's your third question.
- We may not get to eat anything.
- I don't remember anything.
Crab stew made with
fresh ocean crab is located where?
You know where it is, right?
[Everyone seems to know where this one is!]
- You know where it is, right?
- Crab is mine!
One, two...
[Time to verify their answer!]
[Even Team Sum-Jin-Kang finally
gets their first dish!]
[Everyone successfully locates
the crab stew.]
[You just wait, crab stew.]
It's natural for the eyes to gravitate
toward the best looking dish first.
You tend to look at the dish
that you want to eat the most.
[Huh?]
- Jae Suk! Jae Suk just took a bite!
- Wait!
- Jae Suk just took a bite!
- He just ate something!
- Jae Suk!
- He's not allowed to eat!
[While everyone's attention
is riveted on Jae Suk...]
[Blank Ji Hyo also sneaks
a bite of the crab stew.]
Can we kick Jae Suk out of the game
for having taken a bite?
[But it was still so good...]
Here's your fourth question.
Kim Kyung Ho, did you get to see
where even a single dish is placed?
I know where six of the
dishes are placed.
Six dishes?
I've been paying attention to all the dishes
that other team's have gotten wrong.
[Been keeping a careful eye on the
wrong guesses that the other teams took.]
- Kyung Ho shouldn't be taken lightly.
- I think he's lying.
[Kwang Soo, you just wait and see
with the next question...]
You're just afraid that
he's right, aren't you?
Okay, here's your next question.
It's a very common dish in Jeollado.
But that same dish is
made with sweet red beans here.
[Made with sweet red beans...]
[Utterly clueless... sweet red beans?]
The sweet red bean porridge with
tiny dumplings is located where?
I didn't get to see it.
I can't tell you anything.
You must not remember
where it is?
- Oh, that's right!
- You remember now?
- I'm going to take a guess.
- You have five seconds.
Five, four..
[It's all in Jae Suk's hands now.]
I actually got it!
[Misses by one placement-
Acorn jelly muchim.]
- I actually got it!
- I thought you said you guessed.
[By pure luck, Team Sum-Jin-Kang earns
the sweet red bean porridge.]
[On the other hand,
Teams Gae-Jung-Bi and Yittagu miss.]
Wow, I can't believe it.
[I can't believe I got so lucky...]
I don't even like
sweet red bean porridge.
Ugh, we were so close!
Okay, let's keep at it.
[Only one more question left to go.]
I'm so nervous.
Please let it be something I know.
Please!
- We can do this.
- It's all down to luck now.
If it's something we remember,
then we can win this thing.
- Let's go with a tough question.
- Let's go for something we can mix.
- Give us a tough question.
- No one can touch anything right now.
What are you going to do about it?
- What are you going to do if I do?
- I was just saying that you can't.
I'm just saying that you can't...
The perfect companion to makgulli...
scallion pancakes.
[Where are the scallion pancakes?]
- I know where it is.
- Just hang on.
[Leeteuk also seems to know
where it is.]
[Jin Young also seems to
know where it is.]
Yes, that's right.
Ah, I remember seeing this!
- I think we're going to get to eat.
- One, two...
[The final question to the mission-
Where could the scallion pancakes be?]
[And which of these teams will
get to enjoy the 20 dish feast?]
[Team Yittagu earns their
scallion pancake!]
[Team Super Blank Ji with
the tied score... guess incorrectly.]
- That's sanjuk.
- What's this?
[How disappointing!]
[Team Yittagu wins the feast!]
Yittagu is the winner!
[Second place winner, Team Hong-Kook-Soo,
secretly starts eating their food.]
[Disappointed third place winners,
Teams Gae-Jung-Bi and Super Blank Ji.]
[First place winners' solo feast.]
[Team Yittagu's clue- We'd like to introduce
Super Junior's famed hit song, Sorry Sorry.]
[Second place winner's clue- Eat it raw,
eat it grilled, or eat it poached.]
[Teams Gae-Jung-Bi and Super Blank Ji's clue-
Top rated snack regardless of age or gender.]
That's snail dumpling soup.
- Wow, this is really unbelievable.
- That looks so good!
- That looks like too much food for you.
- Look at this deoduk.
- Can I try a bite?
- Can I get a bite, too?
Narsha, I thought you said
that you like me.
Yes, I do like you.
- Are you really going to be like this?
- Bobby, what are you doing?
- What did Bobby say?
- He asked Narsha if she likes him.
[If you like me,
then give me just a bite...]
- Can we take the table away?
- Yes, we should.
Kwang Soo, lift up the table.
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
[Team Yittagu's table
is forcibly taken away.]
Okay, lower it.
Pull it back up.
[This is what you call a to-go meal.]
[Jiri Mountain Solo Concert Performance]
[Green tea research facilities in Hadong.]
[Event singers are rushing off someplace.]
For your final mission, you'll have to find
the real stage to Jiri Mountain concert.
There are five stages that have been
set up for the Jiri Mountain event.
Four of the five stages are fakes where
you'll find a penalty instead of music
and only one of the stages is the real
one where the music will play through.
Only the team that utilizes the clues earned
to figure out the real stage wins the race.
Once all three members of a team steps
on stage, no further changes can be made.
Behind the stage is a
two storied building.
Hidden inside the building are 15 mics
that are marked with the 'R' sticker.
I have to find the 'R' marked mics, right?
Each member must find one of the mics and
stand on the stage of your choosing.
[Team with all three members with a mic must
come stand on the real stage to win the race.]
Gary.
Should we split up?
Do you think we should split up?
I have to find the mic quickly.
- The mics are inside this building?
- I think it's the persimmon.
I saw ginseng, melon, and apple down
there, but I think it's the persimmon.
[Come visit the Jiri Mountain's orchard.]
[The clues that Team Super Blank Ji has
earned through their previous missions.]
[The top rated snack regardless
of age or gender.]
I think that's the best hint we've got.
It's either persimmon or dried persimmon.
- Right?
- Yes.
[Team Super Blank Ji's guess
is the dried persimmon?]
- Just hurry up and find the mics.
- Are they inside the building?
Mic, mic...
[Ha Ha's already searched
through the room...]
[It's a mic!]
Did you find one?
What the heck!
He was standing right next to it.
How could he not have seen that?
[Hides the mic she found,
and goes off to find another one.]
Should we split up?
Hurry up and find the mic.
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi's Bobby
finds a mic of his own.]
When I watch the show on TV,
it doesn't seem all that hard to find.
- I've already looked, and there's nothing.
- You didn't find anything?
- I really didn't find anything.
- Seriously?
Hello.
[An office run-in.]
[Huh?]
[A deep sigh of joy and relief.]
It must not be in here?
There must not be any in here?
[Quietly... slips and runs away.]
[Oh? Gary finds one, too!]
What other snacks could there
be that everyone likes?
- All I can think of is a persimmon.
- I think it's a persimmon, too.
- I kept noticing the persimmon.
- Right? I kept noticing the persimmon, too.
[This team also believes that
the persimmon may be their answer.]
- What other persimmon snack are there?
- Dried persimmons!
[Could their persimmon guess
be correct?]
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi currently have
two mics already in their possession.]
[Gary finds another one!]
- You found one, didn't you?
- No, I haven't found any.
Bobby!
- Jung In!
- Yes?
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi is the first to
find all three mics for their team.]
Run... hurry up and run!
We have to run... hurry!
[The only thing left to do now is for all
three members to go on stage together.]
Jung In, hurry!
Bobby, hang on.
We have to figure out which one.
Gary already found all three mics?
We have to pick one.
Come on, Jung In.
[Gary hands a mic over to Jung In,
who wasn't able to find one on her own.]
- Are we picking the persimmon?
- Apple, melon, ginseng?
- This is what I was thinking.
- Wait a minute.
Which one could it be?
- I think it's the persimmon.
- I think it is, too.
Okay, let's go with the persimmon.
[Just then, Team Super Blank Ji
comes running over!]
[We want the persimmon!]
[If we don't get on the stage first,
then it'll be taken away from us!]
[Team Gae-Jung-Bi selects
the persimmon stage.]
[Team Super Blank Ji is
one step too late.]
- How about the apple?
- You could be wrong about the persimmon.
- Let's go for the apple.
- I think it's this one.
[Immediately substitutes
the dogwood fruit for the persimmon.]
None of our clues indicated
to that one.
I don't think it's that one.
[Team Super Blank Ji selects
the dogwood fruit stage.]
[Team Hong-Kook-Soo finds
their second mic.]
I can't run anymore right now.
[Jin Young's battery is depleted.]
- Kwang Soo!
- Let's take the elevator.
[Busy searching for the mic,
and busy taking care of Jin Young...]
Here it is.
I found one.
Apple, pear, melon...
ginseng...
Apple?
Could it be the apple?
Apple could also mean to apologize.
('Sa-gwa' Apple= Sorry.)
[Apple could mean, sorry.)
We'd like to introduce Super Junior's
hit song, 'Sorry Sorry'.
- What?
- What's that supposed to mean?
[Rubbing the two hands together
in a gesture of an apology...]
Apple?
Could it be the apple?
It's the apple!
- Suk Jin, did you find it?
- I did, did you?
- Where's Narsha?
- I figured it out.
- I know what it is. Come here.
- What is it?
- It's the apple. Apple as in apology.
- Okay!
- Okay, you're right.
- Did you find one or not?
[Only one more mic left to find
for Team Yittagu!]
Narsha!
[Kyung Ho also finds a mic!]
Kyung Ho!
[Jae Suk also has a mic in his hand!]
- Kyung Ho!
- Where are you?
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang suddenly has
all three mics in their possession!]
Narsha!
Narsha, run!
[Team Yittagu also finds
their one last mic.]
Run!
Run down here!
[Team Yittagu is on the move!]
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang also heads
towards the stage.]
Hurry.
Please let the stage be empty.
- Please let the stage be empty.
- Hurry!
[If the stage is occupied by another team,
then their efforts will be wasted!]
The Blue Team is up on the stage!
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang takes the
apple stage?]
That team headed directly
over to the apple stage.
- They already took it.
- What?
- The stage is already taken.
- We're positive that this is the right one.
[The hint that they earned after having
won their second mission.]
Something that's delicious whether
it's green or red...
- There are so many possibilities.
- But that sign said apples and persimmons.
- There's a good chance that it's an apple.
- I think it's the apple.
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang guessed that it's
an apple right from the get go...]
[Team Yittagu steps onto
the adjacent melon stage.]
[Team Hong-Kook-Soo is the
last team to arrive.]
[Steps onto the ginseng stage
without a choice.]
You have all made your
stage selections.
- This is not what we were thinking.
- This is not what we wanted.
Of the five stages...
only one is the real stage.
Four of these stages are fake stages.
I can see the flour sifting out of this one.
It's time to reveal the answer,
and the rest will be penalized!
Is something going to fall out?
Wait...
[Which one of these is the real stage?]
Please!
[Persimmon stage-
Feel the energy of Jiri Mountain.]
[Top rated snack regardless
of age or gender.]
[Dogwood fruit stage-
Come visit Jiri Mountain's orchard.]
[Top rated snack regardless
of age or gender.]
[Apple stage- An agricultural crop
grown from our own soil.]
[Both the red and the green
are delicious.]
[Melon stage- Introducing
Super Junior's hit song, 'Sorry Sorry'.]
[Ginseng stage- Unique texture,
and one of Jiri Mountain's best!]
[Which of these is the real stage?]
[Team Sum-Jin-Kang's apple stage
is the real stage!]
[A flour explosion.]
[A flour snowfall in November.]
[All these hints were
indicating to the apple.]
[Yoo Jae Suk, Kim Kyung Ho,
and Kim Yeon Woo wins!]
Why did you put so much
flour in there?
There never used to be this much flour!
[The final event of the day...]
You're rolling out the red carpet?
[Time for Team Sum-Jin-Kang's
solo stage performance.]
[A serenade befitting of
the falling flour.]
Today's prize is an array of the seven
gifts Jiri Mountain has to offer!
[Apple, melon, dogwood fruit, green tea,
persimmon, ginseng, and wooden container.]
I'd like for the new groom-to-be,
Kyung Ho to take the ginseng.
[Ginseng goes to the new
groom-to-be, Kyung Ho.]
Congratulations, Kyung Ho!
[To all the top singers of our country
who joined us on our show today...]
[We'd like to thank our guests and
to everyone else for their participation.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Wars]
[Seven aliens without their homes
finds their way to our blue planet.]
[Alien life force comes to our earth.]
[Takes over the streets
in their shocking images.]
Don't you earthlings know about this?
[Gets themselves used to
their new lives on earth.]
[But it's not so easy to
get acclimated to their new lives.]
[Greets new earth variety
with full physical force.]
[Must solve the mystery
and return to their home planet.]
[The unexpected twist on
the blue planet!]
[Running Wars]