[Capital of Korea,
Seoul]
[What's the occasion for starting
with band music?]
[Girl with a Bob Cut
By Cho Yong Pil]
[Yoo
Great Birth]
[Korean Beatles in the 21st century(?)]
[Perfect comedic chord]
[Fashion that goes against time]
[Singing at his best]
[Drop]
[Unplugging the guitar cord has nothing
to do with playing the instrument.]
[Embarrassing]
[Fatally attractive Yoo and Great Birth]
[This is the falsetto]
[Focused]
[Full of nasal sound]
[No. 1 on Billboard for stage manner.]
[Guitarist Lee Kwang Ja]
[Drummer Kim Jong Sook]
[On keyboard is Blank Ji]
[For Vocals...]
[Box Office Hit actress Shim Eun Kyung]
[Jong Sook and Rhythm Touch]
[When you go to Nasung
By Sesem Trio]
[Chorus with soul and might]
[7080 fiery stage by sisters]
[You'll get scolded if you don't
send a message.]
[Shouting]
[Even cute choreography.]
[Suspicious singing style by
'Miss Granny']
[Consistently screaming chorus]
[Cutesy]
Bye, my love!
This was the best performance of my life!
[And]
[The best band for the final performance!]
Scream!
[Representative flower boy band
in Korea.]
[Four men of devilish charm who
seduced Asia, beyond Korea.]
[This is the real live performance.]
[A taste of a new song yet
to be released?]
I love you, CN Blue!
Jung Yong Hwa!
[Can't hold it back! Glad to see Yong Hwa
more than a new song.]
Ouch, my stomach!
[Full of humor!
Ending in variety-style!]
CN Blue!
[Welcome CN Blue]
Yong Hwa and Jong Hyun have been
here many times...
but it's the first time for Jung Shin
and Min Hyuk.
This is Yong Hwa's 10th time
on Running Man.
Really?
[Another family member,
Running Man's eighth member Yong Hwa.]
I'm sharing the history.
Jong Hyun seems to change every time
he comes here.
- I got scared looking in this direction.
- Why?
What are you two?
[Shikumuns?!]
I do this kind of stuff too!
I take a shower.
[Take a shower later after
the shooting...]
You look like shitake mushroom brothers.
[Shitake mushroom brothers]
So what are we doing today?
For the city that is jumping to be
a global tourist spot
you're the cultural representatives to
become the 'Faces of Seoul.'
We will go to famous attractions
chosen by foreign tourists.
You will earn medals based on the
missions completed.
At the last spot, you can switch the medals
with something that will determine your fate.
We also selected three colors for the teams
from the ten colors that represent Seoul.
[As for Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Gary, Ha Ha]
[Yellow, the color of ginko leaves that dye
the streets of Seoul in autumn.]
[For Jong Sook, Kwang Ja, Blank Ji
and Eun Kyung...]
[Red, which is the color
of Geun Jung Hall of Gyungbok Palace.]
- I like pink color.
- Pink! It's my favorite color.
- My underwear is pink, too.
- Please be considerate.
[Just the thought of it is horrifying.]
[For CN Blue]
[Blue, for the color of the high and clear
autumn sky in Seoul.]
[Off to the first mission location!]
Go to 'G' market in Yeji-dong.
- 'G' market.
- 'G' market...
Every mission is very important,
so let's do our best!
Let's do our best and become
the representatives of beauty for Seoul.
Eun Kyung, are you strong or fast?
What are you good at?
- What do you do for sports?
- I did Taekwondo when I was little.
And fencing, too.
Actually, CN Blue is good for
the face of Seoul.
[Flower boys CN Blue are the faces
of Seoul in any respect...]
[Perfect if Eun Kyung joins in.]
We should drop out for the sake of Seoul.
But we have the comfortable look. It might be
too much because CN Blue is too handsome.
[Do they look too handsome...
to make you feel uncomfortable?]
What mission would we get?
Do we get it when we get there?
[The beginner Min Hyuk
asks Running Man veteran Yong Hwa.]
[Totally relaxed]
I think when we get there, someone's waiting.
Ten times makes a difference!
[The first attraction of Seoul sightseeing-
Gwangjang Market in Jongno.]
[Feast of splendid flavors that stimulate
the eyes, nose and mouth.]
[Always full of people looking for food-
Representative old-style market in Seoul.]
When I come to a market, I always want to
eat a bowl of soup with rice.
Put a piece of kimchi on top
of the soup!
[Drool]
- It's alive!
- The market is alive!
[What's the first mission of
'Seoul Sightseeing' in Gwangjang Market?]
[Eat food deliciously. If you select the
"Mission Accomplished" card, "Mission Accomplished"!]
- You know about the old-style market?
- Of course we do!
This is the mission for the
representative food item of this market.
That's great. I'm hungry.
[Endless array of food in
Gwangjang Market.]
[Eat at each step and select a card.]
[If you choose the "Mission Accomplished"
card, the mission is over!]
All we have to do is to choose
the right card?
- Find the flag.
- We start from there? Okay, okay!
Let's go!
Let's become the faces of Seoul.
You don't even need to look, it's us!
[Red Team arrives, too!]
They already left!
We just need to eat and choose.
[A beautiful mission that requires only
eating and choosing a card?]
[Walking around looking for 'R1'
with a fluttering heart]
[Full of food befitting of the market
known for its food.]
[What kind of food is at 'R1'?]
It's here!
It's mung bean pancake!
Please give us mung bean pancakes!
It looks really good.
I really wanted to eat this when I had time.
Thank you.
[Looking delicious]
We can get the mission after we eat.
You should dip it here.
It's awesome!
[Touching flavor of mung bean pancake!]
More please.
This is so good.
[Mung bean pancake with its
traditional flavor.]
Look at him winking at me.
He's totally fallen for us. We must
have the style that foreigners like.
My nickname is Black hole.
["Female" Team arrives at 'R1' too.]
- Have some mung bean pancake.
- It's mung bean pancake!
- Here, Sis.
- Thank you.
[Eun Kyung takes care of
her older sisters.]
- If you're not going to eat, give it to me.
- Can you just give me one piece?
- It's really good. It's so good!
- Can you just give me one?
- Eun Kyung, are you going to finish that?
- Yes!
You're so greedy!
[Eun Kyung changed completely
with food in sight.]
[Eat... Eat... Lick and Eat]
[Yellow Team finished in no time.]
[Time to select the cards
'Fail' or 'Success'.]
[Huh? There... are... too many...?]
[Only one 'Mission Accomplished' card!]
Okay, I'll do it!
[The mission is over as soon as he picks
the 'Mission Accomplished' card.]
[Is it a pass on the first go?]
[It's 'Fail'!]
[Oh my]
Fail.
[Since they picked 'Fail,' walk to 'R2'.]
[Wait...]
['Fail' means we can continue
to eat more...?]
Fine, we're fine!
- 'Fail' means good!
- Really?
Thank you for the food!
[It's good,
I don't care what they do.]
If you pick the card on your first try,
it's not a good thing.
[Change of strategy.
Hoping for 'Fail' to eat more?]
[We're the representatives today!
Blue Team CN Blue arrives!]
[They were relaxed,
then rushed to look for 'R1'.]
[Bright greetings]
Hello!
[Happy young men of CN Blue]
Happy New Year!
Wow! It's spicy fish stew!
[Yellow Team already proceeded to 'R2'.]
[This is heaven...?]
[What's the next food item?]
[Ta-da]
[Famous in Gwangjang Market-
Magic Rice Roll.]
[Magic rice rolls that you cannot stop
eating once you start]
We got the jackpot today!
- Picking 'Fail' is better!
- Of course it is!
[Everyone is for 'Fail']
[Even hot fish cakes, too!]
We don't have enough.
[Yoo-hoo]
I hope we keep getting 'Fail.'
It's so good!
[This... is not what we wanted]
I like to 'Fail'!
If another team passes first,
they'll proceed to the next location.
I know, but it's so good!
[Happy]
Fish cake! It's fish cake!
[Red Team picked 'Fail' and came to 'R2.']
Please give us something delicious, too!
- Who is this?
- I'm Lee Kwang Ja.
Wow, the rice roll is really...
Argh, you're really...
[It's difficult to eat together with
Jong Sook and Kwang Ja sisters.]
Why? What's wrong?
It's not easy for me either.
They're like the big sisters of the neighborhood.
[Still eating in the middle of all this.]
[Inhaling like a thunderstorm.]
Eun Kyung, do you like it?
Eat a lot.
[Shim Food Monster focused on the target
regardless of what goes on.]
- Eun Kyung, eat a lot.
- Yes.
[Ouch, so hot! Hot!]
[At this time...]
[Positive young men are being graced
by mung bean pancakes.]
We're done.
Don't you want one more?
[Clean]
Thank you, Granny.
[Time to pick 'Fail' or 'Pass']
Rock paper scissors!
No you can't!
[The icon of misfortune in the team,
Jung Shin's choice.]
[Next location on the first pick?]
[Fail]
[Ah... Of course...]
- Thank you!
We're the faces of Seoul!
[Competition for the faces of Seoul
with no conscience.]
We're the faces of Seoul!
We're the standard of beauty!
Please come here!
[Argument over the face...
I hope CN Blue comes soon.]
[For marketing(?)]
Ladies and gentlemen...
We are Seoul face.
[Please stop...]
[The best?
Wonderfulest(?)]
[Male Team's turn to pick again.]
Please, pick 'Fail'!
[Aiming for failing in the mission.
Crisis that never happened before.]
[Please 'Fail'...]
[Jackpot 'Fail']
[Picked 'Fail' as they wished and
proceed to 'R3'.]
[What other delicious food is
awaiting us...?]
Wow! Wow wow wow wow!
[Bibimbap, Representative food of Korea.]
- This is the real deal.
- Of course this is the taste of Seoul.
[Plus, it's nutty barley rice.]
Why do we have to pass when
the food is so good?
I love the owner here!
I love this market!
[Excited again]
[Sister Kwang Ja, you pick one.]
I'll pick one then.
[Red Team also prays earnestly
for 'Fail'...]
[She has to pick 'Fail' to eat
all these foods.]
[But... 'Success']
[Mission Accomplished]
[Even nice Eun Kyung... exploded.]
[Kwang Ja gets abused
for accomplishing the mission.]
- You ruined us!
- Let's go!
It looks so good.
[All these are still left to be eaten...]
[On the other hand...]
[it's a feast here.]
Of course, barley rice goes well
with bibimbap.
Hey, we're leaving behind this, too!
[Upset]
What the heck?
[Food they cannot have...]
[Suddenly depressed]
Look at this with barley rice!
Give me one bite!
[He cannot hear]
Give me one bite! Just one bite!
[Her spirit escaped...]
Brother, just one bite.
[Desperately Cold]
- You're the problem!
- Wait.
We had a hard time picking 'Fail'!
[Rules are rules.]
You can't have it.
Do you have to go this far?
- Thank you.
- You should use your hands.
I really don't want to pick
'Accomplished.'
I want 'Fail'!
[Seduction from 'Fail' is too sweet.]
So what if we lose the game?
Good food is more important.
I really didn't get to eat much.
I came here with an empty stomach.
[Shim Monster's anger explodes]
I said I came with an empty stomach.
I'm really sorry.
- Try it. Hurry!
- Thank you.
[While the crew is looking elsewhere,
taking the dumplings from the elderly.]
Thank you!
Congratulations.
[Anyways, Female Team
accomplished the mission.]
[Kwang Ja gets scolded for getting
them first place.]
[Earned 10 medals for being first place.]
Eun Kyung, show me your happy face.
- Hey, don't pick anything from here on out.
- Wow!
[Kwang Ja's right to pick is taken away!]
Eun Kyung told me to do it.
Shim Eun Kyung!
Let's talk separately later.
[Touched...]
Now we should have something sweet.
[Now they even discuss the menu.]
[CN Blue arrives at 'R3'
after picking 'Fail'.]
You know it's good to pick 'Fail,' right?
[In complete agreement on 'Fail'.]
We need to pick 'Fail' today.
[Another blessing of 'Fail' for
Yellow Team?]
[Mission Accomplished]
[Frigid]
Why success...
Let's make sure we 'Fail.'
Hoping for 'Fail'.
[Pledge for 'Fail' one more time!]
Thank you!
Alive! Bibimbap is alive!
Mix, mix, mix!
[Irony...
And the team of success in bitterness.]
[Cry face]
Congratulations, you're in second place...
[Refusal of compliment]
We never get a chance like this.
[Truly resentful success]
How many rounds are there?
[Food that they could've had endlessly.]
It was endless.
You came in at second place.
[Earned five medals.]
This is meaningless.
- Lee Kwang Soo...
- I'm so excited. We're the first place.
If you eat everything you want, how
can we be the representatives of beauty?
We can eat everything we want
and exercise.
It's already past two.
The standard rule of beauty is that you
don't eat anything past 1 o'clock.
Don't you know?
Do you have a
physical checkup tomorrow?
That's not it.
That's how I keep up my physique.
Do you have a blood test?
[Quiet but strong, Suspicious Eun Kyung.]
You don't need to look for a gourmet place.
The market is full of gourmet shops.
[Gourmet shops everywhere you
look in Gwangjang Market.]
Ha Ha! This is the biggest mistake you
made since you met me.
[Blaming himself]
I'm going crazy! Really...
When Dream (Ha Ha's son) grows up, don't
let him watch this episode.
You left a total failing mark in the history
of variety shows.
[Haroro, the day that he marked the biggest
mistake in the history of variety shows?]
We are the representatives of beauty!
- Let me introduce you to our Big Sister.
- Hello!
[And the cutesy parade by
the little sisters.]
Innocent look.
One, two, three!
[Innocent?]
Sweet face.
One, two, three!
Seoul, Seoul, Seoul, Seoul!
[Young Men of CN Blue,
full of excitement.]
[Arriving ahead of Yellow Team
after a shortcut.]
[Second attraction of Seoul,
Namsan O Tower.]
[You can look down on
the city of Seoul in one view.]
[A representative tourist site of Seoul.]
Take the cable car and go
to the gazebo in Namsan Tower.
Awesome!
[Romance incarnate-
Namsan Cable Car.]
- Where are you from?
- China.
I like China.
We are very famous program.
[Embarrassing]
Seriously! You're embarrassing!
[Kwang Ja, please...]
Do we have to say that ourselves?
Other people can say it for you.
We are... beautifulest.
What the heck are you saying?
[Alien language?
Appearance of 'beautifulest' again.]
[In Kwang Ja's dictionary, 'est'
in all words means superlative.]
Why are you embarrassing us?
[What a weird sister...]
[Hurry hurry]
You have to keep running in Running Man.
[Young men of CN Blue arrive.]
- CN Blue is here, too!
- Already?
We're going together?
Hey, they ate everything!
But we get on the cable car together!
What's this?
It'll be great if we end up having
a meeting!
[Shut the door!
Self bomb removal from the cable car.]
This is my first time.
[First time for the young men of
CN Blue at Namsan Tower.]
I'm from Seoul.
[Red Team on its way to the viewing
tower in a cable car.]
What a great view.
[Open Seoul view.]
Let's promote the cable car of Namsan
to the world!
Let's!
Namsan! Namsan! Namsan!
[Kind people... you'll receive lots of luck.]
Why can't you say anything?
Cheer Namsan!
Are you embarrassed of your sisters?
[A little...]
[Picturesque Seoul after the snow].
You get good exercise if you walk up
to Namsan.
Then you can climb up on your own time, Sis.
Namsan is a great place for exercise.
Sis, you'll develop muscles that way.
That's why you exercise!
He has 340 muscles all over his body.
It's so refreshing!
[Arrived in Namsan full of fresh air.]
[What's the mission at Namsan,
the center of Seoul tour?]
[In the middle of the plaza, in front
of Namsan Tower.]
[Colorful shirts and a drawing?]
Start with picking a mission order.
I think the middle one is good.
[Eun Kyung instead of Kwang Ja
whose right has been taken away.]
Please don't open it.
I'll explain first.
For this mission, with the background
of Seoul Tower that foreigners like
take a photo together.
Take a nice photo with citizens.
Open the paper to see what kind of
picture you need to take.
Pass if 15 people succeed in
'cham cham cham' together.
[My goodness!]
Fifteen people?
Hurry up and gather 15 citizens.
Fifteen people!
Take your red shirts.
Get ready!
Let's bring the guys we like!
[First casting for a boy eating a popsicle.]
Let's wear this. Hand!
How nice.
- Let's go take a pretty picture.
- Let's go!
Are you good at 'cham cham cham'?
[Blank Ji casts a young married couple
on a date.]
[Sister Jong Sook invited a
foreign tourist.]
[They need to hurry so they can try
the mission before other teams arrive.]
[Also together with Chinese kids on
a tour with their families.]
Let's wear this. Your arms!
We are Korean best, beautifulest.
[That darn 'beautifulest'...]
[It's Seoul, it's Seoul]
[Ca-ca-ca-ca cable car,
A little scary!]
[A lot of excitement]
[CN young men arrive at the tower
while singing the cable car song.]
[Yellow Team is still waiting
for a cable car.]
- We're from Jeju Island.
- Jeju island?
- Did you get here on a plane?
- Yes.
- When?
- It's my Grandpa's 70th birthday.
When can we do this?
You have two left. Pick one.
[Pick one of the two mission cards.]
[What kind of picture will they take?]
[Despair]
Pass if you take a picture
of 20 people jumping together.
Please bring 20 people.
Five each.
Anyone good at jumping?
Are you good at jumping?
[Search for jumping experts.]
Are you good in sports?
- Jump, one, two, three!
- Are you good in sports?
[Jump]
- We'll create a great memory for you.
- One, two, three!
[Surprise jump]
[Good. Quick reaction.]
I love Taiwan.
[Friendly Min Hyuk]
[Jump]
One, two, three!
Okay, okay!
- Your brother?
- Yes.
Together?
One, two, three, jump. Okay?
One, two, three!
Okay!
[Min Hyuk casted brothers from Taiwan.]
[Yellow Team arrived last.
Checking the mission order paper.]
Pass if you take a selfie together with 15
people, showing all eyes, noses, and mouths.
- Children...
- Isn't it better to have a tall person holding it?
[More advantageous to have a
tall person taking the picture?]
[Although they arrived late,
if they pass the mission first, 10 medals.]
He should have long arms!
[Found a foreigner who is very tall.]
[He has long arms, too.
Perfect body condition.]
Help us. Join us.
[But the communication is...]
- Game, game! Mission, mission!
- Okay.
[Not sure what it is,
but he accepted the request.]
- High five.
- We have one.
[Complete with casting Chris
in charge of the camera.]
We should have children.
Please help us. It's taking a picture.
You can wear this.
- Who do you like the best in Running Man?
- Ji Suk Jin!
Come here! Come here!
[Forced fans, selection by selfish motive
Brother Big Nose.]
Please wear this.
Come with us.
[So cute]
Wait, how many do we have now?
Now, number as you sit! Start!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven!
[Cute children and
Chris on opposite ends.]
[Red Team is complete with 15 people.]
Nice to meet you.
My name is Kim Jong Kook.
Why did they laugh?
[She finds Sister Jong Sook's
pronunciation funny.]
[Re-try]
My name is Kim Jong Kook.
We have all 15 people.
Now you have 19 people with
the 15 people who came.
- Please come this way.
- I'll interpret, too.
Can you tell them to take
three steps back?
One, two, three.
Come on, everybody!
[Easy to understand
Simple Kwang Ja's interpretation.]
Thank you. You're good.
Everyone, I'll say 'cham cham cham.'
What happens then?
You have to point the opposite way from me.
[Rule of 'cham cham cham'
Point to the opposite direction from the crew.]
[Time for Kwang Ja's interpretation]
[Cham cham cham!
Yay!]
No!]
[There can't be any more accurate
interpretation than this.]
- Do you know what their mission is?
- What is it?
They have to play 'cham cham cham' and
have everyone pointing the same direction.
We can't even do it with four...
[Preparing for the first trial of
Red Team's mission.]
[It's CN Blue!]
Ready!
So handsome!
Look this way!
We need to play 'cham cham cham' now!
[But the head keeps turning...]
[Beautiful]
[Sister... I'm sorry...]
[They're the only ones I can see now.]
[They look good...]
Jong Kook, her eyes are fixed
on CN Blue!
[The girl's head that's not turning back...]
[I'm going over to that team.]
- Who do you like the best?
- Everyone!
Then what about a hug?
Cham cham cham!
[My chin that is no longer mine...]
[Mission or whatever...
I'm so happy...]
[Come here! Sisters busting a team
member who lost her spirit.]
What are you doing?
Get yourself together!
- You can do it, right?
- She's about to faint.
You can do it, right?
[Wish came true.
I can do well now.]
You know this,
but turn your body completely, too.
Ready.
[Tension]
Cham cham cham!
[Oh my god...]
Husband! Husband!
[NG for the girl whose mind
is elsewhere...]
How many times did I tell you!
[Blank Ji and the fan girl turned
themselves in.]
Jong Sook,
please check who got it wrong.
No, we don't even need to check!
[Checking the photo]
We don't need to look...
[Come here]
He got it wrong, too!
Say something to him!
[This sister!]
Why did you do that?
[Disgraceful Kwang Ja who
pretended not to get it wrong.]
What's your name?
[Yellow Team in waiting
Six-year-old Yoon Chan from Busan.]
Say something in Busan dialect.
Dialect.
[So cute!]
[Blue Team's turn]
Let's go! Fighting!
Scream!
[Young blood! Blue Team overflowing
with fighting spirit!]
I'll blow the whistle without warning!
It'll go 'peak,' then 'snap.'
Peak, then snap. You don't know
when you'll hear the whistle.
[Interpreter Min Hyuk in this team.]
Okay, okay, we got it.
[Success only if the feet of all
20 people are in the air.]
- What grade are you in?
- We just became 7th grade.
We're fans of Leessang.
What are your names?
Lee Seo Kyung, got it.
[He's memorizing the name of
his fan Seo Kyung?]
[Ready]
Seo Kyung! Seo Kyung!
[Strategy to disturb their focus]
Seo Kyung! You said you're my fan!
[Success?]
We did it!
[Focused Seo Kyung despite
Gary's interruption?]
Everyone jumped!
[Oh! So far so good...]
[But... only Seo Kyung...]
[Oh...]
Seo Kyung! Seo Kyung!
It's okay, you did well.
You did well.
Gary called your name.
Thanks, Seo Kyung.
I won't forget this!
[Yellow Team's mission-
Taking a selfie with 15 people.]
- Chris already knows.
- Once chance, once chance!
Only one chance.
Just one push.
Okay, that TV monitor...
You see TV monitor, one...
Come together and put your
faces close together.
We can do it! Let's do it in one take!
[Chris and children, Fighting!]
- Let's do it!
- Just get up!
Put your faces next to mine.
Chris has to be in the picture, too.
Chris, your face inside.
Come closer, closer!
Huh? You already took it?
One shot! One shot!
He already took it?
[Already?]
Please check.
You need to have everyone's eyes,
nose and mouth showing.
[Everyone needs to look
at the camera...]
[What are they doing?]
[Look at the camera!]
[Yellow Team failed on the selfie mission.]
It's because we couldn't communicate
with Chris.
[Taking pictures without realizing
the situation.]
[Next time]
I need to check we're all here.
We have 15 children, right?
Right?
- We can't be nervous.
- Just throw your arm.
My hair? My hair is like a girl.
[I'm a girl]
I'm not a man.
[Ha ha ha ha]
[Red Team's little happy mood maker.]
[Re-trial for Yellow Team with the children
on a busy schedule.]
[Where did they go?
The ones from Taiwan...]
[Unexpected twist! They left
with their group to the next location.]
[Retrial only when they have 15 people]
[Adding one foreign tourist in a rush.]
- Can I take off my backpack?
- Yes, yes.
Don't worry, don't worry.
[Guide Yoo with the backpack on
and the scarf on.]
[Now, one more time...]
Put your faces together.
[However they say it, Chris
understands well.]
Long! Long!
Is Yoon Chan in? Yoon Chan!
Look at the camera.
Yoon Chan, look at the camera.
[Accept only if everyone's eyes, nose
and mouth are in the picture.]
[One, two, three as promised]
[How about this time?]
We did it! We did it!
[Wow! Perfect!]
[Yellow Team Mission Accomplished]
[How did it go?]
Chris, thank you!
[Successful strategy of Chris' long arm
plus children's small faces.]
[Yellow Team arrived last and finished
the mission first.]
[Congratulatory ceremony]
Thank you!
[Thanks everyone who helped.]
[Yellow Team's solidarity shined.]
It's a gift for you! Take it!
[Shirts for souvenirs]
They're so cute.
[Envy...]
We're getting a lot this time.
[Gained 10 medals for being first place
in the Namsan Tower mission.]
- This is a lot.
- Do we end up being the faces of Seoul?
[Currently Yellow Team earned 15 medals.]
[And leaves for the next site first.]
Should we just go for one direction?
It's luck anyway.
[Gamble.
Decide on one direction first then try?]
One direction?
[Good news to
'cham cham cham' delinquents.]
[Interpreter Kwang Ja appears again
for Chinese friends.]
[Agreement on pointing in the
right direction.]
[Would this strategy really work?]
[50/50 chance for success or fail.]
Think this is the last time. Please!
[Everyone pointing the same
direction as promised.]
[Now the issue is the direction of
the crew's finger.]
[Did the goddess of fortune
stand with them?]
[Everyone's pointing this direction
as promised.]
[The crew's hand
[Red Team Mission Accomplished]
We did it! We did it!
[Unified trick worked!]
[We're last again...]
[They get to circle around like the
Yellow Team they envied...]
[Upgrade! To the center!]
[To the back!]
Accomplished!
[Thank you everyone]
You are the second ones.
[Red Team gained five medals]
You received five medals.
Now please proceed to the next site.
Yes, we got it.
It's okay, we're the second place.
- This is pretty good.
- Yes, this is pretty good.
[Go, Yellow Team after a
complete turnaround.]
We could become the faces of Seoul.
[Conscience
Is that okay?]
- Why can't we?
- Right?
[Noise marketing also exists.]
[Jump]
[Everyone succeeded this time?]
[Oh... just one person]
Good feeling.
Retrial right away.]
We did it this time.
[Oh!]
[Success!]
[Finally a successful jump by everyone!]
[We do it too!]
[But... we're the last ones!]
[We appreciate all the citizens and
tourists for your help.]
- Go!
- Let's go, let's go!
[What's the next destination in Seoul?]
[Third attraction in Seoul]
[Korean Language Gaon Street
in Gwanghwamoon.]
This is my first time here.
Pass if you find consonants and vowels of
Korean alphabet hidden in the street
and put together the word
'hun min jung eum.'
Consonants and vowels are
hidden on this street.
You have to find them and put
together the word 'hun min jung eum'.
Can we steal another team's word
when they have theirs?
[If you hang the word on the board
in front of King Sejong, you win!]
- Okay!
- We got it!
Eun Kyung, why don't you join our team?
[Hangeul Gaon Street
that connects stories.]
Where is 'hun min jung eum' hidden?
[Take a close look]
[Did Big Nose find something?]
['M' of 'min' is found]
[Kwang Ja snatches it right away.]
[Jong Sook!]
It was there!
[There]
That's right!
[Red Team gained 'N' too]
- What are you doing, Eun Kyung?
- I just went blank all of a sudden.
[Flustered when everyone
came together suddenly?]
[Gained 'I' in no time!]
[Eun Kyung receives 'N' unexpectedly.]
[Sprint]
Eun Kyung, run away! I'm sorry!
[She handed over 'N' to Kwang Ja.]
What's this?
[Out of battery?]
- Are you staggering?
- To do this suddenly...
[Get your energy up...
We just started the race...]
[Blue Team found vowel 'eu']
We found it! Isn't this it?
It wasn't snow?
[Very densely packed snow?]
I thought it was snow.
Okay, so we're supposed to
look for these!
I found it! I found it! Okay!
[Blue Team gained
'EU' and 'M' in no time.]
[Obtained 'J' hanging up high
using a water bottle.]
[Of course she's our Ace!]
[This time, she gains 'O'.]
[Even 'M' and 'Hu'!]
Awesome! Where is my team?
[Ha Ha gains 'J'!]
[Ha Ha, even the vowel 'U']
[Fierce fight right next to him.]
[The scene of beautiful love (?)
for the Korean alphabet.]
[Eun Kyung hangs on even in
a 3:2 situation.]
Eun Kyung! Eun Kyung!
[She spends all the energy she gained from
eating at Gwangjang Market earlier.]
You don't even go easy on a girl!
[Such is the heartless world
of variety shows.]
[Begging?]
Just give me this one.
[She saved 'N']
[Just innocent Kwang Ja was caught.]
[Honey, I'm a girl!]
How can you be a girl?
- How can you be a girl?
- I'm in charge of beauty!
[Jong Sook gained a few.]
How many did you collect?
[Blue Team's Jung Shin and
Jong Hyun enter!]
[Attack right away!]
We don't have too many.
Let's negotiate. I'll give you one.
- You have too many.
- I'll give you one.
- Let's make it two.
- Okay, take this one first.
[Ok, Starts with 'O' out of
the two he has.]
And the hat for 'O' to make it 'H'
[Even 'U' to make 'H']
Look for one. There are a lot!
Look!
[Jong Sook is rushing to escape.]
[The whole CN Blue arrives!]
You haven't given me one.
There are a lot of them!
[Four hyenas chasing a tiger?]
[Plentiful]
Fools...
I can't do this.
[Trying to call a team member...]
Someone's coming!
[CN Blue Korean alphabet hyena
is coming!]
[Sprint for the food!]
Wait!
[Blank Ji escapes as she
throws food.]
[It's not easy to get Ace Blank Ji.]
Let me just use one.
Wait, my team! It's okay.
Why is she so fast?
[Putting together 'hun min jung eum'
with stolen consonants and vowels.]
[Complete through 'hun min jun']
[They only need 'O' and 'eum']
- Eun Kyung!
- Ji Hyo found a lot of them!
[Red Team reunited in the park.]
[CN Blue stole everything!]
[Same goes for Jong Sook, too!]
I had ten!
- We need 'u'!
- I had 'u'!
I gave it to them!
We have to get it back!
[Red Team Kwang Ja in action!]
[Kwang Ja jumps into the
center of hyenas.]
[Severe love for Korean.]
I need 'u'!
[Eun Kyung joins in.]
I'm sorry.
[Red Team vs. Blue Team.
Fierce Fight!]
- Eun Kyung, catch him!
- He's too fast.
[Did something pass by?]
Eun Kyung, he's not fast. You're slow!
[Totally exhausted.]
[Rambling]
Jae Suk, Giraffe is aiming for you.
Be careful!
[Kwang Ja is biting off from
every team.]
Eun Kyung!
Your sister is getting attacked!
[Eun Kyung is coming!]
Hey, come here!
[Interesting sight.
All three teams in one spot.]
[Intense battle to take
and to be taken.]
[Kwang Ja steals 'u']
[Bang!]
I can't see! Eun Kyung, take it!
[Passes 'u' to Eun Kyung just
like American football.]
Take it to Jong Kook!
Eun Kyung, I'm sorry.
[I'm tired too.]
[Yellow Team's mid-point check.]
I have 'min.'
[Blue Team is also putting together
'hun min jung eum'.]
[Eun Kyung saw Jong Sook.]
[Successfully protected 'u'!]
[Only a silly laugh from the
tough situation.]
Hurry, hurry, Eun Kyung!
Seriously... it's really Running Man
just like the show title.
There is no such thing as managing
my image here.
It's tougher than a sports day.
You feel like you're dying, right?
- I lost weight.
- It's not easy.
Let's go!
[Red Team arrives first at the
final destination.]
Once it's attached, it can't be stolen.
Let's hang it. 'H'!
[Putting together
'hun min jung eum' in order.]
[Short of 'N,' 'J,' 'EU,' 'M']
[Blue Team arrives!]
[Jong Sook attacks Blue Team
right away.]
[Blue Team hangs them first.]
[Red Team tries to stop.]
[This is how precious
'hun min jung eum' is.]
Don't you get ticklish?
No!
[Eun Kyung obtains 'J'.]
[Min Hyuk blocks Red Team's board.]
[A quick pass to Jong Sook.]
[It's almost like American football...]
[Eun Kyung's energy is depleted.]
[Blue Team's win only if they gain 'J'.]
[Yellow Team, Kwang Ja and
Blank Ji enter together.]
[I have to steal it...]
[Fight breaks out again.]
[Blue Team is complete if they
only have 'J'.]
[Sudden attack from Yong Hwa.]
[Yong Hwa obtains 'J'!]
[Now if they just hang 'J'.]
[Blue Team completes 'hun min jung eum'!]
[Blue Team CN Blue is first place!]
[Next, Red Team completes
'hun min jung eum'.]
[Delayed regret...]
Yes, we should've come sooner.
CN Blue, please come this way.
[First Place Blue Team- 10 Medals.]
[Proceed to 'S' duty-free shop
in Jangchung-dong.]
[Full of energy]
Eun Kyung, you said you wanted to run.
What happened?
I did run.
Watch it on TV.
- She wanted to run...
- I got tired and got on the ground.
[Run for five seconds,
then rest for five minutes?]
You said you heard about it
from Yon Jae.
You should've let me do some warm-ups,
but you told me to run out of nowhere...
This is how variety works.
[Arrival at 'S' duty-free shop
in Jangchung-dong.]
[The last mission to become the cultural
representatives of Seoul happens here!]
[They look like they're searching
for something...]
R Box...
[What? R Box?]
[Find two R Boxes hidden from the basement
through the third floor and gather to R Flag.]
[Many games are in R boxes.]
[Rule: They can decide to play the
game they find.]
[It's crucial to find the game that works]
well for the team as soon as possible.]
[Yong Hwa finds an R Box.]
I was born to be on Running Man.
[The game Yong Hwa found is
'stacking coins'.]
Stacking coins...
So I have one now?
Somewhere here...
[Jae Suk finds an R Box too.]
[Mr. Cylinder Game]
Okay!
Eun Kyung has her search pose on.
[Eun Kyung recovered energy.]
[Fast]
[007 Eun Kyung.
Moves seen in Hollywood spy movies.]
[Kkuk finds an R Box.]
['Name the time' game]
[They make their guesses on
what kind of game it is.]
I want to go shopping.
[Yong Hwa finds the second R Box.]
When I find it so quickly, it doesn't
feel right.
[Chicken Fight]
Can I defeat Jong Kook?
- Did you find any?
- No, Jae Suk.
- I found one. Let's go!
- Really?
[They need to find one more.]
- The game is good for us.
- Really? What is it?
- It's 'Mr. Cylinder' game.
- I found it!
[They find the second R Box.]
[What kind of game is in there?]
[Titanic Game]
[Titanic?]
[What kind of game is it?]
Where is the R Flag?
- Hurry!
- You're here first.
[Blue Team arrived first.]
[Yellow Team tries to switch a game.]
- Switch, switch!
- Okay.
[Both teams switched both games.]
[Red Team with no clue arrived, too.]
- You have two game boxes, right?
- Yes.
I said it's good to be the first team
to find the games.
[The special right given to the
first team to arrive.]
[The right to choose the game.]
[The team who wins in the game
has the right to choose the next game!]
We shouldn't have switched!
We can do this one.
[Blue Team has the right to
choose the first game.]
Please yell out the mission you
feel confident about.
If you don't win, it doesn't matter.
We'll go with luck.
For fun!
[A fair game for everyone?]
[Mr. Cylinder Game (Russian Roulette)]
[100 percent luck.
If the doll pops up, you lose.]
What happens if I smash the container?
One from each team will participate
in the game.
Only one has a different color at the tip.
Eun Kyung could get picked for
the chicken fight.
Is there a chicken fight?
[Oops]
[Alright...]
[Already in battle pose.]
What's wrong with you since the
market today?
[Betrayer (?) Haroro spilled the secret
of the chicken fight.]
[Hopeful]
Pick one please.
[It's Jong Hyun right away.]
It's Jong Hyun!
[Next, Yellow Team's drawing]
I don't think it's you, either.
It can't be me.
- As long as it's not me, it's okay.
- It's not me.
- It's you, Suk Jin!
- It's me?
You said it's not me!
We lost.
[Yellow Team's loss of will to fight
with the pick of the unlucky Big Nose.]
[Red Team is... Ji Hyo!]
[Pressure]
Now, you won't be just playing this game.
- There is one more thing.
- What is it?
- You have medals, right?
- Yes.
You have to decide as a team
how many medals you'll bet.
Wow, I don't know about
this one.
If your team wins, you get double.
If your team loses, everything is taken away.
- Let's bet everything.
- No, no.
- We'll end it all.
- No! What's wrong with you?
[He's going to cause big trouble...]
You're so nervous...
[Yellow Team bets five with
Haroro's persuasion.]
[Three for Blue Team]
[Three for Red Team, too]
Suk Jin is really lucky when
he is lucky.
If Mr. Cylinder flies away,
you fail right away.
It'll be funny if it comes up right away
when you push it in.
But that's not what we want.
[100 percent game of luck!
No one can say for sure!]
If it's not this, we have to do
the chicken fight.
[Chicken Fight Welcome]
I decided, I decided!
[Mr. Cylinder Roulette Game.
First Player Big Nose.]
[Success for Big Nose.]
[Next up is Jong Hyun.]
[Jong Hyun's rough, successful move.]
You still have a lot!
[Back to Big Nose's turn.]
I'm going to the second floor!
[Success for Big Nose's second trial.]
We still have a way to go.
- It feels like the second floor.
- You're lucky to begin with.
[Jong Hyun's easy success.]
- Ji Hyo, the other side.
- No, don't tell her. Ji Hyo will take care of it.
Don't do it!
What do you know about this?
It's popping up!
Not there! Not there!
[Big Nose's consistent attack on the
second floor is a success.]
[Tension builds up with each move.]
[Are you... that nervous?]
[There are only a few left.]
You have to go with the first one you see.
[Focused eyes]
- That's a good spot!
- It's popping up!
[Extremely tense for the viewers, too.]
- Just a place you see.
- That's right!
Does this game usually last so long?
White or red?
That's not important.
[Who cares about that...]
Challenge!
You took too long.
[Right now is the timing for variety?]
[Players and the viewers are
completely focused.]
- That's the one!
- You can't help it!
That's it! That's it!
Does it take this long?
[Fierce competition on Mr. Cylinder Game.]
- No, no!
- This one?
[Was this... such a fierce game?]
[Lucky guy Jong Hyun with a scream.]
Fighting!
Ji Suk, if Ji Hyo doesn't get it this time,
her team will pass.
We only have three left.
Ji Hyo's team will make it.
[If it's not Ji Hyo,
then it's one of the two.]
[Careful]
Ji Hyo, just do it. You shouldn't think.
This is the new unlucky celebrity.
He's the old unlucky celebrity.
This is the meeting of the old
and the new.
Ji Hyo, it's okay. You can do it!
[Moment of fate]
[Please... Please...]
[Crossing of happiness and sadness]
Red medals will be taken away.
You didn't touch anything, did you?
Good job!
- We can do it, Ji Hyo. It's okay.
- We can do it.
This is not important.
[Determining first place between
Big Nose and Jong Hyun.]
[If Yellow Team wins, it's
a hefty 10 medals.]
[Plus it seems they have a
secret game.]
I'll go first.
[Jong Hyun's speedy success.]
[No way!]
[In only two moves!]
[It took so long just now...
but in two moves...]
[The icon of misfortune, Big Nose,
even recognized by the God of Variety.]
[Surprising results
the more you think about it.]
I think your variety shows will go
well this year, but...
So the medals from Yellow Team
will be taken away, too.
Blue Team will take six medals.
[Blue Team earns medals!]
[The shock is not going away...]
We have two more games left.
Blue Team can choose a game again.
When I say one, two, three,
yell it out together!
One, two, three! Titanic game!
Okay!
[Why a water tank?]
[It doesn't look like a game
that requires physical strength.]
Now I will explain it to you.
There is a small glass bowl in the
water tank.
Everyone will take turns and add in
a marble in the bowl.
The bowl will get heavier.
[The team that sinks the bowl loses!]
- That's what Titanic meant!
- That's interesting!
[Sinking glass ship!
That's why it's Titanic!]
[Picking the player for the Titanic Game.]
[Blue Team's Min Hyuk is up!]
- One, two, three!
- It's me!
[Yellow Team's Gary is chosen!]
- You can do it!
- I can do it! I can do it!
I hope it's Eun Kyung.
[Kwang Ja got picked.]
That's great! He is the unluckiest one
in that team.
[Red Team is in crisis mode after
placing last in the previous game.]
[Yellow Team plays hard with five.]
[Three each for Blue Team and Red Team.]
- You play a timid game.
- We're not timid. We're feminine.
- Gary, I put my faith in you.
- Okay, okay.
Kwang Soo, do it right.
[She's so... worried...]
I'm really going to do it right
this time! I mean it!
[Challenge of determined Kwang Ja.]
I'm going!
[Kwang Ja makes a bold move and
adds a big marble.]
Go strong? Okay, let's go strong.
Go strong.
[Gary adds another big marble.]
It can come up to this much.
[They're still relaxed in the beginning.]
The one after me will get caught.
Not me!
- You're still fine.
- Then put it over here, on the edge.
- Put it in the end to balance.
- Once you drop, it's over.
Why don't you do it, Sister?
I wanted to be picked!
Eun Kyung, you should say something
too, about where to put it.
- This is the first time for me.
- It's first time for all of us.
[This kind of game is not common...]
[Meanwhile, Gary drops a baby marble.]
[Burst of criticism]
Play like a man, seriously!
I'm scared to meet a guy like you.
I'm afraid to meet a girl like you, too!
Jae Suk, this is why we broke up.
[What would be the fate of this glass boat?]
[The glass bowl is full of marbles]
[The audience wants the presence of
the Variety God on Kwang Ja.]
Kwang Ja, please save the variety show!
Put a small one in.
[As the marble size gets smaller,
hissing gets louder.]
That's not at all like Kwang Ja.
Kwang Ja, that's too small.
- Come back to the old you.
- Is this how big you are?
Is that your size?
Why do we have to talk about this?
Do I have to hear about the size
of my bowl too?
- Is that the size of your heart?
- Is this game to hurt people?
This is the size of your
future girlfriend's love for you.
Can I pick a bigger one?
Of course!
Kwang Soo, no!
It's really dangerous.
[He can't change the marble
once he picked one.]
Gary, it's really dangerous this time.
Really!
- It's really heavy. Not this one!
- It's okay.
Really?
[Middle-aged Big Nose
feels weak all of a sudden.]
Gary!
Seriously, that's not the right one!
- It's okay.
- Really? It's okay?
- That's not right...
Wait, stay still! It's moving!
Stand back!
You know about life?
Life doesn't fall apart so easily...
Nice, Gary!
Yes, show them!
[Min Hyuk also drops a big marble
following Gary.]
[This is men's titanic]
Hey, it's over this time.
We're done!
- Put it right here.
- We're done!
Right here.
- Here here.
- Kwang Ja, put it here.
- Put it right here.
- No, Kwang Soo, listen to me. Here.
Just put it down!
That's okay.
Three, two, one!
Gary, a small one.
It's lower than the water level,
but water's not coming in.
[Gary of no-ideas-no-thoughts
drops in a chic manner.]
[It's Min Hyuk's turn again.]
- Don't pretend to be so tough.
- Just do it fast! Don't look at it!
- Wait, it's dangerous.
- You have to go fast.
Three, two, one!
[Glass bowl floating lower than
the water level.]
It's really dangerous there.
[Kwang Ja drops carefully.]
How can it not drown?
[Gary drops again in a cool manner.]
[Min Hyuk drops next...]
[Sinking]
[Blue Team's loss.]
[Blue Team's medals are taken away.]
[Yellow Team's Big Nose vs.
Red Team's Eun Kyung]
We can go big now.
- Gary? Gary, this size is okay, right?
- Of course.
- Why do you ask Gary?
- Why not? He's on my team.
[Big Nose drops a marble]
- You can go with a big one.
- Yes.
Eun Kyung!
[Eun Kyung's success with
a big marble.]
Pretty cool.
Keep going with a big one.
- Not there!
- Why not?
[Dangerously tilted glass bowl.]
What am I supposed to do?
Every moment is nerve-wracking.
I really like Suk Jin, but I really hate to
be on the same team as him.
Hey, it's okay. Trust it!
You have to do well. On the right side!
Grab a big one.
Why don't you grab a big one?
I'm very timid.
I'm sure he's more timid.
I don't lose out to anyone.
[No. 1 King of Timid, Big Nose
full of pride.]
That's wrong.
Suk Jin's nickname is Baby Elephant Dumbo.
He's timid and he falls for lies easily,
so he's Baby Elephant Dumbo.
You told me to pick a big one,
so why do you pick a small one?
That's how life is.
[Life lessons learned in variety.]
- You can go with the mid-sized one.
- Sure, go with a mid-sized one.
[Shaky]
Please be careful!
[She became very bold.]
[But Big Nose Dumbo is agonizing with
a bean-sized marble.]
- I dropped a mid-sized one.
- This is my style.
Dumbo! Dumbo! Dumbo!
Flap, flap.
[Flappy ears that move even from
a light breeze.]
Flap, flap!
- Don't do that!
- Why?
[Flappy ears are flapping
one more time.]
- This looks good.
- You have to be careful.
- This is it.
- No, it's still okay.
- She picked a big one.
- A big one?
[Eun Kyung makes a bold move
and drops a pretty big one.]
[Just by looking, it seems dangerous.]
Please, please, just this time.
Nice, nice! Three, two, one!
[Big Nose's Success]
[Glass bowl went lower than
the water level again.]
[Time for sinking is coming close.]
You did it!
[Scary moment]
Please sink!
- Sink! Sink!
- Okay!
- It's good!
- Two, one!
Please...
[Eun Kyung's turn again.]
It's okay. You can do it.
We have to win.
Slowly!
[Lightly]
My goodness!
[Please...]
Three, two, one!
[Eun Kyung's miraculous success.]
It's okay! It's okay!
[Eun Kyung's legs gave out.]
[The marble... is dropped.]
[Titanic.
Red Team's win!]
You shouldn't have dropped that one.
You should've picked a smaller one.
Yellow Team's five medals will
be taken away.
[Red Team gains medals!]
[Finally the last mission to become
the faces of Seoul.]
[The final victory will be determined here!]
This is the last place for the
mission today.
First, Yellow Team, please move back
since you don't have any medals.
[Yellow Team has no medals?]
[Yellow Team bet all the remaining medals
on the third game, 'Stacking Coins'.]
[Yellow Team's player Jae Suk.]
When? When are you going to drop it? When?
[Yellow Team's loss.
All medals taken away.]
Therefore, Yellow Team lost the right
to participate in the final mission.
[Zero medals.
No right to participate in the final mission.]
Can you just give us one?
[Four empty-handed men...]
[Opening the last hurdle to become the
cultural representatives of Seoul.]
This is roulette!
[Giant Roulette]
Here is a giant roulette divided
into 100 sections.
You can put as many stickers as the
number of your medals on any place you want.
We have 25 medals.
We have 25.
[And zero for Yellow Team]
Can we each give one to Yellow Team?
[Wow, how did we get so lucky?]
There is no other angel like you.
[Suggestion of donation for two medals.
One from Blue Team, one from Red Team.]
We'll show you how we can
win with two.
It's not possible to get one of
the two out of 100.
[Kind Blank Ji.
Since they went through a lot together.]
[Blue Team's happy approval]
In my opinion, I think it's good to give you one
from our team and one from the other team.
- Thank you.
[Yellow Team gains two medals with
the grace of colleagues.]
- You are very kind.
- Don't live your life like that in the future.
You have to always go safely in life.
[Jong Sook,
a long speech after giving one sticker.]
We'll create a miracle with two stickers.
We need to show that there can
be hope like this.
[Blue Team in the strategy meeting
to determine how to put the stickers.]
[If they are picked, they become the faces
of Seoul. They need to be careful.]
[Blue Team is complete.]
[Red Team puts stickers on, too.]
[Finally, Yellow Team puts
two precious stickers.]
[Two percent of hope until the end.]
[Which is the one team that will become
the faces of Seoul?]
- Go strong!
- I'm really nervous!
[Yellow Team looks like they
already won.]
Aren't we really shameless?
With two yellow stickers...
- It's only once.
- Yes!
If you get the white color,
we'll turn the wheel again.
One, two, three!
[The giant roulette is going strong.]
[Who will be the faces of Seoul?]
- Yellow! Yellow!
- Red! Red!
Please! White, white!
White! White! Please, white!
[White was picked.
Rematch.]
White! White! White!
[Red Team missed victory
by one slice.]
One, two, three!
[Second match!]
[The roulette is going stronger
than the last time.]
[Cheering became more intense.]
[The final winner is determined
from this roulette.]
White!
[Who will be the cultural representatives
of Seoul from Running Man?]
[Blue Team- Final Winners!]
[Running Man's cultural representatives
of Seoul- CN Blue!]
[Red Team lost again by one slice.]
[Blue Team's joyful ceremony.]
I told you I had a good feeling about
this today, right?
The winner is CN Blue!
[CN Blue is the final winner!]
- Eun Kyung, you worked hard today.
- I thought we'd win.
This is my first time in a variety show.
I thought there would be some script.
Your sisters feel bad for you.
I'm sorry!
It's true reality. It was really fun.
I made really good memories.
Beautiful!
The faces of Seoul are CN Blue!
Subtitles by DramaFever
College Special.
[2014 Running Man College Festival]
[College students meet Running Man.]
You will make a boat together
and race across Han River.
[And... Back to the Han River]
We're back here again!
[Han River crossing race with
college students.]
[Nothing is impossible for Running Man.]
[Running Boats that are made with
materials beyond imagination.]
[What is the last boat in the
Han River race?]
[Running Man Next Week-
Han River Race.]