[Four years of history on Running Man.]
[Running Man's emblem.]
[Name tag elimination.]
[Between all the hiding and attacks
without a moment of rest...]
[they now have moments where they cannot
differentiate what's real and what's not.]
[And that's why...]
[they are now about to face all the thrills
of a World cup competition.]
[For the first time ever-
A live coverage of name tag elimination.]
[Welcome to MC Yoo's live show.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[April, 2014- 'A' park in Samamdong.]
[Jae Suk's brightly colored outfit.]
What is this that you have me
wearing right now?
[That's the outfit that you often see
during a wrestling match.]
Today is the day of Running Man's
2014 Idol Athletic Competition.
But why am I dressed like this?
Why am I dressed like this if
it's the day of the athletic competition?
- Today's competition...
- I guess I'm not participating today?
You are going to be our
MC of the day.
[Today's MC?]
Are you kidding me?
We're going to have some impressive
idol guests on our show today.
You won't be participating on any teams,
and you'll be the MC during the entire show.
- We've been wanting to do this for a while.
- You sure that'll be okay?
Are you sure that it'll be okay for others
if I don't participate on their team?
Can you take responsibility
for what the consequences may be?
Here's your mic and your cue cards.
This is so frustrating.
[MC Yoo is given the list of today's guests.]
This is no Idol Athletic Competition!
[Why?
We're this country's representative idols.]
Come on, are you serious?
Okay, fine.
Then can I just get started?
Okay.
Hello to all our viewers.
[MC Yoo opens up with his official MC voice.]
We are about to start our
2014 Idol Athletic Competition
on this beautiful spring day,
and I'm honored to be here as your MC.
Without further ado, I will now introduce
you all to the idols
who will be participating in our
2014 competition here today.
Let's all meet our first idol guest.
Please come on out!
[First idol guest of the competition.]
[Animal beasts- 2PM.]
What are you doing over there?
[Blank Ji has been transformed
into one of the beast idol members.]
[Overly confident entrance.]
[Precise movements.]
Nice!
[Blank Ji is pretty spot on
with her dance moves.]
Ma'am!
What are you doing?
[Blank Ji's heart is about to pound
right out of her chest with excitement.]
[2PM is about to make Blank Ji's heart
flutter right out of her chest.]
[Taking her heart right out of her chest?]
What are you doing over there?
Playing games with your hands?
What is this that you're doing
with your hand?
[Ending the dance with a romantic performance
from all the beastly members.]
[A ten out of ten performance!]
Please welcome 2PM to the competition!
Taecyeon couldn't be here with us today due to
a scheduling conflict with his weekend drama.
But a nice older lady seems to be here
to fill in his spot.
- What do you mean, an older lady?
- You are an older lady!
- I'm more like his older sister.
- With that bright red lipstick on your lips.
What are you trying to do here?
And here's our Nichkhun.
- Hello.
- I really didn't think that you'd come today.
- I couldn't miss out on this.
- I can't believe that Nichkhun came.
I had to come and see you.
I'm so happy to hear that you came to see me,
but when it comes to Running Man...
- I think this may be my 7th time on the show.
- It might be closer to ten times on the show.
You even came with us to Thailand,
and that episode was such a huge hit.
Our show became such a huge hit after that,
and you became pretty big too, so it's nice.
You know that you've become quite
successful since that episode aired.
- So when did you meet your girlfriend?
- I'm grateful for all my happiness.
I'm grateful for all my happiness.
[Aww... how cute.]
If you're happy with your life,
then what else could you wish for?
What's going on today?
- What's what going on?
- What is she up to?
- The weekend dramas are on right now.
- I'm not talking about weekend dramas.
- Are you talking about Taecyeon?
- No, I'm talking about Tiffany.
What is Tiffany doing?
[And here's the moment
we've all been waiting for.]
- She has the day off.
- She has the day off?
- Yes, she's sleeping.
- She's sleeping?
- So I guess you've already talked to her?
- Wow, it's hot out here.
Okay, please help me welcome
our next guests!
[Who are the second batch of their guests?]
[I'm the best... 2NE1.]
[What kind of collaboration
will they be showing us this time?]
[These older men have returned
to their 21 year old selves.]
[2NE1 team is full of energy!]
This feels like a real celebration.
Wow, this is awesome!
[Dancing Tiger.]
What is he doing?
[Extreme discomfort.]
[Crazy sense of rhythm.]
[The two men are about to
show off their own moves.]
[In perfect harmony.]
[Trying to one-up the idols with their
old dance moves.]
[His old 'door' dance moves which
he hasn't shown off in a while.]
Hip hop isn't all that difficult.
Just think of there being an imaginary door,
and you just need to step through the door.
[One step through the imaginary door,
and the dance move is over.]
Wow, I can't believe that
you're all here!
We've got the members of 2NE1,
and the two older delinquent boys here.
- What did you say?
- You're saying that you're not a delinquent?
You look like the bully that I used to see
during my school picnic outings.
I dressed with care today.
Is that tiger on your shirt
one of our guests today or something?
[MC Yoo's bratty behavior is trying
to put the tiger to shame.]
- Who's the participant here today?
- I am the Tiger!
What are you trying to do?
I'm just trying to live up to
my character.
This is seriously...
This is going to be an embarrassment.
- We want to see who the next guests are!
- Do they really have to come out?
- Ugh, seriously.
- We want to see who it is.
Let's welcome our last group of guests.
[The final group of idols who will
be the destroyers of the competition.]
[Wait, that song is...]
[They're idols?]
[Yoon Jong Shin and idols...
Jong Shin's Army.]
[Physically struggling idol...]
[Jong Shin- 45 ; Suk Jin- 48.
Their 'Get fit' dance.]
What are you guys doing right now?
[What kind of a performance do these
ancestor idols have in store for them?]
[Not too bad of a start.]
[Above anyone's expectation.]
[Ah... those were the days.]
None of you are in sync!
[Even though they've practiced the dance,
they can't remember the moves.]
[Crab dance?]
[Whatever, let's just circle around.]
[Jong Shin is finally starting to look happy.]
Okay, thank you for the performance.
[Protesting the end to their performance.]
- Your time is up.
- We had a grand finale!
- We still have this move left!
- We enjoyed your show.
Jong Shin, you should turn around and
take a look at what's on the screen.
[Jong Shin, 20 years ago in his prime.]
He's a part of our team as the leader.
Where are Yang Hyun Suk and
Park Jin Young?
Why do you ask?
I came out on the show because I was told
that they would be here today.
[He really didn't know...]
Thus, we have a total of three
teams today.
2PM, 2NE1, and Mystic89.
You will be divided into the three teams
that you see on stage here
and we will now start our
2014 Idol Athletic Competition!
[2014 Idol Athletic Competition.]
Sirs?
Please move faster and come this way.
Your shirt is made up of all our colors.
- I see that you're right. My shirt...
- Your shirt is all the team colors.
[The best kept secret that they're all
just starting to realize.]
- Ah, because there are three teams?
- Yes, that's right.
- Your shirt is hurting my eyes.
- Why?
- You should just go away.
You will be traveling to your various
destinations in your team car.
- What about Jae Suk?
- MC Yoo will have to drive by himself.
What? Why do I have to drive by myself when
everyone else is traveling with their teams?
- Are you a spy?
- What did you say?
- Are you a mafia member or a spy?
- Why would you travel alone otherwise?
MC Yoo will have to be the first one
to arrive at each location
and get all the preparations ready
for each game and mission.
Is he being punished or something?
[Must have everything prepped in
order for the show to go on smoothly.]
- I can't believe this. This is absurd.
- That's what you have to do as the MC.
[It's a lonely path that
MC Yoo must travel on.]
[On their way to first mission location.]
[Blank Ji is singing a duet with Jun K.]
[A true fan is showing her roots.
Blank Ji knows all the lyrics to a 2PM song.]
[Blank Ji is acknowledged as
a true fan of 2PM.]
That was awesome.
Just what are we doing today that
I have to drive there by myself?
How can I not be a part
of an athletic competition?
Seriously... how can you make me
dress in an outfit like this
when we have 2NE1 and 2PM
as our guests?
[It actually looks pretty good on you.]
We're here.
[Lone MC Yoo arrives at the destination.]
- Please come to the MC spot.
- Seriously.
What is all this?
Huh?
- And this is for you too.
- What is this?
[A vital tool for an MC-
A mini megaphone.]
- The first mission is a City Marathon.
- What's that?
All five members of each team will have to
come up with some sort of an act that is
befitting of the city and will have to run
in a marathon relay form.
And you will need to follow them along
and keep announcing what's going on
and lead them on to what they need to do.
[Iconic thoughtful MC Yoo-
A whole new way of MC'ing is on your way.]
- Let's go!
- You go on ahead, Ji Hyo.
Please pick up your speed.
Yes, that's right.
This is an athletic competition, so run.
- I think we need to hurry on over there.
- Are we in a rush?
It's 2PM.
Just as I had thought... very nice.
Ma'am, you must hurry.
Yes, that's right.
That's the 2PM I know.
- We're the first ones here.
- When it comes to athleticism...
The competitiveness of this team
is so admirable.
[Team 2PM is overflowing with energy.]
That's right.
That's the spirit.
This is the energy that we need to see.
What are you guys doing when everyone else
is running over to their positions?
Come on, you need to hurry.
Come on, pick up the pace.
You need to hurry it up.
[This team looks as though they're about to
start an office athletic competition.]
- Mystic! Mystic!
- Come this way, Team Mystic.
- Come this way.
- No, our spot is in the middle.
[They're greedy for the center spot even
though they were the last ones to arrive.]
What are you guys doing?
Anyway, thank you to everyone
for being here today.
As for your first mission,
it's going to be a marathon.
- It's a relay marathon.
- Seriously?
- It's a real marathon?
- You'll be running in a relay form.
There will be several missions along the way,
and you'll have to complete each mission.
The first team to cross the finish line after
completing all the mission wins the race.
The marathon will be done in teams.
- How long is the path?
- How would I know that?
- Stop asking me such useless questions.
- Why are you being so rude?
[Crabby MC Yoo]
- No more of these types of questions.
- What happened to the old Yoo Jae Suk?
I thought you were
supposed to be a very caring MC.
- Please step back.
- Who do you think you're trying to hit?
- What is that?
- Is that for each of the teams?
[Each team's music video tape
will be used as their batons.]
The last runner must run into the editing room
and play the video inside the case
and that music video will be played on an
endless replay mode for the rest of the day.
[The winning team's music video will be on
replay mode on Prism Tower's screen.]
- That sounds great for the winner.
- We have to make sure to win.
Run until your lungs burst!
- That's so awesome.
- That's so great.
[An unbelievable offer to the singers.]
[Their competitive streak is
up even higher.]
Okay, then I need everyone
to get in their position.
- Where is it?
- You need to tell us where we need to go.
- Just figure that out for yourselves.
- Tell us where we need to be.
Stop relying on your MC for everything,
and figure things out for yourselves.
- Where do we have to go?
- Just start walking and follow the cameras.
[MC Yoo is forcing them
to be more self-reliant.]
Only the first runners will remain here, and
the rest of you will have to find your spots.
[Who will be the lucky winners to
fill up this huge screen?]
When you round this corner,
around the corner of this building...
you're going to see a coffee shop.
You'll have to go into the shop and buy
a hot cup of Americano.
- Then give us some money.
- Look at him moving to the inner lane.
[Jung Chi slyly sneaks over
to the inner lane position.]
- Most men would concede that spot to a girl.
- Yes, that's right.
Why are you guys being like this?
[The inner lane is mine!]
What's that over there?
Number two is over there.
- Oh my goodness.
- What are those dogs doing there?
I see a bunch of dogs over there.
[What is the mission that they're going to
have to do with these large dogs?]
- I bet they've got something planned.
- Look at how big they are.
- Do you like animals?
- I like cats.
But dogs this size...
On my goodness!
Hi.
What do I do?
[In reality, Sandara is afraid of dogs.
What is she going to do?]
I think she's afraid of dogs.
The mission that you will have
to do here is
one member of the team will have to run
with the other member on their piggyback.
- Can I switch my spot?
- What are we going to do?
No, it's okay.
[Panic]
[But... there's someone who's more devastated
than any other at this bit of news.]
[Dear God...]
Is it going to be a pop quiz or something?
You have to run with these flippers on.
[R4- Run with flippers on.]
This is what a person naturally looks like
when they run with these things on.
[The final runner's mission.]
You have to run to the control room on
the sub terrain level to hand over your tape.
[Run to the control room on the sub terrain
level and hand over the tape to win.]
[Just who will be the winning team to
fill up this gigantic screen for the day?]
Okay everyone.
Okay, we will now be starting our marathon.
We've got Jung Chi, Park Bom, and Woo Young.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes, we're ready.
Okay, ready...
set... not yet, Park Bom.
That's some fierce competitiveness.
Don't you think that you're
going overboard?
Ready, set... go!
[Idol Athletic Competition-
City Relay Marathon- Start!]
[MC Yoo also gets on his way on his bike.]
Woo Young, Jo Jung Chi, and Park Bom.
They're all well on their way.
[Current standing-
Jung Chi, Woo Young, Park Bom.]
Where is the second position?
I'm at a total disadvantage.
[First mission-
Buy a steaming cup of Americano.]
- One cup of hot Americano, please.
- A hot cup of Americano.
You're not that far behind.
No need to lose hope for falling behind a bit.
[2NE1's Park Bom also arrives
at the coffee shop.]
Hello, one cup of Americano please.
Okay.
Seriously, what am I doing on this bike?
I should be one of the runners!
Did everyone get their hot cup
of Americano?
I didn't order a cookie.
[In the end, he parks his bike
to enter the coffee shop himself.]
- Hello.
- What took you so long to get here?
As you may all already know, there's no reason
to feel nervous for being a little slow.
As soon as you get the coffee...
there's the coffee right now.
- You startled me.
- I see it coming.
You have to take the tray with you.
[Jung Chi, from Team Mystic89,
is the first to get on his way.]
Okay, here we go again.
[Woo Young is also headed towards
R2 in second place.]
This is really hot!
Wow, that's so hot!
Park Bom is taking her time, isn't she?
[Totally unexpected!
Team Mystic89 is in the lead!]
- Mystic89!
- Yeah!
Why isn't my team member coming?
- Mystic89!
No, not yet.
You can't pass it off yet.
You have to have the coffee
and the cookie first.
I have to drink this?
[This steaming cup of coffee?]
What did you say?
You have to drink it first.
I have to drink this whole cup?
- Hurry, Woo Young!
- Hurry up and drink it.
Yes, you have to drink the coffee.
- You have to drink the coffee.
- Can I drink it for him?
- No, you can't.
- Drink it quickly.
Bom and Sandara don't drink coffee.
- Seriously?
- No, they don't.
[What are they going to do?
Neither Bom or Sandara drinks coffee.]
- If they have any coffee...
- They can't fall asleep?
- No, they can't.
- Do you have stuff going on tomorrow?
- No, we don't.
- Then they can sleep tomorrow.
Tell them to just study tonight.
Park Bom!
[Navigation and personal cheerleader-
A diverse MC Yoo.]
The one thing I hate the most is running.
I hate running the most.
[First and second place holders are currently
struggling to finish their cups of coffee.]
- Can we drink it together?
- What did you get?
- Ouch, that's so hot!
- Run!
- You have to drink this whole thing.
- There's no need to feel disappointed.
- Your coffee may even be cool by now.
- I can't drink that.
- I have to drink this myself?
- You two can drink it together.
- I can't drink this.
- I can't drink coffee either.
[The problem is that neither one of them
can drink coffee.]
[What are we going to do?]
Drink up.
[VJ Gwon Yeol to the rescue.]
Drink it up.
Are you listening to her?
'Drink it up!'
Cookie?
You want a cookie?
You like coffee, don't you?
Drink up the coffee.
[It's burning the roof of his mouth.]
You can finish it now.
We're finished.
[2PM also clears the mission.]
Once you're finished drinking it,
you have to shoot it into this basket.
Then you have to pick one of these dogs
and walk it over to R3.
[Come on, let's go!]
Challenge.
[Big-nose is first to take the shot.]
Ugh, I missed it.
I need to shoot it harder.
Challenge.
[Fail... fail...]
[In the end, even the PD in charge helps
gulp down the coffee for 2NE1.]
Come on, you need to hurry.
[Oh? Did it make it in?]
[It bounced off the side!]
The wind needs to stop blowing!
Stop the blowing wind!
Challenge.
[Will 2PM's Junho succeed this time?]
[Goal in!]
Okay, you may get going to the next stop.
This bike is mine.
[Please take me for a walk.]
Okay, you can get going now.
[Junho chooses the border collie
to take for a walk.]
- Okay, Junho is on his way.
- Let's go.
Okay, Junho is on his way.
Off to the next stop.
Junho is first to get on his way.
[Like the 2PM member walking him,
this border collie is full of energy.]
[And the bike riding MC is right on their tail
without ever resting his chattering mouth.]
[Meanwhile, these two are still struggling
to make their shots.]
This is seriously driving me crazy.
[2NE1's clean shot in the basket.]
- Do I have to pick one?
- You have to pick a dog.
We're in big trouble.
[Sandara with her fear of dogs chooses
the calm malamute to take with her.]
Come this way.
Where's the arrow?
Oh my goodness.
No, it's this way. Where are you going?
Come here.
You have to come this way.
Come on, let's go play.
Okay, this way.
What's this dog's name?
Oh my goodness!
[Sandara is being dragged along by a dog
that's as big as she is.]
- Come on, let's go. Lead it this way.
- Come on, let's go.
Nice dog.
No, not that way!
What is it?
What's wrong with you?
The other way...
we have to go the other way.
What a cute dog.
What's the dog's name?
This way.
Nice dog... good!
[Such elegance.]
This is no good.
[Big-nose passes by Sandara!]
Sandara!
Just pull it along!
I don't want to hurt its neck
by pulling too hard.
[Bom can no longer stand just watching,
so she runs over to help.]
Let's go.
- Give me the leash.
- I don't want to hurt its neck.
[Bom's authoritative charisma.]
- Follow the arrow marks.
- Let's go!
Hurry!
[2PM's Junho is almost to R3 already!]
Hurry up and give me the tape!
Hand over the baton to the third runner.
- Give me the tape.
- Hand over the baton.
[2PM is currently in the first place,
and the baton is passed to Blank Ji.]
- Can we just get going now?
- Yes, you may get going.
Okay, you guys are doing great.
[Running alongside the truck and the bus-
This is what a city marathon is all about.]
[Big-nose closes in on the R3 mark
soon thereafter.]
- One, two!
- Hurry!
- The dog looks so elegant!
What a sweet dog!
[An immediate U-turn.]
[Big-nose's petting of her head
must've rubbed her the wrong way.]
- Suk Jin!
- Hey!
[How dare you touch my head!]
[Big-nose tries one more time to
gently lead her back to position.]
[Current second place holder, Mystic89,
finally gets on their way.]
What are you saying is hurting you?
Okay, this way.
[2NE1 with their fantastic teamwork
also passes off their baton.]
Let's go!
[Mr. Capable's energy level
is through the roof!]
- I'm so sorry!
- No, it's okay.
[Giraffe transport is losing steam.]
[On the other hand, Tiger is catching up
quickly with frightening speed.]
[City Marathon's unknown variable-
The traffic light.]
Do you want to lean on something?
Like that tree over there?
- Maybe against that tree?
- Where do we have to go?
- Can we sit on something while we wait?
- I can hang on this post.
Are you okay?
[Runners in R4 are waiting anxiously.]
Look at how relaxed they look.
[Team 2PM is looking relaxed
and at ease.]
Where are my team members?
It's possible that the other team members
may be a while yet.
I thought you were just some
random bike rider passing us by.
[A random bike rider
in a colorful silk shirt.]
Hand him the tape.
[Blank Ji and Junho arrive at R4.]
[But the hand off isn't complete yet?]
You have to answer this question correctly
before the next runner can get on his way.
[They must answer MC Yoo's question.]
On your way to R4, there was something
about energy conservation.
The question is- Electricity is ___,
and the crude material is ___.
What are the missing words
in that question?
The answer was on your path to R4.
The question is- Electricity is 'blank',
and the crude material is 'blank'.
Electricity is...
Electricity has to be 'man-made',
and crude material is 'nature made'.
[Do you think that this is an essay exam?]
You can take another guess, Ji Hyo.
- Okay, let's go back for the answer.
- You sure the answer is back there?
[Turns back around to find the answer.]
He's like a solid piece of rock
on my back.
[Giraffe transport with rock Jong Shin
is almost depleted of his energy.]
Wait!
Wait a second!
It's digging into the spot
where I just had my surgery.
[A painful spot on his body...]
It's getting me right on that spot.
That really hurts.
Hey, my body is about to rip in half.
Someone help me!
I'm going to lose my balance if
you do that.
[Each and every step is purely
agonizing.]
You're just absurdly tall.
- Okay, there they are.
- Hurry!
- That's not my team members.
- Is that Jong Kook?
[Team 2NE1 arrives at R4.]
- We're in first place right now!
- A little bit more, Kim Jong Kook.
I had no idea how important it would be to
choose the right order of runners.
Hurry!
That's not the issue right now.
You can put her down now.
- I will now give you your question.
- I'm so sorry, Jong Kook!
[The charismatic rapper's voice is cracking
during her rushed apology.]
- I'm so sorry!
- No, it's okay.
- I'm really muscly and big boned.
- You have such a great personality.
[Though she may be fierce on stage,
she's actually a cute softie in person?]
Okay, here's your question.
On your way to R4, there was something
about energy conservation.
What are the last three digits of
HanJun Electric's Customer care number?
- HanJun's what?
- Customer care center.
- Is it '116'?
- No, it's not!
- The last three digits are?
- 116!
- You scared me for a moment.
- What are you doing?
- Ugh, you had me there for a moment.
- I can do whatever I want.
- Seriously...
- Where is it?
[Team 2PM is searching frantically
to find their answer.]
Jun K is acting really weird!
I think he must be really exhausted.
[Are you that exhausted?]
HanJun customer care!
[Oh? This is the answer
to Team 2NE1's question!]
[And right next to it...]
[Electric is domestic,
but material is imported.]
[The answer to their question
is discovered!]
[They must return and answer
their question!]
- You don't think they took the lead, do you?
- No, they don't have the answer either.
[Team 2NE1 is blindly guessing at their answer
to avoid having to go back.]
Should we go back?
123?
- That must not be right.
- Hurry up and tell us!
- The last three digits...
- 123.
[Amazing! Mr. Capable
can even guess the answers now!]
[But... huh?
When did he get all the way over there?]
[As soon as he heard the bell,
he sprinted off to R5!]
[But the problem is...
he didn't take the baton!]
- Baton! He didn't take the baton!
- Gary!
[Take the baton with you!]
[Can't hear you!]
[Members, and even the staff members
take off hot on Gary's trail.]
- Unbelievable!
- Gary! The baton!
[But I'm... full speed ahead Gary!]
Where's my bike?
My bike!
Your baton is right here!
No, no!
[But he's so far ahead that even the
cameras can't catch up to him.]
[Already down at the end of the street.]
Hey, Gary!
The baton!
You have to take this with you!
- Hey, you have to go back, and start over.
- I have to go all the way back?
You have to pass off the baton
at the R4 mark.
[Rule of the relay marathon.
Baton must be passed off at the starting line]
Come back here.
Come back to the starting line.
Hurry!
I really am completely exhausted right now.
- I really am completely exhausted right now.
- You wasted too much of your energy already.
- Why did you run so hard?
- Jong Kook is piggybacking him back.
[Tiger transport is back in business.]
- You have to pass off the baton.
- Okay, we're back.
- Hurry.
- Why did you just take off like that, Gary?
I'm completely exhausted right now.
Give me the baton.
[Back on his way with
the baton tape in his hand.]
[His speed has slowed down considerably.]
Come on, hurry!
[Team 2PM is anxious from having lost
their first place spot.]
Okay.
The question is- Electricity is ___,
and the crude material is ___.
Electricity is domestic,
but crude material is imported.
[Correct answer for 2PM.]
Wow, he's fast.
Gary!
Chansung!
Do you have a motor on your feet or something?
[Usain Bolt in flippers.]
Wait for me!
Ugh, why is he already here?
[Gary, having completely exhausted himself of
his energy for the first time in two years.]
[Usain flipper, Chansung is closing in
like a beast.]
Ugh, I'm too exhausted.
What is that?
Is that a koala?
- I feel like I'm going to poop my pants.
- You have to hold it.
Jong Shin, you have to hold on
really tight.
Okay, they're almost here.
[Can't believe what they're seeing.]
Why is he hanging on you like that?
What are you two doing?
CEO Yoon, why are you
hanging on him like that?
- Please come this way.
- You have to answer the question.
Everyone else is already gone.
Okay, here's your question.
You just passed by a bus stop.
What is the number of that bus stop?
- What many digits?
- It's a five digit number.
- We have to guess the five digit number?
- Yes, it's a five digit number.
- Not one, but five digits?
- What were you doing while hanging onto me?
- You should've taken notice of these things.
- You two should just go back and look.
- How are you going to guess the five digits?
- 11424?
11424?
[Are they seriously getting
their hopes up?]
11422.
11413.
11... you really are a bad man!
- Here comes someone.
- You see someone?
[Finally arriving at the final flag station.]
It's Gary!
Come on, Gary!
Run.
You try running in these things!
[Usain flipper Chansung's
final spurt of energy.]
[2PM's Nichkhun runs full speed ahead.]
[2NE1's Minzy takes off hot on his trail.]
[Will it be beast idol, Nichkhun
or Minzy of beastly female strength?]
[Cross the road over to the Prism Tower, and
insert their music video in the playing deck.]
No!
[Caught at the red light again!]
[Thanks to the unexpected turn of events,
Min Ji is given the chance to catch up.]
[The victory is any man's
game at this point.]
- Why don't you stay a bit longer?
- No, I have to get going.
No, stay just a little bit longer.
[MC Yoo abandons Team Mystic to MC
the first and second place teams.]
[Green light!]
He's way too fast!
[Both teams make it into the
Prism Tower!]
[They must now find the control room
on the subterranean floor.]
[2PM's Nichkhun is in the lead.]
[And Minzy is right on his tail.]
[A fierce battle between these two singers
with the music video hanging on the line.]
[Just who will be the first to find
the control room?]
[The other team members are anxiously
waiting in front of the huge screen.]
[The winning team's music video will be
played on the large screen all day long.]
- Who do you think will come on the screen?
- Excuse me?
- You know that it's not going to be us.
I don't even know where the rest
of my team members are right now.
[Right here...]
[But Team Mystic is still giving it their
best shot all the way through to the end.]
We lost.
We lost all because of Yoon Jong Shin.
[Oh, CEO Yoon...]
Okay, the winner of the marathon is?
[The music video that will be played on
this gigantic screen all day long is...]
[The victor of that honor is...]
[2PM? 2NE1?]
[The star of this honor is... 2PM!]
[City Relay Marathon- 2PM wins!]
[Having arrived by the split of a hair,
2PM's MV will be played all day long.]
Gary gave us some major laughter,
and 2PM wins this competition.
Chansung was so fast.
And in those flippers!
- This is for MC Yoo.
- Can I at least know what it is first?
Ah, prize for the first place winners?
To the winners of the first round, 2PM...
Here's your prize for winning the first round!
[First place prize for winning
the first round in the athletic competition.]
That's always a good thing to have.
[An unbelievable advantage is given to those
who have these coupons in the final round.]
Jung Chi actually has a radio show
that he needed to record today.
- He has a radio show he needs to get to.
- I have a prior work engagement.
Why do you have to have other
work scheduled today, of all days?
- Today's his only day that he has to do that.
- Seriously?
- He has to go?
- Will Jung Chi come back after his radio show?
His agency will decide that
for themselves.
[Just come back as soon as you can.]
- Then I will now get going first.
- Why are you leaving first?
- They keep telling me to go off first.
- Tell the MC to eat his lunch on his own.
You didn't even do anything,
so why would you be hungry?
I'll just get going first.
I'll see you all later.
Yes, I'll see you all in a bit.
Where am I being rushed off to now?
Just what...
It would be so nice if I could drive,
and eat with everyone else.
This is all for the fairness
of the game.
I would still be a fair judge
even without you going through all that.
[Telescopic field in Seoul]
Okay, everyone gather around.
[Second round in
the Idol Athletic Competition.]
- What do you think all that is?
- I'm not really sure.
[For this round of games,
Eddie Kim will join Team Mystic89.]
Everyone needs to put on the costumes
that you all see laid out behind you.
[MC Yoo instructs everyone to put on
the potato costumes.]
[The potato costume is hilarious to look at
even without them doing anything in it.]
The men should help the women
with their costumes.
- How am I going to move around in this?
- This is really hard to move around in.
- I've never worn anything like this before.
- This is your first time wearing it?
- She can't fit her head through.
- I can get my head through the opening.
Stop teasing me, Jong Kook.
I will now explain the rules
of your next game to you.
It's MC Yoo's Survival Game!
[MC Yoo's Survival Game.]
[What could that be?]
To explain MC Yoo's Survival Game simply
I will be the one to decide when and why any
one of you will be disqualified from the game.
[MC Yoo is in charge of deciding who will
stay and leave the game.]
There are several games that we've
prepared to determine who will stay or leave.
If you are not chosen or pass those games,
then those people will be disqualified.
The important thing is who will remain
to the end of the game.
The team whose member is the last player
remaining will be the winner of this round.
[A special advantage ticket will be given to
the team whose member is the last to remain.]
- I need all of you to yell out, 'Guess it'.
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
- Guess it!
- Yes, that's what you need to yell out.
Okay, the first game is...
Guess MC Yoo's taste buds!
- Yes, you need to guess my taste buds.
- Ramen.
- I know what he likes.
- You need to guess what I like to eat.
If you look over to your side,
there are five different dishes on the table.
He likes donkatsu.
You need to go and choose a dish
that you think I will like the best.
And of those five dishes, I will eat four
that I like, and I won't eat the other dish.
That's pretty cutthroat.
The person who brings the dish
that I don't eat will be disqualified.
- That's the way this game will be played.
- Why do we have to know what you like?
Just eat it!
- He's so unbelievable.
- Just eat whatever is brought to you.
I'm just going to pretend that
I didn't hear what he just said.
[He should be trying to get
on MC Yoo's good side...]
[Jong Shin immediately falls into
the butt-kissing mode.]
Yes, he's very whiney.
I'm going to tell you this right now.
I'm telling all of you this right now.
Don't bring the dish that Kim Jong Kook picks.
[All the decisions will be MC Yoo's choice.]
Go!
[Guess MC Yoo's taste buds!
Grab a flag while dressed in the potato suit!]
[Nude potato.]
[A fierce battle of the potatoes.]
[To be fair, MC Yoo
can't see who picks which flag.]
[Park Bom still hasn't been able to
pick up her flag.]
[She steals Jun K's flag instead
while he's incapacitated.]
- You shouldn't do that, Park Bom.
- There's another one right behind you.
[All their real personalities are
starting to shine.]
[Jun K potato is starting to show off
some gag moves while lying on the ground?]
Everyone needs to stand in a group with
others who have chosen the same dish.
[All the same dish holding people
must stand together in a group.]
[Ice cream-
Suk Jin, Nichkhun, Junho, Sandara Park.]
[Ramen- Jong Shin, Ha Ha,
Woo Young, Minzy.]
[Sweet and sour pork-
Muzy, Eddie Kim, Jun K, Gary.]
[Sweet bread-
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, Park Bom, CL.]
[Chicken- Chansung, Jong Kook.]
Okay, I will now get started.
I'm pretty full at the moment
and just like Ji Suk Jin just said,
these are dishes that I normally really like.
- Okay, I will now get started.
- I really don't know what he'll choose.
That sweet bread looks really good.
[Hmm...]
I know that he likes fried foods.
[Picking up those chopsticks
must mean...]
[Opens the lid to the pot of ramen.]
[The ramen group is cheering Jae Suk on.]
Even though I normally already love ramen,
I didn't have any soupy food with my lunch.
[It seems as though he's craving
something soupy.]
Can't you eat something else first?
You chose that real quick.
I know that I could eat this later,
but then the noodles would get soggy.
That's right!
[Ramen is chosen.]
[Jong Shin, Ha Ha, Woo Young,
and Minzy pass the round.]
I knew that he'd pick ramen.
Okay, I ate ramen for my first choice.
[The second dish that his taste buds
are craving is...]
Doesn't your mouth feel a little dry now?
I know what kind of foods you like.
Ugh, I don't know what to choose.
- Go for something sweet.
- Yes, satisfy your sweet tooth.
Right now... I don't want this to melt.
You should be saving that for the end.
[His eyes are locked on the ice cream.]
- You should save that for last.
- Just go ahead and eat it.
- Ugh, I just don't know.
- You need to eat real food first.
- I don't know.
- That looks so good.
You should save the dessert for last.
- You don't know the right way to eat.
- There's an order to how you should eat.
- Just eat what you're craving.
- Take a big bite out of it.
[About to take a bite!]
[Got happy for nothing...]
Be a man and take a big bite.
[This time... take a big bite.]
Stop being such a brat
and just eat it!
Who just said that?
[MC Yoo and the Tiger's never-ending
mind playing games.]
Seriously.
Just bite it off.
It's in his mouth.
[Suk Jin, Nichkhun, Junho, and
Sandara Park passes!]
I think you're going to get
a stomachache.
[Two out of five dishes are selected.]
[Only two more dishes left to go.]
I would eat all of this if I wasn't
so full already.
[MC Yoo is heading towards
the chicken.]
- That's going to make you fat.
- What a difference.
You need to eat some more.
There's no bad time to eat chicken.
That'll make you fat.
[About to take the bite.]
[Chicken is selected.]
[Jong Kook and Chansung pass
with their chicken selection.]
I didn't realize that was
Jong Kook's selection.
He's been ridiculing everything I do.
[This is so fun!]
[How can this be...]
[That food isn't going to sit well
in his stomach.]
[Bratty Tiger is getting on
MC Yoo's last nerve.]
I feel like I'm going to get indigestion.
Ugh, I'm going to get indigestion.
[Three out of five dishes are selected.]
[Just one more dish left to go.]
It's one or the other.
Either the bread or the sweet and sour pork.
[Sweet bread vs Sweet and sour pork.]
One of these dishes will not be eaten by me.
Those of you who chose that dish
will unfortunately be disqualified.
Make some noise for me.
Who chose the bread?
Yoo Jae Suk!
[Giraffe's ineffective cheering.]
Who chose the sweet and sour dish?
[Is that a girl screaming?]
- The bread?
- Yoo Jae Suk!
[Trying to sweeten him up?]
Sweet and sour pork?
[Please pick the sweet and sour pork!]
[MC Yoo's final dish selection.]
[Sweet and sour pork in the right hand,
and sweet break in the left hand.]
[MC Yoo's eating performance.]
[Please pick the bread.]
[Please pick the sweet and sour pork.]
[MC Yoo's explosive eating show.]
MC Yoo's decision.
Suk Jin's disqualified.
[MC Yoo's the one in power...]
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes.
Okay, I'm going to eat one
of these dishes.
[A very tense moment.]
Why do I feel so nervous
over such a trivial thing?
[Bread vs Sweet and sour pork.]
- So that's what he picked. Really?
- You have to swallow it.
[A bite-mark on the bread.]
[MC Yoo's final selection is the bread.]
[CL, Kwang Soo, Park Bom, and Ji Hyo pass.]
Yoo Jae Suk!
How can you get eliminated right away
during your first game?
[Muzy, Eddie Kim, Jun K, Gary-
Disqualified.]
We will now start our second game.
You know which game it'll be, right?
We don't know anything.
Just what is it that we're
supposed to do?
- Just leave us alone.
- I'm just an MC doing as I'm told.
And you guys are assistant MC's
to me right now.
- We're supposed to be your assistants?
- Yes, you are.
Okay, our second game is,
Mr. Can Game!
Mr. Can game will be our second game.
This is a random game of chance.
You will see several flags on the ground
with different numbers on each of them.
Just like with the earlier game,
you will each choose a numbered flag.
[Must select one of the flags on the ground
which are numbered from 1-14.]
The person who's holding the number which
pops out of the can will be eliminated.
[Starting with number one, the number that
pops out of the can will be eliminated.]
- What does that mean?
- Do you still not understand the game?
No, I still can't understand it.
Once everyone has a flag in their hand,
I'm going to play the Mr. Can game up here.
- Then a numbered knife will be inserted...
- Ah, that can game?
- Yes, that's right.
- I thought you meant the other Mr. Can.
No, that's not what we're doing.
[Not the Mr. Can from our distant memories.]
[It's the game, Mr. Can.]
- No, we're talking about the actual game.
- I get it now.
- I finally get it now.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes.
- Ready... get, go!
This is just a random game of chance.
[Everyone is carefully choosing their number
with intense focus and concentration.]
[Poor Giraffe and his tall height...]
Woo Young, and Bom still need to
pick their flags.
[Everyone completes their selection
of the flags.]
Okay, everyone has selected
their own flags.
[Mr. Can Pirate takes center stage.]
[They all line up in order from 1-14.]
Everyone needs to lift up their flags
so that we can all see your numbers.
- As long as it's not my number, I'm fine.
- I need my assistants to help me out.
What's the point of having to put my hand
on his shoulder?
- What's the point of doing this?
- It means that we're doing this together.
It means that we're doing this together.
It means that we're one as MC's.
We're MC'ing this game right now.
My arm is starting to hurt!
Just start the game already!
I thought it was the other Mr. Can.
I'm so disappointed now.
[Assistant MC's shoulder
is starting to hurt him.]
- His shoulder is hurting him.
- Then switch spots with him.
[MC army is switching up
their formation.]
It means that we're doing this together.
You're not assistant MC's for nothing.
Okay, we're going to do this together.
We'll start with number one.
- Number one would be the best.
- That would be so awesome.
It would be so awesome if
number one pops out.
[Back to being the bratty Tiger.]
You know that I'm very unlucky when it
comes to things like this, right?
[Mr. Yoo with his infamous streak of bad luck
when it comes to these games...]
[Bratty Tiger passes the test!]
[Too bad.]
Please move to the back if you've passed.
Next up is our Sandara!
Number two.
Okay, Sandara.
[Sandara Park passes.]
This is really nerve wrecking.
[Such a simple game,
but the nervous level is through the roof.]
I like the reactions from my assistant MC's.
[His assistant MC's are starting to find
their roles in the game.]
- Okay, number three.
- Why am I getting so nervous?
Okay, Chansung.
[The knife doesn't seem to be going in?]
No, I got it.
[He was only number three,
so how can this be?]
- No, number three was right.
- Are you sure that was the right slot?
And thus, Chansung is disqualified!
[Chansung of Team 2PM is disqualified.]
[Team Mystic89's Ha Ha also gets
disqualified from this round.]
[Final round of MC Yoo's Survival Game.]
So the final tally is, there are
still four members of Team 2PM left.
Nichkhun, Junho, Woo Young, and Blank Ji
are still left in the game.
And the only team with five members
still left in the game.
One person still hasn't been disqualified,
and is still left in the game.
[Team 2NE1's members still left in the game-
Jong Kook, CL, Park Bom, Sandara, and Minzy.]
- And Team Mystic89, they're already...
- The chance of us losing is getting higher.
- Our team members keeps getting disqualified.
- There are only tree of you left.
But you won't know what'll happen
until the game is over.
And for our third and final game,
it's MC Yoo's Challenge!
We will now start MC Yoo's Challenge.
Can you bring out the chin up bar?
Don't you think that puts us at
too great of a disadvantage?
[A giant metal bar is brought out.]
[MC Yoo's final round of game is,
The Chin Pull Up Bar.]
- Can someone give us a demonstration?
- Can Chansung please step up?
Please watch Chansung and
get a sense of what you'll have to do.
- Chansung is good at things like that.
- He's pretty light, so he'll be good.
Wow, he's good.
[Physical strength befitting of his
beast idol image.]
But the expression on his face
is starting to turn sour.
[Beast-like expression is starting to
show through on his face?]
- Chansung did 12.
- Chansung has 12.
Chansung is a very strong person,
with great athletic abilities.
[Chansung succeeds in getting 13.]
- Why don't we have Eddie give it a try?
- Show us how it's done.
Please show us how it's supposed to be done.
One, two, three...
[Light and easy movements.]
You're slowly starting to feel it, aren't you?
He started off nicely.
You have to keep going as
long as you can.
[Keep it up for as long as he can to
increase his screen time?]
- Thirteen.
- Do one more.
- One more, and you'll win.
- That's the only way for you to win.
[Eddie Kim succeeds in getting 14.]
- Okay, you will have to decide.
- Do we have to guess the number of pull-ups?
I will tell you how many I can do.
And you'll have to decide whether I'll be
able to do that many pull-ups or not.
[Must decide whether MC Yoo will be able
to do the number of pull-ups or not.]
Okay, I say...
[What's the number of pull-ups that MC Yoo
will decide on?]
18 pull-ups or more.
Yes, or no?
[Will he succeed in getting 18 or more
pull-ups or not?]
[MC Yoo calls out a pretty high number.]
How long has it been since you've
done chin pull-ups?
To be honest, it's been over a year
since I've last done any pull-ups.
- How much do you weigh?
- I weigh about 66-67kg.
[Second piece of information- Weighs 67kg.]
- Can I touch your body real quick?
- My body?
Yes, just lightly.
- Touches and checks his arms.
- Is your arm relaxed?
Don't you think that you're touching me
a little bit too much?
I don't think you should be
touching me that much.
[Coach Kkuk is checking out
the metal bar for himself.]
Okay, is everyone ready?
[The team with the most number of members
left at the end of this round wins the game.]
[Just like earlier, all three teams seem to
be struggling to make their decision.]
All three games we've played are all so simple
but they've all been so nerve wrecking.
He hasn't done it in a year.
[Will MC Yoo be able to succeed?]
What do we do?
[Will Jae Suk be able to do 18?
The result will determine the outcome.]
- Pick the higher possibility.
- Do you think this is a better bet?
[Fail- Jong Shin, Park Bom, Sandara Park,
Woo Young, and Nichkhun.]
[Succeed- Suk Jin, Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, CL,
Minzy, Ji Hyo and Junho.]
Okay, 18 was what I said.
[Nation's beloved 43 year old MC
attempts at getting 18.]
[With everyone watching his
every move...]
[Start the challenge.]
[With everyone counting along together...]
- He's shaking.
- Please! Come on!
[Both his arms are already
shaking considerably.]
What's wrong with him!
[Already succeeds in getting ten.]
Please show this nation
what you're capable of!
[Even though he may look like
he's struggling...]
[He's still not giving up on his challenge.]
[The onlookers look as though they're the ones
attempting the challenge themselves.]
[With every last ounce of his strength...]
[The ones who chose the 'Fail' side
are starting to look anxious...]
[A man who doesn't know
how to give up...]
[Just three more!]
[Everyone is cheering him on as one.]
[Looking quite exhausted.
However...]
[With the energy from their cheers,
he does his 16th pull-up.]
[Just two more.]
Republic of Korea!
Everyone's watching you right now!
[Just one more left to go...]
[They're all desperately
cheering him on as one.]
[He needs to make just one
more attempt.]
[Even though no one will blame him
even if he does end up failing...]
[But not even making the attempt
will be the true failure.]
[That's why...]
[I must try.]
[MC Yoo's challenge-
Succeeds in getting 18 pull-ups!]
[A truly admirable attempt
that they can't help but respect.]
[Never giving up in a battle
against himself...]
He's fierce.
[Fierce and admirable determination.]
Okay, everyone.
2NE1 wins!
[2NE1 wins with three members
still left in the game.]
[Team 2NE1 receives a special voucher.]
[Arrives at the final location.]
Can you hear me?
[Checking the mic in each of the rooms.]
Yes, we hear you.
Depressed Mystic Team,
can you hear me?
What is he saying?
[Seeing their angry reaction,
their mic seems to be working just fine.]
Okay everyone.
This is your ultimate final round.
We will now start one on one on one
name tag elimination game.
[1:1:1 name tag elimination.]
Each team will draw a number.
And the 1:1:1 name tag elimination will start
according to the number that you draw.
As soon as a member is eliminated,
the next player will come in immediately.
So the team with the last member still
in the game will win the whole competition.
[The team with the last member still left
in the game will win the whole competition.]
2NE1 members aren't girls.
- Why?
- They're just our chance at a win.
[This is CEO Yoon's competitive stance.]
We can't go easy on them.
Think of ourselves as a corporation.
Do you think that Jong Kook will
be concerned about the 2PM guys?
Yes, of course.
Don't you think that it would be wise for us
to team up with 2PM to eliminate Jong Kook?
- Yes, we should.
- Let's practice our sad face.
Can you do that?
Let me see.
You totally got it!
Keep that expression on your face.
[All he did was to take off his glasses.]
[I'm sorry for whatever I
may have done...]
You won a special privilege card when you won
the second round of games, right?
Yes, we did.
You can choose one member from
either one of the other teams
and you can deprive that person from
participating in the name tag elimination.
[Choose one person form either of the other
teams and prohibit them from participating.]
I think it would be wise to
choose one of the 2PM members.
- Yes, I agree.
- You're choosing one of the 2PM members?
I have a bit of a bad news for you.
One of you will not be able to participate
in the name tag elimination game.
[One member from Team 2PM will not be able
to participate in the name tag elimination.]
Team 2NE1 chose your team.
[The person who draws the 'x' ball will not
be able to participate in the game.]
[Blank Ji is chosen.]
No, that's bad!
- You're the best out of all of us.
- But are you really a 2PM member?
But I'm a member of Team 2PM.
Then I'll keep an eye on everything
and coach you guys through.
We should be okay then.
2014... Idol Athletic Competition.
We will now start our 1:1:1
name tag elimination game.
Everyone... as you may all already know,
there's no such thing as mercy in this game.
You will have to eliminate your opponents as
quickly as possible for you to survive.
Team 2NE1, Team Mystic89,
and Team 2PM.
The first player from each team
must now enter the game arena.
[Time for the first player
to make their entrance.]
The game will start as soon as
you come into the arena.
You have to rip off the name tag
from your opponents' backs.
It's the name tag elimination game.
[First player for Team 2PM- Woo Young.]
[First player for Team Mystic89- Muzy.]
[First player for Team 2NE1- Sandara Park.]
[The battle begins now.]
There's only one rule.
Eliminate your opponent's name tag.
Team 2NE1 with the most number of players,
with six members still left in the game.
And here comes one of our first players.
Here comes our players.
We've never broadcasted it live like this.
- Muzy has made his entrance.
- Why are you telling the others that?
I have to since I'm MC'ing this event.
Okay, Muzy is on the second floor
right now.
Okay, Muzy is on
the second floor right now.
[Teams in their own rooms can listen
to the live broadcast of the game.]
He's broadcasting the whole game?
[For the first time ever-
MC Yoo broadcasts the name tag elimination.]
This is a live broadcast of the game.
I hope everyone enjoys the game.
Even though I may not have looked like I was
doing anything today
I've been busier than anyone else.
I hope everyone recognizes that.
[Walking around to keep broadcasting
the show live to all the listeners.]
Seeing that I haven't heard anyone
screaming out loud yet...
It seems as though Muzy has gone down
to the first floor.
I can hear his cackling laughter,
and here he comes right now.
Muzy is passing by me right now.
Since this is a live broadcast,
he's now going to the third floor...
No, he's going back down to
the second floor.
- Okay, Muzy.
- Why are you telling everyone else all that?
- Why are you only talking about our team?
- What's wrong with him?
What kind of a live broadcast is this?
- He's only talking about Muzy.
- Not much has happened so far.
I think a couple of our players have just
run into each other on the first floor.
I think there's some action on the 1st floor,
and I'm going to go check right now.
[MC Yoo runs down to where
all the action is.]
It's getting to that time where we should
be getting our first elimination.
Ah, I can hear something down here.
There they are.
It's Woo Young!
[Muzy of Team Mystic,
and Woo Young of Team 2PM.]
It's 2PM's Woo Young!
[Total concentration.]
We still don't know who the first player is
from Team 2NE1.
Seeing how we still don't know who the
first player from Team 2NE1 is yet...
there's a high chance that it's
one of the female members.
There's a high chance that it's
[Sandara's immediate plan is
to stay in hiding for now.]
Why don't we shake hands
before we get started?
There's no time for that.
You must get started right away.
- I just want to shake your hand.
- Muzy's not to be taken lightly either.
[After offering a handshake in peace,
Muzy immediately launches into an attack.]
[Listening intently to the live broadcast.]
[In extreme danger!
Muzy's name tag is in Woo Young's hand!]
I don't know what's going to happen!
[MC Yoo's highly excited voice is
conveying the level of anxiousness.]
I don't know what's going to happen!
[Woo Young- Out!]
Woo Young is out!
Woo Young is ousted!
[A reaction similar to that
of a World cup win.]
Woo Young is ousted!
[A totally unexpected win by Muzy!]
Muzy!
Wow, Muzy!
That was totally unexpected!
How do you feel right now,
Woo Young?
You must be extremely flustered right now.
I started it off so nicely too!
How do you feel right now?
- I just feel really, really...
- Really, really, right?
I'm sure you must be quite
flustered at the moment.
How can this be?
[Team 2PM's first player-
Woo Young is out!]
Okay, 2PM's second player will now come out.
Second player to make his entrance.
I got it now.
I got the feel for it now.
I still have one more chance.
[Woo Young still has one more chance?]
- Remember the certificate that you received?
- Yes.
[Team 2PM earned a certificate when
they won the City Marathon game.]
That ticket will give one of the members
an extra life in the game.
[One member of the team will have two chances
to play in the game.]
[A lottery to pick who will get two lives
Oh no, what do I do?
[Woo Young is chosen.]
Ugh... it should've been Nichkhun.
Put your faith in me, Ji Hyo.
[I will pay this humiliation back tenfold.]
Woo Young was so very close.
[Off on his way to find
the next hot action spot.]
I have a feeling that Team Mystic89 is in
an extremely good mood right about now.
Ah, number two!
It's 2PM's Chansung.
- Yes, it's Chansung.
- Chansung is our second player.
Chansung's good.
You have to work together, Muzy.
Use your brain.
[Work together with the other team, Muzy.]
Okay, where could the 2NE1 player be?
2NE1 could really win if they keep up
this battle tactic.
I'm positive that the 2NE1 player
must be hiding out somewhere.
Yes, this is 2NE1's room.
Okay, so the first player...
So Sandara is the first player?
- Please don't say that.
- Be quiet.
[Once MC Yoo knows something,
then the rest of the world will also know.]
[Excited to hear that their opponent
is quite the easy prey.]
This is what live broadcasting is all about.
[Constantly moving live broadcast.]
Muzy is heading back down to the first floor.
He's pondering whether he should or not.
I think someone is heading up here.
I think someone is headed up
here right now.
[Chansung and Sandara.]
[And is that Sandara's name tag?]
[Just five minutes ago.]
Let's work together
and eliminate the other player.
[Team 2NE1's first player,
Sandara is out!]
Chansung has ousted Sandara Park.
Unfortunately, Sandara must now go up
to the eliminated player holding cell.
It's now time for Team 2NE1's
second player to come out.
[Team 2NE1's second player- Gary.]
You have to stick it out in there.
Last as long as you can.
With the exception of Team Mystic,
the other teams are now on their 2nd players.
No, I'm not going to do that.
It sounds as though there's something
going on up on the third floor.
Shall we go up and see what's
going on?
Let's check and see what's going on.
Gary.
- Gary is the second player.
- It's Gary.
It would be nice if Gary and Chansung
went at it against each other.
[All three players are now facing off
against each other on the third floor.]
Something tells me that these players
have agreed to work together.
Why are you two working together
and leaving me out in the cold?
They're right outside.
Fighting, Chansung!
Look at how relaxed they look.
None of our team members are smiling.
They look like a crazed group of lions
who are just dying to come out here.
Work together with them if you don't think
you can take them on, Chansung.
- There's Muzy...
- Why are you two closing in on me?
I have no other choice.
I already agreed that I would.
You have to be understanding, Chansung.
Your team has too many guys.
- Even though his team are also all guys...
- Mystic89 is still on their first player.
[His mouth never seems to take a break.]
There's no mercy when it comes to
the name tag elimination game.
Since I feel that this fight may get
a little rough...
Can you please keep it down?
You're making me feel even more nervous!
- Why do you keep doing that?
- It's because this is a live broadcast.
[What a bratty little MC.]
Chansung is slowly starting to
get backed into a corner.
Chansung is now being cornered.
[Gary and Muzy vs Chansung.]
Chansung must somehow get himself out.
Muzy is attempting to grab his right hand.
But Chansung's strength
is nothing to scoff at.
[Chansung's fierce defensive moves.]
Gary!
[As the battle escalates,
so does Jae Suk's voice.]
Muzy is now...
Chansung is way too strong!
Seriously!
He's like tuna fish!
[Strong Chansung Tuna.]
It's now or never!
Will it be Muzy or Gary?
[Muzy escapes another close call.]
[And Chansung is ousted.]
Muzy's name tag is in his hands...
Oh, Chansung is ousted!
- Muzy's good.
- He's really good.
Chansung is out.
Who will be 2PM's third player?
Amazingly enough,
Muzy is still left in the game.
He's a perfect member of our team.
You gave it your best shot, Chansung.
But it was nearly impossible to handle
those two by yourself.
It's not easy to be ganged up on, is it?
Two members of your team have now been
ousted by Muzy's sly moves.
Whatever the case, Chansung is now ousted.
How disappointing for Chansung!
[Junho also gets ousted by
Gary and Muzy.]
Gary and Muzy... I think it's about time
for those two to face off with one another.
Yes, I think the time has come for them
to battle one another.
If you keep this up...
Gary must make a cautious decision.
If Gary keeps working with Muzy,
and makes any mistakes...
then you might get betrayed and
get ousted by Muzy in the end.
Gary is the one who usually gets
betrayed in situations like this one.
- Do you know the idiom, Tosa-gu-pang?
- No, I've forgotten what that means.
It means that once a dog wears out
his usefulness to his master...
- Then I'll get abandoned?
- Yes, that's correct.
Come on, why would you say
something like that?
- Since we don't really know Muzy very well...
- Yes, you're right.
It's been fun.
There's nothing we can do about this.
[Finally... It's Gary vs Muzy.]
They just shook hands even though they didn't
really mean it, and they're now going to
start battling each other.
Gary's speed and strength are
quite impressive.
[Muzy's ferocious attack.]
Did he get your name tag?
Gary!
[Can Muzy really oust Gary?]
His name tag is in danger!
[Gary is in an extreme state of danger!]
No!
Gary!
Gary's in big trouble right now.
[By the split of a hair,
Muzy gets ousted first!]
[That's our Random Mr. Capable, Gary!]
Muzy is ousted!
That's our Gary!
CEO Yoon went to the bathroom again.
[Of all times, this is
when he has to go to the bathroom?]
Muzy is finally ousted!
[Team Mystic89's first player,
Muzy, is finally ousted!]
Can you edit out the shot of my stomach?
I was so concerned my stomach would show!
I'm seriously begging you.
Edit out that shot of my stomach.
[Yes, we'll do it for you.]
His stomach was shown on screen.
Muzy lasted for quite a while.
Team Mystic89's Muzy
has finally been ousted.
Even though your team still has a lot of
players left
but that still doesn't give you
a very good chance of winning.
I may not know about anything else,
but if our CEO Yoon is about to come out...
then I really pray that he won't come across
as looking sad or pathetic.
Muzy definitely pulled your weight
by doing the best you could for your team.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Muzy.
It's now time for Team Mystic89's
second player to come out.
There he is.
Nichkhun is finally here.
What the heck!
Can't we talk a little bit first?
[Show no mercy!
Immediately launches into attack mode.]
Gary is in big trouble now.
Nichkhun is in full attack mode.
Nichkhun already came out before
Muzy could even get out of here.
[Gary vs Nichkhun.]
Gary is once again showing us his stomach.
We can now see Gary's stomach again.
[Mr. Gary is so relatable.]
Nichkhun has very long arms.
But Gary's strength
is nothing to discount either.
Even though Nichkhun is strong himself...
If the next member of Team Mystic was to
come out now and join forces...
Actually, I can see Yoon Jong Shin
carefully making his approach right now.
[Just then, CEO Yoon makes his appearance.]
[Fails at an ambush attack on Nichkhun.]
He's eyeing Nichkhun's back.
[We told him not to do anything hasty...]
We can't forget that there's still Jong Kook
that we have to consider.
He's trying to talk this out.
Are you going to help me, Jong Shin?
If we oust that other team first...
Seeing how his stomach seems to have
more mass than his arms...
[His stomach looks more distended than
when he used to be on Family Outing.]
I'm going to join forces with Nichkhun.
[CEO Yoon and Nichkhun agree
to work together.]
Yoon Jong Shin and Nichkhun
have now allied.
Gary is currently backed up
against the wall.
If those two gang up on Gary together,
that will make things very tough for Gary.
Gary... Yoon Jong Shin has his left arm,
and Nichkhun has his right arm.
[Gary's surprise counterattack.]
But Nichkhun has very long arms.
[Gary escapes from imminent danger.]
Gary.
You're really strong.
[Is CEO Yoon trying to swap his
alliances with Gary this time?]
[Even his own team members are
speechless at the absurdity of his actions.]
Wow... seriously.
No, but we still need to get Jong Kook.
Sorry, Gary.
The two are back to attacking Gary together.
[CEO Yoon and Nichkhun resume
their alliances.]
Gary is backed up against the wall.
The hand is on his back!
[Gary is back in danger!]
Yoon Jong Shin is... look at him.
- Okay, I got it.
- I don't know what he thinks he got.
I don't know what he thinks
he's got right now.
[Yoon Jong Shin- Out!]
Yoon Jong Shin is out.
Yoon Jong Shin.
Just as everyone had predicted,
in all history of Running Man...
he was most pathetically...
He was most pathetically ousted.
The most pathetically ousted in
all history of Running Man.
I don't know what happened but
one arm just pulled me down.
I thought you were battling an anaconda.
- It was like you were battling an anaconda.
- Gary is amazing.
This darned Running Man show!
He's heading back down after showing us
one very pathetic sideshow.
One very pathetic show.
Swapping alliances here and there.
It's time for the next player of
Team Mystic89 to come out.
[Next player- Kwang Soo.]
[Even though he's normally a weak player,
he's a strong force amongst these members.]
[Huh?]
The third player is Lee Kwang Soo.
[Give me that mic!]
[Nichkhun rushes over immediately
after having heard the announcement.]
What are you going to do?
Are you going to attack me?
[Nichkhun vs Gary vs Kwang Soo.]
You need to think about this carefully, Khun.
We still have Jong Kook left to battle.
- Once I'm ousted, there's Jung Chi...
- You're talking like Jong Shin.
There's still Jung Chi, Dong Hoon, and
Suk Jin left.
Do you think you could eliminate
Jong Kook with them?
Let's say that you could
eliminate Jong Kook.
- Then can you eliminate him?
- Why wouldn't you be able to?
Are you going to eliminate
Kim Jong Kook or me?
Who do you think will be easier?
You have to be smart about this!
As long as we can oust Jong Kook together,
I don't care if I get ousted.
I like that idea too.
- Okay, fine.
- Who does Kim Jong Kook think he is?
I never said that.
Who does Kim Jong Kook think he is?
[Unbelievable...]
You can attack me if Jong Kook wasn't around,
but we still have Jong Kook left in the game.
Lee Kwang Soo has long arms,
and he's quite strong as well.
Trust me.
[Kwang Soo and Nichkhun ultimately
decides to join alliances in the end.]
- You're going to get betrayed.
- Nichkhun is slowly making his move.
Lee Kwang Soo and Nichkhun
are joining their alliances.
[How can this be?]
- No, that's not even right!
- He fell for it.
Lee Kwang Soo and Nichkhun
are joining their alliances.
I'll stand in front of you.
They have joined their alliances,
and Gary is being cornered right now.
[Gary vs Kwang Soo and Nichkhun.]
This is very different from when Jong Shin
and Nichkhun were attacking him earlier.
Lee Kwang Soo now has Gary locked
in his tight viselike grip.
[Is that Nichkhun's hand on
Kwang Soo's back?]
[Nichkhun ambushes Kwang Soo!]
[Kwang Soo- Out!]
Nichkhun betrays Kwang Soo!
- Nichkhun betrays Kwang Soo!
- Wow, Nichkhun...
Nichkhun betrayed Kwang Soo.
Nichkhun betrays Kwang Soo!
Nichkhun is the best!
Even if Kwang Soo offers his alliance,
don't ever trust him.
If he offers he alliance, agree to it,
then eliminate him right away.
[Their pre-race meeting.]
[Okay... went just as they had planned.]
[Betrayer Giraffe is betrayed by
his own deceitful plan.]
Nichkhun betrays Kwang Soo!
Team Mystic89's ace just
came down crumbling.
Team Mystic89 is in an utter state
of bewilderment right now.
- How can Nichkhun do that?
- Nichkhun betrays Kwang Soo.
- We have to oust the 2NE1 Team.
- Nichkhun just betrayed Kwang Soo.
[His fierce streak of competitiveness
behind the sweet and innocent face.]
[Okay, who's next?]
Okay, I'm searching around to see
where Gary could be hiding.
But I still haven't been able
to find him.
Something is happening on
the second floor.
I'm headed down right now to see
what's going on down there.
At last, Gary is besieged on the ground.
[There they all are.]
Ha Ha and Nichkhun are attacking Gary
together, but Gary isn't going down easily.
Nichkhun has Gary's left arm, and
Ha Ha is even using his legs to subdue him.
[Breaking out the arm bar move.]
He's breaking out the arm bar move!
I never realized that you needed moves
like that in the name tag elimination.
[Ha Ha locks him down with the arm bar move,
and Nichkhun takes care of the rest.]
Gary is ousted!
Gary is ousted.
[Gary ultimately gets ousted from
being ganged up on by the other two teams.]
[What cowards...]
I keep getting glances of this outfit,
and I really do not like it.
I can't believe that I've been
wearing this shirt all day.
I can't help but think that wearing this
outfit has been my real challenge.
We are now climbing up to
the third floor.
The next 2NE1 member that comes out
could be at a great disadvantage.
Oh my, look who it is.
It's Minzy.
But you have to remember that
Minzy is not your average girl.
- Minzy.
- Minzy is quite strong herself.
[It's not good to run into them
so quickly like that...]
- Ha Ha right now is...
- She's so strong!
- Nichkhun is...
- Come help me, Nichkhun!
Ha Ha, can you not handle her
by yourself?
I'm sure that you can see for yourself that
he can't, and that's why he's asking for help.
No!
[I can't believe they're ganging up
on a girl like that...]
[Gong Minzy- Out!]
- How disappointing for Minzy.
- Seriously.
[I can't take this anymore.]
Minzy had to have the strength of
two men to oust her out of the game.
[Fueled by desire for revenge.]
How could they have done that to a girl?
I'll be back.
- Fighting!
- See you later.
[You just all wait.]
[Because I'm on my way.]
There's a very tense air in the atmosphere
at the moment.
It's Jong Kook.
Kim Jong Kook has finally
made his way out.
[Even the announcement is enough
to give them a scare.]
[Who will face off
against this ferocious Tiger?]
It's war now.
Let's go.
Let's go right now.
After having listened to the live broadcast
of what just happened to Minzy
it's possible that Kim Jong Kook is more
fired up than he normally is.
[I have to find a good spot.
I need to surprise them with my attack.]
Come on in.
- He sounds so scary.
- He wants us to come in.
- Come on in.
- Kim Jong Kook is standing in the darkness.
- He's standing alone in the darkness.
- He's angry at us right now.
[The Tiger's rage could be seen
in the fiery glint in his eyes.]
Even from this far away distance,
I can see the anger simmering off of him.
This battle with Kim Jong Kook will be
the true highlight of today's competition.
[Jong Kook vs Ha Ha and Nichkhun.]
If Kim Jong Kook is defeated now,
that will make things very tough for 2NE1.
[Ha Ha is ousted in a blink of an eye.]
[Shaking in their boots.]
It's Jong Kook against Nichkhun!
Ha Ha's already ousted.
Ha Ha is ousted.
[Jong Kook vs Nichkhun]
[Mystic89's fifth player, Suk Jin,
runs out to help Nichkhun.]
After Jong Kook, there's CL...
there's the next player.
[Joins alliances with Nichkhun
as soon as he comes out on the scene.]
- You in, Nichkhun?
- Yes, I'm good with it.
Please be careful.
[Jong Kook eliminates Nichkhun's name tag
at the speed of light.]
[Nichkhun- Out!]
[Strongest player,
Tiger vs Weakest player, Impala.]
[What a tragic scene.]
[Suk Jin- Out.]
Ji Suk Jin is out.
[This scene almost puts the ousting
of CEO Yoon to shame.]
As you've seen in the past,
it's very angry Kim Jong Kook.
He looks very angry at the moment,
and even in his moment of anger...
Even though I feel a little fearful,
I'm still going to attempt an interview.
Even though I'm extremely
fearful right now...
I feel like I'm doing this interview by
putting my life on the line.
There was that brief moment of danger,
but you were able to escape it safely.
Do you feel that you have a chance
at winning?
- Yes, I see.
- We have to win.
- We've made it this far, so we have to win.
- Yes, I understand.
Can I have this back?
As you've all just heard, he vows that he'll
win since he's made it this far.
[Jung Chi and Jun K are busy
trying to scope out the scene.]
[Ferocious Tiger is requesting
a bottle of water.]
This is a very dangerous situation.
Please don't ever attempt to do this yourself
if you run into Jong Kook out on the streets.
If he's angered, then it could be
a very dangerous situation.
He's so quick!
Yes, here you go.
[Tiger spring his attack on Jung Chi.]
[Eliminates his name tag before anyone
can even realize what's happening.]
Did he get you?
[Jung Chi- Out!]
[Jun K is also ousted!]
It's time for the seventh player
to make his entrance.
[Only one more person left to defeat.]
[Woo Young makes another entrance with
the chance given to him by the certificate.]
At last, it's time for the final face-off.
[The final super match.]
[Woo Young vs Jong Kook.]
It's Woo Young.
[Woo Young's ambush attack.]
What are you doing?
It's Woo Young.
Jong Kook has him in his grasp.
Woo Young is caught in Jong Kook's grasp.
Jong Kook has lost a lot of energy from
having eliminated so many others earlier.
[No matter how strong he may be,
there's a limit to his stamina.]
[Woo Young escapes his moment of danger
with a surprising spurt of speed.]
Woo Young!
[Everyone's totally focused on
the broadcast.]
Woo Young and the name tag!
He almost has the name tag in his hands!
[Jong Kook and Woo Young both have
each other's name tags on their hands.]
They're spinning around in circles!
Jong Kook has Woo Young's name tag!
[Will he eliminate it...
or will he be eliminated?]
[Woo Young- Out!]
[2NE1 wins!]
We won!
[Celebration of sheer joy!]
The winning team of the 2014
Running Man Idol Athletic Competition!
Congratulations to 2NE1!
[2014 Idol Athletic Competition-
2NE1 wins!]
I would like to say a word
to Hyun Suk.
Buy me dinner.
Buy us dinner.
Can you express that message
to Hyun Suk with a dance?
[Buy me dinner.]
[The doorstep hip hop dance
which never seems to get old.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Everything is flipped around backwards.]
[Once the mystical pill is swallowed...]
[then time travel to the past starts.]
[Time to determine a new victor.]
January 29, 2011.
[A new twist to
Sherlock Holmes' mystery.]
[What if they were to go back to the moment
when Yoo-ames Bond was locked up in jail?]
- What's his special power?
- Don't do this to me!
[Next Week's Running Man-
Running Man's Time Travel.]