Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man- Cooking Battle]
[Kang Gary- 36 Years Old.
2014 Cooking Battle Contestant.]
I'm not sure, I don't really remember what
it tasted like the first time I tried it.
All I remember is the sweetness,
and the slight savory taste.
That's the taste I remember in my mouth.
That I believe... was none other than love.
[New Year, 2014.]
[New Year's first dinner table.]
[What would you like to have?]
[Food battle for the honor of being the first
dinner of the New Year starts now.]
[Determine which will be the ultimate
dinner menu for the new year.]
[A battle more serious and sincere
than any other battle in their history.]
[Ultimate ingredients and cooking secrets
they've gathered from all over the country.]
It's a work of art.
One cup of rice, and five cups of water.
[Put everything that you have
into your cooking.]
I've been given the secret,
and I've brought its art to life.
[And judged by the best
chefs in the country.]
You've ruined it.
You've totally ruined the dish.
[Cooking is no joke.]
[14 hours earlier-
Somewhere in Gyunggi-Do.]
[A gas station?]
[Jae Suk makes a lone appearance.]
- This is our first show of 2014.
- Yes, I'm aware.
Happy New Year.
It seems as though all our members have been
scattered separately in different locations?
[At the same time- Jeonra Station.]
Happy New Year to everyone.
It's 2014.
And I've been cast away
by myself somewhere again.
I'm so lonely.
[At the same time- Seoul Gimpo Airport.]
[Who's at the airport?]
Did you have some ramen
late last night?
[Gary's face is all bloated from having
eaten salty ramen late the night before.]
[At the same time- Kyungsang Harbor.]
This is the harbor in my hometown.
[Blank Ji is excited
to be back in her hometown.]
I'm back in my hometown today.
This is my hometown's most famous spot
called, the 'Homigot'.
This is the spot where it's said that
the sun rises the earliest in our country.
[Homigot is said to be the landmark where
the sun rises the earliest in our country.]
[We wish everyone the happiest 2014.]
[But what is Blank Ji doing here?]
There's something else
I want to point out about this place.
I really wish that Jae Suk and
Ha Ha were here with me right now.
I bet they'd be shaking in fear right now
if they were to see this.
When I was little...
I used to spend my time by the water here
catching crabs and clams.
This is what I'm very familiar with because
this is the environment I grew up in.
[What reason did Blank Ji have to
come back to her faraway hometown?]
[What is the reason for all the members being
scattered separately all on their own?]
Why are you making me feel so lonely by
separating me from the other members like this?
This is your first mission of the new year.
[Time to pass out the first mission
of the new year.]
What is it?
Find your mate inside the gas station.
It's not Ji Hyo, is it?
You have to go find your mate.
- Is it a guest?
- Yes.
Am I going to get coupled off?
Go find your mate inside the hair salon
who's in there waiting for you.
[First mission of the new year-
Find your mate!]
A mate?
Are we doing our race with a mate?
Am I going to be paired off
with Kang Gary again?
Is it going to be Song Ji Hyo?
Hang on a second.
It's a girl.
This coat is a girl's size.
He's here.
He just came in through the doors.
[Who could Gary's mate be?]
I'm nervous.
Who could this person be
that's making my heart flutter?
[Who are the people that are making
these members' hearts flutter?]
Who could it be?
[Jae Suk is searching through the gas station
to find his mate.]
I don't see anyone in there.
Hello.
[Sharing New Year's greetings with his fans
in between doing his mission.]
I'm curious to see who it is.
What if it's Kwang Gyu again?
It can't be, can it?
[The back of his head...]
Seriously?
It's him?
[Immediate disappointment?]
Come out here, Soo Hong.
Excuse me.
I said, come out here, Soo Hong.
What are you... seriously?
- What are you doing here?
- Shouldn't you be shocked and surprised?
[Jae Suk's mate- Park Soo Hong.]
- I can't believe it's him.
- I don't like being stuck with you either.
- Come here. Come here right now.
- Can't you at least say 'hi'?
[Their 20 years plus of friendship leads
to bickering the moment they see each other.]
- Sorry for all this.
- Thank you for everything.
- Please excuse us.
- Do you want to take a picture with me first?
Hurry up and get out here.
- What's going on?
- What are you doing here?
They went to the trouble of letting me hide,
so I at least wanted her to get a picture.
Why do you want her to take a picture with
you when she doesn't even want one?
- I just wanted to be considerate.
- That's not being considerate.
- Then you should've just taken one.
- Jae Suk.
- Don't you know how to greet someone?
- There you go again.
They told me that it was going to be
a couple race and I got Park Soo Hong.
I thought it would be someone better.
Why does it have to be you of all people?
- Anyways, good to see you.
- Right?
To introduce him briefly, he's
an old friend whom I like considerably.
Also, Happy New Year to all our viewers.
My partner is Park Soo Hong.
He's an old bachelor.
He's past the old bachelor status.
You can just think of him as an icon of all
the old single men who live by themselves.
He and I graduated college together
back in 1991.
He's two years older than me.
He is the sign of the dog, born in 1970.
[Soo Hong isn't able to say a word
as Jae Suk does all the introduction for him.]
I can't believe I'm partnered up with you.
What?
I'm right.
And since we're now in year the 2014,
he is now 45 years old.
He has five years left
before he turns 50 years old.
He is a very dear friend of mine.
Say hello, and wish everyone a happy new year.
- I've already given your introduction.
- You call that an introduction?
Am I just here for comic relief?
Shouldn't you let me talk since
I'm on the show as a guest?
- I am talking to you.
- That's not talking.
It's true that things are going well for you
since you're such a chatterbox...
- But are you kidding?
- He loves to cook.
He also loves to go clubbing.
Even though he did tell me that he will
continue to go clubbing in the new year
it's still nice to see him out and about,
especially as a guest on our show.
- It's good to see you, Soo Hong.
- Jae Suk.
My partner is, Park Soo Hong.
This is Running Man's first episode of 2014.
[Anyways, please meet Jae Suk's partner,
Park Soo Hong.]
[Then who's Ji Hyo's partner?]
Partner!
Have you seen anyone who's dressed
in the same outfit as I am?
[She sees someone in the distance who's
dressed in the same outfit as she is?]
[Even just the silhouette suggests
that the partner is a man.]
[Who is this man,
who's to be Ji Hyo's partner?]
[Who could it be?]
Partner.
[Ji Hyo's partner- Lee Dong Wook.]
[I know who it is!]
Lee Dong Wook!
[Friends of the same age
that she recognizes at once.]
Lee Dong Wook!
[Friend!]
[So happy to see a friend
in my own hometown.]
- Good to see you, Dong Wook. Happy New Year.
- Same to you.
We were in a recent drama together,
and he played a married man I had a crush on.
[Dong Wook played married man in a drama that
Blank Ji chased after in their recent drama.]
- Good to see you, Dong Wook.
- It's good to see you too.
[Reunited as partners.]
- There's something that I'm curious about.
- Okay.
Why did we come all the way here?
We're here... to sight-see.
Isn't it nice?
Look over there.
- Look at how beautiful it is here.
- You need to do a better job.
Why are you making me carry
our segment of the show?
[These two friends immediately bicker
back and forth as well.]
- Wish everyone a happy new year.
- How about a grand bow to our viewers?
- Right here?
- Of course.
- Where else would we do it?
Happy New Year to all our viewers.
- Please look kindly upon me in the new year.
- We wish you all a year full of good health.
Please give a lot of support to Running Man,
and to Dong Wook as well.
Please show a lot of love
for my hometown as well.
[Big-nose is waiting for his partner in front
of his partner's home.]
You have a very nice figure.
Who are you?
[This person is...]
[With her long lean legs...]
[And long straight hair?]
[And a slender body to boot?
Who could Big-nose's partner be?]
Are you a man or a woman?
[Who could it be?]
[Big-nose's partner is the total opposite
of what he was expecting!]
[Suk Jin's partner- Kim Kyung Ho.]
I had really high hopes when I saw
your long flowy hair.
- Did I disappoint you?
- No, you didn't disappoint me.
- You sure?
- Okay, just a little.
- Have you been well?
- I'm starting off 2014 with Kim Kyung Ho.
- It's nice to see you.
- Really good to see you. It's been too long.
[Kwang Soo is waiting with anticipation
for his partner as well.]
Park?
What are you doing here?
[John Park?
The Idiot Brothers are reunited?]
[Kwang Soo's partner- John Park.]
Kwang-Park-Cross!
- I've gotten better, haven't I?
- You must've been practicing a lot.
[John seems to have practiced their
teams' battle cry.]
[Who's Gary's partner whose been waiting
for him at the airport?]
[Gary's partner- Rainbow's Jae Kyung.]
I can't believe that
I'm partnered with Jae Kyung.
You guys have been too kind to me.
You're so pretty, Jae Kyung.
Thank you.
Can he be any more obvious?
What is he doing?
Why is he being so obvious?
Listen to that voice!
I bet he's an actor.
Pretty impressive.
Sir!
It's nice to meet you.
[Ha Ha's partner- Infinite's Sung Kyu.]
You and I are a team?
This is a good match.
He and I are a good fit.
- This is actually my hometown.
- Seriously?
[They find out that Jeonju is
Sung Kyu's actual hometown!]
- I know this area very well.
- Hello everyone.
Did you know that Infinite's Sung Kyu
originates from Jeonju?
- No one knew.
- I don't think they even know who I am.
How can this even be possible?
[Last but not least, who's Kkuk's partner?]
[Cautiously walks into the hair salon.]
If it's someone who's getting their
hair done at the salon at this hour...
[Someone does seem to be in the room...]
Is she... my partner?
That model in there?
[That's the world famous model,
Song Kyung Ah...]
[Is she... or isn't she?]
Hello.
By any chance...
- Are you here to be a guest on Running Man?
- No, I'm here to prep for a photo-shoot.
I see, I'm sorry.
I apologize for the intrusion.
I thought you were here for Running Man.
You're a famous model, right?
Yes.
She's not the one.
[I was told that my partner
would be in here...]
Is someone who's supposed to guest on
Running Man in here right now?
Are you here to guest on Running Man?
[Even asking the salon clients...]
Wait a minute.
I see some things in here.
I guess not.
Are you a photographer?
[How strange...]
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you again.
But it's just that there's
no one else in here.
I was told that someone would be in here.
I was told that my partner would be in here.
Sorry, but I'm sure I'll be back again later.
This is really strange.
No one else is in here.
[Where's my partner?]
[Carefully searching through every inch
and corner of the salon for his partner.]
[That's so strange...
There's no one else in here...]
[Back to Song Kyung Ah's room
for the third time.]
- It's just that there's no one else...
- I'm actually here for a Running Man shoot.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello!
[Jong Kook's partner- Song Kyung Ah.]
She really is a world famous model.
[Kkuk was completely fooled by the joke
played by the world famous model.]
Wow, but you really are...
- She really is very tall.
- I'm sorry, but I wore my heels today.
- I'm sorry for making you feel uncomfortable.
- No, it's okay.
- No, I'm not bothered by it whatsoever.
- He keeps backing away from me.
- But if I stand too close to you...
- You keep backing away from me.
Can you guys pose for a picture together
since you two are a team?
Can we do the picture once she
changes out of her clothes?
We're starting the mission by ourselves?
[It's an all day mission
with just their partner only.]
Are we going to be spies or something?
I've been waiting for a day like that to come
for the past three years, but...
Oh! We've got a text.
[Everyone gets a text message regarding
their mission at the same time.]
The dawn of the new year
has risen again.
Running Man's first mission
for the year 2014...
- It's Running Man's 2014 Cooking Battle.
- Cooking battle?
What?
A cooking battle?
[Soo Hong has yet to even say a word.]
- A cooking battle?
- A cooking battle.
- Are you a good cook?
- I'm a really good cook.
- I'm really good at cooking.
- You know how to cook?
- You're a good cook, right?
- I can't cook.
- You can't cook?
- Are you a good cook?
I don't really know how to cook.
Along with your partner... partner.
The team that wins at the final judging
of your cooking wins the entire race.
The theme of your cooking is,
'2014's first dinner menu'.
Please make a dish that you'd most
like to eat as your dish for the competition.
- Nangmyun.
- When the competition...
[Simple 'nangmyun mania'.]
The cooking competition will start
at seven o'clock this evening.
You'll only be able to participate if you can
get all the secrets and ingredients by then.
We will now start our
2014 Running Man Cooking Battle.
- Go!
[First dinner of 2014!
What is the one dish that you'd want to have?]
[2014 Running Man Cooking Contest.]
[Winner's prize- Two golden horses.]
- Is that real gold?
- Is there an 'R' stamped on it?
This is amazing.
This really is an amazing prize item.
Then we each get one of these horses
if we win the battle?
We each get one.
We each get one of these.
[The power of the golden horses
filling them with motivation.]
Aren't you pretty good at cooking?
[Kyung Ho's known
for his talented cooking skills.]
I'm not very good at making the dishes
that I make look pretty.
But I'm really good at making
the dishes taste pretty good.
The most important thing is
making these dishes taste good.
What good is it to have it look pretty
if it doesn't even taste good?
- Oh... cooking?
- Aren't you a good cook?
I do like to cook... but food directly
correlates to how you look.
So I do have a lot of interest in food.
- Yes, I have a lot of interest in it as well.
- Yes, your physique shows it.
[Yes, we know.
We know that all too well.]
- In that case... shall we go get going?
- Yes.
- My mom is a chef.
- Seriously?
[Jae Kyung's mother is a chef!]
- Then you must be a good cook?
- I do like to cook.
That implies that you haven't
had a lot of experience with cooking.
- I'm in charge of the cooking at the dorm.
- Really?
[All of the guests seem to be
pretty familiar with food.]
Soo Hong.
You're a good cook, aren't you?
This whole morning since
we've found each other...
There's not a single thing that I've
been able to say or do of my own accord.
- That's what variety shows are like.
- Hello to all the viewers out there.
I was told that things are going to go my way
when I had my fortunes read for the new year.
- But I don't know if they were right.
- It's because we're filming this in 2013.
I'm sure that things are different
because this episode is being filmed in 2013.
Since this is still technically 2013,
you'll have to wait until next year.
Then today must be my last day
of bad luck.
So that's why I haven't been
able to talk at all.
I can't believe I'm with someone who won't
even allow me to speak when I'm the guest.
But Soo Hong... aren't you the best
when it comes to cooking?
Soo Hong really is an amazing cook.
Don't you even have a certificate?
In traditional Korean cooking?
- Can't I just talk for myself?
- Sure, go ahead and talk.
Yes, I do have a certificate for traditional
Korean cooking, which is difficult to earn.
- Don't you have another one?
- Like what?
Don't you have any certificates other
than just your Korean cooking certificate?
- No, I don't.
- You only have that one thing?
Which level is your certificate?
There are no levels.
It's just a certificate.
Are you doubting me right now?
I'm just going to leave
if this is how you're going to be.
- I'm not doing it. I'm not doing the show
- Sorry. I didn't mean it.
- I can't believe you're getting pissy.
- I'm not getting pissy, but you're...
He never used to be like this
when he was in his twenties.
But ever since he turned 40,
he gets pissy at the drop of a hat.
So we're teamed up together
until seven o'clock tonight?
You have until then to gather all the methods
and ingredients that you'll be needing.
We've already determined your
genre for you.
And your ingredient is...
Fish.
- Fish?
Is there any dish you know how
to cook with fish?
- Fish?
- Yeah.
Sushi.
Even though sushi is nice, you need
something warm for the dinner table.
- Soup.
- Soup... soup.
You keep trying to take over.
We're partners here.
We've prepared a car for you,
so go where you can get the fish you need.
- You can eat too if you're hungry.
- Should we go eat something, Soo Hong?
You haven't eaten anything yet, have you?
You just go eat yourself.
- You're not going to eat?
- I think eating now will upset my stomach.
- Why?
- Because of you.
You're upsetting my stomach.
- It's because of the way you introduced me.
- Then how else was I supposed to do it?
- I was just telling them how old you were.
- Have you always been such a fast talker?
- You didn't know that?
- I can't even handle it.
How else was I supposed to say all that
if I were to talk slow?
We don't even have a lot of screen time.
There are a total of seven teams.
Just think about there being seven teams.
Just a minute alone would be seven minutes
and ten minutes per team
would equal 70 minutes.
So we don't have a lot of time.
That's why we have to talk fast.
- Let's come. Come this way.
- Then let's go eat something.
- I thought you didn't want to eat.
- But you said you wanted to eat.
Since Kim Jong Kook is infamous
for his affinity for chicken breasts...
and Miss Kyung Ah has to stay conscientious
about what she eats to keep her slim figure.
The cooking genre for our
health conscious team is...
Chicken.
Since you have to find yourselves a healthy
chicken to use as your main menu item...
you have to go pay a visit to
the chicken doctor.
- Chicken Doctor?
- Chicken doctor? Seriously?
There really is a chicken doctor?
That's actually a bit of a tongue twister.
- You have to go visit the chicken doctor.
- Right now?
- Okay. Not sure who that is, but let's go.
- Okay.
There's a chicken doctor?
A chicken doctor.
A chicken doctor?
I bet he'll be pretty funny.
- What if it's Mr. Lee Gae In?
- Oh!
- Maybe you're right.
- Maybe it'll be Mr. Lee Gae In.
[Kwang Soo and John Park's
main ingredient is, noodles.]
Then let's go to all those three places.
[On their way to the three most famous noodle
places in Choonchun to learn the secrets.]
What do you think about mixing the broth
from all those three famous places together?
- Like jjamppong?
- Mix all those three tasty broths together.
- A little bit of each broth?
- Then I bet we'll get something incredible.
[Are you being serious right now?]
What else do we have to do with the noodles?
How else can we make it delicious?
I think the most important thing is how we
make and cook the noodles themselves.
Because I think that would change
the flavor of the whole dish.
That's a good way of putting it.
That sounded really professional.
I think it would be best if we kept
using words like that later on.
Flavor.
I don't think I've heard that word being
used in real life before.
Then I'm the Chef,
and you're the Sous Chef today?
- What's a Sous Chef?
- Assistant Chef.
- Which is a higher position?
- Chef.
Shouldn't I be higher?
But you're going to do
as I ask you to do, right?
Rather than saying that I'm taking orders,
maybe we can say that I'll help.
[Who will take the higher position?]
Something more equal.
- Then let's just be couple chefs.
- Okay, couple, it is.
That way we'll be equal.
[Just complete your dish...]
[Because...]
[A battle that you haven't even fathomed
will soon be taking place.]
[A real nerve wrecking battle.]
[Who dares to take cooking lightly!?]
[12 hours before the competition.]
[The members are dispersing all over
the place to get the freshest ingredients.]
[Harbor seafood market.]
- Since this is an outdoor market...
- A fresh seafood market.
Hello.
Sis!
Is she a friend of yours?
- That's my older cousin.
- Hello.
- Where is it?
- Over there.
- It's nice to be in your hometown.
- Isn't it nice?
It's so good to see you!
[Heading into the market by
her older cousin's introduction.]
[All of the freshest sea crabs from the sea!]
[Seafood auction market!]
[A place where the freshest crabs
in the country originate from!]
[Looks like the auction
is about to take place!]
[Fresh crabs as far as the eyes can see.]
Look at how they're foaming at the mouths.
Come on. You want
them to bite you or something?
Look at how pretty their color is.
[Not an easy thing
to see such a fresh selection.]
[An early crab auction is well under way.]
[A energetic auction atmosphere.]
You know what this is, Dong Wook?
This is when they sign
to signal what they want.
[What are you two doing?]
[No rest in their auctioning of the crabs!]
[The customers' hand gestures are
starting to move at an even faster speed!]
[Fascinated by what they're seeing.]
- Keep that up, and you'll have to buy it.
- Maybe I'll win the auction.
This is so fascinating.
We have to be smart about this.
This is a big amount.
[Let's buy some crabs!
Ji Hyo and Dong Wook getting ready to join.]
- You're going to buy all this?
- No, just one line of it.
[All they need is just a few...]
Can you show us how we need to sign?
[Trying to learn the hand gestures.]
Five, six, seven.
The scissors sign is seven.
This is eight.
They're going to start.
[Next auction is about to start!]
[A huge auction where 800 crabs
are being sold!]
[The auction is about to start!]
[Having offered 5,200 won per crab
without even knowing what they're doing.]
Number 260 for 5,200 won.
[Ji Hyo inadvertently wins the auction.]
Number 260.
Please raise your hand.
Did he just say that you won?
How many crabs are there?
- 800 crabs.
- What are you going to do with 800 crabs?
[A whopping 4,160,000 won worth.]
I just started signing.
What are you going to do with 800 crabs?
- I'm sorry, but we don't have the money
- We just need to buy a few crabs.
We only need one or two crabs.
[They just need a couple to cook their dish.]
We can't eat all these!
- We can't eat all these.
- Thank you.
[Thankfully hands over two crabs.]
5,200 won.
[Thus, they buy themselves two crabs.]
The auctioneer just told me that he'll
give you guys bigger and better ones.
This is what you need.
[Much larger ones for the same price
as the smaller ones!]
- Thank you.
- People in my hometown are really amazing.
- These two huge crabs...
- Thank you.
- Make sure to win first place in the battle.
[Great crabs, great people, great spirits.]
[Ji Hyo and Dong Wook- Fighting!]
[Ji Hyo luckily saves herself from the danger
of getting a houseful of crabs.]
[Meanwhile,
on the other side of the country...]
[First head banging of 2014?]
[Rearranging his hair back into place.]
We're here in Taewan...
Kyung Ho and Suk Jin are headed
to get some fresh oysters.
To this wintery seaside...
For all the hardworking fathers out there.
But I really am feeling pretty hopeless.
[Arrives in a peaceful seaside village.]
- It's so peaceful here.
- So there are oysters here?
[They came to get oysters,
but where are the oysters?]
[Changing into clothes appropriate for them
to go in the water to get their oysters.]
Why did we have to come all the way here for
oysters when we could've gone to the store?
- It's much fresher here.
- What?
Then are you saying that the people who buy
their oysters are buying not so fresh ones?
[His frustration is bringing out his dialect.]
I like the way you said that.
I bet the neighbors around here
are laughing at us right now.
They're all probably wondering
what we're doing.
So this is what it looks like.
Dig, pull it out, and crack it open.
Let's go oyster hunting.
- Let's just bite down and do what we have to.
- My rocker image is out the window today.
[Momentarily putting his rocker image aside.]
[Thus begins the arduous road
for our rocking homemaker.]
Remember us telling you that you have to go
get your own ingredients in this nice weather?
- You each get a bottle of this.
- What is this?
We're going to have to get on a boat.
[Have yourselves a bottle of
medicine to help with the motion sickness.]
What kind of a program is this?
To make us take medication?
- I feel nervous. What's the studio thinking?
- Why did you even come on the show then?
- I was going to start the new year right.
- Then just drink it.
Just down it.
This actually tastes pretty good.
They did a good job with these
motion sickness drinks.
Why do you keep talking so much?
Can't I even say anything?
You've been talking all day yourself!
Seriously.
Can't I even talk on your show?
Fine!
Then you do all the talking by yourself.
Have you decided
what you two are going to make?
- Look at how he's pissy again.
- What do you mean, pissy?
- They can just edit this out.
- Edit what? How are they going to edit it?
How can they edit it in the midst
of your talking?
I'll just smile then.
I'll just keep smiling, so let's go.
- Catching fish is no joke.
- Catching fish isn't easy.
- Is this what they're always like?
- I don't know.
Why are they doing this on the episode
that I'm guesting in?
[With it being the first episode of 2014,
this one is tougher than usual.]
- Hello, Sir.
- Hello. Please take good care of us.
[Off to the middle of the ocean to
catch their fresh fish!]
I don't know what we'll be able to catch.
The captain just said that the fish won't
open their mouths if the water's too cold.
- Because they're cold.
- Because it's cold.
I know that it's cold out here,
but the ocean is one season behind.
- It's one season behind.
- Really?
So if it's the middle of the winter for us,
then it's mid-autumn for the fish.
- So it's late fall in the ocean.
- Then spring means the middle of the winter?
- Spring is winter.
- No way.
How is our spring their winter?
[Soo Hong seems to be pretty sure
of his opinion.]
I fell into the Han River last week.
It was really cold.
It wasn't late fall, but total winter.
- It's the middle of winter.
- Then try falling in the water in spring.
Then why do you go to the beach to swim
in the middle of summer?
- Shouldn't you go in the fall then?
- These days...
- Many people do go in the spring.
- What are you talking about?
Because it's warmer...
No, I meant you have to go in late fall.
[Getting more and more confused.]
Late fall would be summer water
temperatures.
You're confusing me.
Is the camera guy walking away because
he thinks what I'm saying is ridiculous?
- Can you blame him?
- Why is he walking away from me?
- He's saying the ocean is better than you.
- What are you talking about?
[Ditzy Soo Hong with his silly ideas...]
[Will they be able to catch
even a single fish?]
[At the same time- Najoo.]
This place feels like our past history is
still very much alive and breathing.
[Where is the place that
Gary and Jae Kyung are visiting?]
This building was built in 1884.
It's a really old traditional home.
[Nampa Gotek (Old House)-
A 130 year old historical home.]
- I feel like our teacher will be scary.
- I bet our teacher will be dressed in hanbok.
[Will they be able to meet their teacher
who'll teach them the secret of cooking?]
- Do you hear those birds?
- It's such a beautiful house.
- Hello.
- Are you our teacher?
[Could this be their teach who'll be
teaching them the secrets of cooking today?]
[Teacher Kang Jung Sook-
A master in traditional cooking.]
- We are here to learn your teachings.
- Yes, I've heard.
But I feel so bad.
I'm not sure if I'll be good enough.
I could feel your energy
the moment I touched your hand.
[A strong energy that was felt
the moment he touched her hand.]
- What is Najoo famous for?
- Najoo...
Najoo is very famous for the Asian pears.
And also, in Najoo...
We're also well known for our meat.
We're very famous for our beef.
- Najoo's beef bone soup.
-Yes, our beef bone soup.
Najoo's beef is famous.
We're well known for our beef bone soup.
We're going to use our two most famous items,
the pears and beef for our dish.
We're going to be making 'sanjeok'.
(Korean shish kebab.)
[Secrets of sanjeok!]
- Go and win first place, okay?
- We have to win first place.
- Please take good care of us.
- Yes, make sure to win first place.
[But... what's that?]
[A special feature of this home-
A low chimney.]
If the chimneys are too high,
then all the smoke could bother other homes.
So our chimneys are low to the ground,
so that the smoke won't bother other homes.
I'll live my life like those low chimneys.
- Yes, do that.
- I vow to do it.
I really believe that you will, Gary.
Should we try calling Song Ji Hyo?
- Do you like your partner for the day?
- My partner is a work of art.
Anyone else's partner that you felt envious of
or wanted to be partnered up with?
Song Ji Hyo.
[Tries calling Ji Hyo, whom he
wanted to be partnered up with.]
The customer you are calling
cannot be reached.
What is she doing right now?
Did she turn her phone off because
she's paired off with a male partner?
She's crossing the line...
Oh, there she is calling me.
Hello?
- Kang Gary!
- Song Ji Hyo!
- Where are you?
- Me?
Where do you think I am, you fool?
It's Monday, so I'm inside your heart.
[He's so crazy...]
- Kang Gary.
- Yeah? Where are you?
- Who's your partner?
- My partner?
Yeah.
Why?
Are you jealous that it might be a girl?
Yes, I'm jealous.
So where are you, Gary?
Me?
I'm just down in the southern parts.
Who's your partner?
My partner is sitting right next to me.
- Is your partner good looking?
- Yeah.
How could you say that so quickly
without even a moment of hesitation?
I said he's good looking
because he really is good looking.
- Is he an actor?
- Yeah.
- He's an actor?
I see. Can you put
him on the phone for a minute?
Put your partner on the phone first.
I just have some things that
I wanted to tell your partner.
The things you like,
and the things you don't like...
I wanted to tell him some things about you
so that he'd know how to treat you well.
[From your Monday partner, Kang Gary...]
- He knows me as well as you do.
- He knows you well?
What other guy out there
knows you as well as I do?
Why would you think that
you're the only man who knows me well?
Did you go clubbing again last week?
[That enemy of mine...]
[Meanwhile, Jong Kook and Kyung Ah are headed
to Namyangju to meet their chicken doctor.]
In all honesty though...
most chicken dishes are really good, right?
- As long as we season it right.
- Yes.
[Still undecided as to what
they're going to make.]
[First meeting-
Awkwardness is still in the air.]
[Ten minutes or so later-
Slowly starting to talk...]
I have an older brother.
And I also have an older sister.
[30 minutes later-
An avalanche of nonstop chatter.]
I get the feeling that you're a lively,
and pretty easy-going person?
[How did he ever hold himself back
from all that chatter?]
- Let's talk comfortably to each other.
- Sounds good.
[Agreeing to speak comfortably to each other
for the sake of their victory.]
- Then lower our speech?
- Yes.
Okay, I'll do that then.
- Just don't hit me.
- What are you talking about?
I don't ever hit girls.
[How are you getting along with
your partner?]
I had no idea that
Jong Kook was such a talker.
I really had no idea.
He's built like a mountain, but...
He just won't ever stop talking.
- How many ideas was that? Three?
- Two.
- That was about three ideas that I had.
- Samgetang.
- What else... the poached chicken?
- No, that was my idea!
[They seemed to have grown closer-
Telling each other their own ideas.]
I think imaginative creativity
is needed when it comes to cooking.
Have you ever seen those cooking shows?
[Wow... this guy really does talk a lot!]
Is he your usual ideal type?
Well, if it wasn't for all his talking...
I really tend to be attracted to manly guys,
and he seems really nice too.
Okay, we're here.
[Finally arrives at their destination-
Chicken doctor's home.]
I think this is where he lives.
[An elegant country house?
Who's the chicken doctor that lives here?]
I bet it would be really nice
to live in a place like this.
[Even planting his own napa cabbages
right in his front yard.]
- I feel like it's going to be Mr. Lee Gae In.
- Really?
[Could it be Lee Gae In,
with his infamous love for chickens?]
- Hello.
Hello.
It's you!
[That voice!]
[Could it really be the person that
they've suspected all along?]
- You can't drop by unannounced like this.
- It's been so long!
It really is you!
You really are the chicken doctor!
- I'll be right out to open the gates.
- We're coming in.
[His unmistakable voice.]
Unbelievable.
You knew what you were talking about.
[Finally meeting their chicken doctor.]
[My beloved chickens...
Chicken Doctor- Lee Gae In.]
[In the best spot out on his yard...
there's a luxury chicken coup.]
Our main ingredient is chicken,
and we came to meet the chicken doctor.
[Came to meet the chicken doctor
to receive his help.]
I don't think the chickens
will like seeing you.
- Because you're the chicken breast killer.
- I know.
[The chicken breast killer is here!]
Yes, I know.
If I were to ever go to hell,
I'd be surrounded by breastless chickens.
- Those chickens would be waiting for me.
- Look at how nervous my chickens are.
[Jong Kook is here.
Let's hide!]
We have a cooking battle at
seven o'clock.
- Our main ingredient is chicken.
- Chicken.
We have to get a really nice chicken.
It's difficult to get a chicken like this
around here.
I bet you'll be shocked at
the quality of my chickens.
- We've never had this type of chicken.
- If Yoo Jae Suk tried my chicken...
I bet he'll think that
you brought back an eagle.
- Ingredient is what makes it.
- That's the most crucial part.
[Good ingredients are what make
the best dishes!]
Huge drumsticks where the meat
just falls off the bones.
Since you two are here...
I normally don't brag about my chickens,
but wait here a minute.
In case of a moment like this,
I've prepared a picture album of my chickens.
[Chicken photo album?]
[Must've been in a rush
to show off his chickens.]
- You should be more careful.
- We should get a hen.
[Kyung Ah wants a mature hen?]
[The meat on the hens are supposed to be
more tender than that of a rooster.]
[Even though he said he didn't want to brag,
the chicken doctor brings out some pictures.]
[Showing off some
of his best looking chickens.]
You took some really good pictures.
- You really must love chickens.
- I didn't take these pictures.
I had a photographer come out
to take these pictures.
- I had them professionally taken.
- Why did you have these pictures taken?
What's the reason for these pictures?
I'll be honest with you.
I'm not sure about these chicks,
but we already ate these guys.
So you took the pictures as a memory?
[As a way to thank the chickens for
their sacrifice?]
- You know who ate this one?
- Who?
Tae Jin Ah.
Mr. Tae Jin Ah ate this one?
I've got them all.
Ones that Dok Go Young and Jo Hyung Ki ate.
Pick the one that you want to eat.
- You can each pick the one you want.
- I want a girl one.
So just pick whichever one you want.
It's their fate on the line.
You have to be careful when you come in.
[Which chickens will they choose to be
the ingredient for their dish?]
You have to walk in slowly.
[Carefully walks into the chicken coop.]
- This is where they sleep.
- It's a nice setup.
[Must remain gentle and quiet
to get the ones that they want.]
So you want that one and the white one?
Okay, go wait outside.
[They're about to get their chickens
from the chicken doctor.]
I was going to choose something a bit bigger
than the white one.
[Which one should he get...]
[You guys look so much prettier
than any other day...]
Ah... I don't know what to do.
[Huh? He's coming back out empty handed?]
- You don't want to let them go?
- No, it's not that.
- But...
- Yes?
- Let's do it like this.
- How?
- It's not that I don't want to give it away.
- Be honest with us.
- I'm going to give it to you.
- Okay, so what is it?
I have other chickens just like them.
They have cousins.
[Their cousins are nearby?]
I have others that I grow in the wild,
so they taste even better.
Because they've had a better diet,
I'm just thinking of you guys.
- So I'll call them to give you two chickens.
- You just said you're going to give it to us.
[But he just said that he was going to
give them two of his...]
Then why did you even show us
your pictures?
I just wanted to show you how they've
been raised here in my house.
Why did you make us think that
you were going to give us yours?
In exchange...
for having come to my house...
- I'll give you some eggs.
- You're giving us some eggs?
[Giving away some of his eggs as a gift
for coming out to his house.]
[Much larger and better
even at a quick glance.]
- They're different.
- Look at these colors.
[Eggs instead of chickens.]
- I bet these will be good enough.
- You can boil these.
I'll give you a head of cabbage too.
[Winter cabbage as a bonus!]
Pulling the cabbage out of frozen ground
isn't an easy thing to do though, is it?
[Winter cabbage!]
You can pull these leaves off,
and make soup with it.
They're still fresh on the inside.
[Kyung Ah seems to know
what she's doing.]
You're good at that.
Not bad.
- This is really nice.
- Can we take some scallions too?
Sure, take some scallions with you.
[Kyung Ah showing talent for spotting
the ingredients needed for their dish?]
If you're going to pull some out,
then pull out the whole bunch.
[A whole bunch of fresh winter scallions!]
Winter scallions grown outside like this
are much tastier than greenhouse scallions.
- That's why I have these out here.
- Kyung Ah has an eye for spotting these.
I didn't even think to take these.
- I didn't think of it either.
- Thank you.
[Song Kyung Ah is a good partner to have.]
It's now 2014.
The first weekend of the new year...
If someone were to cook you dinner,
what would you like to have?
- What would you like to eat?
- Chicken soup with clear broth.
The kind of soup with whole pieces of
bone-in chicken.
[A bowl of hearty chicken soup that can be
shared with the entire family.]
Okay, I understand.
[Gae In wants them to win since he had
some help getting them the ingredients.]
Thank you so much.
[Thank you to Mr. Lee Gae In for your
enthusiastic help.]
Let's go!
Are they all oysters?
I think these are oysters.
[These are all oysters?]
[It's a field of oysters!]
How can these all be oysters?
Look, someone is picking oysters.
- Are these all oysters?
- Hello.
- These are all oysters?
- It's an oyster field.
[The two men are now walking
on top of an oyster carpet.]
I can't believe this is all oysters.
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Mr. Big-nose!
- Yes, hello.
[Familiar with her Running Man characters.]
- These are all oysters?
- Yes, they're all oysters.
- Then we can just pick them?
- You can't just pick any one of them.
You have to make sure to pick
the big ones.
- I want to see what the meat looks like.
- The meat?
Can you crack one open for us?
How do you do it?
[Seeing the expert at work.]
Stick it on the side and crack it?
- Open it up like this.
- Wow, look at that meat!
[Fresh oyster!]
You can't get it fresher than that.
How is it?
It tastes totally different than the ones
that you get from the market.
- Is it sweet?
- It melts in your mouth.
- The aftertaste is so sweet.
- I want to try one too.
- I think we need to start.
- Let's start picking our oysters.
Let's pick the freshest oysters here,
and make the ultimate oyster dish.
[Perfect ingredient for a
strength inducing dish.]
[Nature's perfect
nutrition packed food- Oysters.]
[Fresh oyster even
the crabs can't seem to resist.]
Where are the eyes?
[Pounding away for the past several minutes.]
- Why are you so bad at that?
- Give me a minute.
[The rocker seems to be struggling
with his oyster.]
I'm so annoyed!
[Explodes in seventh octave.]
I'm really bad at things like this too.
But you're even worse than me.
Can you turn that camera off for now?
Start filming again when I get
better at cracking these.
[Rocker's sense of pride is crumbling in
front of the hard shelled oysters.]
You look so modest right now.
- Who?
- You.
- Your stance looks so modest.
- I may sing rock, but my life is a ballad.
Your life is like a smooth ballad.
Look at how modest you look right now.
I'm going to hear about
how I look like a woman now.
[They thought all they would have to do is
pick up some oysters from the ground...]
[But wow, is this ever hard...]
What kind of meat do you want to get?
- What kind of meat do you want?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- I want a roasted tenderloin.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the fish meat.
[Handed a bucket of little fish
to use as their bait.]
You're acting like a kid.
[Little Hyuk with a lot of fears.]
I'm worried about catching the fish too.
I normally can't touch fish.
- Have you ever been fishing before?
- We need to catch some fish.
I don't think I can do it.
- I'm scared.
- Watch how I do it.
- If you can't even do this...
- Do we just hook it?
I'm too scared and I don't think I can do it.
Jae Suk is very squeamish.
He used to cry all the time,
and was known for being a crybaby.
We met when you were 19, right?
Right after school?
- Yeah, we did.
- You were such a snot nosed kid.
- I showed you around the station.
- You said I was a snot nosed kid?
You must have really big ears
to be able to hear what I said.
- I should be able to feel it.
- Yes, I feel something.
- Then you just bob it in the water.
- Like this?
Just bob it along like that.
I don't know if the fish
are even going to bite.
- It would be nice if we caught one.
- We have to catch something.
[Will they be able to catch their fish?]
[Ten seconds later.]
[20 seconds later.]
[30 seconds later.]
[Quiet...]
I don't think we're going to
catch anything.
I haven't gotten any bites.
[Already ready to give up
in less than a minute.]
You're being ridiculous right now.
Fishing could take hours.
It takes a while to get a bite.
It doesn't start right away.
I don't think I'm suited for fishing.
It's because you're trying to catch
the fish with your talking.
I hate boring things like this.
I hate having to wait around.
I'm not good at waiting around like this.
There's absolutely nothing out here.
[Starts to fish even with his chatty
little brother standing next to him.]
You have to feel for it.
[You must learn to be patient...]
See?
My line is moving.
- What's moving?
- My line is moving.
[Oh? Maybe he's caught something?]
[Did he already catch something?]
I'm telling you that my line moved.
[Huh?]
Your line is caught in my line.
[The two fishing lines
are tangled up together.]
I can't believe that happened.
Hang on a minute.
I think we need to be further apart.
Go over that way.
[Sending Jae Suk away from him to prevent
the lines from tangling again.]
I think I've got something.
- Did you get something?
- Yeah.
[Huh?]
[He caught himself some seaweed.]
You caught a big piece of seaweed.
I don't know about fishing.
Let's just catch one.
Just one.
Remember when Duk Hwa was
on the show?
We went out fishing,
and we didn't catch a single one.
Please take care of me, my bait.
Oh! I got something!
I got something!
[It seems as though he really
did get himself something this time?]
- Jae Suk!
- Really?
[What did he get?]
[Wow! He caught something!]
[It's a rockfish!]
I can't believe it!
We caught one!
Unhook the fish.
There's definitely fish in the water.
[Who knew they'd catch one so quickly?]
[You must be more talented than him?]
[Feeling uplifted right away.]
This can't be done if you're nothing
but a chatterbox.
You're good at this.
I'm sorry, little fish.
[Feeling grateful and sorry to the fish
at the same time.]
I feel really bad for the fish.
[Fresh rockfish's bodily protest.]
That's great.
I'm telling you that this is my year.
This really is the year for me.
Look at how big it is. It's as big as my face.
At last... Our dear viewers.
At last, by catching this rockfish
I think we'll be able to participate
in the rest of this episode as well.
- We've now caught our rockfish.
- I caught the fish!
I bet that will be amazing
when we cook it.
I'm even shocked at myself.
- That was really great.
- You know what we should do?
When you start to feel the line dip,
you need to wait a minute.
- Sop bobbing the line when you feel that.
- Okay.
- You have to stop bobbing then.
- Look at you acting like you're all cool.
What are you talking about?
I'm not acting like I'm cool.
[Back to bickering once again.]
We just started fishing.
You are so unlucky, little fish.
To be caught by Soo Hong of all people.
I'm going to dip my line right here.
This is the spot.
[A fierce fishing competition.]
I think I've got the feel for it now.
Please let me just catch one.
[Let me just catch one fish...]
Even Soo Hong's caught one.
Please let me catch one too.
[Unable to stand seeing his friend
catch one when he hasn't been able to.]
I wish I could catch a tuna or something.
You want to go fishing for tuna?
You got something!
[Did Jae Suk get something?]
Turn it!
[The fishing rod is bent almost halfway!]
[Is it... really a tuna?]
It's way too big!
You have to keep turning it!
[Just what could it be?]
[Are Dong Wook and Ji Hyo fishing too?]
I caught one!
I've got one!
[She really did catch it.]
- It got one!
- Don't come this way!
[It's a squid!]
[The squid shoots water at Dong Wook.]
I got it.
- I caught one.
- Let's eat it.
- I caught it.
- Are you going to cook another dish?
No, I'm just going to eat it.
- I'm going to eat it as sushi.
- We're making sushi out of it.
That's where I grew up.
Where?
[Seaside village where Blank Ji grew up.]
[Fresh sushi with the squid
that she just caught herself.]
It's good to just eat it by itself too.
Try it just by itself.
- Isn't it sweet just on its own?
- Yeah, it's really fresh.
[The sweetness of fresh squid.]
Can't we have some soju with this?
[Huh? Alcohol?]
[Did he bring something?]
- I don't have anything.
- You had me fooled for a second.
[A place where the fresh sushi,
and sounds of the ocean go hand in hand.]
Squid sushi, and my partner.
[Tastes even better to eat it
with a friend.]
[Arrives at the destination that
Mr. Lee Gae In told them about.]
- Hello.
- Hello, Sir.
- Do you know Mr. Lee Gae In?
- Yes, I know him very well.
He told us to come here.
[It's a place that Lee Gae In himself
frequents often.]
All these guys...
I don't think we should talk too loudly.
We need one for us to make our dish.
[Frightened Mr. Capable.]
[Fearless Kyung Ah starts chasing
the chickens around.]
[Who is that girl?]
They're all gathered over there.
They're trapped.
It hit me!
- It hit me! What do I do?
- Catch it!
You're too good at that.
Don't you think that you're too good?
Go catch another one.
Is your mouth the only thing
you brought here?
What are you doing?
You're nothing like how you are on TV.
- I just want to watch you catch another one.
- What are you doing?
Go catch one.
I'm going to stay here and play with this one.
I have to look around to see
which one would be best for us.
- That one.
- Which one? This one?
You're a good catcher too.
- You're a man, after all.
- That wasn't so bad.
There's something innocent
about Jong Kook.
He's pretty easy to order around.
You just work him right,
and then he's off to do your bidding.
Then he's off running to do your bidding.
[Meanwhile, out in the ocean...]
[An unbelievable force!]
[Their voices are rising at
the excitement and the thrill.]
[Just what could be at the other end
of the fishing line?]
You have to be careful,
or the line is going to snap.
You can't keep pulling like that.
I bet it's caught on the ocean floor.
[It's caught... on the ocean floor?]
[Ah... so that's why it was so bent over.]
It's caught on the ground.
We were all excited over nothing.
This is a little embarrassing.
[The embarrassingly empty fishing line.]
This is really embarrassing.
[Unsure of what to do with themselves
from the embarrassment of their reactions.]
It's just that your fishing rod
was so far bent over.
- I didn't know what you had.
- I thought that I got a tuna or something.
I thought that you were going to get
a whale or something.
I got excited when you started
getting so excited.
[Both are embarrassed from
the overreaction.]
I didn't overreact that much.
- I thought it was going to be something.
- I thought I had gotten something huge.
I was shocked at how bent
that fishing rod was.
So this is why people like to fish.
- But we didn't get anything for it.
- It was caught on the floor of the ocean.
- I thought I was going to catch a shark.
- I can't believe that was for nothing.
You want me to hook it for you?
You think you can do it yourself?
I don't think I can hook it.
[Pissy older brother coming over to help
Jae Suk hook his bait again.]
You're really good at doing
things like that.
- You have to do things this when you cook.
- You really are a man.
[Soo Hong has many hidden talents
that we weren't aware of.]
You've got something.
[I've got a bite?]
Really?
[Soo Hong's line again?]
[Could it be?]
[Another fish!]
Jae Suk!
Jae Suk, I did it again!
- It's huge! Look at the size!
- Look at how happy our captain is.
[Even the captain seems to be happy.]
It's a total riot over here, everyone!
Jae Suk!
We're going to have a feast!
- This must be his year!
- This really is going to be my year!
- Look at that.
- This really is a big one.
I want to know what that feels like too.
- Jae Suk.
- Yeah?
- Try over here.
- Where?
In that bucket.
You said you wanted to know what it's like.
[That's where he's told to fish?]
Why don't you try saying something?
You were so excited earlier.
What are we supposed to do when you remain
so quiet during the filming of the show?
I vow to catch something.
I'm not going to live it down if I don't
catch something right now.
Tell everyone that
you went home empty handed.
- Why do you think you haven't caught any?
- Seriously!
I'm just telling you to host the show.
You love talking during the show.
'I don't think I'm made for this.
I'll just make my living with talking'.
'I vow to everyone'.
- 'My dear audience...'.
- Please.
Please let me just catch one.
[Desperately praying to just catch one.]
I have to catch one.
[Camera staff]
- I caught two.
No way.
I couldn't have caught another one!
Then I would feel so bad for Jae Suk.
What do I do?
[It seems as though
he's caught something again...]
Did he catch another one?
[Caught another one!]
[His third catch!]
Jae Suk!
I'm the man!
- Stop acting like a brat to me!
- I haven't caught a single one!
It's Ji Hyo.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Hi Jae Suk.
What is it?
- Are you making anything yet?
- Things are crazy over here.
- We're catching a ton of fish over here.
- Take a picture.
[Even picture proof.]
- We're fishing right now.
- Fishing?
This must be... 50cm? 60cm?
- You're not cooking?
- We're still gathering up our ingredients.
- She's already started cooking?
- When are you going to start cooking?
I'm calling because we've already finished
cooking and our dish is so delicious.
How can you be cooking already?
Anyways, make sure that your dish is good.
We're catching...
Good luck catching your ingredients,
and with the cooking. See you later.
Captain... Captain.
Why haven't I caught anything yet?
They're fishing right now.
- Some soybean paste.
- Put in a little soybean paste.
[Add some hot peppers to give
the broth a little spicy kick.]
[King crab stew- Put the lid back on and
bring it to a boil to deepen the flavors.]
Then we'll try the porridge
while that comes to a boil.
[Time to try the crab porridge while
the soup is brought back to a boil.]
We're going to win first place.
We're going to win.
A delicious king crab dinner.
We're going to cook king crabs which is ideal
for many people to share over dinner.
Will this be enough?
[Learning how to cook authentic Bibimbap.]
I need to know how to make this right.
This is all about the effort you put in.
You have to mix it by hand without
using those plastic gloves.
This is how you give it that authentic taste.
There's one other thing that you need to add.
Something that can't be left out.
- Here it is!
- Spicy pepper paste!
[None other than the red pepper paste.]
- This pepper paste is...
- Can I taste it?
Give it a taste.
[The paste that will give life to the dish.]
- This is the real secret right here.
- There's cooked ground beef in that paste.
- There's also honey in that paste.
- This is real good for your health.
[Jeonju's Bibimbap is complete-
A work of art in both looks and taste.]
Do you have a special name
for your dish?
[Ha Ha- Dream's Daddy.
Name of his dish- 'Everyone's Bibimbap'.]
The food, Sung Kyu and I
are like the holy trinity.
- Do I have to mince it again?
- Yes, you need to mince it really fine.
- Then what can I do to help?
- See this onion?
We need to mince that too
and mix it in here.
It gets too liquidy
if we grind it in the mixer.
- So we have to mince it all by hand.
- Doing it by hand is the best, right?
That must be why everyone stresses
the importance of doing it by hand.
This is all about the love and effort
you put into it.
That's why love and effort is
what really makes a dish.
[Love is a huge ingredient of
any successful dish!]
that must be the infamous naju pear.
[This is the infamous naju pear!]
How is it?
- It's so sweet. Sweet as honey.
- Sweet as honey?
Is it good?
- That's so sweet.
- That's how good naju pears are.
It's so refreshing.
[The special combination of sweet
and refreshing within these pears.]
I think this is the perfect dish for us.
It's not too difficult to make.
The best thing about this is...
while prepping the ingredients...
- All my stress seems to be melting away.
- Right?
I feel like I'm dicing away all my built up
stress and frustrations with my knife.
Mince up the meat first,
then mince up the onion...
and mince up the pear too.
This is homemade soy sauce that
I made at home myself.
- You made it yourself?
- Of course.
As old as this house is...
We've been adding on newer batches of soy
sauce to the original batch from 200 years ago.
We just keep adding on newer batches
to the existing batch through the years.
See this sugar?
You need to add a bit of sugar to this.
[Adding a little bit of the sugar to
the mixture will bring out the luster.]
You always add some to any meat dish.
You always have to add a bit of ginger
to any beef dish.
[Adding a small amount of ginger to meat dish
will eliminate the heavy scent and taste.]
- Your hands must be so cold, Gary.
- It's okay. My hands are nice and warm!
[Cheery Servant Gary.]
- Add a spoonful of sesame oil.
- Sesame oil, okay!
[A big spoonful of the sesame oil.]
That looks so good.
[Set it aside to let the flavors meld.]
[Preparing the fire
in the traditional hearth.]
The wood coal is prepared like this.
This is amazing.
[Even the soy sauce condiment for
basting the kebabs with is ready.]
- You don't add any hot pepper flakes.
- Okay.
- You're shaping it?
- Yes, we've got to shape it.
Can I shape mine into a heart?
You can do it however you'd like
But traditionally...
This is how you shape it to
prevent it from crumbling apart.
So until it's somewhat cooked,
you can't really touch it.
Shall we try cooking this now?
[It's time to cook it on the coals!]
I can smell it!
Smell that.
- You're doing a good job.
- That smells so good.
- You sound like an expert, Jae Kyung.
- This is great for my stress relief.
[As if simmering herbal tonics...]
[Made with their love and effort.]
The waves are so calm that
it actually feels like we're out on a pond.
This is what everyone does at least once
whenever you're on a boat.
[We'll do it too!
A scene from Titanic!]
[I feel like I'm flying, Suk Jin!]
The victory will be ours!
[You just wait... we're coming!]
- That must be it.
- That's it.
That must be it.
I hear that's really good for you.
It's all over this place.
['Teot' is all over the place.]
We've got it!
It's Teot!
- Just pull it off.
- The freshest ingredients possible.
[Teot to add to their oyster dish.]
Take a look at where we're at,
and what we're doing.
- We're on the ocean right now.
- Sitting on top of the ocean.
[Two middle aged men gathering
Teot out in the ocean.]
[Kwang Soo and John Park are
at a famed noodle master's place.]
My name is Jo Sung Jong.
Making the dough is very simple.
- Is it made of buckwheat flour?
- Yes, it's a buckwheat flour mix.
We're going to add some water,
and some yeast to the dough.
- There can't be any air in the dough.
- No air pockets?
Let's get started.
[The expert's demonstration.]
Would it be okay if we got off of our knees
since we're not mixing the dough yet?
Let's stay respectful.
[The Giraffe isn't fully understanding
the sacredness of this lesson.]
[Kwang-Park couple also trying their hand
at making the dough.]
[A sacred atmosphere for their lesson.]
I ask that all the viewers also kneel down
as they watch our segment.
[Do you want them to change their
channels on you?]
- This is what you want.
- It already forms into that shape?
[The expert's dough is already taking shape.]
[What are you doing?]
You're not going to get any
noodles from that.
[His dough is stuck all over his hands.]
Is that to make some sort of
sticky bread?
- Did I add too much water?
- Yes, you added too much water.
[Dough expert?
John Park's dough is taking shape.]
[Even the expert is giving
John credit for his skills.]
I think you should be in charge
of making the dough.
[Perfectly shaped noodles.]
How long do you boil it for?
- One minute five seconds.
- A minute and five seconds?
- You have to count it in your head.
- Are you counting?
[Must rinse it under cold running water
before the noodles start to get soggy.]
[In the bowl and it's complete.]
[Squeeze out the excess water,
and wrap it into a ball and put into a bowl.]
[John Park's turn to give it a try.]
[He really is noodle Park!]
Add some spicy sauce to it.
Then some sesame seeds.
[Add spicy sauce, sesame seeds, seaweed,
and sugar in that exact order.]
[And finish it off with a squirt
of some sesame oil.]
[Adding the sesame oil makes it look more
appetizing as well as the added flavor.]
[Giraffe tries to follow
the expert's example.]
Wow, that looks so good.
- What is that? It's just seaweed.
- It looks like a rice ball.
You added too much seaweed.
That's seaweed noodles.
[While all the cooking secrets
are being gathered...]
- Teacher!
- Yes?
- This is my show of appreciation for you.
- You did great.
[A heart shaped sanjeok
as a show of her appreciation.]
Isn't our Teacher so chic?
She told Jae Kyung to just leave it.
When you and I both quit singing,
we should open up a restaurant.
[And the taste?]
We got first place.
I feel like we've already won
first place.
[First level taste to make them feel
assured of their winnings.]
Radish, bean sprouts...
- Let's add some mushrooms too.
- Mushrooms.
[Learning the secrets to making
the ultimate spicy rockfish stew.]
There's some spicy pepper paste in it.
You have to remember all this because
you're going to have to cook it.
[Soo Hong with his cooking certificate trying
to figure out the ratio of the ingredients.]
I gave you all the meat,
and I've got nothing left for myself.
I meant that I'm glad I gave you
all the meat.
[Back to their bickering as usual.]
I think it would be safe for us to make
two different dishes.
- I thought we only needed to make one.
- I vote for this dish...
- And that other dish.
- Hot and sour fish?
[Spicy rockfish stew and Sweet and sour fish.]
[Fresh caught eel.]
- Look at that eel. Is it a sea eel?
- Yes, it's sea eel.
[What are they going to cook with
oysters, teot and sea eel?]
[The rocker is busily jotting down memos.]
- This is where the sweetness comes from.
- It's pretty sweet.
You don't use any sort of MSG or sugar?
I think I've got it now.
[And Teot and oyster muchim.]
That smells really good.
[Time for a little taste.]
[This is the fresh taste of nature.]
Everyone!
It's time for the pride of Jeonju!
I'd like to introduce the son of Jeonju,
Infinite's Sung Kyu!
Why is no one around?
Excuse me!
He's a celebrity!
Son of Jeonju!
Please welcome Sung Kyu!
He's going to give out free hugs!
[A free hug event?]
[A cute baby is first.]
[Jeonju's daughter not recognizing
Jeonju's son.]
[Who is that man?]
What did you do around here
when you were little?
I used to build sand castles.
- Want to build a sand castle?
- Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Dong Wook takes the first turn.]
Out.
No, we don't know that yet.
I haven't taken my hand off.
As soon as I started!
[Suddenly breaks out in a fight?]
What the heck is this?
As soon as we started!
Childhood memories, my butt!
Okay, Dummy.
Give me a piggyback ride for losing.
Do you know how hard it'll be to give you
a piggyback ride on the sand?
I came all the way here
just for you too!
[Giving her a piggyback ride
all the way back to the car.]
[Blank Ji automatically breaks out
into a song.]
Your lyrics are all wrong.
My pants are about to fall off.
[Ha Ha still hasn't given up on introducing
Jeonju's son to the crowd.]
Okay, everyone.
He is the son of Jeonju!
The pride of Jeonju!
I'd like to introduce Infinite's Sung Kyu!
Please welcome him
with a huge round of applause.
Would you all like to join hands and play
a round of Ring Around the Rosie?
[Proposes a round of Ring Around The Rosie?]
To the other side!
Four people!
I can't believe they're doing
everything I tell them to do.
[Preparations for the competition
are now complete.]
We don't have time to fool
around anymore.
We're running late.
[Time for everyone to rush off
to the competition stage!]
[The sun is starting to set...]
[The competition is looming over their heads.]
[Receives a text message just then.]
It's an hour before the competition.
Come to the competition stage in Seoul's
Taepyeong District.
You will not be able to participate if
you're not there on time.
[Unable to participate in the competition
if they're not on time.]
[This is... where the battle will take place.]
Hello?
- Hi, Jae Kyung.
- Mom, it's me.
I have to make Sanjeok today.
- Take some large scallions...
- Okay, scallions?
Dice both the white and the green parts
into a length that's about one cm.
You have to dice it all really fine.
Look at how good Jae Kyung is
with that knife.
[I'm a Chef's daughter!]
[Jae Kyung's hidden cooking talents
are about to be revealed!]
I can usually tell what's in a dish
when I taste the food.
- Really?
- Yes.
[Kyung Ho can guess which ingredients are
used in a dish when he tastes the food?]
- I always thought that was cool.
- You're a cooking genius.
[But...]
It's too bland.
- This is way too sweet.
- It's too sweet?
[The Rocker's mental breakdown.]
- A spoonful of soy sauce...
- And sesame oil.
[These two are trying to memorize the recipe
given to them by the master.]
[This is going to be perfect.]
Did I already put
the sesame seeds in here?
[My mind has gone completely blank...]
- We have to stir-fry this?
- We have to stir-fry it.
This too?
[Can't remember...]
In a big porcelain bowl...
Just like that.
[Does this team have a secret weapon?]
The egg broke!
[Who knew that their secret weapon
would self-destruct on them?]
Are you trying to bring
a dead chicken back to life?
Are you bringing a dead chicken
back to life?
[Noodle mania studying hard
on their course of action.]
You're really detailed.
We just need to do everything
that's written on here.
[But...]
[The dough is the problem!]
Is it okay to serve it like this?
What if we get cussed out?
[It's almost time!
The start time is looming above their heads!]
[Run!]
It's John Park!
Only two minutes left.
There they are.
- John Park!
- I didn't know it was you.
[Everyone's finally arrived
at the cooking stadium.]
It's the Clubber Brother.
[The two clubbers greet each other
enthusiastically.]
[A little awkward to be seeing each other
in a brightly lit up place.]
[Time for the judging panel
to make their appearance.]
Who could they be?
[The first judge.]
[Celebrity Chef- Raymond Kim.]
[Everyone's shocked to see someone so
famous entering their arena.]
[Followed by...]
[Traditional Korean cooking expert-
Shim Young Soon.]
[Webtoon author- Jung Da Jung.]
[A webtoon author who hit it big
with her very first cooking webtoon series.]
[The last member of the judging panel.]
[Chocolatier, Louie Kang.]
[The biggest cooking masters in
Korea are here as their judges!]
How are we to live up to their standards?
[They have to satisfy their taste buds.]
- This is no joke.
- May I call you 'Mother'?
- Why are you even asking her that?
- She just looks so maternal. That's why.
Sis... you remember me, don't you?
She doesn't go clubbing, Soo Hong.
I'm telling you that I've met her before.
So I'm asking her if she remembers me.
Whether you call me 'Mother' or 'Sis'...
That's not going to make any difference
in my judging.
[Stay alert!]
- That's wrong!
- This isn't how I do it?
You totally ruined the dish.
[Only the taste will be judged.]
[Who will be the last person laughing?]
[The real cooking battle is about to start.]
[Running Man Cooking Battle]
Subtitles by DramaFever