Running Man
[He has returned.
The return of the Korean Monster.]
[And... another hero.]
[Double heroes.]
[The last episode of 2014-
Running Man's red carpet entrance.]
You look pretty only a few
times a year.
[What a rude thing to say
at the end of the year.]
- It's snowing pretty hard outside.
- Yes, it is.
Of all the things that have happened, can
you share what left the biggest impression?
What we remember the most?
Ha Ha and I went on a tour
to the States last week.
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha recently came back
from their tour of the States.]
What about you, Kwang Soo?
I'm sure it's the scandal he remembers.
Wang Ji Hye, you're so dead!
Wang Ji Hye!
[Kwang Soo's scandal that Ji Hye
has shone a light on for the world.]
- What about you, Ji Hyo?
- What do you remember, Ji Hyo?
Me?
What's seriously going on
between you and Gary?
He seriously asked me to date him for
a month for the sake of our show.
- That doesn't sound so bad.
- That's how things get started.
Today's race is, the Foreigner Club Race.
Foreigner Club Race?
We will introduce you to our guests
who will be perfect as your leaders.
[Running Man's Monster is on the scene.]
- The first Korean Major leaguer...
- He will be soon joining the major leagues.
Baseball club?
Winning the best new player, and the MVP
title in the same year as the first in history.
[2006, 2007, 2009, 2010, 2012-
Strikeout King for all five years.]
- That's amazing, isn't it?
- That's beyond impressive.
[Number 99]
[The Korean Monster that
took over the Major Leagues.]
[The national Major Leaguer-
Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[Part of the Running Man family-
The return of Ryu Hyun Jin.]
2014 Foreign Club Race Special
with our very own Ryu Hyun Jin.
Starting right this moment...
nine hours will start to count down.
You have nine hours from now on.
Nine hours is what you will have
to complete the entire mission.
I think we're going to wrap up
the filming within nine hours.
- I doubt that.
- That would be awesome.
- Let's go out to dinner after we're done.
- Let's go out to dinner!
[Thanks to the short filming day,
making plans for end of the year outing?]
- That would be great!
- That would be the best.
[Seriously?]
If you can complete your missions and
get to the final location within nine hours
then a surprising gift
will be waiting for you there.
- Ryu Hyun Jin isn't here yet, correct?
- No, where is he?
Find Ryu Hyun Jin on time and
get him to say a fixed line for you guys.
That will be your first mission.
The line you need to hear
from Ryun Hyun Jin is...
It's steamed buns!
- You can check under the steamed buns.
- It must be inside there.
She's really good at picking
things out.
- I'm...
- Leave the pizza one for me.
I'm going to take the pizza bun.
I'm sure something is stuck
to the bottom of the bun.
- Is something written underneath?
- 'I'm handsome, and you're pretty.'
- That's tough.
- This one is really hard.
This is what I need to hear
Ryu Hyun Jin say to me?
[Kkuk's steamed bun.]
- You have small eyes...
- And I'm chubby.
[If that actually is the line, it'll
be an easy one to get him to say.]
Get him to pinch my cheeks and ask,
'Do you like me?'
- That's not that bad.
- I think it should be okay.
- I think I can do this one.
- What is it?
'I'm really, really cute, aren't I?'
- I don't know about that one.
- Does he have to say 'really, really?'
- Yes, he has to say those words.
- He likes to say those things.
- Okay, my turn. Oh! I'm good.
- What is it?
'Jae Suk, don't touch me.'
See? I'm good.
- Let me have that one.
- What the heck!
[A very easy mission, indeed.]
- 'Jae Suk, don't touch me.'
- That's the easiest one.
- What is it?
- 'Yay, I have 14 wins!'
- Does he have to say it just like that?
- Yes, it must be 'Yay, I have 14 wins!'
- That's hard.
- This is hard.
How am I going to get him to say
'Ryu Hyun Jin is a monster pitcher.'
- He has to say that?
- And he has to say his own name, too.
I think I can do this one.
'Are you pissed off at me?'
- What?
- 'Are you pissed off at me?'
'Are you pissed off at me?'
Kwang Soo and I have the easier ones.
- I think Ryu Hyun Jin is...
- Who says 'Really, really' these days?
[Let's just finish eating
these delicious steamed buns first.]
You'll be given a time limit.
- You'll be given 15 minutes.
- Okay.
The clock will start ticking
the moment you walk out of here.
The person who finishes last
will receive a penalty.
- Only the last person in?
- Yes, only the last person to finish.
The weather outside is about
negative seven degrees right now...
Only the person who finishes last will
have to be without a coat for the day.
[No coat for the loser of the mission.]
[Kkuk may catch a cold...]
- 15 minutes will start now.
- I understand.
[Find Ryu Hyun Jin and complete
the mission within 15 minutes.]
[Ryu Hyun Jin is at a nearby building
that is marked with the 'R' flag.]
Go!
[Terrifying Foreign Nine Inning-
Hell Training- Start.]
[Must hear the specific line
they're given from Ryu Hyun Jin.]
- There it is!
- Where?
['R' flag is discovered.]
[Ryu Hyun Jin is inside this building!]
We have to go up.
Can he be anywhere in this building?
- I don't know which floor he's on.
- Maybe he's eating.
There are over ten floors
in this building.
- This isn't going to work.
- Want to work our way down from the top?
- What's in there.
- Hello.
Hello.
By any chance, is Hyun Jin in here?
- Excuse me?
- He's up on the 13th floor.
Thank you!
He's up on the 13th floor!
Let's just go by ourselves.
Let's just go.
Jong Kook, he's just up the stairs.
You just yelled out that he's up
on the 13th floor.
What are you doing?
Do you think I'm that stupid?
[Jae Suk keeps climbing up the stairs.]
- There's the sticker.
- Let's go!
[Hyun Jin is somewhere within this room...]
- Hello.
- There he is!
[There it is!]
[Ryu Hyun Jin is discovered!]
Hyun Jin!
[Running Man and the Monster
reunite after a year!]
[Sorry, we can greet each other later,
but our mission comes first.]
- You've gotten even cuter!
- I brought you some steamed buns.
- Wow, I can't believe he's here.
- How did you get even cuter?
You've gotten really, really cute!
[What are these guys doing?]
You have to listen to me.
[Jae Suk finally arrives.]
What are you talking about?
No, you have to listen!
[Jae Suk, don't touch me!]
Hey, when did you get so cute?
I like you!
I like you so much!
Ugh, be quiet!
- Hyun Jin!
- Why are you looking so cute today?
[Gary's mission-
'Aren't I really, really cute?']
What are you doing?
What are you guys all doing?
[Kwang Soo's mission-
'Are you pissed off at me?']
[Suk Jin's mission-
'Ryu Hyun Jin is a monster pitcher.']
[Ji Hyo's mission-
'I'm handsome and you're pretty.']
[11 minutes left on the clock.
There's not much time!]
[Ha Ha's mission-
'Yay, I have 14 wins!']
I just saw a newspaper article on you,
and the headline said, 'Monster.'
- It was seriously...
- Stop that!
- What are you doing?
- That's so disgusting!
[Being punished for his
disgusting behavior.]
[Jae Suk's mission-
'Jae Suk, don't touch me!']
- Hyun Jin... Yay, I have 13 wins.
- Why are you so cute?
- Why are you so...
- Time out! Something's going on here.
- You're really, really cute!
- Hyun Jin, you really are...
- None of us are going to succeed.
- You're so handsome!
- Wait.
- No one's going to succeed like this.
- Get in line and take turns.
- Let's have one person at a time do it.
- Okay, let's do that.
- Hyun Jin, I'm so disappointed in you.
- Why?
- How old are you?
I really am disappointed in you
about something.
You never responded to any of my texts.
I really am disappointed.
- But you didn't answer when I called.
- Are you crazy?
[A phone call from the Korean Monster...
Kwang Soo made a grave mistake.]
Get out of here.
- I was just kidding!
- Forget the show, and just go home.
- You're over.
- I was just kidding!
Hyun Jin, I've been telling you that
you look great and you're looking slimmer.
You even did your hair today, too.
Hyun Jin, you look very...
- He's looks very, what?
- What are you talking about?
- What are you trying to say to Hyun Jin?
- He looks like what?
- What are you trying to say?
- The thing that all men like to hear.
What, that I have a nice build?
That I'm built really, really big?
That I have a really, really nice body?
[Explaining everything to
help benefit their own mission.]
Monster... a total monster!
[Something's definitely going on here...]
Yay, I have 13 wins on Running Man.
What about you?
Yay, I did it!
[Finally gets what's going on!]
- Yay, I have 15 wins.
- I have 14...
[Yes, that's it!]
I have 14 wins.
Yay, I did it!
I know what Ha Ha's mission is.
- Do you want me to not like you?
- No, you have to like me.
Then I want you to ask me that.
No, you can't touch him!
Don't touch him!
[Dirty Jae Suk is immediately reprimanded.]
- Is this what I have to do?
- I can't touch you like this, right?
- I can't touch you, right?
- Don't touch me!
[I get it now!]
[Jae Suk is first to succeed his mission.]
One person at a time.
I can't get it otherwise.
Yay, I got 13 wins on Running Man!
I got 14 wins... but.
[Got you, didn't I?]
[Shocked by Hyun Jin.]
Kang Gary is really, really handsome!
[The members are slowly
starting to feel anxious.]
Ryu Hyun Jin, how can you
do this to me?
[Kkuk's mission- 'Do you like me?'
while pinching both cheeks.]
Do you like me?
[Pinch my cheeks.]
[What you said earlier...]
Why don't you just tell him
what to do instead?
Okay, I get it!
- Just do it for me once.
- I didn't get my chance yet!
- Yay, you got 13 wins, right?
- What was that?
- Yay, how many wins did you have?
- Me?
Yay, I had 14 wins.
[Yay, I succeeded!]
[I don't want to face the penalty!
The battle ensues.]
- Why are you so cute!
- Kershaw is a monster pitcher.
- Wow... what would that make you?
- Ah... I'm a monster pitcher?
So who would that make you?
You're better than him, aren't you?
'Who would that make you?'
Just tell him your mission instead.
- Just tell him what to say.
- Who are you?
- Ryu Hyun Jin.
- That's right. What are you?
[That's right. What are you?]
Ryu Hyun Jin is a monster pitcher.
[Big-nosed Brother is the third to succeed!]
Hyun Jin, you are...
something that all men wants to hear.
- That I'm cool?
- Yes, that's right.
What about me?
- You've gotten cooler.
- You've gotten prettier.
- She's really asking for it today.
- And!
- What?
- And?
- What is she saying?
- Go!
[Blank Ji, go to the back!]
And you're pretty?
- Do this while you talk to me.
- Do you like me?
Do you like me?
He did it, right?
He did it.
[Only three are left to go!]
What happens when I don't
answer your calls?
What are you going to say
if I tell you I'm disappointed in you?
- I'm really, really cute.
- I'd be annoyed.
Ryu Hyun Jin.
You're pissed off.
- You're pissed off.
- Okay, good.
- Today, I'm...
- Hey, Ryu Hyun Jin.
- I'm really...
- Kwang Soo, are you pissed off at me?
- Hyun Jin, you really are...
- You're so cute.
- How are you cute?
- Hyun Jin!
- I'm really, really...
- Gary keeps repeating that word.
You two should just be a couple.
What a really, really absurd thing to say!
- I really haven't a clue.
- You're cute, right?
How are you cute?
I'm really, really good looking.
Tell me how you're cute!
Okay, I get it.
- You are...
- That I'm chubby cute?
- No, that's not it!
- That's not it?
That I'm chubby cute?
- No, that's not it!
That's really, really not it!
I'm really, really handsome, aren't I?
- So how are you cute?
- Oh, I'm really, really...
[Time over!]
Is it 'I'm really, really cute?'
'I'm really, really cute, aren't I?'
[Five out of seven members
succeed their mission.]
As mentioned earlier, the two of you,
who did not complete your mission on time
cannot wear your coats during
any of the missions today.
They can just walk around
in each other's arms then.
Maybe this is my chance.
[Monday Couple's story continues on.]
And we have another special guest
who will be joining you today.
- Another guest?
- There's someone else?
Ryu Hyun Jin invited the guest himself
to come and participate on the show.
Do you remember when I got the news of
my draft during my first time on Running Man?
So I have invited someone who
may be getting drafted this year...
[With the possibility of joining
the major leagues in front of his eyes...]
[Republic of Korea's best
shortstop player.]
[The man with 40 homeruns and
100 RBI's under his belt.]
[He's here.]
[The man with the five million dollar offer.]
[In the final stages of signing
a deal with the major leagues!]
I've invited Kang Jung Ho, who
may possibly become a major leaguer.
['The King of Peace', Kang Jung Ho!]
- Is he really coming on the show?
- I'm a huge fan of his!
Really?
[Future major leaguer, Kang Jung Ho.]
[Sports world's latest hot icon!]
- He has a really nice body.
- It's really, really nice.
You really, really are something.
[Welcome!]
My name is Kang Jung Ho
of Nexen Heroes.
He will be the first Korean batter to
join the major leagues, right?
[First Korean batter to face a contract
deal with a major league team!]
I was shocked when I first saw you though
because you look much slimmer on TV.
Wow, look at the size of his thighs!
[Thick as tree trunks!]
You're a kid compared to him.
You're not so tough anymore, are you?
- You're just a kid compared to him.
- Can you do us a favor and take him down?
[Feeling reassured with Hyun Jin
and Jung Ho as their guests for the day.]
We've got a monster batter
and a monster pitcher.
We're the ones who sent
Hyun Jin off to the major leagues.
- What are you talking about?
- Yes, that's right.
- No, we were the ones to send him off.
- He got the news while on our show.
[Received the news of his major leagues
contract while filming the show in 2012.]
I remember that show as well.
[During the filming of the 2012 episode.]
[Fellow senior major leaguer,
Chu Sin Soo saw the news first.]
- Congratulations.
- Is he going?
[Confirmed news of his major league contract
during filming of the show in 2012.]
[Welcomed the biggest moment of
his life with Running Man members.]
- Thank you.
- Seriously?
[25.73 million dollar contract
for Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[Highest paid contract for
a Korean baseball player in history.]
Will you find out the news today?
I should find out the news today.
[The day of the filming, December 22,
was the fateful day he joined the ranks.]
- I bet you'll get it.
- I feel so nervous for him.
It's not like you're the one getting it.
You must choose the location of your
winter training yourself
and find your own way to that location.
You must think about it carefully as not to
waste any time and remain punctual
so that you can complete your training.
If you fail to do so, then you have to start
your search over until you find it.
A total of five people successfully completed
the mission with Ryu Hyun Jin, correct?
- Yes.
-Then you'll be given a 50% chance.
If you see the 'R' flag at the site,
then you've come to the right location.
If you don't see the flag at the site,
then you must hurry to the other location.
- You can take both?
- Yes, you may take both.
[Time to choose the location.]
- Then we have to choose one or the other?
- We'll have to stick together.
Gorae University admin building,
or Dongduk University Main building.
Dongduk All Female University!
[As predicted.]
We think this will be the place.
But Jung Ho thinks it's the other place.
- But how do we know...
- This is my third time being on the show.
My guess is...
it's going to be the all-female school.
- That's what I think, too!
- I agree!
[It's one or the other.
What will their selection be?]
- Wow, it's really cold out.
- Gary, are you going to be okay in this cold?
- Ugh, what am I going to do?
- Ugh, it's so cold!
- Gary, let's just hold onto each other.
[Could this be more of a gift
rather than a penalty for Gary?]
Ugh, I'm cold!
Hurry up and get in!
It's cold out here.
- We're going to Dongduk University?
- Yes.
Should we ask Jung Ho to confirm?
Jung Ho, where are we going?
- I think we should go to Gorae.
- Come on, think again.
[Jung Ho, the answer is always
an all-girls school!]
- Jung Ho.
- Yes?
When the majority agrees on something,
you should just go along with it.
[Possible major leaguer's
stubborn streak.]
[Nine hours on the clock.
Let's focus and succeed!]
Dongduk University...
That's probably right, don't you think?
- It can't be the other place.
- Jung Ho, do you watch Running Man?
- Yes, I watch it often.
- Really?
- When Hyun Jin played baseball...
- Ah, Supernatural Baseball episode?
I was going to come on the show
last year, too.
But I didn't have the kind of pull
that Hyun Jin had.
He didn't have the pull...
- Wait, didn't Suzy come on as a guest, too?
- Yes, for the baseball game.
Suzy even went to throw
the first pitch at Dodger's Stadium.
What did everyone say?
Did they think Suzy was pretty?
- Yes.
- Really?
- I was really shocked at Puig.
- Why?
Koreans I know are pretty bashful and
have a hard time with approaching people...
but he's not like that at all.
He wanted to take pictures with Suzy
as soon as he saw her
and he kept touching her head.
- He kept touching Suzy's head?
- It probably caught Suzy off guard.
- I'm sure she was flustered.
- That's what foreigners are generally like.
They're very friendly and
easy to approach.
- Jong Kook, Han River is frozen over.
- Yes, it is.
Han River usually
freezes over in the winter.
[Crosses the frozen Han River
to rush over to their location.]
This is the place.
[Finally arrive at Dongduk University.]
[Nine hours on the clock-
Must hurry through the race!]
Where?
Up there?
Please let 'R' marked flag be here.
- This is the place.
- I hope that it's here.
- Isn't that the 'R' flag?
- Where?
[Off to Dongduk University's main building!]
[If the 'R' marked flag is here,
then they've come to the right place.]
- Is this the main building?
- Yes.
- This is the main building, isn't it?
- What are you here for?
- We're filming Running Man right now.
- Really?
- Yes.
[Jae Suk's coat fur collar
is wrapped around his throat.]
Kwang Soo, I'm too cold to be out here,
so can you call me if the flag is here?
It's way too cold out here.
You must be students here?
I won't get in your way.
I thought you were our staff members.
Would you like some help?
Let me carry that for you.
[Even though the flag hasn't been found,
his priority is to lend a helping hand first.]
- That's not for filming of Running Man?
- Is Running Man not filming here?
Where do I need to take this?
Where do you need to take this?
Come here, Jong Kook.
Are there no elevators?
[Help out the students,
and search for the flag, too.]
- I don't see the 'R' mark here.
- No, this isn't the place.
- No, don't mention it.
- You haven't heard we were coming here?
- no.
- Okay, then this isn't the place.
- Have you seen an 'R' marked flag around?
- No, I haven't.
Excuse me, but have you seen
any 'R' marked flags around here?
[Not a single person has seen
any 'R' marked flags around here!]
- There aren't any students around.
- I don't think this is the right place.
- The school is on break.
- It's not here. This must not be the place.
- There's no air of excitement here.
- The school is way too quite.
- Everyone's on school break.
- Right?
Then this isn't the right place.
Have a great day.
[No flag! Dongduk University
isn't the right place.]
- This isn't the right place.
- We've got the wrong place, Hyun Jin.
- This isn't the place.
- Then I guess Jung Ho was right.
- Jung Ho was right.
- Really?
Let's get in the car and get going.
Hurry, Jong Kook!
- Seriously!
- It's the other location.
- This is all your fault, Kwang Soo.
- I thought it was the other place.
No, you said this was the place.
- No, I really said it was the other place.
- Who was it? Who said to come here?
- Me.
- It was obvious that it was the other place.
Hyun Jin is the one who said
we had to come here.
I really wanted to check out
an all-girls university.
He's never been to an all-girls
university before.
[You should've all listened
to me from the beginning...]
I'm a huge fan of Kang Jung Ho's!
She says she's a fan of yours, Jung Ho.
[Nice fan service.]
Congratulations on MLB!
Good luck!
- Look at the smile on his face now.
- Seriously.
Did you see how quickly he turned
to get a look at his fan?
- Wow, seriously.
- You're like a totally different person now.
[The first big smile on his face
since they started filming.]
He snapped back so quickly when
he heard his name being called out.
I can't believe we picked the wrong place.
- 'R' mark...
- There are a lot more people here.
We need to find the main building.
- There's the 'R' flag!
- Where?
- There it is.
- There's the flag.
[Finally discovers the 'R' marked flag
that they've desperately been searching for.]
[Terrifying Foreign Nine Innings-
Let's go!]
- There's something on the inside.
- Over here!
Here it is.
[Finally arrives at the mission site.]
We just went there because
it's an all-girls school.
['R' marked flag isn't going to get
in the way of their primal instincts.]
The 'R' marked flag wasn't
the most important aspect of it.
What is it?
- What is that?
- What is this?
- Is it the same game we played with Ji Sung?
- Maybe they should've thrown it to you.
Terrifying Foreign Nine Innings
winter training.
- Here's your first mission.
- It's coming from the ball.
Teamwork reinforcement training.
[2014 Winter Training-
1. Teamwork Reinforcement Training]
You must go and bring back a student whom
you'd like to carry on your mission with.
It must be students with the last names
of either 'Ryu', 'Hyun', 'Jin'...
'Kang', 'Jung', or 'Ho'.
Draw a ball and bring back a student
with the last name found on the drawn ball.
Where are we ever going to find a student
with the last name, 'Ho?'
- Seriously.
- Draw the ball and show it to the camera.
[Time to draw for the last name.]
It doesn't matter if they see it, right?
- It's 'Kang.'
- Wow, you got lucky.
- You can draw the same last name.
- 'Kang' won't be too easy to find.
- That won't be too hard, I don't think.
- 'Kang.'
Wow, what's with you two?
[They're really connecting today.]
- I'm in trouble.
- Why?
I got 'Jin.'
I hope he gets a tough one.
Ho, Ho, Ho!
[Which name will Kkuk draw?']
Jin!
[Kkuk draws 'Jin.']
That's great.
What did you draw?
[Kang Jung Ho draws 'Jung.']
Yours is 'Hyun.'
[Kwang Soo draws 'Hyun.']
[Which last name will Hyun Jin draw?]
- What is it?
- It's 'Ryu.'
- It can't be 'Yoo.'
- No, that's allowed.
- No, it has to be 'Ryu.'
- No, 'Yoo' is acceptable, too.
- No, it's not!
- This isn't a word game!
Who says that I can't?
I'm telling you that it has to be 'Ryu.'
It has to be the name you drew.
'Ryu' is what's written on the ball.
That's what you have to find.
- It has to be 'Ryu?'
- Yes, of course.
- You're such a brat, and I hope it's a 'Ho.'
- Ryu!
[Jae Suk also draws 'Ryu.']
See?
You drew the same name!
- But mine is 'Yoo.'
- No, you just said yourself that it's not.
- No, it can't be 'Yoo.'
- When did I throw a fit about it?
Did he or did he not throw a fit?
- He said it has to be 'Ryu' only.
- Hyun Jin, 'Yoo' is acceptable.
No, it's not.
Okay, you may get started!
[Off to find their own students
with the drawn last names.]
[It's ticking closer to
the final mission time.]
- 'Ryu' is really hard.
- At least we didn't draw a 'Jin.'
- 'Jin' barely even exists.
- Anyone with the last name, 'Jin?'
Anyone with the last name, 'Jin?'
Anyone?
By any chance, is your last name, 'Jin?'
Wow, how am I going to find someone?
Is your last name, 'Jin?'
No, it's not.
Jin?
Anyone with the last name, 'Jin?'
Anyone?
- No, I don't know.
- Not me.
Fighting.
Hello.
[Ryu is out searching for
someone with the same last name.]
- It's 'Kim.'
- Any friends with the last name, 'Ryu?'
No, there aren't.
- 'Ryu' is too hard.
- Hello.
- By any chance, is your last name, 'Ryu?'
- No.
- There aren't any 'Ryu!'
- Last name, 'Jung?'
Anyone with the last name, 'Jung?'
[First mission outside of the baseball field-
Forgets his shyness to start his mission.]
Anyone with the last name, 'Jung?'
- Any friends with the last name, 'Jung?
- No, there aren't.
Anyone with the last name, 'Jung?'
- My last name is 'Jung.'
- No, it needs to be a woman.
Will I be able to find someone
before the day is over?
Ugh, it's cold.
Don't go into the closest building
just because you're cold.
[Coat-less Monday Couple heads inside
the building to escape the cold.]
Ugh, it's really cold out there.
[Discovers a group of students
inside a lecture hall.]
- Hello, can we interrupt for a moment?
- Anyone with the last name, 'Kang?'
[Monday Couple is on the search for
the last name, 'Kang.']
- Come here!
- By any chance...
Any males with the last name, 'Kang?'
- Do you have your student ID?
- My student ID?
[Did he clear his mission already?]
- She's not a student here.
- What? She's not a student here?
[Finds out that they're a group of
high school students here on a tour.]
- They're high school students?
- She's so pretty!
[It was too good to be true...]
By any chance, is your last name, 'Ryu?'
[Yoo Hyuk is busy trying to find someone
with the last name, 'Ryu.']
Anyone with the last name, 'Ryu?'
Ryu!
Excuse me, but what is your last name?
- Excuse me?
- It's Ryu.
What?
Ryu?
Your name is Ryu Song Ju?
Can I please check your student ID?
Yes, please.
Wow, this is really...
Yes, just a moment.
[Verifying her student ID.]
['Yoo', not a 'Ryu!']
- Is 'Yoo' not acceptable?
- You said yourself that it's not.
[He told Hyun Jin with his own lips
that won't be acceptable.]
- She says her family goes by 'Ryu.'
- You told Hyun Jin that 'Yoo' can't be used.
[Who was it that told Hyun Jin earlier
that 'Yoo' won't be accepted?]
Have a good day and thank you!
Ugh, seriously!
[His mouth is always the problem.]
What was I thinking?
[One student is calling a friend with
the last name of 'Ryu' for Hyun Jin.]
- Would you like to speak to her?
- Hello?
This is a guy.
It needs to be a girl!
- It needs to be a girl?
- Ugh!
I didn't know that.
It needs to be a girl.
- Please find someone for me.
- We're trying.
- You're in Sweden?
- Sweden?
[Student with the last name 'Ryu'
she's calling is currently in Sweden.]
Anyone with the last name, 'Ryu!'
Is there anyone out there
with that last name?
[Kwang Soo knocks on a lecture room door
in search for his last name, 'Hyun.']
Hello.
May I please come in?
I apologize for interrupting
in the middle of your lecture.
Hello, please excuse me.
Anyone with the last name, 'Hyun', in here?
Anyone with the last name, 'Hyun?'
[Just then...]
[Hyun Jin Sun]
I'm sorry, but may I please borrow her?
I've been searching everywhere,
and I can't find anyone with that last name.
- I really need someone with that last name.
- Is Yoo Jae Suk here, too?
You must like Jae Suk?
Thank you, and I'll have her
back soon.
[Kwang Soo is first to find his partner.]
Thank you.
- Where do we have to go?
- One floor above.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me!
[Monday Couple finally
steps out into the cold.]
Any women with the last name of 'Kang?'
[Strikes gold and finds one immediately.]
Are you a student here?
Do you have a student ID?
Her name is Kang Eun Ji!
[Gary's partner is found!]
Are you free right now?
I need your help with a game.
- I'm really bad at playing games.
- It's okay, I'll do everything.
Wow, there are so many
students here.
[Big-nose finds his way
to the crowded library.]
Is your last name 'Jung?'
I feel like it is,
but you're just denying it.
Anyone with the last name 'Jung?'
Me.
- Your last name is 'Jung?' Seriously?
- Yes.
[Suk Jin's last name is found!]
- Is it really 'Jung?'
- Yes.
Jung Ah Young.
- Will you come with me?
- Me?
Yes, you can come with me
and you can see Yoo Jae Suk.
- I saw him.
- You saw him?
- Then you can see Song Ji Hyo.
- She's over there.
She's in there?
Have you already seen everyone?
[Blank Ji is approaching the students
one by one inside the library.]
- What's your last name?
- Kang.
[Her last name is finally found!]
I can't believe it.
Okay, let's go!
I've found her!
[Ha Ha finds Jin Hye Rin,
an exchange student from China.]
- There she is.
- Where?
Where?
Jin?
[Jong Kook finds Jin Jeon Ae
from Singapore.]
- Hello.
- Excuse me, what is your last name?
Wow, I've found my Jung!
I've found her.
[Kang Jung Ho finally finds his partner.]
- Is this for a movie?
- A movie?
- Are you here to shoot a film?
- I'm a baseball player.
[This student mistakes
Jung Ho for a movie star.]
- I play for Nexen Heroes
- Really?
- Hello.
- I'm a huge fan of yours!
- A lot of people seem to recognize you.
- No, it's okay.
[With the looks of a movie star,
Jung Ho also finds his partner.]
[The only two that are left...]
[Are Hyun Jin and Jae Suk
who are still searching for their 'Ryu.']
- She's a Ryu.
- We need 'Ryu.'
- Ryu?
- We have one here.
- She's right here.
- Where?
Her last name is 'Ryu?'
Where is she right now?
- She's on her way here right now.
- Excuse me, but what is her name?
- Yeon.
- Is your last name really 'Ryu?'
May I meet with you for
a moment?
Yes, I'll head over there.
Everyone, let's go!
Student, why are you putting
all that lipstick on?
[Ah Young is getting herself
prepped for the camera.]
I'm so nervous right now.
Ryu!
Ryu Yeon!
Her name is Ryu Yeon.
[A grateful meeting after
an hour of searching.]
Ryu!
Anyone with the last name of 'Ryu?'
I'm totally ruined.
I haven't found anyone.
I have a friend with the last name of 'Ryu.'
I have a friend with the
last name of 'Ryu.'
[A kind student offers to call up
her friend with the last name of 'Ryu.']
Yes, she's in her fourth year here.
Ryu?
Which one?
Which one of you is 'Ryu?'
- She's the one.
- In the white coat?
Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hello.
[The final mission partner is finally found!]
[With his beautiful partner,
Ryu Couple finally gets on their way!]
We'd like to thank everyone
for coming here to help out.
I'm sure you must've been caught off guard
by our presence here during your studies.
- I'm sure you're all very busy.
- Shall we start with Gary?
- Who did you bring back?
- My partner's name is Kang Eun Ji.
- Kang.
- Yes, she's in the stock club.
- She's in the stock club?
- I brought her to introduce her to Suk Jin.
We should have a little chat later.
- What are you majoring in?
- I'm majoring in media.
- She wants to get into broadcasting.
- Her dream is to become a producer.
[Jung Bora dreams of becoming
a producer.]
- I'm in Architecture.
- In Architecture.
- She's in Business Administration.
- She wants to be in business.
- She's in nursing.
- In nursing?
If anyone collapses during filming...
[Good candidate of that right here.]
- What is your major?
- Department of preface seoeo.
- Department of preface seoeo?
- What is that?
- Spanish language.
- Ah, Spanish?
- Senorita!
- Que pasa!
[Shouts out all the Spanish
that they know.]
Free Mararia.
[Big Nose's version of Spanish.
Greets him with the name of a Spanish player.]
Real Madrid.
[Real Madrid- Spanish he learned from
watching Cristiano Ronaldo's game.
He doesn't like sports,
but he loves to read.
- Really? You like to read?
- He's like me.
But I saw him playing a game on his
cellphone in the library.
- What were you doing?
- I was passing some time.
- You were passing time?
- Yes, by playing a game.
In the library?
Then why didn't you just
go home instead?
[Why were you playing a game
in the library?]
- I'm majoring in politics.
- Political science?
She recently broke up
with her boyfriend, too.
So you went out on a blind date to
spite him? Did it go well?
- No.
- It didn't go well?
- Your last name is Ryu?
- You actually found someone?
- What is your name?
- It's Ryu Hyun Jung.
- Hyun Jung?
- Ryu Hyun Jin and Ryu Hyun Jung?
- It's very compatible!
- You two suit each other.
What are you majoring in?
You should talk to her.
How do you feel about L.A.?
[Do you like L.A.?]
[She says she already has a boyfriend.]
Here's the game you will be playing
with the partners that you've brought back.
- What's that?
- Are those jump ropes?
What is that?
It's couple jump roping.
You'll have to do some jump ropes
while facing each other.
The couples will take turns
doing the jump ropes
and the nine couple will have to
do a total of 150 jump ropes.
- What? That's absurd.
- Do a total of 150 or more, and you succeed.
[A total of 150 or above to succeed.]
If you succeed within three tries
out of the nine you'll be given
then you'll be given the top best hint.
If you succeed within five tries,
then you'll be given a mid-level hint
and on seventh try or above,
then it'll be the low level hint.
We'll go in the order of our arrival.
- In the order of our arrival.
- Then we'll have to go first.
- We just need to do 15.
- Will she be okay in those shoes?
- Will you be okay in those shoes?
- You should take off your shoes.
- She says she's okay.
- Do what you're comfortable with.
Women are much better in heels
than what we men think.
[Each couple will have to do about
16 each to meet the total of 150.]
One, two, three...
four, five, six...
seven.
[Gets caught on Gary's foot.]
- It got caught on your foot.
- No, it didn't!
- You guys were in sync.
- It looked like you could do it.
- Who's next?
- We were second to arrive.
You have to do about 20.
We have six so far.
We have six.
- Ready... set, go!
- We could've done more.
- Jump.
- What the heck?
[Kwang Soo couple's record- Zero.]
[So the plan was to jump
when he said, 'Jump?']
- What were you doing?
- You didn't understand the plan, did you?
You should've jumped when I told you to.
You should've have told her
to jump like that.
- Third couple.
- Seriously.
- Is he stupid?
- What are you two doing over there?
[How are you ever going to jump
if you flip the rope that slowly?]
- Okay, it's Jung Ho and his partner's turn.
- How many do we need?
- More the better.
- 25 or more, if you can get it.
- Can you all move back a little?
- Just do 40.
- Just get us 100.
- Kang Jung Ho, fighting!
[Monster batter, Kang Jung Ho-
He is on the move.]
[Huh?]
[Totally unexpected.]
[He was so confident to start,
but he ends up getting zero.]
[Feeling of betrayal.]
The rope is much longer than
I expected.
Why did you even ask us how
many was needed?
[After asking how many were needed,
who knew it would be a zero?]
- Why even ask us how many was needed?
- You're full of air.
Don't even ask us how many are needed.
[Variety isn't as easy as I thought.]
- We only have six so far.
- The girl is flipping?
- Just watch the game.
- We were practicing.
[The total is still at six-
Jong Kook couple's turn.]
[Better as expected.]
Six, seven, eight...
[Jong Kook and partner- seven.
A total of 13 so far.]
Only a total of 14 from four teams.
- A total of 13 from four teams?
- This isn't as easy as it looks.
- Ugh, seriously.
- Don't worry about a thing.
Her father is a 400m dash athlete
and her mother is an 800m dash athlete.
[Comes from athletic parents.]
Ready, set, go.
One, two, three, four...
five, six, seven, eight...
[Wow, in perfect harmony!]
13, 14, 15, 16...
[More than 15 so far!]
[Ha Ha's mic falls off!]
No, don't go there!
[Wow, an impressive record!]
- Don't come into the playing field.
- I was picking this up.
[Yellow card for coming into the arena.]
- Okay, it's our turn.
- Ha Ha did 27.
- So what's the total so far?
- A total of 40 so far.
40?
Then Yeon and I need to do 50?
- You did really well.
- How many do we have left?
Think of this as our last chance
and let's do this!
[Jae Suk couple's turn.]
- They're good.
- Four, five...
[Very stable in their form.]
13, 14, 15, 16...
[Very stable looking stance.]
23, 24, 25, 26...
[Already over 25!]
31, 32, 33, 34, 35...
[Succeeds with 49 jumps!]
[More than the five previous
teams combined.]
- That was great!
- You did almost 50!
- That was awesome.
- Kang Jung Ho, what was your deal?
[Feeling embarrassed.]
- Get us another 20.
- You can do this.
[A total of 89 so far
with three teams left to go.]
[Big-nose couple goes in
at a very crucial moment.]
- Today's your day.
- Do it, Big-nose!
- Get it done, Suk Jin!
- Big-nose!
- You're making me feel pressured.
- Today's your day.
- You want it slow? Tell me.
- Yes, I want it slow.
- Slow?
- Yes.
Can you look me in the face just once?
[His partner is too afraid
to look at him in the face?]
- I feel too shy.
- Can you look at me in the face just once?
She hasn't looked at me once.
Does he look like your ex-boyfriend?
[Finally gets the courage
to look at him in the face.]
Ready, set, go.
[Huh?]
[As expected?
Big-nose's record- Zero.]
It's Big-nose's way to continue to do it
even if it doesn't work, okay?
- That's how we do this, okay?
- What are you doing?
[Big-nose still hasn't changed
even after five years.]
- Ji Hyo, get this done for us.
- Okay.
[Ji Hyo and her partner's turn.]
[A total of 89 so far.]
[Blank Ji needs to get at least 30
for the success to be even feasible.]
- You can do this, Ji Hyo.
- We needed to get more in the beginning.
- Ready, go!
- Set, go!
One, two...
[What is this, a magic show?]
[How did the rope get caught there?]
She lassoed in a man.
[Blank Ji's inescapable lasso.]
With the additional two,
the current count is at 91.
[Blank Ji's record- Two.
A total of 91.]
- Hyun Jin, finish this up!
- Can Hyun Jin get 59?
- He needs to get 59.
- Is he good at this?
- He's really good at this.
- His partner looks good, too.
- Are they good?
- Okay, fighting.
[Starts immediately!]
[Wow, they're good!]
[They messed up the beat.]
- You did it too fast, Chubby.
- No, I didn't.
- They were doing so well, too.
- Okay, this is how you do it.
[First attempt is a huge fail
without even coming close.]
How about the couples
who aren't good go up to the front?
- Let's go, Suk Jin.
- Okay.
[Pretends not to be it, then gets caught.]
- Couples who aren't good.
- There's no change even after five years.
[But...]
Zero have to go up to the front!
[Kwang Soo and Jung Ho attempt
to sneak to the back.]
- Let's go stand next to Jung Ho.
- Who do you think should go first?
- I'll go first.
- Okay, you go first.
- Let's get it done this time.
- Fighting!
We don't have many chances left.
[Attempts to practice with
their hands tightly held together.]
- You don't need to jump that high.
- Do you not like your partner?
Get ready.
Pretend that you're doing this
with your dad.
- Set, go.
- One, two, three, four..
- Good!
[Oh, what's gotten into Big-nose?]
Eight, nine, ten...
[Second attempt-
Big- nose's record is at 14.]
[Completely unexpected.]
- He did 14, Ji Hyo.
- You did good.
[Not a bad start.
Next up is Blank Ji's couple.]
- 14 is the new expectation.
- Sir, have some ambition, okay?
Your team is in danger, okay?
[Sir, please help us out.]
Set...
- You have to get in the shot.
- What are you doing outside the shot?
- Don't be nervous.
- Okay.
I'm sorry, I was being overly sensitive.
Set, go.
One, two...
Was it me?
[Sir...]
You're first in line now.
[Moved up in line
due to their failing skills.]
- Who's up next?
- It's our turn.
[Next up is Kwang Soo couple-
Another member of the zero club.]
When I jump, okay?
I'm curious to know what Kwang Soo is saying.
Why are you talking your way through this?
[Nation's best known schemer attempts
to talk his way through this, too.]
- Just do it.
- One...
Jump!
[How is anyone expected to do it
to that slow beat?]
We agreed that you'd jump
when I told you to jump!
[The suffering this student is put through
for having met a bad partner...]
[Butt-head Kwang Soo... get in line.]
[The battle for the first place
in line is getting fierce.]
- Jung Ho just made a mistake earlier.
- A total of 17 so far.
[The goal is 150-
A total of 17 so far.]
Show us your skills.
[We have faith in you, Kang Jung Ho.]
- I'll get us to 50.
- There you go.
Look at that expression on his face.
[Always such a determined look
on his face.]
[No more kidding around...
I'll show you what I'm made of!]
[Oh my!]
[Speeds his way to one... and it's over.]
What are you doing?
Are you playing around?
- What kind of jump roping is this?
- What is he doing?
[This isn't what I had in mind...]
He almost fell over, too.
[Monster Batter's plans aren't going
as well as he hoped.]
- Jung Ho keeps messing up.
- Those two look really good together.
- Why do they look so good together?
- Ready, set, go.
[A nice and gentle start.]
[Gets caught on Hyun Jin's foot again
on the seventh jump.]
She's really good.
[If this had been a baseball field...]
A total of 24 so far from
five teams.
A total of 24 from five teams,
and we got 14 of them.
[The most shocking part of it all is that
Big-nose couple had 14 of them.]
[How frustrating of these rest...]
We need Gary to get some done for us.
Why are the good ones messing up?
- They were pretty good in the beginning.
- I don't get it either.
She'd seriously be much more comfortable
if she took her shoes off.
- Why are you telling her to take them off?
- Then she'd have to give up something else.
Wow, you're really stubborn.
- Just give her a break.
- Everyone's very sensitive right now.
- Let's leave them be, okay?
- Let's cheer them on.
- I'm just teasing.
- We're all on the same team.
Okay, here I go.
Okay, let's concentrate.
Let's get over the first hurdle.
[Just need to get over the first hurdle...]
Take them off!
I told you to take them off, didn't I?
Is that so difficult?
[The pride she has in her high heels
cannot be broken.]
[Gary's pride is wounded for having
to join the zero club.]
Listen, just pretend that I'm
not even here.
Just think of it as
you doing this on your own.
- I'm not here, okay?
- How is she to do that?
How is she supposed to pretend
that you're not there?
- With as big as you are, too.
- Just think of it as I'm not even here.
[How is she expected to do that
when standing in front of a mountain?]
Just think of it as you
doing this on your own.
Don't you think that you're too big
for her to pretend you're not there?
- Okay, let's go.
- Set, go.
If you're not even there,
then why are you getting caught?
Get over there, and stand first in line.
You're still at 24.
[Which means the remaining couples
needs to do about 60 each.]
[There's still hope with Ha Ha's team.]
Ha Ha was really good.
[Broke through 40!]
[A unanimous ovation from everyone.]
- How many do we have?
- A total of 66.
[With Ha Ha's impressive addition,
a total of 66 so far.]
[But Jae Suk's team is the
only couple left.]
[Needs 84 to succeed...]
You just need to do
almost 100 for us to succeed.
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
[The Zero Club is full of comments.]
- You can do this.
- Even if you each had done five...
- Let's do this.
- It's not that difficult.
[Sped up too much from all the anxiety.]
[The goal is 150-
Second attempt fails at 81.]
This is our last chance
to earn the best clue, isn't it?
[This is their last chance
at the highest level clue.]
[I will show them
what I'm made of this time!]
You have to jump higher than this.
[They must succeed if they want to
finish the race within the nine hour limit.]
[Third attempt-
Kwang Soo couple to go first.]
Just do as you were doing.
Why are you taking off your shoes?
- He's making me nervous.
- Kwang Soo, did you step on a pile of poop?
It's just the color of my socks.
[Trying to liven up the atmosphere
with his attempt at humor.]
[Their final chance at earning
the top level clue!]
[Kwang Soo couple surpasses
the three count mark for the first time!]
[Even surpasses the ten count mark.]
[Much more than expected!]
[Passes the 30 mark!]
[Kwang Soo's record- 39.]
- How many?
- 39.
- We'll go next.
- Okay.
[Next up, Blank Ji and her partner.]
- You can do this.
- Ready.
Set, go.
[What a surprising twist of events!]
[Completely unexpected
from this couch potato!]
[Our Mister is getting into his groove.]
I can't believe this!
[Blank Ji couple's record- 20.]
You got 20.
You should've done that
from the beginning, Señora.
- He finally has a smile on his face.
- They got 20.
He finally has a big smile on his face.
[Next up- Gary couple.]
[The shoes finally came off.]
You should've listened to me
from the beginning.
Everyone take their shoes off right now.
- Get ready.
- Feel the beat.
Set, go.
- One, two, three...
- Much more stable this time.
Seven, eight...
[But the rope gets caught on Gary's foot.]
I really thought we were
going to do better!
Why aren't we doing better?
Why!
[Gary's barefoot record- Seven.]
[Jong Kook couple- One.]
[Big-nose couple- Two.]
You should've counted along with us.
[That was some excuse.
Blaming it on having counted alone.]
[Hyun Jin couple is up next.]
[Six.]
[ A total of 75 so far.
The remaining three teams must get 75.]
[It's back to being Jung Ho's turn again.]
I noticed that Jung Ho
doesn't even talk to his partner.
[Remains silent in the back and
only asks if she's ready at their turn.]
[Jung Ho still seems bashful
about playing these games.]
He's trying to be the bad boy.
[But... there's no more back up now.]
[This is his last chance to save
his image as the Monster Batter.]
[I vow to show you all this time.]
[More stable thanks to her
grabbing on to his jacket?]
She's actually pretty good.
[Her skills had been eclipsed
by Jung Ho.]
[Surpasses the 30 mark!]
Nice!
[No signs of slowing down!]
Wow, they broke 50!
[Grits down on his teeth to keep going.]
[Best record so far at 64!]
[Kang Jung Ho does it!]
[Kang Jung Ho saves his reputation!]
Kang Jung Ho!
[Impressive student sticks it through
with Jung Ho to the end.]
Grabbing onto him had helped.
[Saves himself in the face
of a variety show.]
That was good.
That was really good.
[This is the true face of a champion.]
Okay, it's all over now.
[With Jung Ho's addition,
they are now at 139.]
You can't let your guard down, okay?
Okay, here we go.
[Clears the jump rope mission.]
- Jung Ho really won it for us.
- Jung Ho did great.
[Jung Ho couple brings home the victory.]
Please take the cards.
[Next two location cards are given out
upon clearing their mission.]
Look at Hyun Jin's face.
Here, you can take one.
[Only one of these two locations
is the real location.]
[The clock is still ticking. Pick the
wrong place, and it's time wasted.]
- It's the bowling alley.
- Let's go to the bowling alley.
[Which of the two is the correct location?]
- I think it's the bowling alley.
- I think it's the gym.
Thank you to all the students
for all their hard work.
I know it wasn't easy,
but everyone still worked so hard.
We'd like to thank everyone again
for their participation.
[A sincere round of thanks.]
[2014's final winter days-
Terrifying Foreign Nine Innings.]
[They're back on the road.]
[Which of the two locations
is the correct one?]
- Which of the two will it be?
- There's not much we can do at the alley.
- But I'm leaning towards the bowling alley.
- Which of the two do you think it is?
- I think it's the gym.
- Let Jung Ho pick it this time.
[Which of the two will Jung Ho choose?]
- I think it's the gym.
- You think it's the gym?
- Okay.
- You think that's the right place?
[Trusting in Jung Ho's instincts
to head over to the gym.]
- I can't believe Jung Ho did 64.
- We would've failed without that.
- That was unbelievable.
- Hyun Jin kept getting tripped on his leg.
- He's worse than I thought he'd be.
- Well...
I'm okay with having been bad at it
since Jung Ho did so well.
I bet I'll be faster
than Hyun Jin at running.
- Suk Jin jogs around all the time.
- Right?
- I've seen you run before.
- It's different because I'm a pitcher.
- Since he has to pitch all the time.
- Pitching like he does isn't easy.
- He's a genius.
- What about you?
- I have to keep trying.
- A genius and one who keeps trying.
He was born with his skills.
I bet you resent someone with such
natural born skills from time to time.
- Yes, I totally resent it.
- I can understand that.
Stop acting like that because
it's annoying.
[Jung Ho's been born with
natural skills of his own?]
People from other teams may think
that I don't have to try as hard...
That's right, you're the same as me.
But my teammates can see
how hard I have to work at it.
- They all say that you work hard?
- Then ask people that I know.
I've asked, and you don't.
[Ah... you've already asked?]
- I have to work at it, too.
- A hardworking genius.
[Jae Suk is a hardworking genius?]
- A hardworking genius?
- Yes, the scariest kind there is.
Everyone's kissing your butt right now.
- I'm a huge fan of yours, Jae Suk.
- I want to grow up to be just like you.
I'll confess that to you right now.
I think this is the place.
[Would Jung Ho have been right,
and will they find the flag here?]
- There's the 'R' flag!
- Do you see it?
[Immediately discovered the
'R' marked flag.]
- Kang Jung Ho is the best.
- He got it right, again.
[Jung Ho's unfailing gut instinct.]
I thought it would've been
the bowling alley.
- What is this?
- I think I smell chlorine.
Wow, what is this?
[A giant sized bowling lane
on top of the swimming pool.]
[Another baseball command is thrown.]
Here's your second mission.
It's control strengthening training.
Human bowling.
It's a simple game of knocking down the pins
with your bodies as the bowling ball.
If seven of you can get a strike,
then you get the top level hint.
Four to six people getting a strike
would get you a mid-level clue.
Anything lower than that will get you
the lowest level hint.
[Only two hours are left on the clock.
Must succeed as quickly as possible.]
Should we slide down on our bellies
or on our behinds?
[They can slide down
whichever way they'd like.]
We can push you down your butt.
[The lanes are very slippery.
The never ending slippery lane.]
[Getting the speed and the aim right
are key to succeeding this mission.]
[The lane is too slippery
to even sit still on.]
What is he doing?
[Wait, and I'll save you.]
[Makes his way over
to take the dive together.]
Seriously!
[The human bowling balls gets soaked
before the mission even starts.]
[Pretends to help out, then...]
[Yoo-Lee Brothers' warm up method.]
Let's see who wins this battle.
[About to exhaust themselves
from doing all their warm-ups.]
[First human bowling ball- Kkuk.]
[He's reduced to coaching himself now?]
Or slide down there and kick
with your foot.
He looks like Lee Sang Hwa.
[A fierce start.]
[If only these two would go down!]
[Strike!]
I thought he was
Captain America sliding down.
[Point one- Slide down fiercely...]
[Point two- Then spread out his body
as wide as it can go.]
[Point three- And the rest... is pure luck?]
[Strikes off into a nice start.]
- Okay, I'll go next.
- Fighting!
[Hikes up his shorts a tad bit too high.]
[Gets his hair ready to slide down the lane.]
[A bit of a partier look
for his bowling slide.]
[Add in the gaze...]
[Looks already ready for a strike.]
[His looks may be enough to take down
the bowling pins on its own.]
Wow, he's seriously so ugly.
[Yoo Hyuk's off to a loud start.]
[Slides off at top speed.]
[Slides into the camera at top speed.]
[Fails to get the strike.]
[One- Glare down at the pins
as if he's going to eat them alive.]
[Two- Slide down as if
he's one with the lane.]
[All these moves turns into
a bubble of failure.]
[The agony of his head smack is felt
even as he pops out of the water.]
Let's see Kwang Soo go next.
- You can do this.
- You have to succeed, Kwang Soo.
You have to do the hair first.
[Variety styling befitting
of what may be coming up.]
I vow to succeed!
[Muttering to himself
about getting a strike.]
You're looking good.
[Kwang Soo takes off.]
[An elegant dive like a mermaid.]
[If it had been a diving mission,
that would've been a ten.]
[Mermaid Kwang Soo fails to
get a strike.]
[Eyes are shooting laser-like beams...]
[But his body isn't listening to his brain.]
[Fourth human ball- Haroro.]
[Transforming himself
into Gary Oldman style.]
Okay, you're mine.
[Gary Oldman Haroro's turn.]
You have to get this done, Dong Hoon.
[Bowling is not about the mind,
it's all about the heart.]
[Misses getting his strike by
only one pin!]
[Aimed perfectly...]
[And spread out in perfect time...]
[But his body was too short.]
I'll do your hair for you.
[Fifth human ball, Big-nose.]
He looks ten years younger.
[Looks ten years younger
with his hair pulled down and forward.]
[With shoes on both of his hands
as part of Big-nose's plan.]
Go!
Why won't you shout it out with me?
[Big-nose is requesting
for everyone to cheer him on.]
[A clean strike!]
[Spreads his arms out like wings
and wipes down all the pins.]
[A man always full of surprises, Big-nose!]
[All the young fans are pulled
towards Big-nose as if by a magnet.]
[But the cold hearted star pushes his fans
aside to climb up on the lane by himself.]
I did it.
You have to do it, too.
Here I go!
[Sixth human ball- Gary.]
[A jump slide.]
Doesn't that hurt?
[With only seven cleared,
fails to get a strike.]
- Didn't that hurt?
- Yes, it hurt.
[Seventh human ball- Ji Hyo.]
[Slides down as if she's
at the waterpark.]
[Fails to get a strike.]
- She's such a girl.
- She knocked down four.
[Eighth human ball- Jung Ho.]
[Kang Jung Ho, fighting!]
- Don't hurt yourself.
- You can't hurt yourself.
- You've slid into a base before, right?
- Yes.
He just asked Jung Ho if
he's ever slid into a base before.
- I'll go.
- Go!
[A powerful slide.]
[Turns his direction aside by grabbing
onto the mat like a golden glove champion.]
[At a 90 degree knockdown.]
[Bravo, Kang Jung Ho!]
[Power, Speed, and aim.
A perfect strike.]
[A standing ovation from the spectators.]
[The bent leg slide that can only
be seen during a pro baseball game.]
[And the ability to grab onto the mat
to turn the angle of his slide!]
[And the total focus to keep his eyes
trained on the target to the very end.]
[Wishing a sliding run into the major leagues
as fierce as this strike.]
[The last human ball- Ryu Hyun Jin.]
[Total of three strikes so far-
If he succeeds, a midlevel clue is theirs.]
[Monster takes his turn.]
[Striking out is my specialty!]
[Monster is on the move.]
[Monster charges directly
toward the pins.]
[Their mouths fall open at
Monster's power.]
[A perfect strike.]
[Another standing ovation.]
[This is the monster sliding.]
[It is number one specialty to get
his fans up on their feet!]
- Ryu Hyun Jin!
- He strikes out even on the show.
You're all about the strike!
[Perfect aim.]
[Knocks down seven with his legs,
and the remaining three with his hands.]
[Gets the job done at a crucial moment.
The Ace Monster.]
It's one of those three?
[Thanks to Hyun Jin's work,
they earn three possible clue cards.]
- It's one of these three.
- Okay.
[Monster strength dumping.]
[Come here, Kang Jung Ho!]
[You can climb up here yourself.]
It's one of these three places.
- There's not much time left.
- We don't have any time!
[Not much time left on the clock.]
Mokdong baseball field.
- Incheon baseball field.
- They're both baseball fields?
- Jamsil baseball field.
- Mokdong!
[Immediately selects
the Mokdong baseball field.]
- We're heading to Mokdong, right?
- Yes.
- Why were you so sure that it'd be Mokdong?
- Isn't that Nexen's home field?
- Yes, it is.
- Mokdong is it.
- Then it has to be Mokdong.
- Mokdong is Nexen's home field.
- We've got Jung Ho here. Jung Ho.
- Yes?
- It's Mokdong, right?
- Yes, it is.
[Jung Ho and Hyun Jin have been
pretty accurate all day.]
[The time is running out,
will Mokdong really be the right place?]
- Is this it?
- Yes, this is it.
[Final destination spot...
Off to Mokdong baseball field!]
Why aren't any of the lights on?
The lights should be on.
[The field is completely dark
without a single light on.]
I feel like this is the right place.
- This is Nexen's home field.
- But the place is dark.
[The closer they get to the location,
more nervous they're feeling.]
This has to be the place.
[If this isn't the right place,
then they fail the mission!]
[There's the 'R' marked flag!]
[Hyun Jin's guess was right on the mark.]
Wow, we were right!
[Final location- Mokdong baseball field.]
We would've been in big trouble
if this had been the wrong place.
[Must get up on the mound
as soon as possible!]
- Run!
- Where? Is it this way?
- You know the way very well.
- Of course.
This is where I always
have my jjampong delivered.
[As soon as they walk through
these doors...]
[there exists a gift!]
- What is this?
- We failed.
- It's dark out here.
- We're too late.
[The field is dark as night.]
We're too late.
- Did we fail?
- We failed.
- This is the field?
- What's going on here?
[Did their nine hours run out already?]
[The mound can't even be seen
through all this darkness.]
I can't even see anything out here.
[But just then...]
[Who are these people standing on the mound?]
[Standing on top of the mound...
are a bunch of students!]
[So many students to greet them...
Did they succeed or fail?]
Did we fail or succeed?
[Still can't figure out what's going on.]
Hello, we're the baseball team from
Wondong Middle School.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Thank you.
You guys must be so cold.
- Wondong Middle School, right?
- Yes.
I'm reading that the school's student body
went down by 20 students in 2010
and they almost had to shut down their
team. Within only two years in 2012
they won the 43rd Presidential game
in the middle school rank of the nation.
[Won the 43rd presidential baseball game
for the middle school rank.]
[Created the miracle of winning two
national games in a row.]
They saved the school with their miracle,
and there are now 46 players on the team.
- Are you the whole student body?
- Yes.
[The entire student body of the school
is gathered in one place!]
My name is Yoon Jin Hyuk,
a pitcher and captain of our team.
Yoon Jin Hyuk!
It's an honor to meet the celebrities and
the players whom we've only seen on TV.
- Are you crying?
- You must've been nervous.
- No, don't cry!
- It's really nice to meet you!
It's been the dream of these players to
meet Ryu Hyun Jin and Kang Jung Ho.
Since you made it here within
your time limit
they were able to meet the baseball heroes
that they've truly wanted to meet.
Congratulations.
[Today's race is a huge success!]
- We had no idea.
- We didn't even have a clue.
Thank goodness we didn't miss the time.
[Even though they had no idea...]
[This is the reason why they ran
and worked so hard all day.]
It's truly an honor to meet you all.
I hope that everyone will continue
to practice your skills
and the most important thing in baseball
is to remain healthy.
So take care not to get hurt, and
don't ever give up and continue to train
and I hope to see you all again
in the pro league in the future.
- Kang Jung Ho?
- That was cool.
I'm so proud of you all for
having come so far
and like Hyun Jin just said,
take care not to get hurt
and I hope that you all become
a hard worker like I am.
- This is really meaningful.
- Yes, this was a very meaningful race.
[Heroes of their dreams
have now become their companions.]
Here's to hoping that you become
an amazing baseball player.
Congratulations.
[A very meaningful race.]
I truly feel like we've just received
the biggest prize by meeting you all tonight.
I'm so happy to know that all the efforts
from the day were for these children
and had we known what was at stake,
we would've worked even harder.
- Yes, we would've came here sooner.
- Thank you everyone.
- Thank you.
[The seedlings of the future dream trees.]
- How about a group picture?
- That's why we're all standing here together.
[To our beloved monster, and our
hero heading into the new future...]
[Fighting!]
One, two, three, Fighting!
[Let's all cheer brightly into the new year!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[2015 New Year's special guests.]
[Lee Seung Gi, and Moon Chae Won.]
Is this insured?
[The top actors' variety entrance
to help ring in the new year.]
[We've made all the right preparations.]
[Ringing in the new year with
everything they've got.]
[Thumping hearts from the excitement,
and thumping hearts from the shock.]
[A heart thumping race
from these A list actors.]
You just wait.