[From a faraway galaxy...]
[on the Running Man star...]
[On the verge of the year 2014's end,
from the far galaxy of Andromeda Nebulae...]
[Seven alien life forms lose their way from
home and come to the blue planet...]
[Earth, the third planet from the sun
in the solar system...]
[A village on the foothills
of the Jiri Mountain...]
[From the clear blue skies,
falls seven bright rays of light.]
[A mysterious cone head falls down
from the clear blue skies up above.]
Where am I?
[A cone head alien, Kwang Soo.]
Could this be...
planet earth?
[A questionable life-force
that he has never before seen.]
Are you...
human?
[Are you... human?]
[Another alien crashes down on earth.]
Am I at the wrong place again?
[Musclebound elf, Kkuk.]
[Blunt haircut alien's crash landing.]
I used to live right next to that sun.
What is this planet?
[An alien with the bizarre
half-shaved head.]
[Kiddo alien, Haroro.]
[Crash lands next to the cowshed
of all places.]
[Another aliens falls down to earth
while still half asleep.]
[Purple alien princess, Blank Ji.]
Sir.
Hadong choechampandaek?
[Landing on earth...
is a grasshopper monolith.]
Is this earth?
[Andro-Grasshopper, Yoo Hyuk.]
[What is the reason
for their arrival on earth?]
Is that a monster?
It didn't even notice me.
Are there others of my kind here?
I wonder if many other aliens
have landed here.
It's nice to meet you.
Where am I?
[A message from his wrist unit.]
[An emergency situation.]
To those who have crash landed
on planet earth.
Come to the 'R' marked flag,
your contact location.
- Is this planet earth?
- I must find this 'R" marked flag.
Okay, let's go!
[This is the front of his face?]
Why am I on this planet?
Where did all my friends go?
Human... goodbye.
I will not forget you.
[Goodbye, weirdo.]
- Who are you!
- Brother Gae!
- Why are we here?
- Which planet have we landed on?
Why am I suddenly talking like
I'm in a historical drama?
I don't know either.
Come hither!
[A unique combination of ancient
architecture, and alien uniforms.]
What's that?
Look who it is!
- Are you supposed to be a girl?
- Why have we landed here?
[Unfamiliar sight of his blond hair.]
- Are you supposed to be a boy or a girl?
- What are you supposed to be?
- Which character are you supposed to be?
- I don't know.
- Gary, I'm Gary Oldman.
- Call me, 'Gary-Opatra.'
- What's wrong with your eyebrows?
- It's nice to see you.
I think he looks quite nice.
- What are you supposed to be?
- I don't know. Legolas, maybe?
- What's a 'Legolas'?
- The archery guy in 'Lord of the Rings'.
- Ah, I know that guy!
- But I have a beard, so I can't be.
It's a grasshopper!
[It's a real grasshopper!]
[Just then, Princess Blank Ji
comes to join the group.]
- She just looks cute!
- You're not an alien!
I am an alien.
- I can't even look at you.
- You really do look like a grasshopper.
- Take off your sunglasses right now.
- I'm supposed to keep them on.
[Tries to pick a fight with the kiddo alien
from the displeasure of his own looks.]
- Look at my hairstyle.
- Are you a middle aged woman, Gary?
[Old woman hairstyle and weird eyebrows-
Alien Gary is also greeted.]
[Off together to find the
'R' marked flag.]
There's the 'R' marked flag!
[Kwang-Cone head discovers
the 'R' marked flag.]
- There's the 'R' marked flag!
- Where?
[The alien group also discovers
the 'R' marked flag.]
- Let's go!
- Don't walk so fast.
Who's that?
It's a cone head!
- Don't come any closer!
- He looks like an egg sack.
- It's an egg sack! He looks so delicious!
- Don't come any closer!
- Hey, Egg Sack.
- Egg Sack?
- I wish I could eat your head.
- Come on!
- Hey, where is the other one?
- Where's Suk Jin?
[Where's the Big-nosed Brother?]
What's that?
[What the heck?]
[Looks of shocked expressions
on their faces.]
[The biggest shock of them all.]
You look so shocking!
[I'm the Big-nosed Alien!]
It's just my nose.
- I can't even look at you in the face.
- He's the most shocking of us all.
- How do you think that you look cool?
- I'm the coolest looking one of us all.
- What about Gary and Ji Hyo?
- Why do they look so normal?
- What's he supposed to be?
- He's just ugly.
- Is this the extent of my costume?
- We're all from the same star though, right?
[Even though their origin is unknown,
everyone has a very unique look.]
Gary, you don't look like an alien,
but just an unattractive person.
- I look like I'm just doing this for fun.
- Like someone from one of the reality shows.
[Like a unique individual man out for a walk
while wearing his space alien outfit...]
- But you look like a total alien.
- Wow, look who's talking.
I feel like an alien like him
really would exist out there.
[Seriously...]
- Why are we all dressed like this?
- Let's see what's supposed to happen.
News from the
alien communication center.
You have all landed on planet earth,
a planet in the solar system.
- This is planet earth?
- I've heard of this planet.
This planet is extremely different
from the planet where you hail from.
If you successfully carry out
your mission here on earth
you'll get the chance to send out a distress
signal to return you to your home planet.
I want to go back home and
see my mom.
With the success of each mission,
a helpful hint will be given to you.
If you desire to go back to your home planet,
then successfully complete your mission.
- Yes, I want to go back.
- Did you hear Sir E.T's lecture?
- Yes, I've heard his lecture.
- He said he suffered while on earth.
- E.T. is my grandfather.
- You do look a lot like him.
- We look alike, don't we?
- Your forefather is an egg sack.
What are you talking about?
I'm not an egg sack!
- Are you insulting my grandfather?
- You were born from an egg sack.
[Thus, the seven alien life forms
make their crash landing on earth.]
[Crucial missions that these seven
aliens must complete.]
[Will they be able to go back
to their home planet?]
- Wow, so this is autumn weather?
- Shouldn't we try out some earth food?
- Yes, we should.
- What's this?
- I think it's fruit.
- It's soft persimmon.
[Beautifully ripened earth fruit,
soft persimmons.]
This is my little brother!
What is my little brother doing here?
- Hello, Ma'am.
- Hello.
[The aliens are met with a cheerful
greeting from an elderly grandmother.]
Jae Suk, where did you get
that money from?
[That's my money...]
[Deep fried sweet rice!]
- How much is this?
- 5,000 Won.
- Here's 5,000 Won.
- What have you done to your faces?
Ma'am, we're here from another planet.
Whatever!
- Good luck with your sales!
- Thank you, ma'am!
[Unable to step away from
the earthling street market...]
- Where are the dried persimmon strips?
- They're inside.
Auntie, some dried persimmon strips.
Oops, what am I saying?
- Why did I just say that?
- What's an 'auntie'?
- Have you been to earth before?
- Are you bragging right now?
- Those are my favorite!
- How much for the persimmon strips?
- 5,000 Won.
- Okay, 5,000 Won.
- That's a lot of persimmon, right?
- Here's the 5,000 Won.
I got back the 5,000 Won bill
that I just gave her earlier.
[Is this their spaceship command center?]
- Isn't this our spaceship?
- Isn't this what we all came here on?
This isn't what we came on.
Just get in, because we have to get going.
Do you even know how to
drive this thing?
[Interior is decorated in a fashion
befitting of the outer galaxy.]
My head is scraping against the ceiling.
Okay, let's go!
[Spaceship takes off!]
[Goodbye...]
[With a good first impression of earth
still fresh on their minds...]
[They're off to the first mission site.]
Even though earth is really nice,
there's still no place like home.
Yes, you're right.
[Must successfully complete the missions
in order to return to their home planet.]
- Back to our home.
- Back to space.
Wow, but look at the scenery outside.
- Wow, it's really nice.
- It's so beautiful.
[The curving river through
the midst of Jiri Mountain...]
[Driving down the beautiful scenic road.]
[And the never-ending fields
on either side of the car.]
[Just then, they receive
their first mission.]
[First mission- Create mystery circles.]
[Spread out and find the missing pieces
to a giant puzzle to complete the puzzle.]
[Complete the puzzle to send out
a distress signal out into space.]
a distress signal for their rescue.]
[But can only travel in a straight line
through the rice fields.]
We wish you the best of luck.
[Arrives at the first mission site.]
It's so beautiful out here.
It's so pretty.
[The fields surrounds
the outskirts of Jiri Mountain.]
I'm getting very good
feelings of energy from this place.
- What?
- What would you know about it?
[Andro-Grasshopper suddenly
knows the theory of divination?]
The gravitational force is
very strong here.
- I just can't seem to get used to it.
- I can feel my face drooping.
- You look like a radish head.
- What?
You look like a cabbage head.
[Cabbage head vs Radish head.]
[Just a couple of root vegetable
doppelgangers here on earth?]
With the puzzle pieces being so big,
it has to be tough to piece together, right?
What are you talking about by yourself?
[Big-nosed Alien's concentration level
takes a dive in this foreign land.]
Listen to me, mystery circles are large.
Looking at it from up close,
you won't be able to see it very well.
- You have a fly in your ear.
- It's like a flytrap.
[Create a mystery circle- Round one.]
[All seven aliens take position.]
My shadow looks scary.
Those must be the puzzle pieces.
We have to find all those pieces
to create the puzzle?
My clothes are so reflective,
and I'm having trouble seeing.
- Let's get this done in one try.
- Let's do this!
- Dong Hoon's too shiny.
- What is he saying?
- What?
- Can you turn sideways? You're too bright!
Send me a telepathy message!
[Is he... really doing it?]
What the heck did he say?
- Let's go back to our home planet!
- Let's do this!
- Let's go back home!
- Let's go back to our home planet!
- Fighting!
- Let's go home and back to our families!
Let's do this!
[Ready]
[Start!]
[Starts off at a dead run
at the sound of the whistle.]
[Gary-Opatra is the first
to find a puzzle piece.]
[Find the puzzle piece.]
[Purple Blank Ji also finds
a puzzle piece.]
I found one by pure luck.
[Muscle bound Elf... and Andro-Grasshopper
also find their own puzzle pieces.]
Where are the other pieces?
- I found one!
- What?
[Kiddo Alien is the first
to find a second puzzle piece.]
I need to be careful.
[Big-nosed Alien, Kwang-Cone head, and
Andro-Grasshopper find their second piece.]
[Now it's time to head back
to their meeting spot.]
[Will they be able to find all the pieces
to complete their puzzle on time?]
[But... Big-nose gets lost with
his puzzle pieces in hand.]
Do I have to go back to the left?
This place is too wide,
and I don't know where I'm going.
[Meanwhile...]
[Finds a puzzle piece
close to the meeting spot.]
[Back towards the meeting spot.]
[Kiddo Alien also closes in
on their meeting spot.]
[Must now complete the puzzle
to succeed the mission.]
What is this?
[Impossible to understand the puzzle
unless all the pieces are together.]
You have to hurry!
- There's no time!
- Over here, Ji Hyo!
Song Ji Hyo, over here!
You have to come and get this!
Where is it?
Here it is!
- Why am I getting so tired?
- The gravity force is nothing to mess with.
[Must endure the force of gravity
to get back to their meeting spot.]
I can't do this anymore!
[Must complete the puzzle.]
- I think it's a screw!
- My legs are getting tired.
[With more puzzle pieces on hand,
a clearer picture starts to form.]
[A picture of some sort of a screw
can be seen in the middle.]
Isn't that a screw?
Hurry, Jong Kook!
[Grasshopper and the Kiddo Alien
come to help Blank Ji.]
- Where did Suk Jin go?
- That goes down below.
[It seems that Big-nose
is still nowhere to be seen.]
- Where did Suk Jin go?
- Is this where it goes?
[Big-nosed Alien finally comes to his senses
and hurries back to the meeting spot.]
I have to get back.
We have to succeed the mission.
Suk Jin is finally heading back.
It's over.
- Hurry up!
- I think it's a star.
- It's almost complete.
- I went way out of the way.
[All the pieces will be back together
as soon as Big-nose gets back.]
[It's now comes down to how fast they
can fit all the pieces back together.]
Come on, we can do this.
- We have to do this.
- It's a screw.
[Complete the screw in the center.]
We have to complete the screw.
Here's a piece.
- That's it.
- Get the screw pieces together.
- Is this right?
- Yes, that's correct.
- No, that's not it.
- Let me see that.
[The screw is correct, but they seem to be
confused with the background picture.]
- I need one more edge.
- Let me see that.
[Ten seconds left on the clock.]
- Hand that to me.
- Here, take this!
[Level of anxiety is on the rise,
but the pieces aren't fitting together.]
[Will they be able to complete the puzzle?]
[They miss the final piece,
and unfortunately fail the mission.]
- Flip it over and put it up there!
- This was the final piece.
- Flip it over!
- It's up there!
You're so frustrating!
Flip it over!
[He looks like he'll flip over first
before the puzzle piece is flipped over.]
- Do you all get it now?
- Is this right?
[They now know what the completed
puzzle is supposed to look like.]
This game is really aggravating.
- This is ridiculous.
- Is this it?
Let's do it like this. Kwang Soo
and Ji Hyo complete the screw
then Jae Suk and I will complete this end,
with Suk Jin and Gary on the other end.
Mister, getting the pieces here
isn't the end of the mission.
What are you saying?
Then what have you done?
- Why are you just standing there watching?
- I fit a lot of the pieces together.
I'm starting to get a pool
of sweat in my cone.
I feel like all my sweat is
sloshing around in there.
Do you have water in there?
You're like a sea squirt.
I don't want the viewers to
misunderstand.
It's not that we're annoyed, but we're
frowning because it's so bright out here.
- That's why we're squinting.
- But we're having a great time out here.
You're providing me with shade.
Get under here.
He's providing some shade.
- I have a very long shadow.
- I feel like I can finally see.
- Yes, I feel like I can finally smile.
- This is some great shading.
I can barely open my eyes
when you lift up my collar.
[Create the mystery circle- Round two.
Back to their positions.]
Hey, you should dress like that
for your next album concept.
- Why are you saying that?
- Andromeda concept.
It's been awhile since you've done this,
so it's time to bring back the space concept.
- That's a great idea.
- Right?
- Yes, that's a great idea.
- Stop singing ballads in your tight shirts.
Like this?
[Falling perfectly in sync with each other.]
[We'll let you borrow the costumes
for your next album.]
Okay, you'll be starting from different
positions for the second round.
Ji Hyo, look around and see
if you can find where the pieces are.
Where's the other one?
- Do you see your pieces?
- I can only see one!
- Get ready!
- Fighting!
- Let's go back home!
[Start!]
[Off to another strong start!]
[It's a battle against time.
Must hurry back with the puzzle pieces!]
I'm much faster this time.
Very speedy!
[At a much faster speed
than the first round.]
[Everyone finds their first
puzzle piece in the blink of an eye.]
- We can't find Ji Hyo's piece.
- Gary, I can only find one.
- Where's the other one?
- We can't find the other one!
I need one more.
[In the meantime, Kiddo Alien is first
to find his two puzzle pieces.]
[Races back to the meeting spot.]
I have the screw pieces.
[Andro-Grasshopper also finds
all his puzzle pieces.]
[Kiddo Alien is first to arrive,
and pieces his portion back together.]
[Half the screw picture is completed.]
I have a lot of eyes on my head.
I know where everything is.
[The ability to see more
than others can.]
I know where everything is.
Hurry back!
[Kwang-Cone head, Grasshopper, and
Big-nose rush back to the meeting spot.]
This part broke off.
[Where in the world
is my second puzzle piece?]
[The puzzle piece is discovered.]
- Gary, I see it!
- Hurry!
[They must now rush back
to the meeting spot!]
Where is the pointy part?
Is this it?
[They're fitting the pieces back
together at a much faster speed.]
- Is this right?
- That's right.
- You have to run!
- Isn't this it?
- Where does this go?
- Let me see that.
[Big-nosed Alien and Muscle Elf
are almost back to the meeting spot.]
- That one goes here.
- Hurry up!
- I know where this one goes.
- Okay.
- Someone go and help Jong Kook.
- Hurry!
Suk Jin, go help Jong Kook.
[I'm not helping anyone.
My nose is the real fish to fry.]
Hurry, Ji Hyo!
[The puzzle will be complete with
Gary and Ji Hyo's pieces.]
- Hurry, Gary!
- I'm almost there!
[The two rush back to the meeting spot.]
Go, and help Ji Hyo!
We need one more piece here.
[The puzzle is starting to take form.]
- Ji Hyo!
- Sorry, Jae Suk.
It took me too long to find this.
I'm so sorry.
- Let me take that, Ji Hyo.
- No, it's okay.
[The seven aliens become one
in the face of the mission.]
Just throw it to me!
[All the puzzle pieces
are fit back together...]
[But have they successfully
completed the puzzle?]
We got it!
[First mission- Create a mystery circle.
Successfully completed!]
[All the aliens came together as one
to succeed their mission.]
What's your problem?
I did my best.
My pants don't even fit me.
My pants doesn't even fit.
- They'd slide off whenever I ran.
- You're just taking it all off, aren't you?
- You're so brazen about it.
- They made me wear pants that won't fit.
- Just put on a belt.
- They don't fit me at all.
What you're seeing right now is an important
clue as to how you can escape planet earth.
[What is the secret message hidden
behind this picture of the screw?]
[Each offer their own set of opinions.]
[What is the secret hidden behind
the mystery circle mission?]
[Their home planet may even be visible
through earth's clear blue skies.]
- Doesn't this look pretty as a picture?
- Is this the right place?
I think this is the right place.
What could this be?
[What awaits our alien friends here?]
Earth is very beautiful.
Planet earth rocks.
- What's this?
- Why is there exercise equipment here?
[A treadmill?]
- What is this?
- I didn't exercise even on our home planet.
- There really is exercise equipment.
- Do we have to run again?
[Do we have to keep running
here on earth?]
What is all this?
What is this?
It's not even weighed down?
Why are you punching that thing now?
Why are you swaying back and forth like that?
It's because I can't punch your face.
Seriously, just hit that instead!
That's similar.
Why would he hit me?
Here's your second mission.
Find food on earth.
What?
Food?
We have prepared some food for you
to help relieve your hunger.
Food.
To help you acquire food since
you don't utilize your hands when eating...
- What? When have we not used our hands?
- I just used my hands to eat earlier.
What do you know about us aliens
for you to say something like that?
- Have you ever been to our planet?
- That's just their preconceived notion.
You have to eat the cookies above
the treadmill machine while it's operating.
You must decide the order of players,
and eat as many cookies as you can
and you must touch off with the next
player once you've eaten your fill.
- There's going to be food on this belt.
- Really?
- Why would you put your foot on there?
- There's going to be food on this belt!
[Dirtied alien food table.]
[Gary-Opatra is having a tough time
understanding the earthling mission.]
Okay, I get it.
As a group, you have to eat
a total of 100 cookies.
- 100?
If you successfully eat 100 cookies
as a group, you succeed the mission.
Please bring out the cookies.
What kind of cookies are they?
Ah, those?
[Earthlings' favorite, popped rice cookies.]
You must consume all the cookies in
the basket to reach your goal of 100.
Can you make the beeping sound?
His nose is starting to
droop off of his face.
Don't put your foot up there!
Why are you putting your foot
on the food table?
- I'm not eating any!
- Haven't you been taught any better?
- I'm sorry.
- You've no right to say anything to me.
- You've no right to say anything to anyone.
- Look at how funny he looks.
- I just fixed my hair.
[Did Gary-Opatra fix up his hair?]
- Where have I seen him before?
- I've seen him at the hair salon.
A popular hairstyle
amongst middle aged women.
You can find a middle aged woman
with this hairstyle anywhere you go.
- A tough middle aged woman.
- You know the style, right?
Wasn't there a lady who was on a singing show
that came out singing a disco song?
[D.I.S.C.O singing lady from
the singing show?]
[Gary's own rendition of do the disco!]
[Gary from another star!]
Okay, please start your challenge.
A kind earthling child will place the cookies.
[First challenger.
Big-nosed Alien.]
[Please do not try this at home.]
What if the cookies fall down to the floor?
[Any cookies that falls down to the ground
will be used for the next challenger.]
- Wow, you guys just think of everything.
- This game looks hard.
- You guys are something else.
- I can't see past my nose.
- Your nose could get in the way.
- How am I going to eat this?
[The cookies are placed in
an 'S' formation.]
- I can eat them like this.
- You can move them with your nose.
Suk Jin, these cookies are really dry,
so you may not be able to eat very many.
I think you should just open up your mouth
and start sucking them in your mouth.
- Or grab them with your lips.
- Are we ready?
Let's go!
[Let's eat!]
- I'm sure we can eat at least a hundred.
- Second player, get in position.
- Okay, fighting.
- Fighting!
- Let's get this done in one try.
- Let's go back to our home planet!
Here it comes!
[So fast!]
[Big-nose manages to get a big fat zero.]
[He's unable to eat any.]
He hasn't eaten a single one!
[Big-nose finally gets
his first taste of the cookie.]
Eight... nine.
[An expert at cookie flinging.]
- Eat some, Suk Jin!
- Keep your mouth open.
[A giant serving of the cookies.]
[But he only manages to get one.]
- Get out of the way, next player.
- How many did he get?
[Big-nosed Alien gives up,
and Gary-Opatra is tagged in.]
[Looks like a frilled lizard.]
Don't you find it hard?
[Gary lizard continues
his feasting of the cookies.]
Gary's doing a good job.
He got a lot in his mouth.
[If the treadmill
will shower me with food...]
- He got a lot in his mouth.
- Keep giving it to me.
[Third player,
Kiddo-Alien keeps utterly focused.]
[30% of the cookies in the basket have
already been placed on the treadmill.]
- You're doing a great job!
- How many has Gary eaten?
- Why wasn't I able to do what he's doing?
- Gary, you're doing great!
He's sucking them all in.
It looks like you're sucking them in.
[Gary-Opatra succeeds in consuming 14.
20 of 100 have been consumed.]
[Third player, Kiddo-Alien.]
[Wow, he's good!]
His mouth is too small.
Ha Ha's mouth is too small.
[Even with his small mouth,
he still manages to suck them down.]
- Dong Hoon's aim is really accurate.
- See how he's sucking them down?
He's like a vacuum cleaner.
You're doing great!
Wow, you're good!
[Kiddo-Alien's shocking performance.]
[Kiddo-Alien consumes 19.
39 of 100 cookies have been consumed.]
[Fourth player, Purple Princess Blank Ji.]
Why are they bouncing off of my mouth?
Suck them in like this.
There you go!
Wow, she must have a big mouth.
[A shower of popped rice cookies.]
There's more coming!
Don't close your mouth!
Open your mouth right now!
[Kwang-Cone head is on a rampage!]
- Open your mouth!
- Next player!
[80% of the cookies in the
basket are gone.]
[Fifth player, Andro-Grasshopper.]
You have to bend down more.
Just like that.
- It's much harder than I had thought.
- Just inhale them.
[Andro-Grasshopper
is getting the hang of it.]
- He's gotten the feel for it now.
- You're getting it now.
[Sucks them all down with
that frightfully large mouth of his.]
- How many has he gotten?
- You'd better eat a lot of it.
Give me more!
[He didn't get a single one!]
[All the cookies in the basket are gone!]
[First round- 53 of the 100 are
consumed. Mission failed.]
- There's no way to be good at this.
- Having a big mouth is very helpful.
Having a big mouth is advantageous.
Let's have Kim Jong Kook go first.
- Give it a try, Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- Put it down in groups of five.
- Should we try that?
Put it down in groups of five,
and it'll give five separate tries.
[The chances of succeeding the mission varies
depending on how the cookies are dispersed.]
Ji Hyo, putting them
down like that is no use.
Put them down like this.
- Put them behind this line right here.
- Then you do it yourself!
What? It'll be quicker for her to do it
since she already has them in hand.
- Seriously.
- Yes, put them there.
- What you're doing won't work.
- Put two more down here.
- Put them up here.
- Then it'll fall off right away!
I'm sorry.
- What do you have to be sorry about?
- I always feel sorry.
- Is he apologizing for me?
- They were talking about me.
- You weren't talking to me?
- No, we were talking to Suk Jin.
[First player, Muscle-bound Elf.]
- Let's do this.
- It'll come at you fast.
- It may rub against your lips.
- It's slower this time. Eat them all.
[Right into his mouth.]
[Wow, he's fast!]
[A mouthful of cookies.]
You should've gone earlier!
[First player, Muscle-bound Elf,
consumes 19 of 100 cookies.]
Those cookies were placed perfectly.
- Place the next ones exactly the same.
- We should place them like this.
- Place them in intervals... down here.
- One, two, three, four...
He has a really big mouth, too.
- Kwang Soo has a big mouth.
- Okay, that's good.
- 13, 14, 15...
- You don't have to be so exact about it.
- How many more do you want? Five?
- Five.
- How many is it so far?
- You two look like you're playing house.
- They're playing house.
- Are you guys playing house?
It would've been nice if we had
always gotten along this well.
Lie down in an angle like I did.
It's really helpful.
[Try doing what I'm doing.]
- Prop up his head a little.
- His lips have to touch a little bit.
- No, that's good.
- No, down a little bit more.
- No, that's good. Stop pulling.
- No, just a little bit more.
[When can I start eating the cookies?]
- No, like this.
- Is this a construction site or something?
- Pull up! No, down a little.
- Okay, that's good.
Okay, that's good.
[Why is it so hard to get some cookies?]
- No, he's good to go.
- Okay, you have to succeed.
- Ready.
- Pull down his chin!
[Sucks in the first row
of popped rice cookies.]
- He ate a ton just now.
- We won't count the ones he dropped.
[A continuous line of cookies
inside his huge mouth.]
[Kwang-Cone head consumes 20.
39 of the 100 cookies are consumed.]
- He ate 20.
- Give me ten groups of five each.
Set the speed at three.
- Scatter them around like this.
- Here are five.
[Alien vacuum cleaner requests groupings
of cookies in a zig-zag pattern.]
- Here are five.
- Set the speed at three.
- Do you think you can do this?
- I'm going to eat them all.
- It'd be cool if you can eat them all.
- This is a great idea.
- I'll eat them in groups.
- Will your lips be okay?
- Just suck them down.
- Get ready.
- Remove your hand.
[That really hurts...]
- What were you thinking?
- That really must hurt.
What were you thinking?
[Throws the well-being
of his lips to the wind.]
[Kiddo-Alien consumes 11,
thus consuming 50 of the 100 cookies.]
- I'll go next.
- Okay.
- Let's just finish this.
- Keep sucking while chewing.
Don't try to chew and eat right now.
- Okay, here I go.
- You should lay down.
- Place the tray underneath.
- Won't five be too fast for you?
[Kwang-Cone head bashes his head
on the overhead camera.]
Can't you be more careful?
- Is the camera okay?
Please be more careful.
- Okay, are you ready?
- Will you be okay with the speed at five?
You're sitting up too high. You have
to receive them from down below.
Just chew to decrease the volume,
but there's no time to swallow, okay?
- Get ready.
- Lower the speed to four.
[Let's succeed this mission,
and return to our home planet.]
You have to open your mouth wider.
No, you have to get closer!
- Chew!
- Here they come!
[Inhales the next batch of cookies.]
- I told you to get lower!
- That was plenty. He can't fit anymore.
I told you to get down several times,
but why did you keep staying up there?
- He ate a lot.
- Why are you scolding him when he ate a lot?
He did a great job,
so why are you scolding him?
[Didn't I do a pretty good job?]
- He ate quite a bit.
- 19.
[Andro-Grasshopper consumes 19,
thus consuming a total of 69 of the 100.]
19 was a lot,
so why am I being berated?
You could've done better.
I'm just saying this for your benefit.
Fine, I'm sorry.
[Muscle Elf's unrealistic
expectation from others.]
- Who's next?
- Ji Hyo hasn't gone yet.
Ji Hyo should go next.
- Okay, here we go!
- Wait.
- What's he doing?
- No, hang on.
- You're putting her head on your lap?
- Wow...
- You need to open wider.
- Am I in the right spot?
[The alien couple works together.]
- You have to angle her head more.
- You have a small mouth.
- Chew if you can.
- Here it comes.
- Chew!
You have to chew!
She got a lot in there.
She got a lot in there!
Keep chewing!
[Small mouthed Princess Blank Ji-
An ace even in outer space.]
- I ate a ton!
- You got a lot in your mouth.
That was a lot for a girl.
[Purple Princess consumes 15,
thus consuming a total of 84 of the 100.]
- Wow, she did great.
- I think this is a good method.
- Ji Hyo did great.
- Gary could finish this.
- Gary, you could finish this.
- Okay.
- Tie it back with a rubber band.
- Can you tie back my hair?
Can you give me a rubber band?
- How do I tie this?
- I'll tie it back for you.
[His fierce visual is enough to incite
laughter with a simple tie of the hair.]
He seriously looks just like some of
the women in my neighborhood.
He looks like them
even with his hair tied back.
His haircut really is something else.
[Hair is transformed into a ponytail style.]
You look really cute.
It makes you look ten years younger.
- Looking good, Gary.
- Tell me when to chew.
You can finish this.
You can do this.
[16 more to succeed the mission.]
[Eat the first row of cookies first,
and the second line if possible.]
- Gary, you have to finish this.
- Let's just finish this.
[Gary must end this game.]
Move your hand out of the way.
Chew!
[Wow, he got a lot in his mouth!]
[He ate both rows of the cookies!]
[And here's the next line!]
- He got 20 at least.
- Great job!
- You got both lines in your mouth!
- You did great!
- You did great, Gary.
- That was amazing.
[Gary-Opatra consumes 20, thus
consuming a total of 104 of the 100.]
We did it!
[Second mission- Find food on earth.
Mission success!]
[The MVP of the game, Gary-Opatra.]
Gae Eun did it.
That was the highest count.
That was awesome.
Hey, Gary.
That was really attractive.
Why are you falling for me?
That's making me feel uncomfortable.
- You're making me feel uncomfortable.
- You look much better now, Gae Eun.
You look much better with
your hair in a ponytail.
You!
You have succeeded your
second mission.
Here's your hint.
[What could this be?]
- Blow it off.
- No, don't blow it.
[Wait, this is...]
- Isn't this the snail sign?
- Like for the internet?
[Could this be the popular internet sign?]
- What's this?
- For an address of some sorts?
- Why are you handing it to me?
- It's heavy.
[What could this symbol mean?]
[Off to the final mission site!]
What does that symbol mean?
- I have no idea what it is.
- I don't think it's the snail sign.
- What is it then?
- Is it a pathway?
[A path or a maze?]
- It's the direction for the screw.
- That's it!
- It's the direction it's screwed.
- Signal to turn it to the right!
- It's the direction for the screw.
- A direction on how to tighten it.
But I don't know how to apply this.
My alien friends,
thanks for all your hard work.
Complete the final mission,
and you'll be able to return home.
But...
It won't be that simple.
If it means that I have to return
alone, then I won't go.
[What is the final mission that
awaits these alien friends?]
- Please get in the car.
- You want me to get in?
[Huh?]
[This scene is...]
Am I going to be a spy?
[Full of anticipation and excitement.]
[A mysterious message.]
[You're a Martian.]
Your real identity is that of a Martian
from the planet, Mars.
Mars is my home planet?
You must go out there and eliminate everyone
from the planet, Venus, to succeed.
[Eliminate all the aliens from Venus
to succeed his mission.]
[Weren't we all from the same planet?]
How many Martians are there?
Am I the only Martian?
- Some are from Venus and some from Mars?
- Okay, get out there.
We're not all on the same side?
I have to do this secretly?
[Martian, Kwang-Cone head,
is left befuddled.]
We're not all the same.
[Martian's mission-
Eliminate all the aliens from Venus.]
I have to eliminate everyone
from Venus.
[Next up, Kiddo-Alien.]
Why are they splitting us up?
[He's also invited to enter the car.]
Your real identity is...
a Martian.
[He's also a Martian?]
You are from the planet, Mars.
You must eliminate everyone from the
planet, Venus, in order to succeed.
[Martian Kiddo Alien is given the same
mission as Kwang-Cone head.]
Why are you giving me a mission
like this all of a sudden?
Why are you burdening me like this?
Why are you suddenly... can you not do this?
Can we do this next week instead?
I'm not feeling prepared for this.
[Andro-Grasshopper's
enters the mission vehicle.]
What is this about?
I'm a Martian?
[He's also a Martian?]
You're from the planet, Mars.
[This alien... and this alien, too?]
You're a Martian, from the planet, Mars.
[They're all from Mars?]
You must eliminate everyone from
the planet, Venus, in order to succeed.
[They're all given the same mission.
Eliminate all the aliens from Venus!]
- How many Martians are there?
- Eliminate all from the planet, Venus.
So it's a battle between
Mars and Venus?
[A battle between Mars and Venus.
Everyone receives the mission in secret.]
[Good luck, Martian!]
[And the one last remaining alien...]
You are from the planet, Venus.
[You are from the planet, Venus.]
[Muscle Elf is the only alien
from the planet, Venus.]
There are Martians mixed in the midst
of the other seven alien members.
You must find out who the Martians are
and eliminate them
in order to return to your own
home planet.
[Eliminate all the Martians in order
to return to your own home planet.]
Okay, you're all set.
You may get started.
[But the fact that he's the only one from
Venus is unknown to everyone else.]
[Which means...]
- I'm a Martian?
- You're a Martian.
[Six Martians...]
You're from the planet, Venus.
[Against one from planet, Venus.]
[Venus vs Mars.]
A battle between Mars and Venus.
But how do I know which one is which?
[The problem is that their identity
is unknown to each other.]
So I'm from another planet?
Am I the only one who received
this secret mission?
Is this a spy mission?
[All six Martians are thinking that
they are the only Martian around.]
Anyone who's on the same team with
the blond haired alien is at an advantage.
[Will the six Martians be able to work
together to oust the only alien from Venus?]
[Mars vs Venus.
Intergalactic War- start!]
Am I the only Martian here?
What is going on here?
The hint given...
[The hints they've been given so far...
seem to indicate who the Martians are.]
The screw and the snail symbol.
The screw...
[No idea what those hints indicate.]
Ugh, this is giving me a headache.
Kwang Soo.
- Jae Suk, you haven't forgotten our deal?
- Come here.
[Kwang-Cone head and Andro-Grasshopper
are already forming an alliance.]
- I'm telling you the truth.
- I'm trusting you this time.
I'm telling you the truth.
Let's team up.
[But neither one of them are revealing
which planet they're from.]
- We could be from the same home planet.
- Let's not do this to each other.
- I'm serious.
You don't want Kim Jong Kook
to win, do you?
- We can't have him win.
- No, we can't let that happen again.
- No, let's not let that happen.
- I'm going to eliminate him no matter what.
- You have to keep your promise.
- I promise.
I'll see you later.
[They're parting ways after
forging an alliance...]
Okay, think about those hints.
But what do those hints...
[That's what we thought!]
Jae Suk.
Don't be like this, Kwang Soo.
- There were two hints, right?
- Kwang Soo, let's not be like this.
- Don't do this, Kwang Soo. I trust you.
- The screw...
Okay, Jae Suk.
[Hurry!]
[His turn?]
[But this one is still here.]
Why haven't you left yet?
Don't be like this.
[Meaningless schemes by
the two Martians.]
- I'm seriously trusting you.
- Just leave.
[They could eliminate all this suspicion by
just coming clean about their identities...]
I can't lose him like this.
[Turns around again.]
[Never-ending relay of betrayal.]
What is this?
[Martian Kiddo Alien,
and Martian Gary-Opatra.]
[Remaining cautious.]
- What have you been told?
- What?
Well, I...
- I don't really remember.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- I may be suffering from amnesia.
- Tell me, I really want to know.
- What did they tell you?
- They didn't tell me anything.
- Why didn't they tell you anything?
- They told me to just leave the car.
- Tell me the truth.
- You tell me first.
- I'm being serious.
- Come on, Gary.
- Lately, we've...
- You're smirking right now.
- We haven't talked much lately.
- I know we haven't.
But they really didn't tell me
anything.
[You're both Martians with the
same mission.]
Let's go meet up with others,
and talk this out.
[Leaves in search for others while
remaining full of suspicion for each other.]
Wait, but...
What were you just about to do?
- What?
- I saw that glint in your eye.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm really disappointed in you.
- I'm the one who feels disappointed.
Come on, let's go.
Why are you being so weary of me?
Come on, hold my hand.
- Hold my hand.
- I'm fine.
[From their inability to tell each other
that they're both Martians...]
[In the end, they leave with
their two hands tightly held together.]
Wow, Gary.
[Once the sun sets, no one can return home.
Only 21 minutes left until the sun sets.]
Are there more of us from
Venus or Mars?
I can't seem to figure that out.
[Deity of Jiri Mountain?]
- Where are you from?
- I can't tell you that.
- We've already told each other.
- I'm from Jamsil.
I'm sorry to ask this, but is
there an event going on nearby?
[Grand Opening event for
an alien grocery store!]
- I just wanted to ask.
- You're the weirdest looking one here.
- Kwang Soo is...
- Ji Hyo, are you the Fifth Element?
I really am the fifth element.
- She's lying.
- What do those two previous hints mean?
[What is the hidden meaning
behind those two hints?]
[And this alien from Venus is watching
all this from up above.]
Look at Kwang Soo going crazy.
[Martians are unable to trust each other
and start their attack on one another.]
- Jae Suk, which planet are you from?
- Kwang Soo!
- Stop being so ridiculous about this.
- Once the sun sets, it's all over for us.
[Once the sun sets, no one can
go back to their home planet!]
- Look up there.
- The moon is already up.
[My home planet is somewhere
up in that sky...]
One of us needs to get ousted!
[All the Martians are suspicious
of one another.]
[Traitors Cross!]
[As long as it's not me!
Starts the attack on Andro-Grasshopper.]
[What are these Martians doing
to their own kind?]
- The Traitors Club must stick together!
- Someone needs to be eliminated!
Running Man is entertaining.
- Kwang Soo, today's the day! Grab him!
- The sun is setting.
- You have to grab one of them.
- U!
- UEE!
- I miss you!
- Gary, come on!
- You want my help?
[Just then...]
[Kiddo Alien eliminates
Andro-Grasshopper's name tag!]
[He has to be from Venus, right?]
What the heck!
[Martian]
[I'm not... the only Martian?]
[Martians eliminates another Martian.]
I can't believe that I've been had
by those traitors.
[Andro-Grasshopper- Out!]
Wait a minute...
Everyone looks quite shocked here.
- Wait.
- What does this mean?
Who was shocked to see that?
[Since they can't trust each other, they
can't even let on about their shock.]
[Extreme confusion in their heads.]
[This one alien is still monitoring
everything that's going on.]
A Martian has been ousted.
Wow, I'm about to lose it.
A Martian's been ousted.
Why didn't he tell me that he's a Martian?
See?
Jae Suk was a Martian.
Something feels off.
When Jae Suk was eliminated,
everyone had a shocked look on their faces.
As if they realized that he
shouldn't have been eliminated.
[Venus vs Mars]
- What was Jae Suk?
- What?
- Martian.
- Martian? Really?
[Muscle Elf finds out that
Jae Suk was a Martian.]
A Martian's already been ousted?
A Martian's been ousted?
[Even the only alien from Venus doesn't
know how many Martians there are...]
I wonder if half the members
are Martians?
[Even in the midst of all this,
the sun continues to set on the horizon...]
- I think those hints that we received...
- We need to figure out those hints.
Yes, that's right.
We all need to figure out the hints.
[But the Martians have yet to reveal
their true identities to each other.]
- Jae Suk was a Martian, right?
- Yes.
Jong Kook, are you from Venus?
Yeah, I'm from Venus.
[He's from Venus?]
I'm being honest.
I'm from Venus.
Seriously?
I'm from Venus. Anyone else
from Venus, tell me who you are.
- Don't be like this and help me, if you are.
- Are you really from Venus?
Anyone else from Venus?
[They all raise their hands
up in the air.]
If you're also from Venus, then
why are you trying to oust me?
- Are you really from Venus?
- I'm from Venus.
You wouldn't be lying about being from
Venus when you're really a Martian, right?
If anyone else is from Venus,
then come stand next to me right now.
- Are you telling the truth?
- Of course.
[Even though he tells them the truth,
they still don't believe his words.]
- What do we do?
- What are we going to do?
[Staying extremely weary
of one another...]
[Muscle Elf climbs over the wall
to start his attack.]
[Just then...]
[Gary-Opatra's ambush attack.]
[Martian... another Martian!]
[What are we doing right now?]
- He's a Martian.
- He's clearly a Martian.
[These Martians continue their attack on
each other, making Jong Kook's job easier.]
[Venus vs Mars]
Wait, what's going on here?
[Add one more to the list of Martian
who ousted his own member.]
Everyone we eliminate
ends up being a Martian.
I think I need to eliminate more and see.
But what if it ends up being
another Martian?
- Are you really from Venus?
- Get away from me!
- Just get away from me right now!
- Come on, don't be like that.
[Muscle Elf doesn't want
the infamous traitor by his side.]
- Are you really not going to do it?
- Do what?
- You look so lonely by yourself.
- I can't trust you.
I'm always left on my own
whenever we play name tag elimination.
Think about this.
Two Martians have been ousted so far.
Which heightens the chance that
I'm from Venus, but I can't show you that.
[I don't need to know!]
- Just do it by yourself.
- The others keeps coming after me.
That's good for me because
I can just monitor from afar.
- What if it ends up that I'm from Venus?
- It's okay.
It's okay.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- It's okay.
It's like this. I'd rather part from you
than be tricked by you.
Don't you agree?
Haven't you felt like that before?
Isn't that part of the fun?
Getting tricked?
No, it's not.
[The time is running out for their chance
to return to their own home planet...]
I think we're all Martians.
I think we're all from Mars.
- Suk Jin.
- Yeah?
- I think you're right.
- I think we're all from Mars.
I think we're all Martians, and
we're just eliminating our own kind.
[Could we all be Martians?]
We should all gather together and
announce that we're all Martians...
- I think you're right.
- Confess that we're all Martians.
We need to stop eliminating each other.
- I think that's the right thing to do.
- I think you're right.
- Don't you think that's right?
- You're a Martian, aren't you?
- You're a Martian, right?
- What about you?
You're a Martian, aren't you?
- Yes, I'm a Martian.
- I'm a Martian, too.
We're all Martians.
I think Jong Kook's a Martian, too.
Anyone who'd confess to being from Venus
inevitably ends up being from Mars.
Let's go check on Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
We've already eliminated two Martians.
[Ugh, they're so frustrating...]
Let's go check on Suk Jin.
- Let's go check him out.
- I'll suggest we eliminate Jong Kook.
[Just be honest with each other,
and eliminate Jong Kook to win it!]
I think we can be sure whether or not we're
all Martians if we eliminate just one more.
- Stop it, Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry.
- Stop it.
- I can't help it.
Suk Jin!
- Yeah?
- Jong Kook is nearby right now.
- That's not the problem right now.
- What is it?
Our guess is that we're all Martians.
- Why would you think that?
- We're all Martians.
- Jong Kook said he's from Venus.
- No, he's a Martian, too.
[Purple Princess Blank Ji is convinced
that Jong Kook is also from Mars.]
Instead of fighting each other like this,
let's just eliminate Jong Kook first.
Should we go?
What if several of us end up getting
eliminated in our attempt to oust him?
- But we have no other choice.
- Think about this.
- Jong Kook will eliminate someone anyway.
- Suk Jin, let's go get Jong Kook.
Let's promise not to eliminate one another
until we get Jong Kook first.
- You're the least trustworthy person.
- I'm being serious.
- Can you promise me that?
- Okay, let's go.
- You can't betray us.
- I promise that I won't.
- Promise not to betray each other.
- I promise.
[This is the loyalty that lies
between Traitors Club.]
See?
[Martian]
We shouldn't be acting like this!
[And look where you wound up...]
[Martian, Big-nosed Alien- Out!]
I'm telling you that I'm right.
This is what I've been trying to tell you!
We're all Martians.
Do you get it now?
Do you believe me now?
- Then what do we do now?
- There's no sense in eliminating any more.
The most important thing is to
solve the riddle behind those clues.
- Let's eliminate Jong Kook first.
- Why do you want to eliminate everyone?
- You're from Venus, aren't you?
- No, I'm not.
[Kwang-Cone head is now being
suspected of being from Venus.]
- Gary, he's from Venus.
- I really am a Martian.
- Are you a Martian?
- I don't know.
I'm not going to say anything
about anything.
Whenever I say anything,
I end up on the losing end.
[The Martians are once again...]
- I'm not going to say anything.
- Be honest. Are you from Mars or Venus?
- I'm a Martian.
- Let's go before the sun sets.
[Proposing that they go to
eliminate Jong Kook.]
Then go to Jong Kook right now
like you want to.
[I can't help the way I am.]
- Why do you keep doing that?
- I really don't know either!
- You really don't know?
- I don't know, but there's no time.
I can't go home anymore.
I'll be in trouble if I come home late.
I have to get home before it gets dark.
My mom said bad men come out at night!
What if the screw is indicating to his head?
My head looks like a persimmon.
- My head is just...
- And this means a screwed up life.
What are you saying about my life?
Just think about it!
What's that supposed to mean?
- Let's go, the sun is about to set.
- The sun is starting to set.
[Last chance to get back to their home
planet. Sunset is almost upon them...]
[They must decide on their fate
within the next 15 minutes!]
I really want to believe that
you're from Venus.
- That I'm from Venus?
- Yeah.
- Are you from Mars or from Venus?
- You said you're from Venus.
- Are you from Mars?
- No.
Be honest with me.
There he comes right now.
Are you guys trying to...
There's Ji Hyo over there.
- Where did Ji Hyo go?
- She's over there.
Come here, Kwang Soo.
[Mars- 3 vs Venus- 1.]
- You're both from Mars, aren't you?
- No, I really am not.
Wait, are you all from Mars?
- That's what I've been saying all along.
- But you're from Venus.
Yeah, I did say...
that I'm from Venus.
Is Jong Kook from Mars, too?
[One from Venus and three from Mars.]
[A battle of the minds.]
Jong Kook is the only blonde here.
- Wow, this is...
- Why? Are you worried about something?
How can this be?
No, I'm sure one of us is
from Venus.
Ouch.
- It's a mosquito.
- Is it a mosquito?
Did you get bit?
There are tons of mosquitoes.
Knock it off!
- What are you doing?
- I'm sorry!
But I didn't rip it off!
I could've, but I didn't!
[Just then...
Gary-Opatra's ambush attack!]
- What is he?
- See?
Is he a Martian?
[A Martian eliminates
another one of his kind.]
See? I told you.
You're all Martians.
I just thought... because
he kept eliminating everyone.
[Martian, Kwang-Cone head- Out!]
[Only ten minutes left on the clock!]
How can this be?
[Jong Kook vs The Monday Couple]
- What are you? Are you a Martian?
- I'm a Martian.
Am I from Venus or Mars?
Am I confused about this?
Wow, this is unbelievable.
- This is completely unexpected.
- Let's stop this and just solve the riddle!
Okay, there's the screw.
That's for the Phillips (One) screwdriver.
Does that mean there's only one from Venus?
[Could the meaning of that really be...]
[The one screwdriver,
and number 1, in Taiwanese...]
[The two hints are indicating
to the number, one.]
[Which means only one of them
is from Venus!]
I've been telling you all along
that I'm from Venus.
[Oh, no!]
I'm from Venus. I've been
saying that from the beginning.
- Are you really from Venus?
- The most unbelievable thing is...
I thought there were only a couple from
Mars and the rest were from Venus.
But one after another,
Martians kept getting eliminated.
There's not much time,
so we should just end this.
- We need to get going.
- We're not ready to go.
[Reality finally sets in.]
- Do you remember getting eliminated by us?
- Yes, my old enemies.
[A battle between old enemies.
Mr. Capable vs The Monday Couple.]
I have no idea why we
eliminated everyone.
[The victims of fratricidal war.]
You know that I don't belong here, right?
No, you definitely belong here.
Suk Jin is handing his 'Race Starter'
title down to you.
How absurd.
I was given the chance to do something,
and I ended up eliminating everyone.
I couldn't even believe what
I was seeing.
The writers are something else!
My golden hair, and from a Golden planet?
- What are you thinking about?
- What have we been doing all this time?
- What were you thinking! I told you!
- I've been too busy eliminating everyone!
Why wouldn't any of you listen to
what I was telling you!
Now that I think about it,
I haven't eliminated a single person.
[Unbelievable...]
I haven't eliminated anyone. I was going to
get Ha Ha, but you eliminated him for me.
- I didn't know what was going on.
- Whether we live or die, let's do something.
There's no time.
We need to put an end to this.
[Will Jong Kook eliminate the two, or
will the Monday Couple eliminate Jong Kook?]
- Seriously!
- Ji Hyo.
We have to eliminate him
no matter what.
We need to grab Jong Kook.
[Mars vs Venus.
Who will be the ultimate victor?]
Ji Hyo, get behind him!
[Princess Blank Ji is in danger!]
[But she escapes the moment of danger!]
[Just who will get to
return to their home planet?]
[Who will end up being the victor
of this fierce battle?]
[Blank Ji from Mars eliminates
Jong Kook from Venus!]
- Am I from Venus?
- No, I'm from Venus.
[No, Gary and Jong Kook's name tags
got ripped off simultaneously.]
Wait, we won?
Ji Hyo!
[Purple Blank Ji survives!
Martians win!]
[Venus vs Mars
Intergalactic Battle.]
[Purple Blank Ji's sole victory.]
- Ji Hyo's the sole winner?
- What about me?
- It's not fair that I was the only one.
- Wait, I didn't win?
You've all been wanting a fight against
Kim Jong Kook, so that's what we did.
[But even with all we did for you...]
- You should've told us that!
- We had no idea.
- You didn't tell us that.
- Just tell us to eliminate Kim Jong Kook!
I just want state that this all happened
because we don't trust each other.
- You're responsible for this.
- You're the one who caused this!
- You're the one who bred all our suspicion!
- He's right!
[Will never accept their own responsibility!]
You should all take me as an example.
I came clean about being from Venus.
If the rest of you had come clean
about being from Mars...
Had you all been honest about yourselves,
then this would've ended right away!
I'm from Venus,
and you're all from Mars.
- Why couldn't you all just do that?
- Stop scolding us.
- These two are seriously...
- Me?
- Are you talking about me?
- I'm about to lose it.
- No, it's these two, Suk Jin and Dong Hoon!
- I was honest all along!
- Ugh, you egg sack!
- Ugh, seriously!
This is why I don't like Martians.
- They're no good.
- No good!
- Song Ji Hyo may return back home.
- Leave!
[Princess Blank Ji may now return home.]
But I'd like to propose something.
Can she take someone with her?
- The truth is...
- She'll be too lonely by herself.
We'll give you a choice to make.
We have prepared a relocation
fund for you to move to earth.
- Relocation fund? As in gold?
- How does she get so lucky every time?
- What's this?
- Are you kidding me?
- Wow, look at all that gold!
- How much gold is there?
[A basket full of gold
for her relocation fund.]
You can take the gold and make a new
life for yourself here on earth.
Or you can return back to
your home planet.
- If she leaves, she can't have the gold?
- This place isn't bad.
There's a condition to you taking the gold
and stepping up on the earth platform.
You must live on earth dressed
in the garment you're currently wearing.
That's the condition for taking the gold.
You must send us a picture of yourself eating
dinner at a gas station in that garment.
- That's no big deal.
- I wouldn't even hesitate!
I'd for sure take the gold!
[Stay on earth in her clothes with the gold,
or dress normally and leave without the gold?]
What are you even hesitating about?
- Let's split the gold!
- There's nothing to think about!
I'd even sleep in this getup.
- I really can sleep like this.
- I'll even come back next week like this.
The fact that you're even hesitating about
this shows that you don't need the gold.
[She's frivolous to even hesitate?]
You have to send us two pictures as proof.
- Two pictures?
- One picture at dinner...
and one more taken in front
of your house.
And lastly, another picture from her bed.
- I like that last picture idea.
- Why are you even hesitating? I'd do it!
You have five seconds.
Five, four, three, two, one!
[Chooses the relocation gold!]
[Purple Blank Ji's pictures of
evidence will soon be revealed.]
I'd have reasons to hesitate.
Looking the way you do,
you have the right to hesitate a bit.
The rest of us can do some events and
make our living since we're stuck on earth.
- We can make our new lives like that.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Let's go.
- We can start working this weekend!
[We wish all our aliens lots of luck
with their new lives here on earth.]
[One hour after filming wrapped...]
[Purple Blank Ji having dinner
with her earthling Monday boyfriend.]
[After dinner at the gas station...]
[Greets her earthling fans...]
[In the parking lot of her house...]
[Right before going to bed.]
[Goodnight!
- Purple Blank Ji.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Making a living as a salaried
employee in Korea means...]
Do I have to take the subway?
[Beat the exhaustion and the crowd to
make it to work on time!]
[Morning stress that's repeated
every single morning!]
[There's no such thing as
being late to work!]
[Overcome the foreign language barrier
and sign the contract with the foreign buyer!]
You're so catty.
[I will do whatever I must
to get that contract signed!]
[Getting through the day is busy enough,
but I have to attend a meeting?]
[No limit to brown nosing the boss.]
[But we have a surprise of our own!]
[An event for all the
salaried employees out there!]
[Next week on Running Man-
Salary men's Super Race!]