[Year 1854, Australia.]
[When everyone came here for gold.]
[Nine other people also
came here after gold.]
[Duel of Running Hills]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Year 2014 Melbourne, Australia]
[160 years after the Gold Rush]
Have a nice day.
Wow, I'm here.
[30 minutes ago]
Use public transportation to get to
Victoria State Library. Get there fast!
State library?
Victoria Joorib Do Seo Gwan.
[Kukk gets here first.]
Wow, it's magnificent.
[Victoria State Library opened in
Melbourne in 1854.]
[An ancient tome.]
Stars of Running Hills.
There are books about the history
of Running Hills in the library with stars.
The books have one to four stars.
One person may open one book each.
The moment you open the book, the stars
will be yours. It will signify your rank.
Blue lights!
Like in the movies!
It's amazing.
- It would've been perfect if he wasn't in the view.
- What?
It's beautiful.
Wow, it's like the movies.
Good morning, Australia.
Hi.
Nice weather.
- Woo Bin!
- Hey.
- Let's team up today.
- Of course!
- We're black and white. Perfect.
- Yes.
- We got this.
[Reading for 10 minutes...]
So do I open the book?
This library is beautiful.
- Are they all books?
- Kwang Soo.
- How are we going to find them?
- There are so many!
There are so many!
- Buddy.
- Huh?
Feel free to use the library ladder.
I can reach it!
Buddy, use it.
There you go.
It's easy.
It's beautiful.
Amazing.
[It becomes his
the moment he opens it.]
If it's one to four...
A three isn't so bad is it?
You can just leave it here and
look for a four. And maybe come back.
No!
- You mean leave it here for you?
- C'mon! I don't want a three.
I'm just going to open this one.
[Where did Jong Kook go?]
You found one?
How many stars?
- How many?
- My friends!
My friends!
I found my book here in
my hometown.
Do I open it?
No!
I want to go in too!
Jae Suk!
Take me with you!
[Acting again.]
No!
[A manor in the Gold Rush era.]
What is this?
What happened?
Huh?
There is all old furniture.
What happened?
I found the one with three.
- Jae Suk!
- You're here.
When did you get here?
You have three stars?
Oh what?
I have four!
- I see them.
- Four-star!
Okay I see it.
- Do you even know where we are?
- Here?
- Of course I do.
- Tell me.
- It's the Wild West.
- That's America!
- No?
- This is Australia.
It's the Gold Rush era.
-  Year 1854.
- Gold Rush?
Year 1854 Gold Rush.
Is this a blouse or what?
- It's a blouse.
- Yeah, so what?
- You like clothes like these.
- So what?
They gave me this.
- What's taking everyone so long?
- Yeah.
We have an Alps boy.
Are we selling hot dogs?
- He's a four-star.
- One hot dog please.
But what do the stars mean?
He looks good.
He's the only good looking one.
Hey! Do it again! Roll!
Did you taylor your clothes?
Why do you look so good?
They just gave me these.
I got a blouse!
I'm a father to a child but
I still have to wear suspenders.
What does being a father have
to do with suspenders?
You've been wearing
Groucho glasses for years!
- This is my nose.
- Is it really?
This one is real.
It's here.
Three stars.
That's not bad.
Only four are left.
Did you find one?
Yeah.
- How many?
- It's a three.
I found one too, but no one
has found a four yet.
- No one?
- No.
I found a two.
But no one has found a four.
They found a three and two twos.
So there's only one three.
But there are two fours.
That's why I'm not leaving.
Hey!
I opened it.
It's upside down.
You have to open it.
I got it!
No! Kwang Soo!
I knew this would happen!
Lee Kwang Soo!
You will pay for this!
You have to do it again.
That's no good. Do it again.
Someone did this already? Who?
Do it again.
I rolled about three times.
Hey friend!
Aren't we friends?
What's wrong with you?
You had no pants to wear?
Isn't that a bit unfitting?
- Hey!
- Ji Suk!
Gosh!
- Hear me out.
- I came all the way here to get you.
Try to understand.
I found this three-star one.
He told me that I had to find a
four-star. And then he stole mine.
- Let's team up today.
- I'm a one-star.
It wasn't just him. Ji Hyo...
How about this?
[Forces him with the one-star]
Ji Suk!
- Ji Hyo! Not that one!
- No!
- Hey!
- How come you're a one-star?
They both came at the same time.
There was a two-star book.
It was a two.
Ji Hyo! You want to look
at it together?
- Our hands are in it together.
- Together.
- Okay.
- Don't cheat.
Close your eyes for a sec.
One, two, three!
Gary and I shared a two-star.
We looked at it together.
Gary couldn't find one.
Howdy Sheriffs.
They are our ranks!
We're sheriffs?
[This is an ancient manor in Australia.]
You will have your chance to
increase your rank badges here.
We can increase them?
We will pick the game and the
players to play the game.
The players picked will wage
their star in the duel.
But I only have one.
Having more is a huge advantage.
The sheriffs that are not picked may
bet their stars on who is going to win.
Or we can lose it all.
You don't have to bet if
you don't want to.
But if we want to win,
we want to make bets.
When you win, you will receive
double the amount of stars you bet.
You will lose them when you lose.
What should we do
when we have only one?
You have to be cautious.
Isn't that just obvious?
Be cautious?
- What?
- What's your rank?
Make me your deputy.
The games were important.
The first game is Ddak-ji.
I like Ddak-ji.
- The players will be...
- The two hats?
Kim Jong Kook and...
Rain!
Both players will play Ddak-ji.
Who ever flips the other Ddak-ji wins.
Each player will bet their own stars. The
rest of the participants may place their bets.
I don't know how good they are.
The last time I played was
in elementary school.
He still plays now.
He even practices at home.
No, I don't know about this.
You have to give me an advantage.
- I don't know how good Rain is.
- Show us how you'd do it.
Show you?
Try it.
He's good.
Ji Hoon bet his only badge.
- It's his last one.
- He's desperate.
- I'm desperate.
- Yes.
Okay! Adios! Rain!
Jong Kook!
Bet on Ji Hoon, he's desperate.
I will bet on Jong Kook.
Kwang Soo!
- This is...
- I thought we had something.
I don't know about this.
- It's okay!
- Then I bet on Jong Kook.
- You said that it was okay.
- Kwang Soo!
- Can I change my mind?
- No.
Jae Suk!
I will show you!
Okay! Okay!
Give him energy.
One game or one out of three?
One game!
- One game?
- Yeah! One game.
Wait! No spreading legs.
Should I play like this then?
Well it is new.
- It's cute!
- Yeah, it looks good.
One two three!
You look cute.
Three stars are at stake.
Let's go!
- He's going! He's going!
- Please no. Please.
It won't flip.
It's really heavy.
- No pressure.
- No, no.
You have to follow through.
You have to do it quickly.
Okay, you almost got it.
Get it next time.
- I should have bet on him!
- Ji Hoon could've gotten him on the next turn.
Why am I so good?
- Rain's star is now taken.
- He no longer has any.
You just need to bet against Jae Suk.
No.
I'm betting two this time.
What do I do when I no
longer have a star?
Borrow some.
Who made him lose his star?
Give me one.
- Then let him borrow yours!
- I only have three.
- Give it.
- It's mine!
Share the wealth.
Do you know how many times
I've lost because of you?
- I will give you this. Pay me back.
- Yes sir.
- Pay me back.
Each one of these will be really valuable.
What this time?
This time it will be
Song Ji Hyo vs Gary.
What a tragedy.
They have only one each.
What's going on?
Look how serious Ji Hoon is.
- Is it your last one again?
- Yes sir.
I'm betting along with Ji Hoon.
This one is serving with eyes closed.
He's good at games with eyes closed.
Close your eyes and pour water
in the cup on top of someone's head.
- On my head?
- No.
You will pick a partner. Whoever
pours to the blue line first wins.
- Yes sir.
- Ji Hyo is a better choice because she's a girl.
- Gary is good.
- I'm good. I'm really good.
- But you could lose on purpose for her.
- No, because I only have one.
Do you remember how you
got here in the first place?
Sorry, but that's just life.
Okay.
I won't help you next time.
Okay!
- Make your bets!
- Just go against Jae Suk.
Bet against Jae Suk.
- Why me?
- My friends.
You are waiting for me
to make the bets first.
Wait for him. He's good.
- I like Gary.
- No, bet on Ji Hyo.
- Gary.
- No!
Why?
- Song Ji Hyo.
- Jae Suk is really bad at bets.
Song Ji Hyo!
You're all going to fall.
You just won the last game,
so you will lose this one.
Choose on whose head
you will place the glass.
- Choose Kwang Soo!
- Yeah, choose me.
Suk Jin, Jong Kook, and I
bet on Gary.
Jong Kook is good at this stuff.
I could be too much
pressure for him.
No pressure.
I choose you.
Yeah, go for Jong Kook.
I need the pressure to do well.
Yeah, Gary good choice.
It should be Kwang Soo.
- I pick Kim Woo Bin.
- Yeah.
- Why?
- He looks good.
The pressure could
make her do better.
Close your eyes.
Okay. Ji Hyo?
She can't be good at everything.
They are covered.
Ready?
Get set.
Go!
Right now.
- Right here.
- Right here?
- Yeah.
- I'm dying.
You can't look Ji Hyo.
- Am I good?
- Okay.
Stop! Stop!
I'm out of water.
I can't tell if I'm there or not.
Okay, Song Ji Hyo.
- Okay, Gary.
- He got this. He can do it.
- Okay!
- Gary is good at these things.
Rough! Rough! Go rough!
Rough! Rough!
Rough!
You got Ji Hyo.
Just go easy! Easy!
Easy!
Ready go!
We won!
- You said rough!
- That's rough?
You got it!
- I can get it next time.
I'm so nervous.
I want to win.
Ready! Get set go!
You're missing it.
Ji Hyo got angry too.
I didn't get him?
Just go!
Ji Hyo is angry. We're angry.
Everyone is angry.
She got really angry there.
She's got some temper.
Gary, I bet all I have on you.
- You bet everything on me?
- Ready!
- Go!
- You have to stay still.
- Why did you move?
Why move?
You did it on purpose to
get me soaked!
It's like a shower.
Why is this so hard?
I'm going to try something else.
- What is it this time?
- She opened the lid.
Did you really lose your temper?
Should I try this?
No, don't do it.
Don't lose your confidence.
- Just do as you were doing.
- Don't lose your confidence.
Ready! Get set...
Go!
- Did she do it?
- She got it!
I got it right?
I got it! I got it!
You've got it!
They are right.
Betting against me always wins.
Can I bet against myself too?
Ha Ha has six!
This time we will have
Kim Woo Bin and Yoo Jae Suk.
Competing in...
stacking Australian coins.
I'm not good at stacking.
You get to stack 10 to 15.
When the stack falls you lose.
I'm bad at this.
I'm bad at stacking.
I'm going to bet only one.
Bet two! Bet two so that you will
have a sense of responsibility.
What are you doing?
Fifteen!
Jae Suk has fifteen.
- Good! Good!
- That's our plan.
This is our plan!
That's ten.
- Just win once!
- Please tip over.
Don't move your feet.
Be careful.
You're shaking the ground.
Nobody move!
Sit!
This is a delicate sport!
Please just tip over.
Huh?
- What?
- What did you say?
He's about to hit him for this.
- You're about to knock it with your knee.
- Be careful.
Tip over!
It's good!
Don't move!
Don't even be happy!
Be happy later when it's over.
One, two, three!
Take it slowly.
Look at the angle.
If it falls during this turn,
then it's on Jae Suk.
You have to be daring.
Be daring.
Be daring. Just drop it.
- He's shaking.
- Just let it go.
I knew it.
You just have to bet against Jae Suk.
Gary, it's okay.
I told you.
Are you going to start without us then?
We have nothing.
We're the same as we were
in the morning.
I'm sure we can buy more somewhere.
Let's buy some at the
souvenir shop.
Don't worry Gary.
We can buy some out there.
What's that?
Look at them.
- They are.
- Wow it looks fun.
Wow.
Where did you get these cars?
They are nice.
- It's so cool.
- How do you open these doors?
It opens forward.
It's nice.
Yes! Nice!
Woo Bin! You look good in this.
- You think my hat is going to fly off?
-  Yeah, the wind will blow it off.
We have nothing!
We start from nothing!
Let's go. Start!
But it's out without the AC.
'I want to avoid the sun.'
'I want to avoid the sun.' (Rain's song)
Riding a convertible in Australia.
We're driving in a classic car with
the modern background.
- Amigo! Amigo!
- Adios!
Here we go!
I think we rode on every possible
mode of transportation in Australia.
Even this.
- It's good!
Go! Let's go!
[Year 1854 Running Hills]
[Gold Rush center in
the Australian wilderness.]
[It's as if time stopped
here 160 years ago.]
[This is the last challenge for
our sheriffs.]
Wow what is this?
What year is this?
- It's like their traditional village.
- Hi.
[Zero Stars]
Ji Suk Jin, Yoo Jae Suk, Kang Gary
[Two Stars]
Jung Ji Hoon/Rain
What is this?
[Three Stars]
Kim Jong Kook
Song Ji Hyo
Wow.
They really look real.
[Five Stars]
Lee Kwang Soo
Hi!
How are you?
I'm fine thank you and you?
- Yes I'm doing good. Go straight up there.
- Yes sir.
[Six Stars]
Ha Ha
Hi, thank you.
Hi.
Finally.
[Seven Stars]
Kim Woo Bin
Sheriffs of Running Hills. We will
now find the best sheriff of you all.
Steal the badges of the other sheriffs
and increase your number of badges.
You can only rip the name tag of the sheriff
whose number of badges is less than yours.
I got it!
What's up Mr. Smith!
I have the advantage.
I can take anyone's name tag.
You may fulfill the missions
in Running Hills to receive stars.
No, no! I need to hurry up.
The last sheriff left will receive
a special treat.
How can we accomplish seven
different missions?
Do you have something against me?
It's over.
Finally I...
Wow, that scared me.
The person with one star cannot take the
name tag of someone who has two.
But if that person
takes it off by mistake...
Then one of his stars will
be given to the other person.
Having more stars is an advantage.
I've always wanted to
live in this era once.
It's really like the wild west.
It's so cool.
I like the atmosphere.
- How many do you have?
- I have three!
- I won with Jong Kook.
- You couldn't win more?
No, I couldn't win more.
You're a big jerk if you take mine
off right now.
Since I'm at the highest
position in this town.
You should salute when you see me.
Howdy sir.
- Good.
- You're the best sheriff sir.
Good.
Everyone! Help me to
keep the peace of this town.
Keep going. Trust me and
have a fulfilling day.
Have a nice day!
Hi.
What are you doing?
- Ji Suk!
- Yeah, out of time?
- It's easy.
- Say good luck!
Good! Good!
Fail! Fail!
It's no good.
Yeah sorry, J. It looks like you failed.
You have to get it on your next mission.
Okay. I will try.
How you doing, mate?
I'm Cain.
I'm Nal Yu.
Nal Yu?
Oh Nal Yu.
I have this for you.
[Classic Bowling: Score a strike
within two minutes to receive a star!]
- Yes start.
- Are you ready? Let's go.
Go!
Strike!
Come on! Come on! Hurry up!
They are giving me energy.
And when I fail they go, 'awww.'
- Okay try!
- Okay one more try.
I will make it for you!
Oh gosh.
Two minutes.
- Sorry.
- Sorry. You failed the mission.
- Keep going, good luck!
- Thank you!
Thank you!
I couldn't have done it without them.
They are great people.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- Good luck!
- Thank you!
- High five.
Thank you.
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo! I'm here!
Kwang Soo! It's today.
- Sir! Yes sir!
- Yes.
- You have more already?
- I have four.
- How many do you have?
- You have four, five, six.
Wow.
Let me go get one more.
I've waited four years for
this moment.
- Hey! Hey!
- Traitor! Cross!
The stars were important.
Come here.
- You know what I want right?
- I can't believe this.
Let's make it quick and good.
Jong Kook, can you take mine off?
- No.
- You don't want to?
Take it off.
Fine then.
Okay! I will let you go.
Me too.
You're the man!
I'm free to go?
Okay take care!
Now that's what I'm talking about!
He's practical and reasonable.
Let's make a living with this.
This isn't bad.
I don't want a miserable death.
I can't ever allow myself... No.
Today is our day.
If we can't win today,
we're just stupid.
- It's Jae Suk.
- Just rip his name tag.
- Come here.
- Okay.
- Everyone, I just finished my mission.
- You don't have any stars?
What?
No, that's not it.
You don't have any?
Please let me finish a mission.
- He doesn't have any.
- No.
We will let you go then.
Okay Sheriff.
Thank you sir.
- You better behave.
- Yes sir.
- I hear a lot of things about you.
- Yes sir!
- Take your glasses off.
Sit! Sit!
Sheriff! I think you need to
take charge here.
He is kissing my butt here.
I make allegiance to you
and you only sir.
- I would never give in for a six-star.
- Sir!
Can you let this happen?
He just slapped me.
He knows how the ranks work here.
Make me your loyal servant.
You're a young talented man.
I will be your dog for my life!
Look at these fellas.
- Sir, I will go get one star then.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Don't go anywhere else.
- Are you going to let him go?
- Keep going.
- After what he's done to me?
He's my favorite kid.
- Are you disobeying me?
- No sir, I'm sorry sir.
I'm sorry sir.
- I was foolish.
- Don't say that.
- Yes sir.
- He's nice.
Look how he runs away like a girl.
We have to get Jong Kook
the next time we see him.
And Rain... we need to take
out all the strong ones.
We have to get them right now.
I need four stars at least.
I wonder what the mission is.
I have a bad feeling
about going this way.
I should go back that way.
I shouldn't go that way.
Do I have to live like this?
I have to live like a coward.
It's Gary.
- Gary!
- Yeah?
- How many do you have?
- Me too.
Which ones have you tried?
You have two stars!
- I tried the hitting one.
- You have two.
Yes.
- You have three?
- I will collect some and give them to you.
- I will help you.
- Why?
- Anyone can get me right now.
- Yes.
So I will just help you.
Not now. I will get some more.
- Let's go together then.
- Okay.
I can't run. I will help you.
You have my word.
No, it doesn't work like that.
I will give you more!
- Accept it.
- Not now.
I will finish the mission there
and give it to you.
I will give it to you.
You will never win the missions.
I will!
I will give them to you! Really! Hey!
No! Not now!
Hurry! We don't have time.
Just one.
Let's go! It's Gary!
- Give me one at least.
- Not now!
Not now!
It's now!
Aww come on.
[The apex predator]
Hey! I will help you!
See?
We should have teamed up.
How can we team up in this game?
- It should be four stars including Suk Jin's.
- Four stars.
Okay!
How many is that then?
That's a lot.
- I'm going to win today.
- Take Jong Kook's.
I will.
- This is for you.
- Thank you so much!
I got four.
[Take only one can out within
the time limit.]
- Well done.
- Okay! Thank you.
[Wear pedometer and dance to
get it up to 150 within a minute.]
This is so hard.
How can I make it more dance-like
than this?
150.
235, well done!
Okay.
You passed the mission.
I think you passed.
- Okay thank you.
- Thank you.
I have to go. Bye.
I have more stars now but there
are so many people like Kwang Soo.
And Ha Ha has a lot.
If they work together, they can get me.
Even if they didn't
they could still get me right?
Ha Ha, we need to go take out
Jong Kook or Ji Hyo.
- Let's take it off right now.
- When we can.
You and I should get Ji Hyo and
then work our way up to Ji Hoon.
She's probably in there. You know
this is our one and only chance.
- Oh! You have two now.
- Sir yes sir!
- Nothing wrong sir
- Good.
Come here.
What were you doing here?
Were you doing your mission?
I'm almost at the same level.
Do I not deserve your respect?
Same level?
- How dare you to say that?
- This is why I like him.
- This is mutiny! Can you believe this?
- How dare you!
Don't you have eyes?
Come here.
- You're getting on my nerves.
- Come on.
You're getting on my nerves.
Hey! You don't need to do that.
Sheriff! You're going to let him do that?
- Sir yes sir!
- Good, good.
- The mission over there is nice.
- Yes sir!
- Go there.
Okay, you can go.
- I can't believe this.
- What are you looking at?
- What?
Stop! Stop!
- I'm just going to...
- Just go back in.
- He's defying the order!
- Let him go.
- Okay?
- Deputy Lee!
Are you filming The Wizard of Oz?
Will you just go?
I can't stand this anymore.
Geez.
Take him out.
Take him out when you see him.
Taking out people will be faster.
Missions will take forever.
Hey! How many does he have?
- He's the apex.
- Look who's here.
Sir yes sir!
How many is that?
- I have too many to even count.
- I got your back sir.
I'm not a concern to you sir.
Me neither.
I'm a nobody.
One, two, three...
Who do you think you're touching?
There's Yoo Jae Suk over there.
Not me yet.
You can take him.
Because if Gary and Suk Jin...
I already got them.
You're truly the king.
I guess Kwang Soo is next.
Us three. Us three.
What about Jong Kook and Rain?
- Give us one chance.
- We will take care of it.
- Give us one more chance.
- If I see you again, I will take it off.
Yes sir.
I will crawl like an ant.
- What about you?
- I will stick to the ground like a piece of gum.
Low.
- You sound trustworthy.
- Take good care sir!
What a beautiful world.
The world is upside down.
He's still here.
That young'n!
We should have gotten rid
of him when he was a lad.
The world is going backwards.
They say power corrupts people.
He has no respect for his seniors.
Look at his arrogant face.
That young fella! Him!
He's been an Heir since he was a lad.
I've heard of it too sir.
He's just...
Right in front of the wood-splitting.
You promised!
Let me go do wood splitting real quick.
Then before you go...
- Okay.
- Then I won't get you.
Here.
Let me do the wood splitting.
I'm giving you time because
you like it so much.
Just one please! You're like school
bullies robbing pocket change.
- Just one for now!
- You can go.
Is it him or me? Choose.
[Kwang Soo's stars = Ha Ha's stars]
No, it's not that. Let me finish
this one then. Wait here.
Wait right here.
- Let him go, buddy.
- Buddy?
- How many stars do you have?
Hey! You need to give me one too!
Run! Run!
What's going on?
What? How many do you have?
- This is driving me nuts.
- Let's just go.
Let's go!
- I can't believe this.
- Let's go!
What is this?
It's right here.
It's alluvial gold.
They are washing alluvial gold.
- You have three minutes.
- Three minutes, okay.
Gosh.
Half way!
Geez.
This isn't easy.
No?
What exactly am I doing right now?
What am I doing?
I can win this much gold if I win...
Okay, let's have a look.
No?
Tiny tiny little ones, sir.
Very tiny little ones.
Here!
- Very tiny! Very small.
- Here here.
It's here.
You need a microscope for this.
Here, gold. Gold.
- Cool!
- Cool? Yeah.
Gold.
- One dot.
- Yeah!
Did you see it?
Geez. They just confirmed it for you.
Gold gold gold.
- Oh cool.
- Cool.
Here we go.
That one?
- See? It's in here.
- Here?
Yay! Little tiny bit of gold!
Where is it?
Oh! It's right here.
- Okay thank you.
- Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Do I get a star?
You have found gold.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Okay!
[A scroll instead of a star?]
- I want it.
- Yeah okay!
They like it. Bye!
Bye!
What is this? Huh?
- What's this?
- This is a map sir.
That's a treasure map.
That's the Running Hill.
That's where the treasure is.
Oh really?
Right now sir,
we're down here.
Here. Up or down?
No, that's for you!
- Oh cruel.
- What's your name?
My name? Mr. Yoo.
- I like that.
- Mr. Yoo?
Yeah, Mr. Yoo.
And you! What's your name?
- Karkar.
- My name is Jess.
- Jess! Okay, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. Bye thank you!
Bye bye! Have fun!
Bye, bye.
The Australian girls like me.
Bye!
I feel like I'm leaving
the fairy land.
They are so cute.
Where is this leading to?
Is there a quiet place?
What is this?
Where is this? Huh?
Isn't this this?
That's where I am.
Is this the right place?
I think it's this place.
What is this?
- Excuse me.
- Yep.
Uhh... mission?
- Is this here?
- Yeah, but you're gonna go underground.
Underground?
Yeah yeah, okay thank you.
Can you show him the way
to the underground?
Okay thank you.
What is this? Huh?
I feel like I'm going to the magic land.
Okay, thank you.
This is going underground.
Woo Bin! I'm here.
Kwang Soo and Ha Ha are over there.
I will take them out the next time
I see them.
Oh yeah? Can you just take them
out right now?
- Okay I will.
- They took one of mine again!
- They took yours?
- Yeah.
It's like when I take your tag off.
Then I will have to give one to you.
Then... do you want me to
give you one?
- No.
- You're good?
- You'd rather take them all later?
- Yes.
Okay then.
You have more than Kwang Soo?
Of course.
- Then take him out. He's a threat.
- I will be back.
You have to take him out.
You want me to take Kwang Soo with you?
The world couldn't be more beautiful.
I will go get him for you.
Let's take out Kwang Soo.
That's good enough for me.
Kwang Soo was so polite every
time I saw him. I felt so bad.
Go!
I'm sorry.
I need to get this.
Today is the day!
Ran out of time!
Okay! One more.
- Last!
- One more okay.
Super power.
Thank you sir.
I got nine.
Over there!
- Wait.
- Where did Kwang Soo go?
He must be doing the missions right now.
They didn't see me.
When did he join him?
It's Ha Ha.
Sir yes sir!
He's running away.
He went that way.
You want me to get him?
From the other way?
He went the other way.
Go! Go see if he went that way.
Okay.
Sir yes sir!
I won't take it off. I won't.
- Where is Kwang Soo?
- He's doing the whipping mission.
- Whipping.
- How many does he have?
He has eight. You can just...
Wow how many do you have sir?
Hey you know he took
all the stars from me.
- I did not.
- I think it's time to eliminate him.
- Sir! Sir!
- Don't get weak.
Wait!
- Thank you.
- Let's go get the giraffe.
Huh? How?
He had so many stars, how?
Geez. Good for him.
That's power.
He deserved it for abusing his power.
What is this?
Okay thank you.
It's going underground.
What is this? It's chilly.
It's scary.
It's hot outside, but it's chilly in here.
How far is this going?
The lights went on.
Okay thank you!
There?
This is like Indiana Jones.
It goes in so far.
What is this?
[Red glittering star badge?]
The One Badge.
- It's the One Badge.
- What?
Anyone with the One Badge may rip off
name tags regardless of
the star-count for 10 minutes.
- 10 minutes?
- 10 minutes.
You may wear it now, or
you may wear it later.
The duration is 10 minutes.
- Just 10 minutes?
- You can't give it to others.
I don't die even if I
get my name tag taken?
Wow.
One thing is for sure.
I'm going to use this badge...
to take out Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo!
I'm going to get you.
It's going to be a mess
when I get out there.
I'm going to get Lee Kwang Soo first.
Watch!
The One Badge!
It's only ten minutes. Lee Kwang Soo!
You have humiliated me.
I will get you.
You act like you're mighty because
you have a few more badges?
Just watch.
I will finish you.
The One Badge has been found.
What's that? The One Badge?
The person with the One Badge
can take out anyone.
There was the One Badge?
Dang.
I knew it.
I didn't think I could win so easily.
There's got to be a time limit.
I don't have to run into him
and lose my name tag.
That will be just heart breaking.
I should just hide then.
All I've got is time.
Australia shooting is so hard.
The can is light.
- How did you have...
- Huh? Ji Hoon!
You were taken out?
- Yes.
- How?
- I was betrayed by Kwang Soo.
- Again?
- You have to tell me when someone is here.
- Okay.
I can't take yours off anyway.
Grab his arms.
And I will be loyal to you.
I told you two days ago
that I will not betray you.
Okay okay.
You want me to stay with you then?
- That's a good idea.
- Okay.
- Ha Ha disappeared all of the sudden.
- Hey.
He's just...
You can't trust him.
He is reliably bad.
- Do you feel betrayed?
- Yeah, I do.
That's Running Man.
You know after a few
times you get angry.
Someone did that for three years.
Me.
Woo Bin is going to win anyway.
No, there's the One Badge.
Whether Jae Suk has it or Jong Kook
has it, their targets will be Woo Bin.
- That's game then.
- Getting Woo Bin's name tag ends the game.
- Let's go then.
- Where?
To the hotel.
Where's the restroom here?
10 minutes?
I have to find Lee Kwang Soo first.
For 10 minutes, this is my street.
Let's go.
This is what you call waiting
for the opportune moment.
What's that?
The One Badge?
Sir yes sir!
Let me take Jong Kook's tag off!
- You have a lot of stars.
- Yes sir. I will give them to you sir.
No, I don't need them.
Please.
I was immature when I was
young. I'm sorry sir!
You were speaking some rather
mean words to me earlier.
- I was...
- You made a fist at me.
- I always carried a disease.
- Switch hats?
Finally I have a hat that suits me.
- Where is Woo Bin?
- He went that way earlier.
- What about Ji Hoon?
- I took him out sir.
- And Ji Hyo?
- She's doing her mission somewhere.
- I saw Jong Kook going in for a mission.
- Yes.
- Will you take out Jong Kook for me then?
- Yes sir.
- Good. You know about this badge?
- Yes sir. I was shocked sir.
- How did you know?
- They made an announcement.
Oh no.
That's why everyone is hiding.
Even if it weren't for the announcement, anyone
would have ran away from your presence.
Turn around.
- Sheriff.
- Turn around.
- Not that it's a problem.
- Turn around before I lose it.
- I can turn around.
- Turn around if you don't want any trouble.
- But...
- Turn around.
They say people abuse power
when they have power.
Okay, where did you get all this?
I can take stars from him?
If you take his name tag right now,
you get to have all his stars.
Really?
Director! What a cruel thing to say.
Please leave us to talk privately.
I don't want you to interrupt.
Look. Turn around.
Sir!
- No! No!
- Sir!
I have always wanted to call you sir.
- Then take out Jong Kook in front of me.
- Yes sir. I can do it sir.
- You're going to betray me again?
- No sir.
It's just that taking you out
right now is too easy.
- It's not fun.
- Absolutely sir.
- It's too obvious. I hate obvious.
- Take out Jong Kook right now.
- Yes sir.
You don't need any words.
Just go and take him out.
- Okay go.
- Thank you sir.
- He's splitting wood.
- Good.
I will go get him.
Wait for him to finish his mission.
Let's go!
- Thank you!
- Here's your stuff.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you. Good job.
It's not over yet!
Good job! Good work.
- Take it off.
- I will take it off sir.
Please! Let me take it.
Jong Kook!
Are you holding him for me?
Sir! Sir!
You cannot forget!
I will take his and give it right
back to you.
He's taken so many from me.
- No!
- Okay, you can go.
- Are you ready to do your best for me?
- Of course.
- Will you do your best for me?
- Okay! I will trust you then.
- Okay!
- Wait.
- I will take them off for you.
Get your hands off of me!
They are my stars!
I can't believe a two-star
insults me like this.
Good work sir.
Will you help me too?
Right here.
- What are you doing?
- I'm helping you.
What are you doing? You can go.
- Go now!
- I should have finished you back then!
I should have finished you!
That's what happens to the
hounds after hunting is over.
Why can't you talk softly like
that normally?
It's so nice.
Look at you. You know
how to warm up to people.
- I like you.
- Of course sir.
I think I like you.
- Shall I end this now?
- You just have so many.
They look really good on you sir.
Done! One, two, three, four...
- No need. Let's go.
- Yes sir.
- I think Woo Bin is determined.
- I think it's time to end it now.
- Yes sir.
Thank you for giving me the chance to
exact my vengeance.
I will protect you.
You have nothing to worry about.
- Even after your expiration is due...
- I will get you a new hat when I win.
- You look like a mess.
- Yes sir.
No matter how hard it is,
you should always dress up.
- Like me.
- Thank you sir.
- It's running out.
- Really? Let's go.
We need to get Woo Bin.
We could lose it all to Woo Bin.
You must be careful. Let's go.
- Where is he?
- Where is Woo Bin?
The target is me.
Is Woo Bin over there?
I don't think so.
The wind is blowing right before
the final battle.
- It's almost over.
- I know, please give me some time.
My friends told me to win this.
- Where is he?
How many badges does Woo Bin have?
He has a lot. Even if you
were to take mine... 20...
I'm glad I have a lot of badges at least.
- Or you would have taken mine.
- I would not.
- You would have grabbed me by my wrist.
- No.
I should have found Woo Bin.
Let's go hide.
And see how many Woo Bin has.
If he has more than you...
Then take mine and win.
You see my devotion? Huh?
- You are devoted.
- I will devote myself for someone else's victory.
I'm the type to devote myself.
It's called a sacrifice.
Sacrifice.
- Beautiful.
- Yeah, I sacrifice.
- You're like a brother.
- I am.
Give them to me right now.
I think I need them.
You must be kidding.
You are kidding.
He took Jong Kook's.
You could go to Woo Bin.
Give them to me right now. I'm sorry.
I was talking about sacrifice.
Yeah, you can sacrifice right now.
It's for the greater good.
Don't touch me.
I will give them to you.
Your attitude is changing.
I was being nice to you.
Is this your last day on Running Man?
- Your attitude is back again?
- Is this your last day on Running Man?
- You're not going to put them on for him?
- No, why would I?
You were putting them on me earlier.
You want me to put them on
so that they will never come off?
- What are you saying?
- Put them on for good?
You want badges on for life?
Gosh.
Two left?
Ji Hyo and Jae Suk.
The One Badge is over.
Okay.
- Hello!
- Hello! See you again.
Hi!
Wow, look at all these
stars you have.
Wait, what do the stars represent?
That's really long...
- You want them?
- Yes!
Can I have one please?
Sorry, but only one!
Sorry! You keep!
Thank you so much.
Sorry! Bye bye.
Bye!
Karkar!
I wish I could give them all.
But I still have the power for that right?
- No! You have 19 now.
- Why?
That's a gift!
- That's a gift.
- You have 19.
I know that you're nice.
I just gave one. Imagine how
much she wanted this.
19 now.
Have you seen Jae Suk?
Wait.
How many do you have?
How many?
21.
Oh.
- We have the same.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- I see.
- Do you really have 21?
You can tell.
I have this many too.
You know if you miscount,
it gets you back right?
- I think it's about the same.
- What?
- Yeah.
- You can take it off to find out.
- Should I?
- It could get out back.
- I know.
You look like you're convicted.
What do you want to do?
Be a man?
- You want to do it?
- Sure.
But have you seen Ji Hyo or not?
- I haven't seen her.
- Really?
Oh.
- When did you collect so many?
- Huh?
When did you collect so many?
It's a long story.
I've been working hard.
I think we should take out Ji Hyo first.
Shadow in operation.
There are two One Badges.
One may take off the name tags.
The other one cannot.
But there is only Ji Hyo left.
What?
What's that mean?
What's going on?
I'm sorry!
- Woo Bin!
- What's going on?
Life is futile.
I should have just given
these to all of those little girls.
It's so good!
Shadow is the best!
[30 minutes ago]
Thank you!
Shadow?
What does this mean?
The One Badge is running out.
Look for him!
- Where is he?
- How many badges does Woo Bin have?
It's here.
Why is there one more?
Shadow?
- It says 'Shadow' on it right?
- Yes.
This one is different from the
One Badge from earlier.
You may revive someone taken out
and be invincible for five minutes.
- Ji Hyo!
- It's Ji Hyo.
I have two One Badges.
You can revive us?
- I can revive one.
- Just one?
That person and I can join together
have have absolute power for five minutes.
But five minutes after that person
disappears too.
He will disappear.
- Ji Hoon! Go.
- Go Ji Hoon.
If you take everyone out
within the time, you win.
And I promise to split the
winnings seven to three.
Go Ji Hoon.
Let Ji Hoon win.
What's going on?
I'm sorry! Let's go!
This is the best.
Woo Bin!
I'm sorry. Let's end it here.
We have the One Badge.
Woo Bin!
Where are you going?
Woo Bin! It's over.
It's over Woo Bin.
- It's not over.
- Let's just go.
Go where?
Five, four, three, two, one.
It's over.
We can't do anything about it.
Geez.
Kim Woo Bin! It seems that you got
yourself 23 stars while I was getting mine.
Of course.
- 23 right?
- 23.
- What should we do?
- What else?
We have no place left to go.
It was a fun time.
- It was fun.
- In Australia.
In Australia... with you.
Thank you.
I get to face Kim Woo Bin,
the hot shot nowadays.
- It's an honor.
- Stop it.
I will die honorably.
Wait!
So this is how you play?
You hold the vest!
Good job. You worked hard.
Good job.
You won fair and square.
It looks like Ji Hyo has won.
Woo Bin has won.
Woo Bin has won?
Good job.
Finally after three visits,
you get to win.
He was talking about never coming back.
Good job.
Woo Bin won on his third visit.
- Here is the prize.
- What's the prize?
Woo Bin! Take us out tonight.
Woo Bin won!
- Congratulate him!
- It's real money!
I think I'm smiling for the first time
in three days.
- It's all thanks to your help.
- Will you visit us again?
I will come back.
If I didn't win today, I was
really going to think about it.
Ji Hoon and Woo Bin really worked
hard this time.
Let's applaud them.
I would like thank those
who have helped us.
We will see you in Korea.
Thank you!
Subtitles by DramaFever
- We may go far away today.
- Really?
Let's go. Let's go, let's go!
Where's the bus?
I didn't get off here.
No way. No!
- Last for the time limit?
- We can do it.
I said Gwangju.
Where are we going?
- Where are you going?
- Help us.
- Again?
- Isn't it next?
Wait!
- Don't you fall!
- Okay. Yes sir!
[State Cross]