GoldSubtitles
The first ever Running Man
National College Ddakji Tournament!
[2014 Running Man National
College Ddakji Tournament]
[College students from all over the
nation will come together...]
[with each university's reputation on the line.]
[Everyone will fight for the winning title!]
Who will become the
ultimate Ddakji Master?
[Today we will find out who the
true winner is.]
[Youth!]
[Excitement!
Twist of fate!]
[The 2014 Running Man National
College Ddakji Tournament will now begin.]
[7:40, Seoul Mok-dong, SBS Building]
Good morning! I have to hurry and
make my way to Pusan right now.
- Suk Jin, I'll be back!
- Okay!
I'm going to leave first since
I have a long trip!
I'll be back!
And I, will go to Incheon University,
to meet with some of the country's finest.
Incheon! Sounds good!
First I need to figure out what departments
there are at Gangwon University...
[Each member is being assigned to universities
in different regions early in the morning.]
Let's go! Kyonggi University!
I've never been to Junbuk University.
Anyways, I am the current
Running Man Ddakji King.
[What do you mean Ddakji King?]
[30 minutes ago at the SBS rooftop]
What are you feeding us so
early in the morning?
- I want cold noodles!
- I haven't had breakfast yet!
[Seven different types of meals.]
[Let's eat first.]
[Yum]
Now that you've all chosen your meals,
we will tell you.
Today's race is the first annual
2014 National College Ddakji Tournament.
There is a label in front of each
of your meals.
Please take off your label.
[The region each meal is representative of
is today's destination.]
- Koryo University! I love Koryo!
- I'm going to Pusan!
Please leave for each of the schools
you've chosen
and select two team member to participate
in the tournament with you and bring them back.
Okay! Let's go! Let's go!
The ones that are like the wind.
Those types are good at this.
Guys that are like me.
Guys that move as quick as lightning.
They're the ones I need to find.
Slam! There's a specific way
to do it. Slam!
[Mr. Capable's strategy in flipping
over the Ultimate Ddakji in one try.]
I can teach them how to do it.
I have a painful memory at
Kyonggi University.
I tried to get into Kyonggi University
but didn't pass my entrance exams.
I applied to be part of the 43rd
freshmen class but...
Unfortunately,
unfortunately I did not get in.
[Just like that all the members
are split up across the country.]
In the case of Kwang Soo
he can leave about now.
Today's weather...
humidity, temperature, wind speed
are all perfect for playing ddakji.
[He's decided to use public transportation
since the university is within Seoul.]
- I only have a 10,000 won bill...
- It's okay because a lot of people are getting on.
Hello.
We have a total of seven people.
No, this is my money...
- How many total?
- Seven people total.
- I put 10,000 won in.
- You did? Is that enough?
1,050 won multiplied by 7...
7,350 won.
So then I need 2,650 won back.
[Cling cling cling cling]
[The unending stream of coins.]
You should have given me
change for some 1,000 won bills.
There are way too many coins.
- Are you by chance a Koryo University student?
- Yes.
- Really? Koryo?
Do you have a 500 won coin
by chance?
Wow, amazing!
Have you ever played ddakji by chance?
When I was younger I did...
- Where are you from?
- Pusan.
- You're from Pusan...
- I have a coin.
- Would you mind if I gave you change?
- No.
Thank you.
My pockets need to be light
so that I can--
This is my first time seeing a celebrity.
So this is what it's like living in Seoul.
Did you just recently move here?
It hasn't been that long since you came here?
It's only been two months.
- These cameras are filming, right?
- Yes.
Wow, amazing.
[Keeps saying everything is amazing.]
You only keep saying 'amazing'.
It may sound like I'm
just saying it...
What?
[10:35 am
Big-nosed brother's arrival in Jeonju]
We don't have time!
I need to quickly get my team
together and head back to Seoul.
I don't have time so I am
off to get my team together quickly.
I see Pusan University up there!
Pusan University.
Hello! Hello!
Where do most students hang out here?
Right here!
[Students are starting to gather
at the news of the arrival of Ji Hyo.]
Chuncheon!
I'm here! Gangwon University.
[Gangwon University, Chuncheon campus]
There it is.
[Chungbuk National University]
Wow, the weather is really nice.
[- What?
- Gasp!]
[Gary also arrives on campus.]
[Kyonggi University]
[Students spotted!]
[Surprise!]
- What major are you guys?
- We are sports science majors.
We could have been the same major!
I wanted to study sports science here
and I didn't get in!
- Sports science major?
- Sports science.
- Nice to meet you. Are you also?
- Yes.
Sports science?
Is everyone sports science?
We could have all gone
to the same school together.
Hold on. Before we take a
large group picture.
The reason I keep asking about sports science
is because no matter what
I want someone from sports science
on my team today.
I have to assemble a team and I have a painful
past with the sports science department here.
I was rejected from here.
I got as far as the entrance exams.
There will be a simple contest later.
- I'd like you guys to come and compete.
- Will do!
I have a feeling about you.
What else do you do?
- Dance...
- Dance? Show me your dance moves.
One, two! One, two, three, four!
[Wow!]
[Poppin']
This! This!
You gotta show these moves!
I have a feeling about you.
Good job!
- Make sure you come through. Noon.
- Okay.
- 12 o'clock. Field. Be there.
- Got it.
- Later at noon! Good luck!
- Okay!
Pretty impressive! Bye!
Anyone good at playing ddakji?
Ddakji! Anyone good at ddakji?
[Just then- discovered another
great candidate.]
Hello.
Hello. Oh, picture?
- Wow, smart! Where are you going?
- The office.
- Are you a teacher? A teacher here?
- I'm a professor here.
- Have you played ddakji?
- Yes.
- You know about ddakji?
- I know.
- We should play ddakji together.
- Let's play together.
Really?
- There will be a contest at 12pm.
- Here?
No... in the field!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay thank you.
- 12 o'clock.
- Okay.
- You have to come! I need your strength!
What the--
Can you speak Korean?
I can speak Korean.
I can speak English.
You're pretty refreshing.
Refreshing. Thank you.
- What's your name?
- My name is Joey.
- Joey?
- Yes.
- How old are you?
- I was born in 1988.
'88... Then I'm older than you.
- I'm 85.
- 85? Then you're like my older brother.
- Please show us what you can do.
- I hit it?
You have to hit it and flip it over.
- Just once?
- Yes.
[Taking his sunglasses off to do it right!]
[Judge]
[Slam]
- Did it flip over?
- This one did but not this one.
- Then you didn't do it.
- Oh really?
- But the sound was really loud.
- Yes, it was really loud.
- Do you have time today by chance?
- Yes, I do.
- Because we have a ddakji tournament today.
- Really?
I should be able to...
Then, if you can, later...
at two... can you meet us here?
- Sure sure.
- Thank you Joey.
- Thank you.
- I'll see you later.
[Koryo Team Member Joey (26/Japanese Lit.)
Skill: Outstanding Power. Talent: Korean.]
[Shouting]
[Bustling]
[Students are pouring in]
[The gym is packed with students...
for who?]
- I'll explain!
- Okay!
First, I'll be selecting two students
from Pusan University!
However, who has seen the episode of
Running Man where we make the boat?
[Is this an army base?]
But today, you get a scholarship
for playing Ddakji! Ddakji!
[As long as it's with you, we don't care!]
You'll be going to represent the
school, Pusan University!
[Me! Me!]
Pusan University can you win?
[Abundance of energy at Pusan University]
Ji Suk Jin! Ji Suk Jin! Ji Suk Jin!
[Without fail, forcing people to
cheer him on once again.]
Ji Suk Jin! Ji Suk Jin!
Not only are we bringing two participants with
us, we will also need a cheering squad.
So for those of you who have time today
we have a bus prepared for those who
want to cheer us on.
Anyone feel that they just
have to go?
Please tell us in 30 seconds why you have to
go and why you should be cheering on your team.
I'm a liberal arts student.
And I lead the cheering for the
liberal arts department.
Really?
[Surprisingly loud voice]
Go! Go! Go!
Ole! Ole! Ole!
Then we'll have a male captain
and a female captain.
Let's go!
- Do you have time today?
- Of course!
- We're leaving at one--
- Don't have to ask me twice!
- You might get back late. Is that okay?
- Of course!
- You might want to call home--
- It's okay!
Okay. Wow, you're very energetic.
- Anyone else?
- Me. Me. Me.
[Unique way of speaking]
- What is your major?
- Spain, Central and South American design major.
- Is the cheering team completely filled?
- We still have space.
Please pick me!
I ran all the way here to do it!
Why? Tell us in 30 seconds why
you have to do it.
The reason why I have to do it is because
originally I was supposed to take tutoring classes.
I was supposed to be in tutoring
but then today, my tutor had her baby.
So I was thinking, I'll just go home
and study after I eat
but then my friend called me and I ran
over here even before I finished my meal.
For this?
Because you wanted it so bad?
I ran over here because I have to
be on the cheering team.
- Sweat. Sweat.
- Sweat? Where?
- Can you dedicate yourself to Junbuk today?
- Of course! Of course!
Voice volume test.
Please shout 'Go Junbuk' three times!
Go Junbuk University!
You can do it! You can do it!
You're on the team!
You can take one friend with you!
- Who?
- Her!
Since you can take one friend!
- Thank you!
- Who do people say you remind them of?
Yoo Jae Suk!
Wow, you really do! Hold on.
You really do look like him!
[Oh my...]
You really look a lot like him.
I look like Yoo Jae Suk.
My dad is going to yell at me.
- Okay! You're on the team!
- Thank you!
[Meanwhile, Ha Ha is at Incheon University.]
[Inspecting the campus with a
crowd of students that look like him.]
What do you think about that person?
Wow... wow...
[Walking ddakji alert!]
Let's go after him!
Wow!
Where are you going?
[Walking ddakji is running away?]
Excuse me!
[Get him]
Excuse me! Excuse me!
[We're not bad people!]
We have to get him.
[An anonymous man possessing
both strength and skills.]
That was a ghost...
How could such a person exist...
- Do you know him?
- No, it's my first time seeing him.
- He's in my department!
- What's his name?
Get his number!
Just the back! Get his back!
Excuse me. Wow!
- We saw you from behind and were surprised.
- I ran because I was surprised.
We really liked you when we
saw you and you look really fit.
We don't need anyone else.
I just need you on our team.
Then I will play for the school.
[Ha Ha successfully recruits one
team member from Incheon University.]
This is nice! Great!
Please give him a round of applause.
He will represent you all!
[Incheon Team Member, Lee Hyung Joo (25)
Skill: Envious calves. Talent: Running away]
[While the nation's best ddakji players
were being gathered...]
[Jae Suk is the only one
yet to meet anyone.]
Forget it.
[It's not easy finding someone.]
Let's try that again. No more fooling
around. Not many play while kneeling.
That's right.
[The long road to becoming a ddakji king.]
[Try... and try...]
[No matter how hard they try...]
It's not easy finding someone who
can play ddakji well.
[Right then]
Ddakji... by chance...
have you ever played?
- Where did you come from?
- Someone told me you were here.
Really? Then can you play
for me once?
Can you play when you're
so out of breath?
But... the way you hold it... like this.
[Vectorman style]
Are you an athlete?
- Yes.
- What types of sports?
I like jump rope and Taekwondo.
You did a bit of Taekwondo, didn't you?
- I did a bit.
- Can you kick for us?
- A kick?
- Yes.
You said you did Tawkwondo for a bit.
- Is there anything else you can show us?
- Yoga and stuff like that.
Yoga? Can you show us a
yoga position?
[Shaky]
I should do it like this.
[Surprised]
I'll try one more time.
I feel very confident about ddakji.
Try hitting it with this.
One more time. One more time.
One more time!
You can stop now.
I think you have a lot of anger
built up internally.
[It is hard... finding a ddakji master...]
[Kkuk goes to the sports science
department to find his ddakji players.]
Hello.
[Surprise]
How can we help you?
Truth is, today, Running Man is holding a
National College Ddakji Tournament.
So I was hoping to find team
members from this class.
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
Please come to the front
one at a time.
[First contestant]
You have a very clean cut hairstyle.
You must have known I was coming.
- Have you played before?
- Yes, I played a lot when I was younger.
[It must have been a while
since you played...]
- One more time? Would you like to try again?
- Yes. One more time.
Let's try one more time!
Return to your seat.
Anyone else? Next?
[Right then, appears a strong presence.]
He has immense arm strength and
can most likely beat you.
Really?
It's definitely possible.
Why don't we take a look?
You're tall and fit...
He's short...
[Sorry, did you hear me?]
- How tall are you?
- 185cm.
Wow you're very tall.
[Mr. Capable vs. Gangwon's Ace]
[They made contact]
[Very similar power]
Then let's see how you are at ddakji.
Hold on.
What's going on with your position?
- What are you doing?
- I just have to flip it over.
My position isn't that great
when I play either.
[Fly]
You realize though
that regardless it didn't flip over?
[But by volume he is the current winner.]
[Slam]
His strength is excessive.
You're so strong that it did a
complete 360 in the air. Try again.
[Again!]
[Kangwon University player, Choi Tae Jin (25)
Skill: Strength. Talent: Strength.]
[Meanwhile, Suk Jin has a large
cheering squad.]
[Yoo Hyuk's younger sister
was surprised by the loud noise.]
Strong but...
[Officially kicking off the search
for ddakji players.]
[In comes a handsome, athletic young man.]
Doesn't he kind of look like Gary?
[We name thee, the Kang Gary of Jeonju]
[Big Nose's demonstration]
[Jeonju Gary flips it right back over.]
[Endurance test]
[Wimper...]
You are strong.
Do you really want to go today?
I'd love to go. Please take me.
Can you win the ddakji tournament
for the school?
[Junbuk Team, Choi Min Gyu (25/Athletic Major)
Skill: Gary of Jeonju. Talent: Strength Showoff.]
Volleyball team?
Where is the volleyball team here?
- It's back there.
- Is that so?
[Volleyball training facility]
[Athletes are intensely training]
[Gary unknowingly is intimidated]
Coach... Coach...
Yes?
- We have a ddakji tournament today.
- Okay.
And I thought volleyball players
might be good...
Ddakji is all about the strength
when you bring your arm down.
And I heard the team here is good...
[2013 Chungye League Champions]
- Will you let me take one of your players?
- Yes, go ahead.
Thank you. The players are so
serious I'm not sure how to ask them.
Wow! Look at them jump!
[Spike demonstration]
[Strong spike]
This is it!
Ddakji all ends here!
I'll try to get the spike.
You're ruthless.
I'm seriously scared!
It's really scary!
I almost drooled this much just now!
Just as I thought,
the volleyball team is outstanding.
I'd really like to take a player from
the volleyball team with me.
You're good-looking.
No, I'm not.
- Your name?
- Sung Soo.
- Park Sung Soo?
- Yes.
Then today Sung Soo,
you will be our ddakji champion.
[Kyonggi, Park Sung Soo (20/Sports Science)
Skill: Good-looking. Talent: Lightning-speed.]
[One more player left to choose
in Incheon.]
[And the line of ddakji challengers]
Wow this...
This is unreal!
It's unfair! Hold on! That! That...
[Bring it on!]
[King of all ddakjis]
Excuse me.
Let's be fair and play with the
ddakji that I brought.
Please put those down in front of you.
That's really inconsiderate.
And now, we will test your skills
one person at a time.
Accuracy and focus.
[An encouraging hug for each
person that fails.]
One! Two! Three!
[Darn...]
This isn't easy!
Friend, please raise both arms
in the air!
You're really nervous!
[Sweat does not lie]
Please give him a round of applause!
Get a wave going.
[Encouraged by the wave--]
[Huh?]
One more time! One more time!
I'll do it right! I'll do it right!
Cheer three times! Go!
[Your youthful energy and confidence makes
you that much more of a beautiful person.]
[This time?]
[He flipped it!]
[Incheon, Park Hyun Jin (24/Int'l Trade major)
Skill: Persistence. Talent: Armpit sweat cheer.]
Please stand over here for now.
Now! What is your nickname?
- Mister Bean?
- Mister Bean!
There are so many characters
in Incheon!
There have already been so many! I
predict you will be our final player Mister Bean!
Here we go.
- I have to get it on the first try?
- On the first try. You only get one chance.
[Fail]
The one who can turn back time!
[But no matter how many times he turns
back time, he cannot turn over the ddakji.]
Good job! Good job!
You can do it! Go to the cheer team!
Cheer for us!
There's sweat in my eyes.
I really just got sweat in my eyes.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo.
Use the pointed corner to--
I know! Stay quiet!
Start!
[Final competition to selecting the team]
[Koryo, Ji Chang Dae (20/Pre-med)
Skill: Gentle looks Talent: Maneuver ddakjis]
[Kyonggi is having a running competition.]
[Gary gets last place.]
[He's a Running Man...]
You will all dance without music now.
Ready, start!
[The guy from earlier.]
[Witty]
[Stamina]
Thank you everyone for
playing so hard.
[Kyonggi, Lee Dong Jun (21/Business major)
Skill: Almost Gary's junior. Talent: Dancing.]
Please go for it now.
[Success]
[Kangwon, Han Joo Hyun (24/Veterinary major)
Skill: Goofing off. Talent: Goofing off.]
Busan = baseball.
And baseball = Busan.
[Pusan, Sun Sung Hoon (21/Child Psychology)
Skill: Perceptiveness. Talent: Optimism.]
[Opposite direction this time!]
[Pusan, Lim Suk Hyun (24/Aviation)
Skill: Quick-thinking. Talent: Optimism.]
We will return to Pusan University
as winners! Fighting!
[All teams have now been finalized!]
[With the exception of one]
I only need to find one more person.
- Oh no! I'm sorry!
- It's okay!
You don't know anyone that's
good at ddakji, do you?
I don't know anyone here.
Wait! Right here!
[Right then!
A strong force is felt from behind...]
[Will he be Jae Suk's ddakji savior?]
Are you really good? Seriously?
[Finally]
[He's arrived]
[My ddakji fairy]
Hey! Kwan Jin!
[After a long search, the two
finally come together and meet.]
- Why are you so good?
- That's what I'm saying!
- Did you do this for the first time today?
- No, I've played since I was young.
- Where did you grow up?
- Just in the country. I grew up in the country.
Can you show us how you
did that one more time?
You're really strong!
I feel like I can breathe again!
One more time please!
[Perfection]
[An unusually long day...
Didn't think I'd find you...]
[My ddakji fairy]
[Where have you been all my life?]
[Refreshing ddakji energy drink.]
You are really good!
I feel so much better!
- What's your name?
- Shin Hong Kyu.
- Hong Kyu?
- Yes.
Hong Kyu!
Want to go play ddakji?
Hey! Hong Kyu!
- Let's go!
Professors and countless peers
Hong Kyu and I will go abroad for a
ddakji adventure. We will be back!
If it's with Hong Kyu,
we will definitely win the scholarship
and make sure that the scholarship
funds are available immediately.
[2014 National College Ddakji Tournament
Depart for Jamshil immediately!]
Go get your stuff!
Everyone we will return winners today!
- Fighting!
Let's go! We got this!
On behalf of Incheon University
the Armpit Sweat Fighter and
loud-mouth brothers will return winners!
Junbuk University! Fighting!
We will win!
[To bring honor to the school]
Kangwon University!
Fighting!
A cheer team will also be coming
with us today!
So for anyone who has time today,
we have a bus prepared to take you.
For those who can and would like to cheer on
their team, the bus will take you there and back.
Okay?
Beat them! Crush them!
Overcome them!
Kim Jong Kook!
Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
[The overwhelming energy
of the cheer teams.]
We are headed towards a ddakji victory!
- We will win.
- Let's change the world with ddakji!
- Okay guys? We will change the world.
- Yes, we will win the ddakji tournament.
[Change the world with ddakji! Go!]
[2:15 PM, Pusan Team arrives in Seoul]
[All teams to report to
the Jamshil Student Gym by 3PM]
Ji Wook, Hong Kyu we are here.
Here's the gym.
We're here!
Okay!
Ji Wook, Hong Kyu!
It's the moment of truth. Let's go!
[The undeniable nervousness now
that the time has come.]
Don't be nervous!
[And now begins the war between the
teams with their school's reputation at stake!]
[All the teams have gathered in one place.]
[Nervousness is heightened upon
meeting opposing teams.]
This is going to be really competitive.
Why is everyone so fit?
You guys are being unfair!
Thank you everyone for gathering
here from different parts of the country!
- Incheon! Incheon!
- Pusan! Pusan!
[Must not lose this fight!]
There is something we must decide
before officially beginning the tournament.
- What is it?
- How many teams total do we have?
- Seven teams!
- Yes, we have seven teams.
So we must pick a team to
automatically move on to the next round.
So we've prepared a game for us to see
how well you can work together as a team.
- That looks like rope.
- What is that?
- Is it tug of war?
- One! Two! Three!
[Special tug of war?]
The game we've prepared is
a tug of war made for 21 people!
There are seven sides with room
for 21 people total!
There is a place for each person
on the team at the end of each side.
Please wrap each band around your waist
and look to see that three of your
colored flags are in the ground ahead of you.
One team will win when each
team member has a flag in their hand.
Second place and on
have no meaning.
Only first place!
What do we do about Ji Hyo's team?
[Strategizing before the game as
each team prepares.]
We have to do well here.
This won't be easy.
Ji Wook! Hong Kyu!
One, two, three... Fighting!
We have to lower ourselves and
crawl on the ground.
We need to stay as close
together as possible when we pull.
You're so scientific!
Each person needs to pull their own
flag. You can't get it for anyone else.
Strap this on tightly. Very tight.
[The tiger's team is all about strength,
naturally.]
We are directly across from
Kim Jong Kook's team...
It'd be a bit easier if we
were on the side.
But since we are directly across...
To be fair, we will all sit down!
Please have a seat!
Each person gets one flag.
Please sit down!
There will only be one winner in this game!
One winner!
Ready!
[Everyone is as tense as the ropes
they are strapped to.]
The tiger charges forward with his cubs.]
[Only onward]
Just a little bit more!
[Everyone is holding on for dear life.]
[The Pusan seagulls are falling apart.]
[Flags are so close, yet so far...]
[Jong Kook's Gangwon team is the
closest to their flags.]
[One flag picked!]
[Chungbuk University is also very close.]
[One flag picked]
[Barely moving]
We got this! We got this!
One, two, three!
[Shaky]
Try pulling from the other direction!
One, two, three!
[Just a little bit more...]
[One more flag left]
Ji Wook! One more!
Just a little bit more Ji Wook!
[Currently in second,
Gangwon team has two more flags]
[Growl]
[Wild beast]
[Gangwon also has one more flag left!]
Let's all come together! Ji Hyo!
Go that way! Go that way!
First let's all pull in the same direction!
[Incheon, Junbuk and Pusan
have all allied.]
[Expressing their love for each other?]
[Discouraging the tiger team]
[Battery out]
Kwang Soo! What are you doing?
Get up!
[Must stop the first place team!]
[Chungbuk and Gangwon currently
each have one flag left.]
[Gangwon University exerting all the
power they can.]
They are not human!
Gary! Pull this way!
[The winners of this game...]
[can pass a round...]
[Who will win?]
[Desperation]
[Unpredictable]
[Pusan U, Koryo U, Incheon U, Kyonggi U,
and JunBuk U each have zero flags.]
[Chungbuk U, and Gangwon U
each have two flags]
[Oh... Oh... he's reaching out...]
[No!]
[Gangwon University win!]
[Disappointed]
It's okay! Good work!
[A victory possible because they
all worked together.]
So with that, Kim Jong Kook's team will
automatically move on to the next round.
[Victory dance]
[Angry Ji Hyo explosion]
Ji Hyo looks the strongest out of
the three of them.
These guys keep falling over!
And now the most important part!
Each team will leave to make their ddakjis.
[Off they go to make their ddakjis
for the competition.]
[Tournament location
Seoul, Jamshil Student Stadium]
[Meanwhile, youthful energy is
gathering from all corners of the country]
[Gangwon University]
- Kim Jong Kook, fighting!
- I love you Kim Jong Kook!
[Total of 300 students arrive to
cheer for their teams.]
Let's go Chungbuk University!
[Receive their cheering supplies]
[And everyone gathers together to eat.]
[Fills themselves up with food]
[They are now fueled with energy
to cheer on their team.]
[The place where there will
be a victory.]
[The very place where the energy
of the youths will all come together.]
[Five minutes before the tournament]
You have to move quickly so that
the ddakji flips over quickly.
And you just have to work on accuracy.
That's it. Then we're good.
You got it back! You got it!
Okay? And confidence is important.
Imagine they are standing there
and look at them.
[Laser]
[Final workout]
[Nervous]
One, two, three! Fighting!
- Please stop now.
- No way!
- You can't do this before the tournament.
- Let go!
[It's okay...
this guy is always like this]
1,000,021! 1,000,022!
[The students cheering for their schools
have filled up the entire stadium.]
The first annual 2014 National College
Ddakji Tournament will now begin!
Enter the teams!
Gangwon University and Kim Jong Kook!
[Choi Tae Jin, Kim Jong Kook, Han Joo Hyun]
Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
[Kyonggi University and Gary]
[Lee Dong Jun, Kang Gary, Park Sung Soo]
[The perfect combination of
athlete and B-boy.]
[Koryo University and Lee Kwang Soo]
[Ji Chang Dae, Lee Kwang Soo, Joey]
[Multicultural team]
[Bo Yoon and Young Taek who also
participated previously came to cheer.]
[Pusan University and Song Ji Hyo]
[Lim Suk Hyun, Song Ji Hyo, Seo Sung Hoon]
[Prepare yourselves everyone!
Ji Hyo is here with the manliest of all men!]
[Incheon University and Ha Ha]
[Park Hyung Jin, Ha Ha, Lee Hyung Joo]
[The strong team made of wit and strength.]
[Junbuk University and Ji Suk Jin]
[Bae Jae Hyun, Ji Suk Jin, Choi Min Kyu]
[The two terminators with respect
for their elders.]
[The crowd goes wild]
[Chungbuk University and Yoo Jae Suk]
[Jung Ji Wook, Yoo Jae Suk, Shin Hong Kyu]
[Two legendary ddakji champions]
[The energy is rising in the stadium]
All seven teams have now
entered the arena!
A special guest appearance today
by A-Pink!
[Energy is rising even higher with
the appearance of the six ladies.]
Hello, we are A-Pink.
[No No No by A-Pink]
[A-Pink's cute and refreshing performance.]
[Mr. Chu by A-Pink]
[Everyone Chu together]
[Is this real life?]
[In an instant the performance turned
into an army base visit.]
[Blank...]
[A-Pink's performance...
As warm as the spring sunlight.]
[High energy]
We did not realize this tournament
would escalate to this level.
Is this tournament really so important for all of
you to be here, much less for A-Pink to be here?
I wonder if all of this is truly worth it.
But you will all end up holding your
breath as you watch on.
Despite their busy schedules, everyone in
A-Pink came to cheer everyone on today.
So we can't just let you leave.
We'd like you to help draw the battles.
This is like the World Cup of
ddakji tournaments.
Gangwon, who automatically is entered in the
semi-finals, can be found in the top right corner.
So the first team will be chosen...
The first team to play in the
quarter finals is...
Chungbuk University!
And the next team that Eun Ji chooses
will play against the first team, Chungbuk U.
[Anxious]
Oh no!
I'm sorry, Pusan University!
[The first battle
Chungbuk U vs. Pusan U.]
Cho Rong and I both chose
our hometowns.
Really?
[Eun Ji from Pusan and
Cho Rong from Chungju]
Next is Na Eun.
Kyonggi University!
Incheon University!
Incheon University and Kyonggi University
will play against each other.
Koryo University!
Junbuk University!
The drawing is now complete!
A big round of applause for A-Pink!
And we will now begin our first match.
Chungbuk University and Pusan University!
Please welcome them with a
big round of applause!
The first team to three will move
on to the next round!
The first battle! Chungbuk University
versus Pusan University!
Players enter the ring!
[Heated cheering competition between
the two schools.]
To ensure that the ddakjis do not go against
regulation and they abide by the standard sizes
only ddakjis with the R sticker
may enter the ring.
We have someone else over there as well.
[A second judge is inspecting
Chungbuk University's ddakjis.]
When did you get here?
Hello.
Nice to meet you. You must have
been called to work here at the last minute.
I was told this was a national event...
Is that what they told you?
Judges have inspected the ddakjis
for each team.
And when each ddakji passes the test,
an R sticker will be placed on each ddakji.
We will draw numbers to determine
the order in which we will play.
We will now begin the quarter-finals!
[With the encouragement of their
cheer teams behind them...]
[Each player goes up against each
other for victory.]
We will play rock paper scissor to determine
who will place their ddakji on the ground.
Rock paper scissor!
[Pusan University wins.]
Do just as we practiced.
Focus.
Remember what we practiced.
Good luck, Suk Hyun!
Let's go Pusan University!
[Regardless of the opponent,
we cannot lose.]
[Suk Hyun fail]
[Victory comes so quickly,
you cannot let your guard down.]
[Ddakji King Jae Suk's turn.]
[Even the Ddakji King must be nervous.]
[Each team's cheering is getting louder.]
[Suk Hyun's second turn.]
[What?!]
[Suk Hyun wins!]
[Unexpected results]
Flipped over the left hand! Flipped
over the right hand! We have Ji Hyo!
[Ji Hyo wins]
Song Ji Hyo! Song Ji Hyo!
[One cannot look past her
just because she's a woman.]
[Lift]
[Jo Hyo did not succeed,
but she was very close.]
[Ji Wook's turn]
[Ji Wook wins!]
[The team quickly caught up for
the score to be 1:1]
[The ddakji master is third.]
Be careful! Careful.
[Hong Kyu win!]
[Chungbuk loses twice in a row.]
[And now the first players go
up against each other once more.]
[I've already lost one too many times!]
[The ddakji just bounced off.]
You have too much power in there!
Release some tension in our arms.
[Blank Ji taking care of his arm.]
[It flipped over again!]
[Unbelievable!]
Blank Ji's back to back victory.
The score is now tied at 2:2.
[The unexpected rise of the weakest team,
Pusan University.]
I will have a stand-in for this round!
The gentleman with the glasses up there!
[Stand-in selected from the crowd]
Have you ever played ddakji before?
- I've played often.
- You'll do well today?
- You can do it?
- I can do it!
[Tension rises with the entrance
of a new player.]
[Stand-in looks like he can
play ddakji well.]
Please tell us your name and major.
I am an urban engineering
major and my name is Choi Sol.
He is my stand-in!
Please do well on my behalf.
- Good luck!
- Please give him a round of applause!
Rock paper scissor!
[Stand-in wins!]
[Ji Wook vs. Choi Sol]
[There is nowhere else to go.]
[Each player holds the fate of their school.]
[Now Ji Wook's turn to attack.]
[He couldn't have gotten it again
on the first try...?]
[Ji Wook wins!]
[He wins once again at lightning speed!]
[Ji Wook's outstanding performance.]
[Entry into the semi-finals]
[Pusan's beautiful spirit]
A round of applause for Incheon University!
And Kyonggi University!
[Witty cheers pouring in from all teams.]
Rock paper scissor!
[Gary's advantage!]
Gary will now begin.
The first attempt is very important.
A very tense moment.
[Gary fail]
[He's hit many ddakjis but never
on such a large scale.]
[Extremely nervous]
[Ha Ha fail]
This is about the time
sweat starts to collect in the hands.
[Gary's swing]
- Shouldn't it be flipping over about now?
- Honestly, it should be flipping over about now.
Between the ground and the ddakji--
[Darn]
Ha Ha may not have come down
as hard as Gary
but he definitely hit it exactly
where he needed to.
More than strength, this is about
hitting the center of the ddakji directly.
And with that, Ha Ha wins!
Ha Ha's team now leads
with one point.
[No way...]
Gary was more powerful
but Ha Ha was more accurate.
Which means we have a chance
against Kim Jong Kook.
Everyone! Please say
Kim Jong Kook is easy as pie!
- Kim Jong Kook is--
- Easy as pie!
Ji Suk Jin, you're being a bit
biased right now.
Please be a little more discreet
with who it is you're cheering for.
We have Hyun Jin from Incheon U.
Playing him is our
volleyball player Sung Soo.
There are powerful players.
[Accuracy vs. Power]
[Unbelievable power]
Had he just hit the center of the ddakji,
it would have definitely flipped over.
[Darn... Complete turnover]
[Hyun Jin hit it right in the middle]
The ddakji will not move at all
if you do not hit it in the middle.
[Is it accuracy or power?]
He did it!
[Sung Soo wins!]
It was not strong but because it hit
the middle, it flipped over.
[Score is tied once again at 1:1]
The ddakji's condition and energy
in the stadium are all different
so it's hard to predict what
will happen next.
The score is now 1 to 1.
Back to square one.
[Dong Jun succeeds on the first try!]
He hit that right in the middle.
That's right!
He hit it dead in the center!
Kyonggi University is now leading 2 to 1.
Initially, Incheon was confident
they'd defeat Kyonggi U.
But there has been an unexpected
turn of events!
- Ha Ha's Incheon was a strong candidate to win!
- That's right!
They play very well.
[Gary's ddakji just grazed the center]
He just barely missed the center.
[Ha Ha fail]
I did not realize that ddakji
could be so much fun.
That was so close!
It was so close!
The ddakji's condition also plays
a large role in this game.
They've won the match!
Kyonggi University collects an unexpected
win and will move on to the semi-finals!
That's right.
Incheon University, who was expected to win,
drops out of the race in the quarter-finals.
We truly thought Incheon University
would win!
Next! We have
Koryo University and Junbuk University!
This is a battle between
Koryo University and Junbuk University.
[Both teams are prepared for their match.]
The first player for each team,
please step towards the center.
I really wanted to die when I lost
twice in a row earlier.
- You wanted to die?
- I sure did!
The ddakjis are considerably
thin for both teams.
Because of that,
it's difficult to flip over the ddakji
but also difficult for the ddakji
itself to flip over.
Because it's stuck to the ground,
hitting the center is that much more important.
[Min Kyu win!]
[Contrasting reactions]
Junbuk University stand up!
He is the ace on the team.
The ace of Junbuk University.
Lee Kwang Soo is now up.
Lee Kwang Soo will go first for this team.
Junbuk University is another team
expected to win.
[Flipped over... almost!]
[Thank goodness]
As you can see,
this person has played before.
And that pose can be most effective
for this type of match.
While the cheering can be encouraging, it can
also put a lot of pressure on you when playing.
[What?]
He looked at the ddakji and
then hit next to it.
Kwang Soo is going barefoot.
He is taking his socks off.
Giraffe will now play barefoot.
With each passing round, he is
slowly taking off another layer of clothing.
His posture was good.
As we said before,
the ddakji is noticeably flat...
[This time he slams down on it
while standing]
[Jae Hyun wins!]
[Junbuk leads 2:0]
He hit that one right in the middle.
It is now Ji Suk Jin against Joey,
our foreign friend.
[Joey is their last hope]
[Will Suk Jin be able to close out the match?]
[Desperate]
Joey! He flipped it over on the first try!
Koryo just turned the tide of the game.
Koryo University has suddenly
come to life!
Back to the beginning.
This is the team's ace.
If he loses here...
[Min Kyu wins!]
[Even before he got to show off his skills.]
[A warm round of applause to
Koryo University for all their hard work.]
[Junbuk officially in the semi-finals]
[Quarter-finals complete]
Junbuk University defeats Koryo University
and enters the semi-finals.
We are now in the semi-finals!
Chungbuk University versus Kyonggi University.
There are not very many options.
Yoo Jae Suk was formerly
the ddakji king.
This is Yoo Jae Suk's chance to shine!
[His chance to use his muscles.]
His power can be felt in that last strike.
Next we have the volleyball player.
He's stepped back.
He has another chance!
[The intense match]
He flipped it over!
[Return of the ddakji king]
Yoo Jae Suk's smile has now
returned to his face.
He is now smiling once again.
Gary is another strong player.
[Gary flips it over in one try]
- That brings the score 1:1 now!
- Unbelievable!
[Tied once again in a matter of moments.]
[Each swing makes the heart race
a little bit quicker.]
- This is another strong player.
- He is a strong player.
That's right! That's it!
Kyungbuk takes the lead once again!
There's nowhere for us to go anyway.
Relax.
[Oh...?!]
It spun around twice!
- It's not easy to make it spin twice.
- It is definitely no easy feat.
And it is Yoo Jae Suk's turn once again.
Typically when you hear that type of noise,
it is the sound of the ddakji flipping over.
Will the team be able to defend this...
[No way!]
[Back to square one]
Everyone is left speechless.
Everyone, applause!
[Shin Hong Kyu versus Gary]
Kang Gary versus Shing Hong Kyu.
[To crush him or let him off easy?]
Everyone is wondering who will win.
[Hong Kyu has not been
able to hit the ddakji.]
[Hong Kyu wins.]
[Advancement into finals.]
This is so moving.
This is really entertaining.
He hit the ddakji. He wins.
This ddakji competition has
the fervor of the World Cup.
This is amazing.
Finally, Gangwon University...
[Gangwon University is up for the first time.]
[First Running Man Nationwide
University Ddakji Competition]
Junbuk University
versus Gangwon University!
You may already be aware, but this
is the candidate most likely to win.
- He is a champion.
- That's right.
He's the strongest candidate to win.
You saw earlier, but Junbuk University
has two especially strong students.
Junbuk University has begun.
But you don't necessarily
win because of strength.
Physically they are stronger
and have quite a few advantages.
[Bae Jae Hyun versus Han Joo Hyun]
It's powerful...
but you also have to be accurate.
You have to be accurate.
[Player Joo Hyun attacks.]
[Goofing around.]
[Succeeds in first try.]
That was amazing.
[This is the power of the strongest player.]
- One try!
- He gets it in one try!
Okay, now...
Gangwon University gets through
the preliminary round.
They get it in one try.
[Choi Min Kyu versus Choi Tae Jin]
Now it's Junbuk University’s turn.
Better to be accurate than too ambitious.
There you go. Be comfortable,
be comfortable.
Do it your way. Do it comfortably.
Be comfortable.
It's going over, it's going over.
He's very lucky.
He's very lucky. Overflowing with
strength. He must be nervous.
As we get deeper into the competition,
the passion in the arena gets stronger.
[Min Kyu's second attack.]
[Fail.]
Should have been more accurate.
It'll flip. Do it your way.
Be comfortable.
Here we go.
[Easily succeeds.]
Is this how it ends?
[Two flips in a row.]
This is really unbelievable.
Even the other university students
can't seem to believe it.
The fate of the team is in
Suk Jin's hands.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Ah, he lost his chance.
[But Kim Jong Kook wins.]
Such a shame.
Ah, he lost.
Running Man's Kim Jong Kook.
It'll be a victory for the self.
The record is pretty flawless so far.
Suddenly, the audience...
Yoon Eun Hye!
They are chanting Yoon Eun Hye's name.
Why is everyone doing this?
This is a very effective tactic.
It was effective.
It's Ji Suk Jin's chance.
Suk Jin has to do this.
Here's his chance.
Ji Suk Jin's chance.
[No one's expecting much.]
[But today I'm going all the way.]
That was a bit weak.
[Chanting Yoon Eun Hye again.]
The Yoon Eun Hye chant
seems to have an effect.
[If I can't do it this time,
it's over for me.]
What's going on?
[The tiger has lost to Impala.]
[Suk Jin's miracle.]
He's done it!
This is something none of us expected.
This is amusing.
[First players are up again.]
This is really unbelievable.
Junbuk University's player...
there he goes.
Here he goes.
Hey. Be accurate, be accurate.
What is this?
What is going on?
[The never-ending miracle.]
What is this?
Didn't I tell you? The competition
isn't over until it's over.
It's not over until it's over.
This is amazing.
Okay next round. Junbuk University
is getting ready. The cheers are amazing.
Who knew ddakji could be this fun?
This is why we can't stop playing.
This is why we can't stop playing ddakji.
[Min Kyu wins.]
The two come to the center.
Who will win?
One team will advance.
The team got through thanks to Suk Jin.
A lot of strength went into that.
He's shaking.
I didn't know it'd be this nerve-wracking.
The Junbuk player was
probably very nervous.
At ease.
The ddakji has divided into four parts.
It's broken into four parts.
That's how hard they're working.
Yes, the ddakji has exploded.
The second round.
[Min Kyu's second attack.]
[It flipped!]
[A come-from-behind victory!]
They came from behind to win!
Junbuk University!
[Junbuk University
advances to next round.]
Ji Suk Jin. In four years,
he finally won something!
I don't know how to say this,
but the eternal victor failed.
It's like Brazil getting eliminated.
The players gave it their all.
Because of Yoon Eun Hye,
Kim Jong Kook fell apart.
Kim Jong Kook was the turning point.
It was all thanks
to the audience cheering.
[The finals.]
[Junbuk University versus
Chungbuk University.]
[Jung Ji Wook: speed of lightning.]
[Shin Hong Kyu: ddakji genius.]
It was an amazing victory.
[Yoo Jae Suk: legendary ddakji master.]
Kang Gary.
[Choi Min Kyu: special ace.]
[Ji Suk Jin: miracle maker.]
[Bae Jae Hyun: the terminator.]
[Only one team will win.]
[Will it be Chungbuk University?]
It's good we got this far.
[Or miracle Junbuk University?]
If we can't win this, it's over.
[Choi Min Kyu versus Jung Ji Wook.]
[Min Kyu wins!]
[Palpable nerves.]
Kang Gary fighting!
[He goes for it.]
You have to be accurate.
[Ji Wook's turn.]
[Fail.]
[Increasingly passionate cheers.]
Will strength win over speed?
[Success! Choi Min Kyu can do it.]
[Power trumps speed.]
[Ji Suk versus Shin Hong Kyu.]
[Ji Suk wins.]
[Will Ji Suk's miracle streak continue?]
Will Suk Jin flip it?
[Miracle Suk Jin's success!]
How is this possible? How?
Miracle.
[Chungbuk University puts
all their faith in Jae Suk.]
[Will the king of ddakji be able
to rescue Chungbuk University?]
[The ddakji doesn't even move.]
[Terminator Jae Hyun's attack.]
He has a very unique way
of attacking by kneeling.
Yoo Jae Suk tries again.
A lot of effort went into that.
Next player up.
Will the ddakji move for this player?
Here we go.
Will it be a clean sweep 3:0?
[This turn might determine everything.]
[Jae Hyun fail.]
[Jae Suk's turn again.]
[Jae Suk success!]
The god of ddakji.
- My failure...
- Your turn is over. Forget it.
- Come from behind!
[Ji Wook's attack.]
It was a good effort.
The ddakji doesn't move as much for them.
Will he be able to close this?
Min Kyu is the ace.
[Ji Wook has a chance to win.]
[Ji Wook fails.]
[Ddakji turns twice before falling.]
Needs to be more accurate.
[A bit lacking in strength.]
[Again, ddakji turns twice before falling.]
This is drying up our blood.
It certainly is.
I feel bad for them.
Suk Jin brings on the next round.
Let's see how this goes.
How will it turn out?
Will he do it?
Min Kyu can end it all right here.
This is his chance.
Here he goes.
[It flipped!]
[Junbuk University Winners!]
[Ji Suk started the miracle.]
[Junbuk University finished the miracle.]
[The First Running Man Nationwide
University Ddakji Competition.]
Junbuk University wins!
The team Ji Suk Jin led!
- Today is Ji Suk Jin's day!
- It certainly is.
It's all for Ji Suk Jin.
Everyone, please give him
a round of applause.
This is really an extraordinary feat.
We'd like to thank everyone
for spending this time with us.
The Running Man scholarship goes
to Junbuk University.
I had a feeling we might win,
but I didn't think we really would.
I am so moved that I could
help them in getting this scholarship.
Also, our Min Kyu and Jae Hyun
and everyone who came.
I sincerely thank you.
I love you. Thank you!
Fighting!
This goes down in Running Man history.
It's been four years since Suk Jin
has led a team to victory. A historical feat.
Let's give Suk Jin a round of applause.
You never know when the next
ddakji competition will come up.
To all our students and all our viewers
hold on. We'll come to you again soon.
The first Running Man ddakji
competition ends here. Thank you!
You all worked hard.
You did well.
Subtitles by DramaFever