[Han River...]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[South]
[North]
[With the river in between...
lye two different fates.]
[Just what awaits them?]
[Seokang University- 7am]
Hello, it's a beautiful morning.
Hello.
Here is your first mission.
[Everyone starts
their first mission on their own.]
Oh. Hallyu star race.
A race with the top Hallyu stars.
Choose between the two Hallyu stars, and
go to the location where one of them waits.
Choose between the two Hallyu stars...
[Choose the Hallyu star whom
they are a fan of!]
Wow, so we're going to meet
a Hallyu star?
But we're Hallyu stars too, aren't we?
[Hallyu rabbit-
Southern end of the Seokang Bridge.]
[Hallyu Giraffe-
Northern end of the Seokang Bridge.
[Two Hallyu starts waiting for their own fans
with the river in between.]
Hallyu giraffe?
Kwang Soo's not a Hallyu star.
Hallyu giraffe.
Giraffe?
That giraffe of ours?
This has to be a total dud.
This one is a total dud, isn't it?
Rabbit.
Who could this rabbit be?
Who wore the rabbit mask?
I know that there was a rabbit.
Impala, tiger, grasshopper...
Gary was the monkey.
- Hey, Gary.
- Where are you going to go, Suk Jin?
I'm going to go to the rabbit.
I have this feeling that the rabbit
is going to be really cute.
- Ji Hyo?
- No, I said, I think the rabbit will be cute.
Ah, you think the rabbit will be cute?
I've made my decision.
Giraffe!
Rabbit!
- Which one?
- Giraffe!
Rabbit!
I'm positive that everyone's
going to go to the southern end.
The rabbit is going to be a girl, isn't it?
I know who the giraffe is going to be,
but I'm not sure about the rabbit.
I'm too uncertain to trust the rabbit.
I'm nervous that it'll be Song Ji Hyo.
Let's just get going.
But where are we right now?
I slept the whole way here,
so I'm not sure where we are right now.
Are you studying right now?
You're not one of our staff members, are you?
I thought you were one of
our staff members.
I'm sorry for disturbing your studies.
This is how we usually start off.
I'm positive I know who
the giraffe is going to be.
And since I personally really like rabbits,
I'm going to go see the rabbit.
[Blank Ji is a fan of Hallyu rabbits.]
Forget it.
Let's just go.
I think I should go see the giraffe.
Because the rabbit...
It's possible that the rabbit could be a ruse,
and I might be on the losing end by going.
Oh, you girls startled me.
- What are you ladies doing?
- Are you for real?
Can I shake your hand?
Are you exercising or something?
- Are you out exercising?
- Yes.
- Then why aren't you exercising?
- Can we get a picture?
Wouldn't it be more meaningful
to be in the picture together?
We should be in the picture together.
Wait, you forgot to take this!
[What bashful couple of girls...]
Bye, ladies!
Have a nice workout.
That was funny.
Those girls are really funny.
Those girls were so cute.
Ugh, I don't know where to go.
Your gut instinct is always the right one.
The Hallyu rabbit.
Okay, let's get going.
I want to go to the northern end
of the Seokang bridge.
It's past Mapo-Gu near Sinjungdong.
[Hallyu giraffe or Hallyu rabbit-
Decision making process is now complete.]
[With the exception of Jong Kook and Jae Suk,
everyone else decides to go to the rabbit.]
South and North...
So it must be across from each other.
Someone is trying to call me.
Song Ji Hyo is calling me.
She can't be calling me right now.
Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Jong Kook.
- Yeah?
- Where are you right now?
- I'm headed out somewhere right now.
Ah, you're already on the move?
- Yeah, I'm on the move.
- Okay, Jong Kook.
Hurry, okay?
After that phone call from Ji Hyo...
I don't think Ji Hyo is the rabbit.
So it makes me wonder if it'll be a good idea
to check and see who the rabbit is.
So I think I may go to the
southern end now.
[Jae Suk heads to the northern end
all by his lonesome.]
[Jae Suk arrives at the northern end
where Hallyu Giraffe awaits his arrival.]
[The piano melody can be heard
playing softly from the tent.]
[A romantic melody that can be heard
along the banks of Han River.]
[Where this piano melody can be heard from...]
[In this place...
a Hallyu giraffe awaits.]
[Could it... really be Kwang Soo?]
[On the southern end,
a Hallyu rabbit also lies in wait.]
[Gary is the first one to arrive.]
Am I the first one to arrive?
Am I the first?
I'm suddenly feeling a little bit bashful.
I suddenly feel really
embarrassed and nervous.
- Are you the only one here?
- Yes.
[Old man Big-nose,
and Muscle boy Kkuk also arrive.]
Do you think this is what our fans feel like
when they come to our fan meetings?
- Feeling this nervous energy?
- Are you nervous?
Yes, I'm nervous.
Who's that?
[All the fans rush over
to meet their Hallyu rabbit.]
[Everyone with the exception of Jae Suk
arrives to meet the Hallyu rabbit.]
I'm so curious to find out who the rabbit is.
I thought you were going to be the rabbit.
- No, I'm not the rabbit.
- I knew you weren't it when you called.
Welcome to all of you who made it
here to meet your Hallyu rabbit.
Thank you.
Hallyu rabbit, whom I'm sure all of you
are curious to find out about...
Okay, it's time to meet the Hallyu rabbit.
Please welcome our Hallyu rabbit who has
become a household name.
She'll soon be making her appearance.
- Hallyu rabbit!
- Look at all the bubbles!
I'm positive that it's a girl.
[A pink heart in the midst
of all the floating bubbles.]
- Rabbit!
- Look at all the bubbles!
[At last...]
[It's the moment where they get to meet
the Hallyu rabbit they've been waiting for.]
[It's Suzy!]
[The goddess of Asia- Suzy.]
Rabbit!
It's Suzy!
[Everyone rushes forward to greet Suzy.]
[Welcome Suzy onto the show!]
You look prettier every time I see you!
[Sensible enough to greet everyone
with a cheerful high-five.]
- Are you the sign of the rabbit?
- No, I'm the sign of the dog.
- Then why are you a rabbit?
- Because she's cute as a rabbit.
- And her front teeth are like a rabbit's.
- Is that why?
- Yes, I've heard that a lot of people.
- All rabbits should now be called 'Suzy'.
So all of us are Suzy's fans today.
This is like a fan meeting.
Why... how are you this pretty?
- How do you get prettier every day?
- What's your secret?
We're not giving you lip service right now.
How could she have gotten
so much prettier just in the past year?
Yes, you're so much prettier than last year.
- Then the other one really must be Kwang Soo?
- Jae Suk is the only one there?
[In that case...]
[At the other end of the bridge-
It's the Hallyu giraffe and Jae Suk.]
Hey, Lee Kwang Soo!
[Could... the Hallyu giraffe...
really be Kwang Soo?]
[Curiosity... killed the cat.]
[Our very own Prince of Asia,
Lee Kwang Soo.]
[Fitting of the moment...]
- What are you doing!
- Jae Suk!
- I was serenading you!
- What are you doing right now!
- Jae Suk, it's a Hallyu star special.
- Do you want a beating?
You called me way out here...
a taxi won't even come out here!
What do you think you're doing!
You are such a schemer!
You called me way out here
for this?
- What are you doing?
- Just wait, we have more fans coming.
[Hallyu Giraffe isn't aware that
no more people will be showing up.]
I only came here because I didn't know
who the Rabbit was going to be.
I knew you'd come.
You're the first guest to show up.
Thank you to my first fan.
How am I your first fan?
If I have to choose just one moment
when I've felt the happiest...
then it would be this moment
that I get to spend with my fan.
- What are you doing?
- What did you do that for?
[He just wanted to touch the face
of this Hallyu star.]
[The Hallyu star wave.]
Put your hand down!
Everyone, I now have a girlfriend.
You want to know who that is?
My girlfriend is none other than...
all you ladies out there.
- What are you doing, Jae Suk!
- Knock it off!
- What are you doing!
- Just knock it off!
- This is my fan meeting!
- I'm not your fan!
- No, you are my fan.
- No, I'm not your fan.
I don't know who else will be coming,
so please be a little bit more patient.
- I could be the only one.
- No, that can't be true.
Who's the Hallyu Rabbit?
I came here only because I didn't know.
I don't know either.
All the members have arrived
at the other side.
- The fan meeting is now over.
- What?
Yoo Jae Suk, you are Kwang Soo's
only fan.
- You're the only one.
- What?
Who's the Hallyu Rabbit?
It's Suzy.
[Seriously angry.]
- I can't even pick my own team?
- Suzy!
- Suzy! I wanted to pick Hallyu Rabbit!
- Can I go back to Suzy?
- Where do you think you're going?
Suzy texted me a couple of days ago,
but I never got to text her back.
- There's no way you got a text from her!
- I have to go to Suzy.
You schemer! I'm missing my
time with Suzy because of you!
- Is it really Suzy?
- Suzy!
- Suzy, I'm sorry!
Suzy!
Suzy, I'm sorry!
[Can you see her?
Suzy's smiling on the other side.]
[One the other side of the river,
people here are on cloud nine.]
This show is Prince of Asia,
Lee Kwang Soo's fans...
vs the goddess of the Hallyu wave,
Suzy's fans.
[Hallyu star race.]
The race will take place by utilizing public
transportation in the city of Seoul.
The team that passes the mission first will
be given a chance card for winning.
The Hallyu star of the winning team can
bring someone on from the other team.
Or the winning star also has the choice
to kick someone off their team.
This is dangerous because
Jae Suk is on the other team.
Or you also have the choice to keep
the team just as it is right now.
You have to keep it as is.
It can't get any better than this.
- Please choose your mode of transportation.
- Go get it, Kwang Soo.
[Team Giraffe- Bus vs
Team Rabbit- Subway.]
It's the subway!
[Nation's first love, whom men
all around the world fell in love with.]
[Goddess of our nation, Team Suzy.]
[Prince of Asia...]
[Prince of Asia, Team Giraffe.]
[A fierce competition!]
Our uniforms have a Hawaiian feel to them.
- This is supposed to be a fan meeting.
- You're right.
So we're dressed the part,
as if we're going to a fan meeting.
Should we come up with
a name for our fan club?
- How about Suzy's Club?
- We love Suzy?
- What do you think?
- How about... 'A day of Suzy'?
Okay, A day of Suzy.
Yes, it really is a day of Suzy.
I feel like we've just won
the lotto or something.
So it's like a special date
with the star or something.
[A dream-like date
with the goddess of Hallyu.]
[Just having Suzy by their side...
is more than they could've asked for.]
We can take those stairs over there.
[Makes their way to the subway station.]
We have to get some ice cream
later too, okay?
- Your treat, okay?
- Okay, it'll be my treat.
- Are you filming any movies right now?
- Movie?
- Yes, I'm going to start filming soon.
- No, don't do it!
There's probably going to be
a kiss scene in the movie!
- A kiss scene?
- Don't do it.
- We're not going to be able to stand that.
- Let's be supportive of her career.
- Let's accept her stardom.
- What are you saying right now?
[Sincerity of a true fan.]
- We have to be supportive of her.
- Don't you have a lot of older male fans?
- I'm not sure.
- I bet you do.
[Astounded by the sight of
Suzy in the subway station.]
- Let's take a look over here.
- This is set up like the airport.
[That's our ace!
Blank Ji calmly takes a look at the route.]
- We can take this one.
- Okay, let's get on the train.
- Let's get on the subway.
- I bet Kwang Soo's team is pretty depressed.
Can you buy me something to eat?
I don't have any money.
Don't you have any money?
Seriously?
- Look here...
- I'm going to kick you off my team.
Yes, do it!
Please kick me off your team.
Because I really want to go.
I want to go to Suzy.
It makes me so angry that I have no way
of getting you back right now!
I'm your one and only fan right now.
- I'm your one and only fan for the day.
- Thank you.
[A one on one date with the Giraffe...
A dream he wishes he could snap out of...]
Buy me something to eat! Don't
you think that you're being too stingy?
No, I've made up my mind.
I'm definitely kicking you off the team.
- I'm definitely going to kick you off.
- Then you'll be left all alone.
A star can't exist without their fans.
Ugh, seriously.
You can't be a star without your fan.
- I wasn't thinking clearly, I'm sorry.
- Seriously.
Hello ladies.
- Hi girls.
- Where are you girls going?
- We're going to school.
- Aren't you on summer vacation?
You're going to school even though
you're on summer vacation?
- Do you want an autograph?
- We're heading to Sang-Su Station right now.
Do you know how we can get to
Seonyu Park from that station?
- Do you know?
- No.
- Where are you girls headed?
- Sung San Middle School.
[Time to board the bus.]
Hello.
[This bus route seems to be
heading towards Seonyu.]
We just need to go two stops.
What were you doing?
- Were you taking our pictures?
- Were you taking pictures of us?
- You need to be in the picture too.
- Want to take it together?
- Let's just take it together.
- Come here.
Come on, let's take it together.
- Let me see the camera.
- I'll take the picture.
- Will you take the picture for us?
- What?
[Jae Suk wants the Hallyu star
to take the picture of him instead.]
No, not like that. But can
you take one of me with the girls?
[Hallyu star seems bewildered by the request
that Jae Suk seems to be making.]
One, two, three.
[With the President of
Hallyu Giraffe's fan club.]
- Thank you.
- You need to take a picture of me too!
[Refuses to take one of the Hallyu star.]
Don't you want to take one
with me too?
[No, it's okay.]
- Why are you so pushy?
- I'm not being pushy.
- They said they don't want one.
- But this is a Hallyu star race.
I really want you girls to cheer me on.
[There's your cheer.]
That was funny.
These girls are really funny.
Hey, kid.
Come sit down over here.
[Is this really happening?]
I'm sorry.
He scared you, didn't he?
Come sit down over here.
[Yoo Hyuk steps up to rectify the situation.]
You're on your way to school too?
Is everyone going to school today?
- Isn't it still summer vacation?
- We have to get off the bus now.
[Yoo Hyuk is keeping the Giraffe
segregated until they get off the bus.]
- Bye.
[Goodbye, Hallyu star.]
The energy is so upbeat
and happy on our team.
How are your more aggressive fans?
Some of them seem like really fervent fans.
- Aren't they kind of cool?
- Yes, somewhat.
Yes, I like it when they do that.
Because I'll do the same thing to them.
- We're here.
- This is where we get off.
We're here already?
[In the midst of all their cheer and laughter,
they didn't even notice that they've arrived.]
Let's take the second exit,
and head toward the river.
What would you like Suzy?
Which one of these do you like, Suzy?
- I want this one.
- Okay.
- I'll pay for this.
- Suzy's paying.
- The star is buying her fans ice cream.
- Stars like you are rare.
- You are a rarity for sure.
- That's so sweet!
There should be a newspaper article about
Suzy buying her fans ice cream.
I'm going to upload this on SNS.
[Picture proof.]
I see the sign over there.
Let's take the second exit.
[Both teams arrive at Seonyudo.]
[Run to the park without wasting any time.]
We're the first to get here?
- Are we the first ones here?
- Hello everyone.
Here's your first mission.
'I'm your paparazzi'
You've had experiences with
paparazzi as a Hallyu star, don't you?
From this moment on, you
yourselves will become the paparazzi.
Even though you've always had
your pictures taken
you will now have the chance to be
the ones to take the pictures.
There are several cameras
hidden throughout this park.
You will have to find those cameras
to become the paparazzi yourselves
and covertly take pictures of your
opposing team members.
The pictures have to be a full
and clear shot of their faces
and the team who successfully takes a picture
of all their opponents first wins the mission.
Okay, we understand.
Then the other team wins the mission once
they get a picture of us two?
- Yes, that's correct.
- That's too big of an advantage for them.
- But you were the first ones to arrive.
- Maybe we can wait for them in hiding.
Okay, let's go find those cameras first.
[Photo-shoot with the Hallyu star.]
This place is so big.
Where are we going to find the cameras?
[It is imperative that they get
their hands on the cameras first.]
If the other team tries to get a picture,
then let's jump in each other's shots.
Yes, that's what we should do.
We should stick together.
So they can't get a shot of
our face alone.
- You know that we're at a disadvantage?
- Yes, I know.
This is all your fault!
This is all your fault.
I'm getting really angry all of a sudden.
No, it's not my fault.
We're going to win.
Let's go!
[Team Suzy finally arrives at the park.]
[This fervent fan tries to do whatever he can
to stay ahead and protect his star.]
- Jae Suk!
- I found it.
[Yoo Hyuk discovers a camera.]
[Hallyu Giraffe also finds a camera,
and teams up again.]
[All they have left to do now,
is plan their attack.]
- Let's go hide.
- How do you work this thing?
[He is so high maintenance!]
The other team arrived just
before you did.
I will tell you about your mission right now.
Hallyu star race's first mission is,
'I'm your paparazzi.'
You yourselves will now
become the paparazzi.
[Become the paparazzi and capture
a picture of your opposing team members.]
Kwang Soo, I think there are
two entrances to the park area.
Since we haven't seen any of them yet
there's a good chance
that they'll come through here.
- We should hide somewhere around here.
- That's right.
Kwang Soo.
[Discovers Team Suzy receiving their mission.]
[Erase all traces of themselves.]
[Places themselves in hiding.]
[Waits in hiding to capture
images of their opponents on their camera.]
So they're already waiting for us in hiding?
Do we have to do it from hiding?
Or can I look at them in the face?
- That is up to you.
- So we can get in their faces?
You can hold them down,
and we'll take the pictures.
You have to find the cameras first.
You may get started.
We're at an advantage here because
they won't be able to get you easily.
[Come on...]
[Plans of attack are now in place.]
I have to get their pictures
as they're entering the park.
[The prey enters the lion's den
while staying oblivious to their plan.]
[Preparations are now complete.]
[Let's finish this off in one shot!]
[Paparazzi's complete camouflage.]
Don't look over there!
[Discovered right away!]
- He's over there.
- Don't look that way.
- There it is over there!
- Where?
[Fails at their initial plan, and
immediately starts chasing after them.]
[Transforms themselves into
the in your face paparazzi duo.]
[Capturing pictures of a moving target is
proving too difficult for these amateurs.]
Suzy!
- Suzy! I'm a huge fan of yours!
- Suzy, can I just can a picture?
Let us get just one picture!
- Let me just get one picture!
- Suzy!
Come here, Suzy!
- No, you can't!
[This Hallyu star is used to
avoiding the camera lens.]
[Loyal fan, Haroro,
steps in to protect Suzy.]
[A parade of shots of Ha Ha
trying to avoid the camera lens.]
[Why are you taking pictures
of your own fan?]
[Pins him down to take the picture.]
[Needs a clear shot of the full face
in order for the picture to count.]
No!
[The flash keeps going off without any rest.]
Yeah, I got it.
[Ha Ha's face is captured.]
Yeah, that's enough.
[Just then, Kkuk comes rushing in.]
[Kkuk is after Kwang Soo's camera.]
Jae Suk!
Take the picture!
- Hurry up and take the picture!
- I'm doing it!
[The terror of Kkuk is captured on film.]
[Hallyu Giraffe ultimately loses
his camera to Kkuk.]
Why would you let him take that
away from you?
How could you not even protect me?
- Huh?
- What were you doing?
Weren't you even going to protect me
while he attacked me for my camera?
Look at how scary Jong Kook looks.
He's a total monster.
Look at his mouth and teeth.
[Kwang Soo distracts the opponents
for Jae Suk to sneak in for a picture.]
[At this distance,
even an amateur may be able to pull it off.]
Watch out!
He's trying to take it from up above!
[Their plan is foiled by Ace Ji Hyo!]
Watch out!
He's trying to take it from up above!
Be careful!
[Blank Ji becomes their new target.]
He's trying to take the shot from up above!
Lee Kwang Soo is trying to get the shot!
Let's get one of them.
Come on, Gary.
Get her!
Get Blank Ji.
[Attacks Ace Ji Hyo.]
Ji Hyo, let me get a picture of you.
[Covers her face with her hair.]
[Is that a ghost?]
[Kkuk makes his appearance.]
[A face-off between the two paparazzi.]
- Where did you find the camera?
- Hurry up and take the picture!
[A battle of the paparazzi.]
[Sticking together like glue to avoid
getting a solo shot of them taken.]
[The close relationship between
this star and his fan.]
[A total photoshoot.]
[The star is made a complete mess of.]
[Doing everything he can to protect his
face from the camera lens.]
[Goddess of Hallyu's sole chance.]
Do you know where the judging table is?
- Got it.
- You got it all?
- That's good, right?
- You took 51 pictures.
You got a clear shot of Lee Kwang Soo.
There should be one of Jae Suk too.
[Jae Suk's picture fails since
it's not a complete shot of his full face.]
You succeeded with the shot of Lee Kwang Soo,
so you only have Jae Suk left to go.
You just need to get one of Jae Suk.
[Back to the scene of
Hallyu Giraffe's humiliation.]
[A flood of flashlights
befitting of a Hallyu star.]
[Another successful shot of Kwang Soo.]
[The President of the Fan Club
is the only one left remaining.]
[Hallyu star does what he can
to protect his fan.]
[A successful shot of Jae Suk.]
[Kkuk heads over to the judging table.]
We're at too big of a disadvantage.
[Unable to win against
their six on two attack.]
- This is just absurd.
- Do you owe them anything?
- Why would I owe them anything?
- Maybe that's why they're after you.
This is all your fault!
- How is this my fault?
- This is all your fault!
- I got a clear shot of Kwang Soo.
- Really?
Take a look at the pictures.
It was a total war out there.
Take a look through all the pictures.
I took some too.
- Suzy already captured Kwang Soo earlier.
- Really?
So in that case...
Suzy, what are you doing?
Where's the police station around here?
We had our camera stolen,
and... come here, Kwang Soo.
[The biggest victim of the mission.]
- This is my camera.
- He had his camera stolen away from him.
This team is full of delinquents
with two girls and four boys.
- They all attacked us.
- That's too bad.
They pushed down on our pressure points.
Don't you think that's going overboard?
[Suzy busies herself by taking
pictures of their angry disposition.]
[Project title-
'This is unfair' by Suzy.]
[Judging of Kkuk's pictures.]
This one?
Let me reenact it for you.
[An immediate reenactment.]
I was right.
- Is this what you're referring to?
- This is the perfect reenactment.
- Is this the shot?
- Yes, this is the shot.
This is really hurtful to my pride.
- Suzy got the shot of Kwang Soo's face.
- When did Suzy take the picture?
And Kim Jong Kook captured a successful
shot of Kim Jong Kook's face.
Team Suzy wins this mission.
[Team Suzy wins!]
- How could you all have gone to the Rabbit?
- Then why would you go to Giraffe?
Had I known that Suzy was the Rabbit,
then I totally would've gone there too!
This Hallyu star doesn't even have any money.
He wouldn't even buy me anything to eat!
- Why are you bringing that up?
- The fan should be taking care of the star!
I have a feeling that you'll
soon be joining our team.
[First candidate to be kicked off the team?]
You may be going back
and forth between the teams.
I do feel a bit nervous about that,
but I've been really nice to Suzy all day.
As mentioned earlier, Suzy now has
a team member chance card.
[A chance to swap out a member
should she choose to do so.]
I ran in and saved you
from a dangerous situation.
You can either bring someone in,
or send someone out of your team.
- What happens if I bring someone in?
- If I go, then he loses his Hallyu stardom.
Suzy would never be that cruel.
[What do I do about this situation?]
I'll give you some time
to think about it.
- I've always admired you from afar.
- I've always loved and supported you.
- I think...
- State your decision on the count of three.
- I'll send someone out.
- You're sending someone out?
- Just tell me who you're going to send out.
- It could be you that she sends out.
[You could be the one.]
Suzy's already turning her back on you.
- Suzy keeps turning her back on you.
- What are you talking about?
It's going to be one of you two!
I bet my whole fortune
that she picks Suk Jin.
You just have to say who it is,
and that person will leave your team.
[Time to reveal her decision.]
- I don't think it's going to be me.
- Okay, I understand.
Thank you, Suzy Bae.
[Suzy steps away from the situation.]
Suzy, we'll be able to look at each other
with smiles on our faces again, right?
- We can do that, right?
- Sure!
I've never been wrong about
these kinds of premonitions before.
I'll whisper it in your ear,
so just step away from the team, okay?
- Step out where?
- Just over there.
So the last person to stand remaining
will be joining our team.
[The last person remaining
will be the one to get kicked out.]
He's already the president of my fan club,
so the new person will be the VP.
I'm the president of his fan club.
[Gets the uniform ready for the new member.]
I would sincerely like to thank everyone
for coming here today
to welcome a new member to
Hallyu Giraffe's Fan Club.
One of you five members will
soon be joining our team.
So the new member to join our team
will have to pay a small joining fee.
That's because we're a new fan club too.
Song Ji Hyo, go join Suzy over there.
- Thank you.
- It's disappointing, but we'll see you again.
Hallyu Rabbit is the best!
Suzy, I'll see you soon!
- Ha Ha, you may also step aside.
- Thank you.
- What the heck?
- I have a feeling he'll be joining us later.
Out of my way!
Rabbit!
- Ji Suk Jin?
- Yes?
Can you step aside a little?
Are you playing with me right now?
- Don't play with me!
- You're just moving aside, that's all.
[Extremely sensitive at even
having to move over to the side.]
Next up is, Gary.
You may go join your team members.
Now it's between you two.
We will now make the final announcement
and welcome a new member to our team.
This is a pretty big shirt,
so even Kim Jong Kook could fit into it.
I don't know why Suzy chose
the person she did.
- Ji Suk Jin?
- Yes?
Can you move back over here?
Why do you keep making me go
back and forth like that?
Just make it quick!
Once we announce the decision that
Bae Suzy has made between these two
this new member of our team will be
honored with an official spot on our team.
Yes, this person will be
honored with the VP position.
- 30,000 won is the joining fee.
- Yes, that's correct.
- The fee has to be paid right away.
- Do we get something for the fee?
- No, that will pay for our meal.
- You'll get this shirt for it.
That'll be the cost
for the shirt and the meal.
- I thought there would be something else.
- We're not really set up for that yet.
[All they have to offer in this fan club
is the mutual love for their star, Giraffe.]
Then I will now make the announcement.
- Ji Suk Jin, can you please say a word?
- I don't believe that Suzy will betray me.
- Yes, I have always been a fan of hers.
- How about you recite a poem with her name?
- Su.
- Suzy, I love you.
- Zy.
- Ji Suk Jin loves you.
- Wow, that's very touching.
- I don't regret my decision.
Okay, Kim Jong Kook.
Your turn with the poem.
- Su.
- Suzy is...
- Zy.
- Is the prettiest girl on this earth.
Okay, Kim Jong Kook...
[Will he leave... or stay?]
Please go join your teammates.
[Kim Jong Kook remains on Team Suzy.]
[Ji Suk Jin is kicked out.]
Congratulations...
We congratulate you on
getting kicked off the team.
Now that you've become a member of our team,
let's take a picture to commemorate this.
[A picture to commemorate having become
the VP of Giraffe's fan club.]
Give me a piggy back ride.
I said, piggy back ride. This should
be a perk for being on your team.
Had I known that Suzy was the Rabbit,
then I would've joined her team.
[Paparazzi mission- Team Suzy wins.]
If we win the next mission,
we're going to send him back to you.
You should just carry both the shirts
around with you all day.
You just wait and see. I'm going
to make you regret your decision.
You just wait yourself.
- Should we get going?
- Let's go.
I took the subway train earlier.
- We have to get there before them.
- Yes, of course.
What are the benefits of being on this team?
Suzy bought us all ice cream.
- He won't even buy us food.
- Come on.
Buy us a bowl of soup or something.
[Team Suzy- Bus vs Team Giraffe- Subway.]
I haven't taken the bus in so long.
- Is this the bus stop?
- Come stand over here in the shade.
- Stand over there.
- Come stand over here too.
This is a direct route to where
we need to go.
- They'll all take us there.
- We can take this one, or that one.
The bus is here.
- Can we pay with a card?
- You don't need that cash.
- Don't you even know that?
- Didn't you take the bus to school?
- No, I didn't.
- Don't you have a card?
The innocence about you makes me
want to protect you even more.
[Boards the bus with their Hallyu goddess.]
We come from a time when we had to
use bus tokens and tickets.
The first time I took a bus,
it cost me 70 won.
[The never-ending smile on this goddess' face.]
You can take the seat.
[Very polite President Yoo Hyuk.]
Then shall we sit down too?
[Hallyu Giraffe Fan Club-
No regards to a person's age.]
- You can sit down over here.
- No, it's okay. We'll be getting off soon.
I'm still very healthy.
[The card left on the seat
next to the young passenger.]
Is this your face?
That looks like my picture.
Thank you, but what is it that you like
so much about Kwang Soo?
- What do you like about him?
- What do you like about me?
[Since there's nothing specific...]
- You like my height?
- Want to shake his hand?
Don't force him to shake your hand.
Have a good day.
This is the place.
Ji Hyo is so good with directions.
[Seoul Mapo District- 'D' Health Club.]
- Are we the first ones here?
- Seriously?
What are we going to be doing here?
- Thank you all for coming.
- Congratulations, Jong Kook.
- I heard that you've moved?
- Isn't this your new home?
Here's your second mission.
Star's physical fitness.
[Hallyu star's physical fitness.]
You have to spin the hula hoops
while hanging off the bar behind you.
[Rule- Spin the hula hoop while
hanging off the bar.]
This is a loyalty game.
You must do a total of 60 seconds or more.
[Since it's a healthy club,
Mr. Muscle Head will start them off first.]
[The clock will start once they
get on the bar first.]
Kwang Soo's record was four seconds.
You're doing it!
[With this being Kkuk's background,
he already shows a strong knack for it.]
You got this.
You did ten seconds.
But I have a feeling that I looked
awful while doing it.
[Team Giraffe arrives.]
- I think we need him off our team.
- These guys are depressing.
No one even recognizes me.
All anyone even cares about is Jae Suk.
- I don't know why this fan club even exists.
- Excuse me, VP Ji.
Please stop insulting our fan club.
I'm trying my best here.
So what's this all about?
For this mission, we have to spin
the hula hoops while hanging off this bar.
I can't do the hula hoop even
while standing flat on my feet.
I can get maybe three at best.
If we win this mission,
I can kick Suk Jin off my team, right?
Seriously, I already told you earlier,
but he'll be bouncing back and forth.
[Team Suzy's first official turn.]
- Take your time.
- He's actually quite good.
There you go!
- There you go!
- He's such a beast!
- This is what we have to do?
[Kkuk is working out his whole body.]
- I feel really weird doing it.
- You're a total monster.
- I really can't stand even looking at you.
- You really are like a beast.
[Immediately launches into an attack mode
on their opposing team.]
- Your record is 13.5 seconds.
- Is this actually even feasible?
- Suzy's really good.
- Hold onto the bar.
Lower your body as if
you're hanging off of it.
- There you go!
- She's doing really well.
- Not bad at all.
- Even Suzy looks awful while doing it.
Even Suzy looks awful while doing it.
What did you just say?
Aren't you in my fan club?
Aren't you going to stand up for me?
Even though we're in your fan club,
we have our own lives to protect too.
Even though we exist as your fans
because we have you
we still have our own lives to live too.
[Team Suzy- 43.5 seconds left to go.]
There you go, Ha Ha!
[Abilities that they've never shown before
emerge in front of their star.]
[Kiddo fan's record- Eight seconds.]
Can you play me some music?
I seriously think that'll help me do better.
This is like club music.
[Transformed into Rhythm Gary.]
[Gary's record- Four seconds.]
- I think the music will help me.
- Ji Hyo, are you good at this?
I don't know why,
but I feel like I'm still on their team.
It makes me feel good when
I see you guys doing well.
- Ji Hyo's good.
- Wow, she's good.
[Ace takes her time and
is showing some staying power.]
[Ace's record- Eight seconds.]
- You guys are really good.
- So who wants to go first?
Want to give it a try?
[Team Giraffe's turn.]
- Spin this for me.
- Even though you may be older than me...
- You still need to speak in honorifics to me.
- You're the newbie in our club.
Spin it to the left like this.
- Like this?
- Yes, like that.
- Ready, set...
- Spin it.
Come on, can't you do it right?
- We'll do it again.
- I'm trying to be as patient as I can.
[Star himself steps up to help.]
I told you to spin it the other way.
[Seemed to be relieved that he's no longer
a part of their team.]
To the left!
[Big-nose is proving to be tough to please.]
[Mr. Bounce in the house.]
[Record- Six seconds.
Not too shabby for this VP.]
He's better than I thought he'd be.
That's good.
There you go.
[Our Kwang Soo doesn't even have to jump
for him to become one with the bar.]
[But his feet need to be off the ground
for the clock to start.]
[He needs to get his feet off the ground.]
It's time.
[A very determined look on his face.]
[One more foot!]
[He's got the feel for it now!]
You're doing good!
[Fan club cheer.]
[Hallyu Giraffe- A whopping 21 seconds!]
- That was good.
- I couldn't have done it without you two.
- I think I got the feel for it now.
- I think we can do this.
What were you staring at
when you were up there?
Why do you even care what
my star was staring at?
- It's because I found him pitiful.
- You are unbelievable.
We're bringing you onto our team
if we win this mission.
And we're going to make you
do all our errands.
- That's a frightening thought.
- Scary, isn't it?
We're going to bring you on,
and make you our errand boy.
We're going to make you do all our errands.
One, two, three.
- What are you doing!
- I'm sorry, President Yoo.
[A special training tactic
just for his President Yoo.]
What were you doing!
You can only exist because of fans like me.
This is no way to treat your fans.
Ugh, seriously.
- Spin it with your waist.
- Why are you moving your whole body?
- Spin it to the left.
- There you go!
There you go!
[All thanks to the help of his star.]
[President Grasshopper is ready to take flight.]
Don't make me laugh.
[A surprisingly unexpected performance
by President Yoo.]
- I was totally shocked.
- 22 seconds.
- You just need to get the feel for it.
Don't make me laugh.
That's why I failed.
[Team Giraffe unfortunately fails
with a record of 49 seconds.]
- We were just cheering you on.
- I was completely shocked.
- You were shocked, weren't you?
- Yes, I was very shocked.
Yes, this will surprise you for sure.
[Team Suzy- Ji Hyo to lead them off.]
You look very natural doing that.
[Not so natural looking anymore.]
[But our Ace doesn't disappoint!]
- You're not called an 'Ace' for nothing.
- Yes, you're very good.
[Record of seven seconds.
That's our Ace!]
[Captain Kkuk to spin the hoop for Ha Ha.]
No, lift up your knees.
Your knees!
[This fan club gets you in trouble
if lacking in physical stamina.]
[I'll just have to do better.]
How does she look so natural
doing that?
[Even escapes the moment of danger
by making it look like she's dancing.]
- Remember the bar dance she did?
- Of course, I do.
[This Hallyu star makes even
the bar exercise look lovely.]
[Oh, my goddess.]
- Remember the bar dance she did?
- Of course, I do.
[Suzy's record- Two seconds.]
You did great!
[We'll just make up for your slack.]
You keep your arms straight
when you hang off the bar, don't you?
You want to give
Suzy some pointers, don't you?
No, it's not that.
- She's still our star.
- You want to say something to her.
Want to spin it after getting on the bar?
- Want me to spin it for you?
- No, that's okay.
[Spins the hoop on his own.]
- I'll spin it for you.
- No, let me start over.
- Get on the bar, and I'll spin it.
- No, I think my way is better.
Listen to us for once.
[Buried resentment from
the other members of the fan club.]
It took him four years to say that.
[It took him four years to say that, Suzy.]
We've all been wanting to
say that to him for four years.
Too bad I couldn't get it earlier.
[Resurrection of King Kong!]
There you go!
He seriously is a total monster.
[A true king of fitness.]
[30 seconds and counting.]
[Hula hoop monster.]
[Record of 38 seconds. Team Suzy
unfortunately fails with 58 seconds]
Wow, you guys are something else.
- Can you help me spin this?
- Okay.
- This is much better.
- Here we go.
One, two, three.
Concentrate.
[His hips have gotten the feel
for the moves.]
Concentrate.
[The Grasshopper has still got it.]
[Yoo Hyuk's record- 25 seconds.]
You do 30 seconds, and I'll do five.
Just do all 35 seconds yourself.
[Giraffe's turn.]
There you go.
[His physical awareness that he's
showing off to his fans.]
[Way to go, Hallyu Giraffe.]
[A stressed out expression on his face.]
[The love from my fans
is what keeps me going!]
- 33 seconds.
- Then how many more seconds do we need?
[Hallyu Giraffe- 33 seconds.
Only two more seconds are needed to win!]
What if I can't even get two seconds?
[Then you'll definitely
get kicked off the team.]
You know how long two seconds
can be, right?
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
About that long.
Didn't you see how long two seconds
can be at the London Olympics?
Please let me last for two seconds.
[His fate rests on those two seconds.]
If you can get this, then you win.
- Just spin it.
- You could just end this right now.
[Two seconds could mean failure
when it comes to Big-nose.]
[The victorious pelvic thrusts!]
[Team Giraffe wins
with a record of 63 seconds!]
- We can kick Ji Suk Jin off our team!
- We did it!
- We can get Ji Suk Jin off our team!
- You're going to kick me off the team?
- You can go back to the team.
- No, you did great.
- Okay, I think we did great together.
- I think we've found the rhythm.
[Team Giraffe now has the chance
to utilize their chance card.]
Who can either bring someone on
from your opposing team
or you can kick someone out,
or keep your team as is.
When I think of an errand boy,
that's definitely Ha Ha.
But when I think about winning,
then it's Jong kook.
But if Jong Kook comes...
then we're all dead.
Because we won't have any say in anything
and we'll just have to do what he says.
[No fan club to speak of anymore.]
It would be best if we could bring Suzy.
- Just take me.
- One, two, three.
[Decision time.]
[Sounds like it'll be either
Ha Ha or Jong Kook...]
You, come here, Ha Ha.
[Team Giraffe's chance card-
Brings Ha Ha on board.]
- Suzy!
- Come here.
- What are you going to do without me?
- What are you going to do with us?
[Why don't you just worry about yourself?]
You guys must've lost your minds!
Get your hands off of me.
[Forcefully welcoming him onto the team.]
- I'll do it myself.
- Just take it off.
Can't you at least
act like you're disappointed?
Suzy did the whole crying bit
without a bit of emotion behind it.
[Seconds mission- Star's physical fitness.
Team Giraffe wins.]
- Hey, newbie.
- Yes?
[Destination- SBS.
Team Giraffe to take the taxi.]
If all four of us are to get in the cab, then
you have to sit up front with the camera.
- I have to do what?
- You have to film us.
[Team Suzy- Bus.
Team Giraffe- Taxi.]
We're here.
You can let us out here.
Thank you, have a good day.
[Team Giraffe are the first ones to arrive.]
Thank you.
- SBS! My place of work.
- There it is.
- I bet they're already here.
- Since they took a cab...
I bet it took them no time to get here.
- Come on, hurry.
- I think I see something.
[The sooner you arrive,
more advantageous it'll be for the team.]
You have the advantage for arriving first.
Here's your mission.
This is an event that all stars get to
experience from Hollywood to here.
It's the handprint event
that you see behind you.
We have hidden several hand printing
boxes throughout the SBS building.
As you can see here with my handprint,
you can get an impression of your own hand.
You have to bring the box back to this
hand printing zone and make an impression.
- All four members of the team have to do it.
- All four of us?
- Then we need to find four?
- Yes, that's correct. You may get started.
- Where are they going?
- What is this?
- We have to take this?
- Here are your rules.
We have hidden several hand printing
boxes throughout the SBS building.
We can't do the hand printing in advance.
- We have to come back here and do it.
- Come back to the zone.
- There are four men on our team.
- You're right.
- Don't worry.
- You may now get started.
- Let's get going.
- Will our names be on the ground too then?
- You think?
- That would be nice to see my name.
- That's not going to happen.
- No, it's not.
No, that's not going to happen.
There it is.
We should've taken the next one.
- I'm sorry about that.
- We wanted to ride with Suzy.
- We feel the same way.
- We want to be with her too.
But we're all Lee Kwang Soo's fans.
- Let's get off here.
- Let's get off on the third floor.
- Want to check out the sixth floor?
- Let's pair off in two's.
- Be careful not to get it taken from you.
- Get what taken?
- This?
- No, the hand printing box.
- You don't get it on the first try, do you?
- She's not good at understanding things.
I don't know if she has bad hearing.
She has slightly bad hearing.
My father has bad hearing too.
[Team Giraffe is busy looking
for the hand printing boxes.]
Wow, the search is on again.
I think it's going to be on the second floor.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
Let's search through this whole place.
I found one!
[The prince of Asia!
Hallyu Giraffe finds the very first box.]
Once you find the box, you
have to go back to where we started.
[Must go back to the hand printing zone
to make an impression of their hand.]
- I saw Jae Suk earlier.
- There they are. They're over there.
[Suspicious to anyone looking.]
- Let's get off here.
- I'm going to go up to the sixth floor.
[Jong Kook and Gary gets off to
get their hand on Giraffe's box.]
Here they come.
[Target in sight.]
Take the stairs and go back to the zone.
[Let's act natural... act natural.]
He's going out the door.
Come on, Gary!
[But you can't fool the Tiger!]
[Hallyu Giraffe is captured!]
Kwang Soo!
That fool!
- That Lee Kwang Soo.
- Where did you come from!
[Anti- fan.
Steals the box from the Hallyu star.]
- I'll do it first.
- Okay, go ahead.
- I'll be back again.
- Where did you two come from!
[Team Suzy-
Muscle fan succeeds his mission.]
- Pass. You may now take a seat.
- I can't go back there?
No, take a rest.
[Rule- Once you succeed your portion,
then you can't go back into the building.]
[Kwang Soo re-enters the building
to find another box.]
[Discovers another box!]
[Even he himself can't believe his luck!]
Wow, how did this even happen?
[I vow to succeed this time.]
[Step one- carefully monitor the area.]
[Step 2- And go straight out the door.]
[But...]
[His unlucky streak
doesn't seem to be ending...]
[Purposely calling out Gary's name
towards the building for distraction.]
Why are you doing this!
[Hallyu Giraffe gets his box stolen
for the second time.]
- Do I have to do this now?
- What else can you do? Just do it.
[Leaves them worrying for
their remaining female members.]
[Team Suzy- Gary succeeds with imprinting.]
[Unbelievable...]
- Where do you keep finding these?
- Did you find one?
I found two,
and they stole both of them away from me.
What are we going to do about the girls?
I didn't even see you guys around.
[Oh?
The box was hidden behind his back!]
So I should just hide it in the back?
- How did you know that?
- It was obvious.
[Ha Ha is the first to succeed
for Team Giraffe.]
So Ji Hyo and Suzy are the only
ones left now?
[Hallyu Giraffe heads back
inside the building.]
Hello.
- You're so pretty.
- Thank you.
[It's a fan meeting no matter where she goes.]
I'm really bad at finding things.
[Suzy's especially bad when it comes
to finding things.]
[Searching through every nook
and cranny of the editing room.]
Isn't that Kwang Soo?
That looks like Kwang Soo.
Awesome!
[Discovers a box in the editing room!]
I feel like I should hide this.
The boxes aren't going to be easy to find.
There's Suzy.
There she is over there.
Which floor is she on?
[Big-nose discovers Suzy holding the box.]
So I pass once I go back
and make an impression?
Was it the fifth floor?
This is the floor.
There she is.
[The attack of Big-nose hyena.]
[Once a fan now attacks.]
- Let's carry it together
- This box?
- Just show me what it looks like?
- This?
- I'm not going to steal it away from you.
- You stole my pillow the last time.
[Suzy escapes away from Big-nose's grasp.]
Suzy, I'm a huge fan of yours.
Suzy, I really am a fan of yours.
Just tell me where you found it.
Let's play for it.
[Shamelessly asks her to play for it.]
- Why would I have to do that?
- I can't fight you for it.
[Just then, Blank Ji runs in to her rescue.]
- Get out of here, Suzy!
- Suzy!
- Bring that back!
- Hey, Suzy!
- Suzy.
[But she's blocked off by Jae Suk.]
- Why are you doing this to me?
- I'm sorry, Suzy.
Suzy.
[Blank Ji reappears to her rescue.]
- I have to protect Suzy.
- I need to take that from you.
[Blank Ji appears out of thin air
whenever her star is in need of rescuing.]
Let's put the box down and play for it.
- Put it down?
- Yeah, put it down and play for it.
[Just as expected.
Big-nose sneaks a steal!]
Run!
Move!
[Jae Suk isn't letting up
on his grip on Blank Ji.]
[Big-nose takes the chance
and makes his escape.]
[Suzy stays hot on his trail.]
Suzy!
Hurry up and run!
[Star chaser for the hand printing box.]
- I need to win this mission.
- Suzy.
I had a feeling I found that box too easily.
I'm going to get you back for this!
Kim Jong Kook!
Kang Gary!
- Kang Gary!
- That Blank Ji Hyo!
- Kim Jong Kook! Get Ji Suk Jin!
- Be quiet!
[But Kim Jong Kook and Kang Gary
are already outside...]
[Thanks to that, Big-nose safely
arrives at the hand printing zone.]
- Suzy hasn't found one yet, has she?
- She did and I stole it away from her.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
[Angry Suzy's fan club.]
[Big-nose succeeds
his portion of the mission.]
I was acting very casual about it.
[Hallyu Giraffe is on the search
for his third box.]
I've used up all of my luck
for this next year.
[Carefully opens up the door...]
[Oh? Another box!]
[Now two years of luck have been used.
Boxes are just rolling in for the Giraffe.]
[I will not have this
stolen away from me again!]
[Carefully hides away the box.]
[Blank Ji is seen heading this way.]
[She fortunately doesn't seem to notice.]
[How can you not notice with
the look he has on his face?]
You haven't found one?
You really haven't found one?
[No one's going to believe that!]
- Come on, let's get out of here first.
- Just hear me out.
[Agrees to step out of the room first.]
I'm starting to get really pissed.
This will be the third time
it's stolen away from me.
Come on, Kwang Soo.
Let me just take it.
No, hear me out.
Jong Kook and Gary waited for me outside,
and took the first two boxes away from me.
- That's really not nice of them.
- That's what I'm saying.
- That's not very nice of them.
- Let me just go.
But that was Jong Kook and Gary,
I had nothing to do with it.
- Just hear me out.
- Just give it to me.
But...
[Will Kwang-Star be able to
leave his own handprint?]
[Suzy goes back on the search after
having her first box stolen by Big-nose.]
[Discovers a box in the studio!]
[Kwang-Star's number one fan
discovers a box of his own!]
[Suzy's on the move!]
- It's Suzy.
- Suzy!
Be careful and hurry!
- Okay, we're all good.
- What about Ji Hyo?
[Suzy also successfully imprints her hand.]
Did Jae Suk pass too?
There's Jae Suk over there.
[Kwang Soo and Blank Ji are still
fighting over the box.]
Jae Suk!
- I hope that I'm not too late.
- Jae Suk!
Jae Suk!
[Kwang-Star desperately shouts out for help.]
Yoo Jae Suk!
Jae Suk!
[Please!]
[Pretends not to hear?
Runs out of the building.]
Why is he running away?
Jae Suk!
[Sorry, but I'll be going first.]
[Kwang-Star is abandoned.]
You can't bite me!
[Kwang-Star bites down hard.]
[Bites down on each other.]
[Tooth for a tooth!]
I can't believe you bit me!
Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk!
- Who's that?
[President Yoo makes it over
after abandoning his star.]
- I barely made it.
- So it's down to Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo.
[Now the only ones left are...
Blank Ji and Kwang-Star.]
[The one to get their hand printed first
wins the mission!]
[Who will be the one to win?]
[Blank Ji safely wins the battle.]
What are you doing!
She bit me and stole the box
away from me!
[A strong way to express their
caring for the star.]
- I kept calling out for you.
- Kwang Soo found a total of three boxes.
- He found three of our boxes.
- And you had all three taken away?
- Thanks for all your hard work, Kwang Soo.
- What in the world are you doing?
- What kind of a Hallyu star are you?
- You're so kind to help us out like this.
Isn't he so nice? You
should've just brought the first box down.
[Thanks to Kwang-Star for finding
three of their boxes for them.]
The victory goes to Team Suzy!
[Hand printing mission- Team Suzy wins!]
You have another team member chance card,
but the number of members will be important.
Will having more be advantageous,
or will having less me more advantageous?
Bring me back onto the team.
You can't go.
You're the star of this team.
[Wants to abandon his own fan club?]
What will become of us if you
were to leave?
Since you're the Hallyu star,
you can't leave your team to join the other.
I'm not a Hallyu star.
- I want to go.
- Think about this very carefully.
[Will Suzy get rid of a member,
or bring someone in?]
I'm sorry for taking this box from you.
No need for you to apologize because
we're not even considering you.
I thought I'd mention that
just in case.
Then I'll just come over there.
- You can't go over there!
- In that case...
I'd like to...
[Time for a decision.]
- Suk Jin.
- What!
[Did Suzy just choose Suk Jin?]
- She just said it.
- She meant to say, not Suk Jin.
- Anyone other than him.
- Why are you speaking for her?
- Suk Jin.
- What?
Me?
[Even he himself is shocked.]
[Completely unexpected!]
Suzy has a very unique side to her.
[Brings Suk Jin back since
they started the day out together.]
She's finally believing in
my unfailing love and loyalty to her.
[Member chance card-
Suzy brings Big-nose in.]
We will move onto the final mission
with the existing members.
You will be walking over
to your next mission site.
- Really?
- It's right over there.
- It's the department store.
- Where?
The first team to arrive at the store
will be given a useful advantage.
- Let's get going.
- Come on.
[In that case, it's time to run!]
- Are you sure this is the right way?
- Yes, this is the right way.
[Suzy is hot on Team Giraffe's trail.]
[Running through the city!]
Hurry!
[Team Giraffe is in the lead.]
I'm only 21 years old,
but I'm the slowest!
[Almost at their destination!]
[Team Giraffe is the first to arrive.]
What's this?
We're in big trouble now.
[What is their final mission?]
- What's this?
- Isn't this bell hide and go seek?
[All-kill bell hide and seek race.]
This is your final mission.
The ultimate Hallyu game.
All-kill bell name tag elimination.
[All-kill bell name tag elimination game.]
Even though Suzy's been on the show a lot,
she's never played the name tag elimination.
[First name tag elimination game for Suzy.]
I'll get rid of you first.
- Why are you saying that to her?
- That's because she's our opponent.
- You won't get away with it.
- It'll be split into two halves.
The two teams will take turns playing
the offense and defense side.
It'll be played in an all-kill style until
all the opposing members are eliminated.
We only have three members
on our team.
The team who eliminates the opponents in
the shortest amount of time wins the game.
[Shortest amount of time wins the race.]
You are free to roam between
the fourth and the seventh floor.
Five members really is...
Not only that, but they
also have Jong Kook on their team.
I haven't seen these bells in a long time.
I've never wanted to win anything
so badly as this in my entire life.
[A forceful way to show his support
to his star.]
- That's not it.
- Shut up!
[Gives the Giraffe a water shower
to stop him from complaining even further.]
- Aren't you my fans?
- This is so maddening.
Ugh, this is so maddening.
So the only plan is to drag this out
for as long as possible.
We can't stay together.
Let's drag this out until
those guys just give up.
- Until they give up and wants to go home.
- It won't be easy with those three.
Ten seconds until the attack.
[Ten seconds until the start of the race.]
Hiding around here won't be easy.
I think I'll hide right here.
Are you playing right now?
[It's been awhile since I've had to
film a race too...]
[All members of Team Suzy finish hiding.]
Start the attack!
We're going to have to start running.
Fourth through the seventh floor?
[You just wait!
We're coming for you!]
[Time is of the essence!]
Where are you going?
Come down one floor below.
Dong Hoon, he wants us to come down.
They could be hiding on the eighth floor.
- Aren't you the Hallyu star?
- Huh?
You want to start searching
from the seventh floor?
[Extreme state of nervousness.
First ever bell race for Suzy.]
I think I'm going to
run this way if I'm caught.
[Just then, Ha Ha comes down to
the fourth floor, where Suzy's hiding.]
I can hear the bell.
[First time experiencing the terror
of the bells.]
[Ha Ha is coming up to the room
where Suzy is hiding.]
[President Yoo is searching
through the toy department.]
[The sound of the bell is getting closer.]
[Blank Ji's hiding spot!]
[But Jae Suk just walks by it.]
I feel like I'm hearing an echo.
A constant echo of the bells.
[It's not an echo,
but it really is the sound of the bells.]
That wasn't it, right?
I think I'm hearing things.
[All the members are on edge from
not having played the game in so long.]
[Jae Suk is about to get on the elevator
after having passed by Blank Ji's hiding spot]
Where are they all hiding?
Should I just stay in the elevator?
I just won't stay in the same spot.
I'll constantly keep moving.
I'll just go back and forth.
What do you think?
That might not be a bad plan.
If I see anyone, then I'll just do this.
Like Jung Min did in his movie.
Come in.
All of you, come in.
I can just do it like this.
Right?
[Another man is hiding in the elevator.]
What's going on here?
This is really scary.
Did someone press the elevator button?
[That means someone must've
pressed the elevator button.]
[The whole Giraffe team.]
You can't all go around together like this.
[That's our race starter!
Big-nose is out!]
Ji Suk Jin, out.
[Gary barely manages to escape
the danger of the elevator.]
Ji Suk Jin, out.
Hey, I can't even find anyone.
[Since they're weak in man power,
they've decided to stay together.]
I think I hear something.
[Ha Ha goes in to search
through the kitchen area.]
[That's where Blank Ji was hiding!]
[But Ha Ha misses seeing her
and just passes her by!]
[Is he gone?]
[Ten years shaved off her life.]
[This time, Kwang-Star
walks towards Blank Ji.]
[Looks into the room once again.]
[Please... just go!]
[Startles each other!]
[Blank Ji is shocked.]
- I just looked in there.
- I saw you.
I just looked in there,
but I didn't even see anyone.
[Song Ji Hyo- Out.]
Song Ji Hyo, out.
[Hallyu Suzy lets her hair down.]
The reason why I let my hair down...
is so that it won't be as easy
for them to rip off my name tag.
Let them try to pull my hair out.
Kim Jong Kook might be hiding
in the emergency exit area.
[Searching through all the emergency exits.]
[As predicted!]
Jae Suk!
[Kwang-star discovers Mr. Capable.]
- Where?
- Up above!
Up above?
- Sixth or the seventh floor?
- Seventh floor!
Up above!
He's upstairs!
[Must corner Mr. Capable!]
[Looking for me?]
Kim Jong Kook is right here.
[Even though they're on the attack,
when it comes to Jong Kook...]
Look at what he's doing.
Can't you just let us eliminate you?
Come on, stop doing that
and just let us do it.
[It's three against one, right?]
[Not even able to budge.]
- Why are you doing this?
- Just let us go!
[The attack team is humiliated.]
- What is the matter with you?
- Seriously!
[Angry Tiger throws
the Giraffe down to the ground.]
[And similar service to his fans.]
Ha Ha, you know what the worst thing
about this whole thing is?
It's the fact that this is for real.
None of this is acted out.
He really made me crumble down
on the ground.
This is so maddening.
- This is making me mad.
- Let's go again on the count of three.
- We can do this!
- One, two, three.
[A full-on attack.]
[Muscle Tiger is surrounded.]
[The lives of these three are in danger.]
[Sounds of agony even after
having eliminated the Tiger.]
- Can't you just let us oust you?
- What?
- Must you really do all this?
- Why do you make us go through all this!
Seriously.
[Kim Jong Kook- Out.]
[Only two more left to go
before Team Suzy is ousted.]
[Jae Suk closes in on Suzy.]
[A nerve wrecking moment!]
[But he doesn't see Suzy and
just passes by her hiding spot.]
I don't think anyone's here.
[Uses this chance... to attempt an escape.]
[With Kwang Soo right in front.
Very bold Suzy!]
[But... he spots her fleeing tail!]
[Calls in members of his fan club
to take off on her trail.]
It's Suzy!
[Suzy desperately tries to hide.]
- She's around here somewhere.
- Who was it? Suzy?
[Positive that this is where she's hiding...]
There's Suzy!
- Hello.
- Hi Suzy.
I'm sorry, but there's no time.
No, don't do that!
Please don't do that, Suzy.
[Suzy does what she needs to
in order to ensure a win for her fan club.]
I'm sorry, Suzy.
[She tried to do what she could
to buy the team more time...]
- Where have you been hiding?
- You did a good job of hiding.
[Suzy's surprisingly good hiding skills.]
I only saw her because she
ran out of her hiding spot.
[Suzy's surprising transformation into
a hunter will soon be revealed.]
[No more time to waste!]
[Gary is the only one left to eliminate.]
- Jae Suk.
- What?
This light on the door indicates
that someone is in the room.
It says that the room is occupied.
[Darn!]
Don't you think that he's in there?
The light wouldn't be on otherwise.
The door was open earlier.
Open the door.
[No...]
I know that the door was
unlocked earlier.
[No matter how hard he tries
to keep it closed...]
[Excuse us.]
No!
Don't do this!
Gary's a really good hider.
- You almost had us.
- But the light was lit.
[Team Suzy's last survivor is caught.]
- The occupied light came on?
- The light was on.
- Why would the light turn on?
- I really had no idea you'd be here.
[The darn green light...]
[Onto the second half-
Time to switch the attack team.]
You need to know what this is all about
since you've never done this before.
I'll hold them down,
and you can rip off the tags.
It's actually quite fun.
Give it a try.
You're good at that.
You have to just rip it off like that.
I've only done it about two times myself.
[Suzy's highly anticipated hunting skills.]
Suzy, Suzy, fighting!
[Team Suzy's attack.]
[Faster time gets them the win!]
I hear the bells.
There are a lot of pretty clothes in here.
I need to get out of here
because I can't concentrate.
There are way too many pretty
clothes in here.
[Kkuk is on the search for
all the emergency exits.]
Emergency exit!
[As predicted, Ha Ha runs over
to the emergency exit.]
[Just then...]
[Makes a fast escape away
from the sound of the bell.]
[But he runs into a dead end!]
[Gary closes in on Ha Ha.]
[Decides to escape head on.]
[Where do you think you're going?]
Come here, let me see your back.
[Ha Ha is ousted within three minutes.
A record breaker!]
Sorry, I had no choice.
[With only three members on the team,
every single member is precious!]
Ha Ha, out.
[We're in trouble!]
[Already?]
[Hunter Suzy is getting fired up with
the announcement of the first elimination.]
[Suzy's on the sixth floor,
where Jae Suk and Kwang Soo are hiding.]
[The sound of the bell is getting closer...]
[But Suzy isn't about to let them get away!]
Suzy, just go.
Ji Hyo!
Over here!
Over here, Ji Hyo!
[Kwang-Star abandons his fan
to flee by himself.]
- Where?
- Over here in the elevator!
Which floor?
In the elevator!
[President Yoo also attempts
to make his escape.]
Why isn't this working!
[President Yoo can't let his star
go off on his own.]
[Suzy keeps her firm grasp on Jae Suk.]
Ji Hyo!
[Doesn't give up on her chase.]
- They're heading down!
- There they are!
Go up!
[Suzy corners Jae Suk onto the escalator.]
[Kkuk runs up the steps after
seeing Jae Suk at the top.]
[Suzy successfully eliminates
her very first name tag!]
Okay, only one more left to go.
[Suzy successfully corners
Jae Suk all by herself.]
Where did Kwang Soo go?
Where did he run off to?
- Here you go.
- Come on, Suzy!
You did great, Suzy.
This really isn't right.
I really hope that my star
remains alive.
[Jae Suk- Out.]
[Kwang-Star is the only remaining survivor!]
Turn off the light!
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
ran off at the same time, right?
They split up like this. Jae Suk
one way, and Kwang Soo, the other.
- Then where did Kwang Soo go?
- I think he went that way.
I'll go check the emergency exit areas.
I'll go check the other one.
Where could he be?
Kwang Soo, make it easy on yourself
and just surrender.
[Kwang-Star is hiding in the darkness of
the restaurant storage on the sixth floor.]
Can you not see me?
Where did he go?
[Suzy is headed up to the sixth floor,
where Kwang Soo is hiding.]
He ran up here, didn't he?
[Gary is also on the sixth floor.]
He ran up here...
and I saw him running across.
In there, I think.
[Not in any of the open rooms,
or in the hallways either.]
[Wait, that's the storage room
where Kwang Soo is hiding!]
Someone's coming!
I'm getting a weird vibe in here.
[Wait, those are... a pair of shoes?]
[Did I see it wrong?]
[Discovers a crumbled up figure of
Kwang Soo behind the curtain.]
How did you know that I was in here?
Come on, I'll let you go.
I won't eliminate you right now,
so follow me out here.
- Where are you taking me?
- I'm taking you out of here.
Just follow me.
So that's where you've been hiding?
You have nowhere to run anyway,
so just follow me.
[Attempts to talk to him
away from the eyes of others.]
[Once a traitor, always a traitor!]
[Shuts the door and runs!]
[Escapes into one of the dining rooms.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
Over here!
[Kwang Soo crawls under the table to hide.]
[Gary sets off again in search of Kwang Soo.]
- Which floor?
- Lee Kwang Soo's up here!
[All members of Team Suzy gathers
at the sound of Gary's voice.
- I should've just eliminated him.
- Gary.
He's up here somewhere.
- He's around here somewhere.
- Where is he?
Where did he go?
Is he in the emergency exit?
[All Kkuk's been talking about all day
are about the emergency exits.]
He was in the restaurant?
I'm sorry, President Yoo.
And to Director Ha Ha... I'm so very sorry.
But today is the last day of my fan club.
Kwang Soo.
[That door was definitely open earlier.]
Don't you think that he would've
went out this way?
[Please...]
I don't think he's in this restaurant, do you?
This is the only room he could be in.
I think he's in here.
- There he is.
- He's in there, isn't he?
He's in there, isn't he?
Jong Kook!
- No, just keep the door shut.
- We'll keep it shut.
[Keeps the tricky Giraffe locked up inside.]
[Calls for Jong Kook with
the Giraffe locked up in the room.]
- Where is he?
- In here.
[Jong Kook is on the way!]
[Doing whatever he can to get out.]
Come on and rip it off, Suzy.
[It's a battle against time.
Time to get the Giraffe.]
[Giraffe's attempt to escape
out the side door.]
[Time to end the battle.]
I'm sorry to all my fan club members!
[Hallyu star Suzy herself eliminates
minor star, Kwang Soo.]
- Is it over?
- It's all over.
It's over.
Here are the final results.
I will now reveal the time it took
to eliminate Team Kwang Soo.
- I don't think it even took 20 minutes.
- We were eliminated very quickly.
14 minutes and 16 seconds.
[Elimination time- 14 minutes and 16 seconds.]
[They lasted longer than expected.]
The time it took for Team Kwang Soo
to eliminate the members of Team Suzy was...
- Is it pretty close?
- It's in the tens.
In the tens?
[Could it be?]
19 minutes and 8 seconds.
[Team Giraffe- 19 minutes and 8 seconds.
Team Suzy- 14 minutes and 16 seconds.]
[Team Suzy wins!]
[Sorry, Kwang-Star...]
- Suzy's the best.
- You guys worked hard.
As a prize for winning,
Suzy will receive a trophy.
[A special gift for Suzy for winning
the Hallyu star race.]
- Is that real gold?
- This is huge!
[A gold trophy!]
Wow, that's pretty.
That's really pretty.
That's really befitting of a Hallyu star.
It's a pretty trophy.
Bae Suzy!
I will continue to work hard
as not to disappoint anyone.
Thank you, Suzy.
Let's all get old together.
[Yes, let's continue to see each other
for long time to come.]
Can Kwang-Star also say a word?
- Winning wasn't what was important.
- No, it was very important to us.
Why are we even bothering to do this
if winning isn't important?
You really are so maddening.
Congratulations to the winner of the race,
Bae Suzy!
Thank you!
[Wishing nothing but luck to our
very own Hallyu star, Suzy!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Idols of the nineties that took
the nation by storm.]
[They make their return
to the variety world!]
[HOT-Sechs Kies-g.o.d-NRG.
The original boy bands are here!]
[And the new idols!]
[SHINee, EXO, Sistar-
The new generation of idols.]
[Legends vs The new blood-
A match like you've never seen before.]
[Will it be the know-how of the originals,
or the passion of the new idols?]
[Must bring laughter if you want to win!]
We're not dead yet!
[Next Week on Running Man-
The return of the originals.]