[Tojeong Bigyeol- Fortune telling of
the past, present, and future.]
[During the Joseon Era, the
practice of fortune telling was founded.]
[Fortune telling became a common and
traditional event starting in the Joseon era.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Fluffy white snow,
falling down on the ground...]
[A cold, winter day.]
[Jae Suk steps out with
a single rose held in his hand.]
Are we going to be coupled off today?
[Jae Suk's partner is...]
[A top notch actress- Moon So Ri.]
[Choked up from the shock of seeing her.]
- For you, So Ri.
- Yes, nice to see you.
[Walking down the runway as a couple.]
I had no idea that you'd be
on the show.
[We're going to do this right.
How do we look together?]
- Are we going to be a couple today?
- I think so.
Why?
I'm... just so happy.
It's an honor.
[First couple of the day-
Jae Suk and So Ri.]
- Some of the older ladies came with me today.
- Older girls?
Is that right?
In that case...
I'm really happy to hear that.
[His reception of his partner is elevated
even more knowing the other ladies are older.]
- I'm the youngest one here today.
- Really? You're the youngest?
Is that really?
Then who's our next guest?
[Then who is Gary's partner,
whom So Ri says is older than her?]
Her hand gesture wasn't
the work of any amateur.
[Who is Gary's aggressively forward partner?]
[The sexually charged female is...
Uhm Jung Hwa.]
[Her sexy catwalk,
befitting of Korea's 'Madonna'.]
Hi.
[The sexy couple- Jung Hwa and Gary.]
Is he my partner?
I love Gary.
I can't believe how light she is!
- Hey, Gary.
- Yes?
Congratulations.
Congratulations on being
coupled off with Jung Hwa.
- Are you disappointed?
- No way! Why would I be disappointed?
- I'm the 'Sexy Queen'.
- Yes, I'm well aware of that.
Next guest, please come on out.
[Who will be on the receiving end
of Kkuk's rose?]
[The queen of charisma- Jo Min Soo.]
- I can't believe it's Jo Min Soo!
- Thank you. Thank you so much!
[Min Soo's rare variety show guest appearance
is a shock to everyone.]
Why did she have to keep saying
that she's the youngest one here?
She's not that young.
It was really offensive for me
to hear her say all that.
- Don't say things like that about her.
- Thank you so much!
[Min Soo's enigmatic personality which flips
back to that of a young, youthful girl.]
Can you two pose together for a shot?
[The woman's charisma has Mr. Capable
frozen up like a block of ice.]
Let's welcome our next guest.
[Ha Ha and Ji Hyo are coupled off,
so who's Big-nose's partner to be?]
[A large hand.]
If that's a woman, then that's her foot.
[Who's Big-nose's partner
behind the curtain?]
What is this?
- Why?
- Here, take this.
[You did say that you wanted
the Best Couple Award...]
Didn't you know? You and I
are the icing on the cake today.
It's really nice to meet you.
[Big-nose gives his rose to Min Soo.]
- You're going to ignore Uhm Jung Hwa?
- I've always been a huge fan of hers.
- He's always been a huge fan of yours.
- Yes, I am.
- Thank you.
- We're all big fans of hers.
Today's the Lunar New Year.
- Yes, it is.
- Happy New Year to all our viewers.
[Happy New Year]
Before we start today's race...
you're aware that many people go to have their
fortune told at the start of the new year?
Many people are going to have
their fortune told lately.
That's why we have prepared a chance for
all of you to have your fortunes told as well.
[Running Man 2014 Fortune Telling.]
We have a fortune telling expert
getting ready to read your fortunes.
We're going to move to a different location
of the building.
Please keep in mind that the fortune
that you're told
will have a deep and meaningful correlation
to the race that will go on today.
- Is the fortune telling for real?
- Of course.
- It's time for everyone to move inside.
- Let's go inside.
[What kind of destiny awaits the
Running Man members in the new year?]
[Walks into a room where a fortune telling
expert awaits them.]
[Lee Yoo Jong- Fortune Teller]
- Hello.
- Hello, Sir.
You'll have your fortunes told
one by one.
- We'll start with you.
- Me?
- Come take a seat.
- Fighting.
- Then we can listen to his fortune?
- I think we all standby and watch.
Are they all going to stay here
and watch me as my fortune gets read?
- Who cares?
- Why are you trying to hide it?
- But to have them here...
- We want to know what'll happen in your life.
Yoo Jae Suk...
[Yoo Jae Suk's new year fortune.]
- The energy that you've been born with...
- Yes?
Of the five elements, you've
been born with the energy of 'Geum'.
- Geum?
- Doesn't that mean, 'knowledge'?
Geum?
I can't be home on Fridays.
('Geum-yo-il= Friday')
You have a strong drive, and an iron will.
And there's also an
instinctive chivalry within you as well.
[Chivalrous Jae Suk.]
But he does have a bit of a temper.
Yes, he does have a bit of that.
People with a higher outlook,
or view in life...
they tend to be looked upon as
natural leaders of others.
I see those characteristics of you
in your fortune.
And when I look at your life line,
between the ages of 34 and 40...
those seven years of life are a time for you to
earn great honor and reputation for yourself.
Then will his life decline after that?
- How could you say such a thing?
- His decline will mean our own decline.
- You're trying to steal his limelight.
- Stop saying things like that.
The years between the ages of
34 and 40...
even though you may have built a great
reputation for yourself...
you may also find some problems arise
that can try to shake up your success.
- But that's already in the past.
- That's already past?
So that dangerous pitfall in your life is
already in the past.
What I can say to you about
your fortune is
you've been born with a very strong,
and solid fortune in your life...
Just like how a large ship cannot be
destroyed by a small wave.
You have the fortune to withstand and
endure most hardships you'll come across.
You won't be easily ruined or destroyed.
Fortune that you've been born with...
You've been born with luck in
both women and money.
From what I've seen,
he doesn't have any luck with women.
Can't you stay quiet?
He's reading my fortune right now.
He has his wife, whom he's
very lucky to have found.
Since you've been born with
luck in women and money...
you will always find yourself lucky in both
of those categories for the rest of your life.
And even your fortune for the new year
seems very strong and solid.
So you'll find that you'll be successful
no matter what you decide to get involved in.
- So just keep on doing what you're doing.
- Okay.
Don't get involved in any joint ventures
until you reach the age of 45.
He keeps wanting me to
start something with him.
- You heard what he said, didn't you?
- Then we'll start after you turn 45.
It would be wise for you to avoid getting
yourself involved in any joint ventures.
That's how your fortune reads.
And as for your fortune for the next year...
[Jae Suk's fortune for 2014.]
If you're planning on expanding your family,
I see that this is the year for it to happen.
[This is the year for him
to expand his family.]
[Will this be the year for your second baby?]
- You see that happening this year?
- Yes, I see that happening this year.
You also show prosperity in offspring,
so the more you have, the better you'll be.
[Prosperity in children-
More he has, better off he'll be.]
I'll work hard to have as many children
as I possibly can.
As for your lucky sign for the new year
I see that the best sign for you this year
is the Dragon, Dog, Sheep, and Bull.
- I'm a Dog.
- I'm the Bull. We have to stick together.
[Dragon and the Bull.]
[And Gary is... 'Gae'?]
(Gae=Dog.)
Thank you, Sir.
[The end of Jae Suk's fortune telling.]
[Next up is, Moon So Ri.
What will her fortune say?]
[Moon So Ri's new year fortune.]
Look at me.
Look at me straight in the face.
[Innocent So Ri seems to be nervous
about having her fortune read.]
I had no idea that he'd read
so deep into my fortune.
As for Moon So Ri...
When you were born...
you were born with a very strong
energy surrounding you.
The energy that's surrounding you
is very strong, but it's not bad energy.
You were born with a very
auspicious energy surrounding you.
For example, I see that
you're a very eloquent speaker.
You have the ability to make others melt
with the words that you speak.
- So I make others melt?
- Yes, you do.
- And also... there's nobility about you.
- Nobility?
[Seems to be very happy to hear
her fortune.]
Yes, this is making me very
happy to hear it.
Yes, this is all true.
I can also see that there's something
that you're not very happy about right now.
If you're unhappy about something,
you have to let it out.
You have the tendency to bottle
all your worries and unhappiness inside.
If you do that,
you'll suffer from emotional distress.
Yes, I have suffered from bouts of
emotional distress ever since I was little.
You've been suffering from emotional distress
since you were little?
I've always suffered from congenital
emotional distress syndrome.
If you're ever unhappy about something,
you have to let it all out.
Keeping it all bottled up inside
is not good for you.
I wish I could do that too.
- I'll try my best to do that.
- You have to do that.
If I look back at the life
that you've led...
I see that you've had to deal with
a lot of various different situations.
Those situations that you've been dealing with
will peak between the ages of 33 and 41.
Those nine years...
will be extremely difficult.
Will be extremely difficult.
[Difficult...]
Your fortune in general isn't bad,
but there are good and bad parts about it.
- Even though you've had some changes...
- I feel like I'm going to cry.
Let it all out!
Don't bottle it up inside!
She really must be dealing with some stuff.
[Having had to deal with many twists
and turns in her life...]
- But this winter will be the last of it.
- It's all over then?
No, this year will be the last.
You just have to endure it for another year.
One more year of suffering,
and it'll all be over.
[Words that truly bring comfort to her heart
which has been suffering for so many years.]
- So Ri is really...
- Please don't cry.
This is a variety show.
- I really didn't mean to...
- I don't know what her situation may be...
- She must be dealing with some stuff.
- Yes, I think you're right.
This may make it seem like my life is
very difficult, but that's not the case.
- I really am happy.
- Yes, I hope so.
[Yes, we know.]
I really am happy with my wonderful husband,
and our beautiful baby together.
But the difficulties that I see
are not apparent in your face.
I only see it in your fortune.
That's why once you get through
this year...
I see that you'll be rid of the heavy burden
that you've had to carry all these years.
So rest your worries.
The biggest attribute I see in your fortune...
is your husband.
You just need to follow your husband's lead
and do as he says.
If you do,
you'll be gifted with much happiness.
I bet her husband will be very happy
to hear this when he watches the show.
I bet he'll be sitting on the couch
slapping his knees in agreement.
I'll be very good to my husband.
[Wishing you two a lifetime of happiness.]
[What will Suk Jin's fortune
for the new year say?]
[Ji Suk Jin's new year fortune.]
He really loves investing his money.
His history in money investing
truly is turbulent.
- No crying, okay?
- Okay.
Can someone hand us a box of tissue?
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Yes.
- You've been very lucky with your wife.
- My wife?
Yes, his wife is really wealthy.
- His wife is really wealthy.
- Why are you even mentioning that?
So his wife is wealthier than him?
- You're lucky with women.
- Yes, I think you're right.
- Your wife is full of wisdom.
- Yes, that's very true.
Don't let your eyes stray elsewhere.
[Warns him to always keep his eyes
focused on his wife only.]
My focus is on my family,
and my family only.
Since your fortune shows that
you have a lot of luck with women
it's very possible that you have female
friends, even though you may not date them.
[Hm?]
[His fortune shows that he has
a lot of 'female friends'.]
[That's not what I meant.]
- I don't mean relationship-wise.
- Ah, friends?
People of the opposite sex can be friends.
I'm saying that if you have a lot of women
in your life as friends...
they will become of help to you in your life.
So I'm saying that you should have
those women in your life as friends.
[Meaning that the female friends that he has
in his life will be a positive addition.]
- So I need to keep them around?
- That's not exactly what I'm saying.
I'm just saying that they'll naturally
come into your life.
That's the kind of luck I see you'll have
with women in your life.
And also...
When I take a look at your fortune
for the year 2014...
I see that you could be mistaken into
thinking that this could be your year.
[A deep misunderstanding...]
He has a way with his words.
Let's just aim for next year, Suk Jin.
- Thank you.
- Why are you trying to end it already?
Your reading isn't over yet!
Just stay seated exactly where you are.
I already heard my fortune.
Thank you, sir.
[I love you, my sweet wife.]
[What will Sexy Queen,
Jung Hwa's fortune say?]
[Uhm Jung Hwa's new year fortune.]
- Uhm Jung Hwa.
- I'm so nervous.
Uhm Jung Hwa... you're a born worker.
[A born worker.]
[Darn!]
That's what she said
she was most afraid to hear.
Moon So Ri was told that she was
born with nobility in her.
[Jung Hwa- Born worker.
So Ri- Born nobility.]
First of all, whether you like it or not,
you're always surrounded by work.
If I were to take a look
at your relationship aspect...
[And the most important part...]
[Love and relationship aspect.]
- That's very important.
- That's what she wants to hear the most.
I really hope that it's a good fortune.
[The younger spectators are feeling
the desperation even more than she is.]
I see that there are always a lot of
love and relationship prospects around you.
Around ages 40 and 45...
I see your desire to have children.
The desire in you to have children...
has already passed.
[Her desire to have children
has already passed?]
It's already passed?
[Since you're such a
young-hearted Sexy Queen...]
- Please take another look!
- It's already passed?
I really love babies lately.
Any relationship that comes into your life
from this moment on
you need to be very clear
about where you stand with those.
[She herself needs to be very clear about what
she wants if she wants to get married.]
- Your wealth isn't in the movies.
- Why not in the movies?
- You're being so greedy.
- You're plenty successful as is!
Your fortune states that you yourself
are responsible for your own wealth.
Your career in movies will be successful
when you meet the right man.
[Wealth will be up to her own abilities, and
the right man will bring success with movies.]
So if you want to live your life
like those that you see in the movies
you will have to meet
your husband in the near future.
But I don't have anyone.
- What are you talking about?
- You have one right here.
[Jung Hwa's man of destiny... is Kkuk?]
If you two get together,
your lives will be like a movie.
[The truth is...
Jong Kook's fortune earlier...]
You need to meet a woman
with bigger eyes.
- Woman with big eyes?
- Yes.
Meeting a woman with a big set of eyes
will be a great match for you.
It's because your eyes are too small.
Woman who's eyes are as big as a Shih Tzu?
- Why are you using a Shih Tzu as comparison?
- Shih Tzu's have big eyes.
[Or the cartoon character, Candy?]
That's right.
I have big eyes!
[Jung Hwa and Kkuk seems to be
the ideal match.]
- Also...
- I'm not going to lose him.
As for the sign of your ideal match, he
needs to be either a Dragon, Horse, Sheep...
He's the Dragon sign!
[Kkuk is the sign of the Dragon!]
You're the sign of the dragon?
[A match made in heaven.]
Since they are your ideal match,
if you meet anyone of any of those signs...
- You need to take a closer look at them.
- Okay.
Your fortune for the new year
looks pretty good overall.
[We hope that you meet
your match in the new year!]
[And lastly, it's Kwang Soo's turn.
His first time getting his fortune told.]
[The members' fortune telling time.
A meaningful correlation to today's race!]
[Lee Kwang Soo's new year fortune.]
When I take a look at your fortune...
I see that you're a very generous
and tolerant person.
And you are a man of beauty and grace.
[A man of beauty and grace?]
You are as sturdy as a tree.
Look at how long and elongated you are.
[Loooong.]
- Is that a good thing?
- That means that you're very generous.
Many scholars have a similar physique.
People who have similar statures
are usually scholars.
You show a very good characteristic.
[Kwang Soo is known for his kind,
and good natured personality.]
- Many people are jealous of you.
- All these guys are jealous of me!
- It's so frustrating!
- Some may say that you're nerdy.
Some may say that you're nerdy.
What do you mean, I'm nerdy?
No, I'm not nerdy!
Yes, I'm sure he's heard that before.
What I mean is, you may be called that,
but that's not the truth.
That's not the truth at all.
- You don't have a fickle personality.
- That's very true about him.
No matter what may be going on around you,
you're not prone to changes.
- You're very true to yourself.
- Yes, he never ceases to betray.
You just need to keep being that way.
Another thing is...
Your character shows a strong
sense and ability for regrowth.
- New business ventures are in your future.
- Business ventures?
Let's start a business together.
Then he should stop being in the
entertainment industry and go for business?
That's a whole separate issue.
- He said, go for business.
- That's a separate issue.
What I'm saying is...
You need to wait until you're at least
36 years old before you start any business.
Right now isn't the time.
You'll be completely ruined if you do it now.
[It seems as though starting a business now
is the worst thing that he could do.]
[They have selective hearing with
only the words that they want to hear.]
- Please listen carefully. I'm trying to help.
- Yes, I understand.
So just keep doing what you're doing
until you reach the age of 35.
Don't deviate from what you're doing now,
and just keep doing the work you're doing now.
Once you reach the age of 35,
things will change, do what you want then.
You can do your business ventures then.
Just wait until then.
Things that are related to your current
job industry will be fine.
You could say that doing something in that
field would be the best option for you.
You're saying that this is the best
he'll get, right?
[He wants to go even higher in his field...]
- So this is the best he can do?
- Not any higher than where he is now.
Then of all the fortunes that you've read,
who has the best fortune of all of us?
[Who has the best fortune
out of the group?]
- Jae Suk?
- Yes, Yoo Jae Suk.
He's been born with such good fortune.
- Just as I thought.
- That's such a relief.
That's a relief for all of us.
Why are you relieved to hear about my fortune?
You each have your own fortunes.
- You have your own fortunes.
- Your fortune is important to all of us.
That's the best thing we've heard all day.
His success means our own success.
Then we can feel reassured for our own
future for the rest of the year.
- We're all set!
- Thank you, sir.
As you've been told before,
you all listened carefully to your fortunes?
I will now explain today's race which is
directly correlated to the fortune telling.
First...
- You're giving us something?
- We all get something?
[They're all handed something...]
[A gold ring?]
Why do I have to wear
a couple ring with Suk Jin?
Your work never ends, Jung Hwa.
You've been told that you're a worker.
- A natural born worker.
- I'm a worker.
Today's race is...
It's a Partner of Destiny Special.
With the fortune that you all
got to hear about yourselves...
We have had the compatibility fortune read
of all our members and our guest members.
[They have been partnered up with the people
whom their fortune is most compatible with?]
[Find the person whom you're
most compatible with!]
That means that there's a couple amongst us
who are more compatible than anyone else.
Then it would be two males as well?
[It could be a couple of the same sex.]
Then that means it's going to be
Jong Kook and Jung Hwa like the fortune said.
I'm told that there's
wealth within me, Jong Kook.
So here's your mission for the day.
Guess who each member is most compatible
with to create five sets of couples.
[Guess the five couples who's fortune and
destiny are most compatible.]
[Board the train of destiny
and succeed the mission as a group.]
[They'll be given a hint as to who the
couples are whenever they succeed a mission.]
You must guess all five couples correctly
once you arrive at the final destination
in order for you to succeed the mission.
[Must guess all five couple correctly
in order to succeed the mission!]
- We have to correctly guess all the couples.
- I wonder who my destined partner is?
[Just who could be my own partner
of destiny?]
If you can correctly guess all the couples,
then you get to keep your gold rings.
Ah... we have to guess them all correctly?
You will have to return the ring if you get
even a single couple wrong.
[Must return the ring
if their guess is incorrect.]
In order to see how compatible you are
with others in the group
you'll be given a chance to swap your
partners with each mission.
- Really?
- Then we're all doing this as a team.
[A match made in heaven race.]
Then let's all work well together so that
we can all succeed together in the end.
[For the gold ring!]
I'll bring home the gold, Honey!
- It's been a while since we took the train.
- It really has been a while.
But... where are we going
on this train?
[A romantic train ride
on this snowy winter day.]
Train station on a snowy day...
It's really romantic.
- But it's so cold.
- It really is cold.
- It's romantic, but it's still cold.
I'm so cold!
[Nine minutes left until their departure.]
Don't you think that we should go and
get some snacks for the train ride?
- Should we go get some snacks?
- Yes, let's go.
- Can we go get some hamburgers?
- Let's do it by team.
- Okay, let's do it by teams.
- And you have to pay with your own money.
- We'll do it in teams.
- I don't have any money on me.
You have to figure that out for yourself.
Borrow the money if you have to.
- Someone from each team needs to step up.
- I'm not good at Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- You're not good? Then step up.
- What are you doing?
- That's why we want you to play.
- If you're not good at it, then step up.
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
[Ji Hyo, Jung Hwa, and Min Soo win!]
- It's not us!
- I thought you had good luck!
We still have a chance.
Don't worry about it.
[Jae Suk and So Ri vs.
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo.]
[Jae Suk and So Ri to go buy the snacks.]
[Eight minutes left until their departure.
Not much time left, so they must hurry!]
- Hamburger!
- And french fries too!
[They all want different things!
Shouting out their orders.]
- So Ri... you should have done it.
- I don't even eat hamburgers.
- Now I have to get burgers?
- Really? You don't eat them?
What time is our flight, did you say?
- Don't act bashful.
- What time did you say was our train?
- What time?
- It's been delayed by three minutes.
[The snow delays the train by three minutes.
This delay will soon cause a shocking event.]
[Jae Suk and So Ri are at a hotdog stand
inside the train station.]
- Are you okay with Americano?
- Yes.
- I like those too.
- Which ones?
Beer can?
[So Ri is more of a can of beer type.]
Yes, hot Americano.
- They won't leave without us, will they?
- Of course not.
I'm sorry, but we're in a bit of a hurry.
Actually, Kim Jong Kook doesn't eat
things like this.
Then we only need seven hotdogs.
[Not even counting the health-nut,
Jong Kook in his order.]
[Just then...]
[The train pulls up at the station!]
They're seriously not back yet?
[What do they do?]
[Jae Suk and So Ri must hurry!]
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Have a nice day!
[Finally on their way back
after getting the snacks!]
- This isn't our train, is it?
- No, this is our train.
[But the snack team is still
nowhere to be seen!]
Is the train here yet?
- They seriously aren't back yet.
- Are we really going to leave without them?
[Will Jae Suk and So Ri get left behind?]
- There they are.
- They're here! Run!
[They arrive just in time
for the train's departure!]
Come on, you need to hurry!
[Close call,
but even So Ri makes it back on time.]
We could've been in big trouble.
Any later, and we would've missed our train.
[A close call right from
the start of the mission.]
[They would've missed the train if the snow
hadn't delayed the train by three minutes.]
[The train departs as soon as
they board.]
- A pretty romantic train ride, isn't it?
- Yes, it's nice.
[A romantic train ride on a snowy day.]
- The train will stop at the Yongsan Station.
- Yongsan Station?
You must get off at the station,
and complete the mission with your partner
and get back on the train as soon as
you've completed the mission.
- We have to get back after the mission.
- If you don't make it back on the train...
- we will be leaving without you.
- Seriously?
All members have to make it back on the train
within the time limit in order for it to count
and for us to give you your hints.
Kwang Soo is usually the one to get
left behind in such situations.
If not me, then usually it's you.
Since we all need the clue,
we all need to succeed together as a team.
[It's a group mission where
they all have to succeed equally.]
- You all need to wear these couple gloves.
- We need to wear them together?
[Rule- They all must wear the couple gloves
together at all times.]
Everyone must put the gloves on right now.
Here are the missions that
you all need to do at the next station.
- Which number?
- Number five.
[Each couple to choose their own missions.]
- We haven't received ours yet.
- Don't look at your missions yet.
You can't open the mission envelopes yet.
Why not?
Is this a joke?
She's getting mad.
So we have to do everything as you say?
Is that it?
All day?
- Say something if you're angry.
- We have to do as he says all day?
I just realized that we've been doing
everything as he says.
- Like putting these gloves on for example.
- Are you mad again?
I'm slowly starting to get a little angry.
- I have to keep doing as he says?
- She really suits Jong Kook very well.
Because Jong Kook is always getting
angry at everything too.
[The angry couple.]
I feel like it's Jong Kook talking
in a woman's voice.
- I'm just asking because I don't know.
- Jong Kook is exactly like you.
- You're a female Jong Kook.
- I'm sorry.
[Yongsan Station-
One minute before the train's arrival.]
- You may open your envelopes now.
- Open it now?
Open it up.
I really hope it's something easy.
- We can open it now?
- What is it?
[Oh my...]
[Everyone's looking a bit lost.]
We have to get a camera out of a locker, and
take a picture with the station in the back.
We have to find money from a locker and
eat green tea noodles and green tea ice cream.
- Seriously?
- Where's the locker?
We have to get money from an ATM and
buy 5 Americanos and 5 caramel macchiato.
- What about you, Gary? What's your mission?
- Me?
We have to find our money from a locker,
and get instant proof of a picture taken.
Your mission is similar to ours.
What about you, Min Soo?
What's your mission?
We have to find our money and buy
four books with 'Fortune Teller' in the title.
We have to get out money from ATM first.
[Train arrives at Yongsan Station.]
You have nine minutes to finish
your mission.
- That's enough time to succeed your mission.
- Let's all succeed our missions!
[Just complete the mission and board
the train within nine minutes!]
[The train will depart
at exactly five o'clock!]
[The door opens...
and everyone must hurry!]
[Run!]
We have to go work, Jung Hwa!
- We have to go work!
- I'm sick and tired of working!
We're two guys and
we're the slowest, Suk Jin.
[They all must hurry to their lockers,
and their ATM's!]
[Into the station!]
[Angry couple,
Jong Kook and Min Soo are in the lead!]
- Where are the ATM's?
- They're over there!
[Everyone goes their own way
to complete their missions.]
[Get 50,000 won out of the ATM and buy
four books with 'Fortune Teller' in the title.]
[Get 50,000 out of the ATM and buy
5 Americano and 5 caramel macchiato coffees.]
0207.
- 50,000 won, right?
- Yes, 50,000 won.
[Both teams withdraw
50,000 won from the ATM.]
We got it.
[The rest of the teams find their way
over to the lockers.]
[Get their money from locker D-51 and
get an instant proof of picture taken.]
[Get money from locker A-13.
Buy and eat green tea noodles and ice cream.]
- Where are the 'C' lockers?
- I don't see them.
Where are the 'C' lockers?
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo can't even
find their locker.]
We're in big trouble.
Let's ask someone.
- Help us find our locker!
- Where are the lockers?
[The time is ticking by...]
[Two minutes have already passed.]
Let's go find a coffee stand.
Hold my hand.
[Jae Suk and So Ri are first
to get their money.]
- Where can we find our coffee?
- That stand might have it.
They don't have Americano.
Caramel macchiato?
- Where are we going to find it?
- They have it here.
Hello. We need five Americanos,
and five caramel macchiato.
[Rush order of five Americanos,
and five caramel macchiato.]
- Here's the money.
- Here's 30,000 won.
There's 30,000 won.
- Thank you.
- Can I get a receipt for that?
[Frugal house wife still remembering to
get the receipt at a time like this.]
Thank you.
- Give us five minutes.
- Five minutes?
- Yes, okay.
- Put them in a carrier please.
Our train takes off in five minutes.
Please get us the coffees
within three minutes.
I'm sorry.
- There it is!
- Where?
[Discovers the
green tea refreshment stand.]
- Ma'am... we need one green tea noodles...
- And one green tea ice cream.
- One soft serve green tea ice cream.
- Very little broth with the noodles.
[Speedy serving of the noodles.]
I'm going to take the gloves off for a second.
- It's not cooked yet.
- Just open it up.
I wonder if we can do this.
There it is.
Let's eat the ice cream first.
[Even the ice cream is served
at the speed of light.]
Wow, that's cold.
We have to eat it quickly.
[Meanwhile...]
[Easy Brothers are still
looking for their locker.]
Do you think that
this mission is even possible?
I'm sure they've already tried it.
- The photo booth is over there!
- Where?
- Over there to the front.
- We have to find our locker!
'C' lockers... here they are.
[Go outside to take a picture of themselves
with the station in the background.]
[They have to go outside for the picture
when they don't even have the time.]
Where?
Where is it?
There it is!
- There!
- Come on.
[Gary and Jung Hwa find
the instant photo booth.]
How do we do this?
Should I go inside?
It won't accept a 10,000 won bill.
[10,000 won bill won't fit.
Must put in two 5,000 won bills.]
10,000 won.
Try it one more time.
- Why wouldn't it fit?
- Right here.
It won't work.
[Off to the convenience store to
get smaller change.]
[Easy Brothers are finally headed
outside the building for their picture.]
[Gary and Jung Hwa are back with
their smaller bills.]
[Jung Hwa heads into the booth first.]
- Is it not going in?
- Why isn't it going in?
We should've gotten change for
another 10,000 won.
[There's no time!
It's more than 5,000 won per person!]
We have to shut the curtain.
You have to look straight ahead.
Okay, I got it.
Are you done, Jung Hwa?
[Still have to make sure that my picture
comes out looking pretty.]
- Jung Hwa!
- I have to take another picture.
- It takes two pictures.
- Seriously?
We will now take the second picture.
I said, I got it.
[But still a pro when it comes to
getting her picture taken.]
All set?
Let's go get some more change.
[Off to get some more change.]
- Where? Do you see it?
- Over here.
[Three minutes have passed.
Only six minutes left on the clock.]
[Jong Kook and Min Soo find a bookstore
with their money in hand.]
- 'Fortune Teller'...
- We need books with those words in the title.
- You have to find the books yourselves.
- We have to find the books ourselves?
[Thank you, Miss Clerk, for your quick wit.]
[Find four books with each of
the letters within the title!]
[Where are you...]
- 'To-jung-bi-gyeol'. I'm going to lose it.
-  'To-jung-bi-gyeol'.
-  'To-jung-bi-gyeol'...
- Oh my goodness. I don't see any.
[Harder to see anything
when they're in such a rush.]
Did they hide it somewhere in
the corner?
[In the meantime...
the time keeps on ticking.]
[They're finally outside!
Must see the station name for it to count.]
[Click, click... jump, and click.]
One of those shots had to have
turned out okay?.
I hope we got at least one.
Keep taking pictures.
We're going to have to...
The first picture isn't even developed yet.
- What's going on here.
- Suk Jin!
[He drops one of the pictures on the ground!]
Take another one.
The picture isn't even developing.
[Only thing they can do
is to keep taking pictures.]
Are you capturing the name
of the station in the background?
[Are they capturing
the name of the station?]
- 'To-jung-bi-gyeol'...
- I don't see anything.
I don't see it...
Here's one! I found one.
Did you find 'Jung'?
I can't believe how tough it is
to find these books!
['Jung' is checked off the list.]
We've got 'Jung' and 'Gyeol'.
You're good at finding those.
Here.
I found a book with 'Bi'.
- We just need something with 'To'.
- That's all we need to find?
[They'll succeed their mission if they can
find a book with 'To' in the title!]
[Looking for a book with all the letters
in the title instead.]
- Here?
- Look here for a 'To-jung-bi-gyeol' book.
[Gary and Jung Hwa head back to the
photo booth after getting some more change.]
Where's my picture?
Your picture should be coming out now.
It's coming out now, isn't' it?
Yeah, I got it.
The screen isn't back up yet.
- Okay, it's working.
- Wow, the picture came out so pretty.
Okay, we're good to go.
[They just need to get
Gary's picture taken now.]
[Awkward]
Come on, hurry!
Let's take one more.
[The Green tea couple on the other hand
is still screaming out sounds of agony.]
[Eat the cold ice cream...]
[And eat the hot, and uncooked noodles.]
Ji Hyo, want to switch?
Let's switch for a little bit.
The noodles are crunchy like cookies.
- So hot!
- The noodles are still really crunchy.
[So cold!]
But the ice cream still tastes really good.
[Noodles... with ice cream as the topping.]
We're done with the ice cream.
[Ice cream is all done!]
[There's no time!]
[Let's run with the bowl of noodles in hand!]
[Finish drinking the broth on their way!]
- Hey, drink some of this.
- Why is this door opening so slow?
[Run three steps,
and take a sip of the broth.]
- Come on, Jae Suk!
- Thank you.
- We still need four more drinks.
- Are you guys done?
- Those guys are done with their mission.
- Four more drinks.
[Feeling even more anxious as they see
another team pass them by.]
It's okay if the Americano is watery.
Make it really weak if it'll be faster.
Please don't make us miss our train.
[Jong Kook and Min Soo only need to find
one more book with 'To' in the title.]
'To-jung-bi-gyeol'!
It's right here!
[They succeed in finding four books with each
of the 'To-jung-bi-gyeol' letters in the title.]
[Jong Kook and Min Soo clear their mission.]
Are we all done?
Let's go.
[Gary and Jung Hwa also succeed
their mission.]
[They need to hurry and
get back on the train!]
- Thank you.
We're sorry for causing so much
inconvenience.
- Have a great day. Sorry again!
- Thank you!
[Jae Suk and So Ri succeed in buying
their ten cups of coffee.]
[Back to the train platform!]
[Will the train of destiny still be there?]
We're all finished!
Here, give it to me.
I can carry those books.
[Run!]
[Miss the train, and they'll be left stranded!]
[First place- Ha Ha and Ji Hyo.]
[Second place- Jong Kook and Min Soo.]
[These two teams make it safely
back to the train platform.]
[Oh?]
[But...]
[The train... is nowhere to be seen?]
The train must've left.
[That's strange...]
[We know we definitely
made it back within the time limit...]
[Just what is going on here?]
[Right before they
made it back to the platform.]
[The platform suddenly seems to be
full of activity?]
[Then...]
What are you guys doing?
[The train doors suddenly close!]
Why is the train moving?
The train is leaving.
[Even the crew members who were still
aboard the train are flustered and confused.]
[The train... is leaving?]
[They find out with the train having been
delayed three minutes earlier...]
[The train leaves this station three minutes
earlier to keep up with the initial schedule.]
If the teams make it back
by five o'clock...
[How can this be?]
Everyone gather over here for now.
[Gary, Jung Hwa, Jae Suk, and So Ri
also make it back to the platform.]
- The train isn't here.
- Run!
- The train isn't here!
- You guys have to run!
- Where's the train!
- Why isn't the train here?
[Since they were given nine minutes,
make it by five o'clock, and it's a success!]
We're still missing one team?
The male team isn't here.
- Isn't this it?
- You can't see the station sign.
[The pictures are
finally starting to develop.]
- What is this?
- It's a good picture of us though.
- This isn't good either.
- I'm going to keep this picture.
[You like the picture?]
The train was supposed to be
here for nine minutes.
You were supposed to board back on the train
after succeeding your missions in 9 minutes.
But what's going on right now is, since
the previous train was delayed by 3 minutes
our current train left three minutes
prior to its scheduled time.
They left three minutes earlier to catch up
to the time that they've lost.
Then what happens to us?
We don't have a train?
So what we've decided to do is,
just like the time that we've figured on...
four of the five teams have made it back
within the time that you initially were given.
- Is it showing?
- Can you see the station sign?
[Everyone made it back with
the exception of this team.]
Okay.
Did you get the picture?
- Okay. Thank you.
- Grab my hand, Suk Jin.
[Everyone will succeed their mission
if only this team can make it back on time.]
If even one team doesn't make it back on time,
then all of you will fail your missions.
- Kwang Soo.
- That's the only team that we're missing.
[Run... run... run!]
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
- Min Soo found all the books.
[Everyone's fate is riding
on the Easy Brothers.]
[They must make it back before
the clock hits 5:01.]
There they come!
- Hurry!
- Run!
[They're finally here!]
There are only a few seconds left!
Hurry!
- Hurry!
- Run!
[Min Soo is showing her competitive side.]
[Everyone's back on the platform!]
We had to take a picture with the
station sign in the background.
[Will they be able to earn their hint?]
- You failed your mission.
- Why?
Do you all see the current time?
Do you all see the time?
[Five o'clock was the deadline.
But it's now 5:02.]
You were only going to succeed if all
five teams made it back within nine minutes.
But one team didn't make it back on time.
What's so hard about your mission
that you couldn't be back in time?
You have no idea how hard it was to get
the station sign in the background.
- What's so hard about that?
- It took four minutes for it to develop.
- The pictures took forever to come out.
- We had to wait for it to come out.
- You should've kept on taking it.
- We did keep taking pictures.
- You should've done a better job.
- It takes four minutes for it to develop.
- We couldn't just take anything.
- You should've been quicker about it.
- You guys should've been faster about it.
- You guys are all being very cranky!
How long have you been on this show
for you to be that slow?
You should've just taken a bunch of pictures
since you know it'll develop sooner or later.
- You should've been quicker about it.
- We did our best.
I'm not going to hold back any longer.
Remember what she was told?
She's not to hold back on her anger.
[After having her fortune read,
So Ri will no longer hold back her anger!]
We do have another train coming.
[Will be on their way on the next train.]
- We need to talk.
- What is there to talk about?
[Scolded by the whole team.]
[On standby until the next train arrives.]
Even though you've all failed due to
Lee Kwang Soo and Ji Suk Jin...
- Yes, you do need to blame them.
- However...
Since the train left without us and all,
we will still give you one hint.
We were going to give out three hints
if they also made it back on time.
- Yes, we need to get at least one.
- We're sorry.
We were initially going to give out three.
Of all the couples that are
sitting here right now...
None of the couples right now...
are partners of destiny.
[None of the current couples at the moment
are partners of destiny.]
But we're such a great fit.
You need to discuss how you're going to change
up your partners before our next location.
[Must decide how the partners will
be switched up before the next round.]
The fortune that we were told
initially held some hints.
[The fortunes that were read during
the opening held some hints!]
- What's your sign, Jung Hwa?
- Why are you asking me that?
- He told you your compatible signs earlier.
- I'm the dragon sign.
[Now that they think about it, she was told
she's compatible with Kkuk's sign.]
You're most compatible with signs of
the snake, horse, dragon and dog.
[Mr. Capable with this dragon sign
is perfect for her?]
[That's right, he did say that.]
It would be best if you met a woman
with big eyes.
[Jong Kook was told to meet a woman with
big eyes, and a curvier body.]
[In that case...]
[Could Jong Kook and Jung Hwa
truly be partners of destiny?]
- But you're not chubby.
- Just sexy?
Here's what I think.
I think Gary and Ji Hyo will be a fit.
[Monday couple, Gary and Ji Hyo
to be a perfect fit for each other?]
- I'm curious to know myself.
- Okay, you two partner up.
- Those two may be good together.
- And you and Suk Jin.
[Finally arrives at the next location
after a long train ride.]
[What kind of a mission awaits them here?]
- All the couples must sit together.
- Sit right here?
- Did you all enjoy you train ride?
- Yes.
We had to transfer a few times.
Here's your next mission.
The mission is called,
'Please answer my call'.
Please go and collect the phones
from all the members.
[All of their cellphones are to be turned in.]
Each couple must step forward
and make a phone call.
If the person on the other end answers the
phone call within the time limit, you succeed.
- The other person has to answer the call?
- Then isn't that pretty easy?
We've already decided
who you're going to call for you.
Please unveil the curtain.
- What is that?
- You want me to unveil it?
[What is that?]
[I'm getting... a bad feeling about this.]
- What is this?
- What are we going to do?
[A giant spinning wheels with the names
of various celebrities!]
How are we going to call Jackie Chan?
They're all names of previous guests
who have been on Running Man before.
And we've also picked those whom you've either
worked with or are already friends with.
Those are the names that you'll find
on the spinning wheel.
Each of you need to come out and
call the name that your spin lands on.
If you don't know their number,
then ask within your group for the number.
You can ask for help to obtain the number
to place the call.
- Since we're all friends, right?
- There's my husband's name, Jang Joon Hwan.
There's one person that I know.
What you need to remember is that
even if you know the number
you'll fail the mission if they don't
answer the call within the time limit.
We're all a team.
We have to help each other.
If all five teams succeed within the first try,
then you'll be given three separate hints.
[Three hints if all five teams
succeed in first attempt.]
- We need to hurry.
- We succeed if they just answer, right?
You succeed if they just answer the call.
- Should we go first?
- You go first.
[Jong Kook and Jung Hwa to go first.]
People don't usually take my phone calls.
That's why you should
always be nice to people.
- Just spin the wheel.
- She said she recently changed her number.
One, two, three.
[Time to pick their first caller!]
[The wheel is spinning!]
- We have to succeed!
- What are we going to do!
[Whose name will get picked?]
[The fate of the mission rides on the wheel!]
- Who? Who is it?
- It'll stop right around here.
[The wheel is full of
names of various celebrities.]
- It's Lee Min Jung.
- Min Jung.
[Lee Min Jung is chosen!]
[She showed a refreshingly attractive
side of herself in the Hong Kong episode!]
[Will she answer their call?]
- It's Lee Ming Jung.
- Min Jung.
- I have her number!
- You have her number?
[Min Jung and Kwang Soo filmed the movie,
'Wonderful Radio' together in the past.]
That's my phone!
[They need to unlock
Kwang Soo's phone first.]
You need to draw your finer down,
and bring the tail back up like this.
[Mission impossible code...]
[Kkuk-Vatar is taking orders from
Kwang-Vatar.]
Go like this, and come down to the middle,
and go down one.
[Kwang Soo's never-ending lock code pattern.]
- Zero... six...
- Yeah?
[Jung Hwa in the meantime is already
calling someone.]
- Who are you calling?
- Lee Byung Hun. (Min Jung's husband.)
What is this?
Who are you to have a code like this?
[They're wasting too much time
trying to unlock his phone.]
- I got to five.
- Then bring it down.
[So frustrating...]
[Secretive Kwang Soo...
with so many secrets to hide.]
I got it.
[Finally gets the phone unlocked.]
[Now they have to find her number.]
Hurry up and call her!
You have to type faster!
Please answer!
I just called her a few days ago!
[Only three seconds left on the clock!]
- Just give us a few more seconds.
- Two seconds.
[She just... needs to answer their call.]
[Please...]
[Time over!]
[Fails the first round.]
She did say that
she's really busy lately.
- You failed the first round.
- She's not answering.
- We just failed the first round.
- Min Jung isn't even answering your call.
- There's no way she wouldn't answer my call.
- What do you mean? It just happened.
[What do you mean, she won't?]
But we could get one of my friends, Jung Eun.
Kim Jung Eun.
[Aha! They could call
someone else of the same name!]
- It could be someone of the same name.
- I know a writer named Kim Tae Hee.
The wheel doesn't state that
it has to be a celebrity.
[I guess... we didn't state that
it has to be a celebrity.]
[Moon So Ri's clever thinking.]
[They lost their chance at three hints-
Time to start the second round.]
[Between Suk Jin and Min Soo,
they know quite a few people.]
- Is that your personal phone?
- Min Soo's wearing toe socks.
You didn't see that earlier?
My fantasy has just been shattered!
I can't believe that the Min Soo of my dreams
is wearing toe socks!
She was wearing her toe socks the whole time
she was on the drama, 'Sandglass'!
- Spin the wheel.
- Spin it?
- Let's spin it together.
- One, two, three.
[Who will it be this time?
And will they answer their phone?]
If it's someone like Ji Jin Hee,
he and I talk all the time.
- Lee Juk?
- Yoon Ah!
Hong Sang... Kim Sang Kyung.
[Kim Sang Kyung!]
[Debonair actor, Kim Sang Kyung,
who showed off his quiet, but goofy side.]
- Sang Kyung.
- Call Sang Kyung!
- Jung Hwa, what's his number?
- I have his phone number.
- Check and see if I have it.
- Isn't he your junior?
Wait, I think...
[Big-nose checks his contact list...]
[And he doesn't have his number!]
[A total waste of time!
He should've asked others instead.]
- You have it?
- Yes, press the phone.
[Needs to check through the contact list.]
I don't know how to use this
since I don't use an iPhone.
[The older man doesn't know how to use
the latest technology.]
[Old man Big-nose... please hurry.]
- You have to enter his name.
- What is he doing?
Kim Sang Kyung.
[Voice command?]
[All the others are cringing at
his behavior.]
- Here it is.
- I see it.
- Hurry up and call him.
- Press it.
- Press this?
[Finally calling.]
[Why is he... making it so complicated?]
[The phone is finally ringing.]
[If he doesn't answer the call,
they'll fail the second round as well.]
- Speaker.
- We have it on speaker.
What are you saying?
[Oh! He answered!]
Sang Kyung!
Hello?
This is Ji Suk Jin.
- Yes, hello!
- It's been awhile.
- What can I help you with?
- I realized that I don't have your number.
He answered the call.
[Nice Sang Kyung answers the call
on the first ring.]
What is Min Jung doing?
We're filming Running Man right now.
We succeeded because you answered
our call.
[Explaining their mission to him.]
Thanks for answering the call.
Jung Hwa has a movie coming out.
And I noticed that she's gotten
even prettier lately.
- I know.
- Seriously?
[Happy to answer and joke around.]
Thanks, Sang Kyung!
Jung Hwa... since there aren't any
real girly movies out lately...
I really feel that your movie
is going to become a huge hit.
What is he talking about all of a sudden?
[A plug-in about her movie
out of the blue?]
I'm sure that she's on Running Man
because there's a reason for it.
[Witty Sang Kyung is mentioning her movie
in her place to help her out.]
Where are you right now, Sang Kyung?
I'm out drinking.
- At this hour?
- I had a feeling.
[That's way Sang Kyung's sounding so upbeat.]
Okay, thanks so much for your help.
[Such a relief that he answered their call!]
[Thank you, Sang Kyung,
for answering the call!]
[Suk Jin and Min Soo succeed!]
Wow, this is hard.
[Ha Ha and So Ri are up next.]
- That way?
- Should we spin this way?
Yeah, that way.
I'll spin up.
How is that any important?
- Spin down?
- You want to spin up?
[These two are totally off synch.]
- Do as you'd like.
- There's no way you two are a match.
Set, go.
[Everyone fixes their gaze on the wheel.]
You might get lucky.
Jang Joon Hwan.
[If they can get So Ri's husband,
Jang Joon Hwan...]
No!
- Go Soo's okay too!
- Go Soo, Won Bin, Kim Tae Hee!
Lee Juk!
Park Tae Hwan!
[Park Tae Hwan is chosen.]
Okay, I know Park Tae Hwan!
I know Park Tae Hwan.
[How does he know his number?]
- I think he's in Australia right now.
- In Australia?
[He's currently participating in
a swim competition in Australia.]
Please.
- Tae Hwan.
- I'd be shocked if he answers the call.
He's doing really well in Australia
right now.
What if he's sleeping?
- He might be swimming.
- What time is it over there right now?
What if he's in the water?
Yeah, he could be training.
[Tae Hwan... it's me.]
[Marine Boy, Park Tae Hwan-
Visiting RM with a huge smile on his face.]
Who's name did you want to
rip off the most?
Yours.
[You remember, don't you?
We were so happy together.]
[Please answer the phone.]
- I don't think he'll answer.
- He answered!
Hello?
[Park Tae Hwan answered!]
[What an honor!]
Park Tae Hwan!
Tae Hwan!
How are you doing, Tae Hwan?
What... what is it?
What's going on?
Hey, Tae Hwan.
We're filming Running Man right now.
Our mission success depended on whether you
answered your phone or not, and you did.
We succeeded our mission!
- Are you doing well?
- I just got back from a match.
- Congratulations, Tae Hwan!
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
- We haven't forgotten about you.
- You have to come back on Running Man.
- When do you want to come back?
- I'll be back on soon.
- Yeah, come back soon.
- It's so nice to meet you.
- Yes.
Moon So Ri is sitting next to me.
Moon So Ri, the actress.
- Yes, hello.
- Hello!
[Unable to hide her awe.]
Thank you so much for answering the call.
- Thanks, Tae Hwan.
- No problem.
Make sure to come back on
the show, Tae Hwan.
- Yes, see you soon.
- Yeah, let's get together for dinner soon.
- Thanks.
- Stay safe!
[Hurray, Marine Boy!
Here's a cheer for you!]
[Ha Ha and So Ri succeed their mission.]
- We have to make sure to succeed.
- I'm getting nervous.
- I don't really know anyone.
- We really don't know many people.
I know all the directors.
But I don't know any actors.
But I can call any of the directors.
I hope we get someone like Myung Soo
or Hyung Don.
- Or even Hong Chul.
- Myung Soo never answers his phone.
Spin the wheel.
Come on, please.
We need to pass so we can succeed.
We have to avoid getting Jackie Chan.
Soo Hong!
- Hee Hyul!
- It's Jin Hee.
It's Jin Hee!
- It's Jin Hee!
- I have his number!
- I have it!
[Easy Brothers are both
volunteering their phones!]
[The mission impossible of unlocking
his phone starts up again.]
Mine's just a diamond pattern!
[Ace unlocks Kwang Soo's phone right away!]
- He's not going to answer your call.
- We just talked last week.
[Calling Ji Jin Hee with Kwang Soo's phone.]
- He's not going to answer.
- He's in a drama.
[He may be filming her latest drama...
Will he answer the phone?]
Jin Hee!
[Dashing and debonair actor, Ji Jin Hee.]
[His duck feathered run
is still fresh on our minds...]
There's still time.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
[Hurray!]
[Jin Hee coolly answers the call.]
Hello, Sir. This is Kang Gary.
Gary.
- Oh my goodness... Gary.
- Hi, Jin Hee!
- Have you been well?
- Yes, I'm doing very well.
We're filming Running Man right now,
and we succeeded our mission, thanks to you.
Thank you!
- Thanks, Jin Hee!
- We love your new drama!
- So you did okay?
- Yes, we succeeded!
- Good, congratulations.
- Thanks to you, we'll be able to go on.
Jin Hee!
- Yes?
- Are you really close with Suk Jin?
- Yes, of course we are.
- Seriously?
Tell everyone how close we are, Jin Hee.
Yes, we're very close.
- Yes, that's right.
- What were you doing just now?
I'm just looking through the
latest script.
- Thank you, Jin Hee.
- Sure.
- Thanks, Jin Hee.
- Jin Hee, it's me, Uhm-Tang.
- Who?
- Uhm Jung Hwa.
- Oh! Hi, Jung Hwa.
- Hi!
- It's me, So Ri!
Ah... So Ri.
You're all there. Then I guess
Jo Min Shoo should be there too.
It's me, Kwang Soo.
I hope your movie becomes
a huge success.
- Thank you, Jin Hee.
- Thank you!
Fighting, Ji Jin Hee.
- His drama is really good.
- Our voices are going to go hoarse.
- I'm so glad he answered.
- We may be able to do this.
- We might be able to succeed.
- One, two, three.
[Time to pick the fourth caller.
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo's turn.]
It would be so nice if we can get
So Ri's husband.
Woo Bin?
[Jung Woo Sung is chosen!]
[Jung Woo Sung, who ended up being
so much more than a handsome face!]
[Will he answer their sudden phone call?]
- I have his phone number!
- You have it?
- What's your lock code?
- I'm pretty sure I have his number.
- I have his number too. Search my phone.
I think I have it...
I'm pretty sure that I have it.
- You don't have it.
- I don't have his number?
[Searching through Ha Ha's contacts...]
- You have a 'Woo Sung'.
- Do you see a 'Jung Woo Sung'?
Should I try calling Kyung Gyu?
I can ask Seo Kyung Gyu for his number.
- I was told he really likes Running Man.
- I know.
[Trying Kyung Gyu's phone.]
Why isn't he answering my call?
- Hello?
- It's me, So Ri.
Sorry, but we're in a huge rush.
Can you give me Jung Woo Sung's number?
- Woo Sung?
- Yeah, Jung Woo Sung. That handsome actor.
- I'll text you the number.
- There's no time. Can you just tell me now?
But... I don't think I can memorize it.
- Okay, just text it to me.
- Let us say 'hi' to him.
- Can my friends say 'hi' first?
- Hello, sir, this is Yoo Jae Suk.
Hello, this is Lee Kwang Soo.
- We're filming Running Man right now.
- Ah... Running Man?
- Yes.
- I see.
Sorry for this sudden call.
- Kyung Gyu...
- Why are you asking for Woo Sung's number?
It's a long story, but to keep it short,
we had to spin the spinning wheel
and we have to call the celebrity
whose name the wheel landed on.
- Thank you so much.
- And Happy New Year!
- Yes, Happy New Year to you too.
- Where are you right now?
[MC Yoo still manages to ask
a question like that at a time like this.]
Can I ask you what you're doing?
What are you doing?
- I bet he's out drinking.
- I'm out drinking right now.
- Thanks!
- Thank you!
I'll text you the number right now.
[Kyung Gyu seemed more urgent to get them
the number than Jae Suk himself.]
- We'll be fine as long as this team...
- There's the text!
Here, call this number.
[They just need to call that number now.]
I don't think he'll answer.
[Will Jung Woo Sung answer the call...
or will the time be over first?]
[They'll succeed as soon as he answers!]
- Just five more seconds.
- Wait!
Everyone's working right now.
Who would answer their phone?
This is all such a joke!
All those people have jobs!
- Min Soo's angry right now.
- It's the truth! All those people work!
Even housewives can't answer
their phones around this time.
They're all busy making dinner,
and taking care of their family!
- You're both doing great!
- They're stating the truth.
This is everyone's busiest time of the day.
This is asking too much of them.
We have to start all over for
the third round.
Do we really have to start all over?
Can't we just keep the successful calls?
Didn't you say that we could earlier?
I'm positive you said that we could earlier.
[We never said...]
- One more peg, and it would've been Ho Dong.
- We have to go to the third round now.
- We were so close.
- I don't think the wheel is very fair.
[Now she's even suspicious about
the fairness of the spinning wheel.]
One side is heavier than the other.
That's why we keep getting the same side.
- That's why it keeps going back that way.
- Look at them looking flustered.
Then we'll give you one special chance.
Nominate one person to come forward to make
the call, excluding those we've already called.
- That's how we'll do the third round.
- Thank you.
- You're a really nice person.
What if we have the number, but they don't
answer because they're working?
There's nothing we can do about that.
- Then we'll start with whomever is ready.
- We'll go.
[Ha Ha and So Ri to start off
the third round.]
[They have a feeling that their
40 year old clubber friend might answer?]
[Team Ha Ha and So Ri choose Jang Joon Hwan.]
[So Ri chooses her husband
without any hesitation.]
The time limit is exactly one minute.
Set, go.
[So Ri tries calling her husband.]
He could be in the shower right now.
Why would he shower at this hour?
[Honey...]
The best asset that your fortune shows...
is your husband.
[The biggest asset in So Ri's fortune
is none other than her very own husband.]
[The most precious person in her life...
be good to him.]
[So please... answer your phone.]
- Yes?
- Honey.
[Success!
He answered!]
It's me... So Ri.
- Um... thank you.
- Success!
[A good start to the third round
right from the beginning!]
I'll put you up on a pedestal from now on.
- Yes.
- You speak in honorifics to each other?
- Congratulations.
- Yes, thank you.
Hello, sir. My name is Ha Ha,
and I'm Moon So Ri's partner today.
Yes, hello.
It's nice to meet you.
- Yes, it's great to meet you too.
- I had to hold Ha Ha's hand today.
Ah... I see.
[The cute couple still acts jealous
after nine years of marriage.]
- What are you doing right now?
- You weren't showering, were you?
- No, I wasn't in the shower.
- Shower later.
[Seizes his chance to act like a brat
and promote his single.]
What were you doing when we called?
I was watching a movie.
I'm sorry, but we have a member
whose name is Lee Kwang Soo...
Can you cast Kwang Soo in one of
your movies?
He doesn't even cast me.
Ah, Kwang Soo?
Yes, he's entertaining.
[Entertaining Kwang Soo.]
[Please look kindly on our Kwang Soo.]
- Thank you!
- Thank you, and Happy New Year!
- Wow... that was great.
- I've never heard his voice before.
He sounds like he'd have a
great personality.
He sounds so calm.
Pick Dong Wook.
[Gary and Ji Hyo select Lee Dong Wook.]
Nothing ever happened between
you two, right?
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Hey!
[Dong Wook answers before
the first ring is even over!]
Thanks for answering my call.
- Okay.
- Hey, Dong Wook. It's me, Gary.
- Hi, Gary.
- It's always the three of us, isn't it?
- No kidding. Am I getting in the way?
- No, you're not.
[Jong Kook and Jung Hwa call Go Soo.]
- I don't have the number.
- Go Soo, is that you?
Yes, hello.
[Mr. Capable succeeds in getting
a hold of Go Soo!]
Thanks for answering the call.
We're filming Running Man right now.
Thank so much for answering the call.
You're so handsome.
[Suk Jin and Min Soo select Kim Hye Soo.]
Yes?
Hye Soo... it's me, Jung Min Soo.
Hi, Min Soo.
I'm calling you from
Jong Kook's phone right now.
Ah, I see.
You must be filming Running Man?
- Yes, I am.
- Happy New Year!
- Thank you!
- Hope to see you sometime on our show!
[Even the fourth caller is a success!]
- I can't believe Hye Soo answered.
- Thanks to her, we're on a winning streak.
[Now it's all up to Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
to make it a clean sweep.]
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo choose
to call Soo Hong.]
[The time is ticking...]
[But their clubber buddy isn't answering.]
I wonder if he's out at a club.
- People in the variety show industry...
- Let's call someone else.
- We're going to call someone else.
- Let's call Gong Yoo.
[Jae Suk and Kwang Soo select
Gong Yoo as their second caller.]
We have to call him.
[Gong Yoo isn't answering either...
Only ten seconds left!]
[Park Myung Soo is their last hope!]
[Time is almost up!]
Hello?
[Succeeds just in the nick of time!]
[Myung Soo answers their call right away
as if he's been waiting for their call.]
- He must've been waiting.
- Thank you!
[A dramatic win.]
It's me, Myung Soo.
- Are you filming?
- Yeah, I am. Are you at home?
Why are you filming without me?
We would've failed had you not answered.
Thanks for answering our call.
I should've answered sooner.
Sorry I took so long to answer.
[Myung Soo is an entertainer
through and through!]
Anyways, thanks.
No, not at all. Call me anytime.
Sorry I couldn't answer sooner.
Hello, Myung Soo.
This is Kwang Soo.
- Who?
- It's Kwang Soo.
What about it?
I've been getting calls from Singapore
ever since I came on Running Man.
Why would you be getting calls
from Singapore?
That I'm doing a good job.
You didn't do well when you were on.
Tell your producers to have me back on.
- What do you want me to tell them?
- Fire Ha Ha and hire me in his place.
Thanks for answering, Myung Soo.
I'll call you back.
- Okay, have fun.
- Thank you, Myung Soo!
[Finally succeeds at the third round!]
- Answered with five seconds left to go.
- I'll give you one hint.
- Yes, give us at least one.
- This was really hard.
Can you give us one hint and tell us if any
of the current couples are partners of destiny?
Can you?
Since we don't have a lot of hints.
[They all work as a team
during times like these.]
- Just tell us how many couples there are.
- Can't you just tell us that much?
If you tell us that there aren't any now,
then we'll really be at a loss.
I can't tell you how many of you are
the fateful couple right now.
Actually, that hint is within the hint
that I was going to give you.
[If they had succeeded their mission,
that would've been one of their hints.]
So I'll just tell you whether or not
any of the current couples are correct.
Of the five current couples...
partners of destiny do exist right now.
- I think it's those two.
- It's Gary and Ji Hyo.
[Monday couple, Gary and Ji Hyo,
or Sexy couple, Jong Kook and Jung Hwa.]
I'm sure that it's Gary and Ji Hyo.
When you say that the couple exists right now,
then of the current couples...
you're saying that the partners of destiny
do exist right now?
There are two correct couples.
Oops!
Two couples?
[Oh... how can this be?]
[The producer accidentally spills
a huge hint!]
- Gary and Ji Hyo are definitely one of them.
- And those two definitely aren't it.
[Running Man members are two steps
closer to figuring it out.]
Knowing that there are two correct couples
right now is a huge hint we've just earned.
[Ah... Easy Brothers...
The way they failed the first game...]
Please just allow us love!
[My fate... handed down from God...]
[Real couples of destiny
will soon be revealed.]
[Entering the final location at last.]
I think they've got something planned.
- I think we're going to get plunged.
- We're being plunged into water or something.
Plunged into what?
[Just what... are they being plunged into?]
[Specially built... platform of truth.]
[Get the wrong answer,
and you'll all disappear.]
- Everyone must return your couple rings.
- Our rings?
[Return the rings.]
- Ones that we're sure of...
- Gary and Ji Hyo.
- And how about the others?
- Jung Hwa and Jong Kook.
- I'm not so sure about Gary and Ji Hyo.
- They're a sure thing.
- Shall I give you your final hint?
- Yes.
[Final hint to help unveil the truth.]
- Everything is riding on that hint.
- Jae Suk and I...
[Lee Kwang Soo's possibilities are Jae Suk,
Jong Kook, Ha Ha, Jung Hwa, and Min Soo.]
- Then who's not on that list?
- Me, Gary, and Ji Hyo.
The reason why it's not me is when he and I
were partnered up, we weren't counted as one.
[If the Sexy Couple,
Jong Kook and Jung Hwa are real...]
[And Monday Couple,
Gary and Ji Hyo are real...]
[Then Kwang Soo's partner of destiny is...]
[Either Yoo Jae Suk, Ha Ha, or Jo Min Soo?]
[Moments earlier, in the picture mission...]
[They switched partners so that it was
Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and Min Soo, Kwang Soo.]
Currently... there are three
couples of destiny amongst you.
[From two couples to three.
That means there's another couple!]
[Which means, either Suk Jin, Jae Suk,
and Min Soo and Kwang Soo are a couple!]
- Come stand over here.
- We only swapped out two couples.
Two of these three couples are right.
And one of us two couples are correct.
Right?
One of you two teams are right.
Two of you three teams are correct,
and one of our two teams are correct.
But the hint that we just received about
Kwang Soo's possible matches...
Of us... I think it's Min Soo and I.
- But you're not it.
- But I'm not it.
Which means, you two are it.
[High possibility that Min Soo and
Kwang Soo could be a pair?]
So of those three teams,
if those two teams are correct...
- Then we either have to swap like this...
- Swap this way?
Or it's this way.
One or the other.
- I don't think that's right.
- No, you two definitely aren't it.
This is really making me take
a real close look at everyone.
- But if those two aren't it...
- I'm positive of those two.
[A huge problem if the Monday Couple
aren't fated to be...]
We have to go with our gut feeling.
Nothing else we can do about it.
This is our final selection
of all the couples.
- No other ways to go about it.
- Then please swap out the jackets.
The couple whom you're most certain of...
Please go up to the platform
and stand all the way to the left.
Aren't we the most certain couple?
[Going by the hints they've received,
Min Soo and Kwang Soo may be their best bet.]
They must be the couple with the highest
known probability of being correct.
That would mean that those two are most
compatible according to their fortune...
Do you have an ounce of
shyness about you?
While we're all standing here talking,
he's trying to get all romantic on her.
Of all the countless number of
people out there...
in some ways, we are most compatible
than anyone else out there.
[Don't you find that amazing, Min Soo?]
[Of the countless number of
people out there...]
[We're the most compatible out of them all.]
You should go on 'We Got Married'.
[Comedy is definitely
best suited for Kwang Soo?]
I'm really nervous.
Shall we go up there?
- You think we're good?
- Hold hands as you go up.
So those two... we're sure of them, right?
We have a very high probability of being
the right couple.
[Even though it's not a
one hundred percent guarantee...]
[Min Soo and Kwang Soo still
have the highest probability.]
And the second most sure couple
can now step up onto the platform.
[Next highest probable couple is,
Jong Kook and Jung Hwa.]
I'm sure of it, Jong Kook.
And I think it's us two after them.
- See? Something doesn't feel right.
- You two have to be it.
It has to be you two.
- Yes, we have to be right about this.
- You two are it.
[Followed by the Monday Couple.]
It'll be a miracle if we get this right.
[Fourth couple, Suk Jin and So Ri.]
[Last couple, Ha Ha and Jae Suk.]
[Did they... correctly guess...
all the couples?]
Are you all set?
You're not going to change your minds?
[No more swapping!]
We'll start with the first couple.
[Time to judge the first couple.]
Confetti will rain down if you have guessed
the first couple correctly.
Please just allow us to love each other.
If the first couple is wrong,
then you all will be dunked together.
- And we will take back your rings.
- We heard you.
Challenge!
Okay, let's see if
the first couple is correct.
The first couple.
[First couple...]
[Partners of Destiny!]
- I knew it.
- My heart's pounding right now.
The element of water is very strong
between Jo Min Soo and Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo has a tree like disposition,
and she has the ability to help him grow.
That's why they're a great fit together.
I love you!
Please help me grow.
Please accept my love!
I want to continue to grow!
- Okay, time to check the second couple.
- We have to be correct about this.
- I'm positive of you two.
- We're the uncertainty.
[Jong Kook isn't so convinced of
himself and his own partner...]
Second couple.
Let's see.
[Second couple...]
[Partners of Destiny!]
- I had no idea, Jung Hwa!
- Jong Kook!
- You two should just start dating.
- How can two sexy people like us...
- Just dunk them in the water.
- Give me your number, okay, Jong Kook?
There are two very solid elements which would
ensure that they would be great in a marriage.
They would be great together as actors
and there are a total of three letters
which indicate their great compatibility.
[That's what you call a
'match made in heaven'.]
- You two should get married.
- Marry each other.
[You're my destiny.]
- Grab him and don't lose him!
- You're my new obsession!
I'm going to make him mine!
Jong Kook, you're mine!
- Okay, the third couple.
- I'm positive about those two.
- What if they're wrong?
- No reason to worry about that.
There are no guarantees that
Ji Hyo and Gary are a couple.
[No solid proof of the Monday Couple.
Just going with their gut feeling.]
- I'm positive of those two.
- There's no way we're wrong about them.
[Will Mr. Capable be right?
Is the Monday Couple fated to be together?]
If we're right about Gary and Ji Hyo,
then I think we'll be able to win.
- I'm sure of those two.
- There's no proof.
[The third couple...]
[Partners of Destiny!]
[Even the fortune tellers are testifying
the compatibility of the Monday Couple.]
- You two really should just date.
- Seriously, you guys.
- Seriously?
- I think your time has finally come, Gary.
- Are you serious?
- We were shocked ourselves.
They can't be just a Monday Couple.
Every fortune teller we've consulted were
in agreement about the two of you.
- Seriously?
- You two are most compatible.
What's the reason behind it?
Those two share a common fate.
They're extremely compatible together.
They each possess an element which would
complement each other most favorably.
They're extremely compatible.
- I also see a huge amount of wealth...
- We're on a totally different level.
You guys would have a really
good marriage together.
- Please link your arms together again.
- This is almost a sure thing now.
- No, we still don't know.
- The final two!
This is the final judgment.
We will reveal the fourth and
the fifth couple simultaneously.
[Checking the fourth and
the fifth couple simultaneously.]
Confetti will rain if you're correct,
but if you're wrong, then you will all...
I really hate this!
The fourth couple...
Song Ji Hyo, is something wrong?
It already feels like we're a married couple.
You two really do look good together.
Okay, the fourth and the fifth couple.
Time to check!
[Having chased after their destinies all day...]
Okay, the fourth and the fifth couple.
Time to check!
[Has destiny...
smiled down upon these couples?]
[A complete success!]
[Couldn't let their guards down
not even for a single moment.]
This is the hardest thing I've had to endure
since having my baby!
I can't believe it.
How did we get it right?
[Still unable to believe their win.]
[To have succeeded with what they had...
They're pretty much masters of the game now.]
With Ji Suk Jin, and Moon So Ri...
Moon So Ri has a very weak water sign
and Ji Suk Jin has a very strong water sign.
These two are able to complement,
and complete each other in that sense.
We should be friends.
- Let's be friends.
- I've made a new friend.
I can see those two amassing a large
amount of wealth together
and especially in the real estate market
or something of the like.
- Maybe in our next lifetime.
- You should buy a building together.
- Let's become good friends.
- I know some good real estate.
Maybe we should go take a look
at some available land together.
I'm telling you that I've got
some sense too.
- He's always up for something.
- I've got a few ideas in mind.
When it comes to Yoo Jae Suk, and Ha Ha...
most people are compatible in only one way...
but these two are compatible and
complementary to each other in every way.
So that's why you're involved in
doing two shows together.
I'll do ten shows with him if I can.
And when I take a look at the compatibility of
the Running Man members as a whole
there's a very strong element of
sheep amongst the group.
What that means is, they as a whole
are usually bright and uplifting together.
[Sharing, giving, and receiving a lot of
bright and positive energy to each other.]
I'm so happy to be taking home the gold again.
- Hope your movie is a huge success.
- Take the gold home, and Jong Kook home too.
[Where are you planning on taking him?]
I'll put it on you.
Where? On that finger?
- Wow, so pretty.
- It's a perfect fit!
- Let's wear the couple rings together.
- Okay, fine.
- He's trying to give them both to me.
- It's a couple ring.
- Happy New Year, everyone.
- Happy New Year!
Please show a lot of love to our show
even in the new year!
- Bye!
- Wishing everyone lots of happiness!
- Happy New Year!
- Be good to your friends!
I found a new friend.
I think I might get married this year.
- Seriously.
- We really hope that you do.
- Hope you do get married.
- Age is just a number, everyone.
Everyone... love can conquer all.
- To all our viewers...
- Happy New Year!
[Happy New Year!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
It's time to prepare for
the 2014 Running Winter Olympics.
[Let's head to Sochi!
2014 Running Winter Olympics.]
[Running Man vs All Star Team.]
It's cold and blustery out,
so let's just get the show on the road.
Name tag elimination on ice has been accepted
as an official game in this year's Olympics.
[No hesitation in this game!]
[Must endure all the pain and agony!]
[A terrifying hell camp that knows no mercy.]
[Who will represent in the 2014
Ice Name tag Elimination?]
[Running Man Winter Olympics]