You only have yourself to blame!
[Desire]
[Rage]
[Betrayal]
[And love.]
[The emotions that made these
women bitter.]
What are you going to do
if I don't win this?
[Running miniseries-
It's Okay, We're Heirs.]
[Early morning, 'O' hotel in Incheon.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[A mysterious group of women gather
in the hotel conference room.]
[The strongest roses in all of Korea
come to take over Running Man.]
[Ice queen, Yoo In Young.]
Did you get to where you are
by making a fool out of me?
[Plays the evil role to perfection
with ferociousness.]
[The role model of
all the hopeful ice queens.]
Hello.
[Method actress, Seo Woo.]
[Undeniable charisma that flows
from her tiny frame.]
[Femme fatale with the body,
Choi Yeo Jin.]
Tell me what you just said!
[Strong acting skills
befitting of her looks.]
- Not many people are here yet?
- No.
[Actress of undeniable charisma-
Kim Min Seo.]
[Powerhouse actress with an innocent face.]
She looks like she always plays the role
of a modern woman in dramas.
They must've called only the most
beautiful women in the industry.
- Only the most beautiful women.
- Hello.
Hello.
[The actress who took Korea by storm-
Lee Yoo Ri.]
[No explanations necessary for
the birth of this nation's evil queen.]
[Lee Yoo Ri is here!]
See?
I told you that we're all pretty.
[What is the reason for all these women
being gathered here together?]
You will each be partnered up with
one of the male Running Man members
and will participate in a game of
a couple's race.
As you can see, pictures of the six
male members are placed in front of you.
In order for you to have the chance
to choose your own partner
we have called you to come in a little
earlier than the rest of the members.
I will take the person whom you
least want to be partnered up with.
You can all tell me who you don't
want to end up with.
In that case, to make things easier...
just hand Suk Jin over to me.
[Considerate Ji Hyo takes the
weakest link off the table for them.]
I'll take Suk Jin for you.
[In Young chooses Haroro.]
[Min Seo chooses Kkuk.]
[Seo Woo chooses Jae Suk.]
I'll take him so that
our height will be compatible.
[Yoo Ri chooses Mr. Gary.]
These members don't even have a clue
that they will soon be meeting you all.
So it is up to you to go and
surprise them.
I think he's going to be
really shocked.
[Time to go and surprise the members.]
[Meanwhile, the rest of
the Running Man members are...]
- Are we starting?
- Yes.
[Each arrive at their own filming location
oblivious to what's going on.]
Who's guesting?
[Although he's clueless about the situation,
he's suspicious about what's going on.]
What am I doing here in my sweats
in this nice penthouse suite?
Do you think that this is a fitting
attire for this room?
What's going on here?
Why am I here?
Just who's coming on the show that
I'm getting fed steak for breakfast?
[These men are clueless... about
the storm that's headed their way.]
[Her expression undergoes
a complete transformation!]
Wait a minute.
Those clicking sounds...
[Min Seo's expression on her face
is now completely different.]
10,027.
[Transformed into a completely
different woman.]
[It's time to raise the curtains.]
[Time for these ferocious women
to slip into their roles...]
[Running Miniseries-
It's Okay, We're Heirs.]
[Time for the show to start.]
Does that hurt?
Huh?
[As soon as the curtain goes up,
they spring into action.]
- This is so good.
- What do you think you're doing?
[Hello...]
All you ever care about is food!
A human being can't survive on food alone.
[A famous scene from her own drama
is happening right in front of his own eyes.]
How are you any different
from a beast?
I'm a dog!
('Gae'=Dog.)
Jong Kook.
Do you ever even think about me?
You just only care about yourself.
You never have
any consideration for me.
Do you even know what it is
that I'm doing for you?
I even lied to the hospital just so
that you could get the director's seat!
And I even fired all the doctors!
What are you going to do about that?
Why are you doing this?
[The scene from
'My Love From Another Star.']
Find yourself another salon.
Hey.
Find yourself another gym.
- This is our first meeting.
- You make me feel so filthy!
I said, get out of here!
Is this our concept for the day?
Whenever I see you...
I feel so angry!
That's enough!
[Haroro joins in on the action.]
Pick it up!
This is the last time I'm doing this.
I'm going to pick them up for one last
time since this is our first meeting.
But... I want you to
pick up one of the bottles.
You're really picking one up?
What's going on here?
- Wait...
- Did you really think...
A man like you... I can
easily end with one single blow!
[Amazing acting skills that are
evident in all her dramas.]
You know that I'm a woman
of my word, don't you?
[What in the world is going on?]
I've already been living my life for
the past five years as a dead woman.
- I've already...
- This is just absurd.
been living my life for the past
five years as a dead woman.
- Ah!
- What is it?
What's wrong?
- My appendix...
- Your appendix?
What's wrong with you?
- Are you...
- Shut up!
Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo?
Do you know me?
- I'm Min So Hee!
- You put a mole on your face?
[With a single mole on her face,
Blank So Hee is born.]
Jung Gyo Bin sent you, didn't he?
- You...
- That's right, Jung Gyo Bin sent me.
That's right.
He sent me here to kill you.
- This useless money...
- Yes, Jung Gyo Bin sent me here to kill you!
I came here to kill you!
[Big-nose brother's overacting.]
[The famous line from 'Wife's Temptation'.]
I'm going to oust this man
and condemn myself to hell as well.
Just go to hell by yourself.
Why bother ousting me first?
This is nothing compared to
the pain that you've given me!
How is this nothing?
Why are you doing this to me?
Awful bastard.
How can you do this to me?
- What is this?
- Do you even love me?
- I thought you said that you love me.
- Is she acting out a scene?
- Let's just die together.
- Wait!
- Why do I have to die?
- Here, eat!
- I said, eat it!
- What is wrong with this woman?
Is this what you've been waiting for?
[The level of acting keeps rising,
and the storyline deepens.]
- I'm going to end everything.
- What are you eating?
What is this?
- They're just vitamins!
- They're vitamins.
- You got plastic surgery didn't you?
- I made my nostrils smaller.
- Hey!
- Pick it up!
Why are you doing this!
[Love is a battlefield
for these six couples.]
I really love you!
I even love your eye goop!
Please realize the love that
I have for you!
[How will this unexpected drama end?]
- What are you doing?
- Cut!
That's enough!
Let's keep doing it
for a little while longer.
- Pick it up.
- Sure!
Nice to meet you, In Young.
[In Young's face is once again full
of smiles as soon as the scene ends.]
You really took me by surprise.
Why were you acting like that?
- I'm sorry for having done that.
- No, not at all.
I was just doing a parody from
a recent drama that I was in
and that just came out without me even
realizing it when I saw your face.
Was it because I'm so ugly?
Instead of blaming me for all this
you need to blame yourself
for being so desirable!
Stop obsessing over Song Ji Hyo.
Turn your attention to me for once!
What am I expected to do
when I can't help my attractiveness?
- You think I'm like this on purpose?
- Cut!
- This is so embarrassing!
- That really was embarrassing.
I didn't even know what was going on
as she just started insulting me.
- Hello, nice to meet you.
- Please take good care of me.
- Would you like to try that again?
- No, thank you. I've got water in my ear.
What is this?
What do you mean, 'cut'?
[Kwang Soo and Yeo Jin's scene
also comes to an end.]
You have to give me a chance
to get my own revenge!
What revenge?
We're a couple.
I chose you as my partner.
[Really? I didn't know that.]
How does it feel to be beat down by
the woman who chose you?
You must work out a lot. I haven't
been hit this hard in a long time.
- He's sweating!
- Not since junior high.
- Why were you acting like that?
- It was a line from one of my dramas.
- It was just a parody of my drama.
- So this was all just a part of the plan?
The slap wasn't a part of the original plan,
but I just got a little carried away.
Seriously!
[Falling in perfect sync with Jae Suk.]
- It's very nice to meet you.
- They told me to hit you as hard as I could.
Yes, you did the right thing.
I usually don't feel it when I get hit.
You really do need to hit me hard.
You really are an actress.
[Hand in hand,
they're off to their next location.]
Her hand is so tiny.
[A rare look at Kkuk's bashful side.]
She just barged into the room and told me
that she's now Min So Hee with her mole.
At least you were taken
off guard by someone you know.
This was my first time meeting her.
- Did you all get hit?
- Yes, and Gary had water dumped on him.
- You had water dumped on you?
- My partner knocked bottles off the table!
All our guests are known for their realistic
portrayal of strong and evil roles.
But all their styles are a bit different
from one another.
In Young is the aggressive type who
can overwhelm her opponents.
Yeo Jin is the type with a very strong
sense of self-esteem and pride.
And in Yoo Ri's case, she's just
a very destructive type.
With Ji Hyo, she's the type to just
beat her opponents down to the ground.
[Ji Hyo is the fighter.]
I know that they play these evil roles,
but look at the lovely smiles on their faces.
- They're all so sweet looking.
- I'm sure they're not like that in real life.
- Of course not.
- We're all very delicate and gentle.
Yes, we know that.
Today's race is...
'Find the Male Heir.'
- Male heir?
- Although you are not aware of this...
Amongst the six male
Running Man members...
there exists second generation heir
to a huge fortune.
[A second generation heir amongst
the six male Running Man members.]
How does it feel to be filming
in my hotel?
[Identity of the heir is found
within two seconds.]
- Does anyone need anything?
- Take whatever you'd like from here.
- Everything in here belongs to me.
- What are you talking about?
[Both are trying to proclaim
that they are the heir.]
- That thing cost me about 38 million Won.
- Just go change your clothes.
[Too embarrassing of a scene to
play out while in their sweatpants.]
- This is a designer brand.
- What are you talking about?
You will have to collect the hints needed to
find the identity of the heir during the race.
The couple who stands on the platform with
whom they think is the heir wins the race.
No one has any clues to
the real identity of the heir yet
and for the first through third place
winners of the games
a hint will be given out.
But only to the women.
[Only the women placing first through
third place will be given hints.]
Then it's possible that the women may not
tell us the hint and decide to go at it alone.
- They can do it by themselves.
- So it's their decision?
- That's correct.
- I have a good feeling about this.
Suk Jin is standing there like
he is the star of this show.
[Full of high hopes.]
One of us is the heir, right?
Who else could be it be but me?
But you're too old to
be the second generation heir.
[Looks more fitting
to be the first generation.]
[Is Big-nose the newest wave of
senior citizen looking second generation?]
The first hint will be given out to the first
three couples that arrive at the next location.
- Okay, I understand.
- You should get going.
Let's get going!
[Off to the first mission location!]
[Mud Battle of Evil queens and Heirs.]
[Their battle is fiercer than
the fiercest drama.]
[Fierce roses- Find the mysterious heir.]
- Let's go, Seo Woo. Come on.
- Okay.
[Hint given out to the first three couples
that arrives at the mission location.]
[Three couples in the same sector
of the revolving door.]
[Each couple is given
their own car to travel in.]
Seriously.
- Do you know how to drive?
- Yes, of course.
- Get going!
- I have to put my seatbelt on first.
[Jong Kook and Min Seo are
first to get on the road.]
We're in the lead, right?
I like that.
Yoo Ri, are you a competitive person?
- I'm pretty strong.
- You're strong?
- I want to win.
- You want to win?
[Yoo Ri shows off her competitive streak.]
- I don't look mean in person, do I?
- No, not at all.
Once my makeup comes off later,
I'm going to look even sweeter.
- My pants are more like a swimsuit.
- Yes, they look like a swimsuit.
Right? I wonder why I
was given a swimsuit to wear?
Water, farm field, or a muddy shore.
- One of those three, right?
- One of those three.
- You're leaking gas!
- Where?
- What? She needs to get gas?
- What is she saying?
- I like the way you work.
- I really thought they were leaking gas.
Really? Something was leaking?
I wonder if it's their air conditioner.
[Mistaken air conditioner drippings
for a gas leak.]
She's so nice to have let us know
where to go, right?
She wasn't giving us directions.
She lied and told us our gas was leaking.
Why are you so naive?
[Kwang Soo and Yeo Jin
arrive at the mission location.]
[Jong Kook and Min Seo beat them
there by the split of a hair.]
You must run over and grab a flag.
- Hurry, Kwang Soo!
- Where?
[Jong Kook and Min Seo are in the lead.]
Your long legs aren't helping you at all!
[Run over and grab the flag!]
Run!
[Jae Suk and Seo Woo arrive
in third place.]
We're late.
Run!
- It's only for the first three couples.
- What place are we in?
Yay, we're in first place.
[Jong Kook and Min Seo in first place.]
We're in second place.
[Kwang Soo and Yeo Jin in second place.]
How are you ever going to
run fast in those shoes?
[Jae Suk and Seo Woo in third place.]
How are you going to run
in those shoes?
Seriously! What were you thinking wearing
those shoes on Running Man?
That's because I'm really short.
- I didn't even know you were running.
- You're going to sprain your ankle.
[Her pride is more important
than a possible sprained ankle.]
- That's because I'm so short.
- This is so disappointing.
- Is it over already?
- She's so competitive!
[Gary and Yoo Ri arrive in fifth place.]
- I just don't want to come in at last place.
- Those aren't running shoes.
- What are you girls thinking?
- What kind of running shoes are those?
- They didn't even wear the right shoes.
- It's because my legs are too short.
She's blaming her legs.
Min Seo, is this the first time
you've ever been outside?
Your legs are way too white.
Is this the first time you've been
outside this year?
We welcome you to this
state of the art open space.
How is this space 'state of the art'?
We need everyone to take a look
at what's in front of you.
[Figurines of all the male
and female participants of the race.]
Is this supposed to be me?
- Why is Gary's figurine so handsome?
- Yes!
Gary, you look like an actor.
This one doesn't even look like me.
[Unlikely Ha Ha.]
Jong Kook's looks like he had a lot
of fat injected into his cheeks.
[Chubby Tiger.]
This is the current standing
of the couples.
Before we officially start the game,
to the first three couple to have arrived
a hint regarding the identity of the heir
will be given to the women only
as well as a chance card to
swap out their current partner.
Seo Woo, please step forward.
Watch out so you don't fall.
- What kind of shoes are those?
- Be careful not to fall over.
- Are those shoes for a store mannequin?
- I think we're of similar height.
What are you talking about?
Here, take a look.
I've never seen shoes like those
in the history of Running Man before.
A lot of people in Japan
wear those types of shoes.
- Make sure no one else sees, Seo Woo.
- I'm going to peek.
- I can see it.
- I just saw it.
My name is written on there,
isn't it?
[Hint- Resembles an animal.]
You can swap out one of the couples.
[An heir that resembles an animal.]
- I'm fine with my partner.
- You want to stay?
You can step back now that
you've made your decision.
- Second place winner, step forward.
- What happened? What's the hint?
- I don't think it's you.
- You don't think it's me?
I can see everything.
[A hint for the second
place winner, Yeo Jin.]
Why are you trying to be so secretive?
Yeo Jin is so tall.
[Hint number two-
Wants to be friends with idols.]
Why are you staring at me?
- Did you see my name?
- It's me, isn't it?
See? I knew it.
I knew it would be me.
Yoon Ah is standing so close to me.
It's because she loves me!
Don't you know that you can't love her?
[The heir has a special soft spot
for the idols?]
I think I know who it is.
[Takes Suk Jin's figurine and swaps
it out with Kwang Soo's figurine.]
- What are you doing?
- We can see what you're doing.
- We haven't even done anything yet!
- Please step back.
- He is the first one to get swapped out.
- Did you really swap me out?
First place winner, Kim Min Seo,
please step forward.
Please be careful so that
no one else can see it.
[Hint number three-
Has released a music album.]
[Several of these members have
released music albums in the past.]
[Her current partner is
singer Kim Jong Kook.]
I'm not going to switch.
[Why will they be coupled off by the time
the final mission rolls around?]
You will now enter the arena where
your first game will take place.
I will let you know what that is
once you've entered the arena.
I just saw it.
What is that?
- What is that?
- I just saw it.
- That's not going to be easy.
- I can hear the staff members snickering.
[This is where the first
competition will take place.]
I will now let you know
what your mission is going to be.
Since we have the hottest in-demand
actresses on as our guests
we have prepared a game which consists of
parodies of classic scenes from dramas.
- Okay.
- The first game is, 'The red earth's desire.'
We have prepared a pond of red clay
which you can see behind you.
The red clay is very good for your skin.
The women will climb up onto
the platform that you see behind you
and wait for their own partners.
The men will wait in standby in the pond
and run over to the platform and climb up
on it with the help of their partners
when the whistle sounds.
- I see.
- Simple, isn't it?
The game ends when there's only
one couple left standing on the platform.
- That sounds like fun.
- It may be fun for you!
- Why wouldn't it be?
- Pushing and shoving us around is fun?
- Yes, I bet he would have fun with it.
- I think the audience will like it.
Seo Woo can't even stand steady
in her shoes right now.
[The fact that she's still standing
is a miracle in itself.]
We have a comfortable pair
of shoes coming her way.
We will play a total of three rounds.
We need everyone to swap out
their shoes with each other.
- His shoes are way too big.
- I'm going to sprain my ankles in those.
No, these aren't very tall.
See?
They just look taller than they are.
There's no need to try to
look this good!
[They seem more worried about having
to say goodbye to their shoes.]
I've never even imagined that we would
be coming to a place like this.
Seo Woo said that the shoes
she's wearing are her own shoes.
She says it's not her manager who
came with her here today
but it's a friend of hers
from her neighborhood.
- Why don't you change your shoes?
- Change your shoes and let's get started.
[Changing a pair of shoes seems to
be taking quite some time.]
Neither one of them want to
take off their shoes.
I can understand that.
Just let them wear the shoes they want.
Do you want me to line
the rubber boots with something?
[The two ladies finally steps down
from their tall shoes.]
[Putting each shoe on with care.]
[How many minutes does it take
to put on a pair of rubber boots?]
[At this rate, the sun will set before
they can even get started.]
- What's taking so long?
- Let's just start the game!
- I'm about to lose it.
- You ladies are so high maintenance.
Just how many Ji Suk Jin's are there?
My ribs are seriously hurting.
Did you poop before you
came this morning?
[This kiddo doesn't sugarcoat
anything just for women.]
I've noticed that all actresses look hunched
over when they're out of their heels.
Why do you women do that?
It's because we like being higher.
- Please get back on your higher ground.
- Why are you standing on a rock?
That's enough!
[The rock stands firm to protect
this actress' self-pride.]
- Seriously, just sit down.
- This is insane.
- Ji Hyo really is so cool.
- Sorry for everything, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, thanks for being so cool.
- We can't even get started with the game.
This makes me realize
just how cool Ji Hyo is.
[Within moments, Yoo Ri is
transformed into a walking giant.]
What are you doing!
Yoo Ri, come stand over here.
- Let's just film this squatting down.
- I've never seen anything like this.
- You have to hook it to your belt.
- Why is she wearing mismatched boots!
Why are you wearing mismatched boots?
- She has on two left boots.
- I'm not playing this game anymore!
She's wearing two left boots!
[Maybe she was too saddened by saying
goodbye to her shoes to have noticed...]
When are we ever going to
get this game started?
[At the end of a very long moment...]
[Everyone finally enters the field for
the game of 'The red earth's desire.']
- Can I get a towel?
- Are we playing the game or what?
She wants a towel!
[Give her a towel before the day is over!]
I'm starting to dislike all these women!
Ready!
I have a question.
[We're just going to
have to do this tomorrow.]
If one of us girls fall off the platform,
are we allowed to climb back up on it?
- Yes.
- Really?
Hey!
Isn't that obvious?
- Kiddo! You, come here.
- ready!
[The evil queen's challenge.]
- I'm coming for you.
- Ready, set...
[The red earth's desire- Start.]
How do I do this?
Do I push them off?
[Protect your own partner,
and push off the opposing teams!]
[Physical brawl begins.]
[Giraffe and Seo Woo simultaneously
get plunged into a clay bathtub.]
[Yoo Hyuk is cornered.]
[Min Seo shows her evil side.]
[These women are fearless in their
determination to protect their own men.]
You're not supposed to kick
with your foot!
[This little tomboy gets a clay shower
in her face from her partner.]
[Team Ha Ha and In Young are struggling
in front of Min Seo from the other team.]
I'm sorry!
[In Young ultimately ends up
getting a clay bath.]
[Evil Yoo Ri is out to hunt down the Tiger.]
[Strength!]
[Yoo Ri succeeds in eliminating the Tiger.]
[Throws people off the platform
with a smile on her face.]
[Hard-core evil queen.]
Here we go again!
Fine, let's see how far this goes!
[Red clay face wash of rage.]
[Yoo Hyuk heads back to the platform
after red clay face wash of rage.]
[In Young tries to pull
Yoo Hyuk off the platform.]
[I'm going to pull all of you down!]
Ugh, I'm so pissed!
[Heir candidate is thrown 2m into the air.]
[I'm coming for all of you.]
[Who even needs these shoes?]
[What is she trying to do
to the Giraffe?]
[She uses the Giraffe as her stepladder.]
[This tomboy uses whatever method
she can think of to get back up.]
[This man is used to getting used
by this group of evil queens.]
[But she's thrown back off
as soon as she's back on.]
[The only thing she can think of
is the Kwang Soo stepladder.]
[Giraffe stepladder is the best!]
[A bashful kiss with the muddy water.]
You should've clung onto me sooner!
Why are you clinging onto me now?
[Blank Ji's throat grabbing proposal.]
[Giraffe, the public stepladder.]
[Mr. Heir, where in the world are you?]
[This is evil queens' battlefield.]
[The game is called to a halt.]
Why do I have a woman's
strand of hair in my hand?
- What happened here?
- Jae Suk.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- There is no end.
- This is endless.
- This is a total battlefield.
- Girls weren't going to push each other.
[Why make a promise you didn't
intend on keeping?]
Since I was unaware of how
ferocious you were going to get
- I'm going to have to modify the rules.
- Okay.
- You didn't realize it, did you?
- They are evil.
- They're too fierce!
- Yes, I agree.
Most women would quit by now,
so what's wrong with you women?
And they keep grabbing me in places
where they shouldn't be grabbing.
[Getting a true taste of their terror.]
Seo Woo first checked to see if
there were any cameras filming her
and then she cursed at me.
I heard that too! Seo Woo first asked
if there were any cameras around
- then she cursed out loud.
- She cursed right in my face.
- This is no joke.
- It was all just a facade.
[I will pay you back for this humiliation.]
You have 100 seconds on the clock.
Couples who are not standing on the platform
at the end of that time are then eliminated.
Ready!
[Red earth's desire- Start.]
[Using her gestured to attack.]
[Stepladder Giraffe jumps up
onto the platform.]
[A tug of war.]
[Giraffe's abdominals are exposed.]
Yoo Jae Suk.
[The two evil queens work together.]
[Tosses Yoo Hyuk off to the Giraffe.]
[Yoo Hyuk gets a good soak
in the muddy clay bath.]
[Everyone has a fierce look
on their faces.]
[Which of the couples will be eliminated
at the end of those 100 seconds?]
[The red clay couple.]
[Only ten seconds left on the clock.]
[Desperate attempts to get on
and remain on the platform.]
[Evil Yoo Ri's high kick.]
[100 seconds are up.]
[Big-nose and Yoo Hyuk are exhausted.]
[Evil queen's relaxed smile on her face.]
Yoo Jae Suk, Seo Woo and
Song Ji Hyo, Ji Suk Jin are eliminated.
Do you know how many times
Yoo Ri kicked me?
She kicked me in the face.
We didn't see that
so please step off to the side.
- Min Seo is no joke.
- No, she's not.
Min Seo with that sweet smile on her face...
she needs to be avoided.
I'm sorry.
No, you're not sorry!
You're all evil!
The couple who raises their joined hands
together from the platform wins the game.
What are you doing?
Why are you holding
all that mud in your hands?
- Okay.
- They've all got some sort of a weapon.
In Young, just grab some small rocks.
Ready, get set... go!
What are you doing
with that mud in your hands?
[Throws the mud in her hands.]
[Yoo Ri launches into attack.]
[She just wants to give them a mud facial.]
- What are you doing!
- Why are you throwing poop at me!
[In Young tries to climb up the platform
with the help of Ha Ha.]
[Your shirt is my climbing rope.]
[All four couples are now
on top of the platform.]
[Each making their own individual effort to
deter each other from standing up.]
That Min Seo is no joke.
- There's only one minute left on the clock.
- What is the matter with her!
[Min Seo puts herself in charge
of eliminating the Giraffe.]
[She could be a judo player.]
[This is an absolute battlefield.]
These are my underwear!
[Could've been overexposure.]
You must've lost your mind!
[Ambush attack.]
[Giraffe diving show.]
Min Seo is no joke.
You have to watch out for her.
Climb up here, Kwang Soo!
[Eyeing for a chance to get back
up on the platform.]
[Speeds up...]
[Kwang Soo and Yeo Jin
win first place.]
[There's no time!]
[Jong Kook and Min Seo
in second place.]
You must feel out of place.
What is this girl's deal?
I saw her flying towards me,
so I just got out of her way.
- Yoo Ri's not smiling right now.
- Can we do it again?
Why?
Do you want to kill them all?
I need the winning couples to stand off
to the side with the rest of the members.
Third place winners, Yoo Ri and Gary.
- Yoo Ri, please step forward.
- Lee Yoo Ri is not your average woman.
Please stand behind the display.
Here's the third place hint.
Do not show it to anyone else.
Yoo Ri did a great job.
- She's seriously no joke.
- She's really strong.
[More than 170cm tall.]
[Is Ha Ha taller than 170cm?]
[Gary is her current partner.]
- I heard all the ladies talking just now.
- I heard them talking too.
[Swaps Gary out for Jong Kook,
who is taller in stature.]
[Jong Kook, Yoo Ri and
Gary and Min Seo.]
- Second place winners.
- That's us.
- Kim Min Seo, please step forward.
- You did a great job.
[Min Seo's second hint and
second chance to swap out her partner.]
[Loves to play ddakji.]
[When it comes to playing ddakji...]
[Then could it mean that it must be
either Jae Suk or Jong Kook?]
[Or could it be the recently crowned
King of Ddakji, Big-nose?]
[Just could be the ddakji loving
second generation heir?]
You know something?
Seo Woo was the real evil one.
Do you know what she did when
the cameras weren't pointed her way?
But she kept acting even when the cameras
weren't around in attempt to deceive us.
[Swaps Gary and Jong Kook back
to their original spots.]
Just put me back where I belong.
I bet she's already moved Kwang Soo
away from her.
[Yeo Jin will now receive
the first place hint for winning.]
Do you want to get punched in
your appendix?
[Yeo Jin receives
the best hint out of them all.]
[What does Yeo Jin's hint say?]
[Using the hint to figure out
who the heir could be.]
I will continue to give it my best.
She's swapping it around a lot.
- I thought she was playing chess.
- What are you doing up there?
[Jong Kook, Ji Hyo and
Kwang Soo, Min Seo.]
- Do you dislike Kwang Soo that much?
- Can I make another switch?
No, you can only do it once.
[It is still unknown as to who will end up
whose partner in the final mission.]
We are all clear here,
and off to the next location!
[Immediately off to the next location.]
[Will it be advantageous to be
the first ones to arrive?]
[Sprinting towards their cars.]
[Tomboy Yoo Ri is in the lead.]
[Huh?
Where is Yoo Ri suddenly going?]
Why are you going over there?
[Could there be a shortcut?
The tomboy throws herself into the pond.]
[The tomboy Yoo Ri makes her own path.]
She could've just cut through here.
[Off to the next location.]
Do you like idols?
[Checking to see if Kwang Soo
could possibly be the heir.]
I'm not really a huge fan.
Who do you think is the most
loyal member out of them all?
Tell me who they are in order.
- Am I the heir?
- Why, are you loyal?
When it comes to loyalty...
- That could be me.
- Really?
[Does her hint have
something to do with being loyal?]
You totally dived in there
and you swam across the pond.
I thought that pond
was put there on purpose.
When I couldn't see the end of the road,
I thought we were meant to swim across it.
There are some teams who have yet
to receive any of their hints.
- Taller than 170cm?
- Yes, taller than 170cm.
[Yoo Ri's already shared
her hint with Gary.]
- That means... Ha Ha is eliminated.
- That's funny.
[170cm or taller...]
Please show a lot of love and support
for Running Man.
- What are you doing?
- I'm showing support for your show.
[This tomboy shows off her PR talent.]
- I actually do my own PR work.
- Seriously?
[Next mission location-
Cutting edge vacant carwash lot.]
[And a red sports car
in the middle of the field.]
[Ha Ha and In Young are the
first ones to arrive.]
- What is this now?
- There's no prize for having arrived early.
- You really are too much.
- You'll have the chance to get started first.
- This is really unfair.
- But you may be the first ones to finish.
Are you sure you don't want to give it to us?
She's changing right in front of our eyes.
Your expression really
doesn't look very good.
- This is a carwash?
- You guys are something else.
[What kind of a drama waits
for them here?]
- Really?
- You two are the same height.
[Automatic and instant growth spurt.]
What are you talking about?
[Invisible high heels keeps these girls'
self-pride afloat.]
In Young just confessed to me that
it wasn't her looks she used to be
famous for but for her fighting skills.
- She's very angry right now.
- Yes, her true self is shining through.
- She's changed after one game.
- The glint in her eye is different.
- I thought she was so sweet.
- Here is your second mission.
It's a game that's correlated to a
scene that's necessary in every drama.
Yes, and that's destruction of evidence.
[Second mission-
Destruction of evidence.]
[A scene that you see every evil queen
deals with in every drama.]
[The obligatory destruction of
evidence scene.]
You'll be given sheaves of paper with
your lines as well as a paper shredder.
- You know what a paper shredder is?
- Is that manual?
The couple taking the challenge
must act out a scene to earn time
and once the whistle sounds, the couple
must run over to the car and get in.
Then they just need to shred the paper
evidence in the shredder once in the car.
If you fail to get rid of all the evidence
within the time limit
then the water from the carwash
will get dumped on you.
[Only 30 seconds to get rid of
all the paper evidence.]
- I have a slight hand tremor.
- What are you talking about?
These girls have every single condition.
- Okay, we'll get started.
- We're not ready yet.
[Practicing acting out their scene to
earn themselves some extra time.]
Why are there so many sheets?
It's not just one single sheet of paper?
- We'll now get started.
- The girls have to take off their hats.
- This is unfair to the rest of us.
- Take off your hat, Seo Woo.
- It's okay.
- My hair gets way too curly when wet.
- Can't we get anything done around here?
- No, nothing.
- Hand tremors, and hair issues...
- My hair is totally curly!
- It's okay, it looks cute.
- It's pretty.
[It's okay, it's a beautiful head of curls.]
- This is after getting my hair straightened.
- It's okay, it's still pretty.
Her hair is naturally curly?
She has so many different styles.
She's getting into her acting mode.
What kind of a role is she playing?
- She's a servant maid.
- That's what she wants to play.
Why are you making her be a maid?
Are you trying to do a remake
of the movie?
That's what she wants to play.
I played the master in the movie,
but I want to play the maid right now.
[Seo Woo played the epitome of
an evil queen in the movie, 'Maid'.]
I was being kind to you just now.
[Can that brutal master be
reborn into a lowly servant?]
[Cleaning the mud off the muddy field-
An impossible task for the maid, Seo Woo.]
[Completely transforms herself as soon
as the word, 'standby', is heard.]
[Jae Suk and Seo Woo, take one.]
Look here.
Why are you doing this to me?
- You think being an heir is everything?
- No, that's not it.
Do you think that you can touch me
like this just because I'm your maid?
Why did you touch her?
[Very detailed acting.]
- You're an awful human being.
- I don't have a manager or any money.
- No, that's not it.
- I'm leaving.
- I'm leaving. Don't grab onto me!
- No, that's seriously not it.
Don't touch me and don't come
to my room every single night.
- Why are you going to her room?
- You are an awful human being!
[What a despicable human being.]
- I said, don't do it!
- I've never gone to your room.
[Several consecutive face slapping.]
- Ugh, this is so maddening!
- Why did you go to her room?
You have extra ten seconds!
[Ten extra seconds to the given 30.
Jae Suk and Seo Woo have 40 seconds.]
You can't just shove it in there like that.
- You can't do it like that.
- Okay.
Those extra seconds aren't even
going to help them any.
- Ten extra second won't even help them any.
- Goodbye.
[Only the first sheet of paper.]
Hurry up.
[But these two rather seems to be
in perfect sync with one another.]
You can be my father-in-law.
'Please just stop it.'
She keeps calling me her father-in-law
whenever we try to practice.
- We're just trying to come up with a plan.
- He's the worst nagger ever.
[While the father-in-law is busy nagging,
these two are running out of time.]
- We're done with the paper shredding.
- Ugh, seriously!
- What?
- We're done with the paper shredding.
That's a lie.
She hid these under her seat.
- She's a liar.
- She's not a very nice woman.
- She's not very truthful.
- She really is an evil woman.
- Why are you hitting a woman?
- What are you thinking?
[Jae Suk is transformed into
a bad boy himself.]
Okay, time for the next couple.
[I wonder what kind of acting they'll do.]
[Second couple- Ha Ha and In Young.]
Why is she getting so serious about it?
[Getting into the mode as
soon as they get started.]
- She's quite annoyed as is right now.
- Ready!
Standby, ready... cue!
Hey!
I'm either going to kill that wench,
or kill myself!
[The cold laser-like glares
beaming out of her eyes.]
[The exact same feeling...]
[Who... me?]
- Look at that glint in her eyes.
- Why does she look like that?
[Come here...]
- Wow, that's some great acting.
- Who else would I be talking to?
There's no need to go this far.
Hey!
Is there a need for all this?
[Is there a need... to go this far?]
- Is there a need to go this far?
- Do it right!
What are you doing in
the middle of acting?
- No, that doesn't count.
- No extra time for them!
[Fails to earn themselves extra time.
Only 30 seconds on the clock.]
Dong Hoon had to open the door,
and In Young just climbed over.
It's already all over.
[Shoves four sheets of paper at once
out of sheer desperation.]
[In Young gets another stack ready.]
[Attempts to get rid of the evidence
by gnawing on the paper.]
[Haroro, the human paper shredder.]
We're totally ruined.
Don't even bother doing it.
[The powerful looking deluge of water.]
This is the end for us.
Get out of the car.
Do you see In Young getting angry?
[This woman is getting even more
steamed up after that cold shower.]
- I can see that In Young's getting angry.
- You have no idea.
- Gary and Yoo Ri's turn.
- Gary and Yoo Ri.
- Gae-Yoo.
- She's expecting way too much from me.
At least she's telling you what to do.
I'm told that I have to figure it out myself.
[Just follow my lead.]
- What is she doing?
- She keeps doing weird things.
[Suspicious looking start.]
- She's really into it..
- You need to get into it too, Gary.
[Lee Yoo Ri, the woman who took
all of South Korea by storm in 2014.]
[The real evil queen is finally here.]
[Gary and Yoo Ri- Take one.]
[Kang Gary... are you ready?]
[How can I not be?]
[Okay, here I go.]
[The muddy carwash has now
been transformed into a club.]
- What are you guys doing?
- Are you here alone?
- Get lost.
- You want me to get lost?
- Can I get your phone number?
- I told you to get lost.
- It's just that I like your style.
- I said, get lost!
I said, get lost!
You dare to block me?
[I'm dual handed.]
15 seconds!
[Earns 15 extra seconds-
A total of 45 seconds.]
- See? Being slapped is the best.
- They got 15 extra seconds?
- Sorry, okay?
- Two sheets at a time.
[Yoo Ri neatly prepares two sheets
for Gary.]
I told you to give me just two sheets.
She's really into her acting.
[Putting in one sheet at a time
is noticeably faster.]
[Extra 15 seconds on the clock.
This could be their chance.]
[Now that they've gotten the hang of it,
able to shred two sheets at a time.]
These are the last two.
- Okay!
- Okay, we got this.
[If they can get rid of this...
then they can come in at first place.]
[Will they succeed on time?]
- We got it!
- Show it to us.
We got it.
[Gary and Yoo Ri succeed.]
[Gae-Yoo couple shows that they are
perfectly in sync with one another.]
Yoo Ri!
I want to go this way.
[Why must you go out that way?]
Stop doing things like that.
[Completely unpredictable tomboy, Yoo Ri.]
First place goes to Gary and Yoo Ri.
[Gary and Yoo Ri take first place
for this second mission.]
Okay, next couple.
Second place slot is still open.
[Fourth couple- Kwang Soo and Yeo Jin.]
[You know that I'm an actor too,
don't you?]
[Kwang Soo and Yeo Jin-Take one.]
Kwang Soo!
[A Triple Axel on the muddy field.]
- Why are you being like this?
- Let go.
Wow, not bad, Kwang Soo.
- Why are you suddenly doing this?
- No, he's lost it.
- No, just endure it!
- What's wrong?
Let go.
- Let go.
- Why?
- He's fallen in love again.
- Even though I love you...
[You still don't want me after this?]
[How did she know that she could
get to me by doing that?]
- Look at how happy he is.
- Get back into your acting!
[The rest of the men are just
showing their jealousy.]
Get into the scene with her!
Get your head on straight!
You have ten seconds!
[Ten extra seconds on the clock.]
[With their ten extra seconds,
a total of 40 seconds on the clock.]
[Calmly shredding one sheet
of paper at a time.]
Hey, you might not be
able to get it this time.
The last two sheets.
[Only two sheets of paper left.]
Yeo Jin looks like wet seaweed.
Kwang Soo, you look like a handsome
heir when you're all soaking wet.
[Heir apparent with the slicked back hair.]
- Too funny.
- You should come out front too, Yeo Jin.
Me?
Look at how long her legs are.
[Don't you know who I am?
I'm super model, Choi Yeo Jin.]
[Instant photo shoot by using
the car as her impromptu runway.]
She really is a model.
[Every single pose she assumes is like
an ad right out of a magazine.]
Give us one last pose.
[One last couple shot with Kwang Soo.]
[Title of the shoot- Autumn couple.]
[Expressing the feel and the romance of
autumn days with their water soaked bodies.]
How can she look that pretty
by just sitting like that?
[Fifth couple- Jong Kook and Min Seo.]
- Just trust in Min Seo.
- Min Seo is no joke with her determination.
- She won't even let me say anything.
- Why is she kneeling down?
[So compliant.]
That's a real transformation.
It's a historical.
[The hip hop hat is transformed
into an aristocrat's hat.]
- That was a great idea.
- It's like 'Muscle That Embraces The Sun.']
[Jong Kook and Min Seo- Take one.]
It's 'Muscle That Embraces The Sun.'
Your Highness,
please be understanding.
- How can I earn back your love?
- That's great acting.
- You are not kind hearted enough.
- Just what...
How are you saying that she is
anything like that child?
Just how... is that wench anything like
the child that died eight years ago?
[Min Seo's top notch acting skills.]
I was just...
Tell me!
That was amazing!
- That was amazing!
- Crowned Princess!
[Everyone cheers on the Crowned Princess
for having slapped Kkuk around.]
15 seconds!
[A total of 45 second with the 15 extra
seconds that they've just earned.]
- They've just used up their 15 seconds.
- They've used it up by getting in the car.
The Crowned Princess has
really bad hand tremors!
Just get it in there.
[The monstrous strength turns
the manual shredder into a machine.]
It's faster than an automatic shredder.
Why did you just give them
an automatic shredder?
He's a total machine.
[Evidence destruction complete.]
[Jong Kook and Min Seo succeed.]
[Jong Kook and Min Seo clear
the mission in second place.]
So there's only one winning slot left?
Okay, let's get started.
[Sixth couple- Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.]
- We don't even know what we're doing yet.
- Okay, we're going to get to it.
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo- Take one.]
[Ji Hyo, let's win this!]
[We'll be fine as long as you
do a good job.]
- Here are the files.
- What are you looking at?
He's playing the bad guy.
[Transformed into
a sharp-tongued bad guy.]
- Stop following me around!
- That's such bad acting.
- He's such a bad actor.
- Please don't throw this out.
Are you picking that back up?
But you already threw it out.
[This bad guy even picks up
after his own trash.]
- He picks up his own trash?
- President Ji.
- What?
- You're rich, aren't you?
Yes, I'm rich.
Is that why you like me?
Are you not from a rich family?
I heard that your house is a lease.
- A lease?
- Only 30 seconds!
[Suk Jin and Ji Hyo only has
30 seconds on the clock.]
You're giving them another 30 seconds?
Ah, 30 seconds total?
So they didn't get any extra time?
Seriously!
Why is the lid coming off?
[Sounds like he has the brute strength.]
- I think we can get this.
- Get what?
Seriously.
[Still far ways to go in his acting...]
- How do you expect me to do that?
- Just hit me like this.
- No, I can't do that.
- What are you planning on doing?
You know what she just said to me?
She wants me to hit her.
[The ultimate plan to earn themselves
some extra time.]
The glint in her eye is different.
- Okay, it's only acting.
- You need to get extra 15 seconds.
[Okay, I'll do it.]
You can earn up to a total of
20 extra seconds.
That's enough.
I'm married now.
[A knock to the face right from the start.]
[This woman is out of control.]
[Another smack.]
[And another smack.]
[Doing everything she can to
stop herself from laughing out loud.]
Why you!
[A woman's greatest weapon...
Her tears.]
[Stops her crying just to smack him again...
and again, and again!]
Here, you can hit him with this.
[A fresh stack of paper to keep going.]
[I don't know how
this is going to end either.]
[Beating Ha Ha around
like simple dance moves.]
No!
Ten seconds!
[Ten extra seconds on the clock to
give them a total of 40 seconds.]
Aren't those sheets all wet?
She already has them all folded.
[In Young already prepared the stack
by pre-folding all the papers.]
- She really is something else.
- She folded them all while acting.
I can't believe she already folded them all.
[Thanks to that,
they're noticeably faster.]
- I think they're going to do it.
- Is that their last sheet of paper?
[Already down to their last sheet.]
[Ha Ha and In Young succeed.]
[Ha Ha and In Young come in at
third place thanks to In Young's plan.]
[Second mission winners- Gary, Yoo Ri;
Jong Kook, Min Seo; Ha Ha, In Young.]
I told you at the start of this race
that you'll be playing the games with the
person that you're coupled off with now
but the couples may get switched around for
the very final round of the mission, correct?
- Yes.
- This is when those changes will be made.
[The changes made to the couples now
will be the final couples.]
I hope that you all have been
very good to your partners so far.
- I've been very good to my partner.
- Seo Woo hasn't had any chances to do it.
- I don't know what could've happened.
- I don't know where I'm going to end up.
[The men are completely unaware
of what could happen to them.]
Third place winner, In Young,
please step forward.
Good luck.
Think about who you think could be
the heir and take a look at the hint.
- That was great acting.
- No, it was a lie.
[Is a big talker.]
[But...]
[They all like to talk a lot.]
[Even her current partner, Ha Ha,
likes to talk a lot.]
[Holding onto Ha Ha for now.]
She's being very serious about it.
- That must've been a very clear hint.
- Is she allowed to do all that?
[Swaps out Jae Suk and Suk Jin's position.]
I'm positive that In Young
swapped out her partner.
Second place winner, Min Seo,
please step forward.
We have to do this well,
and focus on the first place win...
- Ugh, that nagging.
- He's like a nagging father-in-law.
[Wears glasses.]
[These three members are
lost without their glasses.]
[If I put together all the hints that
I've earned throughout the day...]
[Kwang Soo probably isn't it.]
[Swaps Kwang Soo out with Jae Suk.]
[Glasses, album, and ddakji-
Jae Suk seems most likely.]
First place winner, Lee Yoo Ri,
please step forward.
Everything pretty much rides on
the last person to make any changes.
I shouldn't have done so well
in the beginning.
Depending on what Lee Yoo Ri does
once she receives her hint
that will determine the couples that will
enter the final mission location together.
- Okay, I understand.
- Let's win this together, Yoo Ri.
I don't know what the
last mission is...
[What could her hint be?]
You're going to have to
think about this carefully.
[All the men are in extreme
state of nervousness.]
[Everything is now in Yoo Ri's hands.]
Okay, the final couples
have now been determined.
It's time to go to the final mission site.
[Arrives at the final mission site.]
- How many games did you win?
- Two.
Two? Let's trade hint for a hint.
Come on, hurry.
- Height of at least 170cm.
- I'm 170cm tall.
- Don't lie.
- I'm 172.5cm.
- You guys are seriously mistaken.
- He's not much of a talker.
[From aggression to deceit.
Women's final battle to the end.]
Come in and escort the women away.
- No!
- No, you can't!
[Where are they being taken off to
without any explanation?]
What's going on here?
Are we being split up?
- Are we all being split up?
- Are we being taken to different locations?
We get different shirts?
[A different colored shirt in the room
that she's taken off to!]
Do I just change my shirt?
Change right now?
Okay, we'll draw up the viewer ratings.
[Everyone's in their designated spots.]
The person that you're taken to
will be your final partner.
[Time to go meet their final partners.]
[The women have swapped out their
partners after having seen the hints.]
Where do I have to go?
This way?
Who could it be?
I wonder who it could be.
Who's my final partner?
Where's my partner?
There's no one here.
Ugh, you startled me!
I'm partnered with the tomboy?
[Couple change- Gary and Seo Woo.]
- Is it a different partner?
- Ta da.
[Jae Suk's new partner is Min Seo.]
Then I will take a seat right here.
How did this happen?
Did you choose me to be your partner?
Yes, I did choose you.
Then I'm the heir?
[That's what I'm hoping.]
[Full of nervous anticipation.
Who could be Suk Jin's new partner?]
[Yoo Ri swaps Gary out for Suk Jin
after seeing the final hint.]
[What could her final hint have been
for her to have chosen Suk Jin?]
[Final couple selection.]
I will explain the rules of the game.
[Final mission rule explanation.]
Here's your final mission.
King maker.
Turn my man into an heir.
Only one couple to stand on the platform
with the heir will win the race.
But the man sitting next to you
could be the heir or he may not be.
If you think that your man is the heir...
then find that man's name tag and
stand on the platform with him.
But if you think that someone else other
than your own partner is the heir
then either find the name tag of the man
whom you think is the heir
or rip off that person's name tag
from their back to put it on your man's back
to stand on the platform stage
to win the mission.
We will now start the race.
So this is sort of a name tag
elimination.
- Will you make me an heir?
- Jong Kook.
- Please make me an heir.
- Okay, I'll do it.
The victory will be ours.
[King maker-
Turn my man into an heir.]
- Let's go!
- What else do you know?
[It is of utmost importance to figure
out who the heir could be.]
First... I don't think you're it.
Tell me what hints you've been given.
First, the man is over 170cm tall.
- That's me.
- That eliminates you.
No, I swear I'm taller than 170cm.
You can't be the only one
arguing that.
- Come on, let's go find my name tag.
- It really isn't you.
I'm sure that it's me.
The hints that I have right now
is that he likes idols
and he also is...
What is it?
Are you the heir?
- Could it be me?
- I think it could be Ha Ha.
I think it's me.
Who else could it be but me?
Yes, you are the heir.
Your white skin makes you look rich.
I've never heard that before.
- Tell me what your two hints are.
- It's a man of immense popularity.
A man of immense popularity?
Really?
- What else?
- The man resembles an animal.
- Resembles an animal?
- Yes.
- You were partnered with Jae Suk, right?
- Yes, I thought it could be Jae Suk.
- Then Jae Suk could be thinking that too.
- I haven't told him any of my hints.
- You haven't told him any of your hints?
- No, I didn't.
[Gary and Seo Woo suspect
that Jae Suk could be the heir.]
I know that Min Seo swapped
someone out.
[With Min Seo's abandonment,
Mr. Capable and Ace are without any hints.]
We have to keep an eye on the man
that Min Seo's now partnered up with.
Because Min Seo has a total
of three hints.
First, he's released an album.
- Second, he's a good ddakji player.
- That's me!
Third, he wears glasses. But you've
never released an album, have you?
Even though I've never released it myself,
the show I was on released one.
- I think it's me.
- I think so, too!
- Should we just say that it's you?
- Min Seo, I'm the heir!
- That's me.
- I was confused between you and Ji Suk Jin.
Wait, Suk Jin and ddakji... ah!
- He's released an album?
- Yes, he's released an album.
Suk Jin also wears glasses,
and he won the last ddakji battle.
- Wow, this is confusing.
- Right?
[Jae Suk and Suk Jin fit all the criteria
of Min Seo's hints.]
- I think you're it.
- You chose me at the end, right?
- You're not a good liar, are you?
- I'm very good at it now.
- I've had to lie a lot through acting.
- Really? But you never used to be?
- You're not lying right now, are you?
- I did lie about one thing.
[It's plain to see that this evil queen
is in fact a sweet cutie pie.]
- What is it that you're lying about?
- Can I say it out loud?
[She hasn't shared the hint
that Ha Ha gave her earlier.]
- That's what Ha Ha told me.
- That he's a man of few words?
Is that what Ha Ha told you?
Then just think the opposite.
You actually believed him?
You actually believed what
Ha Ha told you?
[But what's the final hint
that Yoo Ri was given?]
Want to start from the top
and work our way down?
- The waiting room is here...
- You make me a little nervous.
You get a new train of thought in
your head once every five minutes.
- Right?
- That might be true.
Gary, you could be the heir bastard.
I mean...
Heir bastard?
[Seo Woo's tongue speaks freely
just like her brain thinks so freely?]
I'll make you an heir.
- Someone chose Suk Jin, right?
- I know. I think it's Suk Jin.
[Mr. Capable and Ace are trying to deduce
a guess from all the couple swapping.]
It feels weird to be walking
down the aisle with you.
[Mr. Capable and Ace are busy
searching for the name tags.]
Hey.
[Lee Kwang Soo's name tag
is discovered.]
[This couple is good at everything they do.]
Okay, put this on my back for now.
[It's up to the team to decide whether
they want to keep the name tag or not.]
If Kwang Soo wants to rip it off,
then let him do it, okay?
[Jae Suk and Min Seo are busy
searching through the first floor.]
- It's in here.
- What?
- The platform is in here.
- The platform?
- What if they hid it around the platform?
- Min Seo, this is the place.
Min Seo, this is where we need to come
when we find either Suk Jin's or my name tag.
- Really?
- We need to find one or the other.
Just knowing where this is at
could be a big advantage for us.
[Kwang Soo and Yeo Jin are walking around
with Gary's name tag stuck on his back.]
- What is this?
- There's more than one name tag?
- You have Gary's name tag?
- Dong Hoon has a name tag on too.
[Suk Jin and Ha Ha both have
Ha Ha's name tag on their backs.]
[There are several of the same
name tags hidden throughout the place.]
[Then we need to hurry before
the others find what we need.]
- You two are partners?
- Yes.
- That's just cheating!
- We have an idea of who it could be.
- We don't have a single hint.
- She doesn't have any hints.
- Just tell us one hint.
- It's about the amount of hair on his head.
[A total lie.
Yeo Jin's confused.]
- What?
- About the amount of hair he has.
I don't think she's heard that before.
You haven't heard that before, have you?
[Unable to control her facial expressions.]
I really can't lie.
[Yeo Jin's face is a clear indication
of whether a lie is being said or not.]
You two should at least get your
stories straight before you tell your lies.
- I know him way too well.
- I can't control my facial expressions.
Just go sit and wait over there
and let me talk to these guys alone.
- Come on, just tell us something.
- Just one thing. We've got nothing.
- Tell us something.
- We're positive that it isn't you.
- You don't think it's me?
- Min Seo has the most number of hints.
- And she swapped you out for someone else.
- Yes, I know.
I think it's Jae Suk.
No one's taking Kwang Soo's
useless name tag.
[Kwang Soo's less than popular name tag.]
Hey.
[Just then, Suk Jin and Yoo Ri are seen
heading toward Jae Suk's direction.]
[Yoo Hyuk gets on idea to play
a trick on them.]
[They take the bait.]
I think that's my name tag!
[Puts on an act by running away with
Kwang Soo's useless name tag.]
[Suk Jin and Yoo Ri take off after them
without even knowing what's going on.]
[All the members rush over
after hearing the commotion.]
[Let's stop them from running
any further.]
[What a mess.]
[Total chaos.]
[A group of people falls for
Yoo Hyuk's bait.]
Just give it to them.
Just let them have it.
[Suk Jin and Yoo Ri thinks they've got
something and start to run away.]
Forget this!
You can have it.
- You scared me.
- I got them.
Did you just trick us?
- You seriously startled me.
- Sorry, Yoo Ri.
[Just wait and see.]
Yoo Ri's angry right now.
She scares me.
[Back to searching for the name tags.]
[This time, he discovers a
'Reserved' sign.]
Min Seo.
[Takes off running again.]
I'm not falling for it this time.
You have to put the name tag on.
[Are you sure you won't
fall for it again?]
[Could it be for real this time?]
[A total con artist... and the hopeful.]
What's wrong with you, Yoo Ri?
What's wrong with you?
[Yoo Ri follows him down
to a different floor.]
Hand it over.
Where's Min Seo?
[Yoo Hyuk plays it off to the end.]
Stop trying to take it away from me!
[Devastated]
Hey!
We don't need any reservations!
[But what is the reason for Yoo Ri
being so hot on Jae Suk's tail?]
[After their final game.]
[Yoo Ri was given the hint
for the first place winner.]
[What did her hint say?]
[Initial, 'J'.]
[The heir's initial is, J.]
[If it's a 'J'...]
Jae Suk, you seem happier now
that I'm no longer your partner.
No, I'm not happier. We just
have different paths to take.
Oh my goodness.
[Jae Suk discovers someone's name tag.]
I see.
[Wait, that's...]
[Yoo Jae Suk.]
[The most likely heir candidate,
Yoo Jae Suk's name tag.]
[Jae Suk, Min Seo, Gary, and Seo Woo
all think that Jae Suk is the heir...]
I can't believe that I just found this.
[Seo Woo closes in.]
[If Jae Suk really is the heir, then that
name tag would mean their victory!]
- Seo Woo, I'm going to put this on my back.
- Okay.
- Let me just put it on my back.
- Okay, fine.
- Come on, Seo Woo.
- I said, I got it.
Come on, seriously!
Gary!
Come and help me!
[Calls out to Gary for help.]
[Jae Suk and Min Seo take the
name tag and run.]
[With the name tag on his back, they run
toward the platform they found earlier.]
- Did you find it?
- We found something.
- Suk Jin's name tag?
- Where are you going?
[Breaks out into a run from
his leisurely stroll.]
- Come on, hurry.
- Did you find it?
[Both members of the couple must be on
the platform together for the judging.]
[We must stop Jae Suk!]
[A physical block.]
Why are you just standing there?
[Kwang Soo and Yeo Jin takes the chance
to go up on the platform themselves.]
[Waits for the judging with
Ha Ha's name tag on his back.]
[Ha Ha isn't the heir.]
[In that case...]
[Jae Suk and Min Seo succeed in
getting on top of the platform.]
Are they it?
[Jae Suk has his own name tag
on his back.]
[Many of these other teams already
think that it could be Jae Suk.]
Please.
[Could he be the true heir?]
- He's taller than 170cm.
- He's immensely popular.
He resembles an animal.
I think it's Jae Suk.
[All the hints that have been given out
seem to point to Jae Suk.]
I think it's you!
- I think it's Jae Suk.
- Right? I think it's him, too.
No way.
[In that case...
could Jae Suk be the true heir?]
It's not him!
[Jae Suk isn't the true heir!]
[It isn't him?]
[Initial 'J' and immensely popular...
If it isn't Jae Suk...]
[It has to be another 'J'...]
I think it's me.
I have a feeling that it's me.
[After the first game.]
[The first place hint that
Yeo Jin received.]
[He's a member of the Traitor's club.]
[The heir is a member of
the Traitor's Club!]
[Popular]
[The heir of this drama is, Ji Suk Jin.]
I can't believe that my dream of being
a second generation heir has come true.
Hey, it's Suk Jin.
- It's Suk Jin.
- It's Suk Jin?
It's Ji Suk Jin.
It's definitely Suk Jin.
[Everyone's sure that the heir
is now Suk Jin...]
It's either me or Suk Jin?
I don't think it's Jong Kook.
It maybe you!
[But this one couple still hasn't
been able to move on...]
- I think my man is the heir!
- What did I tell you?
- Marry me, Kwang Soo!
- What did I tell you!
[As long as they're happy...]
- This must be our wedding hall.
- Yeo Jin, I'm an heir.
- How can this even be?
- If I'm the heir, I'll be right back here.
- You won't abandon me, will you?
- My parents can be here very quickly.
You asked if he'll abandon you?
I guarantee that it isn't him.
[While this wannabe heir is
busy dreaming of what could be...]
[Yoo Ri is busy searching for the real
heir Suk Jin's name tag.]
This is hairspray.
[Sprayed hairspray all over her face
thinking that it was a moisture mist.]
- I thought it was a moisture mist.
- What did you just do?
- Really?
- Yoo Ri, what's wrong with you?
- That's hairspray.
- You're a little off.
- Thankfully, it wasn't an insect spray.
- She's such a positive thinker.
[Such a positive thinking woman.]
It has to be around here somewhere.
No, it's not around here.
I'm not good at finding things like this.
I wonder if it could be under here?
[It's a battle against time.
Who will find the name tag first?]
[Kwang Soo leaves his hopes behind
and starts searching for Suk Jin's name tag.]
[Did he find something
under the tablecloth?]
[Ji Suk Jin]
[He just now needs to stand on top
of the platform with the name tag  on.]
[Just then, Suk Jin
and Yoo Ri enter the room.]
[Please don't come any closer.]
[Something looks a little suspicious.]
What?
- Kwang Soo.
- We need to get it from him.
- Wait a minute.
- There you all are.
[Hyenas smell the scent
and start to close in.]
- My guess was correct.
- I knew it too.
- Okay, let's just go quietly.
- Let's just get out of here first.
[Traitor's Club agrees to leave before
anyone else sees them together.]
I promise that I won't run.
[The three couples agree to go down
to the first floor together.]
[The Giraffe flees!]
[But the other two members of
the Traitor's Club already suspected it.]
[It's war!]
Yeo Jin!
I just need Kwang Soo to get down here.
[The number of
heir hopeful keeps on growing.]
[Kwang Soo is made a mess out of.]
I wonder if he'll be able to
get down here safely.
[No, I don't think that's possible...]
Let's be more dignified about this.
Can you back up the cameras?
Can you please leave us for now?
[Suk Jin's name tag falls into Suk Jin
and Yoo Ri's hands at the end of the battle.]
- Come on, hurry!
- Where's my shirt!
[Gary swipes the name tag away.]
[More chaos ensues.]
- Seo Woo, where are you?
- Wait, I'm coming!
You have to get it on your back.
Yoo Ri is like a bounty hunter.
Wait, Min Seo.
You just hit me in the chin.
[No conceding for these thorny roses!]
- Let's not be like this.
- She says it with a smile on her face.
Someone just get down here
with the name tag.
- We can't have Jong Kook come here.
- One of you come down with the name tag.
No matter how we do this,
Jong Kook is waiting for us below.
- Min Seo.
- Yes?
- Where are you?
- What is it?
[Jae Suk is calling Min Seo away.]
- How many name tags are there?
[It was said that there are
several name tags hidden throughout...]
[While they're all fighting over that one,
let's just go find another name tag.]
[With the exception of Jae Suk and Min Seo,
everyone else is battling it out here.]
[We must find it before their battle ends.]
Let's all join hands
and head over to the elevator.
[They must find the name tag before
one of the other teams gets to the platform.]
[He finds it!]
[Jae Suk miraculously finds
another name tag!]
Let's figure it out once we get there.
But I just can't understand why
you must be the one to take it there.
[Before they come...
they must get on that platform.]
[Just who will be the first to arrive?]
[Jae Suk and Min Seo beat them to it!]
[Steps onto the platform with
Ji Suk Jin's name tag on his back.]
[Can't be...]
[Jae Suk and Min Seo are the final
winners of the race!]
We did it!
I knew we could do it!
I found it by the reservation table.
- I found it by the reservation table.
- Anyone but my old partner...
- I wish it could've been anyone else.
- I'm sorry about that.
Suk Jin, it's over.
[Rushed over without even being
aware that the race is over.]
[Unfortunately, Suk Jin is an heir
in namesake only.]
[A small and humble ceremony.]
It's a ring!
[Min Seo receives a prize of a gold ring
for helping her man become an heir.]
[For Jae Suk...]
[A grand Director's name plaque.]
This should say 'Kim Jong Kook' on it.
But the best part of it all is
that my name is stickered on there.
[That's because we didn't know
who was going to win.]
What the heck is this?
Happy birthday to you...
[A surprise birthday party for Ha Ha,
whose birthday was the day of the filming.]
Your partner, In Young,
prepared that cake for you.
- Wow, seriously?
- Happy birthday.
[These actresses are not only beautiful
in looks, but in their hearts as well.]
[We hope that the next time we meet is
as warm and lovely as it was today.]
Subtitles by DramaFever