[Last week- An adventure that took them
to the ends of the country.]
[A couple race where anything could
and did happen.]
[Haenam]
[A competition where no one
could predict the end.]
[The victors of the first day-
Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan.]
[And thus, the first day
comes to a close.]
[First night- 8 PM.
A cabin in Haenam.]
It started raining all of a sudden.
We were going to have our dinner
by the campfire.
I don't know about anything else,
but Min Jong won't get rid of his headphones.
These headphones are a
camping necessity.
- Really? Why?
- Of course.
What's the point of camping?
To embrace the nature outdoors, right?
[The baby faced man looks aged after
a full day of adventure in traveling.]
You look really exhausted.
We had to move the dinner indoors with
the sudden downpour of the rain.
- It really is raining pretty hard.
- We were hoping to have a campfire.
So we had to make some
sudden last minute changes.
Even though it's a bit of a tight squeeze,
we really hope that you enjoy your dinner.
[So the barbeque dinner is suddenly
transformed into an indoor cookout.]
Listen to that sizzling.
This is the best part about camping.
- Now it feels like we're camping.
- Grilling is the best part of camping.
[The highlight of any campout?
The barbeque!]
Why does my face feel like it's burnt
when it's raining outside?
[One day is all it takes for this man's
skin to take on a deeper coffee hue.]
Just grilling the meat is making my skin
feel like it's burning.
That looks so good.
- You look like the owner of this place.
- What else can I get for you, Sir?
- You know how to speak Korean?
- I know how to speak a little bit.
I took the liberty of leaving some foil on
so that it'll help with your digestion.
Can you get me something for my eyes?
My eyes are starting to tear up.
[The hot coals...
bringing tears to my eyes.]
Make sure to eat your fill of it.
I'm sure you haven't had any meat in a while.
It's not easy to grill meat just
for yourself.
- You live alone?
- Yes.
[A single bachelor living alone,
Ryu Seung Soo.]
- You guys are really good at grilling.
- Does it taste okay?
It's really delicious.
- This is the best.
- Let's eat as much as we can.
[Finishing it off with a bowl of
spicy ramen.]
[20 servings of food disappears
in the blink of an eye.]
What are we doing tomorrow?
- How am I supposed to know that?
- You don't know?
It's because you want to go back to Seoul
if we're doing anything difficult, right?
[Cutting out in the middle of his very first
appearance on a variety show?]
- Did everyone enjoy their dinner?
- Yes.
We had everyone write down what they're
feeling earlier in secret, correct?
[A questionnaire which had them write down
what they truly felt...]
[about the person they were
partnered up with all day today.]
We will now take the time to read
your answers
and find out how you truly felt
about your partners.
Taking this opportunity to get to know
each other better and learn about each other
will be very beneficial to you during
your competitions tomorrow.
Since you were with
just your partners all day
I'm sure there are a lot of things that
you still may not know about other players.
The person whom most people has said
that they want to be partnered up with is...
is Min Jong.
- He got a total of three votes.
- Congratulations.
And also... Seung Soo.
You can't keep peeking at
the answers.
- He must be very curious.
- I think he's very curious.
And in second place, we have a tie.
Dong Joon, Ji Hyo, and  Jong Kook.
They tied with two votes each.
Don't worry, you got a vote too.
- Did you write down your own name?
- And Kim Jung Nan.
- I don't have any? What the heck?
- You got zero votes.
Man Suk also has zero votes.
- Ha Ha and I also didn't get any votes.
- That's seriously very disappointing.
- Jung Nan really didn't get any votes?
- Suk Jin.
[Big-nose, are you really
going to be like this?]
Okay, I'll read what some of you wrote down
for your first impression of your partners.
- 'My partner is...'
- No, Jae Suk!
Is this you?
- Why are you acting all shy?
- This is supposed to be anonymous.
- This is all anonymous.
- Then this has to be Ji Hyo.
Other than a little awkwardness at first,
he's perfectly handsome
funny, kind, and a perfect partner
all around.
- It's nothing but positive things.
- Why not just tell him that you love him?
You purposely spoke up just so that he knows
you were talking about him, didn't you?
- I really didn't know this was anonymous.
- It is anonymous.
[Bitter]
'What was the most difficult moment
that you encountered with your partner?'
When I realized how enthusiastic
he can be.
- Are you good at eating spicy foods?
- I really love spicy food.
I'll go first.
I can do that.
[Diving into missions without any fear...
Dong Joon's unending enthusiasm.]
All he has is his enthusiasm!
'If you could switch your partner'...
I can tell the initial answer was crossed out.
Kim Dong Joon.
I want to see how far his enthusiasm can go.
What the heck is this?
- What are you doing?
- Why not tell him you love him?
[The inquisitive minds would like to know
what else she feels for the young man.]
- Look at how sad Gary looks right now!
- What are you doing?
Can you tell me who she initially wrote down
before she crossed out the name?
Kim Dong...
[The one and only Kim Dong Joon.]
- 'First impression of your partner?'
- She's so beautiful and pretty. Very happy.
I think you two must've had
too much fun!
- I'm sorry, Gary.
- This was a survey. It's not a love letter!
We were supposed to do this anonymously.
We weren't supposed to know who wrote what.
'What is your partner's one downfall?'
Likes to sleep too much.
She pretty much slept all day.
[Sleeps]
[Sleeps again]
[And sleeps some more.]
We all agree with you on that.
I'm really happy with Ji Hyo
as my partner.
- He even wrote that he loves her.
- Love?
I'm really sorry.
Best of luck to you guys.
Let me see how some other people
answered these questions.
We keep reading the same people's answers.
Stop peeking at the answers.
[A very curious middle aged bachelor.]
My first impression of my partner was that
she's very charismatic, and so dependable.
Who could that be?
Positives about my partner would be,
she's cute, affectionate, and has nice nails.
[Sang Hwa's partner- Gary's survey.]
My partner's downfall is that she
at times acts like a ferocious lion.
'The most difficult moment that I've
experienced with my partner today?'
Realizing that my thighs were skinnier and
weaker than hers was humiliating to my pride.
That's not what I meant to say,
Sang Hwa.
I didn't get into the right position.
- Don't even think about falling down.
- Okay.
Sang Hwa, that's not really it.
If I could trade my partner for anyone else,
then I would pick Song Ji Hyo.
It's not me!
I feel so bad for him!
Okay, next survey.
'My partner's first impression?'
He is like a scary looking guy
in my neighborhood.
My partner's downfall?
He keeps complaining that he's hungry.
He kept talking about
wanting to eat something.
I want to stay as Gary's partner.
- I would choose Gary all over again.
- If I could turn back the time...
[Even her sense of loyalty is
gold medal worthy.]
'My partner's impression'...
What are you staring at?
Don't act like you weren't looking just now.
[His eyes automatically keep straying
to the survey sheets.]
To be honest,
my first impression of my partner was...
he was much more ferocious looking than
his reputation deemed him to be.
But pretty soon,
I realized that I was mistaken
and if anything else,
that he and I were extremely compatible.
He proved to be coarse, mean,
and crass.
I found myself drawn to him as if
I had known him for most of my life.
He's a very warm person,
albeit a bit ugly.
- What kind of an answer is this?
- Who is this?
Who wrote that?
The best thing about my partner is that his
face kept getting darker even with the rain.
[That would be none other than a survey
about Oh Man Suk.]
That's describing me right now!
- You're not the only one with dark skin.
- This is an anonymous survey.
- Why are you beating me?
- My skin got even more tan from grilling.
My partner's downfall?
He's very ugly looking.
He's very nice,
but also very ugly looking.
'The most difficult moment of the day?'
- I had to...
- The paper is blocking your face.
I'm just afraid that he's going
to peek again.
Stop looking at the survey!
If I could trade my partner for anyone else,
I would choose Kim Min Jong.
Because he's good looking,
very good looking.
[Kim Min Jong- Very good looking.]
That's a bit harsh!
Poor Man Suk.
- This is all anonymous!
- Yes, it is.
- It's anonymous.
- That's right.
'My first impression of my partner.'
He was so warm, and I felt like I have known
him all my life even though I just met him.
He and I seem to be very similar
in character.
What I like about my partner is that he's
very positive
and he always seems to remain confident
no matter what the situation
as well as his unwavering sense of humor,
and we seem to be so well suited.
One negative about my partner is
his short stature.
No matter what I try,
I keep planted pretty low to the ground.
And I also feel nervous because I'm not sure
when he'll end up betraying me.
If I could swap out my partner for anyone
else then I'd like to choose Ji Suk Jin.
The reason being,
he'd be easy to order around.
He's the type of person who would be easy
to order around and discard when I'm done.
Ha Ha is...
What is this that you wrote
down here?
[Directs the question to the person
who filled out the survey.]
I like Ha Ha, but there's something that
I also fear about him.
My first impression of my partner.
'What is the deal with this kid?'
My partner's best attribute?
A strong sense of self-preservation.
My partner's downfall is that
he's very long.
[Long would mean, Giraffe.]
Sense of preservation,
and what is with this kid?
This must be Joo Hwan's survey.
Next.
My first impression of my partner.
I got cussed out and insulted
from the very first moment of meeting him.
I thought he would be a nice person,
but he's a very prickly person.
Who could it be?
What I don't like about my partner is that
he likes to torment his partner.
Most difficult part of the day was...
The whole day was very difficult.
If I could swap my partner out for anyone else
then I would pick Kim Kwang Soo.
[Kim Kwang Soo]
Don't you think that's going too far?
[Kim Kwang Soo... not 'Lee Kwang Soo'.]
[Even with that huge name tag
on his back?]
My first impression of my partner is her
always sunny disposition, positive attitude
and she's a cute little brat
with a lot of love and affection.
Another positive thing about her is
that even in moments of anguish,
she still sounds cheery and happy.
[Big-nose's cheesy survey answers.]
- 'Most difficult moment with my partner?'
- 'None, I was happy all day.'
If I could swap out my partner,
then I would choose Lee Sang Hwa.
Reason being, I would like to have her
become like my little sister.
You wouldn't even have been able to rent
that car if it hadn't been for me.
Okay, I'm sorry.
First impression of my partner?
I'll have to forget any dreams of
coming in at first place.
But I think it's going to be
a fun day.
If I could swap out my partner,
then I would choose Jong Kook.
I need to get on Jong Kook's
good side.
- Who could this be?
- You didn't write my name down either.
[Bingo!
It's Jung Nan's survey.]
My first impression of my partner
was that I felt a little uncomfortable.
Best thing about my partner is that
he's strong and quick on his feet.
My partner's downfall
is that he talks too much.
I wish that
he'd suddenly fall ill or something.
- It's the best when he's sick!
- Min Jong!
I was just trying to be funny.
If I could swap my partner out
for anyone else...
I would still choose Jong Kook.
I can't betray him.
You're so warm hearted.
Even though I just met him
for the first time today
I really feel like I've known him all my life.
I'm not even kidding how close I feel to him.
Going through a tough day like this together
really makes me feel close to my partner.
[Going through tough times together
makes them feel closer to their partners.]
- I knew we'd be great together.
- We need to work better together.
[No matter what anyone else says,
my partner is the best!]
- You know, don't you, Seung Soo?
- Yeah, I know.
[These tightly knit partnerships...]
[come to betrayal and blame.]
[The biggest moment of uncertainty
in all of Running Man history!]
[Stay tuned for these unbelievable
turn of events.]
[The next day- 5 AM.]
[The breakfast table is already set.]
[A breakfast feast with
the best of Haenam's specialties.]
[But it's still the middle of the night
inside these tents.]
Time for everyone to get up.
You have to come out of the tent holding
your partner's hand
to be able to get your breakfast.
You have to come out of the tent holding
your partner's hand
for you to be able to get your breakfast.
The sooner you get out here,
more food you'll be able to eat.
It's time to get up.
You have to come out of the tent holding
your partner's hand
for you to be able to get your breakfast.
Time to get up.
There's not a huge portion of food,
so the sooner you come, more you can eat.
The sooner you can get out here,
more food you'll be able to eat.
[In just a matter of one single day,
they're already working perfectly in sync.]
You have to come out of the tent holding
your partner's hand
for you to be able to get
your breakfast.
[Even the middle aged bachelor wakes up.]
Time to get up.
You have to come out of the tent holding
your partner's hand
for you to be able to get
your breakfast.
[Thanks to the early rising baby faced man,
Min Jong and Jong Kook make it down first.]
- You can help yourself.
- We can just help ourselves?
[Ha Ha and Man Suk come down
in second place.]
[The sooner they make it down,
the sooner you can get your breakfast.]
[The natural faced beauties.]
It's not easy climbing out of that tent.
Come on, Seung Soo.
[The already long food line.]
Sorry for the lack of variety with the food.
I know you normally get better than that.
- There's no need to say all that.
- Is that abalone?
We have to take all the food so that we
can be entertained by Kwang Soo's reaction.
[Taking all the food is for Kwang Soo's sake.]
- Are you really going to be like this?
- Joo Hwan has to take all the remaining food.
So that Kwang Soo has nothing
but plain rice to eat.
But why are you being so nice to us
first thing in the morning?
I just asked why you're being so nice to us
first thing in the morning.
Are you trying to get us fed early so that
you can make us run that much earlier?
[Why don't you just enjoy
your breakfast for now?]
While you're finishing up
your breakfast...
we will call you up one by one individually
to give you your orders.
We'll call you up one by one
while you finish up your breakfast.
[Give us our orders individually?]
[Just what is going to be happening today?]
[Jae Suk walks into the ladies' tent
to receive his secret orders.]
This tent is so nice.
There are even beds in here.
I don't even know
if I got any sleep last night.
- You know the Mafia game, right?
- Yes, I know.
- We're going to play the Mafia game today.
- Really?
[Mafia Game?]
You can't let anyone else
find out your real identity.
I will now tell you
what your identity is going to be.
Today, you are going to be...
[Today, you are going to be...
either a civilian or mafia.]
We will tell you the rules more in detail
once we gather everyone up.
If the civilian captures the mafia,
then the civilian wins.
But if the mafia avoids getting caught,
then the mafia wins.
Today, you are going to be...
Ah... is that right?
Ah, it's the mafia game.
Today, you are going to be...
[Today, you are...
either a civilian, or the mafia.]
Today, you are going to be...
[Just which one of these members...
is the mafia member?]
[Today, you are going to be...]
[...]
That's it.
No hint of getting flustered,
but just calmly... 'That's it.'
[Orders are now complete.]
- So everyone received their orders?
- Yes.
Today's race is, the popular mafia game,
Mafia vs Civilians.
There are currently members of the mafia
hidden amongst the group.
The objective of the game
is to capture the mafia member.
At the end of each mission
you will choose two people whom you suspect
as being a mafia member and disqualify them.
If at the end of the final mission,
the mafia member is already disqualified
then it will be the civilians' victory.
But if at least one member of the mafia still
remains, then it'll be the mafia's victory.
But if you rank high on your missions
you will be abstained from being
eliminated during the mafia elimination round.
- Up to how many people?
- That's different for each mission.
Mafia members will have to work
very hard.
Once you're eliminated whether
you're mafia or civilian
you can no longer participate
in any further missions.
Two people will be eliminated
per mission.
The ones who are eliminated will have to
prepare lunch for the remaining survivors.
So they will have to have a delicious meal
prepared for the remaining survivors.
- That's a task for eliminated people.
- I really hate cooking.
You can all go on to the next location
with your partners.
You may get started now.
[Mafia game- Start.]
You won't have too much time to determine
who you suspect as being mafia.
I already know who it is.
[Already full of suspicions.]
Ji Suk Jin and Ryu Seung Soo
are the mafia members.
I don't care what he is,
but I'm going to eliminate Jong Kook
and make him cook my lunch
for me.
[Is that because he misses
Chef Kkuk's cooking skills?]
I second that!
- Lee Kwang Soo has a question.
- Do mafia members know who each other are?
- You should know that, shouldn't you?
- I'm sure you know the question to that.
[Even the slightest bit of weirdness
will immediately get you suspected.]
It really isn't me.
I recommend Lee Seung Soo.
Ryu Seung Soo.
The writers aren't going to be
that obvious.
[Why would that be an obvious choice?]
- Why would that be an obvious choice?
- Think about it.
I'm sure that they know that
everyone will be suspecting me.
- They'll know you'll all be suspecting me.
- No.
Why are you stuttering so much like that?
- The writers aren't that stupid.
- Ryu Seung Soo!
Ryu Seung Soo!
If I had my choice,
I would say that it's Sang Hwa.
Yes, I like that choice.
That's a nice first guess.
- I think that Sang Hwa is a mafia member.
- I think we're half mafia, and half civilians.
I'm sure that Sang Hwa's going to be
working very hard today.
I always work hard at everything
that I do.
Mafia!
I think that it could be Man Suk too.
I think that you're going to
be it in the end.
[Trust no one.]
I think it could be Ha Dong Hoon.
I think it's Ha Dong Hoon.
- Don't you think so?
- Dong Hoon gets mad when he's cornered.
It's not me!
[Just which of these members
are members of the mafia?]
[Mafia vs Civilians-
First location- Mud flats of Haenam.]
Don't we have to finish this game
before the tide comes in?
He keeps talking about what we're going to do
if the tide comes in during the mission.
Everyone's pretty sure that
Seung Soo is a mafia member.
[Everyone's already sure that Seung Soo
is a member of the mafia?]
There's almost an invisible sign on your back
saying that you're a mafia member.
This is your first mission.
This will be a very important mission whether
you're a mafia member or a civilian.
We've already identified
one of the mafia members.
- Who?
- Ryu Seung Soo.
[This guy.]
Both the producer and Seung Soo both have an
identical expression on their faces right now.
- You're going to end up regretting this.
- No way.
- No, not at all.
I will now explain your first
mission to you.
Just as it sounds...
it's a crab fight mission.
- What?
- A crab fight mission?
Don't you think that you're being
too harsh with your words?
Then can I just fight as I am?
('Gae'= Crabs or Gary's nickname.]
As I'm sure you saw on your way here,
we've prepared a lane platform.
I saw that.
There are a lot of crabs out in
the mud flats.
Each team has to go catch five crabs that are
the size of your two fingers or larger.
And you have to choose one crab out of
your five that you think will be the fastest
and you will place that crab
in one of those lanes.
- First and second place winners...
- Will be abstained?
- They will be abstained.
- You're so lucky!
[First and second place winners of this game
will be abstained from elimination.]
- You're so lucky!
- We're going to win this one.
[Mafia member or Civilian,
first and second place will be abstained.]
As soon as your five crabs
are approved
then you can place the crab in the lane
without having to wait for the other teams.
- Really?
- Seriously?
[Sooner they come back with the crabs,
the sooner they can get started in the race.]
- We have to go find five crabs.
- But the crab might have a mind of its own.
[First step in the process-
Change into appropriate gear.]
Everyone else's are new except for mine.
Yeah, something is a bit off.
[No matter what the situation,
everything is a cause for suspicion?]
[Everyone sets out to catch their crabs!]
Let's go.
[Check under all the rocks.]
- Jong Kook, I don't see any crabs.
- Do you see any crabs?
I don't even see anything moving.
What if all the crabs are hiding from us?
- They're all hiding in these holes.
- I think they're hiding in the holes.
[Kim-Enthusiastic is stuck in the mud.]
Hey, Kim-Enthusiastic.
Stop getting stuck and catch those crabs.
What is this!
- What is this thing!
- Did you catch something?
[Finds something long and lean
just like his own physique.]
- What is that?
- I caught a sea worm!
- That's not a sea worm.
- What is that?
[But aren't you going to catch any crabs?]
- That's not a worm, it's a clam of sorts.
- Crabs don't usually come out at this time.
They only come out once the sun is up.
[Discovers his first crab
even before the sun is up in the sky.]
[A big one!]
[Crab Doctor, Seung Soo,
finds one after another!]
- Jae Suk!
- Yeah?
- How many have you caught so far?
- I haven't even seen a single crab yet.
I haven't even seen a single crab yet.
Let me see what you have.
- I'm impressed with you.
- See how hard I'm working?
[Hard working Seung Soo.]
- We can't let Seung Soo find them all.
- Sang Hwa!
- Yes?
- Come here!
[Mud flats skating skills.]
Here's one.
This is where we should search.
[Discovers a field of crabs!]
- I got one!
- That's huge!
[Finds a plethora of crabs
out in Haenam's mudflats.]
[Even though catching the crabs
is important...]
[It's more important to catch ones
that are quick and speedy!]
Hey, I've already caught three.
It's huge!
This one is totally huge.
- I've already caught four.
- I have one big one, and two little ones.
Then we're all set.
We've got our five.
[King sized crab is discovered!]
This one is awesome!
What did you catch?
[Sheer size of the crab makes others
scream out loud in admiration.]
[Ta da!
Haenam's king crab.]
[Finder, Ji Hyo,
is more shocked at the sight.]
It can snip you.
This one is big.
We're all set.
[Suk Jin and Jung Nan also succeed
at catching their five crabs.]
I'm telling you that this is plenty!
[Mafia vs Civilians- Crab race.]
[Jong Kook and Min Jong-
First to return with their five crabs.]
We can even make crab stew
with these guys.
Your five crabs are accepted.
[First and second place winners will be
abstained from first round of elimination.]
[Jong Kook and Min Jong are first to
enter their crab in the race.]
[But it keeps trying to go
in the opposite direction.]
- Can you get out of the way?
- Get away from me!
[The king crab gets thrown down
in the lane.]
Did you see that?
[Bigger the size,
the faster they should run...]
- We're here!
- Come on, guys.
[Jong Kook and Min Jong's crab
is currently in the lead.]
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo's crab
is taking a nap.]
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan are third
to enter the crab race.]
[Pinched by the crab.]
[Jong Kook and Min Jong's crab is
by far in the lead.]
[Kwang Soo, Joo Hwan, Jae Suk, Seung Soo's
crabs are loving their starting line spot.]
You may get started.
[More teams join the race.]
[Jong Kook and Min Jong's crab is already
past the halfway mark.]
[Total and utter concentration.]
It pinched me!
[At this rate, Jong Kook and Min Jong will
abstain from the first round of elimination?]
It's not even moving.
[And this loyal crabby friend.]
[Not a single crab is following in Jong Kook
and Min Jong's crab's footsteps.]
[All the other crabs are still remaining
motionless at the starting line.]
[This crab may be moving slow,
but the movement remains constant.]
- That's moving really well.
- That crab is really moving!
[Jong Kook and Min Jong's crab is
almost at the finish line!]
[Falls into the mud flats.]
[Jong Kook and Min Jong's crab
finishes in first place.]
[And a fierce battle for second place.]
[They're all neck and neck.]
[Anxious crab directors...]
[And relaxed crab runners.]
It's moving!
[Kwang Soo and
Joo Hwan's crab is on the move!]
[Picking up some speed!]
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan's crab is all
of a sudden in the running for second place!]
This is your heaven!
The ocean where your home is,
is at the other end of this lane!
[The crab comes to a rest once again.]
I need a crash cart!
[Stay strong, little crabby friend.]
- Let's get you back to the ocean.
- Please!
[When one friend comes to a stop...
then everyone else also comes to a stop.]
[It's not like I can even run for them...]
It's moving again!
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan's crab resumes
its move after a brief rest.]
You can do this!
Just a little bit more.
[Just then... Gary and
Sang Hwa's crab starts to move.]
[Similar to Sang Hwa's speed
skating style.]
- You can't touch the crab, Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
Ugh, they're so loud.
Everyone seems so anxious.
All the mafia members must be
really anxious.
[Mafia vs Civilians-
Second place winners will be abstained.]
[Gary and Sang Hwa's crab
picks up its speed again.]
Please move.
[Jae Suk and Seung Soo's new crab runner
just remains at the starting line as well.]
[Kwang Soo and Joo Hwan's crab
takes the lead once more!]
[Human and the crab are as one.]
[Sang Hwa's expression looks as though
she's the one in the running lane.]
[Gary and Sang Hwa's
crab's last spurt of speed.]
[Gary and Sang Hwa's crab
takes the lead again.]
[Almost to the finish line!]
[Gary and Sang Hwa's crab is looking
promising for second place.]
[Back to its home.]
[Gary and Sang Hwa come in at second place
for the crab race.]
Gary and Sang Hwa in second place.
- We're doing five rounds, right?
- No, the race is over.
They're fighting amongst themselves
right now.
Our crab is just sitting there
and blowing bubbles.
Please return all your hard working crabs
back to their homes.
[Time to say goodbye
to their crabby friends.]
Go back to your nice homes.
Even though you didn't win first place,
you were still the best.
Time for you guys to get back
to the mud.
[Thanks for all your hard work!]
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
So this is what it feels like
to win first place.
I had a good feeling when we
started out this race.
Min Jong picked a really good runner.
We had a lot of potential runners,
but Min Jong picked a really good one.
- That was really close.
- I'm pretty disappointed.
But we had the biggest crab.
First and second place winners of this race
are Jong Kook, Min Jong, Gary and Sang Hwa.
[First and second place winners of this race
are Jong Kook, Min Jong, Gary and Sang Hwa.]
So no matter how suspicious the rest of
you are of these couples
they cannot be eliminated in the first
round of mafia suspect elimination.
- You guys are so lucky.
- There are others that I'm suspicious of.
- Can I say something?
- Yes, go ahead.
I didn't know it would feel this good
to come in at first place in a race.
- Say something, Seung Soo.
- Excuse me?
[Flustered?]
Seung Soo's so afraid of getting
eliminated right now
and that's why he's not even
able to say anything.
It's one uphill battle after another.
He didn't even stay anywhere near me
when we were catching the crabs
because he didn't want to
garner any suspicion.
Please listen carefully.
You will have exactly ten minutes
from this moment to freely question
whether or not someone is a mafia member,
or what they're reasoning may be
or any other questions you may have for
each other to see who the mafia member is.
Spend the next ten minutes to discuss and
find out who you think are mafia members.
Since this is all a couple mission,
you will choose one couple as your suspects.
[The couple that's suspected of being
the mafia members will be eliminated.]
Ryu Seung Soo isn't a mafia member.
[Protection mode of his partner as soon as
he hears that it's a couple elimination.]
- He really isn't a mafia member.
- I definitely am not one of them.
- You're a mafia member, aren't you?
- No, I really am not.
Jae Suk looks so pitiful right now.
I feel bad for him.
One person that I'm sure of is,
Seung Soo.
- But... that's not it.
- Give Seung Soo a chance to talk.
If you think about it once more,
you'll realize that I'm not a mafia member.
- Why?
- Everyone thinks that I look like one, right?
No, it's not because of your looks.
It's because of your behavior.
I'm positive that Seung Soo is it
but I want to keep want to keep seeing him
acting all anxious and nervous like that.
You're so cruel.
[They're all so sure of Seung Soo
being a mafia member?]
What good is there of suspecting
me of being a mafia member?
Just let him survive long enough
to go fishing in the next round.
- We'll just let you come with us.
- Let him go fishing at least.
I really want to go fishing.
- Let him go fishing.
- What are you guys going to do in the end?
- What if I end up being a civilian?
- Then we'll just tell you that we're sorry.
We'll give you our formal apology
if that ends up being the case.
Betrayals come as naturally as breathing
to these people.
These aren't the type of people to feel
guilty over something like that.
[Is Seung Soo a mafia, or is he a civilian?]
Why don't you guys suspect
some other people too?
- What about Man Suk?
- Sang Hwa can't be included in this.
- Man Suk.
- Man Suk, you're mafia, aren't you?
- I really want to be one.
- His voice suddenly sounds different.
[His voice is all of a sudden very different
from how he normally sounds?]
If I were to do my mafia voice,
then it would sound very obvious.
- It's obvious, you say?
- It's obvious to me right now.
[Jae Suk tries to divert their suspicion
onto the other couple.]
Our team may be obvious,
but your team is way more obvious.
[Diverting the suspicion back on Seung Soo.]
Ryun Seung Soo isn't it!
- The writers...
- Hold your tongue.
[Anything that he says gets him suspected
of being mafia even more...]
- What about Dong Joon?
- Yes?
[Directing his arrow at the silent
Dong Joon.]
- Lee Kwang Soo, I'm suspicious of you.
- I didn't even say anything until just now.
[Everyone is suspicious of one another.]
We have to suspect Jung Nan too.
- We're all suspects.
- You're right.
- Yes, we're all suspects.
- I think Min Jong is one.
I'm positive that Min Jong is one,
but we can't do anything about it right now.
Do you remember the survey we
took last night?
[Perhaps the surveys from last night could
be a clue as to who the mafia members are?]
We have to be suspicious of the people
whom we crossed paths with.
You're suspicious too.
[Even if they're suspicious of Jong Kook,
he's abstained from this elimination.]
Seeing how chatty Jae Suk is becoming,
I'm positive that Seung Soo is mafia.
[Their never-ending suspicion
of Seung Soo.]
Just let him go fishing at least.
What happens to the people who didn't receive
any votes for being a wanted partner?
Joo Hwan!
- Why weren't you one of them, Joo Hwan?
- Four people got more than two votes.
Why are you talking so fast?
This is how I normally talk.
Joo Hwan.
- Are you good at cooking?
- No, I'm not good at it at all.
Take this opportunity and learn
how to cook.
[Are you going to eliminate him
just so that he can make you your lunch?]
If I was the writer, I would definitely have
chosen either Sang Hwa or Joo Hwan.
[Man Suk suspects that either Sang Hwa
or Joo Hwan is a mafia member?]
You're not making much sense
right now.
If I could say anything about it,
Man Suk is too ugly to have been chosen.
[He's not mafia because he's too ugly?]
I abandoned my greed to be the star
of any show a long time ago.
I think that even the hat Man Suk is wearing
makes him look like mafia.
[Man Suk's hat looks mafia-ish?]
Get me a different hat.
- I'm sure of it now!
- He's definitely mafia!
[Every action that they take brings
on more suspicions upon themselves.]
There are one or two people
that I'm pretty suspicious of.
Who do you think they are, Min Jong?
[Min Jong's list of
possible mafia suspects are?]
Tell us who you think they are, Min Jong.
- There are two that I'm suspicious of.
- Who are they?
Just spit it out, Min Jong.
Tell the viewers who you think they are.
Joo Hwan is one of them,
and the other is, Ha Ha.
- We had forgotten about Ha Ha.
- Ha Ha's perfect for this type of role.
[The traitorous Ha Ha?]
I think Suk Jin could be one too.
See how his nostrils are flaring right now?
- No, he's not it.
- No, he definitely isn't one of them.
We're all sure that you're one of them but we
can't touch you because you won first place.
None of this matters to me right now.
[Did Min Jong do his best to win the crab race
because he knows that he's mafia?]
I don't care what any of you think.
But I can see all the real guilty ones
from my angle here.
I haven't said this in a real long time, but
don't act like you're quick to notice things.
- Seriously.
- I'm sure that Min Jong is mafia.
[But no matter how suspicious,
he's untouchable during this first round.]
- Don't you think that Seung Soo is it?
- What about Dong Joon?
- Dong Joon looks way too happy right now.
- And he's being way too quite.
- Dong Joon looks way too happy.
- Your ten minutes are up.
- Wait, give us 30 more seconds.
- No, I can't.
You'll have ten minutes after each mission.
You can continue this later on.
I don't think I'll be around
for the next round.
I'm speaking from my 20 years of experience,
but it's always the quiet ones.
[They're certain that the quiet one
is a mafia member?]
We need to think about Dong Joon.
- There's Dong Joon to consider too.
- It's always the quiet ones.
[Mafia vs Civilian.]
[Will they choose the real mafia to avoid
sacrificing an innocent civilian's life?]
I don't think it's Jung Nan.
Song Ji Hyo, and Dong Joon.
Raise your hands if any of you thinks
that these two are the real mafia members.
[Ji Hyo and Dong Joon receive six votes.]
Raise your hands if any of you thinks
that Joo Hwan or Kwang Soo are mafia.
One, two, three.
All of you are very intelligent civilians!
It's not because of you guys,
but it's because another team is the focus.
Raise your hands if any of you thinks
that Kim Jung Nan or Ji Suk Jin are mafia.
[Suk Jin and Jung Nan- 0 points.]
Raise your hands if any of you think that
Yoo Jae Suk or Ryu Seung Soo are mafia.
[Are you kidding me?]
Raise your hands if any of you thinks
that Ha Ha or Man Suk are mafia.
It really isn't me.
It's not me.
[Ha Ha and Man Suk- Seven votes.]
- The voting is over, right?
- Yes.
You two are mafia members!
[Ha Ha and Man Suk are convicted of
being mafia suspects.]
[Time to pull off their name tags to see
if they're really mafia or civilians.]
You did the right thing to choose Man Suk,
but you really made a big mistake with me.
[If a civilian's life was just sacrificed...
then it's more strength for the mafia.]
[Are Ha Ha and Man Suk civilians
or mafia?]
[They'll get their answer once
the name tag is ripped off of their backs.]
[Has a mafia member been placed
under arrest?]
[Or did an innocent civilian's life
just get sacrificed?]
[Ha Ha was a civilian!]
[Fails to apprehend their mafia member.]
You sure are quick
to notice things, aren't you?
Sir, I mean, Inspector.
I just got eliminated from the whole race
and it's only 8:07 AM right now.
[Civilian Ha Ha's morning elimination.]
[Time to check whether Man Suk is
mafia or civilian.]
- No, he's not the mafia.
- All you people and your suspicions.
- I think he's a civilian.
- No, he can't be.
- I really am sure that Seung Soo is it.
- I'm telling you that it's not me.
[The never-ending suspicion
of Seung Soo.]
This will be your last
fishing trip of your life.
Think about what you just did to Ha Ha.
You guys were so adamant about him.
Why are you stuttering so much?
[His truly intriguing identity...]
- He just wants to go fishing.
- What if Man Suk is a civilian?
[Will Man Suk be a civilian or mafia?]
[Man Suk is mafia!]
[First mafia member is apprehended.]
Today, you are... mafia.
[Today, you are mafia.]
- I had a feeling about him.
- Coarse, crass, and deceitful!
[Mafia member, Man Suk,
had everyone completely fooled!]
Ryu Seung Soo will be next!
Ryu Seung Soo!
We now have two eliminated players
and it's only 8:30 in the morning.
To the rest of my surviving mafia members,
kill lots of innocent civilians for me.
I swear I just heard Seung Soo say, 'okay'
to that request.
[That will only get you in more trouble...]
- Why didn't you answer him?
- Why didn't you?
I'm telling you that it's not me.
It really isn't me!
Man Suk.
Even though it's disappointing
that we've been eliminated already...
you really are something else.
How could you have done that to me?
[Feeling betrayed as his partner.]
I was really hoping... that
you wouldn't speak up or anything.
Everything came down to a ruin because
you decided to speak up.
I can't believe that I, the Ace of the show,
got eliminated so easily like this.
They really are going to regret losing
their ace civilian player.
[Second mission location-
A mud flat harbor.]
[Will the civilians be able to place another
mafia member under arrest?]
We wish you the best of luck in capturing
even more mafia members in this round.
You next mission is,
'My name is, King of Fishing.'
Starting with this mission,
it'll be an individual mission.
You will all board the boat with
your own fishing rod
and as soon as you catch your first fish,
then your mission is complete.
But the fish has to be bigger than
your hand.
- I have really big hands.
- This is so unfair!
- Your fish has to be bigger than your hands.
- Then I'd have to catch a tuna fish.
I'll try catching another rockfish.
You didn't even catch
a single one the last time.
In this round, first through fourth place
winners will be abstained from elimination.
You'll have to yell out a code
when you catch your fish.
What?
You're mafia, aren't you?
You really are acting very suspicious.
[Truly suspicious behavior.]
I'm sorry, but that just slipped out.
- Let's just yell out, 'Haenam'.
- Haenam.
- Let's get started.
- Mine has to be pretty big.
Only four of you per boat
as discussed earlier.
[Only four per boat per instruction.]
I've never fished before in my life.
- Are you sure that you're not mafia?
- He really is suspicious.
[Seung Soo's naturally suspicious behavior
that even Sang Hwa is starting to doubt.]
- I'll be shocked if it's not Seung Soo.
- It really isn't me.
- I think it could be Kwang Soo too.
- It's not Seung Soo.
- I think you're one of them.
- I swear that it isn't me.
[Even the infamously devious Giraffe
is on top of the suspect list.]
It really isn't me.
I'll bet my whole life's savings on the line.
[Mafia and civilians' uneasy truce.]
[With dreams of catching their big fish,
each of the boats head out to sea.]
- It's 'Dreams'.
- Oops, sorry.
[Into the mist covered Haenam ocean.]
- I'm a very experienced fisherman.
- Seriously.
- Are you kidding me?
- Watch how I catch all my fish.
- But you didn't catch any the last time.
- Come on.
I was about to catch a really big one,
but my line ended up snapping on me.
[Early 2014- First sea fishing expedition.]
[These two men were all flustered over
the bent fishing rod.]
I'm sure that it's caught on
the seabed.
You got another one?
[Soo Hong, on the other hand,
kept catching one right after another.]
- Jae Suk.
- Yeah?
[Soo Hong caught all the fish...
and Jae Suk only caught humiliation.]
- That was just situational.
- We're all in the same boat.
Joo Hwan's the only one who knows how
to fish, and the rest of us are all the same.
- Joo Hwan knows how to fish?
- Yes, I know.
- How do you know how to fish?
- I used to go fishing with my dad.
He likes things like that.
Fishing, baduk...
[Revelation of Joo Hwan's affinity for
his less than age appropriate hobbies.]
[Just then, Seung Soo suddenly gets up
to head towards the head of the boat.]
[Huh?]
His hobbies are the solitary type.
What are you doing, Seung Soo?
I told you.
He's a bit of a goofball.
[Ryu Goofball.]
And I looked in his phone earlier,
and every picture in there is of himself.
I think I'll be able to relieve that same
moment from that scene in 'Titanic'.
- Titanic?
- Yeah.
Isn't it really nice up here?
[The feeling of being freed with the rest
of the world rushing by beneath your feet?]
It's way too cold up here.
[The cold ocean wind doesn't care
about the Goofball's romantic ideals.]
When else are we going to get to
experience something like this again?
- Then just come back again.
- What?
- Come back again.
- Come back where?
Come back on Running Man.
- How long are we going to be fishing for?
- Until you guys catch something.
All four of us?
Let's all each catch something then.
We can take all four winning spots.
Fighting!
[Something really is off here...]
- I'll just go back over there.
- Yeah, go back over there.
He really is a good guy though.
It's just too bad that he's mafia.
[Enveloped in a veil of ocean fog...]
He really has a nice tone to his voice.
I bet there aren't many out of the 14 of us
who would even know that song.
[And the ones who know that song
are all on this boat right now.]
- That was a really great song.
- You know this song, right?
We all share a similar taste in music.
[This group's average age is 44...
resulting in similar taste in music.]
[These songs came out before Dong Joon
was even born in 1992.]
Remember this song?
I used to really love that song!
[A romantic moment frozen in time
out in the midst of the foggy ocean.]
- Look at all these fish farms.
- I wonder what they're for?
- Maybe we can pull up a net full of abalones.
- Are those nets full of abalones?
- Can you show us?
- We have to catch our own fish.
I don't think Min Jong's mafia.
- He's not even thinking of winning the race.
- I don't think you're mafia anymore.
No, he's not it.
There's no way that he is.
- I just want to get off this boat.
- I would like to see that though.
Can you show it to us just this once?
[The middle aged group wants to see
the abalone laden nets from this fish farm.]
Do you by any chance have any
spicy pepper paste sauce onboard?
We don't care about catching the mafia.
Please just show us the abalone.
[All they care about is the abalone fish farm
that they see in front of them.]
You could get eliminated from this round
if you keep wasting time like this.
- I don't think we're in any danger.
- I don't think anyone's suspicious of us.
- None of us are very suspicious.
- No one will suspect us.
- Please just show us the net.
- Nice!
[The fish farm owner generously agrees
to show them the abalone.]
Please give us some abalone.
Just give us four that are laden
with love.
- This is so fun.
- Thank you for showing us all this.
[We'd like to thank you once more
for your generosity.]
[Haenam's freshest abalone,
pulled out right from the ocean.]
Haenam's abalone.
Wow, that's unbelievable.
[These giant sized abalones
aren't very easy to come by!]
[Slice them up right onboard the boat.]
[Or just bite into the whole piece.]
- Isn't it good, Jung Nan?
- You can't get this anywhere else.
It's actually really sweet.
This is amazing.
[This middle aged group is eating nature's
super food thanks to the generous farm owner.]
[Add another group of lucky boaters
to that list.]
This is so generous of him.
Is it good?
- It's unbelievable.
- Dip it in the sauce first.
You have to try it just as.
Even your reactions tend to be goofy.
Since we have to catch the fish anyway,
I really hope that I can catch a big one.
I really want to catch a shark.
Which one of these works better as bait?
The shrimp or the worm?
The worm works better.
[Fishing novices trying their hands at
baiting their hooks for the first time ever.]
- How do we do it?
- Like this.
- What are those?
- Worms.
[Fish's favorite bait- Worms!]
I'll be the new Kang Tae Gong.
[The very ambitious Blank Tae Gong.]
Come on, sharks!
Take the bait!
Come on, Sang Hwa.
Catch something.
[Just then...]
I think I'm getting a bite.
I got something.
I got something!
[Something's caught on the line!]
[Gary's bent fishing rod!]
It's a strong one!
- No!
- Why can't I reel it in?
[Unbelievable strength!
Just how big can the fish be?]
[He lost the fish!]
That was way too strong.
He escaped after eating the bait.
[The mysterious giant sized something
that escaped after eating the bait.]
[Just what was behind all that force?]
- I think I must've pulled too hard.
- I'm not even getting any bites.
I can't take this.
I'm going to have to see this to the end.
[The giant fish put a dent in
Gae Tae Gong's pride.]
- I'm going to be out here fishing all year.
- Just be a little bit more patient.
What if I really do catch a shark?
But I don't think any exist in this ocean.
Okay.
[These boaters start their fishing efforts
after their impromptu abalone party.]
I think I'm going to be the first one
to catch something.
I have a feeling.
- What did you just say?
- That I'll be the first one to catch a fish.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Luck is on my side.
This will be the end for you
if you don't catch any fish right now.
You really need to catch something.
Otherwise, you're going to get eliminated.
[Seung Soo is at the top of the
mafia suspect list.]
What would you do if I catch
a really huge fish?
I can see the tip of my fishing rod
starting to bob a little.
[The fishing rod's mysterious movements.]
See how it's moving?
- Why is that moving?
- It's because the boat is moving.
It wasn't because of
some fish biting the bait?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk?
I'm just going to catch my one fish,
and leave the fishing world forever.
[Chances of their survival hangs on
catching this one fish.]
I'm really going to catch one this time.
It's a battle against time.
It's a battle against boredom.
But this is the true essence of fishing.
- Have you ever even caught anything?
- Seriously?
[No way...]
What's this?
What's going on here!
[The rod's bending over at
almost a 90 degree angle!]
What if it's a tuna fish!
[Could Yoo Hyuk have caught
his much awaited first fish?]
[Huh?]
- It must've gotten caught on something again.
- That should've been a whale or something.
- Why is it always getting caught?
- Why are you trying to fool us?
Where did it caught now?
Why is it always getting caught
on something?
I don't know if any of us will even
be able to catch anything today.
It's suspicious how serious
Jung Nan is being.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
[Could Jung Nan, with her utterly focused
concentration be a mafia member?]
I got a bite.
I think I got a bite.
I definitely got a bite!
[Could it be a real fish this time?]
[It's a fish!]
I got one!
[Big-nose does it!]
Haenam!
That's definitely bigger
than the size of my hand.
[The fish must be larger
than the size of their hands.]
Mission success.
[Big-nose succeeds the fishing mission.]
I won first place? I caught one as soon as
I put the rod in the water.
- You even got to feast on abalone too.
- This really is a big one.
Look at how big this one is.
Look at the size of this thing.
It's huge!
[Big-nose escapes the elimination round
for having come in at first place.]
- He caught something.
- I guess there are some fish in the water.
- Did you catch something?
- Yes!
- The top four winners, right?
- Only three spots left.
Then there are only four spots left.
Don't be too desperate about it.
That's not what fishing is about.
Fishing is all about patience.
You have to remain calm.
[Is he serious?]
You have to get the feel for it, Jung Nan.
- Look at how I'm doing it.
- You caught one fish. Get over it.
You have to lightly bob it around
like this.
What were you saying right until
you caught that fish?
Weren't you just saying that you've
never caught a single fish before?
But I just caught one.
You know those inflatable balloons that
the gas station has in front of their stores?
Do you prefer them to be moving,
or not moving?
- I like them to be moving.
- So you should move your rods too.
You have to keep them moving
to grab the fish's attention.
- You want me to move it around that much?
- No, just slightly.
- Just lightly up and down.
- That's what I'm doing right now.
Let me at least get a small one.
What are you guys doing down there?
You have to get a feel for the fish.
- Why don't you catch another one then?
- The last fish I caught scared the others.
Does it count if I just catch something
no matter what I catch?
- I got something.
- Really? You got something?
[Jung Nan seems to have gotten something!]
I really think that you did get something.
You have something!
You really did get something.
[An unbelievable strength!
Enough to almost snap the rod in half!]
[Could it be one of ocean's treasures
for this first time fisher?]
- I got something.
- It's huge!
[A gigantic flounder!]
I did it, Suk Jin!
[An unbelievable flounder!]
[All natural flounder,
still alive and kicking!]
This is awesome.
- This would cost 10,000 won at the market.
- No, it would cost more than that.
- This is all natural too.
- It's a totally natural fish.
Here, grab it. I can't believe
she caught something this big.
Look at this.
It's bigger than my face.
- Wow, that's amazing.
- I can't believe you caught a flounder.
You should take first place.
This is worth you taking first place.
At first, I felt something heavy
hitting against my line.
But I didn't pull it back at first because
I didn't think that it was even anything.
Then it started to bang against
my line again.
When I started thinking something was weird,
I found my line dipping really low.
That's when I finally realized it.
So this is how chatty one becomes
after they catch their first fish?
[Fishing success' first side effect-
They become extremely chatty.]
- Wow, Jung Nan.
- I really am impressed.
This was my first experience of my life,
and I can't believe I caught a flounder.
- It's beginner's luck.
- Yes, it must be.
Patience really paid off.
I was about to give up from being so cold.
You should take a picture of her
holding her fish.
One, two, three.
[Spring, 2014- Catching flounders in Haenam.]
[Jong Kook, the thing about fishing is...]
You're standing there like some sort of
fishing master or something.
No, I'm just watching to see
how you catch your fish.
[Fishing success second side effects-
Always trying to give out their advice.]
- Like this?
- Yeah, they bounce around a lot.
I was being very gentle with
my movements.
I never imagined that I'd be getting
a fishing lesson from Jung Nan.
Who would've ever thought that I'd be
getting a fishing lesson from her?
[Coach Kkuk is the one getting coached.]
You were totally right.
- I was right, wasn't I?
- I wasn't so sure about it first.
What he said about the dancing balloons
in front of the gas stations?
[The inflatable balloon comparison.]
You have to keep it moving
if you want to garner attention.
[Big-nose and Jung Nan are as one now that
they've each caught their own fish.]
- You have to keep it moving.
- You have to lure in the fish.
So that's what I did, and I got my fish.
I was just about to give up earlier
when I caught my big fish.
I think that's what life is
really all about.
You sure have become chatty.
[Her chattiness is of Yoo Hyuk's level
after having caught her flounder.]
I was just about to give up...
when that opportunity came knocking.
- That's what life is all about, isn't it?
- Yes, that's what life is all about.
As soon as you're feeling defeated and about
to give up, that's when you get your chance.
You should try moving the work around
with the tip of your fishing rod.
[I vow that I'll catch my fish!]
Who would've ever thought that Suk Jin
would try to school me on something?
You're moving it around too much.
Just move it around very lightly.
Kim Jung Nan just caught something.
- It was a really huge fish.
- Seriously?
It's not even about catching the fish now.
I just want to give a shred of hope.
- Who do you want to give that hope to?
-  To everyone standing around here.
The expression on everyone's face right now...
it's so depressing right now.
I want to give them hope.
Maybe I'm not suited for fishing.
I can't ever catch anything.
I don't know if what we're doing right now
is just some foolish waste of time.
I don't know if I'm just wasting time.
I don't even know what we're doing.
I just want to catch one.
[Wait...]
[and wait some more...]
[Oh?]
What is that?
Anaconda?
I don't know what that is.
Wait.
I think I need to make an alliance.
[Is he giving up on fishing?]
What's so important about fishing?
- Making these memories is what's important.
- You're so right.
[Cast their fishing rods aside...
to enjoy a steaming pot of abalone ramen.]
[Abalone ramen that the boat captain
cooked for them himself.]
[This is what fishing is all about!]
[A delish bite for Gwon Yeol.]
He's a really good eater.
How did you eat it like that
when it's still so steaming hot?
[I was hungry...]
[No matter how good the ramen is,
shouldn't you still pay attention to fishing?]
We're just getting started.
- We're just about to get started.
- You're just eating ramen right now.
No, we're going to get started
as soon as we finish eating this ramen.
We're about to get started.
We're almost done with our preparations.
Where did Min Jong go?
He's battling his motion sickness right now.
- He must have really bad motion sickness.
- It's a battle with motion sickness for him.
[Min Jong is battling his bout
of motion sickness?]
Why don't you spread out some life vests
and lie down for a while?
- I don't think I can even move right now.
- I think I might've gotten something.
- Sitting like that... it helps?
- Yeah, I need to stay just like this.
You poor thing.
- Min Jong.
- Yes?
- Why don't you come and fish?
- Min Jong can't fish right now.
He can't do anything right now.
He doesn't even have the energy to talk.
[Is Min Jong going to give up
on his fishing mission?]
Come on, shark!
Come take the bait!
I thought she was calling out my name.
[Blank Ji is still relentless about
wanting to catch her shark.]
[Could it be?]
I really got something.
Gary!
I really did get something.
- We don't know that for sure right now.
- I'm totally serious!
Gary!
I'm serious, Gary!
I got a sea eel!
[It's an eel!]
I got an eel!
[Blank Ji catches an all-natural sea eel
instead of her shark.]
[She really is our lucky Blank Ji!]
See?
I told you that I caught something!
[Not just anything,
but an arm length sea eel!]
- What do I do with this now?
- How did you get it, Ji Hyo?
[Kim-Enthusiastic grabs the fish for Blank Ji,
who's afraid of the fish.]
- You just felt a tug?
- Yeah.
This thing is really strong.
[The eel wraps it's body around
Kim-Enthusiastic's arm.]
Not only does she catch a large fish,
but she catches an eel!
[Over 50cm long!]
That's not just the size of your hand,
but it's longer than your own arm!
You remember what you said about
wanting me to catch you a shark?
Come on, Great White Shark!
I'm really great at casting out the line.
I'm unbeatable when it comes to that.
Are you standing there patting
yourself on the back right now?
Hang on a minute.
Look at my rod right now.
See how it's being dragged down?
- Look at that right now.
- That's what mine felt like earlier.
- Look at that.
- I think you got something.
It's too light wheeling it back in
for there to be a fish on the other end.
I can feel something pulling!
[Could there be something on
the other end of the pole?]
I got some seaweed!
[Nice and plump seaweed.]
Can't you get any credit for
catching that?
[Hope you take that and make a delicious
pot of seaweed soup for yourself.]
- Song Ji Hyo just succeeded her mission.
- Seriously?
- She caught an eel.
- She caught an eel?
Then I should try fishing for eels.
She caught an eel that's
longer than her arm in length.
Then why am I not able to
catch anything?
This is the only boat where no one
has caught anything yet.
It's because Jae Suk is onboard the boat.
There's that old saying...
if someone of bad luck gets on a boat...
It's not me, but it's because
of Seung Soo.
He's the icon of misfortune.
[Icon of misfortune- Ryu Goofball.]
Stay very quiet.
What's going on?
Seung Soo is getting a bite?
[He may be getting a bite!
Staying quiet as to not to scare it away.]
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- What?
What else do you expect for me to do?
One of us has to get something.
[Carefully lifts up the fishing line...]
[But it's already gone.]
That was an eel.
[Evidence that it was an eel that
had been nibbling on the bait.]
[In that case... steal!]
[Yoo Hyuk's steal.]
You know that's not right.
Why are you coming over this way?
What are you doing?
- I can't believe you guys.
- I heard that there are eels over here.
You guys took my spot.
[Original spot owner, Seung Soo,
is shoved back to the corner of the boat.]
- Excuse me.
- What are you doing!
If you do that,
it's going to tangle up our fishing lines!
Why are you dipping it right next to mine!
- What do you think you're doing?
- I heard that there are eels in this area.
[Just then!]
[Will it save this tall
and lanky fishing hyena?]
[That's what we thought...]
I thought my bloated worm
was a small eel for a moment!
[Just then, Yoo Hyuk gets a bite
on his fishing line too!]
[Another bloated worm.]
So this is why people love to fish.
- Did you catch anything?
- I don't know if I even got a nibble.
- What's that?
- That's where the eel went!
[A staff member was fishing out of boredom,
and caught a fish that they're hoping for.]
[It's a rock trout!]
- What the heck?
- I can't believe he caught something.
Why did you catch our fish?
It would've worked its way down to us.
[All he did was put
a fishing line in the water.]
[An opportunity has finally come
knocking on Joo Hwan's door!]
[Could it be more seaweed for
Joo Hwan too?]
[It's a real live fish!]
[A lively rock trout!]
Okay, I got it.
Take a good look at it, Kwang Soo.
Stop it.
- Take a good look.
- There must be some fish in these waters.
I didn't think there were any
in the water.
[Joo Hwan saves his image at
the very end.]
When am I ever going to catch my fish?
[Joo Hwan closes out the mission by
catching their fourth fish for the day.]
[With Joo Hwan's catch,
the mission now comes to a close.]
I didn't catch anything this time either.
But at least one of you from this boat
was able to catch something.
What does that have to do with me?
- That has nothing to do with me.
- I wanted to be the one to catch something.
That's scary looking.
- Is it bigger than the size of your hand?
- Of course it is.
[Joo Hwan is the last one to be abstained
from this round of elimination.]
How does it feel?
Don't even talk to me if you haven't
caught anything.
[Even Joo Hwan is showing the signs of
the side effects by starting to act cocky.]
Look at the way he's behaving.
[The ease of the victors.]
- You have to snap back the rod.
- Moment you feel it, snap the line back.
[Fishing imitation by someone
who's never caught anything before.]
- My steps feel so much lighter now.
- Are you reliving that moment again?
My hands can still feel the
pull of the line.
Really?
You should just give it a rest now.
- You're going overboard.
- Have you ever caught anything before?
One would think that you just
caught a shark.
I can't listen to your talking anymore.
This is going overboard.
You should go get checked out at the hospital
if your hands are still feeling tingly.
- Fourth fish has been caught.
- It's all over now.
- Min Jong, fourth fish has been caught.
- Who was it?
I wonder if Min Jong is doing okay?
- Is it over? Please let's get off this boat.
- Okay, we'll go back.
Once you start feeling sick like that,
it's absolute misery.
- We're going to head back.
- Yes, let's please go back.
It's all over now.
[But, just then...]
[There's a fish dangling from Min Jong's line
that he left at the back of the boat!]
He really did catch a rock fish.
[But he doesn't even have the energy
to feel happy about the fish.]
- Let's let the fish go.
- You must have really bad motion sickness.
I don't even go out on a river.
Min Jong's totally out for the count.
- Poor Min Jong.
- He just has really bad motion sickness.
He did mention that he gets
really bad motion sickness.
- Some people get really sick like that.
- Are you okay?
He's going to be feeling sick all day.
We're here.
Min Jong, we're back at the dock.
You should feel a little better
once you get off the boat.
[The boat that Min Jong is on is the
first boat to get back to the dock.]
[Min Jong rushes off the boat even before
the boat is docked in its lot.]
Let's go.
[Will Min Jong be okay?]
I have to keep up this pretense
to the very end, don't I?
[What!]
[He's putting on an act?]
It would've been okay if I could've
just caught the fish two minutes earlier.
I'm one hundred percent positive that
those three aren't suspicious of me.
I totally have them fooled right now.
[Out on the mud flats earlier
this morning.]
[The man who was ambitiously
searching for those crabs...]
[His reason for working so hard to make
sure that his crab won the race?]
Since you came in at first place,
it seems you'll be safe this time around.
Yeah, I was able to avoid it
this time.
You're not going to get in my
way, are you?
[At the recent fishing mission...]
[The man who couldn't focus on his fishing
because of his extreme motion sickness...]
[However...]
[Recruiting the help of the boat captain to
catch the fish away from others' eyes.]
All three of these experts are trying,
but they still can't catch anything.
[His motion sickness was all just an act
to avoid other people's suspicion.]
[That's how he was able to completely
fool everyone on the boat.]
Putting on this act is really difficult.
I have to keep up this act
to the very end.
I have to keep up this act.
Don't laugh. You have to look serious.
[The reason why he went through
all this trouble is because...]
[Today, you are... a mafia member.]
[Mafia, Kim Min Jong,
hiding behind a lamb's mask.]
[Continuing to put on his motion sickness act
even after having gotten off the boat.]
Just two minutes sooner,
and I would've caught the fourth fish.
[Disappointed that he wasn't able to
win the free ticket from the elimination.]
I think I got them totally fooled
for the moment, don't you think?
[He actually seems happy about
his deceit?]
- Min Jong's feeling really sick right now.
- Is he okay?
Do you know something?
Can I pretend to smoke a cigarette?
['Mafia fools the civilians'-
Starring Kim Min Jong.]
- He has really bad motion sickness.
- Min Jong says he gets it bad.
Okay, take the camera off of me too now.
[Must you really go that far?]
[Ordering his VJ to leave him to make
his acting seem even more believable.]
We were never really that interested
in catching any fish from the beginning.
We were just happy about eating
all the fresh abalone.
We just decided to fish when we had some time
leftover after all the eating and singing.
But Suk Jin caught something as soon as
he dropped his line in.
- I got a bite as soon as I dropped my line.
- That's amazing.
So is it that the ones who caught something
are always so chatty?
Even though that may have seemed like the end,
that was actually just the beginning.
I don't even have anything to say.
[Just then, Min Jong slowly makes his way
back toward the other members.]
[Keeping up with his act
with his head bent down towards his chest.]
- Come sit down over here.
- Are you feeling okay?
- Min Jong.
- Are you okay?
- Yesterday and today...
- He's had a tough couple of days.
I was thinking earlier today that he is
the most likeliest mafia suspect.
- I don't think he is anymore.
- But after this today, I no longer think so.
He didn't seem to have any interest
in winning this mission whatsoever.
He didn't seem to show any interest
in fishing whatsoever from the beginning.
- But that could be his plan.
- He just wanted to eat some abalones.
- He was just excited to eat the abalone.
- And he got sick almost right after that.
[Suk Jin and Jong Kook sound convinced
of Min Jong's innocence.]
Once you start to feel sick,
it really makes you feel miserable.
He was fine until we ate the abalone.
[This is the art of 26 years of
acting experience.]
Maybe you have very bad indigestion.
I will now tell you how many mafia members
are still left in the game amongst the group.
[Time to reveal the remaining number
of surviving mafia members.]
There are currently...
a total of...
three mafia members still left
in the game.
[Still a total of three mafia members
left remaining in the game.]
If even one mafia is still left remaining at
the end of the game, then it's their win.
[Even if one mafia is left remaining,
then it's the mafia's win of the game.]
Don't you think that Jae Suk could be mafia?
- Jae Suk was extra chatty today.
- No, Suk Jin.
Look me in the eye.
It's not me.
I think there's at least one mafia member
left amongst the Running Man members.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- It really isn't me.
[The devious Giraffe is always a suspect.]
You can just vote me out since I didn't
place anything during our last mission.
We are going to vote you out.
It would really be funny if we eliminated
Seung Soo, but he ends up being a civilian.
I'm telling you that it really isn't me.
If he really isn't, then this really would be
an injustice against him.
- It really would be unfair to you then.
- Everyone thinks that you're mafia.
But what if you end up being
a civilian in the end?
[But is it really time to vote him out?]
You have no idea what you're
doing right now, do you?
- You really think that I'm it?
- What do you think of Jae Suk, Seung Soo?
It's not Jae Suk either. I'm sure of it.
I'm pretty sure that Sang Hwa is it though.
[Seung Soo suspects Sang Hwa
of being a mafia member.]
- You!
- I'm not.
[Every word that comes out of his mouth
ends up sounding extremely suspicious.]
No, I'm not.
- I think it's Lee Sang Hwa.
- I'm telling you that it's her.
The reason being, I think that at least
one of us women has to be one.
But why does that have to be me?
Lee Sang Hwa.
[Just sit still, won't you?]
- You're in no position to say that.
- I want to see if she is or not.
- I vote that Lee Sang Hwa is it.
- I vote that you are.
[Sang Hwa thinks that Blank Ji is casting
the suspicion on her because she's mafia?]
[Did she just nod her head?]
[Is that a sign that
Sang Hwa's guess is correct?]
And you were working really hard
to catch that fish earlier.
-I think one of those guys are it.
- It has to be at least one of them.
Don't worry about us up here,
and you just worry about yourselves.
Just because you caught
a single fish earlier...
- You just caught a tiny rock trout.
- No, it was this big.
I thought it was just a minnow at first.
You have one minute left on the clock.
[One minute left before they decide
who they want to vote out of the game.]
Dong Joon was on the receiving end of
a lot of suspicions earlier in the day.
- I think it's Dong Joon.
- It really isn't me.
[Is Dong Joon being really quite today because
he wants to avoid everyone's suspicions?]
In my opinion, I think it's Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is...
- I'm just a civilian!
Jae Suk kept insisting that
Seung Soo is guilty all day today.
It is a little strange how he has been
so vocal about Seung Soo all day.
I really think that it's Jae Suk.
- I really think that it's Jae Suk.
- I'm only standing up because my legs hurt.
[Any slight movement will earn
these people each other's suspicion.]
- I vote for Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk has been acting strange.
This is so frustrating.
It really isn't me.
- I swear. I'm a civilian.
- I don't know about that.
I'm telling you, Gary.
It really isn't me.
[Still keeping up his act of being in pain.]
We will now take your vote.
- Gary.
- Can you leave me out of this?
[Gary- 0 votes.]
- Lee Sang Hwa.
- It really isn't me.
[Lee Sang Hwa- Three votes.]
- Dong Joon.
- I don't know about him.
[Dong Joon- Four votes.]
[Kwang Soo- 0 votes.]
- You're really going to regret this.
- Yoo Jae Suk.
[Jae Suk- Four votes.]
- I'm telling you that I'm a civilian!
- Ryu Seung Soo.
All the mafia members are
plotting together right now.
- You guys just let Seung Soo off the hook.
- You guys are very intelligent.
You're like a persistent weed.
[Seung Soo's very persistent existence.]
[Min Jong gets zero votes with
his perfect show of acting.]
- Who received the most number of votes?
- Jae Suk and Dong Joon.
- It really isn't me.
- It really isn't me either.
- No last minute change of minds?
- Mafia member is... Dong Joon!
[Mafia member is Dong Joon?]
- Only one way to tell.
- It really isn't me!
[Enthusiastic Dong Joon has been unusually
quite all day... his reason being?]
[Dong Joon was a civilian!]
[They fail to capture a mafia member.]
You should've been more insistent
that you weren't it!
[The members are now trying to
thwart the blame onto Dong Joon.]
Pay attention. Those of you that kept accusing
me and Dong Joon are the real mafia members.
Didn't Dong Joon accuse Jae Suk?
No, I suspected Dong Joon.
[You die, and I die...
these two accused each other!]
The mafia member is... Jae Suk!
[Could Yoo Jae Suk be a
mafia member?]
- I'm positive that it's Jae Suk.
- It's isn't me, Dong Joon.
[Could Jae Suk be one of my allies?]
- And even Gary...
- It isn't me!
[Could Jae Suk have been extra chatty today
to cover up his anxiety?]
[Three mafia members still remain.]
[If Jae Suk isn't a mafia,
then it puts the civilians in grave danger!]
[Jae Suk's real identity
is none other than...]
[Tune in next week for the answer.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[The battle between the mafia and
civilians gets even bloodier.]
[Mafia members' real identities.]
[Civilians' protest to the
mafia members.]
[Trust no one.]
[Suspect and betray one another.]
[True mystery of these mafia's
true identities.]
[Who will be the ultimate survivor?]
[Mafia Game 2]