Subtitles by DramaFever
[The world of a peaceful fairytale...]
[turns into a nightmare!]
[Who will survive from
this cursed fairytale?]
[Snow White and the Seven Dwarves]
[Flying into the mysterious fairytale world...]
[Passing through the room of
odd mirrors...]
[To the castle of a witch!]
Mirror, mirror on the wall...
Who's the fairest of them all?
[Ji Hyo, as Snow White!]
[Giraffe Dwarf, Haroro Dwarf, Yoo Hyuk Dwarf]
[Big-nosed Dwarf, Muscle Dwarf,
Romantic Dwarf]
Is it okay for you
to bring me in so often?
I missed you guys!
[Bluffing Dwarf]
[Ryu Seung Soo]
Now we know our guest!
We know!
[Snow White is more interested in
the apple that the Bluff Dwarf brought!]
I've made a big mistake!
She's more interested in the apple!
He's my teacher!
[Seung Soo taught acting to Blank Ji in the past!]
You feel uneasy in front of him, right?
You can just treat me normally, Ji Hyo.
- I don't think that's helping.
- No, it's making me even more uneasy!
- What's the concept of today, by the way?
- Can't you tell?
[There's a Snow White
eating an apple next to you...]
Obviously it's Snow White!
But Snow White looks so tired!
It's time for her to sleep!
Then perhaps...
Is Seung Soo the prince?
No way!
So, are you saying that
I'm going to kiss my teacher today?
[Fire burning]
Do you have to kiss today?
I think today will be very fun.
[Pardon?]
Your bluff is always the problem!
[The superstar of bluffing!]
I'm dying now.
[Snow White is supposed to faint...]
I'm fainting now.
Is that how it's supposed to be?
That's what the cartoon says!
Once she bites...
The cartoon?
- I meant the fairytale...
- You enjoy cartoons too much!
Fairytale!
Fine, die already to
match the fairytale!
I'm fainting now, okay?
Why do you need to eat
so much apple to die?
You're supposed to die
after one bite!
Are you trying to
get a meal out of it?
How can you eat so much?
I'm just going to take a bite!
Fine, take a bite!
Hey, princess! I think
the poisoned apple is the other one.
Yours is a normal apple!
That's the poisoned one!
Why are you cleaning off
the poison?
I'm eating it.
Bye!
Eat more, more, more!
- I think that's enough!
- Yes, that should do the trick!
That's right!
[Snow White fainted after
eating a poisoned apple.]
Princess!
Yes, an apple for me!
Eat up!
[A bite for Haroro Dwarf]
[A bite for Giraffe Dwarf]
Princess!
[Fainting again after laughing]
Only a prince can save
Snow White from her curse.
There's a prince among us.
The hints to solve the witch's curse
and find the prince aren't here.
But the hints might be in the future,
where civilization is highly developed.
So, if we don't want to save her,
we can just close here right now?
[Angry]
She's up!
Eat more!
[Forced to faint again!]
We may be in a play right now,
but a princess is down.
Yet you look so relaxed
as you eat cookies!
[Embarrassed]
All of you will pass through
the mirror to the future...
Go to the future and find hints about
the curse and the prince's whereabouts.
Snow White will disappear forever
if she doesn't wake up.
- We're ready to accept the new princess!
- It's a pipe dream! Just let her go!
[Resurrected!]
[I can't let that happen!]
The next princess should be
in her 20s!
Shouldn't I be crying right now?
Oh, no!
[Only the Monday Couple Dwarf
cares about the princess.]
So if you want to save the princess
you can travel to the future
through that mirror.
Kwang Soo, you can go first.
How can he get into his character
so quickly?
That's enough!
[Pretending to be sucked into the mirror?]
I can't!
It's not a kidnapping.
You're going in there voluntarily.
You're supposed to go in there voluntarily!
[Is that so?]
Just hang in there, princess!
I'll save you!
I'll save you, princess!
I'm your prince!
Is that truly necessary?
Can't we just go in normally?
You must stay unconscious, Princess!
Don't keep getting up
to peak at us, Princess!
But it's so fun right now!
Princess!
I'm your prince!
[Falling]
[Ha Ha put his foot out]
This is great fun!
[Did the Kid Dwarf come back from the
future to add more fun?]
Princess!
I'll take care of you!
Ji Hyo!
I'm coming for you!
Just hang in there!
Ji Hyo! I'm coming for you!
Is he going to jump
with Blank Ji?
I just heard your bones cracking, Seung Soo!
His knee definitely made
some cracking sound.
[Take care of your joints first
in the future!]
It sounded like you pulled
some muscles, Seung Soo!
I'll save you, Princess!
[And the Seven dwarves started their journey
through time to save Snow White!]
[Seoul, South Korea]
[2014]
Welcome to the future, everyone.
You've traveled through time
to come to a city of the future.
Everything you see around you right now
must be very new.
Yes!
The Princess has woken up
while traveling through time!
Because you put so much poison in the apple,
she's having a hard time!
- Bring her something!
- Someone straighten up her hair!
This mission will be a first-come-first-serve,
individual round.
We'll give the hints about the prince
on first-come-first-serve basis...
So there's really a prince among us?
So there's a prince among us!
It can't be you.
- Who could it be?
- It might be me!
The first-come-first-serve round...
You must find Kwang Soo Dwarf who's
hiding somewhere in this concrete forest.
Kwang Soo Dwarf is hiding somewhere
inside of this building.
[Kwang Soo Dwarf warped into
the wrong place.]
[Who am I?]
[Where am I?]
Please don't tell anyone about this.
Only staff members can be here.
You must find Kwang Soo Dwarf as soon as
possible then give him a piggy-back ride...
A piggy-back ride?
To bring him back here to win.
How can Ji Hyo give him
a piggy-back ride?
She can grab his hair
and drag him here.
Ready, set, go!
We must find him quickly.
I didn't notice when it was only us,
but this costume is a bit embarrassing!
I know.
Hello.
My costume is ridiculous, isn't it?
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
But don't laugh.
My shoulders are already reaching
the ground.
[He's trying to hold his laugh,
but to no avail.]
I'm wearing a costume for
your viewing pleasure on this hot day.
[Embarrassed]
Where could he be?
So I must think as if I'm Kwang Soo.
I don't think you'll find him that way.
I guess not.
He's probably somewhere ridiculous.
That's my hint for you.
What?
That's useless!
Such bluffing won't help you!
What hint?
Where are you, Kwang Soo?
He's tall...
Somewhere near a mirror?
Lee Kwang Soo...
[Searching every corner of the building]
Kwang Soo...
He might be here.
[Where are you, Kwang Soo Dwarf?]
[I'm right here]
I thought I might stand out,
but I'm blending in quite well.
[Is he saying they're similar to him?]
No, that's not what I mean!
[People of the future are getting angry.]
[Kwang Soo Dwarf has failed to build rapport
with his people of the future!]
No one has moved in here yet...
How's it going?
[Yoo Hyuk Dwarf sprints all of a sudden!]
[Seung Soo Dwarf follows him!]
I got him!
Hey, Kwang Soo!
[Yoo Hyuk baits Seung Soo!]
Kwang Soo!
Don't run away!
He's quite good at hiding.
I think...
Look there!
Someone is running!
Who's running up there?
- Is that Jae Suk?
- Yes, it's him.
What are they doing?
If we go this way right now,
we can catch him!
Hurry up!
Song Ji Hyo is coming!
[Jae Suk is trying hard
to make his baiting realistic!]
What is it?
I baited him.
It was for Seung Soo?
[Many got tricked by Jae Suk!]
Take care, see you later!
Sorry to bother you while working, but
can I have a piece of your dried sweet potato?
- My mom made it from scratch.
- Is that so?
[Shameless Kwang Soo Dwarf
raids the food of the future!]
[Delicious!]
[Being generous with
someone else's sweet potato!]
This is very good.
[Big-nosed Brother appears!]
[Disguised Kwang Soo Dwarf
is right behind this door!]
[He misses him!]
[Big-nosed Brother misses him
right in front of his eyes!]
It's so delicious.
[Did someone stop by?]
He's doing a better job at hiding
than I expected!
I remember hiding in this room.
Did Haroro see him?
He's here...
Some weird woman is keeping her head down.
Take a look at the other end.
She's putting her head down way too low.
People around her are not
interacting with her...
Excuse me, but
have you seen Lee Kwang Soo?
- We haven't.
- Is that so?
Okay.
- You really haven't?
- No, we haven't.
[Nervous]
Here...
You can't come in here.
I see.
But that...
Is something wrong with her?
- She's very shy.
- Is that so?
Is she one of the writers?
But she...
Isn't she...
[Yoo Hyuk Dwarf is approaching]
I'm very sorry, but...
- You can't come in here.
- I'm very sorry...
How rude of you to
disturb their meeting.
[Cutting Yoo Hyuk out]
Has he left?
I'm very sorry.
This will be quick.
Get out if you're sorry!
- You should leave first!
- Get out of there!
[First order of business is
blocking Jae Suk.]
[What is it?]
Kwang Soo!
It's so obvious that it's you!
How did you know?
Only idiots couldn't tell
that it's you!
If we win together, we can
win prizes together too!
Let's make this easy!
You know that I'm not
on anyone's side, right?
I know! But are you
going to go to Jae Suk again?
Or side with Jong Kook?
I guess you have a point.
- Where should I go?
- Let's get out of here first.
Let's go, Kwang Soo!
We must leave now!
I'm not going to go with you
if you coerce me like that!
I'm sorry.
Please come with me.
- I'll come with you...
- Quickly, before someone else sees you!
We must run to that emergency exit!
- Thank you.
- Thanks! Quickly, Kwang Soo!
Where's the emergency exit here?
Get down!
Kwang Soo!
Quickly, come this way.
Kwang Soo cannot be using his legs
to move around.
He always must be on someone's back.
On my back!
Quickly, to the first floor!
If we continue like this, we'll win!
We will be victorious!
I want to win too, Kwang Soo!
And that's going to be today!
Let's get off first.
Where should we go?
Where are we going?
We're on our way to victory!
We're almost there.
Almost there!
[Yoo Hyuk and Seung Soo dwarves appear!]
I'm sorry.
Didn't expect to see you here!
Wait, are you going to do this by force?
You can take him up to there.
That's total nonsense.
Just take him up to there.
Otherwise, Jong Kook will...
Oh no, he's here!
[Kook and Gary dwarves join!]
You're the one who found him...
And what will I get from finding him?
Your job was just carrying
him up to here.
There was no point in finding him!
[One must arrive at this table
with Kwang Soo to win!]
[Seung Soo Dwarf tries to carry him.]
[Seung Soo Dwarf fails to carry him.]
Why are you doing this to me?
- I'll give you a piggyback ride!
- Let's form a line!
Snow White joins!
Now she's here!
Damn!
I realized no one was inside!
[This way, Kwang Soo!]
Jump! Jump!
I said jump, you idiot!
[Huge chaos]
Why can't you even run?
[Putting it all on poor Kwang Soo.]
Kwang Soo, it's so unfair!
Let's all make a line here...
And face the table while Kwang Soo
chooses one person for piggyback ride!
- Let's make this simple!
- Okay!
Don't look!
I'm making my choice!
Speak if you must, Seung Soo!
[One moment, Kwang Soo.]
[Seung Soo's cheap trick fails.]
That was a dirty play!
[Harsh criticisms]
- Remove him from this round!
- Disqualified!
Drag him out!
[He's removed from this round.]
What a dirty trick!
Why is he holding a cell phone?
What's going on?
[Giving him a leg split as punishment.]
One, two, three.
Do it one more time!
Don't do it!
Too much!
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo make it
while everyone is distracted!]
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo win
the first mission!]
It's all because of you, Seung Soo!
[All the blame is going to Seung Soo!]
Traitors, cross!
What the heck were you thinking?
[Criticism against Seung Soo
is not calming down.]
You shouldn't have let your
guard down!
[Anyway, Ha Ha and Kwang Soo win!]
The winners of the first round
are Ha Ha and Kwang Soo!
You can just hang out here
and watch them do other missions.
No problem.
This is great!
What did I tell you?
I'll give your next mission right now.
The second mission is
"Talk with Your Nose."
Suk Jin is going to win then!
[Big-nosed Brother has the best nose!]
You must go find computers with
R stickers on them...
and type "Snow White and the Seven Dwarves"
with your nose.
I'll end up pressing
multiple keys at the same time!
After typing, print it and return.
I don't know how to print!
The first dwarf that comes back
will be the winner.
I don't know how to print documents!
You can go to "File," then press "Print."
Can you intercept someone else's paper?
[No interception allowed]
So how can I print again?
Jong Kook!
Just type with your nose first...
Then just yell out, "Print!"
There'll be only one winner in this round,
and the winner will receive the second hint.
Start!
Good luck!
No one's taking care of Kwang Soo's hat.
[The law of game shows is about
being opportunistic!]
[First-come-first-serve...
Speed is key!]
Close it, close it now!
No room for everyone.
I'm sorry!
[They're in such a big hurry,
they leave their cameramen behind!]
- They'll wait for us, right?
- Do you know which floor they went to?
[First, find a computer with an R sticker!]
I'm sorry.
[Only five computers have
the R sticker!]
Where's my cameraman?
[Big-nosed Brother hasn't reunited
with his cameraman yet!]
[Yoo Hyuk Dwarf discovers an R sticker!]
[He starts his mission right away.]
Don't do this!
I was here first!
There are many people here.
Don't be embarrassing.
- Just let me type it once.
- You may not.
Just go find another one.
I was here first!
That means nothing!
Why are you doing this?
Don't be like this!
I guess it'll be quicker to find
another computer!
- Of course.
- I'll find something else!
This is very difficult!
What am I doing?
[Gary Dwarf is trying his best too!]
Wrong character!
Please, please...
Excuse me, ma'am. I'm sorry...
[Big-nosed Brother finds a computer!]
This isn't working!
I can't press it key by key!
Because my nose is big!
He's here!
What?
Already?
Where is my cameraman?
It's invalid if there's no footage of you!
It doesn't mean anything!
You couldn't even try it?
No.
He didn't follow me!
I've never encountered such a situation.
[Snow White and...]
My nose...
[Yoo Hyuk Dwarf is slowly getting there.]
I'm a computer genius!
Did you see how accurate I was?
I'm not even a bird!
Snow White appears!
[Snow White and the Seven Dwarves]
[Now that he's done typing...]
Everything's over!
[All he needs is to print.]
How can I print this?
Ji Hyo!
[Interference by Snow White!]
Where's the printer?
[He'll win once he brings back the paper!]
[A chase between Snow White and a dwarf
that would never happen in the fairytale.]
Jae Suk is here!
Then what happens to me?
I think he has something
in his pocket.
We must confirm with
your cameraman.
Sit down!
[No title]
[Snow White and the Seven Dwarves]
[Yoo Hyuk Dwarf wins!]
He came down first, but
his cameraman wasn't with him...
So he was here first, then why...
What's going on?
He has the sticker!
[Snow White and the Seven Dwarves]
[Has Seung Soo won too?]
My cameraman didn't follow me!
Why?
Is he okay?
Is he sick?
Seung Soo must be feeling cheated.
Here's your cameraman.
How come you guys separated?
I couldn't find him after
he went up on a different elevator.
- Why did you do that?
- So you went up before he did?
You should've gone with him.
We and the cameramen are one-bodied!
The elevator got full...
Then you should've waited for him
after you got off!
- So it's invalid?
- Yes.
I went crazy
and tried so hard!
You did it like this?
That's incorrect!
We have a witness from the
11th floor.
[Moments ago]
Is there a computer that can print?
Does this print?
[Typing...]
Which printer can I use?
[The suspect easily gets the printout
after typing with hands...]
We have a witness from the 11th floor.
What does he say?
He says you printed it
after typing with your hands.
Because there were no cameras!
- He's a repeating offender!
- What a swindler!
He tried to trick us with a water bottle
the other time...
Should we report him to the police?
He then lies about the whole thing!
His tricks are very bad!
How great.
- But Running Man is the best!
- Why?
You find out everything!
[We're always watching.]
Therefore, Yoo Jae Suk is the
sole winner of this round!
This isn't fun!
It's because his nose is pointy!
Just watch the show, all of us had fun!
Such a thrilling race!
But can I please wear something else?
I'm so embarrassed!
- This costume doesn't breathe well!
- But you're an actress!
You may take a break, Princess.
You shouldn't just call her princess.
Treat me like a princess!
I'm no princess right now!
Ji Hyo is no princess right now!
She's truly scaring me!
This random person in the elevator couldn't
even keep a straight face in front of me!
He turned around from me
and violently shook his shoulders!
I can't fathom how hard it is for her!
So the next mission is...
[Finding hidden stilettos
and brick handbags!]
Whoever returns to the
starting point first wins!
[It's a tight race between
Snow White and Kook Dwarf!]
[Something that you can never find
in the fairytale world...]
[A speed race between
Snow White and a dwarf!]
[Who will be victorious?]
[Yoo Hyuk, Haroro, and Giraffe Dwarves
are blocking Kook Dwarf!]
Hurry, Ji Hyo!
Quickly!
[Dwarves are always on Snow White's side!]
Snow White wins the third round!
Done!
[Kook Dwarf in second place!]
This is so tiring.
Why do girls wear such exhausting shoes?
He's coming!
Suk Jin is coming!
- Seung Soo is also coming!
- Seung Soo!
[A race between Big-nosed Dwarf and
Bluffing Dwarf for third place!]
Suk Jin is coming!
[This is as tight as the race for the first place!]
[A battle of pride between
middle-aged dwarves!]
[Bluff Dwarf wins by a split second!]
Suk Jin couldn't even put it on!
Gary couldn't even find it!
I got annoyed.
I'm not even kidding!
I really got annoyed!
We'll give different hints
according to your placement...
Who is the prince?
Which place am I?
There are different hints
according to your placement...
I'll give them out.
These are for your eyes only.
[Hint handout completed]
[Who is the prince among them?]
- Seung Soo.
- What?
Why do you keep calling yourself
an ace?
I really think that
us three are the aces of this show.
You should clean those
bread crumbs first.
- You do bluff quite a lot!
- Of course!
Let me ask you this. What
should I do with my hands when I act?
It's an excellent question.
There should be only one thing
in your head when you act.
Emotion.
Then your body follows?
The fact that you're conscious about your hand
movements already shows that you're not focused.
You saw us acting when
we ran into the mirror before, right?
I was very surprised by
Kwang Soo's acting.
Because he's good?
Because I was so embarrassed!
My face turned red!
How can you be eating bread
after just eating your lunch?
There's a reason why
you're getting fat.
These are all muscles.
[Bluffing Overload]
Please don't do this!
Just don't do it!
His bluffing is too much!
[The Han River Citizens Park]
[Mang Won District]
If everyone completes the mission
successfully...
We'll tell you the place where
the secret of the curse is hidden.
As you can see, there are helmets
in front of you.
Wear those helmets,
and get on those pogo sticks.
Then jump to pop those balloons
with your helmets.
There are eight of you right now.
One of you must stand under that
water balloon.
Everyone must pop the other balloons
before the water balloon pops.
I think Kwang Soo should stand
under there!
No, I want to pop balloons!
- I wholeheartedly recommend Kwang Soo!
- I think Kwang Soo should do it!
I guess it isn't fair to corner
one person against his will.
So let's vote on it.
- Votes for Kwang Soo?
- Yea!
Kwang Soo should stand under the water
balloon per the result of our voting.
Do your best, dwarves!
[All other balloons must be popped
before the water balloon pops!]
I think more capable people
must get that balloon first.
Then Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and I
will start with that one.
Do you think you're really capable?
You're not any different from me!
His bluffing is overbearing!
You're just like me!
Let's get it done in one try!
Cheers!
The second one.
Don't worry.
What's going on?
Is it really going to pop?
[The water balloon started to inflate
at a scary speed.]
[Tiger Dwarf is quite good at
riding pogo stick.]
- Right there!
- This one?
[Fails to touch the balloon.]
There's no one who can do it!
Jump!
[Please save this Giraffe Dwarf!]
[One balloon per person.]
[The second dwarf, Jae Suk, is going.]
That's great!
[Let's go!]
[Jae Suk on a pogo stick keeps missing.]
One more time!
[Nearing explosion]
- Where is it?
- Right there!
[Jae Suk Dwarf loses his sense of direction.]
[Anger explosion]
Jae Suk, please!
Take your time and do it at once!
This balloon is for Ji Hyo!
[That's mine!]
[Let's jump again!]
Give it a strong one!
One, two, three!
[He has jumped over 100 times...]
[So close, yet so far]
Just come back!
I said push up!
[Stress level of the dwarves increasing.]
Pop it!
Pop the damn thing!
Do something!
Did you just buy a hat?
He's just like
Mr. Mousse Kim!
We really can't do this.
Can you switch the pogo sticks?
To the one before?
I think the other one is more reliable.
Does anybody care about
what happened to me?
Get your hand off of me!
[We'll care about you because
you have awesome hair!]
Let's vote again on
who'll stand under the water balloon.
- Let's vote again.
- We're sorry.
This is no easy feat!
We're sorry!
So to be fair, each of you can
come up to me and whisper your choice...
Lee Kwang Soo!
You should whisper!
Kwang Soo.
You.
It's 2:1 between us.
Two votes each!
Is it 2:2?
It's now 3:2!
So it all depends on me?
It's now 4:2!
Now it's 4:3!
I still have to vote.
5:3 for Lee Kwang Soo!
It was a tight race!
- You must succeed this time!
- Of course!
Let's try our best for Kwang Soo!
For Kwang Soo!
This is our last chance!
Who's going to go first?
Let's decide on the order.
Jae Suk goes first,
Kook second...
Seung Soo goes third.
Only the aces...
Why do you keep saying
"Only the aces?"
Seung Soo is willing to go third.
Jong Kook, me, then him.
He always includes himself
among the top three performers!
He's not any different from me!
He declares himself to be an ace!
His bluffing is starting again!
- He's so relaxed now!
- Are you okay?
You'll be so scared!
I feel comfortable
as if I'm at my home.
You look like Jack from
Jack and the Beanstalk.
[Fairytale character
with a water balloon]
[Tiger Dwarf begins!]
[I believe in you guys...]
[Very fast!]
[This is also very fast!]
Show us what you got, ace!
[The bluffing ace succeeds]
We got it this time.
We got it, Kwang Soo!
[Blank Ji the Snow White
is riding a pogo stick!]
[Quite a speed!]
[At this rate...]
[Force of a pressure cooker!]
Quickly!
[Too short]
[Kwang Soo, ready?]
[Is it too much for
the real dwarf, Ha Ha?]
What are you doing?
[Nervous]
[Water slap!]
[Handsome Kwang Soo]
It was hilarious!
[The hairstyle of Giraffe Dwarf
is changing on its own.]
How do you want it, sir?
[They must succeed at this so they can
get the hint and go save the princess...]
- How about the third time?
- What?
What is he doing?
[An endless discussion on
who'll go under the water balloon begins!]
We must vote again.
One person at a time.
I vote for Snow White!
Kwang Soo.
Ji Suk Jin.
One vote for Ji Suk Jin...
Two votes for Ji Suk Jin...
You.
Three votes for you.
Hey, do this right!
[Exploding popularity.]
You're supposed to respect
your elders!
[Congratulations!]
Let's make it this time!
[Blank Ji Snow White begins]
Hurry up!
[She's still an ace
even after becoming Snow White!]
No!
[The sound of air is causing fear!]
It's not boiling water, is it?
[Almost!]
[Lost his balance.]
[It might pop soon.]
No!
This is so scary!
[5cm difference!]
[Coaching]
[What is this?]
[It's touching my head!]
[Bluffing Ace goes pop!]
[Big-nosed Brother goes pop too!]
[Angry Big-nosed Brother]
We though we'd make it this time...
Get out there!
You do it!
[Big-nosed Dwarf's attempt at conscription.]
We really though we'd make it this time.
You've calmed down, right?
We're truly sorry about that.
Are you calm?
- I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
- I'm sorry too.
I'm sorry!
When it touched my head,
I was so scared...
[Sadness of a middle-aged dwarf]
How can you set it up so scary?
[Giraffe Dwarf goes back to the water balloon
to protect the middle-aged dwarves!]
You got this!
[Tiger Dwarf aggressively moves forward!]
Seung Soo is too fixated on
the order!
[Bluffing Ace goes against the order.]
Quickly, mister!
[Save me]
[Good pace]
[Princess Blank Ji succeeds.]
[The sound of a pressure cooker
before its lid explodes!]
[Speed is everything!]
[Rocket]
[You know how I feel right now!]
Quickly, Suk Jin!
[It touches!]
Oh my God!
Where are you, Kwang Soo?
Hurry up!
[Which balloon will explode first?]
[Mission successful!]
[A celebratory pop!]
[Nice teamwork between
Snow White and the Seven Dwarves.]
It was harder to deal with
all that nerve!
As promised, I'll tell you where
the secret of the curse is hidden.
But why do we have to be
cursed all the time?
We spend our week, living innocent lives,
working hard.
Then we come here, only to be cursed!
What have we done to deserve
this curse?
We all have loving families too!
[I'll give you the hint on
where the curse's hint is located.]
[Everyone gets the hint about
where the curse's secret is at.]
[It's time to return to the past
to save Snow White.]
[A small village in a forest.]
[Dotted by many sparkling stars.]
[The land of fairytale.]
[Warping back to this land of fairytale!]
[This is...]
[The land of fairytale where they
used to live!]
Where is Snow White?
You were the one holding her!
You were holding her!
Where did she go?
Snow White!
[Where is Snow White?]
[In the highest place of this land,
in the most secluded room...]
[Snow White sleeps after
eating a poisoned apple.]
[Will the Dwarves be able to remove
Snow White's curse?]
Where's White?
Snow White?
Is this showing something?
[The mirror is showing something!]
Dear Dwarves, the Princess is still asleep
somewhere in the village because of her curse.
Only a prince will be able to
wake her up.
Only a (forehead) kiss from the prince
can wake the princess...
And the only surviving dwarf may bring
the prince to the princess.
So one of the dwarves must go with the
prince to wake her up.
After ousting all the other dwarves!
So there is really a prince among us, right?
The Prince himself doesn't know it yet.
Even to the prince, it'd be most beneficial
to reserve a dwarf that's most likely to survive...
Don't assume that it'll be you!
At least from the prince's perspective...
If you keep behaving like this,
all the dwarves will unite against you!
He should go first!
Be careful!
Stop provoking us!
Seung Soo has decided
that he's the prince already.
[Is it obvious?]
You're not!
You're just conceited!
Shouldn't something like this
be decided by age?
Unfortunately, the witch has
cursed all of your dwarves.
The curse will have each one of you
to be ousted in an unique way.
Use the hints from the future
to figure out the truth of the curse.
And there are many pieces of gold, your
favorite metal, hidden throughout this town.
You'll be able to keep them
when you find them!
Once you oust other dwarves,
you may keep their gold too.
It's over!
But if someone removes the prince's name tag,
he'll be ousted and thus can't remove the curse.
So be careful.
We need to know whom the prince is.
So we can't oust the prince
and the way to oust other dwarves is
something other than removing the name tags.
I believe that you'll find the prince
to break the curse and save the princess!
I'm just going to focus on
mining the gold.
I'll have him find all the gold
and then oust him!
Leave Suk Jin alone so he
can find gold.
Once he has enough gold,
find the way to oust him.
So how can I oust other dwarves?
You have it in your envelope.
You need to figure that out.
I have the way to oust Suk Jin right here.
Rub his nose three times...
[Two hints from the future, one about
the place, and one about the prince!]
You may begin!
I think you're the prince.
Do you think so?
I represent all short people.
- I'll serve you well.
- Sure...
All the gold will be ours!
Who cares about the princess?
[Jae Suk Dwarf is reading his hints
in a secluded place.]
[Castle of the Dwarves]
[The next hint is about the prince.]
[The Prince speaks eloquently.]
Is it me?
[Getting ahead of himself.]
Who could it be?
[Someone who speaks eloquently...]
Ha Ha...
Suk Jin...
[The Prince is famous in neighboring countries.]
[Seung Soo's hint for the prince]
The Prince is not very bright.
[Big-nosed Brother's hint]
That's not a good hint.
Everyone in the group isn't bright!
Who could it be?
Gary?
Gary, Kwang Soo...
I'm feeling something.
The first hint...
[It's not you.]
What the heck is this?
So I'm not the prince.
I knew it.
What is this?
The book that has
the witch's curse!
The Witch's Curse...
It's gold!
Someone will be ousted if
his hair is pulled out.
This curse can only oust a specific person,
and the way to oust each dwarf is unique.
You don't know to whom this curse applies,
so you should be careful on how to use this.
[Someone will be ousted when
his hair gets pulled out.]
The Witch's Curse...
Someone will be ousted if he gets flicked
in his forehead by a hand in an apple glove.
Someone will be ousted if I flick that person's
forehead while wearing an apple glove.
Should I try flicking my own forehead?
[Apple Glove = Regular Glove]
If I die while testing this,
it's over.
It'd be so unfair for me
to be ousted like this!
Should I do it?
I'm not dead!
[So happy to live longer]
But I shouldn't use it right away.
I should wait and see first.
Where is this "Castle of the Dwarves?"
I've been searching the entire village!
Is that it?
Huh?
[That's the Castle of the Dwarves!]
[As he ran to the place...]
[A magic book!]
Someone will be ousted if you make them
do a split in the air and scream.
What's this talking about?
Like this?
How then?
[He doesn't know to whom this applies.]
How can I force someone like Kwang Soo
to split his legs?
If I'm really the prince,
I won't kiss her forehead!
I'll make sure to kiss her on the lips
no matter how she reacts!
[Taking the gold first]
Someone will be ousted if
I write "Out" on their feet...
Huh?
I think Jong Kook is coming here.
Gary did something.
He looks like he did something.
Gary used a pen to write something up there.
Is it some sort of a death note?
- Really?
- Yes, up there.
There's nothing they can do.
Only I know about this!
Don't be scared.
Don't be scared of anyone.
Just get their feet!
[Seung Soo Dwarf has also followed
the hint for the place.]
[Someone will be ousted if
he puts on this neck pillow.]
What is this?
The Witch's Curse.
Someone will be ousted if he wears this belt.
But I must find out which one of them
will be ousted with this belt.
[Now it's all about figuring out who can be
ousted using the ways they've found...]
[and who will survive until the end
to wake Snow White?]
I think I'm the prince.
My image is that of a prince.
I've been called "a little prince"
since I was young.
Where are you going?
I'm just looking around.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk.
I've found the way to oust you.
And what would that be?
I'll have you collect more gold
then oust you.
I really am...
One more thing.
You're not the prince.
You'll be surprised, Jae Suk.
Don't tell anyone.
But I'm the prince.
Seriously.
I didn't want to be the prince...
But they told me I'm the prince.
You know that I have
the first place card, right?
I do.
And you know that I have the
second place card, right?
Good.
You're not the prince.
[Bluffing Dwarf meets the Kid Dwarf]
Do you want to shake my hand?
And form an alliance?
I'll serve you as my prince.
- We'll avoid ousting each other.
- Shall we?
- Okay, a binding promise.
- Don't betray me.
I'll never betray you.
I think you'll do one.
A big one.
I think I'm the prince too...
Shall we take a picture
to commemorate our alliance?
To swear that we'll
never betray each other.
- No betrayal, okay?
- Okay.
The Witch's Curse...
Someone will be ousted if he gets flicked
in the forehead by a hand in an apple glove.
Someone will be ousted if I flick that person's
forehead while wearing an apple glove.
[Cocked and loaded]
What are you doing?
[The alliance dissolved in 30 seconds.]
I was just making a peace sign!
A peace sign!
- Hey!
- What?
I saw you.
I saw what you were doing.
- You were trying to flick me!
- Stop this nonsense!
Do you think I'd be that stupid?
- I saw you with my own eyes!
- No, that's not the case.
What did they do?
[Kook Dwarf appears]
- That's a scary guy right there!
- Excuse me.
You'll be so surprised when I tell you
what my first-place hint is.
He's just like a snake!
[Go away!]
I think he's going to get me!
I think it's possible
that you're the prince.
Then let's talk.
Let's share the hints on
the prince then.
Let's take them out.
- Let's take a look.
- One, two, three!
- Let me see!
- I can only read some words!
Here, the Prince is...
We can't see Kwang Soo's yet.
Can you really not trust us?
After four years?
I can show you this much.
So you should show me more.
I'll show you.
This is why I think you're the Prince.
I'll only show you.
Let me see too!
[Not very bright]
Let me see!
[That must be me.]
We'll all see together!
Let me see too!
Damn, Jae Suk!
What's he doing?
He keeps repeating it!
[5 minutes ago]
Someone will be ousted if he gets flicked
in his forehead by a hand in an apple glove.
I'll oust everyone!
[Burning]
Let me see too!
Damn, Jae Suk!
[The first testing subject]
[Yoo Jae Suk]
Are you trying to kill us with this?
Then I'm going to do the same thing!
- I'll do the same!
- Hold on!
- Don't let him join us.
- Let's read it together...
Then let me see!
[Kwang Soo's First Place hint is...]
[The Prince is a human.]
That's so useless!
This is really all I have!
- Get out of here! Leave!
- But this is really all I have!
You should get up to and go film him.
Go!
Just leave!
Just get lost!
You must believe me.
It was there when I opened my bag!
So if it's neither you nor Kwang Soo...
Who else?
Just go!
We'll have enough information
among us.
Let's switch.
[Not very bright]
[The Prince speaks eloquently]
There's nothing in common...
They're irrelevant. Only because he's this,
that doesn't mean that he can't be that.
Then who could it be?
- You can speak eloquently.
- I think it's this guy.
Yes, if we have to make an inference
from the clues...
It's either that guy
or this guy.
But he can't talk that well.
That's true.
He can speak eloquently.
He's very good at rapping.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but I can talk well too!
You only know how to
make sounds and scream!
Would you please leave?
This guy is the prince.
He must be.
You're the prince!
"Not very bright" is probably
only about your character in this show.
So I think it's highly likely
that it's you.
So then what should I do?
You should stay here because
you're the prince.
I'll be back after
ousting all other dwarves.
Just relax.
So love for everyone?
- If I come back first, you're going with me.
- Of course!
I'm open to anything.
The goal is to make you live
and save the princess.
[Where are you, my prince?]
You only have the half
of the first-place hint, right?
- You know that everyone has a full hint, right?
- That's why I've been looking for you.
- Is this going to be the last?
- Yes.
[Combining their hints will be
quite powerful!]
So we'll reveal at the same time.
Our half-hints...
You might be the prince.
I might be the prince.
If so, then we're meant to be together.
It might be that none of the others
is the prince.
[Not a very trustworthy union between
two traitors...]
Then let me get a flick!
You want to test me?
I might die!
Everything will be over
once we know the prince.
But the others are guessing between
me, Gary, and Seung Soo.
Those are the candidates.
- Let's take out our hints.
- You know you can't tell anyone, right?
Take it out.
[Reuniting half-hints!]
[The Prince is a human, and he smells.]
[A decisive hint.]
Just think about it.
[Human Scent is Gary's newest song.]
It's Gary.
[So, the Prince must be...]
[Gary with his scent!]
[Dear Prince, please wake me up.]
Kwang Soo's hint made it obvious.
He's a human...
and the fact that I could infer the next part
means I can be eloquent!
And I'm not that bright
because I'm very simple!
But it's me, Kang Gary!
I'm a prince, but I don't
even have an entourage!
Where could the princess be at?
Good evening, sir.
It's fine.
I feel a bit uncomfortable.
- I feel very uncomfortable.
- We want you to be relaxed.
Don't make the Prince any more tired.
You're just annoying him even further!
Do you know what I don't like?
I hate the fact that you'll betray me in a heartbeat
if I turn out to be not the prince.
You can leave him up to me and relax,
my dear prince.
I don't feel comfortable around you either.
I can't go too far away from you.
I won't go too far, Prince!
- What did you talk about?
- It's something funny.
- Why are you smiling?
- Take a seat.
[Bluffing Dwarf still thinks he's the prince!]
For Seung Soo,
we need someone powerful.
[Let's get him]
We shouldn't do anything on Gary
because he's probably the Prince!
He won't die anyway!
- Hey!
- What?
[Now he realized what's going on.]
[But it's too late!]
Sit down first!
I'll begin with my treatment!
I want to do it!
[Fighting to go first in front of him.]
I'll be quick!
- That's it?
- It didn't work.
He's not out?
- Mine will take a while.
- Do it!
I'm not it, right?
I'm not it!
[Big-nosed Dwarf tries the belt
on Prince Gary!]
He's fine!
He's not out?
[Tattered]
[Immediately changing their target to
Big-nosed Brother!]
- Get him!
- Don't do it!
There's no other choice.
I must give him a midair split.
[Perhaps?]
[The sound of crows fills
the land of fairytale.]
[Ji Suk Jin, out]
You should do it, too!
[Now the oldest brother is gone,
the second oldest is the next!]
Prince!
Prince Gary!
It'll be over soon!
Just hold still!
It tickles so much!
It'll be over soon!
Seung Soo!
Grab his foot!
[Seung Soo is trying the pillow on Gary
instead of grabbing Jae Suk.]
["Out" written on Jae Suk's foot.]
What are you doing?
What's going on?
[The sound of crows again!]
[Yoo Jae Suk, out]
Which one ousted him?
You did tell me you'll give me your foot
voluntarily.
Don't you think this
was a bit to much, Prince?
- So the split was you, Suk Jin.
- It's me?
- Please give your gold to Jae Suk...
- Why did you pick me?
Then everything that Jae Suk has
should go to Gary.
Gary must be the prince!
So writing on the foot was for you, Jae Suk.
- So where's the champion's belt?
- It's in there.
So this is just about the Prince
getting stronger and kissing the princess!
It's not just a kiss!
That's not how it should be treated!
It'll be to cure the princess!
[In the meantime, Giraffe successfully tricked
Muscle Dwarf to believe that he's the prince.]
He might really be the prince.
Then please save me!
Yes, that's why I've asked you!
Even if you join forces with Seung Soo...
Kwang Soo really must be the Prince!
There're many things that
require the Prince's attention.
I had never expected the way to the princess
would be this far and difficult!
Why are you acting sketchy?
[The Dwarves are getting suspicious of each other...]
- Have you put the pillow on yourself?
- Yes, I have!
- He never tied it around his neck.
- Do you want me to show you?
[Could it be that Bluffing Dwarf's own tool
is meant for his own ousting?]
It'd be hilarious if they call
"Ryu Seung Soo, Out" right now.
See? Nothing happened.
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
[Giraffe Dwarf keeps luring in other dwarves
based on his alliance with Muscle Dwarf!]
[Another innocent sheep is trapped.]
[A flicking has already been tried]
[Now Kook tries his hair-pulling!]
Hey, what was that?
Nothing's happening!
[Immediately changing the target]
You can't do this to me!
I pulled out a lot of hair!
[The sound of scary crows again!]
[Is it Ha Ha or Seung Soo?]
- What? It's me?
- We did it!
[Ha Ha, out]
[Jong Kook Dwarf realizes that everyone except him
made through Kwang Soo's flicking]
[He attacks after sensing the danger!]
[flicking doesn't work!]
Listen to me!
Just listen to me!
[Putting Seung Soo's neck pillow on him]
[The sound of the crows again...]
I'm out?
By what?
It has to be the neck pillow!
We didn't do anything else!
[Goodbye, a tall dwarf who
defied your own fate...]
[Are you on your way, Prince?]
Now it's between us three!
The Good, the Bad, the Weird.
I've been raising a tiger cub, Seung Soo!
[Only the Prince and one dwarf
can go to the princess...]
So now I must choose one of them.
But why am I no longer convinced
thant I'm the Prince?
What if I'm not the Prince?
[Overcome by uncertainty.]
[And a dwarf who's still misguided.]
I think I'm the Prince.
There's no reason for a dwarf to oust
the Prince.
I can't possible afford
to risk removing the name tags.
At least I know that I'm not the Prince.
So it's one of those two.
It's quite narrow.
Where are you going?
I'm going to you.
You've done well to
survive this far.
Right?
My vitality is my strong suit!
I'm afraid it'll have to end soon.
I think you're the prince.
And we can't beat Jong Kook unless
we unite our forces together.
You're certain that you're the prince.
I knew I'd be the prince from the moment
Ji Hyo became the princess.
So I must face Jong Kook by myself?
- Seung Soo...
- Yes?
My goal right now is
waking Ji Hyo up as soon as possible.
Yes, we must wake her up quickly!
And I can't face Jong Kook by myself.
- My goal is...
- I see.
You're fine!
I don't like the principle
of your doing this.
See?
You're fine!
How dare you hit the forehead
of the Prince?
I may not look like the Prince,
but isn't this still impertinent?
I'm sorry.
You may get up.
You're not it.
So it must be Jong Kook.
No alliance!
Let's just get rid of him.
How are you going to do it?
You must have it with you right now.
I do have something.
I do think Gary is the Prince.
But he's not helping me out.
My fighting against Jong Kook would
be like David going up against Goliath...
He'll be a very difficult opponent.
- Hey, Gary?
- Yes, Jong Kook.
[It seems like Kook Dwarf wants to
say something.]
Is...
Is there someone else?
There's no one.
Something's weird.
[This weird feeling...]
It can't be that the princess is
sleeping out on the streets, right?
[Seung Soo is trying to find
Blank Ji Princess first.]
Where is this woman sleeping?
But at this moment...
I think there's someone else.
I don't see Seung Soo either.
[Men in black capes!]
[Who are these men?]
Something's weird.
[What is this weird feeling?]
[And a black shadow that appears
from the back...]
[Then hugs Seung Soo Dwarf...]
[Who is this person?]
It's also weird that there's
no sign of Ji Hyo.
[Wait...]
[Song Ji Hyo]
[Why is she here?]
What's her true identity?
[Ji Hyo, the Snow White that we know, fell
asleep after eating a poisoned apple...]
[She's opening her eyes!]
[The real identity of Snow White is...]
[The Witch!]
The sleeping Snow White was
just an act from Ji Hyo the Witch.
Yes, that's what the Dwarves think.
The Witch pretended to be Snow White
to steal gold from the dwarves.
The dwarves have been ousted.
[Time to get to work.]
[The Witch was in total control even
when everyone thought she was sleeping.]
[The rift and demise between the dwarves
are exactly what the Witch wanted.]
Everyone's confused by my curse.
My world is coming!
[All out curses were created by the Witch.]
[She waited until Seung Soo Dwarf
got separated from the group...]
[Then waited for him with
the Champion belt, his out curse.]
Now that your belt is on your waist,
it's time for you to go to jail.
- Am I dead?
- Yes.
- Really?
[Ryu Seung Soo, Out]
[The sound of the crows is the sign
of the Witch's existence!]
See?
Gary...
It could be that Gary has
allied with someone else...
Wait, Seung Soo couldn't possibly
be ousted by Gary.
[The Witch is putting the crown and Seung Soo's
magic book as bait for the Prince.]
[Please come to me, Prince.]
Prince Gary!
Gary!
The Prince!
Where are you?
Who are you with?
What is he wearing?
A crown?
What is this?
Wait a minute!
I guess this is how I become
a real prince!
[The black feather is the Witch's symbol.]
[Everything is going as planned.]
Jong Kook Dwarf!
- Hey, Prince!
- Jong Kook Dwarf!
Wait a minute! Shouldn't
you be more careful with that crown?
Did you oust Seung Soo?
- I thought you did.
- No, I didn't!
- Wait, don't come any closer.
- Jong Kook Dwarf...
Just don't come any closer!
- Why should I stay away from you?
- Don't come any closer!
Just stay where you are!
You didn't oust him?
No, I didn't!
- You really didn't do it?
- I didn't!
You know I can't lie!
Did you conspire all this with
the Princess?
I didn't do it, Jong Kook!
Just sit down.
What's going on right now?
Why are you avoiding eye contact?
Gary! The Thai Prince!
[Eyes wide open]
The Thai Prince claims his innocence!
I must think clearly.
There's a third person...
Hey, Gary...
- What is it?
- Gary...
Why are you wearing that glove
if you didn't oust Seung Soo?
This has nothing to do with
me, Jong Kook!
Gary...
I found this glove from this bag!
That glove belongs to Seung Soo...
No, Jong Kook.
I didn't oust him!
Look at me straight, Jong Kook.
You can tell right away when I'm lying!
[But right at that moment...]
[Once they realized the identity of the Witch,
the dwarves all ran to her to rip her name tag off.]
[The message has popped up
on every mirror in town!]
[If only they notice the message...]
[They have no clue.]
Everything will be over once I find Ji Hyo
and kiss her.
It'll just be a forehead kiss.
- Whatever.
- A forehead kiss!
Let's really try to find Ji Hyo.
- Then I want you to go in front of me.
- Sure.
Let's think about where the Princess could be
if she's asleep...
Wait!
That's right. At least you
should be on the same wavelength!
This way.
[They had no idea...]
[of what was waiting for them.]
Hey, something's not right.
Hey, who appears in
the Snow White the fairytale?
- The seven dwarves.
- And who else?
- The Prince.
The Witch!
There's a witch in the fairytale!
Remember the mirror?
"Mirror, mirror, who's the fairest of them all?"
"Snow White!"
Don't do this, I'm getting scared.
That's why the Witch wanted to kill
Snow White!
I'm getting goosebumps.
Really, I am!
The Witch, Gary.
"Mirror, mirror,
who's the fairest of them all?"
- Stop it!
- "Snow White!"
That's why the Witch fed Snow White
the poisoned apple!
I'm a prince!
The Prince, the dwarves, Snow White...
But the Witch?
[Ji Hyo the Witch is pretending to be asleep.]
Be careful...
I'm scared of you too!
Why would I oust you?
Everything will be over if I do it!
- But still...
- You don't trust me?
There's no one else
who's more honest than me.
- Be aware of your surroundings!
- Okay!
- Surroundings!
- Jong Kook!
She's lying here.
- She's lying here.
- Who is?
Wait here. Let me
check if she's actually sleeping.
She does look the prettiest
when she's asleep!
- I'm going to kiss her!
- Try it.
Everything will be over once I kiss her.
Should I kiss her?
Should I start?
Hold on.
- I'm going to kiss her!
- Do it!
Let's kiss, Gary!
This crown is annoying.
I'll be watching this side,
so do what you have to do, Gary.
Princess Ji Hyo!
You may wake up now.
I want to see your smile
after waking up.
Wait, I think I'll be ousted
if I kiss her!
- You'll be fine!
- I think something's weird.
Fine.
Please wake up!
[He's trying to wake her up
just like in the fairytale...]
[Her eyes are open!]
[Those of the Witch!]
[She couldn't help but to laugh
after seeing the Prince.]
This is your prince.
Please don't laugh!
I'm going back to sleep!
Just know that I'll continue to kiss you
if you fall asleep.
- Is this how you're going to do this?
- Yes.
[Ji Hyo the Witch is now awake.]
[Now, how can I oust these two?]
So is it over if I take off
Gary's name tag?
Why would it be over?
The solo victory of a dwarf!
Since it has come down to this,
we should put this on him, Ji Hyo.
[I'd appreciate it if you
fought against each other like that!]
- How?
- I don't know!
How?
[The Witch is trying to remove Kook
by using Prince Gary.]
We must hurry, Ji Hyo!
[The only way to get Kook out
is to flick his forehead with a glove!]
[Attack commences]
[Prince Gary's arms are too short!]
[The Witch takes out a pair of gloves!]
[Kim Jong Kook, out]
[Now, only the Witch
and the Prince are left.]
I was waiting for you to come.
But I couldn't go because there were
so many dwarves!
Then you just showed up...
At least you could've given me a sign.
How could I have given you any signal
while the both of you were just there?
Here. You must have
some luck when it comes to gold.
And put this on me, please.
[He seems like he's not suspecting...]
[That's not the case!]
[Flicking attack!]
Ji Hyo!
I'm sorry!
- That doesn't work on me.
- What doesn't?
The flicking!
- It only works on dwarves.
- Really?
I'm here to meet my prince!
I thought you said flicking can
oust anyone!
I think we should find Ji Hyo first.
[He should've looked at the mirror
to know how to oust the Witch!]
Quite embarrassing, don't you think?
Come over here.
You really aren't anything, right?
I'm not anything.
My only mission was to meet you...
You won by yourself before
using the same tactic.
Do you not remember our
matching t-shirts with our names?
All right, I'm sorry.
[Blank Ji's memory attack is super effective!]
Just checking...
You must bring me to the final place.
[All she needs to do is
remove the Prince.]
It'd be great if we split the gold!
Yes, that has been my original goal!
I'm sorry for doubting you.
You thought only because it worked on
Jong Kook, it'll work on me?
Hey, it feels like you've been eating a
lot lately! Quite a lot!
It's because you're tired!
[Still debating whether to take off
Gary's name tag or not...]
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
[I'm sorry, Gary...]
[I'm a witch today, and I want my gold!]
[That thing on the mirror...]
[Is how to oust the Witch!]
There's something written here, Ji Hyo!
[Oh. My. God.]
[Ji Hyo the Witch completely takes over
the Seven Dwarves!]
- You look very annoyed.
- Doubled the annoyance today!
I won this crown!
I can keep this, right?
She completely tricked us!
That crow's feather that Gary is touching...
Ji Hyo?
Does it have to do with
the crows' crying when we got ousted?
It's the same emblem, which was
also shown during the pogo stick round.
It was also shown throughout
the mission.
I thought it was the brand of her clothes!
I thought it represents a designer brand!
So all the gold that's been found so far
is inside of that bag.
So Ha Ha's theory is correct.
So this is what happens to Snow White.
Yes, I told you!
[Ha Ha suggested the golddigger theory
of Snow White while in jail.]
So, today's winner is the Witch!
I'm just sad.
- You saw it, right?
- I saw everything.
You can go home through
that mirror.
Can we just leave normally?
My car is parked right there.
Let's just go!
Quickly!
Let's go!
And this is the end!
Mirror, mirror...
Who's the fairest of them all?
Of course you, the Witch!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Snow White]
[Scary Fairytale]
Answer me 2014 Students!
College girls!
[Pretty college girls who came
to pay a visit!]
I'm your battery, Hye Jeong!
Love's cannon battery!
[Part-time job project to
pay for their summer vacation!]
[Wages are paid in laughs!
Passionate students!]
Are you serious?
We're running a business!
[A strong part-time fighter?]
[The best part-time job!]
[Hiring now!]