- You two are secretly in love.
- Please allow me to love.
- I can't even love whomever I want?
- Don't do anything to earn my distrust.
[Hot and thrilling young love.]
[Secret Love Affair]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[One winter day.]
[Coming to the school all alone
one early morning.]
[This is none other than...]
I guess I'm the first one here.
[Prince of Romance- Lee Jong Suk.]
[And... a letter.]
[This letter was the start of it all.]
[My beautiful, yet cruel fate.]
[An hour later- Time for school to start.]
Some people are late.
- Go get me some milk.
- What did you say?
- Go get me some strawberry milk.
- Do you want to get a beating?
Seriously.
I was just kidding.
Don't joke around like that.
Why are we four the only ones here?
As you may already know...
male and female students of this school
are on very bad terms.
Why is that?
Wait... is Jong Kook playing a girl today?
[That means that they'll be battling
the female students today...]
- Why are you suddenly acting afraid?
- Sit back like this.
- Who is it?
- Okay.
[They don't seem very comfortable as they
try to act like a group of delinquents.]
- I'm sorry about earlier.
- Do you want a beating?
You guys can't fight amongst yourselves.
[Just then...]
[Delinquent Ji Hyo makes her entrance.]
You guys are all still acting like this?
- What are you guys doing?
- You used to play around a bit, didn't you?
Just from your expression alone,
I can guarantee you used to play around.
- What is this? Seriously.
- It's the latest fashion.
- Do something with that hair of yours?
- Why? I think she's adorable.
What did you just say?
[Bad terms or not...
that has nothing to do with me.]
Why don't you call in the other delinquents
that you hang around with?
- Don't even worry about it.
- This is war!
- This really is war!
- Call them in here.
- Friend!
[Who's delinquent Ji Hyo's first friend?]
Who is it?
[Lee Sae Young]
[From an adorable little girl...
to a beautiful young woman.]
[Blank Ji's first friend is,
the campus beauty, Lee Sae Young.]
- Hello.
- Wow! Hi!
[Bad terms aside,
everyone rushes over to greet her.]
- What are you doing?
- Just seizing my chance.
- What is Sae Young doing here?
- This is my friend, Sae Young.
- What is she doing here?
- I just transferred here from Seoul.
She just transferred here from Seoul.
Why are you bowing down to them?
[A little crush]
- I still have more friends out there.
- Tell them not to come in.
[Who's her next friend?]
[Kwang Ja]
This is my friend.
Why are you doing this to me?
I just walked in the room!
Why are you being like this to a girl?
Why are you doing this to me?
[A face that invites a flying fist.]
- I can't stand seeing your face.
- I agree.
- You and your betrayals!
- Why did you treat me like that?
[Kwang Ja lashes out.]
[Chastised for the second time.]
- You!
I dated her for about two days,
and she really is nothing to look at.
- You really are a dud.
- You're such a weak little man.
[Couple Jae Suk and Kwang Ja broke up
during a dodge ball game after a brief affair.]
[Bad feelings are the only thing
that remains between these two.]
- Such an unattractive girl.
- You're the cheapest guy around.
- They used to be in love.
- How far did you two get?
I can't tell you that!
- I can't tell you that!
- What am I going to do with her?
[An old flame with nothing but
bad feelings for each other.]
- I'm so disappointed in you.
- I still have more friends waiting outside.
- You still have more friends?
- Don't you know who's on our team?
- Why? Who do you have?
- We have Samson on our team.
- Samson? Could it be Jong Sook?
- It can't be Jong Sook, can it?
Come on in, my pretty friend.
It can't possibly be Jong Sook.
[HI!]
[Falters backwards.]
This is my friend.
- Are you a girl?
- Why? What's wrong with it?
- That's not a girl.
- Why is your body so buff?
- Do you know how much I love art?
- What are you talking about?
It's my dream to grow up
to be a good wife and a mother...
And I'm a great cook.
[The winner of last week's
cooking battle, Jong Sook.]
Hey, guys.
You think chicken is
the only thing I know how to boil?
I can boil you guys too.
You're doing great, Jong Sook!
I know I can boil you guys up.
We're not going to go easy on you
like we would with other girls.
What?
You think I carry this around to draw with?
- Are you a boy or a girl?
- You think this is to draw with?
- What are you?
- You're doing great!
[The girls team is feeling confident
with Jong Sook on their side.]
- I can't believe it's Jong Sook.
- She really is scary.
What you need to know is that Jong Sook
is not even the leader of our team.
- Who?
- It's not me. There's someone else.
- Who is it?
- Who else could there be?
[There's another student who's
even more frightening than Jong Sook?]
[Park Bo Young]
[The embodiment of ferociousness, Bo Young.]
[Makes her return as the legendary fighter.]
[Bo Young is the leader
whom even Jong Sook bows down to?]
Kneel down!
Sis!
We're all here.
- She is so cute.
- How can she be a leader? She's so cute!
[Most adorable leader in the world?]
- You watch your mouths!
- You're the one who should be careful.
How did you even become a leader
of your bully group?
- I feel a bit awkward right now...
- Stop talking in casual speech with her!
She's older you!
- She's older than me?
- That's right! I'm older than you!
But this guy is way older than
the rest of us.
[A brother who's way above
the rest of the group.]
- He's no joke.
- His age is no joke.
Your dad and I had a drink together
last week.
Why is there an extra member on
their team?
That's why there's a male student who just
transferred to this school.
[Another transfer student!]
[Flower boy transfer student, Lee Jong Suk.]
- Bro!
[Everyone automatically
starts to call him their 'Bro'.]
He's my boyfriend!
- Get out of there!
- It's our 100th day anniversary tomorrow.
- We've been dating for a hundred days!
- You must be dreaming.
We kissed yesterday!
[Oh my God...]
Wait, you kissed him even though
you've already kissed Jae Suk?
[Man killer, Kwang Ja?]
- I can't believe that Jong Suk is here.
- Really... Jong Suk.
[The boys team's image has skyrocketed
with Jong Suk joining their team.]
These three girls are all starry-eyed.
They look like
they've all fallen for him already.
- You look like you've fallen for him too.
- No, not me.
[Even Jong Sook is
getting a little starry-eyed?]
Were you just playing me?
- Just keep adding Yoo Jae Suk.
- No!
- I know that you still have feelings for her.
- Me?
[Jae Suk still has feelings for Kwang Ja?]
So you're the one who's been calling me
with blocked caller ID?
As you may all already know,
Running High School
is infamous for the bad blood that exists
between the male and female students.
You will be competing male vs female students
to end the battle for once and for all.
The race that you all will be
participating in today...
is called, the Rural Romance.
- Rural?
- Are we going out to a farm?
- We're not...
- You're not...
- Not the rice paddy, is it?
- In the middle of this cold winter?
Who would be crazy enough to go out
to a rice paddy in this kind of weather?
- Our producers would.
- No way.
[You know us well.]
[But... there's a couple who's been dating
in secret amongst this group.]
- We made each other a promise.
- Who is it?
[Attacks Jong Suk?]
He just sniffed me.
I didn't sniff you!
- When did I sniff you?
- This race is to find out who the couple is.
[Find out who the secret lovebirds are!]
[A hint to help them find out who the secret
couple is will be given to the game winners.]
[Will it be the secret couple's victory,
or the rest of the students' victory?]
[You're all dead!]
So you must find out who the tragic,
and desperate couple is.
[Which of the two are involved
in a secret love affair?]
It's not me, so you're all dead.
[But why... is Jong Suk acting like that?]
[An hour ago...]
A letter?
[What could be in the letter that
Jong Suk received?]
Hi Jong Suk.
I feel like this secret love affair
that we've been having...
I feel like it's been quite a while already
since we've started this secret love affair.
[Jong Suk is one of the star crossed lovers.]
I know that everyone in this school is
constantly at each other's throats.
So I'm sure that they'll all go crazy if they
find out that we're dating in secret, right?
I heard that there's going to be a race
between the boys and the girls today.
But if we succeed the mission without
others finding out that we're a couple
then I'm told that we no longer
have to keep dating in secret.
Who could it be?
Who is...
What do I do?
To be involved in a secret love affair
in this day and age...
So you're telling me that I have a girlfriend,
but you won't tell me who it is?
[Sweet and innocent Jong Suk is nervous
just at the mention of a secret affair.]
Who would you like for your
girlfriend to be?
A girl who has a pretty neck...
with a bit of an obsessive personality.
I want to be loved.
[Who could be his girlfriend
who sent him this letter?]
[She's here!]
[Jong Suk's secret girlfriend
is none other than...]
Is he my partner?
Thank you!
[Running High's Juliet, Ji Hyo.]
- I'm his girlfriend?
- He's your boyfriend.
What took you so long to come clean
about our relationship?
- I didn't even know that we were dating.
- I know. Me neither.
[Running High's Romeo and Juliet-
Jong Suk and Ji Hyo.]
- What should we do?
- I don't really understand it.
You don't understand?
My partner's intelligence level is a bit...
No, that was just a joke.
We need to be confirmed as a couple.
[Girlfriend Blank Ji is calmly explaining
today's race to him.]
This mission is saying that we have to imitate
the pose that two of the producers
are doing for three seconds.
We need to do it when we're around the other
members and make it pretty obvious
but we have to make sure not to
get caught by them.
- Do you understand it now?
- So make sure not to get caught, right?
- Without anyone knowing.
- Hold the pose for three seconds.
[Their couple mission is going to get
increasingly more difficult with each game.]
[If they succeed their own missions,
they can give out fake hints to others.]
[More fake hints that are given out,
then more advantageous it'll be for them.]
- Let's do our best today, boyfriend.
- Yes, Ma'am... I mean, okay.
You're not doing this for your love,
but this is to win the gold...
No, we're in love.
Yes, we're in love.
We're in love, but this is only
our second time seeing each other.
- So we're just feeling a little shy.
- We're just a little shy right now.
We really are boyfriend and girlfriend,
but we're feeling a little shy right now.
- Just let us be in love.
- Just leave our love be.
Just allow us to be in love.
Why do we have to keep our love a secret?
This is only the second time that we're
seeing each other in a whole year.
[Anyways, Jong Suk and Ji Hyo
are the secret couple.]
- So one of them is dating one of us?
- Yeah, that's exactly it.
That's so exciting!
- That's really exciting.
- Why are you getting so excited?
By the way, today is Tuesday.
Okay, fine.
[Sorry about today, Gary...]
[His mouth is getting dry as sandpaper.]
- Why are you discounting me?
- I don't think that it's you.
- Why not?
- It could be Kwang Ja.
She could be dating him.
She really could be dating Jong Suk.
Just make sure that your team does
their best to win every game.
- Let's make our way to the first game.
- Let's go!
[Will these two... be able to bring
their love out into the open?]
- Go away, Kang Gary.
- Yeah, Kang Gary.
[Time to start Jong Suk and
Ji Hyo's secret love affair mission.]
But I do feel more reassured knowing that
Kwang Ja and Jong Sook are on our team.
Just put your faith in us and
follow our lead.
I don't feel that Kwang Ja's very
trustworthy.
But let's be honest with each other.
Which one of you is it?
[Blank Ji is bringing up the subject first
to avoid receiving any type of suspicion.]
I'm lonely enough already as is...
I vow to find out who the couple is myself.
I don't think it's one of the two
that are sitting up front, do you?
But it's also possible that...
it could be one of the two guys
who are disguised as girls today.
[Blank Ji is trying to divert the attention
over to Kwang Ja and Jong Sook.]
It could very possibly be Jong Sook.
[That clever Blank Ji...
bringing out her acting skills.]
Which one from our team is dating
one of the girls on the other team?
I don't know which one of you it is,
but how can you be so deceitful?
- I know.
- I bet you it's Jae Suk.
[Ha Ha suspects Jae Suk.]
- It's him, isn't it?
- I guarantee it.
[Everyone on this team suspects Jae Suk.]
[Blatantly obvious about his relief.]
You can beat me if it's me.
It would be way too obvious
if it were Jong Suk.
- Jong Suk would be way too obvious.
- And it wouldn't be any fun either.
- I think that it's Jae Suk, and his eyes...
- He's being very obvious about it.
[The boys team is so convinced
of themselves.]
- Seriously.
- Jong Suk isn't being obvious at all.
[Rural Romance's first game-
Arrives at the farming field.]
We really are going to a farming field.
[Huh?
Those two people are...]
[First mission-
Must imitate the two producers' pose.]
[First mission- Link their arms together.]
The others will receive a fake hint.
But if we fail,
they're going to get the real hint
and it's going to help the members figure out
that we're the secret couple.
[So we're going to have to link our arms
together during the game, right?]
Come down this way.
- Why are there three of them?
- Do we have to change our clothes?
Proof that we're a couple-
Whenever there are two staff members
we have to imitate whatever those two are
doing for three seconds ourselves.
We have to make sure that we don't
get caught by the others either.
[Will they be able to pull it off?]
[But first, it's time to
change into your work pants.]
- Work pants.
- They're work pants.
I like being out in the farm.
- I think it suits me very well.
- Okay, we're all set.
Hey, Jong Suk.
Are those pants too short on you?
[The workpants are too short
for Jong Suk's long legs...]
Jong Sook is wearing pretty pajama pants.
You look really cute
in your pajama pants, Jong Sook.
[Fashion leader, Jong Sook.]
You keep grabbing my attention, Jong Sook.
Then I'm going to stomp all over you.
- She doesn't know how to joke around.
- She scares me.
She doesn't know how to joke around.
What are we doing?
This is your first mission of the day.
- It's called, 'Straw Platform'.
- I really love that game.
Do you see the two platforms on
either side?
Each of the teams will climb up
onto your own respective platform.
Then you will race over to the center platform
to stand on top of it without falling off.
Only the person left standing on top of
the platform when the whistle sounds, wins.
- Just one person?
- That's going to be tough.
I think it would be best
to let Jong Sook pass first.
[Come and get me.]
The person who passes the mission
will stay out the rest of the mission.
So the team who's member is the last person
left remaining loses the mission.
- Okay, I understand.
- This is very simple.
- Okay!
- It's really soft and fluffy over here.
[But... the platform mission isn't
the issue.]
[We're going to have to link our arms
together for our own secret mission...]
[But how are we going to manage to do that
without the other members noticing?]
The game will start
at the sound of my whistle.
[Running High's Boys vs Girls.]
There's no reason to rush.
[Two people will be allowed to pass
during this round.]
[Jong Sook is coming!]
[Jong Sook roars her way over.]
[Come on, Jong Suk!]
[Wait for me, Ji Hyo...]
[Kwang Ja's fierce blocking.]
[Jong Sook is successfully
holding off two of the boys.]
[Are you sure... that you're a girl?]
[Sae Young sees her chance and
gets up on top of the platform.]
[A one on one battle between
Ha Ha and Bo Young on this side.]
[Jong Suk finally manages to get himself
freed from Kwang Ja's grasp.]
Get down from there!
[It's Jong Sook that throws him down
to the ground this time.]
[Persistent Sae Young manages to keep herself
on top of the platform throughout all this.]
[And Leader Bo Young is doing whatever
she can to keep Sae Young protected.]
[Time over]
[Only Sae Young from the girls team
passes this round.]
- Both her legs are up on the platform.
- Are both her legs up above the ground?
- Wait...
- Why did you push me so hard, Ji Hyo?
[This is all nice and all...]
[But when are we ever going to link
our arms together?]
What's wrong with you, Jong Suk?
[Sae Young from the girls team
passes the first round.]
[Good cook, Jong Sook with more power
than all four of the boys put together.]
[I vow to succeed our own
private mission this time around.]
I'm going to win this time!
- This is war!
- This really is war!
- Let's fight!
- Jong Sook really scares me.
[All the male students are feeling
so tiny next to Jong Sook.]
We have Jong Sook on our side!
- Hey, Jong Sook.
- What?
I'm going to punch you
in your liver this time.
- Hey!
- I'm going to punch you in the liver.
- Watch yourself, Song Ji Hyo.
- Watch yourself, Kang Gary.
You tried to throw me down
to the ground earlier.
[All he's thinking about is the arm linking.]
- We're taking you down this time, Bo Young.
- You're going down, Bo Young.
[Big-nose and Ha Ha
are targeting Bo Young.]
- Fine?
[Round two]
[Jong Sook leads the team
as she did during the first round.]
[Jong Sook's power makes the others
come to an automatic halt.]
[The secret couple is trying to look natural
linking their arms on top of the platform.]
Come here and just hold still!
[A lovers quarrel during the game?]
[Leader Bo Young pulls herself up onto
the platform by stepping on Big-nose's back.]
[Seizes his chance, and Jong Suk
pulls himself up onto the platform.]
[Oh?]
[Blank Ji links her arm through Jong Suk's.]
[They must last three seconds
in that pose!]
[But just then,
Gary comes onto the scene.]
No, Jong Suk!
[Pretending to pull him down
as not to get caught.]
[Gary fortunately doesn't
seem to notice anything.]
[Ah... so close.]
[Jong Sook ups her power again.]
[It's Samson!]
Get out of the way!
[Thrown onto the ground.]
[All the male students gets thrown down
onto the ground by Jong Sook.]
[Sorry, Ji Hyo...
But I have to survive first.]
[You can't be up there alone!]
[But Samson comes back onto the scene.]
[Jong Suk is seemingly confused from having
been thrown onto the ground by Jong Sook.]
[His secret mission or not,
he's only thinking of the platform.]
[You can't pass the mission on your own!
Get back down here!]
[Time over]
[This is no good...]
[Jong Suk on the other hand seems
thrilled to have passed this round.]
[Jae Suk and Jong Suk both
pass the round!]
We're over.
We're over now.
What were you guys thinking?
You two shouldn't have gone up there.
[With two of their best players out,
what are they going to do with the rest?]
That's not a bad idea.
[How are they going to stop
Jong Sook now?]
What were you guys thinking for both
of you to get up there together?
They were only worried
about their own survival.
[Sorry...]
- Of all things to forget about...
- Why do you think Jong Sook is there?
What else was I to think in the midst
of all that chaos?
- I was just trying to survive.
- I hope that you're happy.
That's going to be pure hell.
Okay, get ready for Round Three.
[But... the bigger danger....
lies for the secret couple.]
- Let's get two of them up there.
- Okay.
- How?
- Let's get two of them up there.
- We'll just leave one of them behind.
- So we're not going to go up there?
[It would be better for Blank Ji to pass
the round to stand next to Jong Suk...]
I bet two of those guys are going to
pass this round.
[Game start]
[This team is looking somewhat pitiful.]
[On the other hand,
this team looks completely at ease.]
What are you guys doing?
[Come on girls!]
[Should we get a little workout in?]
[The marching giant, Kwang Ja.]
[Samson Jong Sook.]
[Leader Bo Young]
[Delinquent Ji Hyo]
[Intimidating Girls Team.]
I'm scared.
- It's Jong Sook!
- No!
- Let's get Gary up there.
- You want to get me up there?
Why?
Don't get me up there!
No, don't get me up there!
I don't want to go up there!
[They're pulling Gary up onto the platform?]
[The Girls Team is trying to get Gary
and Ha Ha to pass through this round.]
[Big-nose goes after Bo Young again.]
I want to get down!
I said, I want to get down!
Bo Young!
[Bo Young is no easy feat.]
[Knocks Big-nose down.]
[The Boys Team is starting to lose
their ground against the Girls Team.]
[Time over]
[Ha Ha and Gary are forcibly
passed through the round.]
I can't leave the game!
- What are you doing?
- What are you guys doing?
[That monster...]
I'm just... they're not going
to let me pass.
[In this case... him of all people...]
[Even though they're winning,
the feeling of defeat...]
You just wait, Park Bo Young.
[But...]
[Secret couple, Jong Suk and Ji Hyo,
are now in more danger than ever.]
[The game is coming to an end,
and they have yet to do their mission...]
[If things don't change, a real hint that
indicates to them as being the couple will...]
[Quick witted members will figure out that
these two are the couple at this rate...]
[Secret couple,
Jong Suk and Ji Hyo in danger.]
[One vs Four.]
The boys team is in the lead.
- No, that's not the truth.
- Are you making fun of us right now?
We're going to lose this if we're
not careful.
It's going to be almost impossible
to turn this game around.
I'm the only one left on our team,
and all four of them still have to pass.
[Big-nose is the only person left
to pass in order for their team to win...]
That won't be too hard.
Two members will be allowed
for this round as well.
- You can be one of them.
- We win if I get up there, right?
[But why does it feel like they've
already lost the game?]
Okay!
There they come.
They're scary.
[Full of desire to win.]
[Knocked off with one shove.]
[Blank Ji and Bo Young takes that opportunity
to pull themselves up onto the platform.]
[Where are they taking him?]
- What are you guys doing?
- That's enough!
[Big-nose ultimately is brought back
to his starting line.]
Why haven't you started yet?
You're the only one left to pass.
[Time over]
[Blank Ji and Bo Young
easily pass the round.]
- You have to conserve your energy.
- We're still in the lead.
[Anyway, Blank Ji
thankfully passes the round.]
[The two are finally brought closer...]
[The arm link mission.]
[This is their last chance.]
- Let's just give up.
- No, you can't give up.
[But Bo Young and Sae Young are
standing between the two.]
[Blank Ji casually turns around to
move closer to Jong Suk.]
[While everyone’s attention is focused
on the last bit of the game...]
[Oh?]
[Jong Suk pulls Ji Hyo to him.]
[Jong Suk and Ji Hyo succeeds in their
mission to link their arms together.]
[Oh?]
[Bo Young's gaze...]
[And Gary too?]
[Did they see?]
Try and come this time.
[Whew... they fortunately didn't
seem to notice.]
[While everyone's focused on
what's going on in the game...]
[This time, Ji Hyo links her arm
through Jong Suk's!]
[Heart is beating fast...]
[Their hidden secret...
amongst these people...]
[Jong Suk and Ji Hyo succeed
their first mission.]
[Then shall we observe Big-nose's
humiliation in peace now?]
[Big-nose shoves Jong Sook off the platform!]
[It's still anyone's game!]
[Big-nose could miraculously
win this game?]
[Big-nose is showing off his fighting spirit.]
You have to get up there!
Pull your feet up off the ground.
That'll count as you being up there.
[Straw platform- Game over.]
Why did you lift one foot
off the ground?
Did you and Jong Sook kiss or something?
Why did you lift one foot off the ground?
We won!
[Rural Romance Race-
Girls Team wins the first mission.]
They're really good at planning.
And thus, the girl team took the win
in our first physical mission.
[Total and utter humiliation.]
Maybe the guys were just trying to be
gentlemen, and went easy on us?
We wouldn't have been able to win
otherwise.
You two, seriously...
If you weren't a girl...
Let's go, just you and me.
[One on one?]
- Lee Jong Suk and...
- What did you say?
And Kim Jong Sook.
A one on one match between those two.
We're not going to go easy on you.
- An unexpected win...
- What do you mean, unexpected?
You really are being too much.
You guys are such gentlemen.
You guys are gentlemen.
You should've been more gentle with him!
[Samson Jong Sook.]
Gentlemen!
- They're such gentlemen.
- Thank you.
- We really are gentlemen though.
- Of course, we are.
- The Girls' Team wins.
[The Girls' Team wins a hint about the
secret couple from having won the mission.]
[One fake and one real hint from Jong Suk
and Ji Hyo having succeeded their mission.]
[Even though it's a relief,
she still can't help but feel nervous...]
I'm so angry right now.
The men are looking so exhausted that I think
we need to stop for our meal before moving on.
Let's play another game before we eat!
- Let's show them what us girls are made of!
- Working out on an empty stomach is best!
I'm done.
I'm done with that.
[Real hint and a fake hint.]
Rural Romance Race.
Go to the greenhouse in Namchon.
[Next location- The greenhouse.]
- What were the hints that we received?
- Let's look at the hints.
Were you two not going to show us
the hints if we hadn't said anything?
- You two are acting funny.
- No, it's not like that.
There are two hints.
- Mine said, 'P and K'.
- Mine says 'J'.
- P and K?
- Yes.
- Let me see.
- What could that be for?
- PK and JK?
- No, PK and J.
- 'J' could mean Jae Suk, Jong Kook...
- Who's PK?
- 'P' would only be Bo Young.
[Confusing to figure out
which one of the two is the real hint.]
If that hint is indicating towards me,
then that's the fake hint.
- We'll be the judge of that.
- She makes it sound simple.
[Just then, they receive a call
from Ha Ha.]
- We've figured out who the guy is.
- Just unbelievable.
[Did Jong Suk get found out?]
It's Yoo Jae Suk.
[The guys still believe that
Jae Suk is the culprit.]
It's Yoo Jae Suk?
- Yoo Jae Suk is the guy, okay?
- Okay.
Take a look at all the girls' faces,
and see who looks most flustered.
I didn't know you were Jae Suk's style.
- Find out who the culprit is on your end.
- Okay, we got it.
[If they think it's Jae Suk...
then that's a huge relief.]
[I'm doing really good at this.]
Pink is my favorite color.
What is this?
[Which couple awaits for
Jong Suk and Ji Hyo this time?]
[Jong Suk and Ji Hyo's second mission-
Clasped hands.]
[Oh my God...]
[One step above the linked arm mission!]
[To have to clasp our hands together
without others seeing...]
Why am I supposed to do that?
- This must be the place.
- Lets go inside.
- Let's just go inside.
- No reason to even hesitate about this.
[The boys team arrives soon thereafter.]
[Oh my... that's much harder...]
- Are you leaving your phone behind?
- What's with those two?
- What are you two doing?
- We're just saying 'hi'.
What are you guys doing?
Congratulations.
Are you two having a little lovers' chat?
[Gary seriously thinks that
these two are dating...]
[But this is a difficult mission.
Will they be able to succeed?]
- Hurry it up!
- What took you so long?
[These girls are quite prickly from their...
hormonal teenage years?]
- You're not gentlemen after all.
- You guys are unbelievable.
Look here.
You little princesses.
Stop just calling us princesses,
and start treating us like princesses.
You guys should've gotten here faster.
[Bickering already before
the game has even begun.]
Kang Gary, you've gotten so ugly.
[Why are you saying such a thing
out of the blue?]
Your next game has to do with
the horizontal bar that you see there.
That's why we've named this game,
The Scarecrow.
- What is that?
- The Scarecrow?
- Isn't she it?
- Do we have to hang from it?
[Scarecrow doppelganger, Kwang Soo-crow.]
[It's a game that brings back
memories from their own childhood.]
[What kind of a game is that?]
['70-'80 men who step up to
personally demonstrate the game.]
[Win the game by avoiding the other team,
and making your way back within four moves.]
- You have to put your arms around my leg.
- Scarecrow.
[Lovers quarrel with his ex-girlfriend,
Kwang Ja, that never seems to cease.]
It's your own fault for confessing your love
to me when you knew I didn't love you.
- Did you really confess your love for her?
- I'm seriously going to lose my mind.
[Short relationship,
and a lifetime of regrets.]
- We're going to play a round as a test.
- Okay, let's go.
[Big-nose and Sae Young to play
Rock-Paper-Scissors to see who'll go first.]
[Big-nose wins.]
You're supposed to throw a 'Rock'
if you're a man.
So why did you throw a rock?
- Yeah, why did you do that?
- Are you two dating?
You know that's not possible.
You have to play defense.
You can block him.
- Scarecrow!
- Okay!
[Hyuk completely blocks off a path.]
- I see your underpants!
- Stop it!
- Scare...
- You have to help us out too.
[Why is she dangling from the bar?]
[What is this?]
Okay, fine.
We'll let you do that.
You still have to make
three more moves, Kwang Soo.
- What?
- You only made one of the four moves.
I have to do all that?
[Only made one move out of the four...]
If you oust yourself, I'm going to...
[His second move.]
Do you think that you're
an acrobat or something?
- I'm going to get you for that.
- You've still got two moves left to make.
Two more moves.
[He now has to remain in this position
without budging to the end.]
He has to stay in that position?
Please hurry!
Please!
[Ha Ha finishes surrounding Kwang Soo.]
[Same plan as Jae Suk.
Bo Young blocks the other side.]
I think this one will be ousted soon.
[Big-nose brother's turn.]
[Easy Brothers' Parallel Theory.]
Why don't we just leave him
to stay in that position?
[Easy Brothers are no threat to anyone
by being stuck in their current position.]
Are you two playing a game,
or being punished right now?
Okay, I'll go this time.
[Just then, Blank Ji makes her move.]
I think his feet are too far up.
[Should we slowly...
start to make our move?]
[Secret couple's second mission-
Clasp their hands together.]
[What is Blank Ji's plan?]
[That's our ace!
Getting as far away as she could from others.]
[Come close to me, Jong Suk.]
[I'll be there soon.
Wait for me!]
[Just then...
Gary makes his move over to Ji Hyo!]
[It's too dangerous to get close
to Ji Hyo at this rate!]
- I don't know what to do about this.
- Hurry up!
He's stepping on the line.
Hurry up, Jong Suk!
[Makes his move towards Ji Hyo
without any hesitation.]
Why are we always involved
in a love triangle?
[What do I do now?]
[Now they have to get back to the starting
line without touching their opponents.]
[Yoo Hyuk succeeds.]
[Kwang Ja is eliminated.]
[Exhaustion hits...]
[Haroro also succeeds with ease.]
- One to...
- It's two to zero.
[Secret couple could've done their mission
by now if it hadn't been for Gary...]
[While everyone's eyes and ears
are focused towards the bar...]
[But they're afraid of getting caught
with their hand clasped in each other's...]
[The game is slowly coming to an end...]
[But to do their mission...]
[There's just not enough time!]
[And it's all because of this one man.]
Okay, My turn.
[Ji Hyo purposely jumped far out to do
her secret mission, but her plan backfired.]
[Having lost her chance at the secret mission,
Ji Hyo still succeeds in this public mission.]
[Ah... we were so close.]
We'll go first.
[First round was a tie.
This round to determine the winner.]
- Should I go first?
- Okay.
You stepped on the line.
[Blocking the immediate area
like they had done before.]
[But it's not easy to maintain
a position like that...]
- I bet Sae Young will do it.
- I'm going to go out this way.
[Ha Ha makes his move to block Sae Young.]
- We can block that area too.
- Yeah, let's block it.
- You want me to stay close?
- Yes, don't go too far out.
[Bo Young goes to keep the other end
blocked off for the opposing team.]
- There you go.
- I can still do it.
[Sae Young is surrounded by Ha Ha and
Gary on either side of her.]
- Okay, next.
- Who's going next?
Should I go next?
[We have to get it done this time!]
[Ji Hyo once again
goes out as far as she can.]
- We have to block Ji Hyo.
- We have to block her?
- Go block Ji Hyo.
- Go Block Ji Hyo.
[Jong Suk steps up to be on his way.]
- Look at her smiling.
- She's happy that Jong Suk's coming to her.
Don't block her off.
[Obvious that Jong Suk will head out
to Ji Hyo even without seeing.]
[The two are brought back together again...]
[Clasping the hands together...
We have to succeed this time!]
[Just then, Coach Kkuk seems to be planning
something up for Kwang Ja.]
[It's Kwang Soo heading over to block
Jong Suk this time?]
It's over if his head even grazes Jong Suk.
[What do we do about this now?]
[Even Suk Jin is headed to Ji Hyo.]
[This is getting tougher and tougher...]
[Even Jong Sook is joining their fray?]
[Almost everyone is gathered
around Jong Suk and Ji Hyo.]
- Block Kwang Ja.
- Kwang Ja? Okay.
- Get Kwang Ja out.
- We have to oust Kwang Ja.
[And finally, even Jae Suk
heads over to that cluster.]
[We can't lose our last opportunity...]
- We got this.
- We're good.
[It's time for them to start
making their way back one by one.]
You can totally do it.
[Sae Young tries hard to escape
her confinement]
We just need Ji Hyo to survive.
We're even at this point.
She just hit my hand.
No, I was just making my move.
[Shouting out nonsense from
having been flustered?]
It's okay.
[Sae Young is disqualified.]
[Ha Ha easily makes his way back
across the finish line.]
She's so cute when she does that.
[Bo Young adorably succeeds.]
[Gary also succeeds!
The little village is only left.]
- They're in trouble.
- My turn.
[Ji Hyo attempts to extract her legs.]
- Scarecr...
- I think she's going to do it.
She's always good at everything.
[Ji Hyo easily makes her way back.]
[It is now Jong Suk's turn.
Will he be able to make his return?]
[Pretty much impossible to extract
himself out of that position.]
- There's no way he can get himself out.
- How is he going to be able to do that?
You keep touching our hair.
Everything he does is ousting himself.
- Jong Suk just threw himself in my arms.
- Eliminated!
[Lee Jong Suk is eliminated.]
Our plan succeeded.
[Thus Jong Suk makes his way back to Ji Hyo.]
[Good job, Jong Suk.]
We just need to oust Kwang Ja, and we'll win.
[It's still a battlefield over here.]
- Okay, here we go.
- I can see the touching.
[How is he supposed to
get himself out of there?]
[Giraffe's back kick.]
Is he allowed to do that?
- I'm fine.
- I'm so sorry.
[Kwang Ja is eliminated after
kicking her ex-boyfriend in the face.]
- Take big leaps.
- Scarecr...
- Ow.
- Crow.
[The game is starting to come to an end...]
[Ji Hyo sticks herself close to Jong Suk
while pretending to avoid Suk Jin.]
- We won.
- We won this game.
[Everyone else's attention is elsewhere...]
[Now is the time.]
[Jong Suk pulls his hands out
of his pockets.]
[Secret couple's second mission-
Succeeds in clasping their hands together.]
[No one seems to notice what
the secret couple so doing.]
[Why is it suddenly so cold?]
[Casually pretending to whisper something
to him after they succeed their mission.]
[Secret couple Jong Suk and Ji Hyo-
Succeeds their second mission.]
[Jae Suk safely makes it back
across the finish line.]
[Scarecrow game-
The boys team wins by 4:3.]
- We easily won that game.
- It's all because of Kwang Ja blocking me.
We still have to remember that there's
a secret couple amongst us through all this.
- Yeah, we have to remember.
- Jong Suk is acting really suspicious.
- Jong Suk doesn't look too happy.
- My legs are asleep.
I saw you standing next to Kwang Soo.
- What were you two talking about?
- I don't know, but it's weird.
[One real and one fake hint from
having won this mission.]
- Can we look at it right now?
- What is this?
We still have more games left to play.
[Unsure of what their hint is saying
since only one of them is the real hint.]
- Okay, let's go!
- We need to figure this out.
[Whew... we succeeded.]
[Real hint and fake hint.]
Do you remember what
their hint was?
Could it be Jae Suk?
I told you that it isn't me.
- How frustrating. I told you it's not me.
- I'm positive that it's Jae Suk.
[Everyone's hunch of it being Jae Suk
is becoming even more resolute.]
- What?
- I really do think that it is Jae Suk.
- You guys are driving me crazy.
- I think it is you too.
I'm telling you that it isn't me.
It's someone else in this car.
I don't know which one of you it is, but
whomever it is, you're a really good actor.
I think that it could be Ji Hyo.
Yeah, it's me.
- I think it's Ji Hyo.
- That's right, it's me.
I think more than likely,
it's Sae Young.
- Why do you think that it's me?
- Who is it that you're dating?
I really hope that it's Jong Suk.
- You and Jong Suk?
- No, I mean any one of us...
[Arrives at their next location-
The public market.]
[What is their next secret mission to be?]
Here?
[Third secret couple mission-
Forehead to forehead kiss.]
[An extremely obvious move that cannot be
compared to the previous two missions.]
[How are we supposed to do that?]
Are we going to have to go out
and buy something again?
[It seems like a shopping mission
of some sort?]
I may not know much...
but I do know that Jae Suk is it.
The funny thing is that he's standing there
looking so shameless as he is right now.
- He's acting like it isn't him.
- That's because it isn't me.
- Look at me. It really isn't you?
- No, it's not me.
- Then who is it? Is it you?
Jong Suk?
- You're acting weird.
- You're suddenly acting weird.
Don't do anything suspicious.
- Don't do anything.
- You said you don't know?
- No, don't do anything.
- What do you mean, don't do anything?
Why is your face getting so red
all of a sudden?
No, it's just that I have a phobia
of being in the spotlight.
[Such a phobia even exists?]
[The girls team finally arrives.]
[Time to show Ji Hyo what her next
secret mission is.]
[Third secret couple mission-
Forehead to forehead kiss.]
What are you doing?
[Miss Capable Jong Sook...
She noticed their move?]
Long time no see.
[He mistakes what they did
as just a way of greeting each other.]
[That's a relief, but...]
Nobody do anything suspicious.
[In here?]
[We have to do the forehead kiss
in this tiny enclosed space?]
[We can do it, right?]
Have you made any guesses as to who
the girl is on your drive over here?
- Yes, we have an idea.
- You guys had better watch out.
[They're done with their deduction?
They seem to be confident in their guess.]
We're nearing the end of this mission.
I'm sure you guys must be nervous.
[If you succeed the mission within your time
limit with a partner, then you'll win a hint.]
Each of the men will now grab a shopping bag,
and the money you need for shopping.
[Kwang Ja reaches for a bag
without even a moment's hesitation.]
[Kwang Ja is confused about
her own identity.]
The men will now choose a girl whom they'd
like to be partnered up with to go shopping.
- Okay.
- Point to the girl you want as your partner
and tell that girl to 'Come out'.
And if the woman is happy with the partner,
then she only needs to grab his hand.
[The girl to grab the boy's hand if
they're happy with the partner.]
- Ji Suk Jin will start.
- Okay, I'll start.
This is making me feel so shy!
What if all the boys come after me?
[What a fanciful dream that is...]
Don't avoid my gaze.
Why are you trying to avoid
meeting my gaze?
[Who's the girl that Suk Jin
wants as his partner?]
Come out!
No thanks.
Jong Suk and I are all set then.
[Okay, we'll get coupled off first...]
[Then maybe things will be
pretty simple after that.]
- Jong Suk and I are all set.
- I have my insurance too.
You can't call her your insurance.
You're going to make her mad by
referring to her as your insurance.
- You think of me as your insurance?
- Why would you say that?
Come out.
[Nice!]
[His face turns beet red.]
You don't even need to say anything.
Just grab his hand if you want to.
Yes, I want to.
[Nice!]
[We succeeded in getting partnered up.]
[Insurance is gone?
Gary loses it.]
You called me your insurance.
You only think of me as your insurance.
- I meant that I'm your insurance.
- Don't make me laugh.
- What are you even thinking?
- I'm sorry to say this...
but you two need to butt out.
- You can't get jealous, okay?
- Of course not.
Come out.
[Jae Suk confidently points to Bo Young.]
What are you saying is different
between him and I?
I just didn't want to take the first person
that chose me. I was going for the second.
[She just didn't want to say 'yes'
to the first person who chose her.]
Come out.
Forget it.
- Cute little kiddo... come out.
- Forget it.
[An immediate refusal.]
[Then which of the male member
it is that she's waiting for?]
You just wait.
Come out, Sae Young.
- Okay.
- Okay!
[Did she really say that?
She chose Suk Jin as her partner?]
It's because he's always getting
scorned and turned down by everyone.
[The only ones left remaining are...
Kwang Ja and Jong Sook.]
I want both of you to point to the girl
you want simultaneously.
- This is driving me crazy.
- I don't even know who to choose here.
They each have their own
attractive elements about them.
[Ah... really?]
This one's cute, and this one's sexy.
You guys are going to make me
lose my mind.
- At the same time.
- At the same time?
[This situation is making them
hesitate in their decision?]
- Let's hurry. We need to go shopping.
- I'm so nervous.
One, two, three.
- Come out.
[Ha Ha and Gary both chooses Kwang Ja.]
[What do I do?]
- I need Kwang Ja in my life.
- No one else will do for me.
It's because I like girls who are cute.
If you treat me like this,
you're going to regret it down the road.
- Can't I even love whomever I want?
- What do you mean by that?
Kwang Ja has to make a decision.
[Ha Ha and Gary are doing whatever they
can to win Kwang Ja's affection.]
- One...
- How about I hug them from behind?
[Kwang Ja is really milking the situation.]
I'll hug one and
Jong Kook will hug the other.]
[Two nervous male students.]
[Kwang Ja behind one,
and Jong Sook behind the other.]
[Who will Kwang Ja choose?]
- One, two...
- Wait, why am I feeling so nervous?
One, two, three!
Wouldn't it have been nicer if
you had chosen me from the beginning?
Teach him what hell is like, Jong Sook.
Seriously, Jong Sook.
Show him what hell is like.
Everyone's partnered up now.
You just need to go out
and buy anything that you'd like.
You can go out and
buy anything that you'd like, but...
You don't know what this is...
But you have to complete whichever mission
you are given within three minutes
which includes your shopping time.
[Off to the market for now
to buy the stuff that they need.]
[They must return within three minutes!]
[A market with countless number
of goodies to buy...]
[What will they bring back?]
- What about the dried persimmon?
- That's what we wanted to get.
[Unsure of what to buy since they
don't know what the mission is.]
- You want to buy clementines?
- Yes, I think clementines would be best.
You're thinking clementines?
Okay, let's buy clementines.
[Suk Jin and Sae Young buy clementines.]
Something like this?
How about some rice?
Want to buy rice?
- How about tofu?
- Okay, tofu.
Can you give us a piece of the tofu?
[Kwang Soo and Gary buy a piece of tofu.]
[Another team has already
bought the clementines...]
How about this?
Dried persimmons.
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha buy dried persimmons.]
- Here's 5,000 won.
- Thank you.
- Want to buy the mackerel?
- Did you see the mission?
- Yeah, the forehead kiss.
[Third secret couple mission-
Forehead kiss.]
- It's a forehead to forehead to kiss.
- We have to touch our foreheads together?
Let's buy something first.
How about jujubes?
- How about the anchovies?
- How much are the jujubes?
[Trying to buy what they need
to do their mission first...]
- How much is this?
- 5,000 won.
What is that?
[Ji Hyo sees Jae Suk and Bo Young
passing them by.]
Just buy whatever.
Let's touch our foreheads together now.
[What?
They're going to do it right here?]
[With no one else around...
with the added thrill and excitement.]
[Almost there!]
[Jae Suk couple suddenly turns and
heads back towards Jong Suk and Ji Hyo.]
[Rushing to buy their merchandise
when they hear someone coming close by.]
Hey, let's go get the clementines!
[The forehead kiss...
Did they just fail their first attempt?]
[Ji Hyo and Jong Suk are first to get back.]
Right here.
[Kwang Ja and Gary arrive soon thereafter.]
Don't let go of each other's hands.
Two minutes have passed.
- Everyone back?
- Yes, we're all here.
[Everyone is back on set.]
Look at the mission that you've chosen.
[The mission they need to do
with the purchase they made is...]
[Pile the items that you bought
in a tower within a minute.]
- We all bought the same thing?
- Let's use the tofu first.
Why did you buy clementines?
- Look at how nice this tofu is.
- Can we stack it like this?
- How do you want us to stack these?
- Just stack them.
[They have to stack all the odds and ends
that they bought and brought back?]
- Stack them up together.
- Just start stacking them.
- Stack them like this.
- I have dried persimmons.
[The time is ticking, and
there are so many things to stack!]
- Put it on the bottom.
- More clementines.
You've got ten seconds left.
- Okay, I think we got it.
- Oh no!
[Time over]
[Unfortunately fails the mission
because of one little clementine.]
- We never should've ripped the bag.
- Who opened up the bag of clementines?
- Why did you rip the bag open?
- No, it's okay.
It's really good though.
[Time for a little snack break.]
But this was a much easier mission
than I had expected it to be.
- Yeah, it was a pretty simple mission.
- We could've succeeded it.
We could've succeeded it if we had
just a little bit more time.
We could've done it if Suk Jin
hadn't ripped the bag open.
But is the secret couple trying to get in
the way of us succeeding the missions?
- Why would they do that?
- To prevent us from getting the hint.
- You think?
- How is it you know all that so well?
- That means you're the girl!
- I was the first one to get back here.
- Your face looks like you're lying.
- Each partner...
[These two are acting like
they're suspicious of others.]
- Really?
- One girl and one guy.
The culprits are in this room.
[Then where else would they be?]
- Do we go with the same partner?
- Let's just keep the same partner.
I like my partner.
But if we keep the same partner,
it'll be hard for us to figure out who it is.
- If we keep the same partner...
- Then let's change partners.
Okay, fine.
[Is Blank Ji trying to avoid suspicion,
or is she...]
- The girls will choose the partner this time.
- Okay.
[The girl's turn to choose the partner.]
[Miss Capable, Jong Sook,
to choose the first partner.]
Let's go together.
Are you kidding me?
Get lost.
[Immediately cuts him off.]
[Physically strong girl student
is turned down from her selection.]
What do you think you're doing?
[You just wait and see...]
You'd better make the right choice.
[Jong Suk breaking out into a dance
to get her to choose him?]
Come out.
[Chooses Jong Suk as expected.]
She meant you.
Lee Jong Suk's mine!
Sorry to ask this,
but can you all leave Jae Suk?
Okay, we won't choose him.
- Come on, Bo Young.
- Choose me.
- You hurt my feelings earlier.
- You and I are a perfect match.
[Haroro is offering
his similar height to her?]
- We worked really well together earlier.
- Don't think of doing anything foolish.
Let's go!
[Ji Hyo's their last hope.]
He's my living hell, Ji Hyo.
[The two grim reapers.]
- Ji Hyo.
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
- Here, Ji Hyo.
- Are you mad?
- What are you doing?
[Chooses her Monday boyfriend, Gary.]
- Why would I be mad?
- Don't you even have any self-respect?
[The Monday couple is back together again.]
It's our turn now, right?
- They're our ghosts.
- The two worst nightmares.
Hey, give me my chance to get revenge.
Aren't we free to choose
whom we love?
Even though we're both girls,
and friends...
- One, two, three.
- You.
[Jae Suk chooses Kwang Ja without
even a moment's hesitation.]
[Jong Sook is refused for the second time.]
He's about to explode.
[Totally at a loss for words.]
[The two must stick together
no matter what happens now.]
Those two are really suspicious.
Don't you think?
Yes, I agree.
[Jae Suk and Kwang Ja are suddenly
receiving everyone's suspicions.]
The way I see it,
those two are the real couple.
I bet it's those two.
Just wait until I get my hands
on you two.
[Okay... things are going well.]
- You have to be back within three minutes.
- Okay.
[Off to complete their shopping
within three minutes.]
We just buy whatever we want again?
[Out with your partner with
your hands held tight!]
Are you a part of a secret couple?
[Sae Young bluntly asks
Jong Suk the question.]
What do you mean, a couple?
No, I'm not.
[They're all starting to seriously
suspect one another.]
- I think the real couple is together now.
- I think so too.
- I feel suspicious of Kwang Soo.
- Me too.
I think the real couple is together right now
and planning something.
[Big-nose's sharp deductions.]
- We want to buy a pair of shoes.
- We'd like a buy a pair of shoes.
[Jae Suk and Kwang Ja wants to buy
a pair of shoes.]
How about a pair of slippers?
12,000 won?
The furry ones are pretty.
Here's 12,000 won.
Thank you! Good luck!
Okay, let's get going.
[Suk Jin and Jong Sook are busy tailing
their suspects, Jae Suk and Kwang Ja.]
What are you two planning?
- It's not you, is it, Bo Young?
- No, it's not.
- I think it may be Sae Young.
- But I'm suspicious of you too.
It really isn't me.
- I think it's Sae Young.
- I think it's you.
[Everyone's starting to suspect one another.]
[All the pairs are starting to make their
way back with their purchased items.]
[Ji Hyo and Gary brings back
a bag of red beans.]
[Stand still with all the items purchased held
between you and your partner's body.]
You're not talking about just
one bean, right?
Yes, just one bean.
Look at how happy Gary is.
Just one bean?
[Keep the item held by your cheeks with your
partner for one full minute.]
[Even the shoes?]
- Together?
- Yes, but we haven't started it yet.
Was this game created specifically
for Gary and Ji Hyo?
- You'd better not drop it.
- There's no way that we can drop this.
[Still remaining suspicious of one another
even as they stand there cheek to cheek.]
[Totally stuck together.]
[Start]
- Be careful.
- You're the one acting suspicious.
- You're acting really strange.
- I feel like it's slipping.
- You can't drop it.
- Dropping it would be suspicious.
[Will become subjects of a lot of suspicion
if they were to fail this mission.]
You'd be more than just suspected.
Let's go for five minutes of this.
Come on, Jong Suk.
[Everyone's doing a good job
of maintaining their stance...]
[15 seconds left to go.]
- Seven...
- I bet the couple is sweating bullets.
[Only five seconds left to go!]
[Pass]
He won't go away!
Are we going to keep going
with the same partner?
My partner and I are going to stay together.
- Shall we swap partners?
- I guess you're all done with scheming?
What are you talking about?
What scheming are you talking about?
[Did he catch on to the fact that there
are secret couple missions?]
It's not me.
- You two are caught.
- It's not me.
- Is Ji Suk Jin going to start again?
- Yes.
You can't hit anyone, Jong Sook.
- You can't hit anyone on a TV show.
- They're fighting over Yoo Jae Suk right now.
I'm seriously going to lose my mind.
[Fighting over their love for Jae Suk?]
And Jong Sook keeps threatening us
not to touch Jae Suk.
- I'm really going to lose my mind.
- I'm going to drive you crazy.
Shall I get started?
[Suk Jin, Bo Young and Gary, Ji Hyo
are already partnered up together...]
[Jong Suk and Sae Young are
partnered up together again.]
- I'm going to lose it.
- I'm going to lose it again.
Can you get out of the way, Jong Suk?
[Frightening moment in time...]
- It's our time.
- You'd better listen to me this time.
Ha Ha is to make his choice, right?
It's my turn to pick?
That's simple.
Okay, fine.
Come here.
Come here, and carry the bag.
I said, pick up the bag.
Pick up and carry the bag.
- Hold my hand.
- I'm going to lose it.
- Should I give you five minutes?
- I'm going to lose my mind.
- Why are you giving us five minutes?
- Give us five minutes.
- Lead the way.
- Lets go.
I don't know what to buy.
- How about leggings like these?
- Yeah, that looks good.
[Jae Suk is trying to end their shopping trip
as quickly as he can.]
- We're getting some leggings.
- Some new leggings for Jong Sook.
- We'll take these leggings.
- How much is this?
Here are a pair of black ones.
Let's go with the black ones.
Just buy whatever.
I'm going to go with the black one.
I didn't know there was a black one.
Hold my hand.
This is just like living hell.
Don't walk too fast,
and don't walk too slow either.
- Not too fast... and not too slow either.
- Listen, Jong Sook.
I'm walking alongside you right now.
[Jae Suk is exhausted from having to
cater to Jong Sook's needs.]
You two must be the couple.
- You two look good together.
- Don't we look good together?
- How long have you been together?
- It hasn't been that long.
We haven't been dating long,
but we're going to break up soon.
How can you say such a thing?
I'm not going in there.
Okay, I'm sorry!
[Jong Sook is mad by Jae Suk's comment.]
- Are you breaking up with me?
- No!
- Don't be in such a hurry.
- Okay, Honey.
You won't believe what we bought.
[Something unbelievable?]
[A bowl of rice?]
- What if this is an eating mission?
- I've got her.
- How can you treat a girl like that?
- If you can't eat, then you're the bad guy.
[All the couples make their way back
with their purchased items.]
You pick it.
I love you.
[Word relay with the item you bought.]
[Word relay game within 30 seconds.]
- Delicious kodari.
P... Pretty leggings that you can buy
from a R-el cart.
S... delicious seaweed that even
the stars enjoy eating.
K... A filling kkot-gam that
I can eat when I feel empty and hungry.
Gam... Gamsa (thanks) for the delicious
bowl of rice!
- We did it.
- Yeah, we did it.
[Mission success]
We did it.
Both teams will receive their own hints.
[Both teams to receive a set of hints from
having succeeded two rounds of the mission.]
[Succeed the secret couple mission, then it's
real and fake hint. If not, just a real hint.]
Are they both real hints?
- It's one real, and one fake hint.
- Which ones are for which team?
[A real and a fake hint?]
[Wait... there being two hints means...]
[During their first shopping trip...]
[While no one was
paying them any attention...]
[Even with Jae Suk, Bo Young, Suk Jin
and Sae Young right next to them...]
[They boldly succeeded their
secret couple mission!]
- We did it, right?
- Yes, I think we did.
[Even after being the first ones
to arrive back...]
[They do the mission again just in case
the first attempt wasn't valid.]
[The secret mission is definitely a success!]
This was my third time.
What have I done to deserve this?
They're coming.
[That's how the secret mission was completed.]
[Thus, one real and one fake hint.]
- Bye.
- I love you.
- Bye Jong Sook.
- Bye.
- It was fun.
- Yeah, right.
Don't think that we're over for good.
What does this mean?
What is this?
- What is this?
- What does that mean?
Don't you think that this is a phone number
or a text message of some sorts?
[Could it be related to a phone number?]
- It's possible.
- What phone number?
[Difficult to make a correct guess since
the fake hint is mixed in there.]
I got it.
Okay, let's go.
It means that one of them is real.
[Real hint and a fake hint.]
- Wait, we need to figure out the hint.
- I know what it means.
[The mysterious number stands for
a person's name?]
Then we need to figure out
who's name it is?
[If they start decoding the numbers...]
[It means it's either
Park Bo Young and Gary...]
[Or Song Ji Hyo and Lee Jong Suk.]
- Why?
- Yeah, it's definitely Park Bo Young.
No, think about the very first
set of clues that we got.
Then what does that mean?
Who's the real culprit?
- Hey, Jong Suk.
- Yes?
- Be honest with us.
- It really isn't me.
- It's not you?
- I haven't even done anything all day!
- Jong Suk, is it you?
- No, it's not me.
Me and Bo Young?
What year was Bo Young born in?
- Bo Young was born in '94.
- She's 24 years old.
[The second set of numbers is '12'.
Could it be Bo Young and Gary's age gap?]
It's Kang Gary.
[Gary and Bo Young are the likely suspects
from what the numbers are indicating?]
[Please... don't change
your minds about that!]
[The final location-
School field in Haejeomun.]
[A giant sized picture frame and
a camera covered in flour?]
[Is it Jong Suk and Ji Hyo...
or Gary and Bo Young?]
- Wouldn't I be too obvious?
- That's why it's you.
There they come.
What?
- Maybe it's not her.
- Bo Young is next.
But keep this in mind.
We have an extra hint that you don't.
[They have an extra hint
that the other team doesn't?]
[A hint that we don't have?]
[All the members walking to pottery village
before they did the market mission.]
[These two are assuming some sort of
a position even here?]
I'm going to lose my mind.
You all keep thinking it's me?
[No way... you want me to do that?]
[The ultimate gesture- The back hug.]
[That's too hard.]
[The mission that they did here is
'The game of love'.]
Yoo Jae Suk will make a heart sign with his
hands and point it towards someone.
He'll direct his heart to the next person.
If Song Ji Hyo accepts,
then she'll do the same thing to Ha Ha.
So it'll go around
in a circle in that manner.
If you don't want to accept
Yoo Jae Suk's love...
then you can choose your own method
to refuse his love.
[Can refuse his love in any methods
that you choose should you decide to refuse.]
[Will we be able to...]
[do a back hug here?]
Will the person accept it or not!
The game of love!
I love you.
- I love you.
- Love you too.
[Mr. Gary's sincerity leaking through?]
- Gary needs to get punished.
- Must I get punished for that?
[Punishment is a kiss on the cheek,
befitting of the love game.]
[Sae Young and Bo Young's
double cheek kiss.]
Hurray!
Mother!
[It's not the kiss we need,
but a back hug we need...]
I just hope that Kwang Soo
doesn't come sit next to me.
[Time to swap seats.]
[Okay... Blank Ji is now sitting
now to Jong Suk.]
[She is sitting next to me now...]
[But suddenly feeling shy about doing it.]
I love you.
[Back hug]
[I don't think now's the time.]
[Automatically breaks out in a fit
of laughter upon seeing Kwang Ja's face.]
[I'm too embarrassed to do
the back hug!]
Here's your real hint.
[Only the real hint is given out
from having failed the secret mission.]
[We're in trouble...]
[Thus, the girl team earned themselves
an extra real hint.]
'Let's start a business'?
[What does this hint mean?]
- Are you guys still figuring it out?
- Let's move it along.
[The hint is making a difference
in what the two teams know?]
[They're still confused over whether it's
Jong Suk, Ji Hyo or Gary, Bo Young.]
He keeps denying that it's him,
but why aren't you doing the same?
- I told you earlier that it isn't me.
- Who do you think it is?
I think it's Jae Suk.
[Jong Suk is flustered from being cornered,
and still pointing fingers at Jae Suk.]
What is taking you guys so long?
- No other choice.
- Okay, we got it.
- We got it.
- We've made our decision.
[Secret couple, Ji Hyo and Jong Suk.
Can they still keep their secret?]
The male team will announce who they think is
the secret couple from having arrived first
and ask the couple to stand in front
of the frame that you seeing the middle.
[Please...]
- Okay, I'm going to count to five.
- Ji Hyo and Jong Suk.
- Okay, let's go with Ji Hyo and Jong Suk.
- Why?
- It's Ji Hyo and Jong Suk.
- Look at how confident Ji Hyo looks.
- But she's an actress.
[Blank Ji is maintaining her poker face
all the way to the end.]
[Last minute chance to Gary?]
No, you've gotten much better
at lying lately.
What are you talking about?
Think about our Christmas special.
[Nervous... and anxious.]
What are you talking about?
Think about our Christmas special.
No, we can't even tell when you're
lying to us anymore.
Then I'll go stand up there right now.
Just hang on a second.
[The team is going back and forth
on their decision to the very last minute.]
[Please...]
Song Ji Hyo and Lee Jong Suk.
[Normally standoffish Ji Hyo was being
unusually friendly with Jong Suk today?]
Lee Jong Suk and Song Ji Hyo.
[Ah... our secret love affair...
Will this be the end of it?]
[Jong Suk and Ji Hyo are ultimately made
to go stand in front of the picture frame.]
[Preparing themselves to get showered
with the flour.]
Okay, time to take the picture.
[You did great today.]
One, two...
Two...
[The camera of truth!]
- I knew that it was you two.
- I wasn't absolutely sure though.
- What made you so sure?
- The numbers.
And Jong Suk kept acting nervous.
It was either Gary or Jong Suk...
and Gary kept working on solving the hint.
- But Jong Suk didn't do that.
- He didn't want to solve the hint.
[Too bad.]
- The extra hint that we got is amazing.
- What is it?
'Let's start a business'.
What does that mean?
Look at the letters of it all.
It spells out Song Ji Hyo and Lee Jong Suk.
I knew something was off.
I felt kind of crappy all day long.
- They were too close all day.
- Did they not have any missions?
- We had a lot of missions to do.
- You did?
What did you guys do?
The first mission was to
clasp our hands together.
I saw the producers holding their hands!
- Who did?
- Why you...
I misunderstood and
thought that they were dating.
[They were just working hard
at their jobs.]
I thought that Jong Suk really liked
Ji Hyo for real.
But I should've known better.
That's not possible.
I guess Gary can go back to
enjoying eating again.
What about Jong Suk?
I told you that I'm not good at things
like this, and not to make me do it.
- I'm not good at things like this.
- It's because Jong Suk is too pure.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Viewer's choice guest for
Running Man's 2014 episode.]
[Yeo Jin Goo, Im Si Wan, and Do Hee.]
Just try going for my name tag.
I'm going to come for your throat.
[A nightmare of a mission that was sent in
by one of their fans in Hong Kong.]
[Three set water game that
is of an unbelievable scale.]
[The flying chair, Blob jump, and Diving.]
[Next up is the acupuncture mat race.]
[A race that's never been attempted before.]
[The agony that cannot be ignored.]
We will show you a good time
through these games!
- I love you!
- I love Hong Kong!
[A race from Hong Kong.]
Running Man is so much better
when I just watch it on TV.