Subtitles by DramaFever
[To Running Man]
[I'm a huge fan of Running Man
from Hong Kong.]
[Hong Kong- A month ago.]
[A young woman is putting all her care,
and dedication into drafting something.]
[What that young woman wanted...]
[got relayed to someone.]
[An audio visual broadcasting center in Paju.]
Hello, viewers, this is Yoo Jae Suk.
I wish you the happiest 204.
[The new year, 2014!]
[Rising stars befitting of
the year of the horse.]
2014 Running Man's choice!
We will now welcome our first rising star!
Who is it?
[2014 Running Man's Choice-
Who is the first rising star to come on?]
[That young man is...]
It's Yeo Jin Goo!
[A rising star who's stolen the hearts
of many women, Yeo Jin Goo.]
- Come this way.
- Come this way, Jin Goo.
Wow, Jin Goo.
Our first rising star of
2014 Running Man's choice!
[2014 Running Man's rising star-
Yeo Jin Goo.]
Go away!
He doesn't look anything like you.
Wow, look at his muscles.
His leg muscles are hard as a rock.
[Little Mr. Capable?
Jin Goo with muscles in all the right places.]
You look like you work out a bit.
Do you work out?
I really like sports.
- I really like sports.
- Your voice!
- Why do you have such a deep voice?
- Maybe his voice is starting to change.
- His voice must be changing.
- Go away.
[Kicked off to the other side of the room
from having made a foolish comment.]
Go away!
Don't come anywhere near him.
I can't even deal with him anymore.
He's driving me crazy.
Jin Goo, can you say hello to
our viewers?
Hello, it's great to meet all of you.
My name is Yeo Jin Goo.
[His voice is full of charisma.]
- How old are you now?
- I just turned 18.
- Seriously?
- You may look 18, but you don't sound 18.
Let's be honest,
he doesn't really look 18 either.
What about him looks 18 to you?
[You of all people have no right to tell
anyone that they look older than their age.]
What are you talking about?
Jin Goo does look like he's 18 years old.
- Look at how nice his skin looks.
- He's supposed to have nice skin at 18.
- Don't you know that?
- Go down there.
[Haroro is kicked down to the end of the line
as well for acting jealous of their guest.]
I can't believe he kicked us down here.
Okay, please help me welcome our next
rising star guest for our show!
[Who's the second rising star of
Running Man's Choice 2014?]
[A girl... A young woman?]
It's Do Hee!
[The hottest woman of 2014- Do Hee.]
- I can't believe it.
- Do Hee!
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
- Say something crass in satoori (a dialect) to us.
- Why do you want me to talk like that?
- Come on, say something for us.
[All her older 'uncle fans' wants to hear her
speak in her infamous satoori.]
I'm going to rip your throat out if you even
think about coming after my [beeping] name tag.
[And coolly turns to walk
down to the front of the line.]
That was great.
[In total and utter shock.]
- Thank you.
- That's my Do Hee.
[A fiery first greeting befitting
of the hot star's current status.]
- I was so nervous.
- No, that was great.
[Was I okay?]
- She's such a great actress.
- She's so good at acting.
- She's so good at what she does.
- Can you teach Kwang Soo how to act?
[Age isn't a factor
when it comes to learning...]
- What are you talking about?
- You can come back up the line.
[Haroro moves back up the line by
selling Kwang Soo out?]
Do Hee is our second rising guest star
following our first rising star, Jin Goo.
So let's welcome our next rising star.
Please come on out.
[2014 Running Man's Choice
third rising star is?]
- Si Wan!
- It's Si Wan!
[From an idol star to a rising actor,
Im Si Wan.]
Im Si Wan!
- Happy New Year.
- Thanks, Si Wan.
- Si Wan's here.
- Happy New Year.
I knew that he would become
a rising actor from his idol star status.
- Our Si Wan is here now.
- It's good to see you.
He was here once before when we had
our Idol Olympics.
[Si Wan was on the show once before
for their Idol Olympics episode.]
- I ripped off his name tag.
- He's been on our show many times.
- Actually, I've only been on this show once.
- It wasn't more than that?
- No, this is my only second time on the show.
- Go down the line.
[Swapping out the host of the show?]
[Kkuk, Haroro, and Giraffe are excited
to be the new co-hosts of the show.]
Yeah, I remember that you were
up against Gary, weren't you?
People usually end up doing well on
their careers after they come on our show.
He made his movie debut after
being on our show.
I saw you in that movie,
and you did such a great job in it.
You have to allow the guest to talk
instead of you doing all the talking.
[Give me back my mic!]
- Just let us do the job.
- Get back to your spot.
[Kkuk, Haroro, and Giraffe-
The three MC's back to hosting the show.]
- How do you feel about your movie coming out?
- I still feel...
I'm sure he's feeling good about it.
[MC asks, and MC answers...]
How does it feel to be back on Running Man
again for the second time?
Of course he feels great about it.
- How does it feel?
- Of course he feels great about it.
His movie is doing great,
and he's back on Running Man!
[I want you three out of here immediately!]
So will these three guests be with us today
for the filming of today's episode?
Yes, that's correct.
We'll now start 2014 Running Man Choice Race.
- Today's mission is a very special mission.
- What is it?
Our writing team received a video file
from overseas not too long ago.
[A video file that the writing team
recently received.]
I'm a big fan of Running Man from Hong Kong,
and I always have a lot of ideas for the show.
[Irene- 21 years old.
A student of Hong Kong Law School.]
[A video letter that they received from
their fan in Hong Kong.]
- She's very pretty.
- She is a very pretty woman.
I really wish to take part
in your production team.
Unfortunately, I don't live in South Korea
so I guess this is the only way I can relay
my idea for the program over to you guys.
I wish that you'd please consider my proposal.
[The proposal and video was made with
love and dedication from this one fan...]
I really look forward to your reply,
and thank you very much once again.
Wish you a Merry Christmas,
and a Happy New Year.
Happy New Year!
Thank you!
- Our utmost gratitude once again.
- She first uploaded this on YouTube.
Then she sent this video directly
over to our producer and writing team.
[She sent this directly to the writing staff!]
Our race was created by your fan,
and it's called, 'The Janggi Race.'
[Today's mission- Janggi Race.
'Janggi'= Korean Chess.]
At the beginning of the show
assuming there are seven Running Man
members and three guest members...
There will be ten chess pieces in total.
Five red, and five black.
There will be a total of five red...
and five green chess pieces.
You will each choose a chess piece
that is different in rank.
[Each player to choose one chess piece.]
Each member will then pick one of them.
And their chess pieces will represent
their identities in the final mission.
The color of their chess piece will represent
the color of their team in the final mission.
Thus, you can't look at your own chess piece
until you get to the final mission location.
[They can't look at their own chess piece
until they get to the final mission either.]
But the person who wins the mission
in the midst of the race
will be given a chance to look at their
own chess piece to see what they have
as well as a change to swap out their
chess piece with someone else.
Then that means you can ultimately change
which team you'll end up in?
Wow, this is making me kind of nervous.
There's no need to know which team
each other belongs to until the final mission.
And I advise everyone not to show their
chess piece to anyone else
because that will be disadvantageous to
their own team during the final mission.
Throughout the day, there will be chances to
swap out which team you'll end up being in.
The chess pieces that will be shown
or swapped with each of the missions
will all be revealed together
at the final mission
and the members who possesses chess pieces
of the same color will be teamed up together
for the final mission,
which you'll be playing as a team.
So my friend today could become
my enemy tomorrow?
You're my enemy every day.
[Janggi piece selection complete.]
[A fate that follows the set of rules
sent to them by their Hong Kong fan.]
[Village gymnasium in Paju.]
- Where are we?
- What is that?
What is all that now?
- What is this?
This is the first mission that Irene Tam
created...
- This is the first mission.
- Ah, Irene?
This is the first game of the mission
that Irene created and sent over to us.
Here's your first game.
For this game,
you'll be divided into pairs.
Pairs?
- I want Do Hee.
- I want to be with Do Hee.
- Me too.
You know that I'm your partner, Do Hee.
Let me see how you do first.
Wow, that's quite a personality
you've got there.
We're going to decide on the teams
before we start the game.
- How you team up will be up to you.
- Why don't you choose your partner, Do Hee?
I'm going to team up with the person
who does the best satoori.
[Decides to team up with the person who can
speak in the best satoori.]
[Keep it simple with just a single attempt.]
I'm really...
am sincere about this.
- That's it.
- I'm really sincere about this.
[Very weak and ambiguous performance.
That's his idea of satoori?]
Okay, we've got him out of
the running at least.
[Even he himself realizes how
awkward he just sounded.]
Okay, it's Gary's turn now.
Oh my... aren't you such a pretty thing.
- Next.
- Okay.
- Goodness... you're so pretty!
- Next!
You're so pretty that you're almost scary.
- Next.
- Come to me.
- What the heck was that?
- How was that any different from mine?
[Is this what a charismatic voice can do?]
- You can't use your voice like that.
- His voice is way too nice.
Suk Jin is next.
If I could be reborn into my life,
you'd be the only woman that I'd love.
You don't need to say anything further.
I think you can just stay in your spot.
[Big-nose's overtly romantic confession
automatically gets him eliminated?]
Next is Si Wan.
[Bleep-Bleep-Bleep!]
[Oh my goodness!]
[Such profanity from that innocent face?]
- We're filming a show right now.
- That's one of my character's lines.
- Do Hee! It's me!
- Just turn around.
Okay, Do Hee's going to
make her selection now.
[Who will Do Hee choose?]
I'm going to choose the person who spoke
the best satoori.
Jong Kook.
[Do Hee chooses Kim Jong Kook!]
[Everyone immediately disputes
her decision.]
He didn't even sound like
he was speaking in satoori.
Did you just choose him because you think
that we're going to play name tag elimination?
- No, that's not it at all.
- Okay, Do Hee and Jong Kook.
[First team is, Do Hee and Kim Jong Kook.]
- Look at how red his face is getting.
- What are you talking about?
[Who will Jin Goo choose?]
I'm just going to choose the person who's
voice is most similar to mine.
[Jin Goo chooses Ha Ha.]
[Second team- Ha Ha and Jin Goo.]
- It's Si Wan's turn.
- No, you did good.
[Si Wan decides to choose the person who can
do the best Kyungsan satoori impersonation.]
- Kwang Soo can start.
- I think I can handle Kyungsando satoori.
- Start.
- I'm being really sincere.
I'm being really sincere.
- Was that Namyangju satoori?
- That's not how I meant to say it!
Ji Hyo's turn.
Si Wan, you're starting to
act like a brat again.
- I forgot Ji Hyo's from Pohang!
- I'm from Pohang.
I forgot that Ji Hyo's from Pohang.
Si Wa-ee!
You've still got it, Si Wa-ee!
I had too much to eat.
[Only satoori he knows are lines
that he's heard from movies.]
Why are you reciting lines from
the movie, 'Friends'?
[Who will Si Wan choose?]
Satoori was pretty close...
and since we have to hold hands...
[Si Wan chooses Ji Hyo.]
Why are you doing this?
She was my only hope!
Why are you doing this to me?
- Si Wan's my partner.
- Si Wan!
Si Wan's grown bolder these days.
You shouldn't have done that, Si Wan.
[Fourth Team- Gary and Kwang Soo.
Fifth Team- Suk Jin and Jae Suk.]
Mission one is about lion dance.
[Team selection for
the first mission is complete.]
Ten members will team up in pairs
to form a total of five teams.
- Okay, let's go inside.
- Okay.
[Everyone heads into
the mission location together.]
- What is this?
- Oh my God.
The acupuncture mat again?
[Actually...
it's a gigantic acupuncture mat track.]
It's the acupuncture mat again?
[Their immediate future is looking bleak.]
- Wow, that looks painful.
- Look at the size of this thing.
[The bottoms of our feet...
are going to feel like they're on fire...]
Why don't you read it, Do Hee?
Read it out loud?
Do I just read it out loud?
I get nervous doing things like this.
- What do I do?
- Just read it.
Today's mission.
Horse race!
[Today's race- Horse race.]
The team to race around the track the fastest
while wearing the horse mask wins.
Okay!
Is this going to be timed?
Yes, this game was sent to us by Irene.
Mission 1A is the acupuncture hurdle race.
Each lion has to complete a sequence
of tasks on the track.
Chinese people traditionally wear a lion mask
for the new year
but we're going to do the race while wearing
the horse mask
since it's the year of the horse.
Each team just needs to race around
the track once while wearing the horse mask.
[First course- Acupuncture hurdle.]
[Second course- Acupuncture obstacle course.]
[Third course- Acupuncture slope.]
[Fourth course-
The ultimate acupuncture track.]
In the case that the hurdle falls over...
we will deduct three seconds
from your total time.
In the case of those obstacle course
markers fall down
we will deduct two seconds
from your total time.
- Then... Kwang Soo and Gary will go first.
- Why?
[First horse- Kwang Soo and Gary.]
This is scary.
Let's make it interesting.
[One person to be the horse's head,
and the other person to be the body.]
What are you talking about, Gary?
- They're going to do it like that?
- How are they going to run like that?
Hey, Kwang Soo...
You're making me feel nervous.
- You can't do that.
- We can't do it like this?
[Other than when jumping over the hurdle,
all four feet has to be on the ground.]
- Are you okay?
- Be more gentle!
- I'm going to run real fast, okay?
- Okay, Gary.
- Follow my lead, okay?
- Ready.
- What are you doing? What are you doing!
- You're too heavy!
What are you doing?
What is this!
[First course- Hurdle jumping.
Or hurdle crashing.]
- My toes!
- Run!
[Horse Gary and Kwang Soo
falls down to the ground.]
Wait!
Get up!
[When are they ever going to
complete their course?]
- That really does hurt though.
- Hurry!
[Knocked down every single hurdle.]
[Approaching their second course-
Acupuncture obstacle course.]
- Just roll, Gary. Roll.
- Roll?
[Horse Gary and Kwang Soo's plan
is to just roll through the course.]
[The agony they're to feel on their feet
are being felt with their whole body.]
I bet that hurts even more.
- I bet that hurts even more.
- That looks so painful.
[Third course- Acupuncture slope.]
[Body Kwang Soo is just being dragged along.]
[Gary... please spare me my life.]
- What are you doing?
- Wait!
[These onlookers are watching
with ease from the sidelines for now.]
[Desperate thrashing of their bodies.]
[Backtracking on the ultimate
acupuncture mat.]
Why are you walking backwards
instead of walking forward?
[Finding their wherewithal to
start moving forward again.]
[Their final course-
Forward on the ultimate acupuncture mat.]
- Why are you moving backwards?
- Wait!
[Barely manages to arrive at the finish line.]
Enough!
Thank you, Irene! We got to
play such a fun game thanks to you!
- I love you, Irene!
- I love Hong Kong!
- I love you, Hong Kong!
- H.K!
- I will never forget you, Irene!
Your time is,
two minutes and 34 seconds.
[Horse Gary and Kwang Soo-
Two minutes and 34 seconds.]
- Do Hee, do you want to...
- Ouch, that hurts.
That really hurts.
- Does it really hurt that bad?
- Yes.
How are we going to do the hurdles?
[The hurdles are the big problem...]
These pants are...
- They're too long.
- The pants are too long on Do Hee.
[The horse costume is way too big on Do Hee.]
These aren't fitting me very well.
You're not being very considerate
to our guest.
Can I pull them up like this?
[The hurdles are too high for
tiny Do Hee to jump over...]
[What are we going to do about this?]
- Do Hee, are you ready?
- Yes, I'm ready.
Get ready.
Do I have to jump?
[The problematic hurdle.]
Do Hee's going to fall over backwards,
Jong Kook!
[Mr. Capable jumps over the hurdles without
hesitation with Do Hee on his shoulder.]
[Horse Jong Kook and Do Hee remain erect
as they move through the course.]
[Easily passes through even the last hurdle.]
What are they doing?
[Time to start running!]
[Passes through the second course
at top speed.]
[Breezing through even the third course.]
[Gritting down on her teeth.]
[Even the onlookers can feel their agony.]
[Zipping through their final course.]
We're ruined.
[The agony finally sets in.]
[Horse Jong Kook and Do Hee completed their
course with phenomenal teamwork.]
[Automatically breaks out in a round
of applause for their teamwork.]
Thank goodness it's over.
- Your record is...
- Yes?
I'm just going to tell you your record,
and you have to add ten seconds to that.
- Okay.
- Your record is 49 seconds.
[49 seconds plus 10 seconds for the hurdles
equals a total of 59 seconds.]
[That's amazing.]
Okay, Jin Goo and Ha Ha's turn.
- Jin Goo's really determined right now.
- Just get moving.
- Good luck, Jin Goo.
- Show us what you got, Jin Goo.
This looks painful.
- That over there is the problem.
- Over there?
[Just you wait... acupuncture mat...]
[Focusing on the preparation
without uttering a single word.]
[Fierce determination...
with his focus on the victory.]
Jin Goo's really determined.
- Jin Goo's determined.
- Yeah, Jin Goo's determined to win.
[Serious young man.
Jin Goo's ready to attack.]
[Bulldozer Yeo Jin Goo,
ramming through the hurdles in his path.]
[Don't block my path!]
[Passing through the obstacle course at top
speed without knocking anything down!]
[He's quick.]
[Hind legs Ha Ha being dragged around by
determined forelegs Jin Goo.]
[Entering the ultimate acupuncture mat path
in the blink of an eye.]
[Even though he may scream out in pain,
he's not slowing down his speed.]
[There's no stopping him!]
Stop tormenting Dong Hoon!
[Knocked down to the ground the moment
they pass through the finish line.]
Wow, they were quick.
[Oh dear God...]
That really hurt.
[The bottoms of their feet are on fire.]
Jin Goo's fierce determination
is something to be reckoned with.
He didn't even say anything.
[Jin Goo having put all his focus on finishing
the race without saying a single word.]
Even his screams were like this...
[Full speed ahead
Ha Ha and Jin Goo's record is?]
- It'll be an additional 22 seconds.
- He said he's adding 22 seconds.
[It's an additional 22 seconds...]
I thought that was the total time.
Your record is...
[What is their speedy record?]
Your record is 36 seconds.
[Their record is 36 seconds!]
- Then what is their total record?
- 58 seconds!
[Real record is 36 seconds, plus 22 seconds,
with a total of 58 seconds.]
[Ha Ha and Jin Goo take the lead
with a mere one second difference!]
The winners can choose to keep their piece,
or swap with any one of the loser teams.
The team that came in at first place will be
given the chance to see their own chess piece
and a chance to swap out their piece
with any of the other players.
The winner will now have a chance to look
and swap out their piece with someone else.
[Ha Ha checks his own chess piece.]
[Ha Ha's chess piece is, the king piece.]
I don't know if it's right for me to
have this kind of honor.
How could this have even happened?
It seems as though...
I'm the main star of this episode today.
You can pick one of the other members
to see what piece they have.
He's still quite young...
but he's got some Kim Jong Kook in him.
[Ha Ha chooses to check Yeo Jin Goo's piece.]
Would you like to swap
your piece out with his?
- No, not at all.
- You're not going to swap yours out?
No, I have no desire to do that.
Yeo Jin Goo is a young Kim Jong Kook.
You can check your own piece first.
You have to open it carefully
so that no one else can see what it is.
[Must open it carefully so that
no one else can see what it is.]
I can see it, Jin Goo.
I can see it.
Even your surprised voice is that deep?
[Even his surprised voice is deep and low.]
And you may now choose one person...
one person who concerns you
and see which piece they have to decide if
you want to swap your piece our with theirs.
[Jin Goo selects Mr. Capable,
Jong Kook's piece.]
[Mr. Capable's piece is, 'Horse'.]
[Jong Kook's piece is higher than
Jin Goo's by two levels.]
- I'd like to switch my piece with his.
- Okay.
Then you may switch out your chess piece
with his in the box.
You may go back to your seat.
- It's another paired game.
- Okay, let's go.
[Ah... that's...]
Okay, everyone come this way.
[What is all this?]
What is that?
They even have the Blob Jump set up.
[Set up all throughout the whole
swimming pool arena...]
[Is a ginormous water game setup that's
bigger than anything else they've ever seen.]
[Just what is the water game mission
that awaits them here?]
I want everyone to read the Running Man's
Big Three relay game sign in front of you.
You must utilize all three games
that are set up in the pool area.
Every game that is played will be measured
in 'meters' to determine your record.
The team that has a combined score of 30m
by playing each course only once wins.
[Big One- Flying chair basketball.]
[Big Two- Blob Jump.]
[And lastly...]
[Big Three- Diving.]
- Diving too?
- No way.
As you can all see for yourselves,
this game is called, Running Man's Big Three.
I'd like to welcome everyone
to the mission.
You have to utilize all three game courses
that we've set up around the swimming pool.
The first team to get a total of 30m
by utilizing all three will win this mission.
Diving.
Flying chair.
Blob Jump.
All three of these game courses.
You have to play all three of these games.
You have the freedom to determine which team
will go first in each of the game courses.
But... the same game cannot be played
twice in a row.
So it's like waiting turns
at an amusement park?
Yes, it's the Big Three.
With the flying chair, you won't know when
you'll get propelled out of the chair
but you'll have to throw the ball the moment
you're propelled out of your chair.
And only those balls that lands within
a basket will count towards your total score.
And both members of the team can
attempt the same game course.
Since the mission is a bit disorderly
we've decided to choose winners for first
through third place, instead of just first.
And the person who comes in at first place
will be given a very special advantage
and second and third place winners will
also be given some sort of an advantage.
The mission will start the moment
the whistle is blown.
You can determine for yourselves where
you and your teammate will start the mission.
[Keeping an eye on your opponents to
determine their game plan is also vital.]
Three.
- Three, two, one...
- We're going to do the Flying Chair.
[Running Man Big Three- Start!]
[Jae Suk and Jin Goo are going to tackle
the tough diving board first!]
Let's do that one first.
Let's go for the diving boards.
You can jump off the 1m board,
and I'll go for the 5m board.
[Welcome to the diving board.]
I don't know which one I should jump off of.
Which meter board should we jump off of?
[They can choose from either
1m, 3m, 5m, 7.5m or 10m board.]
- I don't know about the 7.5m or 10m board.
- Then go for the 5m board.
There's no need to go too crazy with this.
If we can each jump off of a 5m...
[Going up to the 5m board first...]
- This one isn't easy either.
- All I need to do is jump, right?
Hang on a second.
[Meanwhile, Gary and Ji Hyo are at
the Blob Jump course.]
Yes, I heard.
- Who's going to jump?
- Ji Hyo will take the lead on this one.
[As guessed,
Ace Ji Hyo will be the human bullet.]
No matter how many times we do this,
things like this still scares me.
I still get scared of it
every single time we do it.
I know you spent a lot of money on this,
but don't you think you still use it too much?
I'm seriously going to lose my mind.
Jae Suk, are you going to jump
off of the 5m board?
What?
I need to jump 5m at least.
I'm thinking of doing the 1m jump.
How about you jump the 5m board,
and I'll jump the 7.5m board.
You think you can do that?
7.5m is really scary.
- I'm going to go take a look.
- Go check it out.
- Jin Goo!
- What's wrong with him?
- What are you doing?
- What is he doing?
What are you doing?
What are you planning on doing?
[Courageous Jin Goo fearlessly
climbs up to the 7.5m diving board.]
- I can do this.
- You okay with that?
- 7.5m?
- Yes, I think I can jump.
Wow... if we both jump from 7.5m,
then we'd get a total of 15m.
What do you want to do, Jae Suk?
[Jae Suk's climbing up to the 7.5m board too?]
[But... wow...]
[That's really high.]
I'll jump the 7.5m board.
- Will you be okay?
- Yes, I'll be fine.
- I really like the water.
- Really?
Okay, Jin Goo.
Then jump the 7.5m board!
- Okay, I'll do it.
- Okay.
[Courageously walks up to the front
of the diving board...]
Jin Goo's jumping the 7.5m.
7.5m!
I'm going to jump the 7.5m board!
Jin Goo!
Yeo Jin Goo!
Just get back down!
Think about this carefully, Jin Goo!
[All eyes are on him.]
- Hey, Jin Goo!
- Why is he doing that?
Hey, Yeo Jin Goo!
Okay, I'm ready!
[Even with everyone's protest...
it doesn't shake his determination.]
Jin Goo... you can jump come back down
to the 5m if you can't do it.
No, I can do it.
[But... Jin Goo's determined.]
[Okay... I can do this!]
No!
- Jin Goo!
- Is he really going to jump off that board?
[The onlookers are even more
nervous than he is.]
[Oh!]
[Jump!]
[Brave Jin Goo jumps in a single attempt
without a single moment of hesitation.]
[A perfect dive.]
[This is what you call...
a perfect diving form.]
[What am I going to do now?]
[Very cool, Yeo Jin Goo!]
[Jin Goo meets the water.]
[Jae Suk and Jin Goo- 7.5m.]
[Already at 7.5m!
Putting other team members at a panic.]
Wow, he's really brave.
- Wow, you really are something else.
- Weren't you scared?
That was really fun.
[Feeling the pressure.]
5m?
If I were to jump the 7.5m,
then we'd have 15m.
We'd get 15m if I jumped 7.5m.
Then that would give us a huge lead.
[What will cowardly older brother choose?]
[Blob Jump Team is also ready
to take their leap.]
Blob Jump is scary.
[Even the fearless Blank Ji is feeling nervous
to be getting back on the Blob Jump.]
This is no joke to be back up here again.
[Bullet Blank Ji is getting into position.]
This still scares me no matter
how many times I do it.
- Which one are you going to jump, Jae Suk?
- What?
- Which one are you going to jump?
- I was going to jump the 5m...
[Cowardly Jae Suk-
Will it be the 5m, or the 7.5m?]
Just jump the 5m!
You can totally jump the 7.5m.
It only lasts two seconds.
[Carefully walks down the 7.5m board...]
Just jump the 5m.
You just need to endure two seconds.
The jump only lasts two seconds.
Just close your eyes,
and endure two seconds.
[You can do it, Jae Suk!
Jin Goo is trying to give Jae Suk the courage.]
- Jumping this will give us 15m, right?
- Yes.
[It's a battle with his own self...]
- What are you doing?
- Jae Suk!
What are you doing up there?
You're not acting like yourself!
Just jump the 3m.
Just give that up and get back down!
Will you take this back down for me?
I really hate heights.
[I really hate being up high...
but the little brother is watching me...]
Jae Suk.
[One step...]
[And another step...]
Hey!
Put your glasses back on and come down!
- Jae Suk! 5m is still plenty!
- 3m is calling your name!
Why are you doing that?
[Yoo Hyuk is going to jump the 7.5m?
A sight that's hard to believe...]
- Just jump the 5m!
- Fighting!
[He jumped!]
Fighting!
[He did it!
Yoo-ruce Willis!]
[Very cool!]
They're all crazy.
I'm going to jump the 7.5m board.
[The ultimate coward...
has now entered the regular coward status.]
[Still alive, right?]
Hey.
I felt like I was going to die.
What are they doing up there?
[Blob Jump-
Gary and Ji Hyo are ready to go!]
One.
Two.
Three!
[Jump!]
[Ji Hyo's about to fly through the air!]
[It's flying Blank Ji!]
[Wow!
An unbelievable height!]
All I can hear are screams from everywhere.
[Screams heard from all over the place.
Welcome to 'Running Land'.]
- This is fun.
- Did you just say that this is fun?
We need to hurry, Jin Goo.
We need to go over there.
- Why aren't you guys doing anything?
- We're totally ruined now.
[Do Hee's scared of the water...]
I think this is happening right now to
help me conquer my phobia of the water.
How many meters did you get?
[What is Gary and Ji Hyo's record
on the Blob Jump?]
[Wow! 8m!
Highest Blob Jump record to date!]
[Gary and Ji Hyo- 8m.]
[Meanwhile, Jong Kook and Si Wan are
getting ready for Flying Chair Basketball.]
[Kkuk, shoots!]
[Si Wan also shoots!]
[Nice distance, but missed the basket!]
Challenge.
[Kwang Soo's turn to shoot!]
[Oh?]
[Goal in!]
[A perfect shot into a 5m basket!]
5m!
[How can this be?]
[Now if only Big-nose can succeed...]
[My goodness!]
[Two goals in a row in the same 5m basket!]
[Jong Kook and Si Wan
are feeling the pressure.]
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo gain
10m from Flying Chair Basketball.]
[Easy Brothers are off to a good start.]
[1st- Jae Suk, Jin Goo;
2nd- Suk Jin, Kwang Soo; 3rd- Gary, Ji Hyo.]
- I'm going to jump, Jae Suk.
- You're jumping right now?
[Current first place holders are moving
straight onto the Blob Jump.]
They're moving really fast.
[If they get another good record on this,
they may have a shot at the first place]
[Brave Jin Goo...
jumps again without any hesitation.]
[Coward Yoo Hyuk is flying more than
he ever has today.]
[Total mental breakdown.]
[Jin Goo, on the other hand, seems to be
having the time of his life.]
- Isn't it scary, Jin Goo?
- No, not scary at all.
[What is Jae Suk and Jin Goo's
Blob Jump record?]
[Jae Suk and Jin Goo- 7.5m.]
22.5m!
[The goal is 30m.
7.5m more, and Jae Suk and Jin Goo wins!]
[At the same time...]
[Cutie Do Hee is attempting to
jump off the 1m diving board.]
Do Hee, are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
Come here.
This was a huge feat
that Do Hee just accomplished.
[Even the 1m diving board was a huge feat
for Do Hee, who has a fear of the water.]
- It's your turn.
- Okay, I'm going.
[It's now the infamous scaredy cat,
Haroro's turn.]
Why is it so high up here?
[Monday Couple are standing side by side
up on the 5m diving board.]
Didn't you jump off of that earlier?
So how is this any higher?
Can you jump with me?
Let's just jump together, okay?
- With our hands held together like this?
- You can't let go of my hand, okay?
[Hand held couple diving?]
Let's... go.
Monday Couple, fighting!
One.
Two... wait, wait, Ji Hyo.
I'm so scared.
[Even if we're doing it together,
scary is still scary.]
We don't have any time, Jae Suk.
Hurry up and take that off.
- That's what I'm trying to do.
- Come on.
[The teams are starting to rush each other
in their own desire to win the mission.]
You can put the glasses back on
after you take the jacket off.
We have to hurry over to that other game.
The Flying Chair might take us a while.
We just need to throw 8m.
How am I going to jump off this thing?
[This guy still isn't
mentally ready to jump...]
[Kwang Soo is rushing to get himself
in position as the human bullet.]
- Suk Jin!
- Yeah?
Let's do this.
Kwang Soo!
Are you ready?
We have to do this before they finish.
We have to hurry!
[We were thinking that you were
being too ambitious...]
Get up there quickly.
22.5m?
[Jong Kook and Si Wan's combined record
from the Flying Chair Basketball- 11m.]
- If they have 22.m...
- They win if they each score 4m.
- You're right.
- Should we both jump the 7.5m right now?
If we add 15m to our current record,
then our total would be 26m.
Maybe we should do the Blob Jump first?
You want to go jump the 7.5m first?
- Do that quickly?
- 7.5m.
[Will it be the terrorizing diving first...]
[Or will they do the Blob Jump first,
and dive the rest of what they need?]
When are they going to be done here?
Are they done after this jump?
- They're done after their one jump.
- Really? Then maybe we should wait.
[One jump is all it would take, but
this is Kwang Soo we're talking about...]
[Icon of misfortune is headed
to position himself again.]
[Falls in the water
for the second time in a row.]
Hey, what are you doing down there?
Hurry up and get in position!
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
- Hurry it up!
How do I get up there?
[You really are something else...]
Should we go jump off the 7.5m first?
- Should we do it?
- Yeah, let's do it.
We're the cutest couple here.
- Cutie pie!
- Cutie!
- Hurry up.
- This is still scary.
- Fighting.
- You're doing the 3m?
- That's all you're jumping?
You guys go first.
[Easy Brothers are finally done
prepping themselves for the Blob Jump.]
Fighting!
I'm scared!
One, two, three.
[Is it time to fly?]
[Hello, Flying Squirrel.]
[Kwang-Squirrel having lost his
sanity during his flight in the air.]
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo- 6.3m.]
[Shocked Haroro prepares himself to dive.]
[Adorable water splash
befitting of the 3m dive.]
He did it.
[A total of 4m-
The cutie couple is finally in the game.]
What the heck!
Someone jumped.
I just saw someone jump.
[Jin Goo rushes off to check the scoreboard
after hearing the splash of someone diving.]
Kwang Soo just jumped.
6.3m.
[Current first place holders are
suddenly feeling anxious.]
- You go first, Jin Goo.
- Challenge.
[Shoots without hesitation.]
[Easy Brothers get an additional
6.3m from the Blob Jump.]
We need another 11.3m.
[Unable to do the addition...]
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo are currently in
second place with a total of 16.3m.]
We need 13.7m.
[Second place holders, Suk Jin and Kwang Soo
needs 13.7m more in order to win.]
It's not that high up.
It's not as high up as we think it is.
[Jong Kook and Si Wan are quickly
rushing to get ready for the 7.5m dive.]
That's how high this really is.
It's not that high.
It just feels like we're really high up
because of the water.
Here I go.
[Jumps without even hesitating?]
[A really cool diving pose.]
[Impressive dive befitting of
his rising star status.]
[Si Wan gains the 7.5m.
Now, it's Mr. Capable's turn...]
[Jong Kook and Si Wan move themselves
up to the second position.]
[First place holders are
feeling the pressure.]
[Will they score this time?]
[Goal!]
[A whopping 6m!]
[Only 1.5m left to go to win!]
It's right in front of us.
We have to jump 7.5m.
We need 15m no matter what.
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo need 13.7m more.
They have to jump 7.5m each!]
How am I going to jump the 7.5m?
How am I going to do this?
[Kkuk is ready to dive
from the 7.5m platform.]
[A bloody battle for the second position.
Jong Kook, Si Wan vs. Suk Jin, Kwang Soo.]
[Jong Kook and Si Wan still have to
jump the Blob Jump.]
- We have to jump before they do that.
- How are we going to do this?
We have no other choice.
Okay, here I go!
[Mr. Capable has a fear of heights too...]
Look at him.
[Oh my goodness...]
[Mr. Capable succeeds the 7.5m dive.]
[Right on the heels of
the first place holders.]
[Jae Suk and Jin Goo with 1.5m to go,
and Jong Kook and Si Wan with 4m.]
[Please make the goal...]
- It didn't make it?
- They're already at 28.5m.
[Diving is all they have left to face.
If they can dive this, they can win it...]
Come on, hurry.
[But 7.5m isn't an easy height to jump from.]
I'm going to lose it.
[Jong Kook and Si Wan are rushing
to do the Blob Jump.]
Come on, Kwang Soo.
Let's win the Best Couple Award.
- You think we can win the Best Couple Award?
- I think that we can.
[This couple is already preparing themselves
to go after an award that's a year away...]
[Kwang Soo is ready to jump
the 7.5m platform.]
[Best Couple Award...]
[The award is ours!]
[Amazing! These cowardly Running Man members
are fearlessly going after it today!]
[Kwang Soo immediately succeeds his dive!]
You have to jump right now, Suk Jin!
[The victory now rides on Suk Jin!]
He just jumped the 7.5m.
[Jae Suk and Jin Goo, who were in the lead,
are now at a chance of losing their win!]
- He just jumped the 7.5m.
- We're in trouble. We have to hurry.
What's the score right now?
Go take a look, Jin Goo.
Oh my... oh my!
Jong Kook and Si Wan only need
4m more to win.
[They'll lose their first place spot
if they don't hurry!]
[Come on, please...]
[Misses the goal again!]
[Crap!]
- They only have 1.5m left to go.
- Let's hurry.
[Jong Kook and Si Wan only need to jump
4m on the Blob Jump in order to win!]
We have to jump before they do!
Suk Jin!
[Big-nose... will he be able to jump?]
You have to jump before they do!
Suk Jin!
No!
[A fiery competition!]
[Please, ball!]
[Jong Kook and Si Wan are ready
for the jump!]
[Big-nosed Brother!
He jumps the 7.5m!]
[Just who... will... succeed first?]
[Jae Suk and Jin Goo succeed
with the 3m goal!]
[Jong Kook and Si Wan also succeeds
the Blob Jump!]
[Big-nose also succeeds the 7.5m dive!]
You made the goal!
[Jong Kook and Si Wan clear the mission
with a 4.5m record.]
[Suk Jin and Kwang Soo
also clear the mission.]
[Easy Brothers, we really hope
that you win the Best Couple Award.]
[Running Land Big Three-
All three teams succeed with the 30m.]
[The problem now is figuring out
which team came in first.]
Thus...
The first place winners are...
[Which of the three teams cleared
the mission first?]
Yoo Jae Suk and Yeo Jin Goo.
Yoo Jae Suk and Yeo Jin Goo
are in first place.
[By the split of a hair...]
It was a five second difference.
- With a total of 31.5m.
- 31.5m.
And five seconds later, Ji Suk Jin and
Lee Kwang Soo came in with 31.3m.
And two seconds later, in third place...
Remember what I told you earlier about the
first place winners getting a huge advantage?
First place winners can come out,
and take a look at their piece...
and you can look at two other peoples' pieces
and choose to swap it out with theirs.
Second place can winners can look at
one other person's piece
and swap your piece out with theirs
should you choose to do so.
And one person of the third place winners
can choose to do the same.
First, one of the third place winners can come
and swap out their piece should you choose.
[Si Wan is given the chance
to swap out his piece.]
[A mental battle amongst the members.]
[The final janggi piece status...]
[Where do they stand now?]
[The highly anticipated final mission.]
[Just what is the final mission that
their fan, Irene, has in store for them?]
[They'll start off with everyone separating.]
- What is this?
- Come on, now.
[What is this?]
Where are you taking us?
I've only seen this on TV.
What is this now?
I know what I had in the beginning.
[Just how did everyone's
janggi pieces change?]
What is this?
[A large box, and the container holding
their janggi piece is in front of them.]
I had the horse piece earlier.
[Oh?]
It has been switched.
[Ha Ha had the General piece in the beginning.]
[Ha Ha's piece has been switched too!]
Mine's been switched out?
Wow... here I thought I was
going to win.
[The first place winning team member, Jin Goo,
with a chance to swap out the piece earlier.]
[He swaps out his piece with Ha Ha's piece!]
[Big-nose swaps his out with Kwang Soo's.]
I have the horse.
[Totally confused.]
I had the horse earlier.
[Si Wan's piece is still the same.]
Soldier?
This is the soldier piece, right?
So I'm a 'Soldier'?
I'm the 'Cannon'.
I took Kim Jong Kook's piece.
[Jae Suk checks his own piece earlier...]
[Jae Suk's piece was 'Soldier'.]
[Since he came in at first place,
he has a chance to look at two pieces.]
[He checks Jong Kook and Kwang Soo's pieces.]
[Of all things,
they both have to be a 'Cannon'.]
What other choice do I have?
[Without much hesitation,
he swaps out his piece with Jong Kook's.]
I'm sure that Kim Jong Kook is
pretty angry right now.
Seriously.
Private.
Why are you saying that
in such a bratty voice?
You could've said it in a nice voice,
but you said that like such a brat.
[Red Team's General is none other than...
Yeo Jin Goo.]
I'm the General.
General Yeo.
Call me, General Yeo.
This is the highest position?
[Green Team's General is, Song Ji Hyo.]
Please tell me what's going on.
I have no idea what we're doing.
This is my first time seeing my piece,
while everyone has had a chance to see theirs
and you're telling me that I'm the 'King'?
(King and General are the same in janggi.)
- Is this an important piece?
- Yes, of course.
Please open the large box.
[Opens the box to reveal a green uniform,
and a mission envelope.]
What are you doing?
Why are you trying to upset me like that?
[Green Team members change into
green team uniform.]
['Cha/Cart'- Do Hee and Ha Ha.]
['Ma/Horse'- Suk Jin and Si Wan.]
['Po/Cannon'- Lee Kwang Soo and Yoo Jae Suk.]
['Soldier'- Gary and Jong Kook.]
['General'- Song Ji Hyo and Yeo Jin Goo.]
It's a video message.
[A video message in the mission phone.]
The game rules will be announced.
[The rules are relayed exactly as
Irene sent them.]
The game rules will be announced.
Following the rules of
Hong Kong style chess games
the ranking of the five chess pieces are...
General, Cart, Horse, Cannon, and Soldier.
The higher rank of one team can kill anyone
of the opposing team's lower rank.
And of course,
the same rank can kill each other.
[Same rank can kill each other,
and a lower rank of the opposing team.]
So the lower the rank,
the less people they can oust.
So being a lower rank isn't good, right?
So I guess my piece isn't that bad.
I'll oust whomever I can.
If someone of the lower rank ousts someone
of higher rank in the opposing team
then it is deemed ineffective.
So I can oust another soldier,
but I can't oust anyone of higher rank?
- So that's all I can do?
- Time pause?
[Three second pause if they end up
ousting someone of the higher rank.]
A special rule applies to soldiers.
While they're lowest in rank,
they have the power to oust the General.
They can oust their highest ranking opponent,
the General.
[Lowest rank, the Soldier,
can oust the highest rank, the General.]
[A soldier can oust the General!]
- So only I can oust the King?
- No, the Kings can oust each other too.
[Only another General or a Soldier
can oust a General.]
Seriously.
[Total regret mode.]
Kim Jong Kook is the Soldier
on the opposing team.
How do things like this
always happen in my life?
What does that mean?
The Soldier or the General of one team
as to kill the General of the opposing team.
The whole team will lose the mission
once their General is killed.
So once the General is killed,
then that whole team loses.
[Just like in the game of janggi,
the game is over once the General is dead.]
So the ones that I should be careful of...
are the General and the Soldier.
So it's important to protect the Soldier
while ousting members of the other team.
[It's important to protect the Soldier to
oust the General of the opposing team.]
[The two teams' Soldiers
play a very crucial role!]
[Five seconds before the chase begins!]
Since it'll take me less time to lay down
on the ground with my short stature...
I think that'll give me an advantage.
[Game start]
Irene.
This race is for you.
[Letter from Hong Kong-
Janggi Chase- Start.]
[Make way for General Yeo.]
Oh my goodness.
[Nervousness escalates one hundredfold
going through the experience himself.]
I'm scared.
I have to conquer my own fear.
[It's all over if I get ousted!
Even more burden for the General.]
Do Hee!
Are you the 'Cart'?
- I can oust people.
- You're 'Cha', right?
[Members of the same team are revealing
their own status to each other.]
[Do Hee can oust anyone
other than the General.]
[Meanwhile, Si Wan hasn't run across
any of his own team members yet.]
It would be so great if I were 'Cha'.
At this rate, I'm going to get...
I don't think anyone's seen my piece.
[Si Wan and Big-nose come face to face.]
[They're the same status.
Able to attack each other.]
What are you doing here by yourself?
Why are you backing away?
[Seeing how you're backing away,
you must be of the lower rank?]
What's your rank, Si Wan?
[It's three against one all of a sudden.]
- Suk Jin's only 'Ma' position.
- I can oust Si Wan if you'll help me.
That's what we can do.
Si Wan!
[Fast runner, Si Wan.]
He's way too fast.
Jong Kook's on our team.
Why don't I see any of my own
team members?
[Hey!]
[Can attack.]
[Can't attack.]
[General Yeo on the attack!]
Si Wan.
[Wait...]
[Seeing how aggressive he's being...]
[Jin Goo must be of a higher rank.]
Why don't you just surrender since
we're already in this position?
[Si Wan's looking for a chance to escape.]
[But Jae Suk appears out of nowhere
to block off his escape.]
[Nowhere to run.]
[Jin Goo with Si Wan's name tag in his hand!]
I'm the first one ousted.
Where in the world are my team members?
[Green Team's 'Horse' is out.]
Si Wan was a 'Horse'.
Si Wan... is first one ousted again.
[Si Wan was the first one ousted in
2012's Running Man vs Idols too.]
Si Wan's such a fast runner,
so I don't know how you die so quickly.
[Meet the 'Race Starter' of the Idols.]
[Im Si Wan- Out!]
Im Si Wan, out.
Si Wan was the first one ousted
the last time he was on the show too.
Poor Si Wan.
[Come here.
Jong Kook is over there.]
[Blank Ji can sense his presence nearby.]
[She's trying to oust Jong Kook,
thinking that he's her opponent.]
[Blocks off his escape route first.]
[Huh?]
[But he's wearing a green uniform?]
[We're on the same team.]
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
[Still unable to believe even after
seeing him in his green uniform.]
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, we're on the same team.
You really startled me.
[Kkuk bumped his knee in his haste
to hide from Blank Ji.]
- Then everyone's mistaken right now.
- Why?
- Everyone thinks you're on the Red Team.
- Really?
- The situation right now...
- What's your rank?
Tell me what your rank is.
I'm the General.
Then you and I are perfect to
stay together.
What's your position?
Are you the Soldier?
[Mr. Capable is the special Soldier.
Green Team just got a huge boost!]
I can grab them
and you can rip off the name tags.
[Mr. Capable to do the grabbing,
and Ace to do the ripping.]
That would be the best combo!
We have to start hunting.
[At the same time...]
Do Hee must be the General.
Green Team!
- Really?
- I don't know what Ha Ha is.
But since I'm the General...
should I go see what he is?
[General Yeo on the move again.]
Isn't Do Hee on our team?
No, Do Hee's on our team.
What about Jong Kook?
I haven't seen Jong Kook yet.
Whose team is Jong Kook on?
I think he's on your team.
[Wait... Jin Goo's coming toward me
without any fear?]
- You just stay there.
- Where are you going?
[Run!]
[Attack!]
[Quick witted Haroro makes his escape!]
[Gary comes out of his hiding to help!]
[Just then...]
[Kwang Soo springs an attack on Do Hee!]
[Haroro is captured!]
- I'm sorry, Do Hee. I have no other choice.
- Don't do this, Kwang Soo.
I'm going to start kicking.
[Ha Ha is in...]
[Ha Ha rips off Jin Goo's name tag!]
[And Kwang Soo rips off Do Hee's
name tag!]
[Pause]
Isn't this a 'Cart'?
If someone of the lower rank removes
the name tag of someone of the higher rank
then it is ineffective.
[Removing name tag of a higher rank is
ineffective as well as causing a time pause.]
[Three seconds to run.]
Three, two, one.
[Do Hee on the chase!]
[They all know each other's rank now!]
[Capture means they're ousted!]
[Yoo Hyuk makes his appearance!]
[Haroro is trapped without an escape!]
[General Yeo takes care of the situation.]
[Ha Ha- out!]
[Green Team is in danger!]
[Jin Goo runs into his seniors who are in the
midst of filming their drama.]
[Yoon Seo Hyun and Wang Bit Na-
On the scene of 'Two Women's Room'.]
- Have you seen Kwang Soo?
- I haven't seen him. He's not in there.
It's too dark in there to even
see anything.
- What about Ji Hyo? Have you seen her?
- I think so, but I'm not sure.
Where's Ji Hyo?
- Not sure... over there, or there, or there?
- Come on.
- I'm not sure.
- I have to find Ji Hyo.
Goodbye.
Where in the world did she go?
[Someone is coming after his name tag!]
[It's actor, Yoon Seo Hyun, playing a prank!]
- Why are you doing this to me?
- So that's what it feels like.
That's fun.
[Mr. Yoon Seo Hyun with a knack
for variety shows.]
[Ten years shaved off of his life.]
Why did he have to be wearing
blue of all colors?
[Meanwhile, Jae Suk is searching
the opposite end of the building.]
[Discovers Kkuk.]
So this is where you've been.
- This is where you've been?
- What rank are you?
[These two people's fates have been
swapped by Jae Suk's hand.]
- I'm right above you, you say?
- Yeah, you're not that high in rank.
I may not be that high up in rank,
but I can still oust you from my position.
You must be eyeing my General, are you?
[Trying to gather
information from each other.]
- You're not much to look at either, are you?
- What did you just say?
[Oh? Jin Goo's hiding behind him?]
You're nothing to be afraid of.
Jae Suk.
Come on then.
I have nothing to be afraid of.
I'll just rip your tag off,
and keep pausing time.
Seeing the way you're standing there,
there must be someone hiding behind you.
[Jong Kook, with the power to oust the King.
Jae Suk tries to get Jin Goo to safety.]
Should I just put you out of your misery
and oust you right now?
Then come on and do it.
[Childish mind games.]
If you're not even going to do anything,
then just get out of here.
Stop just standing there.
[Just then,
Big-nose starts making his approach.]
[Wait...]
[If you and I gang up on him together...]
[Then perhaps we can oust
Jong Kook together?]
This really feels like a game of janggi.
You're acting like you've got
some tricks up your sleeve.
Even though we're playing it like this,
it's like we're playing a janggi board game.
Yes, you're right.
- Those are pretty good acting skills.
- Why?
You're acting like you've got
something up your sleeve.
- What do you mean, up my sleeve?
- You've got a weak trick behind you there.
- What do you mean, a weak trick?
- What did you just call me?
- I'm just calling it like I see it.
[They're closing in to capture the Soldier
who took a stab at their pride.]
[Want to see what we're capable of?]
- That's a pretty weak trick up your sleeve.
- We can oust him, right?
[Facing off in tight quarters.]
- Wait, Suk Jin.
- You won't get away with this.
[Huh?]
- I smell perfume.
- What perfume?
[Perfume?]
What perfume?
- What perfume are you talking about?
- I can smell Ji Hyo's perfume.
[Blank Ji really is behind the door!]
[Mr. Capable to lure them in,
and Ace to oust them.]
[Mr. Capable lures them into the room
just like they had planned!]
Wait, Suk Jin.
I smell perfume.
[But dog-nosed Yoo Hyuk detects
traces of Ji Hyo's perfume!]
[Ah... we almost had them!]
It's Ji Hyo!
[Desperate escape.]
[His infamous nose does it again!]
What's going on there?
[The Soldier is chasing them?]
What is going on here?
[But after their initial fleeing...]
- Why are we being chased by a Soldier?
- Why are we running away?
- Why are we escaping?
[They can't help but escape from Jong Kook.]
Blank Ji is coming.
[The ultimate combo duo.
General Blank Ji is right behind Jong Kook!]
[Making their escape for now since
they can't win against the General.]
[So close...]
I can't believe this is happening.
I never should've switched my piece with his.
You should've just left his piece alone
instead of making him the Soldier.
You should've kept your Soldier piece
so that you could attack the General.
Would you have kept the Soldier piece?
How could I have known this would happen?
I see what you're saying...
but this still shouldn't have happened.
- That was still the wrong thing to do.
- I'm going to lose my mind.
[To be chased by a Soldier is
driving them both out of their minds.]
Why is our team so weak when all
five members of our team are still alive?
[Let's gather our team together first.]
[No matter where they go,
they can't escape from the Tiger.]
Ji Hyo!
[General Blank joins in on the fray.]
[Grasshopper is caught in the jar!]
[Big-nose in the midst of his escape...
turns around to save Jae Suk?]
Grab him, Jong Kook.
[Jae Suk- Out!]
[What horrible timing!]
[Kills two birds with one stone.]
Our team just lost both
the 'Cart' and 'Cannon' piece.
We have to go get Do Hee.
[Mr. Capable and Ace Duo-
Ousts two opponents in the blink of an eye!]
What is this!
[Meanwhile]
[Where is Kwang Soo slinkering off to
while all this is happening?]
This is a drama filming set.
[This is the 'My Love From Another Star' set.]
I watch this drama all the time.
This is where dramas are filmed.
This place is like a second home to me.
[But why are you looking so excited?]
[Is he practicing his acting?]
Is this where Jeon Ji Hyun's room is?
Then Soo Hyun's room must be in here too.
Soo Hyun and I are really...
He and I are really close.
I talk to him in casual speech
all the time.
[That's because you're older than him.]
[Oh?]
[Just then, The Red Team closes in on him.]
- Are you all together?
- Are you by yourself right now?
[Gary, Jin Goo and Do Hee are all
closing in on him.]
- Can you give me a break?
- Why would we do that?
[Kwang Soo adamantly tries
to fight them off.]
[The only person that
Kwang Soo can oust here is Gary!]
[He can't even oust Jin Goo and Do Hee
because their ranks are higher than his.]
I don't want to get ousted here!
Oust him right now before anyone comes!
Jong Kook!
[Just then]
No!
You did good.
- Let's go.
- Who knew that this would happen?
Did you rip off his name tag?
Can I take this home with me?
[Happy-go-lucky Jin Goo takes
the name tag as a keepsake.]
You're really strong.
I can't believe he lasted that long
even with all three of us attacking him.
[Kwang Soo got ousted while playing
'Drama' all by himself...]
[Players left remaining-
Red Team: 3 vs Green Team: 2.]
[But the survivors of the Green Team
are Mr. Capable and Ace Ji Hyo.]
[No matter how many opponents are left alive,
this is no easy duo to defeat.]
[At last...]
[All the survivors are about to
come face to face.]
What if Ji Hyo's hiding around here
somewhere?
[Extreme state of nervousness.]
This could've turned out really bad.
Do Hee's not the General, right?
Do Hee's not the General.
[Guys...]
[You remember the plan, right?]
Listen to me carefully.
This is what I've learned from playing
this game these past few years.
Jong Kook is going to avoid Do Hee,
and come after you and I.
And while he has us in his grasp,
Ji Hyo's going to try to eliminate us.
That's the chance you have to attack.
That's hard.
We have to try to hold out
no matter what we have to do.
Ji Hyo's going to come after us to try to
oust us, and she'll be after you especially.
That's the chance we have to wait for.
You and I have to both watch out for it.
Don't think about ousting Jong Kook.
- Who are you after?
- Ji Hyo.
- And what about you?
- Jong Kook.
[Jin Goo to go after Ji Hyo,
and Do Hee to go after Jong Kook.]
[It's time.]
[Guys... you have to stay focused.]
[Just like I've trained you...]
[It's time for the inevitable...]
[But they see enraged Kwang Soo
is being led away to jail.]
[During this crucial moment...]
You shouldn't have been
walking around by yourself.
[Why didn't you come help me!]
This is fate playing a cruel joke on us.
The way I see it, Ji Hyo's the General.
- No, the way I see it...
- If I have to eliminate you...
Please understand what I'm about to do.
This will be going down in history.
[Please understand if I eliminate you.
This will be an event for the books.]
[Will it be the Green Team...
or the Red Team?]
[Time to determine the victors.]
[Okay, what we've been trained to do...]
[Mr. Capable's stance
that Gary told us about...]
[That's the stance he was talking about.]
[Just like we practiced...]
[Let's do this!]
[Attack]
That should've been me.
[Are you jealous of my position?]
Can we switch our spots?
I really want to be in his spot.
[Time to determine the ultimate winner!]
I'll go after Jong Kook.
[I have to take care of Jong Kook.]
[Time to move in.]
[Jin Goo quickly pulls his body away
to escape Blank Ji's attack.]
[The two Kings are facing off
against one another!]
[Green vs Red.
A bloody battle between the Generals.]
[Do Hee's got her target locked down.]
[Just then...]
[Gary springs an ambush attack
on Blank Ji!]
[Soldier Gary...]
[Ousts General Blank!]
[Signs of a fierce battle.]
[Could this victory be credited
to their earlier training?]
We won.
[Red Team wins!]
- You did it!
- Gary did it!
The game that we played today was really
an amazing idea by our Hong Kong fan.
[Today's race was carried out exactly as
created by their fan in Hong Kong.]
[Extremely fair... and enjoyable race.]
[Thank you, Irene.]
- There wasn't a single flaw in the race.
- Is the victory ours?
Please bring out the prize.
- I feel so bad for Si Wan.
- I can't believe our team lost.
[A young woman,
timidly walking out onto the set...]
Wait, that's...
[Wait... that young lady is...]
I'm a big fan of Running Man from Hong Kong,
and I always have a lot of ideas for the show.
[She's standing right in front of us!]
You're absolutely beautiful in person!
[A shocking appearance that
none of them were expecting.]
- I can't believe that you're here!
- How did you even get here?
[The truth is...]
- Thank you so much, Irene.
- Thank you.
[All day today...]
[She's been watching all the Running Man
cast members from the sidelines.]
[Wow, it's Ji Hyo!]
- Does that really hurt?
- Yeah, it hurts.
[Fascinated by seeing them in person...
and truly enjoying the whole experience.]
[While watching her idea come to life...]
[Feeling the excitement,
and joy at the same time.]
Hello.
My name is Irene.
It's very nice to meet you.
[Thank you for your love and support,
and it's nice to meet you, Irene!]
Very good, fantastic!
- Your idea was very good.
- Perfect idea.
- Perfect role as well.
- You are so beautiful.
[Showing her their gratitude with
what little English they know.]
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[Irene passes out the winning prize,
gold janggi pieces directly.]
Seriously Irene... thank you very much.
[Thank you so much for your love for our show,
and for your wonderful idea for the episode.]
I like every one of you.
But if it's a game of tearing off name tags,
then I like Kim Jong Kook the most.
[Likes Kim Jong Kook the most when it comes
to the name tag elimination game.]
Out of the way!
To our Idol Game Starter, Si Wan,
who's been with us all day...
and our Do Hee, and Jin Goo...
It's been such a joy having all three
of them here with us on the show today.
But more than anything,
we'd like to thank Irene
for all the help that she's given us,
and for sending us such a wonderful idea.
Thank you!
It has been really amazing today,
and thank you very much once again.
Bye.
Thank you very much.
Running Man... fighting!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[January, 26, 2014-
With our Hong Kong fan, Irene.]
[Do you... believe in fate?]
[Find your mate whom you're
fated to be with.]
[You must change your fate.]
[There's only one chance.]
[Fateful Partner]