Subtitles by DramaFever
[Running Man Presents...]
[Location- Latitude 27 10'36.
Longitude- 153'22'33.]
[Fascinating land of Australia.
An adventure that starts on this land.]
[Mission- Awake the treasure that waits
under the shipwreck.]
[South pacific ocean- Under the shipwreck...]
[The treasure that lies in slumber.]
[Water-Wind-Earth-Fire.]
[When the four elements of the earth collide,
the treasure will awaken from its slumber.]
[At the same time-
In Seoul, the capital of South Korea.]
[Project Name- Adventure in Australia.]
[To all the selected agents-
Gather at 'Q' marina in Seoul.]
[Agent, Kim Woo Bin]
[Agent, Jung Ji Hoon]
[Team Running Man- Find the treasure.]
[Ten minutes ago.]
[Everyone's excited to see the world star,
and one of the hottest actors join them.]
Ji Hoon has very good manners.
He's from Anyang.
- Why are you crying, Woo Bin?
- Woo Bin is crying.
You know why Woo Bin's crying, right?
It's because of the cold wind in his eyes.
- I was trying to look cool.
- His eyes tears up in the wind.
Your eyes are tearing up so much.
[The reason for those tears...]
[My eyes are tearing up...]
Stop crying!
[Can't stop the tears from flowing.]
- Let's both wear our sunglasses.
- Yes, just wear your sunglasses.
- Wow, what a good looking group we have.
- We should all just go to the club right now.
People in Australia are going to be
shocked to see us.
[Adventure in Australia with
the hottest men of Korea.]
I will now announce the teams.
- First, Rain's team.
- Rain!
[Who will be Rain's teammate?]
How about me?
We can be Bi-Gae. ('Bi-gae'= pillow.]
- Let us be the 'Bi-Gae' team!
- How about 'Bi-Kwang'?
The team will be... Bi-Kwang.
[Bi-Kwang to be the first team.]
- Yes!
- He's so useful to have and order around.
He'll be so useful to him on this trip.
I'd like to have him as my partner.
He's the perfect person to have around
when you're going somewhere.
He just follows around without talking much
when you travel with him overseas.
- I feel like I just hit the jackpot.
- You seriously are so lucky.
- That's not what I'm good for.
- He really is useful to have around.
Next up is... Kim Woo Bin's partner.
[Who will be Woo Bin's partner?]
Yoo Jae Suk.
You really are an heir!
He really is an heir to a fortune.
Next up is, Kim Jong Kook.
- You'll be partnered up with Ha Ha.
- My brother!
[Jong Kook and his lil' bro, Ha Ha.]
Then I'm partnered up with Suk Jin?
- Come here.
- Darn!
[Adventure in Australia-
Gary is chosen to take the honor.]
You will now head off to the airport
for your flight to Australia.
Your race will be...
Adventure in Australia.
Find the lost treasure.
[Adventure in Australia-
Find the lost treasure.]
[In the middle of the southern pacific ocean,
a treasure chest lies in slumber.]
A treasure chest is waiting for you
in Australia.
In order to find
the lost treasure in Australia
you'll need the four elements.
Water, fire, wind, and earth.
All four of those elements must collide
in order for you to find the lost treasure.
Everyone must step forward one by one,
and choose a card lying on the table.
Which will determine
which element you'll have.
[How will these cards come in handy later?]
The lost treasure is located somewhere
within Tangalooma Park in Brisbane.
Seriously?
[Off to find the lost treasure!]
[Canberra- Capital of Australia.]
[Where the Southern Pacific
and Indian Oceans meet...]
[A country with the sixth largest
territory in the world.]
[The oldest continent in the world,
and a wonder of natural beauty.]
[A country where natural beauty and
human population co-exists in harmony.]
[6:30AM-
Arrives at Brisbane International Airport.]
A large crowd of people are here to welcome
them even at this early hour.]
Australia!
I love you!
- This is Tangalooma Park.
- This looks like something out of a movie.
[As soon as they get off the plane...
they have to board a helicopter?]
[Headed to Moreton Island, which is located
within Tangalooma to find their treasure.]
[Each of the Running Man agents board
the helicopter with their own team member.]
[Fire up the engines!]
Australia special...
a blockbuster event.
We start the episode here on
the helicopter.
- Is this your first time, Woo Bin?
- Yes.
[This is Woo Bin's first time
on a helicopter.]
- Did you not buy a parachute from the store?
- A parachute?
[The helicopters take flight.]
[Kwang Toad in full effect.]
[Off on their way to find
the hidden treasure!]
[Adventure in Australia-
The race starts now!]
Wow... Australia... amazing.
Look at all the beautiful nature.
It's just magnificent.
Very beautiful, Australia!
[The four Running Man helicopters
in the Australian air.]
[And the natural beauty that
surrounds them.]
[Woo Bin is clinging tightly
onto Jae Suk's hand.]
[Kwang Toad is about to pass out.]
[About 20 minutes into the flight...
they arrive in Tangalooma.]
Wow, this really is something
right out of a movie.
[Tangalooma- Third largest sand island
about 58km away from Brisbane.]
[Largest coastal dunes in the world with 95%
of the island designated as a national park.]
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha's chopper
is the first to touch down on the ground.]
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin are
second to touch down.]
[We survived!]
Do we need to run?
[Oh?... Isn't that an 'R' flag?]
[But it's too far to just walk over.]
Over there!
We need to get to those things.
[Four ATV's on the sand!]
- We need to hurry!
- Run!
Why are they running like that?
This is going to be a lot of fun.
This is Australia.
[Have they found out where the treasure lies?
Must get to the flag!]
There it is!
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha are
in the lead!]
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha take off on the beach
without a moment's hesitation.]
[In a great mood!]
- I think we're going towards that ship.
- Where?
[A gigantic sunken ship
right in front of their eyes.]
[Will the treasure be waiting for them in
the middle of the pacific ocean?]
[Jae Suk, Woo Bin, Rain, and Kwang Soo
soon follow on their own ATV's.]
[Who will take the lead?
Two men, Rain and Woo Bin, take to the sand.]
Hold on tight!
[And...]
Why are you heading towards the ocean?
[Big-nose brother in the driver's seat?]
[Finally on their way!]
This is Australia!
Let's go, Woo Bin!
Let's go!
[Let's go, Woo Bin!]
[An invigorating race
down the open sand beach.]
Other teams are catching up to us.
They're going to catch up to us.
[Rain and Kwang Soo take the lead!]
[Speed racer, Rain!
Takes over the lead without hesitation.]
[1- Rain, Kwang Soo. 2- Jong Kook, Ha Ha.
3- Jae Suk, Woo Bin.]
Wait, look over there!
[Perfect driving!
Rain and Kwang Soo arrive in first place.]
Your challenge is to find the treasure
at the Tangalooma shipwreck.
[Okay...]
What did he say?
We have to get on something else?
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin arrive
in second place.]
Your helmet, Woo Bin!
- What is this?
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you?
Your challenge is to find the treasure
at the Tangalooma shipwreck...
at the Tangalooma shipwreck. Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
- Thank you.
[They don't know what's going on,
but must change into the diving gear first.]
They're not expecting us
to swim out there, are they?
- Under?
- Underneath the water.
[No way...]
[Dive under water?]
[Oh My God.]
[Adventure in Australia- Tangalooma.]
[Open the treasure chest that is buried
under the shipwreck.]
[Deep beneath the ocean...
Awaken the treasure chest from its slumber.]
- It's shallow.
- We have to go down ourselves?
- Very very far down.
- Thank you.
You'll be alright.
[Meanwhile...]
[This team still hasn't even arrived
at their destination.]
We need to go over there, Suk Jin.
- I'm trying, but I can't get there.
- We need to go over there!
Let's go, Rain!
[Rain and Kwang Soo are already
finished changing.]
- Why are we wearing these life vests?
- Calm down.
[Boarding the boats to get closer
to the shipwreck.]
[The cool ocean air...]
There's the 'R' flag over there.
[Withstood so much to
become one with the element...]
[The shipwrecks are now an infamous
symbol of Tangalooma.]
We didn't build that ship, did we?
[You can't be serious...
That's just utterly absurd.]
Really ship?
[You're really humiliating...]
[Adventure in Australia-
Arrives at the center of Tangalooma.]
[Find the hidden treasure chest
beneath the shipwreck.]
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin's boat takes off
in second place.]
[Find the pacific ocean's lost treasure.]
- We have to win no matter what.
- Fighting!
Can we do something?
Bi-Kwang Cross?
Bi-Kwang-Cross!
[Time to put the flippers on.]
We've been on a plane, helicopter, a car,
an ATV and a boat in all this short time.
And now you want us to dive too?
- This is no joke.
- Woo Bin is in total shock right now.
- This is a total blockbuster.
- This was my first time with everything.
First time doing all this
since I've been born.
You must put on your diving equipment, and
you'll find four treasure chests in the water.
[What will they find under the water?]
[There are four sunken treasure chests
beneath the waters of the Pacific Ocean.]
You must choose one of the treasure chests.
Choose one of the locked treasure chests.
[Each of the treasure chests are
locked with their own padlocks.]
You will find many different keys
on the bottom of the ocean.
[Find the locks of keys that are
scattered about the bottom of the ocean.]
[Open the treasure chest by finding
the key that matches the lock.]
[What will they find in those chests?]
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha arrive
in third place.]
- What is this?
- What is all this?
- We have to put all those on?
- What are you guys doing?
What do you think this is for?
Put your flippers on and get in the water!
- We have to put the flippers on?
- What else would you put on? High heels?
[Muscle boy in high heels...
there goes the imagination.]
Hey, Gary. Do you think
that you can find the treasure?
- We have to find it.
- Okay, let's go find it!
- Are you good at diving?
- No, I'm not very good at it.
I'm not good at it either.
I was in the marines...
but I never did the diving.
[Meanwhile, all the other teams are already
in their gear and ready to dive.]
[Now that they're ready to dive,
the power of the ocean frightens them.]
[But athletic Rain jumps in
without any hesitation.]
[What will the underwater life
in the Pacific Ocean look like?]
[All the others follow Rain's lead,
and jump in the water as well.]
[Treading through the water
towards the shipwreck.]
Look at all the fish!
There are a ton of fish in the water!
[Sheltered between the coral,
and the shipwreck...]
[Fish of every color and size
are seen swimming in their habitat.]
- Why are there so many fish in the water?
- There are even more over here.
[All of the members are in awe of
the beauty found under the water.]
[The natural beauty and wonder of
the sunken ship, fish, and the ocean...]
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha also
get ready to dive.]
[This amazing sight is the first of many gifts
that they're receiving from Australia.]
[Rain swimming out to the furthest distance.]
[Leisurely enjoying the underwater scenery.]
[Just then-
He discovers a treasure chest!]
[Dives down immediately.]
[But... he's not gaining any speed?]
[Takes off his life-jacket, which is
deterring him from diving downward.]
[Dives down the right way.]
[He certainly is athletic-
Down to the ground in a blink of an eye.]
[Discovers all of the rings of keys!]
[Good plan! Back to the surface
with all the keys in hand.]
[Rain already discovers a treasure chest,
and gets all the keys in his hand!]
- Rain found something!
- Already?
[Rain's already halfway complete with his
mission before others even get there.]
- Did you see the chest down below?
- I'm going to see if I can open it now.
[But... there are so many keys...]
[Will the ocean let go of
the lost treasure that easily?]
[Jae Suk is feeling anxious at seeing
Rain's progress.]
[This is our home!]
[Is Jae Suk unable to dive down
because he's afraid of all the fish?]
[There's a treasure chest right
underneath Jae Suk!]
[It's a giant school of fish!]
[But he's unable to see the chest
because of the school of fish in his way.]
What do I do with all the fish?
[The formidable Pacific Ocean...]
I don't know if I can
get down there.
[Ha Ha attempts to dive down.]
[Lucky!
Discovers a treasure chest right away!]
[Head butts the sunken ship.]
[Attempts to dive down again
after regaining his wherewithal.]
[But... he's unable
to get down to the ground.]
[Why can't I get down there?]
[Even Yoo Hyuk with his phobia of the fish
makes another attempt to dive down.]
[But can't hold his breath long enough.]
[And Big-nose can't even stay afloat.]
[Woo Bin dives down as if
he's discovered something.]
[Kim Woo Bin is on his way!]
[Diving down below...]
[With one gulp of breath,
grabs a fistful of keys.]
[Dives back down with the keys
in his hand.]
[Dives down without hesitation.]
[Open sesame...]
[Ah... doesn't seem to be
the right key.]
[Yoo-ruce Willis takes a deep breath,
and dives down into the water.]
[Will this key be the right one?]
[Who are you?]
[Monster of the Pacific Ocean.]
[That poor thing...]
You want to try it, Kwang Soo?
Here, you go down and try it.
[And who's this character?]
[Fascinating world of the underwater
Pacific Ocean with diverse sea life.]
[Kwang-sea-cucumber dives down with the
key Rain chose for him in his hand.]
[It's the sea anemone monster
from earlier!]
[Yoo-anemone and Kwang-sea-cucumber -
Are the two sea monsters friends?]
[The first step in Adventure in Australia
isn't going as well as they'd hoped.]
The water is so salty!
What do we do?
This is too hard!
[Will they be able to beat this giant ocean
to get the treasure in their hands?]
[Ace Rain dives down again amongst
all the other floundering members.]
[Will he get the chest opened
this time?]
[It opened!]
[What will he find inside?]
[Is this the lost treasure of Australia?]
[Rain gets his hands on the glass bottle
from inside the treasure chest!]
We found it!
[Seriously?]
Okay, let's go.
I'm exhausted.
We got the orange treasure chest.
[Unbelievable!
Rain and Kwang Soo are first to leave.]
We're taking off!
- Where are you going?
- Rain really is amazing!
No, stay for a while.
Help me get over there.
[Where are you going?]
[The younger of the Easy Brothers is dragging
Big-nose off into the wrong direction.]
You can't hang onto me!
[Even Big-nose's personal VJ, Yoo Suk,
comes in to join the fray.]
Where are you going, Suk Jin?
Suk Jin!
[Big-nose is getting further and
further away from his treasure chest.]
I have to get back to my treasure chest.
[Exhausted Big-nose relies on the jet ski
to get him back to where he needs to be.]
- What are you doing?
- The thing is...
[He has a hard enough time on land,
so asking him to dive underwater is a bit...]
[But the man suffering the most
from Big-nose is...]
- We got ours, so let's go.
- Okay, let's go.
You two can take your glass bottle back
to the beach and receive your next order.
- How did you find that bottle?
- I somehow got one of the keys to open it.
[Check the contents of the glass bottle
once back on the beach.]
- Rain!
- What?
I should be saying that first, right?
You can just do it.
Bi-Kwang-Cross!
[What could be inside the glass bottle?]
You just wait, Gary.
[Gary has been the only member of this team
working hard for the past 20 minutes.]
[Wait just a little bit longer...]
[I'm coming to help you.]
[But... not the world's best swimmer.]
[Gary is working twice as hard as others to
make up for Big-nose's lack of participation.]
[Even the sand isn't helping me out today...]
[I want a different teammate!]
[What? Why is he swimming in place?]
[He's making some progress.
Or maybe not.]
This is really hard.
[Diver Woo Bin dives back down!]
[Random Mr. Capable dives back down too!]
[The ocean...
will I win, or will it beat me?]
[Gary vs Woo Bin-
Who will open up their chest first?]
[Woo Bin gets his chest to open!]
[The chest is opened!]
- I got it to open, Jae Suk.
- What?
[You got it open?]
[But he didn't bring the bottle
back up to the surface with him.]
[Jae Suk's turn to dive down.]
[The glass bottle is now in his hands!]
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin.
Tangalooma mission- Clear!]
[Runny nose from the excitement
of getting the chest to open.]
[Runny nose pirate of the Pacific.]
[Bi-Kwang Team arrives back on the beach
in first place.]
- I got lucky.
- What did I tell you? I told you I'll do it!
[What was it that you did, Kwang Soo?]
[Time to find out what's inside
of the glass bottle.]
[But it's not coming out...]
Can you do this for me?
- Look at how easy that was.
- You're so good at everything.
[On the other hand,
Rain gets it out in his first try.]
We're in total synch.
Bi-Kwang-Cross!
- I didn't know you liked things like that.
- Yeah, I like it.
[Finally able to check the parchment
found inside the treasure chest.]
[So this is Australia's lost treasure?]
What is this?
[Their next location?]
[Wait, it's not the treasure,
but a map to the next location?]
We have to go to the sanctuary
from Tangalooma?
- We have to get back on the helicopter?
- Yes, that's correct.
[Oh My God]
[No... this has to be a nightmare.]
Since your team came in at first place...
Remember choosing a card of one of
the four elements earlier?
Yes.
[Water, wind, fire, and earth...]
In order to find the lost treasure,
you need to find earth's four elements first.
Water, fire, wind, and earth.
These four elements must be combined
in order for you to find the lost treasure.
Each of you may now step up to the table,
and choose one of the 8 cards on the table.
That will determine which of the four
elements you'll each end up with.
[Kwang Soo chooses the element of wind.]
[Rain also chooses the element of wind.]
Since you came in at first place
during the first mission...
you are allowed to ask me
one question.
Of the four elements-
Water, fire, wind and earth...
- No one knows which card they picked, right?
- No, we don't.
You can ask me one question about your cards
because you came in at first place.
[And that question is...]
[Of the four elements,
am I element 'X'?]
You need to figure out who has
which element.
- You ask him about yours.
- About mine?
Rock, paper, scissors.
[You both can ask a question,
so why are you going through all this?]
- I thought you said ask him about mine.
- I really am so sorry.
- But you have to let me know.
- What my element is?
I really don't like to be betrayed.
- I'm going to put my faith in you.
- Then let's just do it this way.
- Let's play Rock, paper, scissors...
- Are you saying that you'll betray me?
No, that's not what I mean.
The winner asks, and no need to share.
[Agrees to have the winner ask the question,
and no need to share their answer.]
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Rain wins.]
[We're saying that both of you
can ask the question!]
Then that rock, paper, scissors
is meaningless.
Bi-Kwang-Cross!
We're going to get the answer together!
[In the end, they're going to hear
the answer together.]
Of the four elements, am I...
the element of 'water'?
[Rain asks the question-
Am I the element of 'water'?]
No, you're not.
- I can only ask one question?
- That's correct.
Since you're not the element of water,
you're either wind, fire or earth.
So you're not water.
[How can these four elements be
correlated to the lost treasure?]
[Just then...]
[Those muscles...]
[Is the muscle boy in the midst of
chastising the padlock?]
[You didn't rip that lid open with
your strength, did you?]
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha
clear their shipwreck mission.]
[It's Kwang Soo's turn to
ask the question.]
No, together. You said
you were going to do it together.
- Hey!
- No, I didn't do anything.
Of the four elements...
Am I... the element of 'wind'?
[Of the four elements,
he Kwang Soo the element of 'wind'?]
Of the four elements...
am I the element of 'water'?
- What are you doing?
- I mean, am I the wind?
I'm going to go with the 'wind'.
Think about this carefully.
You only get one chance.
- Trust me. Go with the wind.
- But if that's correct...
- What about it?
- Then you know what my element is.
Just hear me out.
- You really are something else!
- That's not what I mean!
No, that's not what I mean.
I'm going to ask him about the wind,
but can I talk to him privately?
No way!
Just hurry up and ask the question.
Think about this carefully.
If you betray me now, I will chase you down
to the ends of the earth and make you pay.
Am I...
the element of 'earth'?
No, you're not.
[That's why you should've
listened to him...]
So I'm either wind, water, or fire.
There you are.
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin land in second place.]
- Are you tired?
- I'm exhausted.
[This team confirms their next destination.]
We have to get back on the
helicopter again?
[Exact same response from all the
scaredy Running Man members.]
Okay, let's go.
Bi-Kwang-Cross!
[Bi-Kwang Team rushes off
to their next destination.]
You can ask me a question from this list.
[Of the four elements,
is one of us the element 'X'?]
- Want to go with 'fire'?
- Since we're wearing red?
Okay, let's do it.
Of the two of us,
is there the element of 'fire'?
- Fire?
- Yes.
Of the two of you...
the element of fire...
does exist.
[Jae Suk is the element of 'fire'.]
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
[What's the meaning of these
four elements?]
[The helicopters are on standby.]
[Bi-Kwang Team is off on their way to
Currumbin Sanctuary.]
[The massive land of Australia-
Chopper for transportation to save time.]
[Automatically breaks out in cry of fear
whenever he's in the chopper.]
[Second place winners, Jae Suk and Woo Bin,
also board their chopper again.]
Currumbin Sanctuary.
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha are confirming
their next place of destination.]
We have to get back on the helicopter?
Are we?
Tell me!
[Same response from everyone alike!]
Can we just swim there?
I think we can just swim over there.
I'd rather just swim over there.
[Australia is such a huge country,
and we're on a bit of a time limit...]
[Gary musters up his last bit of strength
to dive back down underwater.]
[The chest finally opens up!]
- You did it all.
- No, we did it together!
- We did it together!
- No, you did it.
- Yes, I did it.
[Still upset Gary.]
We didn't bring our bottle, did we?
[Oh My God]
[After all that hard work,
they forgot to bring their bottle.]
- I gave you the bottle!
- Let's go back and get it.
Let's go back and get it.
So sorry about that.
[Nothing seems to go right for this team.]
I can't believe we forgot to
bring our bottle.
- Sorry.
- Sorry, but one more time.
[Back they go on their boat...
and grasps the bottle tightly in his hands.]
When you two left Korea...
we asked you to choose a card
from the stack of four elements, right?
[Everyone's already gone,
and no one else is left on the beach.]
[Just like the third place winners,
this team doesn't get any hints.]
Australia!
My name is Gary!
[The Gold Coast City down below...]
[And the vast Pacific Ocean.]
It's a shark!
[What is he saying?]
[Arrives at Currumbin Sanctuary
in their helicopter.]
[Who are those guys?]
[A place where nature and people coexist.]
- What are we going to find here?
- Let's just go.
[Just running without
knowing what lies ahead.]
They're right behind us.
The Orange Team is right behind us.
Woo Bin.
Keep your strength up.
[The nature park-
Arrives at Currumbin Sanctuary.]
Rain!
What is that?
It's a kangaroo!
[This place is... a kangaroo haven.]
[Countless number of kangaroos
are right in front of their eyes!]
[An unbelievable sight.]
Kangaroos!
[Someone is waiting for their arrival.]
Welcome to the Gold Coast.
- How's the treasure hunt going?
- Excuse me?
- So far so good.
- Good.
This is your first mission.
[Put on a kangaroo costume and the combined
jump record must be at least 3m to pass.]
What is this?
Kangaroos are all around us!
[Australia Adventure II-
Become one with animals of Australia.]
Is that a stuffed animal or what?
What is this?
[If they want to become friendly with them,
must don a costume to look like one.]
[You want me to wear this costume?]
We have to put the shoes on too.
[It's a full set costume!]
Are you kidding me?
That looks really good on you.
[The new kangaroo world mascot?]
Okay, I got it.
I've got it on.
There are only four finger holes.
[Must put the baby kangaroo in the pouch!]
- What do we have to do?
- I'm 33, and I can't believe I'm doing this.
[There goes his kangaroo act.]
No, that's not how you do it.
- This is 165, right?
- Yes, 165.
- We have to put this on?
- Wow... we have to wear this?
[About to be transformed into
muscle kangaroo and kiddie kangaroo?]
[Kangaroo high jump.]
[Rain is attempting to go for 1.8m.]
- Do you think you can do that?
- You look so haggard after only a day.
[Dark circles under his eyes
after spending the day in Tangalooma.]
- I think I need my sunglasses.
- Why are you putting your sunglasses on?
[Trying to be fashionable
in his kangaroo costume?]
Challenge.
1.8m?
[Athletic Rain...]
[Will he be able to jump 1.8m?]
No, wait.
[Higher than you think, isn't it?]
That's not how kangaroos walk.
[Tiger in kangaroo outfit?]
- Where's my baby?
- Look at this.
[Ha Ha looks like a kiddie rat?]
[Rain makes his second attempt.]
There he goes.
[Trying to look cool this time?]
[A chin up instead of a high jump?]
[The world star is damaging his image.]
- I was just checking it out.
- You have to shout out, 'Challenge' first.
[You ran really hard
for it to be just a test?]
[Kwang Soo loses his turn with
Rain failing his jump.]
- Who's up next?
- Should I go?
[Confident Woo Bin's expression.]
He kept talking politely to the pilot
on our helicopter ride over here.
[Popular actor with polite manners?]
Hey, Woo Bin.
It's all about having confidence.
[Kim Woo Bin- Attempts 1.8m jump.]
[Oh... he's going to jump in place?]
[The same height that
Rain failed to jump a little bit ago...]
[Will this popular actor be able to jump it?]
[Or just a face dive.]
- Hey, Woo Bin.
- Woo Bin.
[He's too embarrassed to
lift his head back up.]
- What are you doing?
- You need to tell me before you jump.
And what was that sound
you made?
- What were you just doing?
- I was just checking it out.
[I'm keeping my eye on you guys...]
[Taping the baby pouch to the body
to keep it out of the way.]
- What are you guys doing?
- We only got 2 hours of sleep in 2 days.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
[Doing whatever they can to
help themselves succeed the mission.]
[It's understandable of Kwang Soo,
but Rain?]
Isn't this cheating?
Come on!
Let us just try it like this.
Why would you do that?
That is so unlike you!
Why is the Ninja Assassin
doing something like that?
- You're from the Dream Team!
- I'm going to do this.
I can do it this way.
Okay, fine.
Then I'm going to do it too.
[Now that I think about it...]
[I was a ninja at one point...]
[Rain attempts a 1.5m jump.]
Okay, here I go.
Challenge.
[Baby pouch is back to its original state
due to everyone's objections.]
[Easily succeeds the 1.5m jump.]
[If Kwang Soo can jump the 1.5m height,
then they succeed the mission!]
Challenge!
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Cheers himself on
whenever he gets the chance.]
[His self-confidence is on the rise.]
[All the other kangaroos leave
as soon as Kwang Soo opens up his mouth.]
Don't go, you guys!
[Their way of refusing to
cheer on the Giraffe?]
I'm going to tell that kangaroo to do it.
Lee Kwang Soo!
[Telling the kangaroos to cheer him on!]
[Oh?]
[Giraffe's hypnosis worked on them?]
[I must succeed!]
[All my friends are standing by
and watching me do this.]
[Runs with all his might... and jumps!]
[Jumps like a kangaroo!]
[Fail!]
It's okay.
[Fellow Rain Kangaroo reassures him.]
It was a very slight miss.
[The kangaroos quietly take their leave.]
Okay, our team is going to take a turn.
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin's turn.]
[Woo Bin attempts a 1.5m jump.]
Looking good.
You got this!
[flies through the air!]
[A clean success!]
There you go!
[Happy kangaroo...
and envious kangaroo.]
How did he do that?
[A combined height of 3m
will clear the mission.]
[Woo Bin succeeded a 1.5m jump.]
[Jae Suk makes an attempt
at a 1.5m jump as well.]
You won't get it done
with that big belly of yours.
Or it'll get caught on your tail.
You're going to worry about
the baby getting caught.
[Grabbing tightly onto his pouch,
tail and the baby.]
[If he can jump this...
then they can succeed the mission...]
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin succeed!]
[Two happy kangaroos.]
[Goes to see the zookeeper as soon as
they clear the mission.]
- Do we have to feed them?
- Feed all of it, and then come back to me.
[Must feed the kangaroos.]
[Giving out snacks to the kangaroos
who were nice enough to stay and watch.]
Feed it to the kangaroos.
The kangaroos?
- Kangaroos?
- We feed them out of our hands?
But they can kick us.
[Off to feed the animals after
a quick lesson on how to feed them.]
Are you scared of them?
[From one kangaroo to another.]
They all look very nice though.
Hey!
Hello.
[They're not going to acknowledge
these fake kangaroos?]
[Woo Bin kangaroo is mimicking
real kangaroos' moves.]
[One friend hops out of there.]
It's eating.
[It really is eating!]
- It's eating, Jae Suk.
- Hang on.
[Woo Bin Kangaroo makes a new friend.]
Is it yummy?
[These two kangaroos are now getting
comfortable with one another.]
Aren't they cute?
[Jae Suk Kangaroo
has yet to make a new friend.]
[One foot on the table,
and time to start snacking.]
They are really cute.
[Adorable kangaroos.]
They're so gentle!
I thought that they'd kick me like they do in
the cartoons, but they're nothing like that.
[People friendly kangaroos.]
[We're one big happy kangaroo family.]
Wow, I can't believe I'm doing this.
I've only seen this being done on TV.
I've never been able to touch them
in person like this before.
Wow... they really are super adorable.
They're so cute.
[He was afraid of them first...
but now he's even petting them.]
- Are you touching them?
- Yeah, they're so cute.
- I feel like it's going to hit me.
- No, it's not going to hit you.
I've seen too many kangaroos being
violent in cartoons.
- I know what you mean.
- You know what I mean, right?
They're usually kicking or punching on TV.
So I thought they were going to be violent,
but they're nothing like that.
I can't help but love these creatures.
[The day that they made friends
with all these kangaroos in Australia.]
[Eat up so that you can grow
big and strong.]
[Back to the world of human kangaroos.]
[Big-nose Kangaroo attempts a 1.3m jump.]
Then Gary can jump the difference.
- Okay, let's do this.
- You can jump that much, right?
[Will Gary's wish be answered?]
I'll just jump headfirst
instead of running for it.
[What?]
[Head butt.]
[A comedic fail.]
I'm not doing it!
[Hopeless Big-nose Kangaroo.]
I'm not doing this!
- Bye.
- Bye guys.
So cute.
Look at it scratching its back.
[The cutie pie is scratching its back
just like a human being!]
Where?
Over here?
[Stopping in their track
to go back to the kangaroo.]
[Does that feel good?]
[I want you to scratch me over here.]
[Second animal mission in Australia.]
[Four different koala pictures?]
[He chooses one picture out of the bunch.]
Now, go find that koala.
[Must find the koala in the picture.]
If you go over there,
you'll find another zookeeper.
Take a picture with that koala, and show it
to the zookeeper for confirmation to pass.
Keeley?
But don't you get the feeling that
we'll be able to find Keeley easily?
I feel like we're going to be able to
come in at first place today.
- Let's go find Keeley.
- You know the feeling, don't you?
Yes, I know the feeling.
I don't think you're going to be
able to do it.
[Kwang Soo succeeded his jump,
now it's up to Rain to succeed his part.]
I know you can do it, but your costume
will deter you from succeeding.
- Okay.
- You're not going to succeed.
[Holding onto his pouch with his left hand...]
[And jump!]
[Jumps with all his might and succeeds!]
[Bi-Kwang succeeds the high jump mission.]
[So jealous...]
[Off to meet their kangaroo friends.]
I've never seen them up close before.
[These Australian kangaroos...]
[are meeting human kangaroos
for the first time.]
I never knew your eyes were so big.
I should've taken my costume off
back there.
[You look pretty hot in that costume.]
I really enjoyed the time that I spent
with the kangaroos back there.
Trying to imitate the animals even in
the way that they look...
is helping the animals
open up their hearts to me.
So that's why I kept this on thinking
that it would help me with the koalas too.
- But I'm so hot now.
- What is that?
What is that?
[Tasmanian Devil- Endangered species of animal
which only exists in Tasmanian Island.]
I've never seen that before.
- It kind of looks like a pig.
- It does in a way.
[Wild animal zoo full of fascinating animals.]
[Even alligators!]
[Bringing a sense of peace to their hearts.]
You had a lot of first time experiences
today like the helicopter ride...
- And what else?
- Riding the four wheeler.
The cool and dashing image that you had
from the drama, 'Heirs' is gone.
You know that you're
a bit of a bumbling klutz, right?
What?
You know that you're a klutz?
I never knew that about myself before,
but being on RM is making me realize that now.
I think all the things that we do may
look easy to the viewers out there.
Because they all looked very easy to me too
when I used to see it being done on TV.
Who are you talking to right now?
Are you telling the viewers that?
[A video message to the viewers out there.]
[After walking for a while...]
[This place is... the world of koala bears.]
[Totally adorable!]
[Koalas sleep an average of more than
20 hours per day.]
How are we supposed to do this?
[They all look exactly alike...
so how are they supposed to find Keeley?]
This is the mark on her chest.
[The big mark on her chest is her trademark.]
[But they're all sleeping
right up against the tree.]
[The never-ending competition for
the third and fourth place.]
[Knee kick.]
How about we do it like this?
Since the two of you are good at this, how
about a competition between Suk Jin and I?
I don't think I can do this.
Between Suk Jin and Ha Ha, the one who
jumps higher will win the mission.
- Will that work?
- Yes, that sounds good to me.
[Big-nose Kangaroo attempts
a 1.2m jump.]
He's even funnier
because he's serious about it.
He's so serious about it.
[Will his toes touch the bar or not?]
[A close call, but he clears the 1.2m jump!]
- I jumped it.
- I'll jump 1.25m.
[Charismatically offering to jump
the additional 5cm.]
He's got to jump more than that, right?
[If Ha Ha succeeds this jump,
then Gary and Suk Jin loses the mission.]
- Fail it.
- You won't get it done.
[This jump has the fate
of the two teams riding on it.]
- Why am I so scared of this?
- You need to think differently about it.
Turn your body a little bit sideways.
[Easily succeeds the jump?]
[What? He fails!]
[It looked like he had it...]
[But his pouch got caught on the bar!]
[Still unable to believe what
just happened.]
[Suk Jin and Gary pass the mission first.]
I thought you had it!
[I need someone to comfort me...]
- I can't believe it.
- You need to let go of your fear.
[Bi-Kwang team needs to find 'Baby'.]
- I've seen them before. We're friends.
- What do you mean, you're friends?
[You seemed so fascinated by them earlier.]
Didn't you see me feeding them?
We're totally friends.
[Suk Jin and Gary have to find 'Harry'.]
Will it recognize its name
if we call out 'Harry'?
Why do you think it's called the captain?
- I bet it's because he's big.
- And he's the boss of the group.
[Even though they have their own guesses,
once they get there...]
[Captain? Keeley? Harry? Baby?]
[Even though they all look the same,
the zookeeper knows their names and habits.]
Look at it chewing on the leaf.
- What if he falls off while sleeping?
- How are we supposed to get a close look?
Harry.
Can we go in there?
Isn't that Harry?
No, that's not the right color of fur.
Harry's fur is darker.
Captain.
Captain?
[Tries calling out the name...]
[But no matter who calls out to them,
all they want to do is just sleep.]
[Could this be Keeley from the picture?]
- The fur looks pretty close.
- Want to take a picture of it?
[Sees a koala bear with a dot
on the chest.]
[Off to check with the zookeeper!]
Excuse me.
Amanda.
Amanda... Keeley.
[Is this Keeley in the picture?]
Sorry, you have failed.
That is not Keeley.
- That's not Keeley.
- Really?
Can you look one more time?
Definitely not Keeley.
- Where is Keeley?
- I can't tell you. You go find him.
Amanda.
We're friends!
I know.
I have the koalas altogether for you.
- There?
- I'm not telling.
I'm not telling?
This is seriously...
things that I used to dream about.
- Dream about what?
- Conversing with someone in English.
[But you barely said a few words.]
- Woo Bin.
- Yes?
Amanda says this isn't Keeley.
Let's go look over that way.
[Decides to look elsewhere in the zoo.]
[Is this... the right place?]
[I don't know.]
[Oh? But...]
Amanda's face is getting red.
[Is her face alerting him to
the koala's location?]
- Come here, Woo Bin.
- Okay.
Did you see Amanda's face?
Amanda is... this is my brother.
- Woo Bin Kim.
- Hello.
He's very handsome.
I'm still not telling.
That Amanda.
I think it's over here somewhere.
Let's look over here.
Because Amanda kept looking
over this way.
I think I'm right about this one.
[Just then, Suk Jin comes up for
confirmation on picture of Harry?]
[It does kind of look like him...]
Sorry, that's not Harry.
This one is 'Sorry'?
- No.
- Sorry?
[Renaming the koala to 'Sorry'?]
[Amanda, we're so sorry...]
Baby... Baby!
[They're still calling out Baby's name.]
[But that koala hasn't moved from
that position for the past 15 minutes.]
Baby!
Baby?
Please look over here just once.
Just once.
Baby?
[Finally shows off its face!]
[Bi-Kwang are convinced that
they've found their Baby.]
You're amazing.
We have to go to the right.
- We have to go to the right.
- Really?
She's over there.
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin are searching for
their Keeley in another area.]
- How did you beat them?
- We have to take a picture.
[They need to check and see if this one
has a dot on its chest...]
I don't know. If this doesn't work,
let's go around to the back.
[I hope that this one is Keeley...]
[Needs the zookeeper to confirm whether
their picture is of Baby or not.]
- Hi, how are you?
- Fine.
- Thank you, and you?
- This is Baby, right?
[It sort of looks like Baby...]
Sorry.
- You have failed the mission.
- Sorry.
How can she be so sure? And
you're not as cool as you think, Jae Suk.
Sorry, but since Amanda turned you down,
you two need to leave.
- We didn't get turned down.
- Yes, you've been turned down, so leave.
Amanda.
[The world star is ruining his image
in so many ways throughout the day.]
Baby?
Look at the long hair around
the ears.
I think it's my koala bear.
The way the ears are shaped...
[What will their hard earned
picture get them?]
Keeley?
[Is it... the real Keeley this time?]
- Yes, that is Keeley.
- Yes!
[They got it correct!]
[Lucky Jae Suk and Woo Bin.]
[How does she know that
just from seeing the picture?]
The ears cover the sides of his nose.
She just said the same thing
that we were thinking of.
The face is very similar.
[Whatever the case, Jae Suk and Woo Bin
successfully pass the mission.]
[The box contains their next mission.]
- There's a surprise in here. Ready?
- Yeah.
[A mission card and
a picture of a license plate?]
[Prepare for tomorrow's adventure
by purchasing food from the market.]
- Bye, Amanda! Thank you.
- Thank you.
Bye, thank you.
Can I take this off now?
I had no idea that it would be
so hot like this.
I was wearing a windbreaker
underneath the costume too.
I'm so dumb.
I can't believe how dumb I can be at times.
I can't believe myself.
Hi, Amanda.
Is this Baby?
[Bi-Kwang are desperately
searching for their Baby.]
[The shape of the ears are similar?]
Yes, you have Baby.
You have succeeded.
[They succeed in finding their Baby!]
Yes, that is our Baby.
- Look at those big beautiful fluffy ears.
- See? I told you.
[The big and fluffy ears are
Baby's unique feature.]
- Thank you.
- Biggest ears out of all the koalas.
- Is there something else?
- Yes, this is for you.
[Prepare for tomorrow's adventure
by purchasing food from the market.]
- Rain, we really are...
- We really are a good team.
[Cruising down the streets of Australia
in the jeep with the top down!]
I can't believe the scenery.
- This is something else.
- This really is something, Woo Bin.
[The wheel is on the other side
in Australia.]
This is so nice.
We really are getting to do
all sorts of things today.
[And what does Woo Bin say to
this situation?]
- This is my first time in this car too.
- It's my first time too.
[Everything today has been a
first time experience for Woo Bin.]
This car calls for a trip down to the lake
or a river to go fishing.
But instead of something outdoorsy,
we have to go to the market in this car.
- We have to go buy food.
- Food.
[I bet the market will shock you too.]
- This is awesome to be driving in this!
- This is so cool!
- This is nice!
- This is a great experience.
- This is what Australia is all about!
- That's right.
I wonder if the team that comes in
at last place will have to cook dinner?
I bet they either have to cook dinner,
or do the dishes.
[An unbelievable privilege
will go to the first place winning team!]
I think we need to come in at least at
second place to avoid having to cook.
[Everyone wants to avoid
having to cook.]
[Next destination- The market.]
[Australian market full of food
and basic household necessities.]
[What will they buy?]
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin are first to arrive.]
- Go pick out whatever you'd like.
- Really?
[A mission card inside the
shopping carts?]
What is all this?
- Salt, and canola oil...
- Let's just go inside.
- This is seriously...
- Let's go.
Are we at the right place?
Hello.
Yes, hello.
Hang on.
First... I think this is some kind
of a bean?
[Everything is in English,
so they're clueless as to what to buy.]
- Can we use a translating app?
- Can we have this translated?
[Rule- Prohibited
from using a translating app.]
[Looks... and looks again,
but everything still looks unfamiliar.]
[Bi-Kwang are next to arrive.]
- You have to choose the right one.
- You do it. I chose earlier.
We picked the middle one earlier,
so let's pick the middle one again.
[Chooses the cart in the middle.]
Zucchini?
- Onion.
- Onion?
- Pork.
[This team's list is also full of
unfamiliar words.]
[Rain is picking up the items
that he thinks is right.]
[But this mission doesn't seem to be
all that easy for the Hollywood star either?]
Excuse me, but is this beef?
Blade steak.
I don't think you'll like it.
- Here's the onion.
- That is beef.
- I got the onion.
- Thank you.
[Rule- Allowed to ask other shoppers.]
High-five!
[Jong Kook and Ha Ha
also start on their mission.]
There are so many delicious looking things.
[Even though the market is full of food...
they need to complete their mission first.]
[Ha Ha's looking for the balsamic vinegar.]
- I can't help you, I'm sorry.
- Balsamic.
[Repeats the word over and over
with his Korean accent.]
[Has no clue what he's trying to say.]
Balsamic.
Bal-sa-mic?
Bal-Sa-mic.
Bal-sa-Mic?
[So close, yet so far...]
Hi.
Where is balsamic sauce?
Balsamic.
- I don't know.
- Balsamic.
Balsamic.
- Balsamic sauce.
- I don't know.
Thank you.
- Balsamic?
- Yes, balsamic!
- Yeah, balsamic. Where is it?
- It's right over here.
- Thank you. You're so kind!
- Ha Ha?
[This Australian guy even knows
Ha Ha's name!]
He's like my Australian uncle.
Balsamic?
[Finally finds the balsamic sauce
thanks to the help of this kind man!]
- Thank you. What's your name?
- Chris.
- Chris. Chris uncle. Thank you.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Fighting.
Jong Kook.
I found the balsamic sauce.
[Gary and Suk Jin are also
busy shopping.]
I can't believe that he's
making me do this.
Why is he making me do this?
[Gary is busy running on his feet while
Big-nose is left pushing the cart around.]
- Comedy?
- Yes, I'm a comedian.
[Finds the milk while amusing
other shoppers.]
[Finds the apricot thanks to the help
of other friendly shoppers!]
- Do you want to double check?
- Yes.
[Ha Ha found the prawns...]
How many?
How do you say, 'enough' in English?
Enough.
(Said in Korean with an accent.)
Thank you.
[Succeeds in getting the shrimp.]
I got the shrimp.
[Bi-Kwang succeeds in getting
the final item on their list.]
- Can you get out of the way?
- Why?
- Out of my way.
- Where are you going?
We're done.
[Bi-Kwang completes their shopping list.]
- Thank you.
[Bi-Kwang succeeds
their mission in first place.]
I'm taking this to the car,
so put this all back.
[Time to head to their dorm
for the night.]
- Tickin... tickin cream?
- Thickening cream? This way.
Tickin... she understood what I said.
Wow, that's so amazing.
This one?
Okay, here it is.
[Big-nose finds the thickening cream!]
- I found the penne, Suk Jin.
- I found the cream.
- You got it?
- Then we're all done!
[Off to the cash register
now that they're done shopping!]
[Checking each of the items
that they've bought.]
- Tickin cream.
- Yes.
And this pepper is... peppercorn?
- I think we're in second place.
- In second place?
[Suk Jin and Gary complete the mission
in second place.]
Help please.
Perch.
I'm not sure, sorry.
She keep smiling at me and
tells me that she doesn't understand.
Perch?
Here's the perch right here!
Nile perch.
[Jae Suk finds the perch.]
Here it is right here.
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin
complete their shopping list.]
- Do you think that we were too quick?
- We're good.
We're in second place right now.
[Off to their final destination of the day-
The dormitory.]
[Who will be the first to arrive?]
We have to keep choosing
whatever is in the middle.
- Wow.
- Bi-Kwang-Cross!
[Palm Beach- A famous beach on the Gold Coast.
One of the most famous beaches in Australia.]
[And their dormitory is
right on the beach.]
[Bi-Kwang is the first team to arrive.]
- Rain!
- Bi-Kwang-Cross!
I told you to just trust me, didn't I?
You are the first ones to arrive,
and as you can see, there are four boxes.
Opens up the first place box.
[Different chests for each place holder?]
[Another mission card instead
of a treasure?]
[You are allowed to pick your roommate,
and the person you want to team up with.]
- What does that mean?
- So this is where we're staying?
[House of extreme luxury.]
- Why aren't you even acting surprised?
- No, it's not that.
Isn't this your first time
at a place like this?
- No, this is just like my house.
- Come on.
How could they have copied it
so perfectly?
How can this be anything like your house?
Look at the amazing view.
Look at all this.
[The amazing view...
has them shout out in shock and awe.]
Wow, this seriously is no joke.
It's a four story house.
[This is their dormitory for the night.]
Welcome.
What?
You're kind of cocky, aren't you?
- You were acting shocked earlier too.
- I'm welcoming you into the home.
It's pretty similar to my home.
- Anyways... we were a great team today.
- We were in perfect sync.
I'm telling you this again,
but you can't betray me, got it?
[Awake or asleep,
must watch out for Giraffe's betrayal.]
[Suk Jin and Gary arrive in second place.]
- Okay, let's go in.
- Of the four elements?
Wow, this place is amazing.
[Lost out on their chance to ask the question
with Gary and Suk Jin's entrance.]
[Automatic gasp in awe at the view.]
I can't believe this!
[While everyone else is
outside looking at the view...]
[This is my chance!]
Of the four elements...
am I the element of 'Fire'?
- Fire?
- Am I the element of fire?
No, you are not.
What was your first element
you asked about?
Wait.
Rain!
What are you doing?
- Did you just ask them?
- I'll tell you what I asked.
- I can't believe you!
- What?
So this is what you're like?
[You may be the Giraffe, but I'm Rain?]
No, I didn't ask him.
- I don't believe you.
- Come on, Kwang Soo.
[Once a friend, and now a foe?]
You asked him if you're
the element of 'wind', right?
I swear to God, I didn't ask that.
I asked if I was the element of 'earth'.
[Kwang Soo's bluff and Rain's lie...]
[They really are the perfect combo.]
But I was told that I'm not.
[Jae Suk and Woo Bin enter in third place.]
This place is amazing.
[So I'm not fire either?]
I thought that this was your house.
[Attempting to ask his question
without Rain knowing.]
- Am I the element of the 'wind'?
- Wind is...
Wind is...
Hey!
You could've just told me!
Wait!
- Seriously!
- Why did you pause!
- Hurry up and ask him.
- I'll ask the question again.
[No choice but to ask the question
in front of Rain.]
Of the four elements...
- Is water...
- Water?
- Water is...
- No, just tell me only.
I'll tell you what I'm told.
You are... not the water.
Since you came in at second place,
you have a question that you may ask.
You can ask if a certain element
exists between the two of you.
And I can answer by either confirming,
or denying that the element exists.
- One, two, three.
- Does the element of 'wind' exist?
The element of the wind does not
exist between the two of you.
I have no idea then.
[Just what is the secret
of these four elements?]
- Is it okay to be wearing our shoes in here?
- Yes, it's okay.
- This place is killer.
- It's amazing, isn't it?
[They feel bad walking around in this
beautiful place with their shoes on.]
- This is a total American drama, isn't it?
- Yeah, it is.
[The same concept as seen in
American dramas?]
- Is it okay to be doing this?
- This is American style.
- Should we swap the teams around?
- Yes.
The team that came in at first place will
have the first chance to swap out their team.
- Do we have to switch out our partners?
- Yes, you must.
[Must switch our their partners.]
You must keep
the four elements in mind.
None of you know what you have
right now.
By switching the teams around,
you may be able to figure out what you have.
[A chance to figure out what their element is
by swapping out their partners.]
[Just what is the final mission
that awaits them?]
I wonder if we have to play the name tag game
without knowing who our partner is?
- Why are you...
- Why do you look so eager?
[Why take such a frightening guess
like that?]
I'm just talking out loud.
Can't I guess out loud like that?
Are you thinking about the
'My Love From Another Star' episode again?
[The ultimate evil, Kkuk, was even more
evil than they had ever imagined.]
I'm sorry, but let me just say
this right now.
Please let me take care of
Yoo Jae Suk myself.
Why must you be the one to
take care of me?
Please let me take care of
Ji Suk Jin myself too.
I must be the one to eliminate him.
[Is he stressed out from having had to
take care of Big-nose all day?]
You did all the work today, Gary.
Stop!
Stop saying that!
And I didn't say this earlier, but
Woo Bin is here to seek his revenge too.
- Revenge against whom?
- He was eliminated so easily the other time.
[Woo Bin was eliminated in one blow
by Kkuk the last time he was on the show.]
[Just the thought of it still makes him
shake his head in shame.]
First place winner must now state who
they'd like to team up with tomorrow.
Since Ji Hoon came in at first place,
he has to be generous and take Suk Jin on.
Ji Hoon needs to experience what
it's like to be teamed up with Suk Jin.
You need to know what that feels like.
- Ji Hoon.
- You need to do it.
If you don't pick me now,
I'm going to pick you when it's my turn.
The person that you choose right now
will also be your roommate for the night.
- Roommate?
- There are four rooms, and you'll share it.
You're going to have to clean the room,
and pick up after him.
Can you get me the towel, Ji Hoon?
[Just the thought of it is enough
to scare him out of his wits.]
There's no way that he can pick Jong Kook.
Then we'll all be finished tomorrow.
Are we going to swap out
our partners again tomorrow?
No, not tomorrow.
[This is their last chance to
swap out their partners.]
- Is Ji Hyo not coming?
- She'll come even if it's just for Gary.
I'll give her a call later.
- She doesn't take your calls, does she?
- No, she doesn't take my calls often.
Okay, I'm going to pick now.
I pick Jong Kook.
[The union of the two ultimate warriors!]
Hey, you guys can't do that!
You need to stop them. That's not right!
We're all dead tomorrow!
No way this can happen.
[Where are you guys going to go?]
I've always wanted to team up with him
and see what it would be like.
[Kkuk looks to be extremely happy
with this turn of events.]
The two strongest guys are together?
[Kkuk and Rain- The ultimate combo.]
Then we will combine our
traitorous instincts together.
[This is how they respond
to the ultimate warrior team?]
- No rules will exist tomorrow.
- I'm going to lay thumbtacks under your bed.
And you guys are going to
share a room together tonight, right?
We'll see if you can sleep tonight.
We're going to take turns to make sure
to keep the two of you awake all night.
We'll take turns and keep you guys awake.
- This is really unfair.
- This is the worst we've had.
[The ultimate team in history-
Kkuk and Rain.]
- They're the Dream Team.
- I feel exhausted already.
Woo Bin's desire to get his revenge is all
gone at the sight of you two right now.
[Woo Bin's desire for revenge has melted away
like melting snow at the sight of them.]
What if Kwang Soo chooses Woo Bin now?
Then we really would be screwed.
[If Kwang Soo chooses Woo Bin now,
there would be no hope for the rest.]
You know what I'm thinking
right now?
If Kwang Soo ends up choosing Woo Bin...
then you two will get the next chance
to make your selection.
Which means, Gary will choose Ha Ha,
and then it'll all be over for me.
[Jae Suk will be stuck with Big-nose.]
It'll be all over for me!
Kim Woo Bin!
[The strongest combo,
and the tallest combo.]
- Go with Ha Ha.
- Come on, Jae Suk.
[Suk Jin chooses Jae Suk.]
[Which leaves Gary and Ha Ha together.]
I feel like I'm going to lose it!
[Inescapable Big-nose roulette.]
- You need to rethink this.
- It's time to start cooking now.
[The long and arduous day
comes to an end.]
[Preparing a relaxing dinner.]
[On the dinner menu-
Australian style steak.]
So that's how you grill it.
- Suk Jin.
- Yeah?
- Can I see your cellphone real quick?
- My phone?
[Why is he asking for
his cellphone all of a sudden?]
Have you decided which room we'll
be using tonight, Kwang Soo?
[Ha Ha and Kwang Soo are planning to
throw Big-nose into the pool.]
[Woo Bin joins in on their prank.]
Have you seen the pool over
here, Suk Jin?
[Big-nose is too busy
sampling the steak he's cooking.]
[Finishes checking out the pool.]
[Just then, Jae Suk joins the fray.]
[Moving the lighting out of the way
so that no one gets hurt.]
[Preparations are complete!]
[Being considerate?
Taking off his shoes and socks.]
This is the least we could do for you.
[All the guys are cheering at
Big-nose's plunge.]
You're in the water already,
so you might as well enjoy it.
[Mr. Capable comes out to
see what's going on.]
Have you ever seen him swim?
He looks so funny when he swims.
- No, it wasn't me.
- These are my pajamas. I've got nothing else.
These are my pajamas.
I don't have any more clothes.
Come over here right now.
I'll give you my clothes.
[Repaying the favor immediately.]
[What do you mean, no?]
[Turns around and tells on Woo Bin too.]
[Woo Bin turns around and runs away!]
[So Jae Suk gets to take his place.]
I had nothing to do with this!
[Jae Suk gets pulled in from
his grilling duties.]
[Come here, Woo Bin.]
[Kkuk goes to get Woo Bin.]
Go get Woo Bin.
Okay, fine.
This is war!
[The guys use steak to
lure Woo Bin in.]
Why did you have to start that joke?
[Just thinking about it gets them angry,
so back into the pool Ha Ha goes!]
Woo Bin!
- I'll go in myself.
- That's no fun!
[Forced dunking that even the heir
himself can't escape from.]
Jung Ji Hoon is the only one
left to go!
[Escaping out of there after witnessing
Woo Bin's forced plunge in the pool.]
[Their next target
is freshly showered Gary.]
[You should've showered later...]
[A domino effect.]
[The only person left dry is Rain!]
I even put lotion on after my shower!
This is Suk Jin's idea, isn't it?
Who's left?
[What was that noise?]
[Water zombies lock their gaze
on their prey.]
[They found me.]
[Their last target, Rain!]
[Rain just changed into his pajamas.]
[Saves his pajamas from their fate first.]
That must be his favorite shirt.
[Eight wet, and excited men having fun.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is Melbourne.
[Their fate depends on these
five elements.]
Once you stand on the dais with
all of these five elements...
[Adventure in Australia Part II-
Find the lost treasure.]