[Turn instant food ingredients
into a sumptuous gourmet feast.]
[A cooking battle like
you've never seen before.]
[You are now the chef in the kitchen.]
[DIY Instant Cooking Battle]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Seoul Gwanhamum Square- 6 AM.]
[Empty street's silent morning.]
[Two men arrive at the nearby bus station.]
[Greeted by the delicious morning scent...]
Ji Suk Jin didn't get much sleep last night.
No, I didn't get much sleep.
- But Jong Kook's already had his breakfast.
- Yes, of course.
- I had some pork for breakfast.
- This early in the morning?
Stop tormenting your mom like that.
She stayed up all night to cook his pork.
- She's stayed up all night to cook his food.
- You need to stop bothering your mom.
What are we doing today?
Your guests for the day are taking
the bus over here right now.
- Why?
- They're on their way here on the bus.
[On the bus?]
Here comes the bus.
[The mysterious bus with
the two male guests on board.]
[Sharp tongued Hong Suk Chun.]
[The crowned prince of dramas, Joo Won.]
[Give Kkuk a big bear hug.]
[Out of my way!]
He hugged me!
He gave me a hug!
Your face is much smaller than on screen.
You have such a small face.
- Is this your first appearance on SBS?
- Yes, it is.
This is my first time being on an SBS show.
- I've never been on an SBS before.
- Seriously?
So this is your first exposure on SBS?
[Running Man will be his first
SBS appearance.]
Joo Won is unbelievably good looking.
- His face is the size of my fists.
- Compare that to his face.
- Why?
- See? His face is bigger.
[A slight exaggeration.
He's just that good looking.]
It would be weird if Joo Won's face
was actually that small.
- His face is tiny though.
- He's younger than I thought he was.
Kwang Soo, have you ever met
Joo Won before?
- I met him at some publicity event before.
- Yes, at some publicity event.
Kwang Soo is good at tagging along
to various events.
I was invited too!
I saw Kwang Soo's latest movie
recently.
I saw his latest movie,
and he really is a great actor.
[Even Giraffe is a true actor.]
I thought he was just a character,
but his acting really impressed me.
Even though Kwang Soo may be a good actor,
who stood out to you the most in looks?
You, Jong Kook.
[Suk Chun has the hots for Jong Kook.]
Jong Kook was getting jealous.
- He fits right in with the rest of us.
- So you like men like Jong Kook?
No, not necessarily.
Out of everyone here, Ji Hyo...
[Me?]
is the only one I'm not interested in.
[What a bewildering and funny comment.]
- Wow, Ji Hyo!
- Why are you even here?
I'm a member of this show.
'I'm a member of this show.'
Did you all see that?
Only he can get away with saying that.
[A very unique man indeed.]
Now that all of you are here,
I will announce the individual teams.
The worst thing for Suk Chun right now
would be to get teamed up with Ji Hyo.
I really don't want that.
I don't want that either!
I wouldn't be happy with that either.
There will be three members per team.
Yoo Jae Suk, Lee Kwang Soo,
and Joo Won will make up a team.
So you put all the best looking people
on one team?
- That's just so obvious.
- It's obvious that's what you did.
Yes, it's obvious that you put
two servants next to Joo Won.
[Servants, Grasshopper and Giraffe
next to Young Master Joo Won.]
Next team is...
Song Ji Hyo...
[It's not me, is it?]
- Gary...
- Ji Hyo!
If you put Suk Chun on that team,
then he's just going to leave.
[Suk Chun will refuse to be on the show
if included on that team?]
and Ji Suk Jin will round out the team.
[Second team-
Song Ji Hyo, Gary and Ji Suk Jin.]
[Final team- Suk Chun, Jong Kook,
and Ha Ha.]
This is a great team!
Today's mission is...
A revolution of taste buds.
You'll each be getting a case.
- Here, take this.
- What color do you like?
[A mysterious map of the world.]
How do we open this?
Seoul's Samchungdong is the
latest trend spot
and it's a place where different cultures
from all around the world are gathered.
There...
you will go find the restaurants that are
indicated on the map
and enjoy the delicious cuisines
from six different culinary backgrounds
and complete the missions
that await you there.
With the success of each of those missions
you will be given a puzzle piece
to complete your puzzle.
The puzzle pieces that you earn will become
very handy to you at your final mission.
You will be given a chance to earn
all your puzzle pieces
so your goal is to earn
as many as possible.
You must now change into your team
uniforms, and get on your way.
[Travel with your teammates to Samchungdong-
Free to choose wherever they want to go.]
So where should we go first?
Let's go eat at
North America and Europe.
Let's start there and eat
our way down.
[Blue Team immediately gets on the move.]
Look at that smile on your face.
[Green Team is all smiles.]
[Orange Team decides to go European style
and heads off to Samchungdong.]
- I come here often on the weekends.
- Samchungdong is so pretty.
- There's a lot of history there.
- Our culture is mixed in there too.
I've seen the guest on the left in a drama
where he wears a mask fighting the Japanese.
Yes, that's our Joo Won.
[The driver immediately recognizes
Joo Won from 'Bridal Mask'.]
As for the taller guest, where was that...
I know I've seen him somewhere...
[Not clear where he's seen Kwang Soo.]
- This guy was on... what was it...
- He wasn't saying it like that.
No, that's what he just said.
[Arrives at the romantic town
of Samchungdong.]
Is this the European restaurant?
This is the place, isn't it?
Yes, this is the right place.
- It's this way.
- Ah, there it is.
Wow, look at all these places.
None of these places are open yet.
[Peaceful streets of Samchungdong
in the early hours.]
[A special treat of being able to experience
the streets while they're still empty.]
There are so many amazing
and beautiful places in our country
but I haven't been able to see
many of those places.
I've always been so disappointed by that,
so I'm very grateful for this opportunity.
Even a simple coffee shop is
so pretty.
All the main streets are very pretty,
but even up these stairs...
I was actually going to buy
one of these places before.
[Can't just pass by without
taking a picture or two.]
Thanks to Gary, I get to experience
the whole European style early this morning.
It's so beautiful here.
Doesn't it feel so weird getting to
walk around here so early in the morning?
I wish I could sit down and write a song
in one of these cafes.
I bet you could get
a song or two out of here.
It's so romantic here.
Perfect for a couple to walk around.
[Cozy little streets meant for
couples in love to stroll around.]
- Sorry, Suk Jin.
- I'll get out of your way.
You two can enjoy the stroll.
- Wow, this place is really nice.
- It's such a beautiful atmosphere.
[Everyone's enamored by
the romance of Samchungdong.]
Yes, if you keep going to the left,
then you'll come up to Chungamdong.
[Sunlit streets of Samchungdong
in crisp summer morning.]
Joo Won's played the role
of being the youngest for so long
and that's why he's so good at
taking care of things like this map.
Unlike this one who still can't do that
even though he's been our youngest.
[Rigid young'un vs Faithful young'un.]
Joo Won just grabbed it
without even having to be told.
But since he's younger than even me,
I should hand down the responsibilities.
So the first person to succeed the mission
will be given the puzzle piece?
So it doesn't matter how many
people try to do the mission?
With you already having experience
of doing a variety show
you really do pick things up
very quickly.
- I think this is the place.
- We're at the right place.
What are they doing?
[What are they doing?]
- It was just so pretty.
- What was pretty?
- The streets and these steps.
- You mean Suk Chun was pretty?
You do look very pretty.
Where are you guys headed?
- We're headed to North America.
- You don't need to tell them that.
- I'm sorry, but that's where we're headed.
- Then we can go together.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
[Cuts in front of them.]
Everything is so beautiful around here.
This is the place.
[Blue Team and Green Team arrive
at the North American restaurant.]
It's hamburgers!
That looks so good!
[A sumptuous feast of
North American style brunch.]
Jong Kook hates things like this.
You are all here to taste
the North American style cuisine.
- They followed us here.
- What? We were here first.
- What did you say?
- They're envious of our team.
We are already like
blood brothers with Joo Won.
- He's going to be called 'Won' from now on.
- Hey!
I told you not to talk to him
in that casual speech yet.
- Why are you talking to him like that?
- This is how he keeps treating me!
- He keeps acting up like this.
- Our team is like a work of art.
Hong Suk said he's going to
set up a small shop for Jong Kook.
I never knew you were so astute
like that!
- That's how close we are already.
- That's right!
Look at how red his face is getting.
It's because I've never been
in this kind of a situation before.
I don't know how I should even react.
- How old are you, Joo Won?
- I'm 28 years old.
Wow, you're so young looking!
You're already 28 years old?
I thought you were only 23 years old.
Look at all the wrinkles on
Kwang Soo's face.
- His face is full of wrinkles already.
- Hey!
Like the title of our race states,
please enjoy all the delicious food first.
- We get to eat first?
- Yes, go ahead and eat.
[Seriously?]
I don't think Joo Won is used to
things like this.
- You're just going to let us eat?
- See?
He's used to having to work for his food.
Even though there are a lot of different
foods you'll be eating throughout the day
but since you're here now, just
enjoy the dishes being offered.
Let's just cut it all up.
[Yum, this is so delicious!]
- This is good.
- Is it good?
- Wow, this is really good.
- It really is delicious.
Look at the sauce on his lips.
I just said, look at the sauce
on his lips.
[His face is now beet red.]
Do you know how I just
reacted to that comment?
[Face frozen in place.]
I can't even say anything
around you guys.
- I really like Suk Chun.
- He's the best.
[Wordlessly concentrating
on eating his food.]
You know that I've been to your place
several times, don't you?
Then don't come anymore.
[What great sense of humor!]
This is why I like Suk Chun so much.
He really is the best.
[While Suk Chun is coldly
cutting off his own customers...]
[Orange Team is enjoying their
European style cuisine in leisure.]
- Comment allez vous?
- Is this a French restaurant?
Yes, welcome to our French restaurant.
If this is a French restaurant, why
is it in a traditional Korean building?
- This is such a beautiful setting.
- It's a collaboration of the two cultures.
Since you guys are here
you will get to taste
some traditional French cuisine.
- French food?
- Sea snails?
Sea snails is what you have
with your beer.
- I'm sorry.
- Wow!
Is that a steak?
Thank you!
Let's eat!
[French style filet mignon glazed with
red wine reduction.]
[Instead of saying 'cheers',
they say, 'Jerky!']
[The tender meat just melts in their mouths.]
Wow, how can it be this delicious?
Wow, this is great!
The sauce is amazing.
[The sauce that accompanies the meat
is the essence of this dish.]
Wow, this is so delicious.
It's like heaven in my mouth.
We've cleaned our plate.
[No need to wash the dish,
since it's already been licked clean.]
French cuisine is...
'Ul-lari, kol-lari.'
(A funny saying in Korean with a twist.)
It just amazed me,
and overtook my senses.
Here's how I'd like to describe the dish.
'Oh-teu, Ku-tuire.'
- That's how I'd like to describe it.
- What does that mean?
I don't know either.
'Oh-teu, Ku-tuire.'
[Time to get their reaction on
their North American styled brunch.]
I really like these types of foods.
I prefer breads and pastas over rice dishes.
- That's what I prefer too.
- But you love strong fermented soybean stew.
Wow, you guys are all
driving me crazy.
Describe your impression of the dish,
and we'll get started on your mission.
Solid.
That's not the right way to express it.
We'll let the other team go first.
[Jong Kook's impression of the dish.]
Let's see... A taste of North America
in the midst of Korean culture?
Yeah, that's the way to describe it.
Okay, we'll go next.
It's Joo Won's turn.
Let's see...
['Let's see' is all of a sudden
the newest catchphrase.]
As if my life has been missing something...
What are you doing!
[Since it's still morning, it deserves
a morning drama-esque reaction.]
This is the reaction
you give in the mornings.
I feel as if I've been reborn
with this brunch experience.
[A dual set of morning drama reactions.]
I will now explain the mission to everyone.
The mission that all of you
will be participating in here will be...
is toast catching.
- We have to catch the toast?
- Do you see the toaster in front of you?
Toasted bread will
jump out of the toaster slot.
You guys come up with the weirdest ideas.
When the toast pops out of the toaster,
you have to catch the toast with your mouth.
[Even if just one person on the team succeeds
in catching the toast, then it's a pass.]
- It actually sounds like fun.
- Respect.
- You guys are something else.
- It's a fun idea.
- What do you think, Joo Won? You like it?
- This is so much better than 2 Days 1 Night.
[I was just kidding!]
[Blue Team takes the first turn
at toast catching.]
Get ready, set...
The toast can pop up at any time.
[The toast will pop at the same time.]
You're about to start drooling.
[Toasts pops up at the speed of a bullet.]
[A full frontal face attack
when they're least expecting it.]
- That's hard.
- I can't believe how hard that popped up!
I can't believe I just got slapped
in the face by a slice of bread.
- Just use the same slice instead of wasting.
- Yes, we can just do that.
- But they're all mixed up now.
- Who cares? Just reuse them.
It just hit him on his nose.
That bread hit Kwang Soo on his nose.
- Come on, we can do this.
- We can do this, Joo Won.
Let's just succeed the mission,
and head out to our next location.
Okay, it can pop up at any time.
What are you doing?
[Took a bite of the toast while waiting.]
- Look at how serious Joo Won is taking this.
- Sorry.
[The youngest of the team is focused
and determined to succeed his mission.]
Look at how focused he is.
Ready.
[The toast landed on his cheek!]
[Hardworking Joo Won is shattering
his cool image.]
Think about your image.
You're an actor!
That doesn't count, right?
Since I used my shoulder?
Yes, it counts.
Yes, that should count
since he didn't use his hands.
[While Joo Won is busy wrestling
the toast with his mouth...]
[There's another person fighting
with his level of patience.]
I don't think you're going to get it.
I'm so annoyed
and I think I'm going to lose it.
Ugh, I'm so annoyed!
[Gary's mission is to move ten beans over
with the use of his chopsticks.]
Okay, you're doing it!
You can do this!
- You're doing it!
- Even my sphincter is tightening up.
My fingers are cramping up.
My fingers are seriously about to cramp up!
[Move ten beans, pop open a soda can, and
fold a paper airplane within two minutes.]
[Stress!]
Amazing.
[After having swapped their roles,
Blank Ji shows off her amazing talent.]
[Falls in love with her all over again.]
- Got it!
- Okay.
[Blank Ji succeeds her portion
of the mission at lightning speed.]
What are you doing? Hurry!
Hurry up and open it!
[Opening up the can is the
easiest portion of the mission...]
[But putting Big-nose on the mission...]
Turn it around and use your thumb!
[Passes the second course!]
[Now must fold and
make the paper airplane fly.]
I have to make this perfectly.
Just fold it however.
It doesn't have to be perfect.
- Gary, it just has to fly!
- But I have to get it perfectly!
[Only five seconds left on the clock!]
Two, one!
Pass!
[Orange Team succeeds
their European mission.]
I fell in love with you all over again.
You looked so domestic.
Since you succeeded your mission,
you win your first piece of the puzzle.
[Orange Team wins the European puzzle.]
- It fits perfectly.
- We got it.
Asia, Africa, North America...
[The more puzzle pieces they collect,
more advantageous it'll be for them.]
[North American Teams are still busy
trying to pass their toast mission.]
[It goes in... and falls back out.]
- It actually went in!
- But you can't have it fall back out.
You have to bite down on it.
That's something that I'm familiar with.
Having it fall back out of your mouth.
Listen to this man.
[Yoo Hyuk acts out like a brat at
the opposing team's toast mission failure.]
Can I do it from this position?
No kidding.
Can we do it like that?
Joo Won knows all sorts of tricks.
- He's good at this game stuff.
- I see now why he was on a variety show.
He's really good.
He's really earnest about it.
Ready, set, go!
- Why would you close your eyes?
- You fool!
It was right over your face,
but why would your close your eyes?
- Why did you close your eyes?
- Because I got scared.
Yeah, instead of using your shoulder,
just have it land right on your face.
[Jae Suk also attempts a new position.]
[Will he get it?]
[It just grazes his tongue!]
- That position might work!
- He almost had it!
This is the perfect position.
- How did you position yourself again?
- I think I was positioned like this.
[A variety of different poses.]
You guys look like SES.
Looking at how we're positioned
with our mouths hanging open...
Ready, set, go!
[Lands on his cheek once again!]
[But...]
Joo Won, you look like your character
from 'Good Doctor' all over again.
You look like your 'Good Doctor'
character again.
You weren't even close.
[Why are you looking so disappointed?]
Did you see how close I got?
Set, go!
[Back to Green Team's turn.]
You might as well have
picked it up with your hand.
Why didn't you just pick it up
with your fingers instead?
- Just use your fingers instead then.
- I used my shoulders like this.
I just used my shoulder like this.
This is the first time in four years that
I laughed at something Kwang Soo said.
- What? I always make you laugh.
- That was too funny.
[Next up is, Ha Ha.]
Is that what I looked like?
So that's what I looked like.
[Yoo-Brat is especially acting up today.]
[Oh my goodness!]
Kim Jong Kook is the best!
[The toast is caught!]
[Monstrous Mr. Capable!]
[Like a tiger pouncing on its prey!]
- How could you...
- Wow, Kim Jong Kook.
I think this is why I think
Jong Kook is the most attractive.
[Green Team wins
the North American puzzle piece.]
- Bye!
- Bye, North America!
- We love it!
- Bye!
- Let's go get some soup.
- Okay, let's go.
Let's go for the soup too.
I'm going to make them wear their soup.
[Blue Team gives up on North America
and also goes for the soup.]
[Orange Team is headed off
to the South American destination.]
Wow, it's so nice here.
[Europe has nothing on this
lovely town of Samchungdong.]
- This place has everything.
- There's a jewelry store.
Gary, aren't you going to
buy me a diamond ring?
I'd need some sort of a promise
before I buy you a diamond ring.
I'd need the diamond ring first
before I make you any sort of a promise.
Why am I even here?
- This really is nice.
- Let's go to South America.
Why don't you take a picture
in front of that red storefront?
- Suk Jin, get in on the picture.
- Take the picture with us.
One, two, three.
[Burst out in laughter after
looking at the picture.]
- I really look like a fool.
- He only has his eyes on Ji Hyo.
[I only have my eyes on Ji Hyo.]
What's that?
- Isn't it Yoo Gwan Soon?
- Wow, it's Lady Yoo Gwan Soon.
- And that's Ahn Chang Ho.
- Wow, that's an amazing drawing.
[Murals of historically famous figures
drawn by local artists.]
- Ji Hyo and Gary.
- This one?
- He has the pepero cookie in his mouth.
- You guys should assume the same pose.
I'll take a picture of you guys
in that same pose.
Is this good?
- Yeah, that's perfect.
- Gary, did you not shave today?
Doesn't it make me look tough?
Okay, that's good.
Hold it.
[Making memories of their own
in the streets of Samchungdong.]
[May the Monday Couple last forever-
Summer 2014.]
What kind of cuisine
is South American food?
- Salad?
- Nachos!
[Nacho and chili fries-
The king of Mexican cuisine.]
- It's really good.
- Wow, this is so good.
- Hello!
- Suk Chun's here.
- It's so nice walking around the streets.
- Isn't it so nice?
[They're all in love with the
charm of Samchungdong streets.]
It's driving me nuts having to
be with these two.
Having you around us is
driving me nuts.
[But Suk Chun really doesn't feel
any attraction towards Ji Hyo?]
I normally don't like girls
who look like her.
We will now start
the South American mission.
It's called, 'I can hear your heart',
and you have three minutes on the clock.
The mission is a success
if even just one of you
can get your heartbeat up above
160 beats per minute.
- How are we going to do that?
- You can either scream at each other...
or you can make each other's hearts
flutter or excite one another.
You can also make each other angry,
or just jump around to get your heart beating.
- Anything is allowed in this game.
- How about kissing?
You can do whatever you'd like.
Yes, exercise is allowed as well.
[Stay tuned- Monday Couple's true feelings
will soon be revealed.]
- Your team was the first to arrive,
- Who has the highest heart rate right now?
Currently, Ji Suk Jin is at 102.
Song Ji Hyo is at 80.
And lastly, Gary is at 77.
- You must have a very cold heart.
- Wait, give us a minute.
- Gary is currently at 80.
- It's gone up by three.
Song Ji Hyo is at 78.
Her heart rate dropped.
[Ji Hyo's heart rate drops.]
- You are given three minutes on the clock.
- This is like the truth game.
[Monday Couple attempts to make each other's
hearts race through this game of truth.]
- This is the truth game for you two.
- Ask each other some questions.
[Monday Couple five years in the making...
What do they really feel for each other?]
[Three minutes on the clock-
I can hear your heart.]
Have you ever really liked me
even for one single moment?
Even for one single moment?
Even if it was just for a mere second?
- I have felt attracted to you in the past.
- That's practically the same thing.
- How does that make you feel, Gary?
- If I can be of some help?
Gary has told me in the past that
he really was interested in Ji Hyo.
- That's for real.
- I have felt feelings for you.
- Your turn to ask the question, Ji Hyo.
- Have you...
ever looked at me as a woman before?
- We all know the answer to that question.
- I'd know if he was lying.
I have.
[An out of nowhere confession
from this bystander.]
Yes, I have looked at you as a
woman before.
[I have looked at you as a woman before...]
[These two are looking more bashful...]
There's been a time...
- Mine's gone up to 120.
- Why is Suk Jin's heart rate going up?
Just looking at these two
is making my heart start to race.
- So you've looked at me as a woman before?
- Yes, I have.
If I had confessed my feelings for you then,
would you have accepted it?
Just sit still!
I want to concentrate.
- I would've ran to you like the wind.
- You're being honest with me, right?
The last time Big Bang was on the show...
[The day the Monday Couple shocked
their fans all over the world...]
Did you kiss me intentionally?
I've wanted to kiss you all morning.
You know those days when you wake up
wanting to kiss that one special person?
- And that was my perfect opportunity.
- Really?
- It wasn't me that did it...
- Ji Hyo's heart rate is increasing.
It wasn't me that did it,
but it was my heart that did it.
- Wow, that's so cool.
- It wasn't him, but it was his heart.
- Do the 5cm test.
- Let's see if it works.
We're just closing in
just for the sake of winning this game.
[Closer...]
- Don't touch!
- That's enough, Gary!
Just touch your nose.
Just let your noses touch.
[Time over!]
Gary's heart rate went up to 128,
and Song Ji Hyo to 115.
- We'll play a truth game of our own.
- But you have felt attracted to me?
Of course, I have.
[Me too, Ji Hyo...]
[If that doesn't get the job done,
then it's time to switch up the game plan!]
[Gives up on making each other excited,
and it's onto the traditional method!]
[Working hard to get his heart rate up!]
Get up!
[Time over]
[Did his heart rate surpass the 160 mark?]
[176- A definite success!]
We should've done this right
from the start!
Why did you have to exploit our love?
[Coach Kkuk steps in to train his members.]
[Kicking his legs back automatically.]
- You're such a cute jumper.
- That's so cute.
Kick your knees higher.
[His heart his bouncing-
Coach Kkuk's hard training.]
We're stopping because I think
this is getting too dangerous.
- How high is it?
- It's at 182.
[Green Team succeeds by a mile!]
Suk Chun.
I guess you and I are definitely older.
You can put the puzzle piece in
the puzzle that you have in the case.
[Both teams win
the South American puzzle piece.]
- How many do you have?
- We have two.
Okay, South America.
[North and South America-
Green Team completes America portion.]
- Let's go to Asia now.
- Okay.
[At the same time.]
- It's much nicer when you succeed.
- Yes, it's much better.
We couldn't have done it without you, Joo Won.
- Where should we go this time?
- Let's go to Asia.
Okay, let's go to Asia.
- Samchungdong really is nice.
- Yes, and it's very peaceful.
[More they see, the more in love they
are with the streets of Samchungdong.]
Joo Won, isn't this town so pretty?
- Bye!
- See you later!
- I want to go on a date to a place like this.
- That's what we're doing right now.
Okay, let's go out on a date.
We've just been proven not to
have any feelings for each other.
No, we're even holding hands
and are out on a date right now.
- Want me to leave you guys alone?
- No, you really are attractive.
- You're pretty.
- I really do think that you're attractive.
Are you confessing your feelings for
each other after all these years?
Even though I've told you this before,
you're really attractive when you're on stage.
When you're singing on stage with your mic
with your stomach sticking out.
You're always pretty, Ji Hyo.
Finally confessing your feelings for
each other after four long years.
I really do think that you're pretty, Ji Hyo.
Why are you leaning into my arms?
It's because we're such good friends.
And we're in this beautiful town
of Samchungong.
The fact that three men are walking together
in the rain like this...
It really is a beautiful thing.
Do you know that the two of you are
poking me with your umbrellas right now?
That's because you're so tall.
It's not mine or Joo Won's fault.
Wow, this is nice.
What are you thinking about, Joo Won?
It's always been a dream of mine to open
a coffee shop around a place like this.
- Really?
- Yes.
- That's a nice dream.
- I really love coffee.
- You like coffee?
- Yes.
I like coffee too.
- I think this is the place.
- Here?
[Finally arrives at the Asian restaurant.]
Asia.
You have to stop by the Asian place.
- Is it rice noodles?
- But they're all different.
[Today is an all you can eat buffet
of different cuisines from worldwide.]
Try this one.
- Hello.
- You guys must be here to lose again.
- Sorry, but you keep getting in our path.
Sorry, but we were here first.
- It's rice noodles.
- Rice noodles?
[Full of oriental flavors...
enough to get your taste buds going.]
[Time to hand out the mission
for the Asian puzzle piece.]
- This is a bowl of noodles.
- What do we do with this?
What is this?
The mission you'll be doing here is called,
'Rice noodle squad.'
You have to stick ten strands of noodles
on one member's face...
Then we have to shoot it off
with the water gun?
[Shoot off the noodle strands
with the water gun.]
Don't stick it on my face
like it's a foregone conclusion.
If we have to do this anyways,
then how about we do this?
Stand the two people up against the wall,
and see who can get them all off the fastest.
[Both teams to go at the same time
to see who can be the first to win.]
- I bet we'll beat you guys.
- Fine, let's do it.
Okay, let's do it.
- Let's pick the member for each other.
- We pick Suk Chun.
- We'll go with Suk Chun.
[Rice noodle wallpaper- Suk Chun.]
[Suk Chun vs Kwang Soo.]
Suk Chun, you really are...
I feel like I've seen you on
'Pirates of the Caribbean.'
[Octopus face and Rice noodle face.]
- Okay, Kwang Soo's ready.
- We have to do this fast.
My water gun is too weak!
[Rice noodle sniper.]
[Water gun face massage.]
[Green Team wins!]
[Sticky rice noodle Band-Aid
on Kwang Soo's face.]
That was too easy of a win.
[Green Teams beats the Blue Team again
and takes the puzzle piece for Asia.]
Then is the puzzle piece to Asia gone?
- Since this was a competition...
- But we worked really hard.
The puzzle piece should be closed out
for Asia.
But we will give you guys one
more chance to win the puzzle piece.
- Give us one more chance.
- Okay.
- If we lose this time, then we'll walk away.
- Bow down to us in gratitude.
[Yoo Hyuk is the only one too proud
to beg for their chance.]
[His darn pride.]
Do you have a back problem?
What's wrong with you?
[Yoo Hyuk is the only one
made to do it again.]
[Bows down with Kwang Soo's help.]
That was my pride!
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
[Green Team leaves after having
insulted the Blue Team.]
Kwang Soo, we're going to Africa next,
so bring this with you to Africa.
- So bring it with you, okay?
- Yes, Sir.
Ugh, I'm so angry right now.
[Meanwhile, Gary is busy trying
his hand at the toast challenge.]
[Finally bites down
after 30 minutes of trying.]
Okay, success.
[Random Mr. Capable's success.]
I almost didn't make it back home tonight.
I really wasn't going to go home.
We did it.
I feel so much better now.
[A man of persistence, Kang Gary.]
We just got a text.
We got a text.
[A text message is sent to all
three teams.]
A special shop where you can win
the gold puzzle piece has just opened.
Please go to 'H' restaurant in
Samchungdong.
So this is a special mission, right?
We have to win this puzzle piece.
[The identity of the gold puzzle piece
still remains a mystery to all the members.]
Okay, let's go.
[The puzzle piece that will give them an
unbelievable advantage at the final mission!]
Hello!
This place truly is very beautiful.
- Look, the flag is gold.
- This is the place.
I think we're the first ones here, right?
Here it is.
[Meet each other again.]
Seriously.
Give them their case.
[What's with the expression?]
- You guys were so happy earlier.
- Happy about what?
Okay, everyone bow down.
What a joke.
[As long as you're in a Korean restaurant,
time to taste some Korean cuisine.]
[Kalgguksu with a variety of toppings...]
[and handmade giant dumplings.]
These are all my favorite foods.
- This kimchi is amazing.
- Napa cabbage is really cheap right now.
Since the farmers works so hard for us,
you have to consume a lot of napa cabbage.
You have to eat a lot of onions
and napa cabbage.
- We haven't seen you guys all day!
- I want some kalgguksu too.
It's really good.
Thank you for the delicious food.
[Please enjoy your meal.]
[Comforting, and hearty hot broth.]
How many puzzle pieces
have you all gained so far?
- Three.
- Three?
- Asia, North and South America.
- Asia, North and South America?
Europe, North and South America.
- Okay.
Europe, North America, and Asia.
- You guys got the North American piece?
- Yes.
[But the Blue Team failed
the toast mission...]
[The puzzle piece really is there?]
They switched the case on us!
- No, this is ours.
- No, we didn't.
[The names on the puzzle
definitely are the Blue Team...]
[What really happened?]
[After having succeeded
the insulting Asian mission...]
- That's not ours.
- This isn't ours?
But they left this behind.
[The case that the Green Team left behind
for them to bring...]
[Without even a moment's hesitation,
they steal a puzzle piece...]
- Why would they leave it behind?
- Let's just take one.
[Takes the North American puzzle piece
and sticks it onto their own puzzle...]
We pretty much succeeded
the North American mission ourselves.
Yes, we did.
[Thus, the North American puzzle piece
becomes Blue Team's property...]
- Hand it over.
- This has our names on it.
- What are you talking about?
- You guys took our puzzle piece.
Kwang Soo, your mouth is hanging open.
- It's because he's eating.
- Your mouth is hanging open right now.
That means that you're lying,
so hand it over.
Come on, just hand it over.
The PD's can tell us if you're lying.
We don't know,
so you guys take care of it.
- Jong Kook will take care of it.
- We didn't see it, so we don't know.
The most important thing is,
we all have to get to the final location.
But your puzzle pieces will play
a crucial role at the final mission.
It's extremely important.
I told you that you can earn your golden
puzzle piece at this location, right?
[And the big power player...]
[A pure gold puzzle piece.]
There are two of these pure gold
puzzle pieces to be won in this location.
[Only two teams can win
the gold puzzle piece.]
Okay, let's get started.
- You seem very motivated.
- Yes, of course.
- We're done eating.
- The mission you'll be doing here...
Is 'Flipper jump roping.'
You'll enter the swinging jump rope one by one
after donning on your flippers.
The counting will begin once all the
members have entered the jump rope
and must jump 20 times.
I used to play jump rope all the time with
the girls when I was in elementary school.
- This is my game.
- Okay.
I won't tell you this again,
but take good care of your own cases.
You have to take care of your own cases.
The case is your responsibility...
I'm telling you this right now,
but at one point while you're walking...
you're going to find yourself lying flat
on your back with your case in your hands.
[Nothing but laughter comes out of his mouth
from the fear of what's to come.]
- Now let's go out and start the mission.
- Let's go!
[Time to go outside and attempt the mission
to earn the gold puzzle piece.]
Give me back our North America.
Just leave it.
It's better to just flip them onto their backs
when they're least expecting it.
They're going to be out flat on their backs
while doing the jump rope mission.
It's because I know what that feels like,
that I feel even more afraid.
Okay, let's do this.
Let's get it done on our first try.
[Blue Team to go first.]
- Who wants to go first?
- I'll go in the middle.
- Then Joo Won go first.
- Okay, let's get started.
['Flipper jump rope'- Blue Team.]
[First jumper- Joo Won.]
Your turn, Kwang Soo.
You have to get in right now,
or Joo Won will die!
- Wait.
- Hurry up and get in there!
Get in!
[As soon as he jumps in... he fails.]
- This is really hard!
- Are you kidding me!
[The nicest youngest member helps
the loser older member get up.]
[On the other hand, the oldest member
chastises the middle member.]
When the rope smacks down on the ground,
that's when you jump in!
[Yoo Hyuk's mouth is busier
than the moving jump rope.]
You're doing good though, Joo Won.
- We can do this.
- Joo Won's really good.
[Look at what's going on here.]
[While Blue Team's attention
is diverted elsewhere...]
[Ha Ha is busy stealing their puzzle piece.]
- Look at what a cute jumper he is.
- Suk Chun is going to exhaust himself.
- Take care of your own case.
- What are you doing?
- What did you just do?
- I brought it back to you guys.
You're in trouble if you took our
North America away from us.
[Did their North America disappear?]
[All the puzzle pieces are gone.]
We just need one more puzzle piece.
[The back and forth thievery.]
[Green Team's turn at the challenge.]
Why are you holding onto your case?
He's afraid we're going to take it.
That's because he was holding
onto the case.
[The Tiger kept the case protected,
but lost his face in his attempt.]
[But he still won't let the case
out of his possession.]
[But thanks to that attempt, we
witnessed some good slapstick comedy.]
Having him of all people fall down
is what made it so funny.
I can't let this out of my sight though.
We're going to go in from here.
[Orange Team's turn at the challenge.]
Go in when the rope touches ground?
Gary's really good.
[Big-nose's turn.]
[Never changing Big-nose.]
You're really killing my flow!
Gary just said that he's killing his flow.
I can't have him doing that
every single time.
He couldn't say it any other way,
so he says he killed his flow.
- He should've at least jumped in there.
- That was the best expression.
- You should've at least gotten in there.
- I'll go in first.
[Blue Team's second attempt.]
Joo Won's really good!
[Joo Won easily succeeds
jumping into the fray.]
[Even Yoo Hyuk succeeds at
jumping into the moving jump rope.]
[Now it's the black hole, Kwang Soo's turn.]
Hurry up and jump in!
[Even Kwang Soo succeeds!
Time to start counting!]
Five, six, seven...
[Perfectly in sync.]
[Win the gold puzzle piece
by jumping 20 times.]
[Doesn't let the interference get to them,
and just continues to jump.]
[20 jumps- Succeeds!]
[Blue Team succeeds the flipper
jump rope in first place.]
This was pure determination.
Congratulations.
[Blue Team earns the first puzzle piece.]
[This is what victory tastes like!]
[Onto the final location after having
completed the tasting tour.]
[A university campus in the city of Seoul.]
[It's already lunch time on this street
bustling with youth and vigor.]
- Did you all enjoy your food today?
- Yes.
It's now time for your final mission.
The final mission is,
'Fusion instant cooking battle.'
[DIY Fusion Instant Cooking Battle.]
[Do it yourself-
Cook the dishes yourselves.]
- We have to use a variety of ingredients.
- But Suk Chun's a chef.
[Restaurant owner, Suk Chun,
could be at an advantage?]
You got to taste the cuisine from all around
the world during your missions today.
[The different cuisines from all around
the world that they got to taste...]
You have to utilize that experience
to cook a dish yourself
and earn the highest level of stars
in order to win the cooking battle.
You will only be using instant and frozen
ingredients during this battle.
- No other ingredients will be allowed.
- This is my specialty.
There are four coolers containing
your ingredients in front of you.
They're filled with easily obtainable
instant and frozen ingredients.
You all earned your share of puzzle pieces
throughout the day, right?
You can exchange one puzzle piece
for one of these ingredients.
You can only get the ingredient from
the same colored cooler as your puzzle piece
and exchange it for only one ingredient.
The two teams with
the gold Korean puzzle piece...
Those teams will be allowed to exchange
that piece for any ingredient of your choice.
- Please open all the coolers.
- All of them?
Yes, open all of them.
[African mission- Blue Team and Orange Team.]
- For South America...
- These really are all frozen.
- How about the dumplings?
- Noodles would be good.
[Blue Team with four ingredients-
Asia, Europe, Africa, Special ingredient.]
[Must be an ingredient with diverse
possibility to create a fusion dish.]
- Let's go with these ingredients.
- I don't even know how to get started.
[Unsure of how to create a dish
out of these instant ingredients.]
The most important thing is how well
these ingredients will work together.
[The key is to choose ingredients
that will complement each other.]
[Blue Team completes
their selection process.]
[Blue Team- Roasted dumplings,
stir-fried rice chicken, and udon.]
- It's stir-fried rice.
- They just chose by random.
Ji Suk Jin's team currently has Europe,
South-North America, and Africa.
[Can choose four ingredients.]
This is a really tough decision.
I have no idea what to pick.
I don't know how to use them together.
How about donkatsu?
Maybe use it with the shrimp?
- What do you think about these?
- We can make some kebobs?
Want to make kebobs?
What are we going to do with that?
I don't think chocolates will work.
[The two men insist on choosing
the chocolate ice cream.]
He keeps wanting to use
the ice cream in the cooking!
- You're driving me nuts!
- I think it'll be good!
Boil the ice cream and eat it like soup.
- You shouldn't tell them anything.
- What are you thinking?
[Just what did they have to eat
during their tour?]
[Orange Team- Donkatsu, shrimp,
chocolate, and spaghetti.]
You can choose from any of the coolers
except for Africa.
Let's be smart about our decisions.
How about mincing up the steak
and use it as pizza topping?
[Steak pizza topping?]
[Use the sauce from the chili chicken
as the spice ingredient?]
Or how about putting some waffles
in the bone soup?
[Waffles and beef bone soup?]
[Fusion makjang drama.]
[Green Team- Chili chicken, steak,
ddeokbokki, and spaghetti.]
These are all ingredients which can be
easily attained from any stores around town.
You may now go to your station at
the cooking site and start your cooking.
[DIY Instant Cooking Battle- Start.]
[Countless number of specialties
found throughout Samchungdong...]
[Our taste buds still remember the flavors.]
[With only the memory of the taste,
and the instant ingredients...]
[They must create a new fusion dish.]
The cooking battle will now start.
Since this is an instant ingredient battle,
you will not be given much time.
- You will have exactly 30 minutes.
- Okay.
[Only the ingredients chosen to be used,
but spices of all sorts will be provided.]
Set, go!
[Blue Team- Roasted dumplings,
fried rice, udon, and chicken.]
[The main feature of this dish
will be the chicken.]
- Should I cook this.
- If we cook it now, it'll get soggy.
[A special panel of judges
will be here to judge their dishes.]
We should make the sauce and
the broth we need to use first.
[Time to make the sauce which will
accompany the feature ingredient.]
We have to make the sauce first.
- We should save the udon soup.
- This is going to be our secret ingredient.
This was a very smart decision.
- This was a great choice.
- How are we going to melt the fried rice?
We can flatten it out on the frying pan,
and use it like burnt crispy rice.
Then lay the chicken on top.
Get what I'm saying?
Joo Won just came up with a great idea.
Go wash the onion and the scallions.
[All of a sudden, Kwang Soo gets
demoted to kitchen assistant position?]
Just do as you're told and wash
an onion and a couple of the scallions.
[Do this for the next three years,
and we'll let you cook something too.]
- Are we going to use these separately?
- No, we have to use them all together.
[Trying to figure out how to
use all the ingredients together.]
- We can't use too much oil.
- Should I cut these up?
What do you want me to do next, Ji Hyo?
- The meat looks really fresh.
- Want me to cut this up too?
The way I want to do it is,
instead of using huge pieces...
[Chef Blank Ji is showing them
how she wants the pieces skewered.]
Once a small piece like this is on,
them cut the shrimp into small pieces too
and skewer that on next,
and alternate between the two ingredients.
- How about the spaghetti?
- We'll wrap the spaghetti in there too.
Then we'll melt the chocolate on the dish,
and only dip half the skewer in there.
[Chef Gary dumps the bag of cocktail shrimp
in the pot of cold water.]
You're putting that in there
before the water's even boiling?
- You have to wait until the water boils.
- No, that doesn't matter.
- Is this how you cook your ramen?
- Yes.
This is going to start boiling anyways.
The chocolate will be in a pretty dish,
and used as a dipping sauce.
- Have you ever melted chocolate before?
- No, I've never done that before.
- That's going to melt really fast.
- Do you think this is a good idea?
- Of course!
- Sure, that's basically what fondue is.
Isn't fondue a pot of melted cheese?
[Melting the chocolate pieces
like a pot of melted cheese fondue.]
Suk Chun!
- Suk Chun.
- What?
Have you ever melted chocolate before?
- Why?
- I was just curious.
- You have to melt it in a water bath.
- In a water bath?
- You can't do it like this.
- Why not?
- Don't you know what 'water bath' means?
- In medium heat?
[Totally amateur Chef Gary.]
Putting this in a bath of
hot water is what that means.
- Thanks, Suk Chun.
- I was just going to use medium heat.
You didn't know that?
[Chocolate is saved thanks to
a tip from Chef Suk Chun.]
[It's melting! About to
become a pot of chocolate fondue.]
Thanks goodness for Suk Chun.
[Green Team- Chili chicken, steak,
spaghetti, and ddeokbokki.]
Suk Chun, what are we making?
- We're going to make tri colored dumplings.
- Tri colored dumplings?
We're going to make dumplings.
[Chef Hong starts off by
dicing up the steaks.]
Are we going to fry it?
[Cutting it into thin slices.]
Look at the way he's slicing that.
It's the thin Italian style.
[A master at thinly slicing the garlic.]
['Love and attention to detail is
the key ingredient to cooking'- Chef Hong.]
[Chef Kiddo has the onion dicing task.]
We don't have much time.
- What about the wrapper?
- Wrapper?
- You have to make the wrapper.
- What do you think?
- You know my skill level.
- You're amazing, Suk Chun.
[Green Team is busy making the filling
for their tri colored dumplings.]
I can tell that this is going to be special.
[Seven out of thirty minutes
have already passed.]
- What are you doing right now, Joo Won?
- Cooking the dumplings.
- You don't think it'll be too greasy?
- But we can't just put it in there.
Yes, you're right.
You do what you think is right.
- Make sure to cook it through.
- We're cooking the chicken too, right?
[A fusion of chicken and dumplings
for the Blue Team.]
We don't have to cook
all the dumplings, right?
Just cook them all for now,
and we'll just eat the leftovers.
[The key to making good dumplings-
Adjusting it to the right heat level.]
[Flips it, and flips it again.]
- You're a good cook, Joo Won.
- He's a very patient cook.
[A master at even roasting the dumplings.
A new star chef is born.]
The sauce is the key.
[Chef Yoo is in charge of making the sauce.]
It's over for us if we ruin the sauce.
[1. Use the soup base that comes
in the frozen udon pack.]
[The soup base is their secret ingredient.]
The thing I'm worried about is... you
think we need the hot pepper paste in it?
Using just this is going to be weird.
[2- Two tablespoons of hot pepper paste.]
[How does his sauce taste?]
- The sauce isn't bad.
- Seriously?
You can't just dip your finger in there.
But that's what most people do.
- What's that?
- Sesame oil.
[3- One tablespoon of sesame oil.]
- Go wait outside.
- Outside where?
I don't want anyone to know
the secret to my sauce.
[No one knows the secret to his sauce.]
How are we going to make
the burnt crispy rice?
[Chef Yoo Hyuk tests the sauce
to see how it tastes.]
- Is it good?
- Try it.
[Yeah, that's the stuff!]
- This is better than my mom's sauce.
- I just want this with a bowl of noodles.
[The birth of Chef Yoo's secret sauce.]
- Ouch, that's hot.
- Be careful, Ji Hyo.
- I think the shrimp is done.
[Even the cocktail shrimp is done cooking.]
One piece of the scallion...
- The scallion is breaking.
- No, you have to skewer it like this.
[The endless possibilities of kebobs.]
Now the shrimp.
Skewer it on like this?
- Don't you think that'll look prettier?
- I think cutting it would be better.
Cutting it too small wouldn't be good either.
Let's just keep the shape of it.
Isn't it pretty?
What do you think, Gary?
[It's a very pretty presentation!]
- What about when you wrap the pasta?
- Shouldn't we cook the scallion first?
No, I don't think we need to
cook the scallion.
- This is starting to look good.
- How about wrapping it with the scallion?
With the scallion?
I think we should just fry it like this.
I think we can just fry it like that too.
But we can't do anything about that.
Should we stick it together
with sticky grains of rice?
How about using rice as the glue?
[What will become of their kebobs?]
[Chef Hong is still busy mincing the steaks.]
[How will the minced steak
play into the dumplings?]
- Can you slice the rice cakes?
- The rice cakes?
- It'll be deconstructed dumplings.
- So they stick together?
[Steak and rice cake fusion.]
- I'm going to take them out.
- Okay.
[Plan is to use the rice cakes as a binder
to fuse the ingredients together.]
[Ball up the minced steak, onion,
and rice cakes together to make dumplings.]
[Chef Tiger is in charge of
shaping the dumplings.]
How big do you want these?
- That's good.
- Like this?
[First of the dumplings
start to take their shape.]
- This is coming together.
- They're really working out very well.
[Second dumpling- Adds the cooked spaghetti
to the minced steak bits.]
So you're going to shape them
into dumplings too?
Wow, that's a fantastic idea.
[Second of the tri dumplings-
Spaghetti dumplings takes shape.]
- We need to pick up the pace.
- Okay, I'll speed it up.
[Chef Hong's third dumpling-
Chili chicken and scallion dumplings.]
Add the bread crumbs.
I think that'll help.
This helps binds it all together.
[Adds the breadcrumbs to bind the
chili chicken and the scallions together.]
- Ha Ha's good.
- That's good.
How about adding in some
parmesan cheese?
- Like Jamie Oliver?
- How about you take the lead?
[Snowy white breadcrumbs
falling from the sky...]
He should've sang like that when I'd
ask him to sing during X-Man days.
[The Cooking Battle is enough to make
the Tiger break out into a song.]
[Perfectly shaped dumplings
with the added breadcrumbs.]
[The tri dumplings are now complete!
Only thing left to do is to fry them...]
What do you want to do with these, Joo Won?
Want me to boil it?
- Let's see how to cook it.
- You can't boil the chicken.
No, you can't boil it.
Either deep fry or pan fry it.
- We have to cook it all the way through.
- You can take care of it.
You look like a chicken frying expert.
- You're boring a hole through that chicken.
- There's a coating on it.
- Is there a batter on it?
- Yes.
This is already seasoned,
but how are we going to cook it through?
- It's already cooked through.
- This is already cooked through?
- Yes, it's already cooked through.
- Seriously? I never knew that.
[Chef Joo Won dumps the chicken
without hesitation to the frying pan.]
Joo Won is cooking with both hands.
[Uses his right hand to pat it down...
and stirs it around with the left hand.]
[Master of the frying pans.]
[Conquering the flavors of the world
with a single frying pan.]
[Judging is now only 15 minutes away.]
[The skewers are frying away
for the Orange Team.]
I think it's almost done.
It's starting to get nice and crispy.
Let's try one at the end.
- We have to dip it in the sauce.
- This is done cooking, right?
- Should we add some water to this?
- No, why would we do that?
- I think it's going to be good.
- Taste it.
[Tastes the kebob...]
[He's laughing?
What could it taste like?]
It's really sweet.
The chocolate...
the chocolate's all I can smell.
All I can taste is the chocolate.
[Maybe the chocolate
wasn't our saving grace...]
I think the spaghetti sauce will be better.
Okay, I'll take care of the sauce,
so you finish this up.
We have to really speed it up.
- I can take care of that.
- I have to start frying the dumplings.
This is like a tight ball of muscles.
Look at that.
[The dumplings Tiger balled up...
It's time to start frying them.]
- It's not working.
- It's falling apart.
[Only ten seconds left on the clock.]
[No time to come up with a new dish idea.]
[The spaghetti dumplings
are falling apart and losing shape.]
I was really shocked.
As soon as I bit into it,
it was just pure chocolate.
You can't taste the donkatsu
or the shrimp whatsoever.
- See? What did I tell you?
- It's just pure sweetness.
- We need something tart.
- I think tomato sauce would've been good.
Let's make the tomato sauce separately
and drizzle it on top.
[Meeting of the melted chocolate
and tart tomatoes?]
Yes, let's try it.
Tart and the sweet.
- Should we just mix it together?
- Let's just mix it.
Let's just mix the tomato sauce in there.
Just put a little bit
of the chocolate in here.
[Add in the melted chocolate
to the warm tomato sauce.]
[It'll definitely be less sweet
than the pure melted chocolate...]
[Loyal chefs are sharing even
the small bits of the kebob together.]
It's not bad.
No, I think...
You know the Indian curry?
That's what this tastes like.
How can it taste like that?
Let's mix it all in.
I can't believe how that tastes.
Try it, Ji Hyo.
- Seriously?
- Try it, it's no joke.
[It was so sweet before,
so how can it taste like that?]
- This is how they make their curry sauce.
- Oh my.
- Doesn't it taste like that?
- It's really good.
- Only five minutes left on the clock!
- Cook it down.
[With only five minutes left to go,
a new sauce is born.]
[Blue Team also picks up their pace.]
I can smell it now.
It's starting to smell really good.
[Crispy rice is also starting to take shape.]
This takes a lot of effort.
[The sound of their love and effort.]
I need to flip this over.
[Chef Joo Won is starting to get serious.]
[Main ingredient, chicken,
takes the spotlight.]
- That looks good just as is.
- Okay, the sauce is coming.
[Time to add in Chef Yoo's secret sauce.]
You don't think it'll be too salty?
[Adds in another huge dollop of the sauce.]
Should we add the noodles right now?
- It's like spicy chicken wings.
- Not exactly what I was thinking.
[Is spicy chicken wings
what we were going for?]
I think this is going to be too salty.
Should we add in some water?
[Dumps in the rest of the secret sauce.
Starting to look a bit salty...]
We have to add the dumplings too.
Add in the dumplings.
[Dumps in the whole bowl of the dumplings.]
- We have to add the noodles too.
- No, we have to add the vegetables.
You're going to dump the whole thing?
No, that's too much!
[Add it all in!
We are all as one!]
- What are you doing?
- Is that spicy chicken stew?
Is that like stir-fried chitlins?
[Only 30 seconds left on the clock!]
- What are we doing with the noodles?
- Add that in too.
[A mixture of all the ingredients.]
- Add some water.
- How about vegetable oil?
Oil?
No, add the water.
- It'll be like ddeokbokki.
- Don't you think that's too much?
[What is he doing to the dish?]
- What is this?
- Just hang on.
[What are we going to do?]
[Orange Team's dish is now complete.]
It tastes like naan curry, doesn't it?
[Tomato sauce and chocolate-
Instant Indian curry.]
[Green Team is also putting on
the finishing touches to their dish.]
[Visually pleasing dish
is also pleasing to the palate.]
[Focusing on decorating the plate.]
[Green Team's dish is now also complete.]
You'd better hurry with that hot pot.
[Hot pot dish chefs.]
[Please let it be good...]
- It's salty.
- It's salty, right? The chicken is salty.
- Let's make it sweeter.
- Okay.
[Adds in the corn syrup
as their finishing touch.]
- You have to plate it and bring it over.
- Okay.
It's good.
Try it.
We're going to start the judging.
- It's really good.
- It's really good all of a sudden.
[Chef Joo Won's turn to give it a taste.]
Wow, what is this?
Isn't it good?
- How did that happen?
- It's really good.
- What are you guys doing over there?
- We're going to be here all night.
Pour some water in there.
[Add the crispy rice on top.]
[Since they're already adding in everything,
another dump of water...]
[Confidently walks out with their dish.]
Shake it up a bit to mix it together.
[Shake it all up to improve the taste?]
It just needs to taste good.
What is that?
Pig gruel?
[DIY Cooking Battle- Complete.]
[Time for the judges to come in.]
These dishes were created solely by using
instant and frozen ingredients.
It wasn't intentional,
but we came up with a killer sauce.
-We also came up with an amazing sauce.
- We truly have the best sauce out of all.
Why did you add in that water
at the last minute?
It made it even better.
It tastes even better now.
[Last minute addition of the water
made the dish even better.]
We will now welcome our panel of judges
who'll help us judge our dishes.
[Time to introduce the panel of judges.]
The newest internet foodie sensation,
Mr. Kim Dong Bum.
- You look like a real foodie.
- He's very famous.
The woman seated next to him
is Ms. Lee Sang Hee,
an internet food blogging sensation.
I love your blogs!
- You're so pretty, Lee Sang Hee!
- Gary says you're cute.
The man seated in the middle is the star of
food for the single men blog, Wui Lee Geun.
Mr. Wui Lee Geun!
[Representative single man of the country
specializing in tips for all the single men.]
Then we have self-acclaimed foodie,
cartoonist, Kim Poong.
[Self-acclaimed foodie, Kim Poong.]
And lastly, SBS' very own foodie and
bachelor, PD Kim Joo Hyung, aka PD Myuk.
- No, he's not a foodie.
- How is he a foodie?
No, he's not a foodie.
These five judges will fairly judge
the dishes that you've created.
After tasting the dishes you've created,
they'll give you a star rating.
Five stars will mean a perfect score.
Is that understood?
You can decide amongst yourselves
who'll be the first to be judged.
Can the judges tell us
what they're looking for?
- Is it the quantity of food?
- No, I'll be looking for quality.
- Do you like salty foods?
- Yes, I tend to like saltier foods.
[Yes! Kim Dong Bum
with the salty taste buds!]
We have our faith in you.
What about you, Ms. Lee Sang Hee?
I prefer simple dishes that are made
with very simple ingredients.
- No need to worry.
- This was made very simply.
Then who'd like to go first?
Ji Hyo, would you like to go first?
[Orange Team is first to be judged.]
- What we were going for was...
- Our dish is called, 'Crazy po-imp rollup.'
'Crazy po-imp rollup.'
It's a crazy rollup of pork and shrimp.
[Pork cutlet donkatsu and shrimp skewers
rolled up in spaghetti noodles.]
[Not the best looking expression
on the judges faces.]
We had no idea that we'd be able to
create a sauce like that either.
It's a fusion of spaghetti sauce
with melted chocolate.
- But it's unexpectedly good.
- It turned out unbelievably well.
- We hope you'll enjoy it.
- It tastes like Indian curry.
We ask that you dip the kebob
in the sauce and enjoy it together.
We stand behind our sauce.
- Why don't you do it, Ji Hyo?
- They should dip it themselves.
No, we were going to drizzle it on top.
- Don't drizzle too much on top.
- This isn't salty at all.
- You'll be amazed by the taste.
- Ladies first.
This is making me feel nervous.
[Time to taste the dish.]
- You're really going to like this.
- It really tastes like Indian curry.
- You'll taste all the ingredients.
- It smells pretty good, doesn't it?
- It smells very good.
- Doesn't it?
- Since this is a fusion dish...
- We went for the flavors of India.
Dong Bum looks afraid to try it.
- Since this is a fashion dish...
- Dong Bum looks afraid to try it.
[Much tougher to slide it off the skewer
than it looks.]
[The judges are engaged in a battle
with the wooden skewers.]
Are you alright?
[The kebobs are turning into a total mess.]
[Is this why they call it a crazy rollup?]
[Takes a sauce shower at the judging table.]
We didn't realize it would be like that.
- Is it that tough?
- It wasn't like this earlier.
You didn't tie it up with a rope, did you?
I have strong teeth,
but that was still very difficult.
It's not easy to eat,
but the sauce really is delicious.
- It's just been sitting for a bit...
- Please be lenient in that retrospect.
What do you think?
I personally liked it.
I personally like dishes like this.
I also like your experimental
attitude towards food.
- If we had more time...
- I really liked that about this dish.
How about our resident foodie, PD Myuk?
Foods that are visually pleasing
are pleasing to the stomach as well.
I really liked how visually pleasing this is,
and it's nice in that aspect.
But with it being so tough to eat
I feel like this is something you serve to
someone whom you have a grudge against.
[A very crude way of explaining.]
That was a very different way
of explaining your experience.
[That's our PD Myuk!
Hands automatically go out to his throat.]
He definitely is very crude.
But please take the effort it took
into your consideration.
[Orange Team's judging is now complete.]
[Time for Green Team's judging.]
The name of our dish is...
'Three beats into the rhythm!'
[A nice name for the tri colored dumplings.]
We used chicken as the ingredient
for one of the dumplings
and steak with some onions and
rice cakes.
Don't you think that you're using
too many technical culinary terms?
[Three different dumplings made up of
various different ingredients.]
[Even serves the dishes personally.]
I see, thank you.
- It's a nice bite size.
- Yes, a single bite size.
- The rice cakes compliments it nicely.
- It's a different judging from the last.
Everyone looks so much more relaxed.
- He wiped his plate clean.
- He ate it all.
That's because you served them tiny bites.
- I was trying to serve them.
- They were really tiny bites.
I don't know if it's because I was so
scarred by the first dish...
No, it wasn't that bad.
I think the dish is a great idea.
But the taste is a bit like
street vendor food style.
That's because we used rice cake sauce.
They all pretty much tastes the same.
They all have a sweet taste to it.
If something is sweet,
then there should be something salty.
I know that you added the red pepper paste
to the pasta sauce, but you can't taste it.
Yes, it needs to taste a little salty.
We're bring that out to you.
We'll bring the salty and the sweet.
I really want to praise you
on your presentation.
You can't help but think 'cheap' when
it's made with these types of ingredients
but there's an aura of elegance
to your dish.
But I personally am not a fan of
carbonara sauce.
[What great news to these people!]
- He doesn't like carbonara sauce.
- We had very limited ingredients.
But I think that women would like
these flavors.
I really like how it's plated,
and how easy these were to eat.
I especially liked the steak bite
with the cream sauce on top.
One thing I was disappointed by
was the plain rice cake.
I wonder if it would've been better
if you had fried it first.
- That's what I was thinking too!
- Yes, you guys should've fried it!
I really enjoy it when I can get
all the flavors together in one single bite.
The taste that can explode in your mouth
as you chew it all together.
So I really enjoyed that about this dish.
[Green Team's judging
finishes off on a very high note.]
We will bring up the rear with our dish.
I don't think you should have very high
expectations for this dish.
The thing we're disappointed by is that this
dish should be eaten while it's still hot.
The name of our dish is...
'Instant chicken wing, dumpling,
and noodle stir-fry.'
[That is one long name for the dish.]
Do you remember the street rice cakes
that you used to eat when you were young?
We tried to bring back that same taste
back from our childhood.
I'd like to be honest
and tell you that the dish is a bit salty
since the chicken itself was salty.
Yes, that's true but also with everyone so
into over-consumption of their food lately
we purposely made it a bit saltier
so that people won't over-eat as much.
Please understand that it's a bit salty
since we were upfront about that aspect.
Why don't you all give it a taste?
Please allow us to also wish you
the best of luck in the new year.
Best of luck in the new year.
[That's six months too late, you fool.]
We're closer to next year
than we are to last year.
Wasn't it swimming in the sauce before?
Don't pay them any attention.
[The presentation of the dish
has been changed.]
Why is he bent over that piece of chicken?
It's just a relief that our dish
wasn't the first one to be judged.
He's going for the water.
[They guessed this may happen,
so came prepared with the water.]
We brought you some extra water.
Just let us know if you need more water.
Did you three make the three components
of this dish separately?
[How the dish was even created
is a mystery in itself.]
It was a chicken wing stew.
[A mysterious dish that they're not sure
how it was even created.]
It's to represent how we are all as one
by mixing all the components together.
That's why we put everything
together in one pot.
After having tried it...
it tastes like you just winged it.
- Don't you think that you're being too harsh?
- No, I don't think so.
With the other dishes,
it didn't taste like instant food.
- You can tell with ours?
- Your dish is very obvious.
- That's just what we were going for.
- That's why our dish is called, 'instant'.
- Then we succeeded!
- Of course.
We purposely left that taste obvious.
Trying to mask the taste of instant food
is just lying.
It's a given that instant food
should maintain that instant food taste.
- What do you think?
- I think differently.
I'm different.
Trying to take instant food
and masking it as real food...
We weren't asking you!
[I haven't even gotten started.]
Stop eating!
When it comes to cooking,
everyone has their own style and method.
Whether it be dumpling or chicken.
But when it comes to chicken wings...
Many people don't get the chance
to eat something like this.
- So this is special in that sense.
- You should thank him for that comment.
The fact that you took such a
special ingredient and ruined it like this...
[A mixture of compliment and
disdain in his judging.]
The fact that you ruined it...
is an insult to the chickens.
I didn't think it was that bad.
What are your thoughts?
The best part during
the judging for me was...
when I got to take a drink of
my water.
That's why water is so precious.
[Cooking note- Water is precious.]
- That's why water is precious.
- There's a message in our dish.
I know that I've told you that instant food
should maintain some of its taste...
but I think you must've misunderstood
the point that I was trying to make.
[A huge misunderstanding on their part.]
- Can you tell us what you think?
- I purposely didn't eat before I came here.
I think I just filled up on water
during this judging process.
I'm disappointed that I had to
fill up on water like this.
I personally really like chicken.
Because chicken tastes good
no matter what you do to it.
[Just what have you done to the chicken?]
- You shouldn't be so biased like that.
- Why does chicken have to be always good?
As much as we work at it,
the chicken has to put in some efforts too.
[Cooking lesson-
Chicken has to work at it too.]
My point is that the chicken
has to work at it too.
I actually had the highest expectation
for your dish when I saw it
because I have such an affinity
for chicken.
- But as high as my expectations were...
- Your expectations were too high.
Your expectations were too high.
[Sorry for having high expectations.]
We had no idea that
you liked chicken so much.
But I still have hope after
these comments.
We are all of the same opinion right now.
[We are as one!]
We are what bound all four
of their opinions as one.
- This is what we were going for.
- Yes, that's true.
Then it's now time to make the judgment.
The judges are now going to take the time
to score your dishes.
I'd like to mention again that this
this got so tough because it got cold.
I think it would be best to give one score
after discussing it amongst ourselves first.
[Very serious looking expression
on these judges faces.]
Ours are very similar.
[Who will be chosen to have
created the best tasting dish?]
The judging process is now complete.
We're very nervous to hear the results.
I get the feeling that it's either
going to be Green or the Orange Team.
We will now reveal your scores.
Are you going to put on those helmets?
Isn't that too much work?
That's going a little overboard.
[Time for the judges to put their helmets on.]
This is the first time I'm getting to
use something like this.
Everyone seems okay with it.
We'll get started with our team first.
- Five stars would mean a perfect score.
- Let's see how many stars gets lit up.
Okay, for the Blue Team.
One, two, three!
[The ever so controversial chicken dish...]
One!
There you go!
[Even though it may not have been the best,
it still carried a good message...]
[That's it!]
[Blue Team- Two stars.]
Two stars isn't bad at all.
That's more than what I was expecting.
- Two stars is very respectable.
- Yes, I agree.
Next up is, Hong Suk Chun,
Ha Ha and Kim Jong Kook.
Let's see how many stars they can score
and if they can beat our two stars.
Nice, thank you.
Will three stars be it?
[There it is!]
Just give us half.
One, two, three!
[Half more, and it'll be a perfect score!]
[Green Team's dish that was unique
even with their name!]
['Three beats into the rhythm' has garnered
positive reviews from all the judges.]
[Will they be able to earn five stars?]
[But Green Team still earns
four and a half stars!]
- So we need to get five stars?
- We win if we get five stars?
- We still have a chance.
- Five stars and you win.
So we still have a chance.
Ji Suk Jin, Gary, and Blank Ji Hyo.
Time to see their score.
They need to get five stars to
beat the Green Team's four and a half stars.
One, two...
they're tied with our score for now.
[Blue Team is guaranteed the last spot.]
- Come on.
- Keep going!
A full star.
Okay, PD Myuk.
[They'll be tied for first place
if PD Myuk gives them half a star.]
One, two, three!
[Please...]
[Orange Team's unique and delicious sauce
made of the chocolate and pasta sauce.]
The sauce is very delicious.
[Their experimental dish that even
the judges seemed impressed with.]
[Will they be able to create a miracle
with their unique and delicious sauce?]
[The fifth star remains unlit!]
One, two, three!
[Keeps counting until the star lights up.]
[Four stars for the Orange Team.]
Hong Suk Chun, Kim Jong Kook
and Ha Ha win the cooking battle!
[Green Team takes home the victory!]
[Today's victor-
Three beats into the rhythm.]
To the three victors...
[Time to hand out the prize
to the Green Team for winning.]
Prizes to our three winners.
Last but not least, I'd like to thank our
five esteemed panel of judges for
taking the time out of their busy schedule
to come help us today.
[Thank you to our panel of judges.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[206th race...]
[Only two wins under his belt.]
[For his third win,
these guests have all gathered.]
[The weakest links that Big-nose
himself has invited onto the show.]
[Sacrificing themselves for
the sake of their good friend.]
- Are you sure you guys are even my friends?
- Why should we take the bullet for you?
[Is their friendship being tested?]
[Running Man vs Ji Suk Jin's friends-
A battle with their pride on the line.]
[And the ultimate battle
that they've yet to face...]
[Next week on Running Man-
Running Man vs Big-nose and his friends.]