Subtitles by DramaFever
Wow, this isn't even right.
This is just...
What's that?
It's moving!
It's staring at me.
It's staring at me right now.
[Something's staring at the Giraffe?]
[This has to be a bad dream.]
[Something is tied to the alligator's tail.]
[What's happening to Kwang Soo?]
[June 2014- Incheon International Airport.]
[All the members are heading out to
participate in the upcoming Dream Cup.]
I love you, Jakarta.
I love Indonesia.
We'll see you in Indonesia.
[You just wait, Dream Cup.
We are coming for you!]
This is the Dream Team boot camp training.
[Last week's boot camp training
with Captain Park.]
[Each and every one of those
challenging moments...]
[And the special lesson that they've
received from legend himself, Cha Bum Geun.]
[Cha Bum Geun and Captain Park-
The training camp led by two legends.]
[We will not be the same
as we were last year.]
[Indonesia- a place where nature and
people coexists in harmony.]
[A place where culture and the passion
of people are alive and breathing.]
[Another stage of dreams will
soon open its doors.]
[Jakarta- Soccer stadium.]
This is the field where
I'm going to score my very first goal.
- Why do you think it's going to be you?
- I'm going to score my first goal here.
[The largest soccer stadium in Indonesia
with seats for 80,000 spectators.]
Let me try it too.
There you go.
Ji Hyo, you're better than most women.
[Big-nose has already
lost the strength in his legs.]
[Big-nose Brother's sternum trapping.]
Suk Jin, are you okay?
- Where is Park Ji Sung?
- I saw him arriving a little while ago.
- What's taking him so long?
- There he is right now. Ji Sung!
[Captain Park makes his appearance.]
- It's so nice to see you!
- Are you going to get started now?
[Everyone's starting to suck up to
Captain Park for a place on the field.]
- What have you all been doing?
- We've been practicing.
- We were warming up a bit.
- We were practicing our kicks.
- We were warming up.
- You're just now warming up?
I think you'll be quite surprised when you
see us running out on the field.
We've been practicing,
and we're so much lighter on our feet now.
- You look exhausted already.
- No, not at all.
I would like to sincerely welcome
all of you to Jakarta.
Today is the day of the much anticipated
Dream Cup game.
[The day has finally arrived.]
[Special boot camping training under their belt.
They're not the same as they once were.]
You are here to participate in a game where
the best of the best in the world of soccer
will be out on the field competing for
the honor of taking home The Dream Cup.
- Park Ji Sung has invited some guests...
- Oh my gosh!
[Wait, that man is...]
[The legend of Korean soccer-
Cha Bum Geun!]
- Have you been well?
- It's Cha Boom!
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be at the World Cup right now?
[Not only is he a soccer legend,
but he's the lead sportscaster for Korea.]
[But what is he suddenly doing here in Jakarta
instead of being at the World Cup games?]
I came because I was worried
about you guys.
- I came because I was worried.
- We're so glad you're here.
We're so glad that you came,
and thank you!
We're working very hard with
the teachings that you gave us.
Coach... hello!
[Haroro is greeting the coach in
the shooting stance that he's been taught.]
Knees bent, chest forward,
and straighten out the leg.
[A one pointer lesson from the legend
that they all took to heart.]
Step up next to the ball,
and then make your move.
[Even received some pointers on how
to dribble the ball more skillfully.]
I had no idea why
you were doing this at first.
But we seriously have improved our skills
greatly since your lesson.
- I heard that you guys have improved a lot.
- Yes, we've improved greatly.
The one pointer lesson you gave us greatly
improved all of our skills.
I felt like everyone took to the lesson from
the coach well and have improved their skills
and I thought that you guys would perform
better if Coach Cha was here in person.
- I can't believe that he's here!
- Thank you, Coach Cha!
[Captain Park paid a personal visit to Cha Bum
and invited him to attend the Dream Cup.]
I wanted to see all of you play in the game
and I also wanted to see for myself
how much your skills have improved.
- We really have improved greatly.
- We can even do heading shoots now.
- I'm going to watch you play in the game.
- Okay!
We will keep your lesson fresh
in our minds.
You have to play well in the game so that
the lesson I gave you guys feels validated.
- Yes, of course.
- I feel like their skills are still lacking.
If you feel that you're up for it...
I was wondering how you would feel about
playing in the game yourself today.
- Are you going to play in the game?
- Well, I...
[Will the legendary Cha Boom play
in the game himself?]
- Well...
- Cha Bum Geun! Cha Bum Geun!
- Seriously?
- Is he really going to play?
- I'm 62 years old right now.
- But still, you're The Cha Bum Geun.
- How about just for ten minutes?
- Not even just ten minutes of playing?
[Age is nothing but a number
to a legend like Cha Boom.]
[Legend will never fade away.]
- I think you will be a huge help to us.
- We will help you any way that we can.
- Who's going to pass the ball over to me?
- I'll pass the ball over to you.
[Player number 11.]
[The Brown Bomber, number 11,
who took the world of soccer by a storm.]
[That number 11 will
once again fly on the field...]
[With a new legend, number 7.]
I will now explain
your Dream Cup mission to you.
The Dream Cup race today will be
carried out a bit differently
than what you have seen
the past two previous years.
In a few hours, the game against
Indonesia's representative soccer team
will take place on this field.
You will each be given a mission to carry out
during the Dream Cup game.
You just have to succeed the mission
that you've been given.
- It's simple as that.
- During the game?
- Yes, during the game.
- During the game!
If Park Ji Sung had to delegate the positions
which the Running Man members would play
then which position out on the field
would you assign to the members?
Based on our current situation,
I'd assign the wing position to them.
That's the toughest position!
- One wing position, and a shadow striker.
- Okay, I like shadow striker.
- I think a shadow striker would be good.
- How about a one-top position?
If one of you were put in
that position...
then I can 100% guarantee
that we'd lose the game.
Wow, Ji Sung normally wouldn't say
something like that.
He says he can guarantee it.
Since Park Ji Sung is the captain
of the Running Man team
he will also have a mission
of his own to carry out.
Park Ji Sung's mission is to score a total
of three goals during the game.
[Captain Park's mission-
Score a total of three goals.]
- And also do a hat trick while playing.
- Wait.
I've never once done a hat trick
during a game soccer.
- Then you can do it today.
- Today will be your first time.
- That's going to be so fun to watch!
- His first and last hat trick during a game.
Was it the game against Malaysia years ago
that Coach Cha played in?
You know the game where he scored
four points within the first seven minutes.
No, it was three goals
within the first five minutes.
But it's pretty much the same thing.
Four in seven minutes or three in five.
Coach Cha, don't you think that
you could probably do that again?
Look at him!
Did you just see his reaction?
How do you expect us to
carry out these types of missions?
I heard that our opponents
are really formidable.
I heard that they're the most formidable
team we've yet to face in these games.
The opposing that we'll be playing today
isn't a team made up of some amateurs.
They're all players who are respected to be
the best of the best soccer players.
To be honest, scoring even just two goals
would still be quite a feat.
- Yes, let's settle for two.
- I think two is a good number.
[Through Cha Boom's negotiations,
they settle on two goals.]
And although we don't know which
one of you will be playing in the game
but in the case of either Song Ji Hyo
or Ji Suk Jin playing in the game...
Let's let Ji Hyo's mission be
not falling asleep out on the field.
Their mission will be to get in touch with
the ball at least five times within the game.
But that's way too easy!
Then are they allowed to kick the ball around
five times once they have it for the mission?
- No, five different times.
- Ah, get it five times from other players?
[Not an easy mission to succeed
for first time participants.]
Then I guess I won't pass them the ball.
[Please, Ji Sung...]
Other than the players already mentioned,
everyone else who's already played before...
Yoo Jae Suk, Lee Kwang Soo,
Ha Ha, Kim Jong Kook and Gary...
Since you've had the experience of being
out on the field already
and have experienced the cheer of
the fans from the stands...
I believe that you will be able to play
with confidence and ease this time.
With that thought in mind, you
each have to score a forward point.
- What do you mean by that?
- You either have to assist or score a goal.
We have to either assist or score a goal?
Then if Jong Kook assists Gary,
and Gary scores, then they both succeed?
That's never going to happen.
[Just as the game states,
that's just a dream.]
- We can give it a try.
- Just pass the ball to each other.
Think of everyone else as our opponents.
If I don't let them out on the field,
then they all fail the mission?
- Yes, if you don't let them out on the field.
- Yes, then they all fail the mission?
[If they don't make it out on the field,
then they automatically fail the mission.]
- Why are you even saying that?
- Just in case I don't succeed my own mission.
If I feel that I may not get to
succeed my own mission.
Coach Cha,
you believe that it's possible, right?
I think the die has already
been rolled out.
I don't think there's any way for us
to avoid the inevitable.
The most important thing for any player
to have is self-confidence.
Yes, you're right.
Even if it doesn't quite work out,
you still have to play with confidence.
- We can do it!
- We're going to think positively.
You've all learned a lesson from me.
I feel very confident.
I would like for everyone to play with
confidence and show what you can do.
- Yes, we understand.
- We won't disappoint you!
- We will show you what we can do.
- We will show you with our actions.
- I will be watching all of you.
- Let's give a round of applause!
[Time for the spectators
to enter the stadium.]
[The stadium fills up with over
60,000 spectators.]
[Dressing room.]
[Italy's legendary defensive player-
Jean Luca Zambrotta.]
[Italy's newest ace- Stefan El Shara.]
[First, it's time for some pictures.]
[Reunites with a familiar face.]
Please help me score a goal.
I'll help you to the best of my abilities
so that you don't have to pay a penalty.
- You two won't get to play together.
- Ji Sung, wait!
[Twins Gae and Jung.]
I can make it so that none of you
get to go out on the field.
[Immediately apologizes.]
Coach Cha, you're here!
You should change into your uniform.
Everyone get up on your feet!
Cha Boom!
[Wow, Cha Boom is here?]
Hey, Mr. Jam.
My teacher.
He's my teacher.
[The world star soccer players pays
their respect to their legendary senior.]
- Your uniform is right here.
- It's right here.
You really expect me to wear this?
Ji Hyo's right here.
- Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Coach Cha is right over there.
[Ji Hyo's ready to go out onto the field.]
Coach Cha, you're in your uniform too.
Wow!
I have to dress the part
as your coach.
Ji Hyo's here.
Hi, Mr. Jam.
This is my sister.
- Hi, it's nice to meet you.
- Wow, I've never seen him smile before.
I can't believe that he's actually smiling.
This is the first time I've ever seen him
smile like that.
[Wow, she's so beautiful.]
There's been a change to the list of players.
- What kind of a change?
- One of the RM members will be starting.
[Kwang Soo is chosen to stand
in the starting line.]
- Please think about it one more time.
- Lee Kwang Soo!
Please stop him from doing this to me!
- Why are you suddenly acting so scared?
- But I'm just not ready for this yet!
- What are you talking about?
How can a player facing a match
not be prepared to play?
How can a player who's about to play in
a match say that he's not ready?
I can be prepared to play
by the start of the second half.
What did you say to me earlier?
You said you wouldn't disappoint me.
[Where did the confident Giraffe
from earlier go?]
- Or you can just not play at all.
- No, I'll play!
[Giraffe comes to his senses from
one stern warning from Cha Boom.]
[The time has come!]
[Time for everyone to become one
and bring each other's dreams alive.]
Let no one get hurt, and let this
be a game of everlasting memories.
[Let's bring our dreams alive!]
[At last...]
[Fourth Running Man Asian Dream Cup.]
[The passion and fervor of the World Cup
is felt in this Indonesian stadium!]
I'm getting really nervous.
[Players make their entrance.]
[Along with the best players in the world...
Giraffe makes his way into the stadium.]
There's Kwang Soo.
[Running Man members watch Giraffe
make his entrance from the bench.]
He's as tall as most of the other players.
[A commemorative photo of starting lineup
with Ji Sung and members of JS friends.]
[Captain Park Ji Sung.]
[Former news announcer, Kim Min Ji-
Ji Sung's fiancée.]
[Striker Giraffe.]
[The Asian Prince has
his loyal Indonesian fans.]
[The honor of standing in the starting line
alongside Captain Park.]
[Last year's Dream Cup participant
who was so full of enthusiasm...]
[But his enthusiasm was met with
a face full of humiliation.]
[Through legendary Cha Bum Geun's
special training...]
[He is now considered to be
one of Cha Boom's pupils.]
[Time to repay his kindness with
action out on the field.]
Lee Kwang Soo!
[First half- Start!]
[The world famous stars  are passing
the ball around out on the field.]
[And Giraffe is standing in the midst
of all those players with confidence.]
[Why does looking out onto the field...
make me feel so nervous?]
[Indonesia's All Stars are their opponents.]
The opposing team is way too good.
[The opposing team's expert footwork skills.]
[Team JS Friends' defense is fortified
with Italy's Zambrotta on their side.]
Dae Se!
[Striker for Team JS Friends-
Jung Dae Se.]
[Captain Park commands the center field.]
- Park Ji Sung, fighting!
[The dribble that ruled European soccer!]
[A chance for Team JS to score!]
Kwang Soo, what are you doing!
Get close to the ball!
[Striker Giraffe is running fast
towards an empty space.]
[Why won't the ball come near me?]
Give the ball to Kwang Soo!
Where's Kwang Soo?
- Lee Kwang Soo... is out there, isn't he?
- Yes, he's out towards the front.
He's running quite well out there
just like a real giraffe would.
[Grass loving Giraffe.]
Kwang Soo!
[Kwang Soo will have a terrifying penalty
to pay if he doesn't score a forward point!]
[Oh...]
[This is my chance!]
Knees bent, chest forward,
and straighten out the leg!
[The piece of advice from Cha Boom...]
[Just like how we practiced!]
Knees bent, chest forward,
and straighten out the leg!
[Will Giraffe pull it off?]
[That's my boy!]
[Kicks the ball just as he learned!]
[Did he score?]
[Coach Cha Boom, I'm so very sorry.]
- Kwang Soo!
- But he kicked towards the goal!
[Giraffe brings laughter to others
with his soccer skills.]
I don't know why, but I'm
suddenly feeling a little teary eyed.
[Team JS's chance at a free kick.]
[Giraffe is given a chance
alongside Captain Park.]
[A whole head taller
than all the other players.]
[Jung Dae Se to be the kicker.]
[People's Rooney, Jung Dae Se,
scores the first goal!]
[Look of excitement on everyone's faces.]
[A cheerful ceremony with Giraffe.]
[Captain Park congratulates him
on a job well done.]
[A signal to swap Giraffe out of the game.]
Lee Kwang Soo, out.
[Mission- Score a forward point.
Nice try, but fails to succeed his mission.]
[Makes his exit from the game with
encouragement from Zambrotta.]
He hasn't even done anything,
but he's about to vomit right now.
- Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo, what's wrong?
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo, you did good.
- Are you okay? Drink some water.
Kwang Soo.
[Completely bewildered.]
Are you okay, Kwang Soo?
Don't you think that was crazy?
- They wouldn't give you the ball, would they?
- They were a bit ruthless today.
- That's because it's a tight competition.
- It's because of their formidable opponents.
But people can't really tell you apart
when you're out there on the field.
You look just like one of the players.
This is all thanks to your grace, Coach Cha!
Thank you, Coach Cha.
From the bench,
you really did look like one of the players.
[Cha Boom is complimenting his pupil
on a job well done.]
[The fans continue to cheer on
Captain Park's performance.]
That was my spot.
I wouldn't have played it like that
had I been in the game.
- Be quiet.
- You wouldn't have even gone near it.
Suk Jin, it's your turn to go in.
[The time has come!
Big-nose's first time in the game.]
Good luck, Suk Jin.
[A look full of worry.]
My heart is pounding in my chest.
[Even in the midst of his nervousness,
he still manages to greet his fans.]
Ji Suk Jin!
I'm so nervous right now.
Ugh, I'm so nervous.
- You're switching out Captain Park.
- What?
[Like a bolt of lightning.]
I'm supposed to take Ji Sung's place?
But Ji Sung has to stay in the game to
pass me the ball.
I can't take over Ji Sung's spot.
[First time playing in the Dream Cup-
Takes over the Captain's spot.]
Ji Sung is coming out?
[Since it's an unofficial player swap,
he can come back out onto the field.]
[Swap of the captains.
Captain Park- Captain Ji.]
He's totally dead!
[This is Captain Ji's time!]
[Full of confidence!
Captain Ji!]
[Suk Jin's mission-
Touch the ball five times.]
I don't care who's watching, but Suk Jin
totally runs like a middle aged man.
[Looks like a middle aged man
playing neighborhood kickball.]
Hey, Suk Jin looks like he's trying to
flag down a cab.
[Taxi!]
[Please go towards the goal post!]
Taxi!
[Captain Ji is desperately trying to
flag down the taxi ball.]
[Suk Jin's mission- Touch the ball five times.
Current count- Zero.]
[The soccer ball is way too fast for
Captain Ji to follow.]
[I will show you what I can do
as the captain!]
Suk Jin!
[Trying to figure out where to go.]
[Definitely too much for him.]
[Jung Dae Se comes out of nowhere
like a beacon of  light.]
[So close!]
[I have to touch the ball.]
[Zambrotta's long center ring kick.]
[Jung Dae Se scores his second goal!]
[What a great offensive player!]
[Shares his joy
with the Running Man members.]
My brother!
He hasn't even been near the ball yet.
He's just wandering around
out on the field right now.
[He's showing us how one can still play
soccer even without a soccer ball.]
I hope that I'll get a chance to get
to the ball once I'm in the game.
[A very sad looking back.]
Suk Jin's done now.
His hand is already on his side now.
[Evidence of his battery having run out.]
[Moment before the first half is over,
the opposing team scores their first goal.]
I bet he's going to touch the ball now.
- He can touch the ball now.
- Oh no, the first half is all over!
[Ball touch count- One.]
[Captain Ji- Penalty guaranteed.]
[Halftime after the end of first half.]
[Giraffe- Having played hard in the game.]
I want to get back out there.
[The Prince of off-sides,
Captain Ji.]
- Everything just happens so fast.
- Do you know what it felt like out there?
I noticed that I was always off to the side
whenever the other team was on the offense.
So I'd run to chase after the ball
but by the time I'd get there,
the ball would already be on the other side.
[Always running in the opposite direction
of the ball.]
There's no such thing as 'off-side'
in neighborhood soccer.
No, there is no such thing.
[Dream Cup Game- Second Half.]
[I'll be going out there
during the second half...]
[Gary takes it upon himself
to start warming up for his entrance.]
[Cha Boom's vote of confidence
in Gary's skills.]
[Stretching]
[Monday Couple even helps
each other stretch out!]
[Looking back...]
[Gary's first Dream Cup appearance
was two years ago...]
[But he was full of mistakes.]
[He had to console himself with
just having been part of the game.]
[Will he show the world a different
side to him this time?]
[Go get them, Gary!]
- Get the ball!
- There he goes!
[The ball is passed directly over to Gary!]
[A low and speedy pass!]
[Nice course!]
[If the ball makes it in the goal,
then Gary succeeds his mission!]
[Really?]
[Goal... so close!]
[By the split of a hair!]
[Mission- Score a forward point.
Gary could've assisted in a goal!]
He almost had it!
It almost made it in!
[That's my boy.]
- Gary, cross kicks!
- Okay, Gary!
- Shoot!
- Gary almost had a goal assist.]
That could've been a great assist.
Even Davao just gave Gary
a thumbs up.
Of all the Running Man members
we've seen so far
I'm getting the best feeling
from Gary.
[Great job, Gary!]
[Haroro's turn to step out onto the
dream field in place of Jung Dae Se.]
Go up front!
[Haroro is running with all his might.]
Cut him off!
Cut him off in the middle!
[A dance instructor's pose.]
Ha Dong Hoon, fighting!
[Full of energy and vigor-
Straight on ahead!]
[Shoved out of the way.]
That's what we look like
most of the time.
- That's not just Ha Ha, but that's all of us.
- That's our natural form.
How like you that was, Ha Ha.
[That's so like you.]
[Team JS on the offense.]
[Kicks the ball over to Gary.]
[Wow!]
This is the stance you should take
when you're either passing or dribbling.
- Yes, that's very good.
- He's good.
[Gary showing off his best
duck butt moves.]
[And...]
[Gary's butt kicks into gear in Indonesia!]
[With a professional soccer player
as his opponent!]
[Gary-butt isn't letting his opponent
steal the ball away from him!]
That was great.
Jong Kook, get ready to go in.
[Time for Running Man's Ace to go in!]
Kim Jong Kook, fighting!
[Jong Kook has the honor of playing in
the game for the third year in a row.]
[Swaps Gary out.]
You did great.
- You almost had a goal assist.
- Ugh, I was so close!
[Even though he was so close,
he still failed to succeed his mission.]
[Team JS' offense.]
[Haroro kicks the ball to the center.]
[A super save!]
Fighting!
Kim Jong Kook, fighting!
[Jong Kook shows off his team playing skills.]
- That's it! That's good!
- Good!
Jong Kook's doing well.
[A kick resembling that
of a professional player.]
- Good job!
- He must know his way around a soccer ball.
- He's changed a lot since last year.
- This is all thanks to you, Coach Cha!
[Playing with determination.]
- He's totally different from last year.
- What has he been doing this past year?
[Other than when you were filming the show,
have you only been practicing soccer?]
Jae Suk, it's time for you to go in.
You want me to go in the game?
Good luck.
I'll be back, Coach Cha.
[Jae Suk is off to study soccer
abroad out on the field.]
Don't make another mistake
like you did last year.
[Last year's Dream Cup game- The nightmare
of having missed the penalty kick.]
I'm so nervous that I think
I need to go use the bathroom.
I wasn't nervous at all earlier.
[But now that the moment has come...]
I borrowed Kwang Soo's contact lenses.
[He even borrowed Kwang Soo's
contact lenses!]
So I guess you can't use the excuse of not
having been able to see this time around.
Why do you keep saying
things like that to me?
I'm seriously going to go out there
and score a goal.
[Swaps Haroro out- Out to hunt down his
goal for second year in a row.]
[Jae Suk's position- Right wing.]
[Ji Sung, Jong Kook, and Jae Suk
stand together on the dream field.]
[Captain Park attempts to pass
the ball over to Jae Suk.]
- Off side!
- Get over to the off side!
[Come on.]
[Jae Suk ran too far ahead of the ball.]
[Retreats back towards the ball.]
He just kicked his own ankle.
[Kicks himself in the ankle.]
[Nice pass!]
[In tip top condition!]
[Giraffe runs over to the bleachers to
instigate the fans into riding the wave.]
[Human wave?]
[The fervor in this stadium is hotter
than the World Cup stadium!]
[Korean soccer's twelfth phenomenon-
White Giraffe.]
[Exhausts himself from his efforts.]
[Dream Cup stadium is on fire!]
Yes, that's right!
- Coach Cha, it's time for you to go in.
- Cha Bum Geun!
Cha Bum Geun!
- Coach Cha, please help us redeem ourselves.
- Wow, this is so amazing.
- Wow, this is so cool.
- I can't run very well anymore.
Cha Bum Geun!
[A legend makes his move toward the field.]
Wow, I can't believe that
this is actually happening.
[A legend's comeback.]
The legend of Korean soccer!
Cha Boom!
[A true legend of Korean soccer.]
[Player number 11- Cha Bum Geun.]
[Korea's first premium major league player
who took the world of soccer by storm.]
[Legend Park Ji Sung.]
[Replacement player is,
Player number 11, Cha Bum Geun.]
[At last...]
[The legendary Cha Bum Geun
steps onto the field once again.]
Cha Bum Geun has stepped out
onto the field!
[Out on the field of green...
one legend meets another legend.]
It's a game where Park Ji Sung and
Cha Bum Geun will be playing together.
It's the meeting of two legendary players.
[The mentor and the pupil,
20 years in the making.]
Park Ji Sung has said that he's never seen
Cha Boom out on the field in person.
[A monumental moment where two
legendary players gets to play together.]
Never in all my life...
did I even fathom that I'd get to see
Cha Bum Geun play in a game like this.
[The two legends stand together as one.]
[The walls of time have no standing as these
two legends move on the field as one.]
Please!
- He has the biggest build out there.
- No kidding, he's the biggest out there.
[The powerful stance of a legend.]
[Like the gentle flow of a river-
Cha Boom passes the ball with ease.]
He just passed the ball
with the heel of his foot.
[Captain Park to Cha Boom.]
[Cha Boom back to Captain Park.
Team play made in heaven.]
He's so amazing.
Okay, he's got the ball.
[Verifies Jae Suk's position...
and makes a long through pass.]
[If he had been just a bit quicker...]
That pass was spot on.
[An unbelievably accurate
and straight pass.]
He truly is a legend.
[Every offense move...
starts with Cha Boom.]
He's trying to give Jong Kook a chance.
Okay, there he goes!
[A four way corner-
Jong Kook, Cha Boom, Ji Sung, Jae Suk.]
[The team's spirit drastically changed as soon
as Cha Boom stepped out onto the field.]
[The perfect chance!]
[Jae Suk shoots the ball!]
[Ah... he unfortunately misses the goal.]
[That was so close!]
[His passes are in a class of their own.]
Wow, he really is set apart from others.
We're so different from last year's game.
We're actually doing really good.
We're actually really good.
[Cha Boom is the one who changed it all.]
[A lost ball.]
[His tenacity drives him down to the ground.]
[The two legends have changed
the whole atmosphere of the team.]
[Current score- Team JS and Friends: 2
vs Team All-star: 3]
Coach Cha needs his chance.
[Cha Boom makes a perfect pass.]
The way Coach Cha keeps passing the ball,
it's always so spot on and accurate.
[The ultimate legend,
blazing his trail out on the field.]
[A chance for the captain
to even out the score.]
[Honey!]
[Ji Sung...]
[The ball unfortunately gets
blocked by opposing defensive player.]
[Not much time left on the clock!]
[Jong Kook and Jae Suk's teamwork
succeeds in stealing the ball.]
[Cha Boom, Jae Suk, Jong Kook-
Three offense and three defense.]
That's good!
[Succeeds at faking his move.]
Jong Kook!
[A move equivalent to that of a pro!]
[The perfect opportunity!]
[If he scores this goal,
then he can tie the score!]
[If this goal makes it in, then
Jong Kook and Jae Suk both succeed!]
[Will they make history in RM Dream Cup
and make the goal with another's assist?]
[Will he make the goal?]
[Misses his footing!]
[How can this be!]
[Loses the perfect opportunity!]
[But his manners are still world class.]
He could've scored the goal
if he hadn't lost his footing.
[Game over]
[Final score- Team JS and Friends: 2
vs Team All Stars: 3]
[Everyone gives a part of encouragement
to one another.]
[Exchanges their uniform with one another.]
[Thank you to all the Indonesian players
who played in the match with us!]
Captain.
[All the members unfortunately
fail each of their own missions.]
Can we do it again next year? Can
you give us one more chance next year?
- Give us one more chance next year.
- I'm only going to play soccer from now on.
- Just give us one more chance.
- Just let us play again next year.
[Please give us another chance, Captain.]
It was unbelievable to see you
out on the field, Coach Cha.
[To think that they got to see Cha Boom
playing out on the field in person!]
How do you feel about playing on
the same field as Cha Boom, Captain Park?
- Yeah, I want to hear how he felt.
- I never even dreamt that it was possible.
It was truly an honor to have been given
the chance to play with him tonight.
When I received my trophy from Coach Cha
as a little kid back in elementary school
he felt like a giant mountain that
I'd never be able to approach
and I realized today that there was a real
legitimate reason why I felt that way.
Just the fact alone that I was able to
play in a game tonight with Ji Sung
was not even fathomable to me before.
I'm just so thankful and grateful
for having been given this opportunity.
[Cha Bum Geun and Park Ji Sung-
Legends are forever.]
[For those who failed their mission...]
[It's time to face the wild.]
[Day Two in Indonesia-
An ominous morning approaches.]
What kind of a mission
are we going to be doing here?
- It's not a mission, but it's a penalty.
- Penalty? We're doing that right away?
Ah, I really could've avoided
having to pay any penalties.
Keep in mind that I did kick
a ball towards the goal.
I made two shots.
- Can you guys not talk about soccer?
- Why?
- Can we just not talk about soccer?
- We're in big trouble today.
- We're going to have to pay our penalties.
- What kind of a penalty is it going to be?
Not a single one of us succeeded
our mission last night.
- No, we didn't.
- Is this a safari?
- It says that it's a safari over there.
- Oh, this is a safari?
[Their penalty... is at a safari?]
What kind of a penalty
is there going to be here?
- This is a safari?
- Wow, it's so huge.
[Welcome to the jungle.]
[Taman Safari- Largest safari in Indonesia for
animals in their natural rainforest habitat.]
[A wondrous world where 2,500 animals of
270 different species co-exists.]
[Free beasts of the wild-
What will they be made to do here?]
What do they have planned for us here?
Welcome to your second day here
in beautiful Indonesia.
- I didn't get a wink of sleep last night.
- Can we play another soccer match tonight?
- It was too much.
- I'd like to play again next year.
My body is getting more and more
used to the role of being a striker.
I think I'd be able to do
a better job next year.
Even though you all played so well
at the game last night
none of you were able to succeed
the personal mission given to you.
So you all have quite the penalty to face.
Before you head off to do
your own penalty mission
we have prepared a small consolation game
which may exempt you from your penalty.
[Consolation for the losers in Safari.]
Why does everyone look so smug?
The penalties must be really stiff.
[No one...]
[Could even...]
[Have fathomed...]
[The stiffest penalty they've yet to face
for the 200th episode special.]
[Today's penalty-
Skydive from 10,000 feet in the air.]
[The head PD went through the experience
of the penalty himself.]
[A battle with one's self to
conquer the terrorizing fear.]
[Those who fail to carry out their safari
mission must become one with the sky.]
- Can you all guess where you are right now?
- We're at the safari.
This is a zoo of a massive scale that's set
right in the heart of the wild.
Your mission will be carried out
with the animals that exist in this habitat.
The mission you'll have to do will be sent to
the cellphone you have in your possession.
Whenever the name of a type of
an animal appears on your phone
you'll have to respond with your name to
the animal species you feel confident about.
For example, if the text says, Elephant,
then Yoo Jae Suk will respond with his name.
Thus the first person to respond with
their name will get to do that mission.
[Key is to respond before anyone else when
they see an animal they feel confident about.]
Since these missions involve animals,
there is no way for us to...
[Baby elephant's enthusiastic greeting.]
[Welcome to the safari.]
If you can successfully complete your safari
mission within thirty minutes
then you are excused
from the ultimate final penalty.
So the quicker we finish the mission,
then better it is for us?
- Okay, let's get started.
- What if we make a typo?
We will not accept a typo.
If you make a typo, then it won't count.
- Okay, we understand.
- Let's do this.
Okay, here we go.
What is it?
Tiger?
[The same species as Tiger Kkuk?]
- I'm not going. No way I'm going.
- It's a tiger.
[Everyone turns down the tiger.]
[Everyone's fingers are frozen in place.]
Ha Ha?
You're taking the tiger?
[Ha Ha... good luck.]
No, I didn't do it.
It really wasn't me.
I sent both of those texts.
I sent both Ha Ha and Jong Kook's name.
- I sent in Ha Ha's name.
- Shouldn't I have had to respond myself?
- Congratulations, Ha Ha. You got the tiger.
- Congratulations, Ha Ha.
[How in the world!]
But I didn't do it.
Someone else can't sign for me.
[Nice... as long as it's not me.]
- It could be a very simple mission.
- But they're not going to put you in danger.
I bet you're going to have to play
some sort of a kissing game with the tiger.
[Wait and see what sort of an unforgettable
memory you'll be making with the tiger.]
[What will be the second animal?]
A deer!
[A gentle deer-
Everyone's fingers start to fly around.]
[Deer mission- Captain Park.]
- Yes!
- Hey, what's this 'Deer Kwang Seun'?
[Kwang Soo's typo.]
- An alligator?
- It's an alligator.
It's an alligator!
[Wow, that's coming out strong!]
No, I didn't do it!
[Kkuk signs Kwang Soo up
for this particular mission.]
- The alligator mission is Kwang Soo's.
- Nice!
I think I know what it's going to be.
Stick your head in the alligator's mouth.
- No, there's no way.
- Keep your head in the mouth for 5 seconds.
I can't do the snake.
I seriously can't even touch the snake.
I can't even touch it with my finger.
Snake, Jong Kook?
- Snake Gary.
- Who did that!
[Blank Ji looking after her
Monday boyfriend.]
Why are you doing this to me!
[Snake mission- Gary.]
Hey, flower snake! (a.k.a. Gold digger)
I already have a snake of my own here!
- We'll get started with you two first.
- Okay.
[Tiger Ha Ha and Deer Captain Park
to head off into the safari first.]
I'm so scared.
A tiger? I'm going to lose my mind.
How did I end up with the tiger?
- Which one of these do we take?
- You'll personally drive this car.
We have to drive ourselves?
Are we going in the same car?
I'm personally going to drive the car?
[Special feature of the Taman Safari is the
experience of driving themselves around.]
How in the world am I going to do
a tiger mission?
I'm seriously going to lose my mind.
A tiger!
I'm going to lose my mind.
Seriously, a tiger?
Ugh, that Lee Kwang Soo!
But a tiger may not be so bad.
Lion, alligator...
they're all pretty much the same.
Let's just go.
I can't do a snake either.
There's not a single thing that
I can do in this place.
If it's a safari...
then we're driving through areas
where the animals roam free?
I feel like I'm going to have to drive
to where all the wild beasts are.
- It's a baby zoo.
- Baby zoo can't be that bad.
Don't you think that it'll be safer here?
I wonder if the tiger slept well last night.
I hope that he's in a good mood.
Wow, we're already in the thick
of the jungle.
[Safari Adventure!]
[In the thick of the wild...
into the heart of the jungle.]
- You may stop the car now.
- What?
It's time for your mission.
[Ha Ha's tiger mission.]
[Take a picture of yourself which also
shows the tiger's full frontal features.]
That's just absurd!
How can I take a selca with a tiger?
What if in my attempt to take the picture...
I could end up losing my head!
[You want me to take a picture of myself
with this fearsome beast?]
Just keep the doors locked
and take the picture from the car.
- Ah, from inside the car?
- Yes.
- So I'm going to stay in the car?
- Yes, take the picture from inside the car.
I'm so relieved to hear that.
[Tears of relief.]
Okay, everyone shut your doors.
And roll up all your windows.
Lock all your doors too.
Okay, we're all set!
No, this is just fine.
Whew!
[In a much better mood!
Now off to start the real safari tour.]
Look, there's a hippo.
I've never seen a hippo up close like this.
Hey, hippo!
Hi, hippo.
[Can you throw me something to eat?]
Wow, I've never seen these animals
so close up like this before.
[First time seeing these wild beasts
up close in person.]
Wow, they must be the baby hippos.
They're so cute.
If we jump over that ridge,
then we'll be able to touch those hippos.
Look!
It's a camel!
Wow, look at them!
They're just freely roaming around.
[What's that loud mouthed penguin
doing here?]
This really is a safari.
Wow!
That's a rhino over there!
Wow, that's big enough to
send our car flying into the air.
Look, it's a deer!
They're headed our way!
[Animals are walking right past all the cars.]
They're all just freely roaming around here.
If that had been a tiger,
I don't think I could've taken the picture.
What am I going to do?
The deers are right over here.
Oh my goodness.
[Totally fascinated.]
Wow, look at this!
What if it kicks our car?
Wow, this is unreal.
[Deer mission- Captain Park.
Discovers a group of deer.]
Aren't those deer over there?
- Park Ji Sung, here's your deer mission.
- Okay.
[Park Ji Sung's deer mission.]
[Take a picture of yourself with
a deer and also a zebra from the car.]
What other animals do you see listed
on the card besides the deers?
Zebras.
- The deer are in this area.
- Okay.
And in order to find the zebras,
you have to drive past the wild beast zone.
You have to drive past the
wild beast zone...
[You're telling me that I have to
drive past these guys?]
But there was no mention
of any zebras before.
You can't do this to me now!
That's just a guarantee...
I have to take a selca?
(Selca= A picture of yourself.)
[Captain Park immediately makes an attempt
to carry out his mission.]
Hey, deer!
Come over here.
[Tries to engage the deer in a conversation.]
I'm for sure going to fail this mission.
[What is he babbling about?]
Can you guys get up from over there?
Come here!
Hi!
Come here.
All these deer...
I think these are all just baby deer.
[He only sees small baby deer.]
I need to go look for some bigger deer.
Bye guys!
You guys are too little,
so I don't think you guys will work.
I'll be back some other time.
Bye!
Wow, all these deer.
This mission is too much.
But you were happy about
having picked the deer mission.
Yes, I'm fine.
If I fail the mission,
then I'll just pay the penalty for it.
Just to warn you,
it's our 200th episode special penalty.
[200th episode...
A penalty like you've never seen before.]
Yes, 200th episode special penalty.
[Unaware of what the penalty is,
but he's getting a bad feeling about it.]
[Meanwhile, Kwang Soo arrives
in the alligator zone.]
What is this?
Why is that guy missing his head?
[It's just a special photo zone to
create an optical illusion...]
It's a real alligator!
[A real alligator!]
[A terrifying visual-
A fierce looking herd of alligators.]
[Mental stupor]
What is he doing over there?
[But... what is he doing over there?]
[Why is he tying a ribbon
onto an alligator's tail?]
Are you okay?
[This portion of the show was filmed under
the supervision of trained professionals.]
It's a real alligator.
[Such a frightening visual that all he can
do is repeat that they're real alligators.]
[Welcome, Giraffe.]
Succeed the mission by untying the ribbon
that's tied around the alligator's tail.
[Why... are you doing this to me?]
It's a very gentle alligator.
How do you know if that
alligator is gentle or not?
[Gentle?]
They're nice animals.
How do you know if he's nice or not?
What if he's in a bad mood today?
What if it got into trouble
with its mother yesterday?
What if he got into a fight
with his girlfriend yesterday?
[I live a celibate life.]
It's moving!
[That's because he's alive.]
This is a real crocodile!
Very nice.
- Want to come?
- He's not a doll?
- Is it a real crocodile?
- Yes.
[Just accept your reality.]
[I won't cause you any trouble.]
No crocodile?
- No crocodile?
- No, don't worry.
Wow, look at my goosebumps.
It's staring at me.
It's staring at me right now.
[Meanwhile, while Kwang Soo is starting to
have a mental breakdown in alligator zone...]
[Seal mission- Ji Hyo.
What does her mission entail?]
What's this?
[Jump!]
[Flies out of the water
like a bolt of lightning...]
[and grabs the fish out of
the trainer's mouth.]
[Oh my God!]
[The seal mission that she thought
was going to be easy...]
You're telling me that I need to do
what he just did?
Okay.
[Okay, seal, let's do this.]
Name?
Hiromi?
Hiromi!
[First introduces herself to Hiromi.]
Hi.
Hiromi, give me a kiss.
[I like this girl.]
Hiromi.
Would you like to dance with me?
[Asks Hiromi for a dance.]
[Oh!]
[Succeeds on her first attempt!]
[Blank Ji immediately earns the trust
and affection of shy Hiromi.]
Hiromi, I love you.
[Hiromi and Blank Ji's dance time.]
[Hiromi's sign of affection-
Ends the dance with a kiss on the cheek.]
Thank you.
I love you.
[Greets Boto, whom she'll be doing
the fish feeding mission with.]
Boto, it's just me.
It's just me, okay?
[Blank Ji starts to climb up the ladder
without an ounce of hesitation.]
[At the tippy top of the ladder.]
Boto.
Let's get this done on our first try.
Boto, fighting!
[Blank Ji signals the start of
the mission to Boto.]
[Here he comes...]
[Boto flies straight into
the air like a bullet.]
[Will Blank Ji succeed her mission?]
This sounds like a pretty fun mission.
Look at him yawning.
How cute are you!
[Suk Jin attempts to get on friendly terms
with the orangutan.]
- Chelsea.
- Chelsea?
Oh, Chelsea.
Hi, Chelsea.
- How old?
- She's four years old.
- Four? Okay, four.
[Four year old orangutan, Chelsea.]
She's like a little baby.
She just jumped into my arms.
Chelsea.
Sweet Chelsea.
[Daddy Big-nose croons to Chelsea
as he would a baby.]
What are you eating?
What's that?
[When did she get the mic cover in her mouth?]
That's my mic.
No, you can't eat that.
That's for my mic.
You can't eat that.
That's dangerous for you to eat.
It's dangerous for you to eat that.
Want to do some jump rope?
Jump rope.
[He's attempting to do jump roping-
one of Chelsea's favorite activities.]
No, come over here, Chelsea.
Come over here.
[Chelsea is unable to comprehend
what is going on.]
No, not that. That's not for you to eat.
Come here, Chelsea.
Chelsea.
[Let go of me, Mister!]
Come here, Chelsea.
[A free spirited bohemian Chelsea.]
Don't climb up so high.
What if you fall down?
[He's actually worried that
an orangutan will fall off the post.]
Chelsea.
Chelsea, where are you?
Wow, I totally feel like
I'm chasing after a little kid.
No, you can't do that.
Don't do that.
Chelsea, come here.
No, you can't do that.
Hey, stop that!
[Chelsea finds a can of formula
in the cabinet!]
[Attempts to eat the formula
right out of the can.]
She found the can of formula.
Hey!
No, you can't do that.
Wow, unbelievable.
Wow, I feel like I'm raising another child.
Come on, let's get out.
There you go.
Here we go.
No, you can't go back in there.
Please!
Come on, Chelsea.
Come here.
[Please leave me alone, Daddy!]
We have to do our mission.
Come here, Chelsea.
[Captain Park is on the search for
bigger deer he can take a selca with.]
- Are those deers down there?
- Yes.
Are they all deers?
Come here.
I'm putting all my hope in you guys.
You guys are my only hope.
Yeah, come here.
Come here.
Come here, you guys.
[What's that all about?]
Want some carrots?
[Captain Park tries to lure them over
with a bunch of carrots.]
Hey, guys?
You over there.
The one who looks like the king.
You have to show some interest in these.
Don't you want to eat the carrots?
Guys.
Look, I've got carrots.
Here, come and get these carrots.
[Just then... a deer shows some interest.]
No, you're way too short!
Do you think that you could climb up here?
Here, come eat your carrots.
I'll give you one.
You can eat this carrot
and lure other deer over here.
[Asks the deer to tell the others
how tasty the carrot is.]
Hey, big kid.
Aren't you hungry?
[But the one that Captain Park wants
is the king deer.]
Yeah, I'm talking to you.
I really like you.
Don't you want to try one of these?
[Captain Park is actually
quite the chatterbox.]
I've got delicious carrots for you.
You're too greedy.
Why are you eating so much?
You need to share with your friends.
[He's all of a sudden trying to teach
the deer some manners.]
I'll give you one too.
These are delicious.
I need to get a bunch of them here
to get that big one's interest.
Here, one for you too.
There you go.
But why is it that only the little ones
are coming up to the car?
Can you get those guys over here?
I need those guys over here.
[Guys?]
You actually look rather big.
Come over here for a minute.
Yeah, I think you might be big enough.
[Discovers a bigger sized deer.]
Can you stick your head out further?
Don't you want this? There you go.
A little bit more.
Put your feet up on the car.
Come on, use your head.
[Tries to convince the deer
into using its head.]
You're going to give up?
You're giving up on me right now?
What are you so afraid of?
Here it is right here.
[Psychologically challenging the deer
as if he's training his soccer juniors.]
You just tasted these yummy carrots, right?
Come and I'll give you more carrots.
We just need to take a picture together.
Yeah, just a picture.
Come here.
I just need a shot of your head.
Just a shot of your head.
Come on.
Here, try a taste of this.
I feel bad about teasing you
with this carrot too.
Can you try doing this with me?
You just need to stick your head in.
Can you come forward a little bit more?
Here.
This isn't strong enough to withstand you.
Okay, just your head.
Okay, I just need your head.
A little bit more.
Just a little bit more.
I just need to take a picture of us.
Do you not want to take a picture with me?
You keep that up,
and you'll be licking my face next.
Hey.
It would've been easier to kiss the deer
for my mission.
Right?
There you go.
Guys!
Don't you guys want some carrots?
Here's a carrot.
Come get your carrot.
You big kids over there.
[Back to advertising his tasty carrots.]
Hey, horns!
Please, come here, horn.
[Who keeps calling me?]
The deer with the horns.
Can you please look at me?
I've got a carrot over here for you.
I think I'm going to fail my mission.
I shouldn't have picked the deer mission.
[Then are the other animals any better?]
[Snake mission- Gary.]
Do not be afraid.
Think of myself as just another snake.
I've always loved snakes.
I've always been one with the snakes.
Relax.
It's all about mind control.
[His terrifying phobia of snakes-
A battle he must win against himself.]
I love snakes.
I've always slithered around
like a snake.
I... I've always loved snakes!
[His mind control flies out the window
as soon as he sees the snakes.]
I love snakes!
[Dance of the tongue in welcome.]
What am I going to do!
Is it dangerous?
- No, not dangerous.
- No dangerous?
Really?
You're a liar!
You're a liar.
- What's my mission?
- Here's your mission.
[What is Gary's snake mission?]
My hands are shaking so badly right now.
Succeed the mission by
wrapping one snake around your waist
and wrap another around your neck,
and kiss the snake wrapped around your neck.
How do you expect me to kiss a snake!
[Doesn't everyone like kissing a snake?]
How old is the snake?
- It's four years old.
- Four years?
- It's a baby?
- Yes, it's a baby.
Okay, a baby.
A baby?
Baby, I'm Gary.
We are friends, okay?
I should try touching it first.
It feels like there's something
on the underside.
It's actually surprisingly soft.
- Is it a cobra?
- No, it's nice.
[It's a yellow python constrictor.]
How do I do this?
[I want to cry!]
[There's another man who's close
to crying right at that moment.]
[Sitting next to him...]
[is a lion king.]
[This is Taman Safari's hottest attraction-
Gets to take a picture with a real lion.]
[With the exception of this one man.]
Wait!
Did you all just see that?
[Even the divine Mr. Capable
can have that terrified look on his face.]
He just opened his mouth at me.
He just... he just
opened his mouth at me.
[He's a bigger scaredy cat than he looks.]
He's not dangerous.
[Come on, Tiger.]
[Jong Kook's lion mission-
Brush the lion's mane ten times.]
Everyone!
Everyone.
That's just seriously...
That wasn't just a yawn.
Anyone who saw that would say...
What do you think of what just happened?
He opened his mouth at me
as if he was ready to bite me.
He was about to lunge for my hand.
- It looked like a yawn to me.
- How was that just a yawn?
[Even the camera PD's are on our side.]
[Just trust me.]
I really thought...
that this mission wasn't
going to be difficult.
I really thought that.
[On the same token, there's
another bewildered man nearby.]
Chelsea, why are you so strong?
Chelsea.
Chelsea!
I'm highly sensitized right now.
I don't want anyone to make any moves.
[What's he doing?]
I think I need to disguise myself.
[Bushman?]
Do I look like a tree?
- Do I look like a tree?
- No.
- No, you don't look like a tree.
- They're asleep?
- Yeah.
I should go untie the ribbon
while it's asleep.
[Attempting to untie the ribbon from
the tail of a sleeping alligator.]
[Nerve wrecking moment.]
[I've got my eye on you!]
[The ribbon is in his hand!]
[Or not.]
[His hand isn't moving
like his mind wants him to.]
[Just untie the ribbon already!]
[Makes another attempt.]
[Succeeds at untying the knot.]
[Now he just needs to pull it free!]
[A total of three ribbons to untie.
Succeeds at untying the first ribbon.]
I feel really dizzy right now.
[Meanwhile...]
[Haroro is so engrossed in the sights that
he's almost forgotten about his mission.]
This is so amazing.
[Slowly drives right past a real zebra.]
I can't believe how close he was.
That was a zebra.
Wow, it's unreal to see an animal like that
so up close like we did, isn't it?
I feel like I'm dreaming.
This is crazy.
[Finally arrives at the gates of
the wild beast zone.]
Wow, I'm a little scared right now.
There are wild beasts in this area.
I should roll up my window.
Wow, that's a lion!
Oh my gosh.
Did everyone lock up their doors?
[Frozen in place.]
[The king of the jungle-
The lion is sitting right in front of him!]
Don't look over at those guys.
[The formidable force of the lions.]
They're not dogs, they're real live lions.
[A huge herd of lions...
Right in front of his eyes!]
I've never seen a lion
so up close like this before.
I'm about to break out in hives.
I have to be in this zone to
get a picture with a tiger, right?
[Haroro is driving past these beasts
in a speedy pace.]
Oh my goodness!
They're all out in the open?
[The real experience of driving past the lions
that roam free without any boundaries.]
Are those guys gentle?
[Haroro finally arrives
at entrance of the tigers' den.]
Look, it's a tiger!
[It's a tiger!]
[Full of frightening charisma.]
It's a real live tiger.
There's a real live tiger
right in front of my eyes.
Wow, it's a real tiger!
Hey, do you see that?
It's a real live tiger!
Look, it's a snow tiger!
How am I going to take a selca
with that?
It really is a tiger.
Wow, I'm just so fascinated that
I don't even feel any fear right now.
Look at that tiger over there.
Wow, there's another tiger
right in front of us.
[A surreal experience that
one only dreams about.]
They won't come near the car
just like those deer.
[Who dares to come here!]
There it is.
[Tiger mission- Take a selca with
the tiger's face alongside of his own.]
No, don't go away.
I can't even really see.
How am I going to do this?
[In order to succeed his mission,
he'll have to lure the tiger over to the car.]
There it is!
It's coming closer.
[The snow tiger is making its way
closer to the car!]
[The tigers are slowly starting to
surround Ha Ha's car.]
[Just then... the snow tiger starts
to approach even closer.]
[Right outside Ha Ha's window!]
[All his fear dissipates!
Haroro lures it even closer to him!]
Even though I'm scared,
I'm not going to get flustered.
[Haroro is in the midst of a tiger field.]
Snow tiger,
I came all the way here from Korea.
Do you know the friendly tiger
from our '88 Olympics?
Hey, can you look towards me once more?
Wow, look at the size of his paws.
Hey, look over here.
[Snow tiger slinks away
after his photo session.]
All these pictures are a total success.
Look, this is a good one too.
[Verifying the pictures he took
of himself with the tiger.]
Success... success...
[Wow, a complete success!]
- Ha Ha, you have succeeded your mission.
- Okay!
[Ha Ha clears his tiger mission.
He is now exempt from final penalty.]
Thanks so much!
[Thank you, Tiger!]
Wow, I never knew that I could be so brave.
[Back to Ji Hyo
and her mission with the seals.]
[Will Boto be able to snatch the fish
from Blank Ji's mouth?]
[Boto was a little too short on his jump.]
Should I bend down even further?
[Blank Ji has to bend a little further down.]
Sorry, Boto.
Sorry, I'll just give it to you.
[Gets herself back in position, and
makes a second attempt at the mission.]
[An energetic jump.]
[Will he get it this time?]
[Blank Ji and Boto- A perfect success!]
[Even the trainer is impressed.]
[A perfect harmony between
Blank Ji and Boto.]
Boto, I'll give you another fish.
Boto!
[A fish treat in joy.]
I love you!
[The Blank Ji Show now comes to a close.]
Song Ji Hyo always succeeds her mission.
Why are you doing the hoola hoop in
the eagle training zone?
I'm absolutely terrified right now, Ji Hyo.
Why do I have to do the hoola hoop
with the eagle sitting on my head?
[A majestic flight...
right onto the top of Yoo Hyuk's head.]
Hang on.
[Must start doing the hoola hoop
before the eagle flies away.]
I'm sorry, but I need you to stay still.
[Ah... he only got one full swing
before the eagle flew away.]
That is one awful trainer out there.
- You just be quiet over there!
- Can we get a bigger eagle on his head?
Seriously... please.
Help me out just this once.
- Help me out just this once.
- Can you use a larger sized eagle?
- You just be quiet. What are you doing?
- I saw a really big one over there.
Eagle, he's not your food.
You can't snatch him away, okay?
- Hey, you just be quiet!
- I wonder what Kwang Soo is up to.
- Have fun hoola hooping with the eagle.
- Seriously, that girl...
[Takes another flight.]
[A last minute U-turn.]
[This eagle is going to bring
the Grasshopper down to his knees.]
I'm breaking out in cold sweat over here.
My whole body is covered in cold sweat.
Alligator, there's your food over there.
- Alligator, there's your food over there.
- Stop doing that and just go away!
- That's a giraffe!
- No, I'm not a giraffe!
- Giraffe!
- No, seriously! Stop doing that, Ji Hyo.
Seriously, stop doing that!
I have to get two more.
[Still has two more ribbons left to untie.]
[Trying to untie the ribbon...]
[While keeping a close eye on the alligator.]
[Using a stick to
pull the ribbon off the tail.]
[He's got it!]
Hey, don't go over there!
No, don't go that way!
You have to go the other way!
[Giraffe almost headed straight
toward another alligator!]
- That could've been big trouble.
- What were you thinking heading that way!
You should've come back this
way, you fool!
Anyways, good luck,
and don't go back to the other alligators.
- Okay.
- That was your second one?
- I just need to get one more.
- Good luck, Kwang Soo.
Let's try to get this done, okay?
Okay, grab the ball.
Now throw it back to me.
No, it's not something for you to eat.
You're going to pop the ball!
Come on, that's the only ball we have.
[Mission- Catch the ball that
the orangutan throws in his direction.]
[Can never predict in which direction
the orangutan will throw the ball.]
Are you playing with me right now?
Okay, look over here.
[Another attempt.]
Grab the ball.
There you go.
Okay, there you go.
Now throw me the ball.
Stop teasing me and just
throw me the ball.
No, no more teasing.
Throw it to me.
No, throw it gently.
Throw the ball!
[Can never predict his throws.]
He's seriously so smart.
How am I going to get this done?
Okay, let's try it again.
[These animals are unknowingly making
it very tough for all these members.]
[Gritting down on his teeth
to brush the mane ten times.]
[That feels really nice.]
I did it.
[Kkuk succeeds his mission of
brushing the lion's mane ten times.]
Thank you.
I'm going to be going now.
[Goodbye, Tiger.]
[Flustered Kkuk behaves strangely by climbing
over the fence instead of using the entrance.]
Bye.
[Kkuk also escapes from having to
pay the ultimate penalty.]
I love you.
I've always loved you.
Why isn't this one getting close to me?
[But he's already past the point
of any mind control.]
Come here.
Okay, I'm going to do it.
[Gary's kiss with a snake!]
I did it!
[Snake kiss... successfully passed!]
Hurry it get them off of me!
I love you guys, and thanks.
[I love you, but please get away from me!]
Please get it off of me right now!
[A playful snake trainer.]
Thank you.
Thank you, snake.
Oh, my baby.
I feel much closer to it now.
I'm curious to know
what my penalty is going to be.
I'm already thinking of what my penalty is
going to be before the mission is even over.
Zebras!
I finally found them!
You guys are my last hope.
I have delicious carrots for you guys.
[All movement is ceased.]
You're not a statue, are you?
Okay, you're not a statue.
But can you fit your big head through here?
[The zebra sticks its head in through
the window without any hesitation.]
Wow, look at your mouth.
No, not me.
You can't eat me.
No, it's not me.
Don't blow your nose on me.
Come back here.
I've got your carrot right here.
Stick your head in through the window,
and you'll have your carrot.
What's wrong with you?
I've got your carrot right here.
[Fails the first attempt- Turned
its head away right before the shot.]
I don't think I got the shot.
[Fail! Both of their faces must be
fully captured in order for it to count.]
You want another one?
[Stamps down his fear
to make another attempt.]
Come on, I told you not to
breathe on me.
Hey, where did you go?
[Full after his carrot snack,
the zebra just walks away.]
Wow, this is really hard.
[Unsure of what to do.]
[There's only three minutes
left on the clock!]
[Jae Suk successfully completes
his eagle mission.]
[Sharing his joy with the trainer
and the eagle.]
Can I get going now?
- Four are still missing.
- Four members still need to make it back.
[Must make it back to the meeting spot
before the time is over to be validated.]
[Just then, a bus drives by in the back.]
Than man totally ruined it.
Mister!
I almost had it.
[Come on, ribbon...]
[Smile, zebra.]
Did I get it?
[Unties the last ribbon... and runs out
of there without even a backwards glance!]
I did it.
[Kwang Soo's alligator mission-
Successfully unties three ribbons.]
I did it.
Thank you!
[Run away, my friend!]
Run!
[Must run if they want to avoid
having to pay the ultimate penalty!]
- You've succeeded your mission.
- Yes, I did it!
[Captain Park finally succeeds his mission.]
Here, enjoy your carrot.
[But they must arrive back at the spot
before the time is up to be validated!]
[The Captain is now the only one left!]
Can you pull your head back out?
Is it over already?
What is Ji Sung's mission
that he still isn't back yet?
- Ji Sung!
- Is he here?
- Did you succeed your mission?
- Kwang Soo!
What's that?
What are you doing?
[The moment he's back, he attempts
to take a selca with a giraffe.]
[Every members successfully
completes their safari mission.]
[All are exempt from the
skydiving penalty.]
[Since we didn't get to do the skydiving,
be sure that it'll be coming your way soon!]
[Don't walk, but Run!
Already the 200th episode.]
I truly don't know how we've made it
to our 200th episode already.
Yes, you're right.
But we've had help from a countless
number of great guests.
We were only able to make it here with help
of great friends like Park Ji Sung.
Ji Sung especially is always such
a great guest to have on the show.
Yes, we're always so grateful.
[Top notch guests who came to share
our joy during the past 200 episodes.]
[But above all, to our amazing viewers who
allowed us to continue our run...]
Let's aim for 1,000 episodes.
We will continue to run hard
every week for you.
We sincerely thank everyone for allowing us
to run every week for the past 200 episodes.
Thank you!
[The only way we know how to show our
gratitude to the viewers is to keep running.]
Subtitles by DramaFever