Running Man
[Running Man presents...]
[Starring Yoo Jae Suk.]
[Ji Suk Jin]
[Song Ji Hyo]
[Kim Jong Kook]
[Kang Gary]
[Ha Ha]
[And Lee Kwang Soo]
[Frozen in a cryogenic state
for hundreds of years.]
[They are being awakened
from their slumber.]
[A hero's resurrection.]
[The heroes are now awakened from
their frozen slumber.]
[Breathing in the outside air for
the first time in hundreds of years.]
[And in the chamber next to his...]
[Another hero begins to stir...]
Stop pretending to be asleep.
- Ugh, seriously.
- That was a nice, long nap.
- Wonderwoman!
- Superwoman!
- How am I a Superwoman?
- I mean, Superman!
What's with this guy?
[A rather suspicious looking hero?]
[Just get back in there...]
- Hey, wait!
- What?
Why are you trying to
shut me in there?
It's an Avatar!
[And a visually shocking hero
awakens from his slumber.]
Avatar!
- Come out here.
- Wow, he looks like the real Avatar.
[Almost as if he jumped out of
the movie screen.]
[Even the awkward movements
are perfectly reenacted.]
Avatar!
Avatar.
[Pull yourself together!]
- Why are you hitting me?
- Pull yourself together.
[Just checking to see if you're
Kwang Soo or not...]
It's Son Oh Gong!
[No need for any guesses as to
who this is supposed to be!]
[The super board.]
What did you say?
[May look like Sun Oh Gong,
but acts like Sa Oh Jung.]
Who's he supposed to be?
Is he Hong Gil Dong?
It's Hong Gil Dong!
[The last and the final hero who throws
the others into a state of fear.]
- Wow, Jong Kook is perfect for that.
- He's the perfect fit for it.
[The charisma...]
[The toughest character of
all the X-Men...]
He's Wolverine!
[No, he's not Elvis Presley.]
- He never changes.
- I'm the oldest out of everyone here.
I don't even know how old I am.
I'm from another planet.
- I'm the richest one here.
- I'm the tallest one here.
- I'm a monkey.
- You're a monkey.
- Why am I not human?
- Let's get out of here and get some air.
I'm going to fly out of here.
[But none of these heroes are able to fly,
and they seem to be rather powerless...]
I see that none of you possesses
any special powers.
- I will show...
- What is he doing?
- What was that?
- What are you doing?
- Are you trying to fly?
Doing that usually drills
a hole into the ground.
All of my powers have disappeared.
These are supposed to be knife-like claws,
but they've been turned into wooden sticks.
- See?
- That feels good, like a back scratcher!
- Really?
- Hey, scratch my back, too!
- Okay.
- What happened here?
[What could've happened to these heroes?]
Why did all our super powers disappear?
Hello everyone.
[A sudden message from
a suspicious looking hologram.]
I'm the anti-hero that placed all of you
in the frozen cryogenic state.
[An Anti-hero?]
I won't let you get away with it
once I get my hands on you.
Yoo-perman.
Jitman.
Kkuk-verine.
- Gae Oh Gong.
- Darn, I'm Gae Oh Gong!
Ha Gil Dong.
Wonder Blank.
Kwang-vatar.
If you're able to see me right now
then it must mean that you've been
awakened from your frozen state.
I bet you've noticed something unusual.
I've rid all of you of your super powers.
Darn you!
You now look like heroes
only from the outside.
- You will not get away with this.
- We don't really look like it either.
In ten hours, the meteor that's carrying all
your superpowers will fall down on Korea.
[The meteor carrying their superpowers
will land on Korea in ten hours.]
You may regain your superpowers by finding
out where the meteor will crash in ten hours.
- No!
- Do you want to get punched?
[Only one place where
they can regain their powers.]
[They must find out where that is!]
Do you believe that you will be able to
find and regain your superpowers?
And... Kwang-vatar.
I want only you to step forward.
- I want only you to step forward.
- What have you done now?
- What did you do, Kwang-vatar?
- Step forward.
- You're up to something, aren't you?
- I'm not doing anything.
Did you plan all this?
Are you the anti-hero?
Those aren't Kwang-vatar's ears.
- What are they?
- They're some fake ears.
I really haven't been able to hear
anything that you guys have been saying.
The way for you to regain
your superpowers are...
What are his superpowers?
It's just his tall height, right?
- He's strength, I think. What did you hear?
- He falls in love at the end.
- No, I didn't.
- You didn't hear anything?
- I did, but I don't think it's important.
- You can't tell us about it, can you?
I will make you pay, Kwang-vatar,
as soon as I get my powers back.
Isn't his comment about how it's
not that important just absurd?
- We don't believe you.
- Don't say things like that.
[What message was Kwang-vatar
given from the Anti-hero?]
[A challenging hero mission that only
the truest of all heroes can pass.]
[Find the unknown location and regain powers
by completing various heroic missions.]
[Kwang-vatar is very quick to adapt
to the earthly way of living.]
I'm sorry, but I really can't get wet in
the rain with the way I'm dressed right now.
My makeup is starting to smear
and wash off.
Successfully complete the hero help
mission to gain access to your next location.
- Where? SBS?
- Hero help mission?
[Complete the hero help mission within
time limit given at a specific location.]
Okay, I understand.
If I had my powers,
I could be there in less than a minute.
[When the heroes are powerless,
they resort to taking a cab.]
I have to take a cab?
While looking like this?
I have to take a cab looking like this?
I'm going to scare them.
[You're going to make the
cab drivers faint.]
Hello, can I get in your cab?
See?
He doesn't look happy about it.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Would you like for me to drive?
Should I just sit back and stay quiet?
[Kkuk-verine must take the public bus.]
What if I get beat up by people?
How am I supposed to
go around looking like this?
The way for you to regain
your superpowers...
Why was I the only one?
[The cab isn't moving very fast.]
If it was back in the day,
I would've just flown there.
You dare laugh?
You're lucky that I've lost my powers.
If I still had my powers, then you'd
be paying a dear price for that.
Do you have money for the cab fare?
[Guess he doesn't have the money?]
[Sangahm Building]
It's raining quite a bit.
[The hero's cape also works as an umbrella.]
Where do I go now?
I know that I'm supposed to go
somewhere and rescue something...
[He must find someone who's in
need for some sort of help.]
This really isn't my style.
People might even mistake me
for Spiderman.
People might not realize that I'm Superman
because I've lost all my powers.
[People are bewildered at seeing
him dressed up in his hero costume.]
Do you need any help with anything?
Is there anything I can help you with?
I'm Superman.
I can help you with anything
that you need.
I'm Superman.
Do you need help with anything?
- You don't?
- No, I have to get to work.
Everyone's really busy right now,
and no one seems to need any help.
[Everyone's declining Yoo-perman's
offer to help.]
Wait.
Hi everyone.
[Discovers an excited group of students.]
Hello, I'm Yoo-perman.
Wait.
Wait, everyone.
No, wait.
I had forgotten for a moment.
- Why aren't you guys in school?
- We're out on a field trip.
[The students are out on a field trip.]
- Study hard, okay?
- Okay!
Don't get wet in the rain,
and study hard.
Don't get wet in the rain.
[Screams of cheer that he's hearing
for the first time in hundreds of years.]
Hello.
[Yoo-perman's exiting flight.]
[Kwang-vatar's in the city.]
They're all staring at me funny.
They're looking at me like I'm a freak!
They're all avoiding me.
They don't even think it's funny,
they're looking at me like I'm a freak.
They're all looking at me
like I'm a freak.
[Entering the parking lot where he heard
someone is in need of some help.]
- Jong Kook!
- Who is that?
- Please help!
- With what?
[Hero, help me!
Finds people in distress.]
We have to get to the airport for
our honeymoon, and our car is stuck.
- Please help us get our car out.
- You want your car out?
You want me to get your car out?
- Yes, this red car.
- This one?
- You want it freed?
[Kkuk-verine's mission-
Free the newlywed's car!]
I'm not as strong right now because I just
woke up from a hundred year slumber.
I wonder if pushing will help
get the car freed.
- What are we going to do?
- How did your car get stuck like this?
- Yes, the red car.
- I don't know how it's going to work.
Wait, how am I going to do this?
I would've just lifted it back in the day.
I would've just lifted this out of the way
and set it down over there.
Please help free our car.
- What is a vending machine doing here?
- What am I going to do?
- Hello.
- Help.
- What am I going to do?
- What is it?
I was just trying to get my change
and ended up dropping the keepsake
that my son gave me.
- You dropped your keepsake?
- Yes.
- Where did you drop it?
- It rolled underneath the vending machine.
Please help me find it, Avatar.
- What am I going to do?
- Can you hold up my umbrella for me?
Just put your faith in me,
and I'll get it for you.
- Please help me.
- The vending machine...
[The giant hero attempts to lift up
the vending machine.]
Just a little bit more.
Come on, Avatar.
I don't think you're going to get it.
- How am I going to get it?
- How will I ever get it back?
- Are you sure that it's under here?
- Yes, I saw it roll under the machine.
[Of all the coins under the machine,
only one of them is her keepsake coin.]
Look, it's all smearing off.
My skin underneath is starting to show.
If your skin starts to show,
then do you start to lose your powers?
No, it's not like that.
It won't make me lose my powers.
[Back to Yoo-perman in Sangahm.]
There's nothing special to being a hero.
This is the sort of things that I help with.
[This hero is busy massaging her neck
while gnawing on a hotdog on a stick.]
Yes, it feels good, doesn't it?
You're really tense in the neck.
- Are you stressed about something?
- Yes.
[Helping the woman de-stress.]
- How does it feel?
- Yes, it feels good.
Yes, it feels good, doesn't it? But I
must get back to my own work now.
Goodbye.
I wonder if anyone else
needs any help.
Help me, Hero!
Do you need my help?
What is it?
- Please help me find my younger sibling.
- What?
I'm supposed to meet my little sister here,
and I haven't seen her in a long time.
- But I can't seem to find her anywhere.
- You need to find your younger sister?
- What is her name?
- Her name is, Kim Da Hae.
- Da Hae?
- Yes.
You need me to help you find Da Hae?
- Can't you just call her?
- I forgot my phone at home.
Really?
Okay, you need help finding Da Hae?
- Okay, don't worry.
- She looks a lot like me.
- Is she your twin?
- She looks very much like me.
Really? Okay, I got it.
Is she wearing pants or a skirt?
- I have no idea what she may be wearing.
- Okay, I understand.
- How long is her hair?
- It's been a while since I've seen her...
Does she like to go heavy
with her makeup or no?
- Is she wearing a shoulder bag?
- I have no idea.
We don't have the time for this.
Just go and find her.
I, Superman, will find Da Hae for you.
Do not worry.
The time has come for me to
finally get to work for real.
[Superman is on the way!]
[But how is he ever going to find
Da Hae in the midst of all these people?]
[At a farm field in Goyang.]
Please allow me to help you, Sir!
I'm Wonderwoman!
What can I help you with?
I'm planning on building a 60 story
hotel on this plot of land.
Really?
Wow, you must be rich.
I buried my deed to the land here
somewhere, but I can't seem to find it now.
[In this huge plot of land?]
- So I was hoping that you could...
- I'll help you!
- I'll find the deed for you.
- Yes, I need to find my deed.
- It's very important that I find it.
- Yes, you'd need it to construct your hotel.
I've already prepared everything
you'd need to help you with your task.
[Shall we start digging?]
[Enters the field with
the boots on her feet.]
Wonderwoman loves to help people.
[Energetically lifts up the shovel.]
This is a very wide space.
Sir.
[Starts the digging in the light rain.]
Wonderwoman...
can do this.
Why are there so many rocks?
I need to find the deed to the land.
[Dig... dig... dig some more.]
[Where in the world is the deed?]
Why am I digging in the dirt
on a rainy day like this?
I wasn't like this 400 years ago.
Back then, with just the flick of a finger...
I would've shaken up this
whole mountain.
Gather up the strength I had
400 years ago...
All the dirt... lift away!
[Nothing's happening...]
Hey, are you guys looking
down on me!
I'm a very capable person!
[This is what you call getting dissed...]
Stop barking at me!
[Pitiful...]
Help me, Hero!
This is the place.
[Jitman hears their cries
for help and rushes over.]
I can hear their cries for help.
Is this the place?
Did you kids cry out for help?
Hi, I'm Jitman!
- You guys screamed out for help, right?
- Yes.
- What can I help you with?
- Read us a book!
You want me to read you a book?
Clap your hands if you want me to.
[Fill in and become a
substitute teacher for the day.]
I'll read you guys a book.
It's morning,
and it's time for you to get up.
Said mom, and that's when he woke up
and remembered yesterday's swimming time.
Swimming goggles, swimsuit, flippers,
and even a pair of nose plugs!
[The kids are immensely enjoying
Big-nose's reading session.]
But we have to wash up
before going into the pool.
- How do we clean up again?
- Nice and clean!
You have to remember to shower before
entering the pool because
you don't want to shock the heart with
the sudden coldness of the water, okay?
How do you shower before
you go into the pool?
- Nice and clean!
- There you go.
Hi.
[Now visits a classroom
full of even younger kids.]
- I have to go potty.
- You have to go to the bathroom?
Okay, I'll help you.
I'm very good with that. Let's go.
Okay, let's go to the bathroom.
Where's the bathroom?
I look cool, don't I?
- Don't I look cool?
- But you can't fly.
- You're saying that I can't fly?
- You're a bat.
No, I used to be able to fly, but I've lost
my powers and I can't fly anymore.
I used to be able to fly back in the day.
You're dressed like Batman,
but where's the Batman symbol?
No, I am Batman.
You can hit me, but you can't hurt me.
It won't hurt no matter
how hard you hit.
No, it doesn't hurt at all.
No, it doesn't hurt.
Give it a try.
It really doesn't hurt.
No, that one hurts.
[Even a hero has his weak spots...]
I hid some money away in my book
without my mom knowing.
- You want me to find that book for you?
- Yes, help me find my book.
[Help me, Ha Gil Dong-
Find the book with my money in it.]
No, that's too scary!
[Ha Gil Dong's weakness-
high places.]
Wow, this is really scary.
Come on, cheer me on.
Cheer on my name.
- Hong Gil Dong!
- It's Ha Gil Dong.
- Han Gil Dong!
Ha Gil Dong!
[Only one of these books is the correct one.]
I see something!
[Did he already discover something?]
What's this?
This is a chain letter
that started in England
and it must be passed onto the next...
Are you kidding me?
Who are you?
Tell me who you are.
- All I did was hide my money.
- Now I have to write a chain letter.
[Must make a fresh cream cake in lieu
of the pastry chef who hurt her arm.]
This is going to turn into cream?
[Must make the fresh
whipped cream with the milk.]
I look really ugly, don't I?
Wow, it's stuck in there.
[Putting the cream frosting onto the cake.]
[Gae Oh Gong's delicious looking cake.]
[Yoo-perman's mission-
Find the younger sibling, Da Hae.]
Wait... is that her?
Wait.
[Yoo-perman spots someone
and runs towards her.]
- By any chance, is your name 'Da Hae'?
- No, it's not.
It's not?
Okay, I got it.
Have a great day.
[Da Hae... just where in the
world are you?]
[Must find the woman who looks like
the woman seeking her sister.]
Okay, I must move faster.
[The same sound repeatedly
coming out of his mouth...]
You're not going to be able to
keep up with me at that rate.
Did you see that?
You won't be able to capture me on film
if you don't pick up the pace.
You're running way too fast.
Even though I may have lost my powers,
I'm still a superhero.
A normal human being like yourself
can never keep up with me.
Is that understood?
I'm going to get back to my searching,
so try to keep up with me.
I'll disappear from the camera
in the blink of an eye.
[He's something else...]
[Looks just like her!]
By any chance, are you Da Hae?
[Could this be her?]
Yes, I am.
[She's found!]
Wait, I've found you.
I've finally found Da Hae.
[A round and round ceremony.]
Okay, shall we go?
You're on your way to meet your sister?
- Yes, I am.
- Are you twins?
[Twin sisters!]
[Successfully reunites the twin sisters!]
Isn't that too weak of a greeting when
you haven't seen each other in five years?
- Thank you.
- This is your sister, correct?
- Yes, it is.
- I must go and help some more people.
[Gives him a sticker as a sign
of her appreciation.]
Thank you, hero!
I haven't given anyone a thumb kiss
to the forehead in quite some time.
I hope that you two will stay together now,
and call out for help whenever you need it.
Goodbye!
Then I'll just be going now.
[A dramatic exit every time.]
[Ask for Yoo-perman whenever
you're in need of any help.]
There aren't that many people
around because it's Monday.
[Kwang-vatar is searching for anyone
whom he could be of help to.]
I'm sorry.
[These ladies are still unaware of
the new person joining them.]
Are you busy right now?
[Attempting to start a conversation
with the lady waiting for her bus.]
[Collapses onto the bench from
the shock and fright of seeing him.]
I'm so sorry.
- Are you going somewhere?
- I'm going to school.
You don't have much time, do you?
I have to find a keepsake coin right now.
But I just don't think I can do it on my own.
Can you help me for five minutes?
[Backs away...]
- Can you help me for five minutes?
- What are you trying to do?
Can you help me for five minutes?
I need to find a coin.
But I just can't get it on my own.
[The kind students agree to help him.]
The fate of this planet depends on it!
You have to put your life on the line...
and help me find this coin.
But I have no idea where it is.
[The nuisance of a hero
relies on these ladies' help.]
[The smart student pulls out her phone
to utilize the flash for better viewing.]
If you'll flash the light under it,
then I'll see if I can find it.
- Do you see it?
- Why is this so difficult?
I've already been here for the last hour.
Everyone, I need your help.
We have to work together.
When I say 'earth', you say, 'ours!'
Earth is... ours!
Louder!
The earth is ours!
Is it in the middle?
Is that it?
[The kind students are helping him find
the coin as if it's their own job.]
- Do you see anything?
- Ma'am.
Why don't you go get yourself
a cup of coffee and come back later?
No, I have to find my coin.
There's no time to get any coffee.
Here it is!
I found it!
Here it  is!
[Could it be the real
keepsake coin this time?]
I found it!
I finally found it!
Thank you everyone!
- What's your name?
- It's Yoo Joo Yeon.
Ji Yeon and Hyun Jung...
They helped save the earth!
[Why does he keep talking
about the earth?]
The earth is a very beautiful place!
Goodbye!
Thanks again!
- Thank you so much, my hero.
- No, not at all.
- Thank you so much.
- It was my pleasure.
[Thank you, Kwang-vatar.
A sticker for your troubles.]
Goodbye, Ma'am!
Promise me you'll never lose it again!
[Kwang-vatar also successfully
completes his hero mission.]
[Meanwhile, Wonder Blank is still busy
digging in the dirt...]
I used to be pretty successful,
but I don't know what happened.
[Desperately wishing for her powers.]
I'm going to give you a command.
Tell me where the deed to the land is
and I'll forgive you
for all your incessant barking.
What did you say?
Walk 20 paces to my right,
and try digging in that area?
I'm going to remember that
bark of yours.
To the right.
One, two, three, four...
[The dogs are guiding Wonder Blank
to where the deed is buried?]
The other direction?
[Wonder Blank is starting to lose it.]
[Gained the ability to communicate with
dogs in place of her superpowers?]
Here?
Okay.
[Starts digging in the spot
where the dogs led her to...]
This is the place, you say?
If I end up finding the deed buried here
then I will hire all of you as guard dogs
in the 60 story hotel building!
[Did they lead her to the right place?]
[Can't be...]
Awesome.
Hey, I really found it!
Guys, I actually found it!
[Did she really find the deed to the land?]
[Wonder Blank seems to have
gotten it right.]
Guys, I really did find it!
[Wow, how unbelievable!]
I can't believe that actually worked,
and that I was able to find this!
Thanks!
Guys, this is all thanks to you!
Oh, it's upside down.
Guys, I'll talk to the President and I'll get
all of you hired on as security dogs!
You just wait!
[With the help of the dogs,
Wonder Blank also clears her mission.]
[But this hero still hasn't been
able to clear his mission.]
Wait, let me think.
Are you just going to keep thinking
and do nothing about this?
- We're going to miss our flight.
- Can you just take the bus there?
- But we didn't bring our bus pass.
- Seriously?
That's no good. I just woke up from sleep,
so I don't have any money either.
Okay, I think I got it.
- Okay, I got it now.
- Are you doing to do something now?
Okay, I'm going to move this
out of the way.
Get the luggage, Yoo Jin.
- Make sure the path is clear.
- Let me help you out.
You're doing great, just a bit further.
- Okay, is this good?
- Just a bit more.
Okay, I'll get the next one.
Kkuk-verine!
You're going to make it to
your honeymoon!
- Kkuk-verine!
- Okay!
[The exit is now open!]
Okay, let's push this one out.
[I will make sure that you make it
to your honeymoon!]
Thank you.
[The wedding car successfully
makes it out of the lot!]
Thank you so much!
[I'm Kkuk-verine!]
- You really are a true superhero.
- It was my pleasure.
- This is for you.
- Thank you.
[Kkuk-verine also clears his mission.]
- Enjoy your honeymoon.
- Thank you.
- Fighting!
- Thanks again!
This is the joy of being a hero.
[Everyone heads off to their next location!]
[Anti-hero will get in their way again if
everyone doesn't make it back on time...]
- I used to be able to fly.
- My joints are rusty from all the sleep.
- Yes, mine too.
- Time to rejoin the rest of the heroes!
[Will all the heroes be able to
make it back in time?]
[First hero to arrive- Yoo-perman.]
[Second hero- Wonder Blank.]
That's my theme song, Ji Hyo.
[Gae Oh Gong also makes it back in time.]
I think I understand why most
heroes suffer from depression.
Most heroes suffer from
loneliness and depression.
[The lonely lives of these heroes...]
We should form a union or something.
- No one even acknowledges us.
- I took this off, but put it back on.
- Why?
- Everyone thinks I'm Elvis Presley.
So I put this back on
even though it's uncomfortable.
Because everyone thinks that I'm
Elvis Presley when I don't wear it.
- I see what you mean. You should keep it on.
- Why does Superman look like such a brat?
And you're supposed to take your glasses
off when you transform into Superman.
My vision's just gotten bad because
I've lost all my superpowers!
And I've never seen such an ugly
looking Batman before in my life.
You have no room to talk. You're
the ugliest Superman I've ever seen.
[Just then, the biggest shocker of the day,
Kwang-vatar shows up on scene.]
I'm really curious to know how
people have been reacting to you.
They treat me like I'm a freak.
I don't think they realize
that I'm filming a show.
They pretend that they didn't even see
me even after our eyes have met.
- I think I'd react the same way.
- Have you tried going to the bathroom yet?
- Yes.
- I have to take everything off.
I had to ask someone to help me
get my zipper down earlier.
- What's going on in here?
- Ha Gil Dong!
[Just then, Ha Gil Dong arrives
past the time limit.]
- What took you so long to get here?
- He looks like a pottery seller in Damdaemun.
You look like the guy from
that show on TV.
Even though you've all cleared your missions,
you failed to show up here on time.
Why did you have to be late?
Therefore, I can only give the final
location hint to only six of you.
[One of the heroes can't be given
the hint to the final location.]
Discuss amongst yourselves and
decide which six will receive the hint.
- What's there to even decide?
- He was late, so he doesn't get it.
- What's there to even discuss?
- I really did try my best.
- All of us here did our best!
- I'm being serious right now.
- But we were still able to get here on time.
- Let's just vote on it.
- You never know what may happen.
- Tell me what you think.
Just say the name of the person
you want to eliminate.
[Relays their vote to Yoo-perman.]
Hong Gil Dong.
Okay, your vote?
Okay, two votes for Hong Gil Dong,
and one vote for Wolverine.
[Unable to maintain a straight face.]
- It wasn't me.
- What are you talking about?
Okay, Wolverine's vote.
- Batman.
- Okay, Batman.
Okay, then it's two against one against one.
- Please don't get too close.
- I have to whisper it to you.
Wolverine...
It's two against two. Two for
Hong Gil Dong and two for Wolverine.
Three votes for Wolverine.
Traitors Cross!
In that case...
- It's all up to Jae Suk now.
- I think this is going to be trouble.
I'm not sure now.
I vote for Batman.
[Ha Gil Dong- 2;
Wolverine- 3; Jitman- 2.]
[Wolverine is chosen
not to receive the hint.]
[I will make you regret this.]
[Everyone except for Kkuk-verine
receives their hint.]
[Place where the light gathers
on Han river.]
We will now move on to our
next location.
[Kwang-vatar's uncomfortable
expression on his face.]
[The information which only he received
at the opening of the show...]
[Is that information linked to
the hint that he just received?]
You can ride with someone else
if you don't want to be here.
[A quiet neighborhood in Seoul.]
I'm serious!
Just me?
Can't you be more secretive about it and
ask me quietly without others knowing?
They're all very suspicious
of me right now.
[Kwang-vatar still sticks out visually
even from a faraway distance.]
Why am I the only one being
called out?
[What's the mission that
awaits him here?]
What's that?
What is that?
[What in the world is that?]
For our next mission, we will
test our hero's level of courage.
[Test of courage?]
You're not...
[The wooden plank connecting
the two buildings together...]
[And double layers of safety net and mat...]
You expect me to cross to
the other side?
You expect me to cross to the other side?
This is a mission for Batman or Superman.
Avatar doesn't do things like that.
An Avatar doesn't have any special powers.
An Avatar is just really tall.
I'm just a tall, blue man.
[That's just absurd...]
Please get up on the roof
of the building on the right.
By myself?
[The terror that's headed their way...
Will our heroes be able to overcome it?]
How many floors are there?
This is ludicrous.
[An uneasy feeling that creeps in
while making his way up the stairs.]
An Avatar doesn't...
Wait, be careful of my ears.
My ears!
[They're blindfolding him!]
- Climb the rest with his help.
- Wait, my foot...
[He's being led away somewhere
while completely blindfolded.]
Can I give up on the mission?
No?
I have no choice but to do it?
[He will not be given any additional hints
if he gives up on the mission.]
Wow, this is too much.
Turn a little to the left.
- Where?
- One more step in front of you.
- There's a slight step down.
- A step down?
[Kwang-vatar arrives at the rooftop.]
We must be outside
because I can feel the rain.
I can't get rained on because
it'll make my makeup smear off.
- Where am I going? Where?
- Almost there.
- There's a slight step up.
- Another step up?
These steps are a bit tall.
What is this?
Is this for real?
Put your hand out to the left and
grab onto the rope beneath your hand.
- Wait, this is for real?
- There's one more step in front of you.
- You guys must be out of your minds!
- Take one more step up.
You have heard me tell you
that this is to test your courage.
If you cross the plank to the other side,
you will be given your next hint.
[Cross to the other side to win
the hint to the final location.]
[A single wooden plank connecting the two
five story buildings together.]
[Will he be able to cross it?]
Can I crawl on my knees?
- I can crawl across?
- That's up to you.
- On the other side...
- This is for real!
Why are you doing this to me?
[Don't you think that
this is being too harsh?]
If you follow the rope across,
there's a bell at the end of the rope.
If you ring the bell to signify that you've
successfully cleared your mission
that's when you can take off the blindfold.
Do not let go of the rope.
We don't want any accidents either.
This is really... Must you really go
this far to test our courage?
I'm not a superhero!
Wow, this is real.
This is for real!
[Must cross this narrow plank
while completely blindfolded.]
What am I going to do?
[All the safety precautions have
been taken.]
[Only one thin rope to help him get across.]
You must grab onto the rope, Kwang Soo.
It's dangerous, so hold onto the rope.
[The rope sways to and fro
from Kwang-vatar's weight.]
[Can't hear anything else except for
his expressions of fear and terror.]
What's this?
[Did he already arrive on the other side?]
Is this the end?
You have succeeded your mission.
You may now take off your blindfold.
[Finally takes off the blindfold...]
[Wait, what is this?]
[This is the terrorizing test of courage.]
[Never any intentions of crossing this one.]
I really wasn't all that scared.
[Can't help but laugh out of the sheer
audacity and embarrassment of the situation.]
Why did you...
Wow, this really is embarrassing.
This is really embarrassing.
Can you just edit out the scene
where I collapsed onto the ground?
[I wish I could turn back time...]
Please edit that out for me, and
play the theme song to Avatar over it.
- Sure, don't worry about it.
- Lower the volume on my panicked breathing.
Please help me out.
[Thus a new project is born...]
Where am I going?
How far am I going?
What?
What is this? This is for real?
[Crossing the wooden plank as if
he's crossing a stiff cliff.]
[Kwang-vatar's great adventure.]
[Sits... lays back... crawls...
Great efforts to reach and ring the bell.]
[Our very own hero, Kwang-vatar...
Coming soon!]
[Second hero, Yoo-perman.]
Where do I need to go?
Jae Suk!
What is that?
[Putting his acting skills to work.]
What is this thing?
You can't be serious!
What are you guys trying to do!
How am I going to cross that
with my eyes blindfolded?
[Kwang-vatar's acting chops to
pull one over Yoo-perman.]
Jae Suk, this is for real.
Jae Suk.
I'm seriously going to lose it.
[How is this even possible?]
[Yes, it makes perfect sense.]
[Yoo-perman enters the building.]
You will need to wear a blindfold
the remainder of the way.
I'm in big trouble.
[Yoo-perman also gets
the blindfold treatment.]
- Watch your steps.
- Seriously.
Yes, this might actually be better
than being able to see below.
I'm going to lose my mind.
[Arrives at the rooftop of the building.]
- Be careful, there's a small step down.
- Okay.
What is this?
We're outside?
- Kwang Soo!
- Jae Suk, just give up.
- What?
- This is really way too much.
- Okay, I got it!
- Jae Suk, it's right in front of you.
- Where is it?
- Step up.
Jae Suk, you really need to
be careful.
Yoo Jae Suk, reach out with
your hand and find the rope.
Make sure you don't let go
of that rope.
- It's very dangerous if you do.
- How do you expect me to do this?
Don't let go of that rope, and Kwang Soo
is waiting for you on the other side.
Jae Suk, I think I heard the plank
crack as I was crossing it.
- Ugh, this is driving me crazy.
- Jae Suk, you should just give up.
I seriously think that I heard
the wood cracking.
Jae Suk.
This is seriously dangerous.
- Tell me where to set my foot.
- Right where you have it.
- But the net underneath...
- This is...
This is seriously dangerous.
How am I going to do this?
This is really dangerous.
It's too dangerous, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, you really should just give up.
Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, I'm serious.
You have to be really careful.
[Whew... what do I do?]
[Your screen has not frozen over.]
- Hey, not being able to see might be better.
- No, don't go that way!
- Is this the right spot?
- It is, but don't go to the left.
[Unable to take the first step.]
Seriously... be careful!
[Putting all his focus into
every single step he takes.]
- Wow, this is insane.
- Jae Suk.
[I can do this...]
[Yoo-perman, the biggest coward,
takes the first step forward?]
No, Jae Suk!
Go back! Step back!
I'm so scared.
Just keep it down!
Just keep it down over there!
- Jae Suk!
- I'm seriously going to fall off.
It's very dangerous!
Just go back!
No, not that way!
[Breathing in shallow pants out of
terrorizing fear.]
Let me know when I've
reached the end.
I can't stop.
Come on, please...
[Can't stop...]
Jae Suk!
[In the midst of his terror, Kwang-vatar
throws an empty water bottle.]
[Look at this guy?]
Is it still far off?
Tell me when I'm at the end.
[But he beats down his own fears
and still manages to forge ahead.]
[There's the bell!]
[Yoo-perman passes the courage test.]
You have successfully passed.
You may now take off your blindfold.
No, don't move and
just take off your blindfold.
[Time to take off the blindfold.]
- I don't know if I can see.
- It's okay, take off the blindfold.
What are you guys doing?
Come here.
- I'm utterly speechless.
- This is Superman's true self.
- This is the true side of Superman.
- What are you guys doing?
Where did he go?
Gwon Yeol!
Give me back my glasses.
How can we entrust the fate of
this planet to someone like him?
You looked like a baby
just learning how to walk.
- What did you say?
- I thought you were learning to walk.
Do you want to get beat?
Wow, this is crazy!
What is all this?
Wow, seriously.
[Yoo-perman crosses over to
the other building after succeeding.]
- You were that afraid?
- You didn't react like that?
- You looked like you were crying.
[Even through their fear, Kwang-vatar
and Yoo-perman still succeed.]
[It's now Ha Gil Dong's turn.]
Let's see what this is about.
- Ha Ha gets scared real easily.
- Dong Hoon!
What is this!
- Dong Hoon, just give up.
- They expect me to... this is absurd!
- No, this is just absurd!
- Dong Hoon, we both failed the mission.
[This duo is having a blast
teasing this fearful kiddo.]
- Ugh, this is just ridiculous.
- Just don't even bother doing it.
I don't think I was even able
to take two steps across it.
This is just absurd.
It's way too dangerous.
We can't overdo it too much right now.
Let's lay off a little, okay?
You will have to wear a blindfold
the remainder of the way.
This isn't even right.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why do you like to torment us so much?
Ugh, this is so scary.
This is even scarier.
[Ha Gil Dong- The resident coward of
all variety programs in the nation.]
[In an extreme state of
nervousness already.]
- Where? I can't see anything.
- Just go straight.
- Ha Ha, it's okay to just give up.
- Did they blindfold you too?
I took about two steps forward,
and I just couldn't go any further.
You actually expect me to do this?
You expect me to do it like this?
This is seriously absurd.
- This is just...
- This is just beyond ridiculous.
- Wait? You want me to step up?
- Yes, step up onto the step.
[Ha Gil Dong is standing in front
of his fateful first step.]
- The rain is making the ground slippery.
- You really need to be careful.
- Is there nothing on the other side?
- No, there's only one rope.
You only have one rope to hold onto
as you cross over.
- I have to step up again?
- You have one more step.
That's just empty air!
[Was I like that too?]
- Ha Ha.
- Yes?
You'll be given a hint if you cross over,
but you may give up right now as well.
- I can cross over however I want?
- But you can't let go of the rope.
How am I supposed to do this!
Why are you Running Man
producers doing this?
You guys don't even know
what you're doing anymore.
I don't think I can do this!
No, not that way!
- Your foot is pointed the wrong way.
- What?
- Watch out, Dong Hoon!
- I don't think I can do this!
I really couldn't do it myself either.
- I can't do it! I give up!
- Are you giving up?
- Give up by shouting it three times.
- Give up, give up, give up!
[Ha Gil Dong fails the mission.]
- I seriously can't do it. I'm too scared!
- I gave up, too.
- No, it's too scary. Don't let go!
- What the heck is this?
[This is fun!]
Ugh, I know how humiliating
that feels.
[Rage and humiliation.]
- Ha Ha, how angry do you feel?
- I know exactly how that feels.
[We're well aware of how that feels...]
You can just jump down from there.
Standing there will only
make you feel even more pathetic.
- He looks so pitiful.
- Where is there a hole in the wall?
I really want to crawl into a hole.
[Unlike Ha Ha, who sets the new record in
giving up in the quickest amount of time...]
[Mr. Capable and Ace don't even
hesitate in their attempts.]
Are you not even afraid just
because you can't see anything?
[Mr. Capable and Ace easily
succeeds their mission.]
- What's wrong with her?
- She is seriously so weird.
- Who is it?
- It's Suk Jin.
- Is Batman coming?
- Suk Jin!
- This is just crazy.
- Are you locked up there?
Only Jong Kook and Ji Hyo succeeded,
and the rest of us failed.
- It's a mission to test your courage.
- I can't cross that.
No, way!
I can't cross that while blindfolded.
[Jitman falls for it hook, line, and sinker.]
- Did you guys cross it?
- Jae Suk, Kwang Soo and I, all failed.
You have to be extra careful because it's
even more slippery with all the rain.
I'm sorry, but I can't do this.
I can't do it with my eyes wide open,
so how can I do it while blindfolded?
- You want me to go up there?
- Yes, just walk into the building.
This is crazy, I can't do this.
Ji Hyo actually succeeded?
Being a hero is a real tough work.
Being a hero isn't for everybody.
My heart's pounding too hard,
and I don't think I can do this.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Yes?
It's a sturdy plank, but it may be slippery,
so you need to be very cautious.
I can't do this. I've told you
repeatedly that I can't do it.
Just get up there for now because
you have to at least attempt it.
- Suk Jin, we gave up too.
- We couldn't do it.
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook were the only two
who were able to successfully do it.
I keep telling them that I can't do it
but they still keep leading me up there.
- This is very dangerous.
- This is an absolutely impossible mission.
- This is a very dangerous mission.
- Especially on a rainy day like this?
My shoes have rubber soles,
so they're extra slippery too.
- Listen to how shaky my voice is.
- Only two people actually did it.
- Only Kim Jong Kook and Ji Hyo did it.
- Wait... this is... but I...
Suk Jin, I almost fell down twice,
so you really need to be careful.
I really have to do this?
I can't just give up right here?
Ha Ha, Kwang-vatar, and I
couldn't do it.
- Is this the plank?
- It's really slippery in the middle.
But keep in mind that once you start,
you can't turn around and go back.
Doing this will help me
toughen up my image, won't it?
- No, I doubt that's going to happen.
- How is that going to change your image?
We're not forcing you to do this,
so think about it very carefully.
- Suk Jin! That's how far we got, too.
- Then I can quit right now?
- Me too!
- I honestly think I can do it.
- Okay, give it a try.
- Suk Jin may be able to pull it off.
- What are you doing?
- That's even more dangerous!
- Are there two ropes or just one?
- I'm seriously going to do this.
- Okay, do it.
- Give it a try.
- I think I can do this.
It's not like I can even see
how scary things are.
- You really have to be careful!
- No, that's the wrong spot!
- This isn't it?
- You have to get in the right direction.
- This is seriously crazy.
- This is it, isn't it?
- Just check the safety of the plank!
- As long as this is stable...
If I can successfully pull this off,
then my life as a hero will be validated!
Yes, there you go!
Little more to the other side!
That's where it gets slippery!
It gets narrower towards the other end.
- You guys are being too distracting.
- This is all because of Jong Kook and Ji Hyo.
- No, this has nothing to do with me.
- I really wanted to do this...
Just do it next time when
you're better than you are now.
- It's too dangerous.
- You actually did pretty decent.
- You actually did better than any one of us.
- Stop lying to me!
[Jitman goes back to the starting line.]
I feel really shaky right now.
Trying to be this courageous,
and that really isn't me.
- Yes, you're right.
- This isn't me. I was being too brave.
Let just go back to who I normally am.
Give up, give up, give up.
[Jitman gives up and fails the mission.]
Let's all give Suk Jin a round of applause
for remaining so courageous.
- You did great.
- Can I give it another try?
No, you can't.
Take off your blindfold and see if you can.
- Seriously.
- Isn't it so embarrassing?
But it's such a relief to me to know
that I'm not the only one.
My son will probably watch this...
That really is embarrassing.
I succeeded, but I still felt embarrassed.
I've been telling my son
to live his life more courageously...
It's okay, it's because you
lost your powers.
[The final hero of the day,
Gae Oh Gong makes his appearance.]
- Gary!
- What is it? Are you all up there?
- This is just ridiculous.
- You have to cross this plank.
- Just look at how high up it is.
- This is no joke.
You have to cross this bridge over here.
This is the bridge.
- We all failed.
- What? That's ridiculous.
- Why are you doing this to us?
Only Jong Kook and Ji Hyo succeeded.
I can't cross that while blindfolded.
That's crazy.
What is this?
- Don't push yourself too hard, Gary.
- Gary's scared of things like this too.
[Gae Oh Gong suffers from fear of heights
after having lost his powers.]
- How much further?
- Watch out for the steps and be careful!
- Grab onto the rope that's to the left.
- Yes, there you go.
- You have to find your balance.
- There's nothing to the right.
Just hold onto the rope
and walk straight ahead.
- You have to go up one more.
- Go up one more, and you can start walking.
- Find your balance.
- Fighting, Gary.
- That's it right there.
- Be careful.
- That's it.
- This is what I step onto?
- Yes, that's it.
- I think he's going to do it.
- This is crazy.
- Wait, hang on a minute.
What is this!
Why are you doing this to me?
I really hate this!
- No, I can't do this!
- We all gave up, too.
- Just give yourself a break and give up.
- I wanted to accomplish something.
- It's starting to rain pretty hard.
- Be careful.
- I'm going to give it a try.
- Okay.
- It's further than you think.
- You can't turn back after a certain point.
Come a little more to the left.
You're going too far off to the right.
Go off to the side a little bit.
Scoot to the right like a crab would.
- No, hold onto the rope and do it.
- Crab, not dog.
- This is scary.
- No, you're doing fine.
- You're too far from the rope. Stick closer.
- Like this?
- You're getting closer to the middle.
- Scream on the count of three.
- What is it?
- Oh no!
- Just hold on.
- No, you can't do it.
- Just sit down where you're at.
What am I going to do?
I can't sit down here.
- Don't let go of the rope.
- It's because of the wind and the rain.
- Is it unsteady up there?
- It's the worst in the middle.
[Works through his fear to finally
bring himself to the bell at the end!]
[Gae Oh Gong succeeds his mission.]
What the heck is this!
[The shame and the humiliation
comes crashing though.]
What are you guys doing?
Seriously!
What were you guys thinking!
[It's okay, everyone else
went through it too.]
[Test of courage now comes to a close.]
Only those who successfully passed
the mission can see this hint.
Okay, since Yoo Jae Suk is closest,
come take a look.
Ugh, I'm so embarrassed.
[Man-made island.]
[Second hint: Man-made Island.]
[Heroes' final mission.]
- This is the last one?
- It's the last mission.
You will either find the final clue directing
you to where you can get your powers back
or you may fail the mission.
The seven heroes will run in a relay form
to beat the bus through one bus stop.
When the first runner gets off the bus
and passes the baton off to the second runner
then the race will carry on in that
manner to the very last runner
and the seventh runner will have to board
the bus the first runner got off of to win.
I'll show you a map of the route.
- You will see the marks noting the spots.
- Wow, it's a long route.
- Look at how long the route is.
- You have to run this whole route.
[Distance between the two bus stops.]
- That's a really far distance.
- It's one stop, but it's still very far.
I remember leaving my umbrella on the bus
when I was a second year in high school
and I actually ran and caught up
to the bus to get my umbrella back.
- Why do you lie like that?
- Are you sure the bus wasn't at a stop?
Why would I lie about that?
It's also very important to determine
which order all of you will run in.
- There are a couple of turns in the route.
- The best runner takes the longest part.
I'm sorry, but my knee is really sore lately,
so I think you're going to have to do it.
If you're not feeling well, then
who in here could be feeling well?
What if I can't hear any traffic
since I can't hear anything with this?
- I can't hear anything either.
- What kind of heroes are we?
[This group of heroes are more frail
and delicate than regular people.]
- Do this is the starting line?
- Can you run to this point?
- How about at this point?
- Someone needs to take over here.
This is our first stop.
Ha Ha needs to get off.
- Bye.
- We'll see you later.
Fighting!
Heroes, fighting!
- Dong Hoon, run extra for me.
- Okay.
[Ha Gil Dong's swift feet are needed.]
- Okay, the Germ Man is getting off.
- I'm Batman!
I'm not a Germ Man.
[Fourth runner, Ace Wonder Blank.]
[Fifth runner-
Kkuk-verine with a bad knee.]
- I'm feeling nervous.
- Yes, me too.
- What am I getting so nervous for?
- I bet my honor as a hero on the line!
[Kwang-vatar attempts to say
hello to the baby.]
Okay, I'm sorry!
[Kwang-vatar's immediate apology.]
- I'm so sorry!
- Forgot how you may frighten people.
- I'm sorry.
- He's sorry.
[That blue man is too scary.]
[On the other hand, Kkuk-verine
is gaining quite the popularity.]
[Kkuk-verine makes many new memories
while waiting for the mission to start.]
[Heroes, are you ready?]
Is everyone ready?
Number one is clear.
- Number two, clear.
- Number three, clear.
- Number four, clear.
- Number five, clear.
- Number six, clear.
- Number seven, clara.
- What are you doing!
- You guys said that at the same time.
[Getting down to the wire!
Beat the bus and save the earth!]
[The key to victory-
First runner- Gae Oh Gong.]
The stupid tail!
[What's needed right now is
Ha Gil Dong's speed!]
[But the ever-unpredictable Jitman
is looking extremely nervous.]
I'm nervous.
[Kkuk-verine... I can do this.]
- Okay, get to your station.
- I didn't know where to go.
[Rushing over to help the grandmother takes
precedence over the mission for Kwang-vatar.]
Thank you.
No, not at all.
Please be careful.
[A very well-mannered Avatar from Pandora.]
I feel like my heart is going to pound
out of my chest. Please get going.
My hands are like blocks of ice
because I'm feeling so nervous.
Okay, I'm about to get on the bus.
Everyone get ready.
Get on this one? Getting on
the bus right now, so get ready!
Bus 5516.
[Gae Oh Gong boards the bus.]
There aren't that many people on
the bus, so we're in big trouble.
This bus is pretty empty.
We're in trouble.
There aren't any cars in the right lane.
We may actually lose this mission.
[Not many cars out on the road?]
I don't see a single car on the road
between Ha Ha and myself.
[Situation alert! This means
the bus could drive much faster!]
There aren't any cars out
on the road.
The street by me is pretty packed.
I'm getting ready to get off the bus,
so everyone get ready.
- Gary is about to get off the bus.
- Get ready!
Wow, why do I feel so nervous?
I'm getting nervous over nothing!
[Making the final turn!]
- The bus is turning!
- Here it comes!
[There's only one chance!]
[Stay energized with
the cheer from the fans.]
I'm so nervous.
What do I do?
Ugh, my stomach hurts.
[Yoo-perman's sensitive stomach acts up
with his state of nervousness.]
Here it is!
I see it coming!
I'm getting off the bus in five seconds.
- He's about to get off the bus!
- It's here! Gary's getting off the bus!
- Let's save the earth!
- I'm so nervous.
[Their hearts are about to burst out of
their chests from nervousness.]
A big crowd is starting to gather in.
We didn't even get stuck at the light.
No light.
[Gae Oh Gong is off the bus.]
Okay, here we go!
[Beat the bus relay race- Start!]
[Gae Oh Gong vs The bus-
Both starting off at the same time.]
[Full speed ahead.]
He's headed this way!
I'm hanging up!
Everyone out of my way.
[Gae Oh Gong's final spurt of speed.]
No, slow down a little bit!
[Hands the baton over to Ha Gil Dong.]
[Take good care of us, Ha Dong Gil...]
- Okay, Ha Ha has the baton.
- Dong Hoon has the baton.
Ugh, whatever.
[Ha Dong Gil's full speed ahead.]
[The Running Heroes are staying
ahead of the bus!]
Suk Jin has the baton!
[Fourth runner,
Ace Wonder Blank is ready to go.]
[Gives Suk Jin a nice push on the back...]
[Jitman, in his forties,
takes off at a dead run!]
[Jitman and the bus are staying
side by side.]
[I'm no longer the Germ Man!]
Hurry, Suk Jin!
[Wonder Blank gets on the move!]
[Wonder Blank gives everything she has...]
Who has the baton right now?
[A peaceful look on her face...
but fast as any other man out there.]
Be careful!
The bus is rounding the corner.
The bus is rounding the corner right now.
We may be able to beat it.
Really?
[Wonder Blank doesn't lower her speed.]
[Touches off the baton to Kkuk-verine.]
[Kwang-vatar is showing
extreme nervousness for his turn.]
The bus just passed me by and
is right behind Jong Kook.
Fighting!
Let's stay strong to the end.
[Kkuk-verine endures the pain in his
knee and runs full speed ahead.]
Here it comes.
I think that's the bus.
[Final runner, Yoo-perman, spots the bus.]
Here they come! I see both
Jong Kook and the bus coming.
[The bus is right on Kkukverine's tail.]
Here it comes.
[Kwang-vatar finally gets on his way
in midst of all the cheers from his fans.]
How are things going?
[A pedestrian walk
in the middle of the route.]
[Safety first!]
[Kwang-vatar shows
good pedestrian manners.]
[Heart is pounding in his chest,
and the mouth starts to dry up.]
[Unlike Kwang-vatar, the bus isn't
slowing down its speed at all.]
I see the bus coming.
What am I going to do?
I see the bus headed this way.
I see it over there.
We're too late.
[Did the bus surpass Kwang-vatar?]
[Keep running!]
Hurry, Kwang Soo!
The bus is right behind you!
What do I do!
[Safely runs around the car,
and takes off running again.]
[Kwang Soo, just a little bit more...]
[Touches off the baton
to the final runner, Yoo-perman!]
[Run!
Win, Yoo-perman!]
Jae Suk, you have to get on the bus!
[Please get on the bus...]
[Running to the last draw of breath...
Running Heroes vs the bus.]
[Who is the ultimate victor?]
- The bus was right behind me.
- I really don't know what'll happen.
- I ran alongside the bus.
- Yes, me too.
- There's Jae Suk!
- I did at first, then I got tired...
- How did it go?
[Did he succeed in getting on the bus?]
I got on the bus.
[Beat the bus relay race-
Running heroes win.]
[Yoo-perman vs the bus-
The final race...]
[Yoo-perman wins.]
Wow, I actually won.
It must be stopped at the light.
[The bus gets stopped at the light
and arrives one beat later.]
- Do I just get on the bus?
- Yes, take it to the next bus stop.
Then we really are heroes.
[Overly-confident group of heroes.]
- There are high, mid and low hints.
- We'll take the high.
There are two high hints, three mid hints,
and two low hints.
If you had failed the mission, then
everyone would've gotten the low hint.
Gary, please step forward.
[What are the hints pointing
to the final destination?]
[Two low hints- Chae Ga Sol.
Kwang-vatar and Gae Oh Gong.]
We'll take a look together.
[The three islands.]
[Jitman, Ha Dong Gil, Wonder Blank.]
[Between Banpo Bridge and
Dongjak Bridge.]
[Top hints- Yoo-perman and Kkuk-verine.]
Please whisper to me where you think
these hints are indicating to.
Ha Ha, you don't know?
The three islands.
Yoo Jae Suk, you can get in the white car,
and Wolverine can get in the grey car.
Really?
Seriously?
Okay, next.
Tell me where you think it is.
Can I just get in the white car?
Just tell me your answer instead of
asking me which car you can ride in.
[Kwang-vatar, you have to
say your answer...]
[White car- Correct answer car.
Grey car- Wrong answer car.]
I don't know if they're behind us, but
they're headed elsewhere, aren't they?
- But they might know where they're going.
- Then we just need to get there first.
We just need to get our powers back.
Gae Oh Gong...
with Yoo-perman and Wonder Blank.
Jae Suk kept saying that he knew where
it was before he even received his last hint.
[Yoo-perman seems a little suspicious?]
[Then it must mean that Yoo-perman
is the Anti-hero!]
- He has to be the one
- Let me tell you something.
- What's between Dongjak and Banpo Bridge?
- Let's ask someone.
- Ask if there are any man-made islands.
- Can I ask you something?
- Where the lights gather in the winter.
- The three islands.
- The three light island?
- What did you say?
- The three light islands?
- That's it!
[Finally figures out the final location
with the help of these kind students.]
- Yes, that's right!
- Thank you!
[Let's go and reclaim our lost powers!]
- Is this where we can get our powers back?
- Let's see.
Will we be able to break this bondage
and regain our superpowers once again?
[Did a meteor really crash
somewhere around here?]
- What's this?
- What is that?
[The ice capsules that kept the superheroes
prisoners for hundreds of years?]
- Kwang-vatar.
- Jae Suk.
- Germ Man, you finally showed up.
- You're the Anti-hero!
[The heroes are starting to
suspect one another.]
- The Anti-hero is amongst us, isn't he?
- I see that you all made it.
[The Anti-hero's voice?]
The time for you to regain your
superpowers has come.
That fateful moment is only
three minutes away.
[The meteor will
crash down in three minutes.]
Find an 'R' marked chair to sit on within
three minutes to regain your lost powers!
Wow, some of these chairs
are specially marked.
Do you also know what I told only to
Kwang-vatar this morning?
The chairs in which you can
regain your superpowers...
there are only six of them.
There are only six chairs that you can use
to regain your lost superpowers.
What do you think is more important?
I hope that you make the right decision.
If you were going to tell everyone,
then why did you tell me?
You've only got three minutes
from this moment.
Can we look under these tarps?
[The final stage to reclaiming their powers.]
[Find and sit on one of the six
'R' marked chairs.]
[Lifting up all the sheets, but none
of the chairs are specially marked.]
[Ha Gil Dong is the first
to find one of the six chairs.]
[Jitman finds a chair of his own
soon thereafter.]
Okay, I found it!
I got one!
Are there only two left?
[There heroes still left without a chair.]
[Only two chairs are left to be found.]
- Something doesn't feel right.
- This was way too easy.
[There is a hidden secret to this mission...]
[Wonder Blank finds her own chair.]
[Just then, Ha Gil Dong discovers
something.]
There's a pattern!
We have to figure out the pattern.
- I'm next to you, Jae Suk.
- Come here, Ji Hyo.
[What meaning does this pattern hold?]
Everyone sit down.
[The meteor is getting closer!]
[The last remaining marked chair
is nowhere to be found...]
- Should we help find the last chair?
- But we've all got ours already.
[Ha Gil Dong attempts to help
find the last remaining chair.]
- It's right here.
- Then bring it over.
- Hey, come here!
- I bet the Giraffe did something.
- Come here!
- What is it?
[Kwang-vatar runs over to claim his seat.]
[Gae Oh Gong arrives too late
and is left without a seat of his own.]
There are only these six chairs.
- There are six chairs.
- Should we move this one over there?
[Is the black and white pattern
the key to this mystery?]
- Move this one over there.
- Over here, Ha Ha.
[Moving while still seated out of his fear
of getting his seat stolen away.]
- Why do we need to match this?
- There's no need for that, is there?
- We just need to match all this.
- Then one person doesn't have a seat?
[The meteor is about to crash down!]
[There is no more time!]
[Seven distinct black and white pattern!]
[With the pattern complete,
there are a total of seven seats.]
We succeeded in making seven seats!
- An Anti-hero can't get in our way.
- We are as one!
[The fateful moment has arrived.]
[The heroes regain their lost superpowers!]
[The magic of using six chairs
to create seven seats out of it.]
- I don't know why, but I'm disappointed.
- I'm actually starting to tear up.
But I saw you moving with
the seat stuck to your butt.
[Thus... the heroes regained
their lost powers.]
[But... he can't fly, can he?]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Suspicious brothers find
their way to Running Man.]
[Rough and charismatic
big brother, Jo Jin Woong.]
[The ice man-
Middle brother, Kim Sung Gyun.]
[The brains of the operation,
the youngest brother, Oh Sang Jin.]
[Stay tuned for the bad boys' return.]
No more politeness after this point.
[The rough bingo race.]
[The unavoidable battle
between the men.]
[Next week on Running Man- Bingo.]