Subtitles by DramaFever
[The excitement of new spring...
comes to find your way.]
[A fateful love just like a scene
right out of a movie.]
[Be true to your feelings.]
[The love, which is as solid as rock,
and will never break.]
[Chapter One- The meeting.]
[Movie- Between Passion and Dispassion.]
[In the midst of these countless people...]
[Where could my fateful love be?]
[Could she be the one?]
[A man of destiny
with a toxic look on his face...]
[Narsha- 34 years old.]
[A fateful meeting with a younger man.]
[It's you?]
[Giraffe gets back into his character.]
Hello, Narsha.
[Their first time ever meeting-
Part awkward, and part embarrassing.]
- This is really awkward.
- It's very nice to meet you.
[Bending down at a 150 degrees angle.]
Hello.
You two are one of our
fateful couples.
[Narsha is acting more bashful
than usual.]
[How will this couple play out?]
[Fate cannot be tempered with.]
[If it's meant to be, then
they will always end up together.]
[Who could be the other half of
Kkuk's sweet romance?]
[Just like a scene out of a movie...
fate comes to find this one woman.]
[Ha Yeon Soo.]
Are you my partner for the day?
Of course.
[Just like that moment ten years ago.]
I feel so reassured right now.
I really want to win.
She's really competitive.
She's a very competitive person.
Sparta!
[Movie- Romeo and Juliet.]
[DiCaprio is in search for his
one true love.]
[A beautiful aquarium and DiCaprio.]
[Sushi and YuCaprio.]
[DiCaprio...]
[We're so sorry.]
[Doctor Stranger's Ji Se Yun.]
[An unexpected sushi romance.]
[Love that comes to find them while
picking out their fish for a sushi meal.]
This is so much fun.
It's about time for a special like this.
[Movie- A Roman Holiday.]
[Ji Hyo is enjoying a relaxing
Seoul holiday.]
[As well as Gary.]
[Romantic Gary is on the search
for Seoul's own Audrey Hepburn.]
[Monday Couple's everlasting love?]
By any chance...
Are you Blank-drey Hepburn?
How did you know that?
[Right at the same time...]
What a beautiful woman I see
standing under the clear blue sky.
Where are you headed?
[Then who could Ji Hyo's love be?]
Yes, I'm your partner.
[Park Seo Joon]
[Then who could Gary's fateful love be?]
[Girl's Day's Min Ah.]
- It's nice to meet you.
I can't believe that a day like this
has finally come my way.
Hurray!
Would you like to share this coat together?
[Movie- Classic.]
Be careful of the steps.
Are you happy, Min Ah?
- Yes, I'm happy.
- I'm really happy too, Min Ah!
[Monday Couple's tangled love.]
[But it's okay,
because today is Tuesday.]
Min Ah!
Watch your step!
[Pottery... love and its soul.]
[Who is this mouse thief?]
[Just like Demi Moore's touch...]
[In this case... should I be doing this?]
[Top model- Ha Hye Jin.]
[Extreme awkwardness.]
What am I supposed to do here?
[Awkward hesitation.]
[Reenacting the movie scene without even
knowing who each other are.]
Who is she?
Wow, oh my goodness!
Hello!
- Hello.
[Finally gets to see who their partner is.]
You're model, Han Hye Jin.
Please have a seat.
Why are you standing up?
Come on, have a seat.
We need to finish what we were doing.
['Love story with the shorty' by Haroro.]
[An adorable woman is
waiting for her first meeting.]
[Then who could be the star of this limo?]
[Richard Big-nose.]
This is it.
I'm Ji-chard Gere today.
Where's my Julia Roberts?
My Julia!
Start.
[Who is Richard Big-nose's
pretty woman?]
Where are you?
Who is she?
[Goddess of baseball- Choi Hee.]
So my Julia is the goddess of baseball.
Hello.
Julia.
- Richard.
- My Julia.
[Suk Jin and Choi Hee- A new couple is born.]
- Wow, it's so nice to meet you.
- Are you my Richard?
We're not going to spend the whole day
in jail today, are we?
No way, not at all.
[Fateful meetings with their loves-
Seven couples are born.]
- Can you sing me a song?
- What kind of a sudden request is that?
- I want you to sing 'One Man'.
- Why do you suddenly want me to sing?
- That's so sudden.
- Just sing me one verse.
- Seriously? You really want me to sing?
- Yes.
[He normally doesn't sing on the show...]
[He's doing it!]
[I guess you must like her?]
[One embarrassed looking man.]
- Didn't they say that it was right here?
- I think I got turned around.
You're just driving around on purpose
just so you could go out on a date with me.
[Who is this woman?]
- It's the perfect weather for a date.
- Yes, it is.
The music should be playing
during moments like this.
And the man usually has a cup of coffee
waiting for the girl in the car, right?
You should've already had the music playing
before I even said anything about it.
Are you normally a bully like this?
- No, that's not my style.
- Then what are you like?
I've always been genuinely
curious about you.
You're curious about me?
[A master of playing hard to get- Narsha.]
It's like this.
Since I've never met you before...
[This young man is not able to
quite measure up to Narsha.]
So I make you nervous?
Don't say things like that.
[This sweet, yet frightening couple...
What else do they have in store for us?]
[A playing field in Yongsan.]
Hello.
It's a great morning.
[All seven couples are
finally gathered together.]
[Seeing who each other's
partners are for the first time.]
- Doesn't she have the tiniest face?
- Isn't my partner so tall?
Wow, her face is smaller than
Jong Kook's biceps.
[Her face is the size of
muscle bound Tiger's biceps.]
Her face really is tiny.
There was a movie that Arnold Schwarzenegger
did a long time ago, titled 'Commando'
in which he had to go rescue
his daughter in the movie.
[They look more like Commando and his
daughter rather than a couple in love?]
Arnold Schwarzenegger rescued his daughter
and carried her out to safety.
Everyone always thinks
that I'm like this huge meat head
because you guys keep saying
stuff like that.
- You are huge!
- You're totally huge!
- You really are big.
- You'll block her face if you flex your arm.
[Could he really block her entire face
just by flexing his biceps?]
[Where did she go?]
Se Yun, can you
introduce yourself to everyone?
Hello, my name is Jin Se Yun,
and I'm on the cast of Doctor Stranger.
[Jin Se Yun- Doctor Stranger.]
You may not remember this, but she was on
the show before with Ryu Hyun Jin.
She was seen constantly  smiling and
laughing the last time she was on our show.
She's going to show everyone how
well-spoken she is this time around.
- Our next guest is now a free agent...
- The Goddess of Baseball.
Yes, that's correct. She has
dubbed herself as the Goddess of Baseball.
[Self-proclaimed Goddess of Baseball,
Choi Hee.]
Hello, my name is Choi Hee.
- This is my first time on an SBS show.
- Is that right?
Please take good care of me.
No, this is not Choi Hee's first time
guesting on an SBS show.
- What do you mean?
- No! Why are you bringing that up?
- Why are you trying to bring that up?
- No, that's not what I meant.
Even though she is telling everyone
that this is her first time on an SBS show...
before she made her debut,
she was a guest on the Truth Game Show.
- There was a show we did...
- No, it's okay.
She made a cameo appearance as
Jung Joon Ha's fake sister-in-law.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
[MC Yoo is looking as green as can be.]
[Proof of Choi Hee's first
SBS appearance back in 2006.]
She made an appearance as
the fake sister-in-law.
Next up, we have Mr. Park Seo Joon.
[A hot up and coming actor,
Park Seo Joon.]
You became a star
because of Running Man, right?
Yes, another actor that Running Man
has helped launch their career.
I have no doubt that he will become
a huge star in the future.
[Frigid negative temperatures
that will forever remain in his memory.]
[The Winter Prince commanded
through the frigid winter waters.]
- Yes, he's a very hard working young man.
- I try my best to work hard.
- Yes, he always tries very hard.
- You're teamed up with Ji Hyo today.
How do you feel about that?
When I met her earlier today...
she was nodding off on the steps.
[Eating while sleeping-
A serious multi-tasker.]
Ji Hyo can fall asleep
pretty much anywhere.
She falls asleep in places that I never
thought were possible for humans.
She even fell asleep ten meters
off the ground.
- Next is Narsha!
- Narsha!
[A lovely mature idol, Narsha.]
- You have a unique helmet style haircut.
- She was imitating my haircut.
Yes, I got a haircut when I found out
that I was going to be on Running Man.
It's very pretty.
Look at the back.
I don't know what it is about Narsha,
but I always find her so attractive.
- Narsha is partnered with Kwang Soo today.
- Yes.
We will wait and see what you two
will have in store for us.
This is a couple race for all seven couples.
[Today's theme is, 'Unbreakable Love'.]
[It's a race that will test the
sturdiness of their love.]
We will be giving you a rock which you will
need for seven different courses.
Okay.
The rocks will vary from a very strong rock
which is practically indestructible
all the way down to a very weak rock which
could crumble from the slightest provocation.
[A total of seven different types of rocks.]
[The sturdiness of these rocks will prove
which of the seven loves are the strongest.]
- There's an egg.
- It's an egg.
- Look, that's an egg.
- That one looks like a rice cake.
After winning each of the missions
you will get the chance to see,
and swap out your rock with someone else's.
These two people are choosing which rock
each of the seven teams will be given.
Let's give the weakest rock to
the couple we dislike the most.
The strength of each couple's love will
be tested at the final location
and the couple who possesses the strongest
rock that remain unbroken
will be the ultimate victors.
The prize given out to the victors today
are on a different scale than anything else
from which you have ever seen before.
[A whole different scale
of prizes for the winners.]
- A diamond?
- Maybe it really is!
That is all I'm going to tell you.
[Winning prize- A one carat diamond.]
- Okay!
- It has to be a diamond.
- Give me a diamond.
- Do you want a diamond?
[Why... you can't handle that?]
[Chapter Eight- Pureness of Love.]
We will now get started with the first game.
Ultimate love's first mission.
It's the Purity of Love which will test
the strength of your male partners.
Something pure?
What's it going to be? Flour?
Why else would they call it that?
The male partners will have to jump through
a course of hurdles from the starting line
and run over to the bouquet that you see
hanging up above in the middle of the field.
You will have to catch the bouquet and
bring it to your female partner.
But since only one man will be able to
get the bouquet hanging in the middle
the remaining partners, will have the
balloons above their heads pop open on them
which are filled with flour.
Oh my God!
Thus, the person who gets the bouquet
will come in at first place in this round.
Then there will be another round to determine
the second place, then another for third.
Then Hye Jin will become the White Witch,
and no longer be the Gangnam Witch.
- Se Yun!
- Fighting!
[Everyone is cheering on their own partners.]
Just don't come in at last place.
- Seo Joon, it's going to be rough out there.
- Okay.
Hye Jin.
Don't get your hopes up at all.
We're just going to be
showered with the flour.
- We're going to be the White Witches!
- I'm going to win this!
[Purity of Love- First round.]
Ready!
[A battle to get the token of love,
the bouquet to their partner!]
[With the Tiger in the lead...]
[Even from afar, his amazing speed
cannot be disputed.]
[Will the Tiger win this round
without any hope for anyone else?]
[Just then, Seo Joon appears out of nowhere
like a flying comet in the sky.]
[Seo Joon's powerful run.]
[Head to head with Tiger's powerful skills.]
[On fire!]
[Please...]
[Seo Joon... takes over the lead!]
[But he unfortunately misses
grabbing the bouquet.]
[The acupuncture mat...
gives them a taste of love's agony.]
[Hurry up and get me the bouquet!]
[That's our Giraffe!]
[Giraffe's partner is giddy
with excitement.]
[The agonizing acupuncture's massage
that can be felt with his whole body.]
[Giraffe is way on the bottom.]
- No! There it is!
- It's underneath you!
[Kwang Soo, are you feeling
the health benefits of the mat?]
[The man with the bouquet in hand...]
[is Seo Joon!]
[Hurry!]
[Gives the bouquet of love to Ji Hyo!]
[Time for some pure love.]
[Ji Hyo and Seo Joon win
the first round.]
What happened, Kwang Soo?
- Your hair looks pretty, Narsha.
- It's unique, isn't it?
- Yeah, it's very Gangnam style.
- But you had the bouquet first!
What happened, Kwang Soo?
- We can swap our rock out now.
- Yes, all thanks to you.
Seo Joon always does great
whenever he comes out on our show.
[Purity of Love- Second round.]
[They must win this mission for a chance
to swap out their rocks!]
[Full speed ahead towards their partners!]
Wow, look at Jong Kook.
[A facial expression often seen
at a sporting match.]
[On the other hand...]
Hurry!
You're doing great!
[Big-nose's hurdle antics.]
[That's not how you're supposed to do it!]
[This fierce animal is full speed ahead!]
[Even gets the bouquet on a single try!]
[Jong Kook and Yeon Soo
win the second round.]
[The rest gets a flour shower.]
[This is what you call pure love.]
[Snowy white hair.]
[The top model has been transformed
into a white witch just as predicted.]
[For the third round, the women will run,
and the men will stand under the balloons.]
Bend your head totally forward.
[Kwang Soo is shaking the flour
off of Narsha's hair.]
[Head bang.]
[A new rocker is discovered.]
I got it all under my shirt.
Are you sure you're not doing it too hard?
No, it's all on the collar of your shirt.
- No, you're okay now.
- I've got the feel for it now.
[Techno dance.]
It's like dancing to a techno song.
[An impersonation brought on
by the flour shower.]
Forward.
[Back to being a rocker.]
[From rock to techno-
A wide range of her musical talents.]
Narsha, hang on a second.
You're going to make yourself dizzy.
But that really hurts.
[And lastly, the salon madam.]
Madam, I'll have you fixed up in no time.
You did good.
- Thank you so much.
- No, not at all.
[Commando Tiger protecting his daughter.]
That was pretty tough.
These games are on a completely different
scale than I expected.
[While Yeon Soo is sitting in ease and
talking about her first impression...]
[The rest of the women are getting ready
to enter a fierce battle.]
- Wow, you're really good.
- It's much higher than I thought it would be.
Please take care of me, Hye Jin.
Please.
Se Yun!
[Who's this guy?]
- All for the diamond.
- This is not a game!
You have to be strong about this.
Okay?
Keep your eyes shut tight, okay?
[One man's wide eyed terror...]
- Ready!
- Watch out for Narsha.
We have to keep our heads up.
[Purity of Love's final round.]
[Run in the name of strength and love!]
[The tallest of the women
are leading the pack!]
Han Hye Jin!
Se Yun!
[Jin Se Yun takes over the lead!]
Narsha, what are you doing!
What is she doing?
[Narsha is taking her sweet old time.]
[Could she possibly be planning
a flour revenge on her partner?]
[Could Se Yun take the victory
against everyone's prediction?]
[So close!]
[Who will get the bouquet?]
[Hye Jin uses her height to her advantage
to get the bouquet in her hands.]
[Se Yun steals the bouquet!]
[A war of the bouquet.]
[Very anxious partners.]
I'm the oldest one here!
My partner is 34 years old!
[Ultimately uses her age as her weapon.]
Don't give up!
[Who cares about your age!]
[Love must be fought for!]
[Narsha gets back into the battle of love.]
Get up!
Young girls these days are so weird!
[Young girls of these days are
still battling over the bouquet.]
[Jae Suk now only needs to get
the bouquet in his outstretched hands.]
[Huh?]
[Against the rules!
Jae Suk steps off the platform.]
[Referee Kkuk blows the whistle.]
- No, we have to do it over.
- Yoo Jae Suk stepped off his platform.
- Why did you step off the platform?
- I had the bouquet in my hands.
[Yoo Hyuk's foul play means
the game has to be restarted.]
He has to be disqualified.
You have to call something
on the shrieker too.
'Ah! I'm the oldest one here!'
- Stop making her scream like that.
- I'm the oldest and the weakest one here.
We're the same age.
Be more understanding of her.
- What's there to be understanding about?
- You have to give her a break.
- She screeches like a dolphin.
- She was the only one down on the ground.
[The oldest woman cannot compete
in this battle of love.]
[There was a time when I used to be
young like these girls too...]
Young girls these days are so weird!
Okay, here we go.
Ready!
- We have to do this.
- You have to get the bouquet.
Get the bouquet.
[Round two of the bouquet battle.]
[A total of ten hands
battling for the bouquet.]
[Hye Jin, Choi Hee,
and Se Yun's fierce battle.]
[Gangnam Witch is beginning
to show her true colors.]
Good, bring it to me.
Se Yun!
Over here, Se Yun.
[Witch Hye Jin activates her full power.]
[Holding on with all their might...]
[But the Witch... is smiling?]
[Who will be the ultimate possessor
of the bouquet?]
- Good, over here!
- Se Yun, I'm over here.
You're almost there!
[Hye Jin drags all the girls
over to where Ha Ha is standing.]
[Ha Ha and Hye Jin win.]
[A white Giraffe.]
[Snowy white flower boys.]
Gary, you look so hideous!
[He hears that quite often.]
Stop saying that!
I already hear that often enough.
Hye Jin!
[The kiddo is ecstatic over
what his partner has done for him.]
Witch!
Gangnam Witch!
[This ugly white boy is watching
the scene without uttering a word.]
This bouquet is...
[The ferocity of this love battle
is proven by the state of the bouquet.]
What are we going to do?
Getting showered by the flour is one thing
but what's even worse is that Min Ah
was laughing and calling Gary ugly.
Gary, you look so hideous!
- Who was she saying that to?
- Me.
Congratulations to Hye Jin and Ha Ha,
who came in at third place.
[Third place winners- Ha Ha and Hye Jin.]
- Gangnam Witch is awesome!
- In second place...
We have Kim Jong Kook and Ha Yeon Soo.
And in first place,
we have Song Ji Hyo and Seo Joon.
- Get away from me.
- Why do your teeth look so yellow?
- What are you talking about?
- Your teeth are looking really yellow.
Yellow teeth are really popular amongst
all the celebrities lately.
[First to lead the new wave of style.]
- It's so yellow.
- Why do they look so yellow?
Yellow teeth are the new wave of style.
[His partner is gracious enough to
help him whiten his teeth.]
The couple that came in at third place can
step forward and receive their hint.
[A special hint regarding
the rock that they currently have.]
- You look like such an incompetent fool.
- You got lucky with your partner.
The width of Hye Jin's shoulders
are as wide as Jong Kook's shoulders.
How can you say something like that?
He really is something else.
[Rock exchanging coupon]
You see all the rocks, right?
Take a good look at all the rocks.
You can exchange your own rock,
or exchange someone else's rock.
- How many times?
- You can only exchange one.
They all look so good.
[Checking to see
which rock looks the sturdiest.]
I can't give you too much time, so you
have one minute to make your exchange.
[Must exchange it for the sturdiest rock.]
[Will the sturdiest looking rock
actually be the sturdiest rock?]
[They exchange their own rock
with Jae Suk's rock.]
I will first give you your own hint.
[Second place winners, Jong Kook and Yeon Soo
are given a hint and an exchange coupon.]
[The Moh's hardness scale determines
the hardness of ten different minerals.]
[Moh's hardness scale...]
[Sounds like a really big hint for
the unbreakable love mission.]
- Doesn't this look really hard?
- Yes.
This looks like a white pebble.
Let's swap this one out for this.
[They choose to go with the one
that appears to be a white pebble.]
That was a good choice.
Since you guys came in at first place
you'll get a better hint
than the second place winner.
[The Moh's hardness scale determines
the hardness of ten different minerals.]
[The hardness of your rock is
stronger than that of Jae Suk's team.]
[Ji Hyo and Seo Joon's is tougher than
Jae Suk and Se Yun's.]
[They ultimately decide to exchange
theirs out for Ha Ha and Hye Jin's.]
Okay, first round is now over.
We will now move on to the next location
for our second round of the race.
[Unbreakable love- second mission location.]
But Seo Joon, do you know what that hint
from earlier was indicating to?
I felt like it was indicating to which of
all the rocks was the strongest
but the wording of the hint
was way too tough to understand.
My understanding is that higher
the density rating, easier it is to break.
I think I know what you're saying.
Something that is tightly bound together
and really carefully cut into its shape is...
But I think that the rock we have right now
may be a pretty strong one.
I think that the rock we have and the one
that was right next to ours, are the strong ones.
- Which rock is the hardest of them all?
- I think that would be...
marble, don't you think?
[Isn't marble pretty easy to break?]
[Unsure of his questionable guess.]
- You're saying granite is the hardest?
- Of course it is.
- Suk Jin is such a weird driver.
- That elder is so frustrating.
Ugh, seriously.
Come on!
- He's such an aggressive driver.
- Seriously.
They say that the way a person drives
is a good indicator of their personality.
That's right, he's all just a show.
What you see of him is just a facade.
Why is he driving so slow when there
aren't even any other cars in front of him?
[What is the reason for Big-nose driving
so slow when there isn't even any traffic?]
It's because he's never been
in the lead before.
Because he's only used to
following someone else?
Maybe you're right.
Now that you say it, I think you're right.
[It seems as though Jae Suk
may have a point?]
That's why he's driving so hesitantly.
[King of ddakji drives in the path of others.]
Is this where we get off?
[Seoul's Samjungdong.]
[Streets filled with tiny shops and cafes-
the perfect spot for romantic dates.]
- What a beautiful day.
- What are we doing in here?
[Mission location- Arrives at a cafe.]
I think there's someone here just
to watch the recording of our show.
Me?
Are you referring to me?
- What are you saying?
- Okay, everyone's now here.
[Tall spectator without a seat,
and his partner who does all his work.]
We've asked you to come to this cafe so that
you could enjoy a nice date with your partner.
This round of games was designed to test
the compatibility of you and your partner.
This mission is titled,
Love is a Bounce Bounce.
- Love is a bounce bounce.
- You guys are good with the titles.
[Chapter Nine- Love is a bounce bounce.]
Did you all see what's below you outside?
A trampoline has been set up outside.
One person will pose the quiz questions
while jumping on the trampoline
while his or her partner can sit in here and
answer the question in ease.
Okay, I understand.
I think Hye Jin will have to be
the questioner for Ha Ha's team.
We'll figure that out for ourselves.
- You just worry about ourselves.
- Okay, fine.
You can also use your body
to pose the questions.
- Song Ji Hyo.
- I'm sorry.
Who is it?
I'm curious to know.
[Who could be calling her at this time?]
Did you get yourself a new boyfriend?
At least tell me when you
get yourself one.
That way I can be more cautious
of the things that I say to you.
[This is the respect between a work couple.]
You need to tell Gary about it
even if you don't tell us about it.
The drama between you two is
so entertaining.
[The Pedestrian Couple is enthralled
by the drama between the Monday Couple.]
You're breathing down on me too hard.
- I'm just breathing.
- My neck is getting cold.
[He's about to catch a cold from the gust
coming from the Giraffe's nose.]
[First challengers- Kwang Soo and Narsha.]
Even if Narsha were to ask the questions,
Kwang Soo won't be able to answer them.
He's really ignorant, isn't he?
Correct answer!
I'm really ignorant too.
[What will be Kwang Soo
and Narsha's category?]
I don't know things like this.
[Person and Character.]
It's about men who you become more and more
attracted to the more you see him.
[Who, me?]
Wow, we have to win this.
We have to place in the top three.
You look like the heroine
of a romantic comedy.
[The heroine of a bickering romantic comedy?
Kwang-Sha Couple?]
It is a romantic comedy
but there needs to be different stars in it.
[The classic friend couple.]
They don't look like a couple in love.
[Outside the café window...
is a large trampoline for the questioner.]
[He must jump high enough to peek into
the cafe window on the second floor.]
- Look at Kwang Soo already.
- I can totally see him.
But he looks so scary.
[The Kwang Ghost.]
I'm scared!
[The concept was definitely
supposed to be romantic...]
Do it with a smile on his face.
[Like this?]
No, never mind.
Don't smile.
[Narsha... accept my love for you.]
- He looks like a monster.
- He really is something.
[Correctly answer the most number of questions
within 60 seconds to win the mission.]
Ready, set, go.
I think I know what it is.
[Wait, that's...]
Batman!
[Batman- Correct answer.]
[The next question is?]
Jo In Sung!
[Jo In Sung- Correct answer.]
- This is easy.
- This is way too easy.
I'm home all alone!
Macaulay Culkin.
[Macaulay Culkin- Correct answer.]
Spiderman.
[Four correct answer already!
Spiderman- Correct answer.]
- He's really good.
- He's blowing his nose.
I think he's an elephant.
- I think I know what it is.
Bruce Lee.
[Bruce Lee- Correct answer.]
She's really good.
Loyalty!
[This man?]
- Loyalty!
- What?
Ah, Kim Bo Sung!
[Kim Bo Sung- Correct answer.]
[Time over]
[Kwang Soo and Narsha-
Six questions answered correctly.]
Kwang Soo and Narsha succeeded in
answering six questions correctly.
I think we got a quite a few
answered correctly.
But that really makes a person
a little bit teary eyed.
- That's going to be you soon.
- I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing it.
Hee's going to do it.
- I'm not doing.
- Your selfishness really is impressive.
[Men's idol: Big-nose, the Bad Boy.
Hee, you're going to be out there screaming
your lungs out in five minutes.
[Big-nose, The Man!]
You're going to be screaming
on that trampoline out there.
I'm not good at posing the questions.
[Next up, Gary and Min Ah.]
- I think this is going to be hard.
- What is it?
[Songs]
You have to correctly guess the songs that
couples like to sing at karaoke bars.
You want us to use our bodies to
sing and describe the songs?
[It seems as though their category
was quite the easy one.]
I don't know too many songs.
We're in big trouble.
[Love definitely is a bounce.]
['Nobody'- Wonder Girls.]
How do you dance the 'Nobody' dance?
[I can't see...]
This is bad.
[Huh?]
I really have no idea.
Nobody!
['Nobody'- Wonder Girls.]
[Only knows the 'You' part.]
Gary, we can't even see you.
A gun?
'Shot by the Gun'?
How did the 'Gangnam Style' go again?
['Gangnam Style'- Psy.]
What kind of a style do I have?
What did he say?
- What is he saying?
- My style!
[He should be doing the horse dance.]
[Huh?]
If Gary looks that sad doing it,
how sad am I going to look?
'The Evil Red Horse'?
- No, it's not.
- Okay, we're not going to be in last place.
Horse!
I really have no idea.
[Passes again- Next question.]
He really is bad.
Ten points.
What is he saying?
'Ten points'?
[Finally succeeds in answering
one question correctly.]
['As if Shot by the Gun'- Baek Ji Young.]
'As if Shot by the Gun'?
[Wow... correct answer!]
I used to sing that song all the time.
[Next question- Wait, that dance is...]
Wait, this is Park Nam Jung's...
[But she needs to know
the title of the song.]
[Time over]
It was 'While Missing You'.
Gary and Min Ah correctly
answered two questions.
Did you get this one?
- 'As if shot by the gun'.
- You got that?
- Did you get this one?
- What's that?
- Gangnam Style.
- Ah.
- The horse dance.
- You don't get it either, do you?
[That's how you do it...]
This is how I always did it.
[The club mania has been
dancing it all wrong this whole time.]
- That's not it?
- This is how you do it.
Next up is Suk Jin.
[Suk Jin and Choi Hee's turn.]
- Hurry up and go out to the trampoline.
- You go out there.
- I don't think I can...
- Yes!
What are you talking about?
Do you know how hard this is?
[Animal]
Okay, get out there.
You're seriously sending her out there?
You may not even show up in the window.
You don't know anything about Suk Jin.
Choi Hee would be much better out there.
[Everyone agrees that Choi Hee
would be the better choice?]
We need to have
the ambulance ready for Suk Jin.
I have really bad joints.
He's jumping as high as
he can right now.
I can't really see.
You would jump much higher
than he can.
[Will old man Big-nose be
safe out there?]
[Start the animal quiz.]
He seems to be enjoying himself
out there.
Jong Kook!
Tiger.
[Tiger- Correct answer.]
What's this?
He's going to lose.
- What's that sound?
- Suk Jin's collapsed out there.
- You don't know that sound?
- Ah, the woodpecker!
[Woodpecker- Correct answer.]
Alligator.
[Next question- Alligator.]
What's that?
- It's a slate.
- Slate?
Purse!
[Losing strength from both
of his legs...]
- Hurry!
- He's collapsed out there.
Suk Jin!
- I'm tearing up.
- Where is he?
Rabbit!
[Rabbit- Correct answer.]
[Three answers correct-
Better than expected.]
[All they can hear is his screams.]
- What is that?
- It's because he's having fun.
It's because he's having fun
jumping on the trampoline.
[Big-nose is having fun jumping down
memory lane on the trampoline?]
Curly!
Animal with the curly hair!
Lion?
[Lion- Correct answer.]
[What is he doing?
Sticking out his tongue?]
A fly?
Snake?
[Snake- Correct answer.]
Hippo.
[Time over.]
Is 'Ah' all he can say out there?
[All the animals makes the same sound.]
This is way too hard.
- We'll go next. Hye Jin is going to do it.
- Why am I going out there?
Okay.
[Is Hye Jin really going out
to the trampoline?]
We have to show them how
good we are.
Hye Jin's going to get a workout.
- Hye Jin is going to be better than Ha Ha.
- She was already 168cm tall in grade school.
- Why are you bringing that up?
- She was the tallest in her class.
- Love!
- How am I to express that?
- It's because she's much taller than me.
- I'm not that much taller than you.
[Bratty little kid.]
Fighting!
[Gangnam Witch, Hye Jin!]
Se Yun, it seems as though this is the
way it's going to go. Get yourself ready.
[The bad boy concept seems to be
going wide spread on Running Man.]
[Due to the fault of being taller
than Ha Ha...]
Wow, this is really scary.
This is scary.
This is really hard.
Set, go!
I can see her hands.
[What's he doing?]
[Question- Playing hard to get.]
[Is she cheering?]
[The shake?]
What is she doing?
[Pass]
[The next love question is?]
What is she doing?
Kiss!
[Kiss- Correct answer.]
I can't see her at all.
What was that?
What could that be?
What is this?
Put your hands up.
Praying?
Is she praying?
Marry me!
Proposal!
[Proposal- Correct answer.]
She's giving someone roses.
A ring!
Diamond ring!
A wedding ring!
[It's very close...]
Why can't he get this?
Okay, a couple ring!
[Couple ring- Correct answer.]
[Three correct answers!]
What is that?
A paper?
Three?
- I love three.
- Samgyetang.
Three?
What about three?
[Time over.]
- Love triangle.
- Ah, a love triangle.
[A very sensible explanation.
Hye Jin is looking exhausted.]
[Ha Ha and Hye Jin- Three correct answers.]
[Kwang Soo and Narsha are currently
in first place.]
Ha Dong Hoon, get over here.
What?
- What's wrong?
- He correctly answered three questions.
- I got three questions.
- He only got three questions correct?
You should've explained it better.
[Gangnam Witch definitely is
a force to be reckoned with.]
So we need to beat six?
It's person and character.
[Jae Suk and Se Yun get
the person and character category.]
I think they're going to do well.
He's doing well.
I just saw him fall.
He just fell so pathetically.
[Act up too much... and you'll
completely humiliate yourself.]
[But his jumping skills are quite good.
Able to see him pretty easily.]
[Jae Suk and Se Yun- Start.]
[First question- Dooley.]
Jump rope?
[Interference]
[Dancing wildly.]
- I don't think I get it.
- What's he doing out there?
He's jump roping.
Pass.
[Next question- The Hulk.]
[I am The Hulk!]
He fell down while screaming.
[Second fall.]
[How humiliating for him...]
[Describing The Hulk
with the use of his entire body.]
[Third fall.]
This isn't going to work.
I'm going to have to explain it.
What's wrong with him?
An alien?
Yoda!
[Yoda?]
[The Hulk is transforming himself
right in front of our very own eyes.]
Don't you even feel sorry for him?
Dracula?
[Time over- Zero questions
answered for Jae Suk's team.]
[Yoda passes out.]
How was I supposed to...
How am I supposed to describe The Hulk?
You seriously didn't get it?
The first one was Dooley.
- What was this?
- The Hulk.
I barely stopped myself from
tearing my shirt open.
When you pulled the shirt over your head,
you looked just like Yoda.
- I almost ripped my shirt open.
- We thought you were ET.
- I can't believe you didn't get any.
- I couldn't get any of it.
It's okay, there's the next game.
Did you notice that
Jae Suk's not even looking at you?
He hasn't looked at you
for the past two minutes.
[Next- Ji Hyo and Seo Joon.
Category- Animals.]
[Seo Joon's impressive jumping skills.]
- He's such a great jumper.
- I'm sorry.
[Question- Giraffe.
How will be describe this one?]
[Seo Joon flies straight up into the air.]
[Huh?]
[That's supposed to be a giraffe?]
He's a really great jumper,
but he can't describe it at all.
[Great jumping skills,
but bad explanation skills.]
Pass.
[Much less...
can't even keep his balance.]
Wow, this is hard.
[Question- A frilled lizard.]
[What is he trying to describe?]
[Blank Ji is slowly starting
to get angry.]
Seo Joon must be really struggling right now.
[Next question- Fly.]
[Comes... and goes...]
[Oh no, what's he going to do?]
- A bug!
- A bug?
You're really bad at explaining things.
[Time over for Blank Ji.]
We actually did a good job with ours.
How is this a frilled lizard?
This is a frilled lizard!
[I'm dead.]
This is a fly!
How is this a fly?
[Ji Hyo... go easy on me.]
[Time to swap out their rocks.]
[Just what role will these rocks play
in the final mission?]
Suk Jin and Choi Hee may come up
for having come in at third place.
[Results of the mission:
Third place- Suk Jin and Choi Hee.]
[Second place- Gary and Min Ah.
First place- Kwang Soo and Narsha.]
You guys got lucky.
[Exchange coupon.]
[First, second and third place winners
are each given an exchange coupon.]
Do you see anything that you
especially want?
He passes over all the difficult decisions
onto his partner.
[Bad Boy Big-nose passes on all
the tough decisions onto his partner.]
- He's such a guy.
- Women are better with jewels.
I don't think this is it.
This one looks weak to me.
[She thinks that Ji Hyo and Seo Joon's rock
appears to be too weak.]
[The final mission and the purpose of
these rocks are still unknown to them all.]
You choose.
That one?
No, that looks too weak.
Two.
- One. Make your decision.
- No, Suk Jin! It's this one!
[Big-nose ultimately makes the decision
to swap theirs out for Ji Hyo and Seo Joon's.]
Go back to your own seats.
This one looks much stronger.
Let's trade it out with the egg.
[What?]
[Gary believes that there's something with
the egg and gambles on the chance.]
[What? An egg?]
Why would you have done that?
[What luck! Kwang Soo
and Narsha get rid of their egg!]
[Lastly, it's time for the first place winners
to swap out their rock.]
[Find the strongest looking rock.]
What the heck?
[Whatever!]
Let go!
[Giraffe explodes.]
What?
[They should be swapping theirs out
for a rock stronger than their own...]
You're asking me to trust you?
What happened with ours?
[Keeping the one they have.]
[Just trust me.]
[All three teams complete
making their decision.]
The next mission will be
your final mission.
If we don't come in at first place,
then is that the end for us?
- Yes.
- I understand.
You heard what he said, right?
Couples like Yoo Jae Suk's couple who
don't even know what they have
or haven't even been able to swap theirs out
are at a great disadvantage at the moment.
We haven't even been able
to get close to it.
This will be your final mission.
This will be your last chance.
Okay, everyone on their way.
[Unbreakable Love-
Off to their next location.]
[Chapter Ten- Love is Hot.]
[Arrives at the next date spot.]
I can already smell all the spicy food.
It's a really popular dating spot.
Ddeokbokki restaurant.
We really have to come in
at first place this time.
There is a team who hasn't even
been able to swap out their rocks.
[Jae Suk and Se Yun haven't had
any chance to swap out their rock.]
[Unbreakable Love- Love is Hot.]
We will give each of the teams
a steaming bowl of ddeokbokki.
[Each team is given 20 ddeokbokki pieces.]
[After the mission is over,
it's time for a ddeokbokki  party.]
We will announce a very simple
couple game
and we will do a drawing of the team
that will first come up to take the challenge.
Then that couple will come forward and choose
the team they'd like to play the game with.
The teams that aren't playing the game will
choose which team they think is going to win
and bet as many ddeokbokki pieces
they'd like to bet on the game.
[The first team to get rid of all their
20 ddeokbokki pieces will win the game.]
First game is, Love is a relay match.
The partners will tie their ankles together.
And they will push the other team down.
It's a sort of a push game.
So the team that pushes the other team down
will win the game.
So it's two against two?
I will now choose the team who will
first participate in this game.
[Time to draw the team
who will be playing the game.]
Who will be the first team to play?
Ha Ha and Han Hye Jin.
They're not of the same height.
Will that be alright?
So they'll have to choose the team that
they're sure they can beat as their opponents?
[In order to win the game,
they'll have to choose an easy opponent.]
[Who will Ha Ha and Hye Jin choose?]
One, two, three.
[Without a doubt- Suk Jin and Choi Hee.]
You think we're that easy?
- I'm going to bet on Suk Jin.
- I'm nervous.
I'm sorry to tell you this, but I'm
not shaking my hand on purpose.
[Big-nose's overly-obvious hand shake.]
I'm depleted of all my energy right now.
Just please go to the hospital.
Take yourself to the hospital!
[The winner of ddakjji war!
After effects of ddakjji efforts.]
And it's because you did too many
of this earlier too.
[And even all the animal charades
that he had to do earlier.]
[Middle aged man's hand shake
from all the strenuous activities.]
We're going to bet on Ha Ha and Hye Jin.
We're going to bet on Dong Hoon and Hye Jin.
- Are you guys seriously?
- We're also betting on Ha Ha and Hye Jin.
Do we just bet on
who we think is going to win?
- Then Ha Ha.
- Yeon Soo!
[Everyone's betting five ddeokbokki pieces
on Ha Ha and Hye Jin.]
[Every single team is betting
their pieces on Ha Ha and Hye Jin's win.]
Everyone that followed Jae Suk's bet
is going to end up regretting it.
- Jae Suk, who did you bet on again?
- I'm not good at things like this.
- I placed my bet on Ha Ha.
- He really is bad at things like this.
I'm just asking out of curiosity,
but did anyone bet on us?
No, no one.
Not a single one of you?
[Other than themselves, not a single team
placed their bet on Suk Jin and Choi Hee.]
If you lose your footing at all,
then you fail the game.
Keep your legs strong.
- Han Hye Jin!
- What the heck?
[Every single team is cheering on
Ha Ha and Hye Jin's team.]
Ready.
[Ha Ha and Hye Jin vs Suk Jin and Choi Hee.]
You can't let him beat you, Dong Hoon!
I'm going to win this!
I'm not going to lose.
[Big-nose immediately launches
his attack on Hye Jin.]
[Unreal.]
[The battle between the two men
to protect their own loves.]
- Ugh, I'm so angry.
- This is too much.
Let's all use both of our hands.
[Okay, let's do this for real!]
[Kiddo is put in danger
as soon as they start.]
[A fiery match between the two teams.]
[This is how it's supposed to be played!]
[This is the fiery match
which we've all been waiting for!]
[Oh? Everyone had placed their bet
on Ha Ha and Hye Jin!]
[We're ruined!]
[Suk Jin and Choi Hee win!]
- Wait a minute.
- Choi Hee!
[Completely unexpected turn of events.]
You did good.
[Big-nose's miracle still continues.]
[Meanwhile, ddeokbokki is cooking
deliciously on the stove.]
Ji Suk Jin and Choi Hee were the only ones
who were able to get rid of five pieces.
This really isn't going well.
Just bet the opposite of
whatever Jae Suk bets on.
[A hundred percent guarantee that
whatever Jae Suk bets on will lose.]
Here's your second game.
Second game is, Love's Sweet Radish.
- Is it like the cookie stick game?
- Yes, you're correct.
We will be playing the cookie stick game
with a sweet radish piece.
The team with the shorter piece
will win the game.
I will pick the team who will
come up first.
[Ji Hyo and Seo Joon.]
Wait a minute.
Are you sure?
Are you sure about this?
What are you guys whispering about?
Let's just get this over with!
- Jong Kook.
- That's right.
[Jong Kook and Yeon Soo.]
I'm going to bet on you guys.
[Love's Sweet Radish-
Ji Hyo, Seo Joon vs Jong Kook, Yeon Soo]
Seo Joon, please take good care of me.
If you back away, then it's over for us.
- I know.
- I'm going to win this.
[Yeon Soo is showing off
her competitive streak.]
You need to stand up and announce
who you're going to place your bet on.
- Can Jae Suk place his bet first?
- Then everyone's going to bet against him.
[Everyone wants to avoid Jae Suk's curse.]
I...
Everyone's looking at me right now.
You're making us nervous.
Hurry up and place your bet.
Yeon Soo will be the only one going here,
but both of them will go on this team.
[Guessing that the two actors,
Ji Hyo and Seo Joon will be the safer bet.]
Suk Jin, we're both actors.
Okay.
Se Yun and I are going to bet
on Ji Hyo and Seo Joon.
Kim Jong Kook!
[The rest of the teams are placing
their bets on Jong Kook and Yeon Soo.]
We're ruined!
[Ji Hyo and Seo Joon are looking
dismayed at Jae Suk's selection.]
We're going to place all our faith
on you and Seo Joon.
[Will Jae Suk's curse continue on?]
- We're placing all our faith in you two.
- Seriously!
In order to keep it really short,
you have to bit it when your teeth touch.
Don't even think about biting off
until I tell you to do so, okay?
[I'm going to win this!]
- Okay.
- She's the best.
- She's going to win this.
- We have to decide who'll go first.
You decide who gets to go first yourselves.
You can decide however you want.
How about we arm wrestle for it?
[That's a cheap shot.]
Oops, I'm sorry.
We'll play Rock, Paper, Scissors for it.
Rock, paper, scissors!
[Ji Hyo and Seo Joon to go first.]
[Competitive Yeon Soo.]
I think we're really going to win this
as long as we bet against Jae Suk.
Seo Joon.
Seriously, Jae Suk!
Don't worry, Ji Hyo.
Do we pick it up with our fingers?
Don't think about what kind of a relationship
you two guys have with each other.
Just play the game and you can just
end it after the game is over. There you go.
- That looks good.
- This is so fun to watch.
Ready.
Why are you getting up so close?
What are you doing, Narsha?
- What is the matter with this lady?
- I want to get a good look.
[We're ready to go.]
[You never imagined that this would be
happening when you met this morning, did you?]
By any chance... are you my partner?
Yes, I am.
[Who knew that this fateful meeting...]
[would lead to such a glorious event?]
Good, they're doing great.
There you go.
You're doing really great!
I told you that we're actors!
[Jae Suk is the only one ecstatic
at the result of Ji Hyo and Seo Joon's turn.]
How big is it?
Wow, you guys really were amazing.
Look at how amazing this is.
This is barely a slice!
[Ji Hyo and Seo Joon turned the
sweet radish into a barely even a slice.]
Wow, this really is...
This is barely even a slice!
I can't help but laugh as I'm
measuring this.
[Unable to stop his laughter.]
- I'm so happy right now.
- Hurry up and measure it.
You guys are couple of treasures.
You guys are really...
Don't go anywhere today.
[Jae Suk just might take them out
for a steak dinner.]
Wow, this really is unbelievable.
- Four?
- 4 mm.
[Ji Hyo and Seo Joon- 4 mm.]
[An unbelievable record
befitting of their actor status.]
- Jong Kook...
- But...
It needs to be paper thin.
We need to be able to see through it.
It needs to be see through.
[You have to do it like this.]
You have to touch each other's mouth.
[In the midst of all this,
Yeon Soo is busy picking out their radish.]
- Yeon Soo.
- Hang on.
I'm going to say this right now, but you
know that our lips will have to touch?
[Only thing Yeon Soo is thinking about
is how they can win the game.]
- She's an actress too.
- I'm going to go with this one.
- We're going to go with this one.
- Pull the table up a little bit.
Sure, let me do that for you.
- When we both feel it, then let's...
- What are you going to be feeling?
[Feel what?]
I meant when we both feel that
it's down to a very small size.
You can't have just the lips meet,
but your teeth have to touch.
[Must get close enough for
their teeth to touch one another's.]
- I know, I know. We got it.
- Take it slow.
Which way are you more comfortable.
Let me see here.
- You can grab each other on the shoulder.
- Tap me on the shoulder as a signal.
It's because we won't be able to speak.
When you feel that you're ready,
lift up one foot like this behind you.
[Kkuk should lift up his foot
when he's ready?]
She's a professional.
Don't worry about her.
We'll go slow.
Okay, we're going to get started.
I don't know if this is going to be okay.
Should we start?
I'm sorry, but why is everyone staring?
[So that we could all see better!]
I'm sorry,
but this is just too good to miss out on.
[All the spectators are lining up to watch.]
- We're going to win this.
- I'll go this way, okay?
- You can bite it off, okay?
- Okay.
Here we go!
[One competitive girl...]
[And one very bashful man.]
Please put down your hand.
Set, go.
There's no need to be in a rush.
[Stop!]
What is this!
It's like a piece of pulp.
It's totally pulp now.
What the heck is this!
[The tiniest sweet radish particle.]
This isn't sweet radish.
It's Jong Kook's tooth.
Jong Kook lost one of his teeth.
[The radish is the size of
one of Jong Kook's teeth.]
- I'm supposed to measure this part?
- What kind of a kiss was that?
That was a sweet radish kiss.
The producers can decide on this one.
Wow, Yeon Soo is something else.
If I were to speak for
the rest of the producers...
- With only a 0.1mm difference...
- Be very precise about this.
This is a very precise calculation.
Kim Jong Kook and Yeon Soo win.
[With only a 0.1mm difference,
Jong Kook and Yeon Soo wins.]
[Jae Suk's curse continues on.]
What have you done to us!
[Yeon Soo's impressive work!]
[Jae Suk's never-ending curse.]
We really are all over without even
having seen our rock even once.
Currently in first place...
is Suk Jin and Choi Hee with ten less
ddeokbokki pieces than anyone else.
Then there are two teams who share
the last place spot.
Yoo Jae Suk and Song Ji Hyo teams
both each have 20 ddeokbokki pieces.
- This isn't over yet.
- No, it's not over yet.
- So they're tied?
- Seo Joon and Ji Hyo did so well too.
[Ddeokbokki is almost finished cooking...]
This is your third round.
I had no idea that a simple game would
exhaust me out like this.
Yeah, I bet it did.
Yeah, I bet you're tired.
Then have you finally decided
that your heart belongs to Yeon Soo?
- He's finally moved on from 'her'.
- Round three.
Goodbye.
Seriously!
- What?
- Stop it.
Can't I even say goodbye
to someone I'm friends with?
[Goodbye... it's all over now.]
The next game is... Egg Love You.
It must have something to do with an egg.
You have to crack and peel a hardboiled egg
on your head and eat it.
But there could be a raw egg.
It's always Kwang Soo.
[The very same game that the variety gods
have gifted Kwang Soo with.]
- You have to crack it on your partner's head.
- This truly is all about luck.
- Then you'll have to eat it.
- On your partner's head?
- Yes, on your partner's head.
- This for sure will be Kwang Soo.
Okay, us three teams will do it.
Let's all bet ten pieces each.
[Gary-Min Ah, Kwang Soo-Narsha,
Jae Suk-Se Yun are up.]
You have to bet on the losing team.
- I bet ten pieces on Yoo Jae Suk.
- We'll bet ten pieces on Kwang Soo.
- We bet ten on Gary.
There's no need to draw this out.
- Let's just move this along.
- Do it quickly.
- Let's go, Se Yun.
- Once you grab it, then it's yours.
You can't touch it to test it out.
[Jae Suk and Se Yun goes first.]
[Jae Suk and Se Yun- A hardboiled egg.]
Se Yun, you have to smash it harder.
- Smash it harder.
- This is good.
[Kwang Soo and Narsha's turn.]
There's not much time.
[Will Kwang Soo get it
in the first try again?]
Two, one.
You have to smash it as soon
as you grab it.
One, two, three.
[Hardboiled egg.]
[This is what you call entertaining.]
That's how you do it.
That's how you smash it, Se Yun.
Smash it really hard.
You did good.
You did really good, Narsha.
[Gary and Min Ah's turn.]
[Hardboiled egg.]
[Sorry, Gary.]
[One full round is made,
and it's back to Jae Suk and Se Yun.]
- This one is it.
- Raw egg!
[Jae Suk and Se Yun get the raw egg.]
[Even though he's covered in raw egg,
Jae Suk and Se Yun still wins!]
Wow, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin's in first place,
and I'm in second place!
[They finally get to see their rock.]
I'm sure that you all must be pretty hungry
so enjoy your ddeokbokki
while we get your cars ready.
[As promised, they finally get to
enjoy their ddeokbokki party.]
[Along with the hardboiled eggs and
the sweet radish they just used.]
[Enjoying the delicious snacks with
their partners and friends.]
[Enjoying a delicious snack with each other
is all part of the fun on a date.]
The cheese adds some richness to it.
[Chapter Eleven- Unbreakable Love.]
[Final location.]
Thank you to everyone for participating
in all the dating games today.
New love is budding everywhere.
Here are the rocks that have stood as your
symbol of strength of your love all day
along with the egg that stood
as part of testimony to your love.
All these have been measured by
the Moh's Hardness Scale.
Here's your final mission.
It's the Rock Battle of Love.
Each couple will have to smash their
rocks against the other team's rocks
and the team who has the rock that still
remains unbroken to the end wins the race.
So we smash it against others?
Can you just throw our egg out?
We thought we were being clever by
choosing to go with the egg.
Gary chose to do that.
First through third place winning teams will
be given a hint and an exchange coupon.
[Third place- Jong Kook and Yeon Soo.]
[Will tell you which three teams has
the three of the weakest rocks.]
[Gary-Min Ah, Suk Jin-Choi Hee,
and Jae Suk-Se Yun.]
- You have one chance to make an exchange.
- Just one?
You have thirty seconds.
I don't think it's this one.
It's way too shiny.
I think you're right about this
one being hard.
- I think it could be this one too.
- Seriously?
[Contemplating between Kwang Soo-Narsha
and Ha Ha-Hye Jin's rocks.]
This one.
[Jong Kook and Se Yun swap
theirs out with Ha Ha and Hye Jin's.]
Wow, so this is what it looks like!
Take a good look.
Let's look through them all.
[Fascinated by all the rocks
that they're seeing for the first time.]
[You can ask any one question,
and I will answer with a 'Yes' or a 'No'.]
[Is our rock stronger than
Suk Jin and Choi Hee's rock?]
The rock that you have is weaker
than Suk Jin and Choi Hee's rock.
I knew it.
I could tell that just from looking at it.
Okay, you do have a chance
to make a swap.
It's either this one or that one.
It's one or the other.
I'm pretty sure it's this one.
We're going to swap it out for this one.
[Jae Suk and Se Yun swaps theirs out
for Ha Ha and Hye Jin's rock.]
- This is your final hint.
- We had no other choice.
[Time for Suk Jin and Choi Hee's turn
to make their swap.]
[We will let you know which teams
have the four strongest rocks.]
Listen carefully.
Here are the top four teams.
This is in no specific order.
The teams are, Jong Kook-Yeon Soo,
Kwang Soo-Narsha, Jae Suk-Se Yun
and finally, Ji Hyo and Seo Joon.
So ours isn't one of them.
You have one chance to make a swap.
Who were the teams again?
[Must swap theirs out for one of the
four teams mentioned.]
I think it's this one.
We've made our choice.
[Suk Jin and Choi Hee swaps theirs out
for Jong Kook and Yeon Soo's rock.]
[Final rock selection for all the couples.]
[Time for the Love Rock Battle to start!]
Okay, here's your first battle.
Gary and Min Ah vs Ha Ha and Han Hye Jin.
We'll for sure win this one.
Place one on the bottom and
smash down on the other from the top.
We're going to win this.
We don't want all the egg yolk to splatter,
so we'll smash down on yours.
Why are you so convinced that
this is actually an egg?
- I'm positive that it's an egg.
- One, two...
I doubt Running Man would be that simple.
Ugh, what are we going to do
with this now?
[Ha Ha and Hye Jin wins.]
Lee Kwang Soo and Narsha.
[Ha Ha and Hye Jin vs Kwang Soo and Narsha.]
Be careful of your hands.
[Ha Ha and Hye Jin to go first.]
Okay!
- We won this!
- That wasn't even a competition!
[Kwang Soo and Narsha win.]
- We just totally destroyed yours.
- What is this thing?
We turned yours into a pile of
powdered sugar.
Next up is Kim Jong Kook and Ha Yeon Soo.
- I don't think that's going to do it.
- I thought that was going to be the hardest.
Is that soap?
It smells really good.
Is it soap?
Jong Kook can smash down even a boulder
with a bar of soap.
- Please, please...
- I think Jong Kook will win this.
I really want to beat Jong Kook!
Go ahead. I'm telling you
that Jong Kook has a good one.
I think I'm right.
Okay, now the other way.
Lee Kwang Soo can smash his down.
What are you doing?
We have to have our turn now.
You can't do that.
[Two pieces]
[Kwang Soo and Narsha win!]
[Kwang Soo and Narsha must have
a very strong piece of rock.]
Ji Suk Jin and Choi Hee.
We're going already?
That doesn't sound right.
- I thought Suk Jin would go last.
- That looks like it's from outer space.
I don't know how this may end
but if Lee Kwang Soo's rock remains in
that state, then he has the strongest rock.
Is that understood?
[Suk Jin and Choi Hee to go first.]
[Suk Jin and Choi Hee's rock
is shattered into pieces.]
[Kwang Soo and Narsha win.]
[Big-nose is not accepting his loss.]
[Suk Jin and Choi Hee's rock is split in half,
and thus loses the battle.]
Kwang Soo's rock must be the strongest.
[Could Kwang Soo and Narsha really
have the strongest rock?]
[Kwang Soo and Narsha
vs Ji Hyo and Seo Joon.]
Ours isn't broken yet.
Okay!
[Ji Hyo and Seo Joon's rock
is also broken down in half.]
[Kwang Soo and Narsha's rock
beats four in a row.]
It's not that theirs is that strong,
but it's because of the large size.
- Why does the size even matter?
- That's why it's breaking everything.
[Kwang Soo and Narsha vs
Jae Suk and Se Yun.]
[It's time... for the final battle.]
[The stronger of these two will be
the final winner of the day.]
So if they beat us now,
then they win the whole race?
The team with the unbroken rock
wins the whole race.
[This will determine who the
winner will be.]
[Please break... break...]
[The winner is still undetermined.]
This is not being broken.
This is just some dust falling off of it.
- You need to really break it.
- They both must be really strong.
Come on, just a little bit.
[Please... break!]
[Kwang Soo and Narsha's rock
is shattered into pieces!]
[Jae Suk and Se Yun win!]
Se Yun!
I can't believe we did it!
- Se Yun!
- That's unbelievable.
I can't believe that even happened!
[They win the whole race by swapping out their
rock with the one chance that they've had.]
[The ultimate token of love...
a diamond ring.]
You're giving us this huge diamond ring?
It's a one carat diamond.
[The winning prize is a diamond ring.]
- How much is that worth?
- That was our rock!
- I'm the luckiest one here today!
The strongest rock is the mineral
with elements of diamond in it.
But the rock you had was one step below
with elements of ruby in it.
One carat diamond ring!
I'd like to give this to my partner, Se Yun.
[Ultimate winners of today's race-
Jae Suk and Se Yun.]
Why did you suddenly swap out our prize
from gold to diamond?
Are you going to give out
an apartment next week?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Chapter Twelve-
The Legend's Next Chapter.]
Our eternal captain, Park Ji Sung!
It's a training race.
[Captain Park Ji Sung returns
to help train for 2014 Dream Cup.]
You really are awful at it.
[Another living legend who has come
to lend a helping hand to Park Ji Sung.]
[Sniper Seol Ki Hyon.]
[Coach Seol Ki Hyon along with
the strongest idol athletes.]
[And...]
[The oxygen tank is back in action
in order to bring home the victory.]
[Witness Park Ji Sung's full power
in person.]
[The meeting of two living legends.]
[Cha Bum Geun and Park Ji Sung.]
[Cha Bum's one point lesson.]
[A mission competition with both
of these legends' pride on the line.]
[A legend cannot accept any defeat.]
Get me a pair of soccer shoes.
[The story of these two men who have
dedicated their lives to soccer now begins.]
[A legend meets another legend.]