[Team Running Man-
Representatives of variety shows.]
[Team Angel- Representatives of dramas.]
[A fierce battle between the two teams.]
[Taking place in the largest set in history.]
[In a battle where no mercy exists.]
[A battle that requires the best
Team Work, Intelligence, and Stamina.]
[Variety world vs Drama world-
With the honor of each category on the line.]
[It all starts now!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Early spring of 2014.
A park in the city of Seoul.]
[An enormous setup in the park.]
[Team Running Man makes their entrance.]
What is this hand thing we're doing?
- I've never done this before.
- Why are we doing all this?
- We are... Running Man!
- We've never done this before.
[Team Running Man]
[They seemed to be confused as they
come down from the lift platform.]
I had no idea that you guys would be so
happy by something so simple as a lift.
You should've done this for us sooner.
We loved doing that.
This is the first time you've ever done
something like that for us.
That was the first time I've ever done
something like that in half a century.
As you can see behind you,
the sign says, 'Team Running Man'.
Then are we all on the same team?
I know that you guys all worked very hard
during our recent trip to Australia
and it seems as though you've only been
working separately lately.
So as you can see, you all will be
teamed up together on the same team.
- Then I bet we'll have seven guests today.
- Are we going to battle another team?
- Is it going to be a younger team?
- Not many people can beat us as a team.
Yeah, there aren't many teams out there
who can beat us together as a team.
Let's see who our opponents are.
Please come on out!
[Who will their opponents be?]
- If it's seven people...
- That's so cool!
[Could they be Idols?]
- Grey hair? Is it a movie director?
- They're not idols.
[We will take on
the Running Man Team today.]
[Team Angel Eyes.]
[Full of friendly faces.]
I saw Seung Ri earlier this morning.
We live in the same apartment building,
but we both ignored each other.
I wondered if he was going to be on today,
so I purposely ignored him when I saw him.
[Welcome to Running Man.]
[Everyone seems to be
very glad to see each other.]
[A fiery competitive atmosphere
right off the bat.]
- We can take them on!
- We can totally take them on!
[Extremely confident Team Running Man.]
I'll take charge of Kwon Hae Hyo.
When I saw Hae Hyo from the back...
You know how when you watch the news,
you sometimes see a team of scientists?
I thought that it was a group of
scientists who came to visit us.
[A team of scientists who are here
to help save the earth?]
[Please save our planet...]
So are these the seven guests whom
we'll be competing against today?
- Yes.
- We really can do this.
Sang Yoon and I played brothers
in the recent drama we were in together.
[Sang Yoon and Kwang Soo played brothers
in a recent drama that they were in together.]
[Ah... that idiotic prince?]
We all know you played the idiot prince.
I told you time and time again,
Mang Goo, Young Goo and Kwang Soo.
[Korea's representative idiots-
Mang Goo, Young Goo, and Kwang Soo.]
[Kwang Soo is one of the three
national idiot representatives.]
Can you all say a word to the viewers?
Let's start with Gu Hye Sun.
It's been so long since
I've been on a variety show.
- Wow, you really are so beautiful.
- Thank you.
[Gu Hye Sun-
Brighter than the spring sun.]
[Her skin is not just porcelain white,
it's almost transparent.]
Standing next to Hae Hyo is
making you look even prettier.
[Swaps out his place immediately.]
[From a research scientist
to a petty company president.]
- Can you say something, Sang Yoon?
- Nice to meet you, my name is Lee Sang Yoon.
[Lee Sang Yoon- Nation's 'Best Friend'.]
- Can you say a word, Hae Hyo?
- It's nice to be here.
- I think it's been about ten years now?
- Seriously?
It really has been a long time since you've
been a guest star on a variety show.
I've been a huge fan of yours ever since
the drama, 'Mister Q'.
What was the last variety show
that you guest starred on?
I don't remember.
It was sometime in the nineties.
[His first guest starring role on a
variety show in the 21st century!]
It's nice to meet you all.
My name is Kim Ji Suk.
[Flower boy next door actor, Kim Ji Suk.]
He's a total airhead.
I'm telling you that he is.
- I agree, he is an airhead.
- He used to be 'Kwang Soo' back in the day.
[Kwang Soo's formidable rival.]
It's been a while since Ji Suk has been
on a variety show though.
- But his image has changed a lot.
- It's changed completely.
But I'm sure that it'll resurface today.
[You all wait for it.
Kim Ji Suk will show his true side later on.]
Ha Neul!
Hello, my name is Kang Ha Neul
and I played a character named 'Lee Hyo Shin'
on the set of the recently aired drama, 'Heirs'.
[The rising new star, Kang Ha Neul.]
Hello, my name is Seung Ri of Big Bang.
[The cutie pie of Big Bag, Seung Ri.]
You paid a lot of attention to
your outfit today.
[His outfit looks like a magician's outfit
from some magic show in Las Vegas.]
It's nice to meet you all.
This is my first appearance on Running Man.
[Popular actor of our time, Gong Hyung Jin.]
So are we going to be competing
against them?
Yes, it's variety world's Team Running Man,
and drama world's team Angel Eyes.
[Variety world's Team Running Man vs
Drama world's Team Angel Eyes.]
[7:7 Super Match!]
Gold envelopes?
Are they going to give us money?
- I think they're giving us money.
- There are two envelopes in front of you.
One envelope is from the drama department,
and the other is from the variety department.
Those two envelopes...
the winning team will take both.
[Both of the golden envelopes will be
given out to today's winning team.]
I have a feeling that the envelope from
the drama department will have more in it.
- You think so?
- They've got the bigger bucks.
They even send their actors on a trip when
their drama wraps up.
- I know.
- We just went to Australia ourselves.
- We went there to film an episode.
- We worked while we were there.
We can't go on any trips because
our show is constantly ongoing.
Because if we go on trips,
it means they're getting rid of our show.
That's why we can't go on any trips.
[To our dear viewers...
please show your love for variety shows.]
Sending us on a trip means
they're getting rid of our show.
[A sudden somber atmosphere...]
Today's competition will be between
Team Running Man and Team Angel Eyes.
Today's race is,
'Selection of the Top Rescue Team'.
[Team Running Man vs Team Angel Eyes.]
[Only one top rescue team.]
[Winner of each round will be given the
first choice option at the final mission.]
You must use your option wisely to
bring home the victory to you and your team.
I will now tell you your first location.
You must all go to the observatory
in Yeouido.
[Variety department vs Drama department-
Battle of the two departments' honor.]
[Team Running Man is back together again
for the first time in a long time.]
I wonder if the writers gave us an easy team
on purpose to boost up our spirits.
It takes more than an average team now
to beat us as a team.
Ji Suk is their hole.
[Variety world's original black hole, Ji Suk.]
Sang Yoon's really bad at
anything athletic too.
- Who?
- He's the type to drop the ball all the time.
We should all take charge of one person.
Ji Hyo can take charge of Hye Sun.
- Ji Hyo will beat Hye Sun for sure.
- And I'll take care of Hae Hyo.
[Big-nose to take charge of Hae Hyo.]
This means that a third of that team
is pretty much equivalent to Kwang Soo.
[Those are pretty good odds?]
[Team Running Man arrives first at
the location, full of confidence.]
Let's go in!
[What is the mission that awaits them
in that tall skyscraper?]
I wonder what we'll be doing here?
- I wonder if we're doing a race in here?
- I think we have a mission in here.
- Are you warming up?
- Yes, of course.
- Suk Jin looks confident of himself today.
- He's our 'ace' today.
[Big-nose seems to be
pretty sure of himself today.]
Suk Jin has his eyes on Ji Suk today.
- Ji Suk's really good.
- No, Ji Suk's not that good.
[You know what he's like...]
[He could be described as
last decade's 'Kwang Soo'?]
This is your first round.
[Team Running Man vs Team Angel Eyes-
First round competition.]
This is a 'loyalty relay race',
which will test your teamwork skills.
[Loyalty relay race?]
- I'm so scared.
- You know what this place is, right?
Let's not do anything that requires
climbing up flights of stairs or anything.
[No way... NO WAY...]
Why do you think we're here
at the 63 Building?
You'll need to climb the stairs from
first floor up to sixtieth in the form of relay.
[Stair climbing from first floor through
sixtieth in a form of relay.]
[Are you... kidding me?]
It's possible that you're going to send
Hae Hyo home during the first mission.
- Sixty floors?
- We'll get a good workout in, so it's nice.
The last relay runner needs to pull their
team's colored flag located on the last floor.
And you can decide amongst yourselves how
many floors each of you will climb.
[Order and the number of floors
they'll climb is up to them.]
[63 Loyalty Relay]
[A total of 60 floors.]
[Up to them to decide how many floors
each player will be responsible for.]
[The first team to reach the top floor to
pull out the flag wins the round.]
Don't you think that Jong Kook should
climb up at least 20 floors?
- No, no.
- 20 floors, at least.
So how many floors is that per person?
Nine floors per person?
In fact, Jong Kook can take
all sixty floors on his own.
[60 floors...
a walk in the park for this guy.]
Who do you think that
I'll be able to beat from that team?
I think that I'd be able to be faster
than Ha Ha at least.
- No, Ha Ha's fast.
- He's fast?
No, you need to take on Suk Jin.
Did you just stay that you think
that you'd be faster than me?
- No, Ji Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
- Hae Hyo is totally dissing us right now.
- How many floors are you climbing up?
- You don't know who you're talking to.
- We have to be quick, right?
[Totally fired up!]
You're tying your shoelaces too tight.
You're going to cut off your circulation.
Your feet are going to turn all blue.
Are you taking off your jacket right now?
- I'm starting to get all sweaty.
- Seriously, Hae Hyo.
Do I need to start warming up here?
[This is how you warm up
in the variety world!]
[Mr. Capable is on the loose!]
[It's Jamsil dance king, Mr. Gary's turn!]
[Ouch, the ankle bone...]
- No, I'm okay.
- He's okay.
It's okay, it'll be peach season soon.
(Ankle bone in Korean=peach bone.)
- You stay out of this!
- Get back in line.
- Why? Why can't I join in?
- Just get back in line.
Everyone take place in line
in the order that you'll be going.
- Let's go!
- Let's do this!
[A teamwork mission-
The 63 Loyalty Relay.]
[Climbing up 60 flights of stairs.
Mission impossible starts now!]
- Is Jong Kook the last player?
- Of course he is.
That's what always seems to happen.
Have you ever seen a bus
change its route?
[The never-changing and always constant
Running Man muscle route.]
[Seung Ri vs Blank Ji]
[Hae Hyo vs Ha Ha]
So you're the third runner?
I thought it might've been Hye Sun.
We're starting out with our weakest players,
but you guys seem to be the opposite.
Who are you calling weak?
This race is no laughing matter.
It's like a race of death.
['Kwang Soo' of ten years ago...
erase the old Ji Suk out of your memory?]
I'll show you what I'm capable of today.
[Ji Suk vs Jae Suk]
[Hyung Jin vs Kwang Soo]
Can you tell me which is faster?
[One- Three stairs at a time.]
That's the first option.
[Two- Four stairs at a time.]
That's the second option.
[Three- Two stairs at a time.]
[There's more?]
[Four- One stair at a time.]
- Which was the fastest?
- The first one.
- Three stairs at a time?
- Yes.
[Sixth player, Mr. Gary, on the 39th floor.]
[Sang Yoon vs Gary]
[Hye Sun vs Jong Kook]
A little bit of anxiety always helps.
[Standby]
I'm nervous!
[Next players waiting on standby
wait around nervously.]
Standby.
Oh my God!
[Only one chance at a victory...
that one crucial moment... will start now.]
Ugh, I'm exhausted.
Go!
[63 Relay- Start the race!]
[A fierce physical battle
right from the start.]
[Ha Neul arrives at the stairs first.]
[They must climb up 60 flights of stairs!]
I can feel the vibration of their footsteps.
Hey, wait for me!
[Ha Neul of Team Angel leaves
Suk Jin in his wake.]
[The ever widening gap
between the two players.]
[Blank Ji of Team Running Man is getting
antsy while waiting up on the sixth floor.]
Hurry, Suk Jin!
Come on, hurry!
- I can still catch up to him.
- Here.
[Team Running Man.
Big-nose to Blank Ji- Baton is passed off.]
This is only the seventh floor,
but why am I feeling so exhausted?
[Blank Ji takes advantage of his exhaustion
to catch up to him!]
[Ha Neul's pace is starting to slow down.]
[vs Ace Blank Ji who's start to
pick up her pace more and more.]
- Move!
- No!
[That's our Ace!
She's already caught up to him!]
- What is it?
- It's nothing!
[Seung Ri is surprised to see
this unexpected scenario.]
Ha Ha!
[Seung Ri pushes Blank Ji out of his way.]
[Baton is passed off
to the third runner, Haroro.]
It's much harder than I thought
it would be.
The steps... the steps are too high.
The steps are way too high.
[Ha Neul is feeling dizzy from having
climbed up ten flights of stairs.]
Hurry!
[Quick footed Seung Ri takes the lead.]
[And Haroro moves quick
to catch up from behind.]
I can hear them getting closer.
- You hear them?
- Yes.
[Haroro steals the lead!]
You don't exercise much, do you?
[Ha Ha prances up the stairs
on his short legs.]
[Team Running Man.
Ha Ha To Jae Suk- Baton pass off.]
We're Running Man!
These are the skills that we've worked hard
to hone in on for the past four years.
I caught up to him and took over the lead.
What is this?
What is this!
[Team Angel's plan isn't going
as well as they had planned!]
What happened?
[Young Seung Ri that they had put
their faith in... is barely able to crawl.]
[Crawls up the last few steps to
pass off his baton.]
Oh my goodness!
[Already a two story gap
between the two teams.]
Jae Suk!
[Huh?]
[Ji Suk in the lead?]
- Where's your baton?
- We have a 20 floor lead on you guys.
- Huh?
- I'm just kidding.
You totally had me fooled!
[Ji Suk got bored from all the waiting,
and decided to play a prank on Kwang Soo.]
I hear someone.
I only hear one set of footsteps.
No!
You're going to have to trample over me.
[Jae Suk in the lead,
arrives on the 28th floor already.]
[Ji Suk's desperate attempts to block him.]
Jae Suk!
[Pushes through Ji Suk's block,
and passes off the baton to Kwang Soo.]
[Hae Hyo pulls his weight to
shorten the gap between the teams a bit.]
You should hurry.
[Hae Hyo is about to drop on his face.]
Kwang Soo sounds like he's vomiting.
Hey, Kwang Soo!
[Giraffe is on the verge of throwing up.]
Ji Suk!
[Ji Suk with a goal catches up to Kwang Soo.]
Gary!
I don't think I can go up any further!
[Wow! Ji Suk really has changed!
He's ready to pass off his baton!]
[However...]
[A leopard doesn't change their spots.]
[A true airhead who loses out on his chance
to take over the lead.]
[But Hyung Jin blocks
Kwang Soo off with his body.]
Gary!
[Gary of Team Running Man finally
gets his hands on the baton.]
[That is one tortured looking face.]
I feel like I'm going to start crying.
Ugh, seriously.
[I feel like death...]
[Gary is right on his tail!]
- You already look exhausted!
- Stop it!
- You're blocking the inner lane.
- There's no way I'm letting you take that.
You saw the short track race,
haven't you?
[Outer course is where all the fun is...]
[What?
Sang Yoon is right above their heads?]
Hurry, Sang Yoon!
I have to do this for Hye Sun!
I need to hurry for Hye Sun!
[Arriving on the 46th floor!
Players of both teams give it their all!]
[Hye Sun is the last runner for Team Angel.
Sang Yoon needs to buy her some lead!]
[Team Running Man's last runner, Kkuk,
gets on his way!]
[Quite a huge gap between the two teams.]
[However...]
[The beast makes his entrance!]
[Runs up the two flights of stairs
in the blink of an eye!]
[He takes over the lead!]
[There's no end
to the strength of his muscles...]
[But he gets held up by Hye Sun
on the 55th floor.]
Please don't go.
- Is this it? Is this the 60th floor?
- What?
[But there's something that even
the Muscle Boy can't win against...]
[The power of a pretty girl.]
- How many flights of stairs have you climbed?
- What?
[Continuing to engage him in conversation and
blocking him from taking the lead.]
Hye Sun.
[You two look like you're here on a date.]
[Arrives at the art gallery on
the 60th floor together.]
- Where do we have to go?
- Where do we go?
[Where you need to go is...]
[To the observatory on the 60th floor where
the whole city skyline can be seen.]
[Must we really pull the flag
and end this round?]
[Jong Kook, what are you doing
up there?]
I'm sorry, Hye Sun!
[Victory is victory!
Must get to his flag first!]
Congratulations,
you pulled out your flag first.
You will now start your real mission.
[What do you mean, 'real mission'?]
What happened?
Here's a walkie-talkie.
[Each member in the stairwell receives
a radio transmitter.]
[A radio transmitter?
What do you want us to do with these?]
[Radio transmitters are passed out
to all the team members.]
You will now start your real mission.
Blue Team, you pulled your flag out first.
Of the 60 flights of stairs which
your team just climbed up
what's the writing that was written
underneath the tiger?
[Say what?]
[Say what about the tiger?]
[In truth, having to climb up 60 flights
of stairs was a fake mission.]
[There's a painting hanging on the wall
in the stairwell of each floor.]
There were a lot of paintings there,
weren't there?
Okay, here's a question for Gu Hye Sun
for coming in at second place.
What is the picture that was drawn above
the writing, 'Rock and Roll'?
- What did you say?
- That's your question.
If you know the answer, then tell me now,
or if not, then you get a radio transmitter.
- A radio transmitter?
- Here.
[They are each given their own transmitter
to allow them to communicate with other.]
The tiger painting...
what's the writing written under the tiger?
Ji Hyo, did you win or lose?
What happened, Jong Kook?
[No one's even listening because
they're all too busy talking themselves.]
I need a bottle of water and a snack.
Who's this?
You need to find the tiger painting.
Hurry and look on the floor you're on.
Did you win or lose?
Just tell me that.
And an ice cold Americano.
[A total chaotic mess-
Team Running Man isn't communicating well.]
[On the other hand...]
A painting with the writing, 'Rock and Roll'
written on it somewhere?
Where's the painting that
she's talking about?
The writing, 'Rock and Roll'.
And the drawing that's drawn above it.
Is she saying that there's
something there?
[Team Angel starts to investigate
all the pictures and paintings.]
[Not even any static on the transmitter.
Everyone listens closely to do their share.]
What's going on here?
What is this?
What's going on?
What is it?
Do you not know which floor it's on?
[Of all these numerous paintings,
there is only one painting of a tiger.]
[It's on the 14th floor that
Ha Ha and Seung Ri ran by.]
What is the writing that's written
underneath the tiger?
[The writing underneath the tiger?]
What's the picture that's painted above
the writing, 'Rock and Roll'?
[The picture that's painted above
the writing, 'Rock and Roll'?]
Look through all the paintings and see if
you can find the writing, 'Rock and Roll'.
Somewhere amongst these stairwells
are some written words.
It's the writing, 'Rock and Roll',
and the picture painted above the writing.
Under the tiger picture.
Are you guys all listening to me?
Find out what's written under that picture,
and tell me what it says.
[None of these seven members are listening
for they're all too busy talking themselves.]
Is there a mission?
There's something written under
the picture of a tiger!
Underneath the tiger picture!
[They're finally starting to pay attention
after hearing the anger in Kkuk's voice.]
Picture of a tiger?
Tiger isn't the problem right now.
I can't even walk at the moment.
[Only Ace Blank Ji starts to catch on,
and begins searching through the paintings.]
[Team Angel on the other hand,
are all searching for 'Rock and Roll'.]
What are you doing?
What is it?
- You don't need to know.
- Where are all my team members?
[Stops using the transmitter
to shout down the stairwell himself.]
Picture of a tiger!
[Not a very clear message-
Only knows to look for the tiger.]
[Did he really say the picture of a tiger?]
[Blank Ji discovers the picture of
a tiger on the 14th floor!]
[The correct answer
is right in front of her eyes!]
[So what about the picture of the tiger?]
[Just then,
Ha Neul also discovers the painting.]
[And Seung Ri also comes down
to join them by the painting.]
Bogoship!
- Bogoship?
- You want me to go somewhere?
No, this isn't 'Rock and Roll'.
Eagle!
Jong Kook, it's a white headed eagle!
[Huh?]
[Since she's unclear about her mission,
she does the opponent's mission instead.]
[Immediately punishes anyone
who tries to get in her way.]
[I'm Song Ji Hyo!]
It's the white headed eagle,
and the tiger is, 'Bogoship'!
- Hurry up and climb up the stairs!
- Where's the picture of the tiger?
Bogoship!
What about the tiger?
- What did you say?
- White headed eagle!
What did you say?
[Seung Ri is relentless in his attempt
to get in Blank Ji's way.]
[Delinquent Blank Ji explodes from within.]
Rock and Roll is, white headed eagle!
- Bogoship.
- What's going on here?
Take her radio transmitter away from her.
Hey, get away from me!
[What did I tell you?
I'm Song Ji Hyo!]
[Frustrated Kkuk had gone down
ten flights of stairs.]
What did you say?
[Jong Kook, please...]
What are they saying?
I can't hear anything.
[Chatty Running Man members.
They're all still talking amongst themselves.]
Kim Jong Kook, what is your answer?
[What is the word that is written underneath
the picture of the tiger?]
Tiger and the eagle?
What did you say?
- What did you say?
- Bogoship!
What about 'Bogoship'?
- Under the tiger is, 'Bogoship'.
- She said, under the tiger is, 'Bogoship'.
Bo-go-ship.
Bogoshipda!
(I miss you)
- Take the 'da' off in the end.
- Take the 'da' off. Just 'Bogoship'.
Correct answer is, 'bogoship'.
[The three letter word under
the picture is?]
[Hye Sun, who's been sitting in the corner
waiting for the answer from her teammates.]
[What is the meaning of that smile?]
- Did we win?
- I don't know.
She hit my head so many times that
I can't even seem to think straight.
Why did she hit you when the
game is over?
- Is the game over?
- I don't know. Did we win?
[They find a lifeless zombie in
the elevator.]
- Are you alright?
- Did we win?
- No one knows.
- The reason why I'm sure of our win...
- Listen to me for a minute.
- But Ji Suk, why are you with Kwang Soo?
Didn't we just win the game?
- When did they take over the lead?
- Who, me?
[No one seems to know
what they're talking about.]
[Guys, I'm right here...]
[He's right here waiting for you guys.]
[Someone save me...]
Why isn't it stopping?
[Even the elevators are ignoring them.]
- What were you guys doing?
- I couldn't understand what you said.
[Everyone comes to gather on
the 60th floor.]
- I couldn't understand what he said.
- I couldn't understand either.
The tiger!
['Tiger' that no one seems to
have heard.]
Tiger!
And it was, 'Bogoship'!
[No one is able to understand each other.]
- I'm sorry!
- What were you thinking?
[Airhead, Ji Suk.
Proves himself to be their black hole.]
- We told you that he's not very good.
- He's not good at all.
He got carried up the stairs by Kwang Soo.
[Leopards really don't
change their spots, do they?]
Anyways, the winning team is,
Team Angel Eyes.
[Winning team is, Team Angel Eyes?]
[Huh?]
What are you talking about?
We won this game.
[Ten minutes ago...
when Kkuk was starting to get angry.]
[Hye Sun sat calmly on the bench listening
to her teammates on the transmitter.]
What's the picture above the words,
'Rock and Roll'?
Everyone go back to your starting point,
and look through all the paintings.
[Team Angel moved according to their
calmly thought out plan.]
[Great teamwork... working in perfect sync.]
[While Seung Ri tried to thwart Blank Ji off
after having discovered the answer...]
[Ha Neul calmly relayed the answer to
his teammates one level at a time.]
It's an eagle!
Do I have to pull this out?
[Team Angel wins the Teamwork Game.]
[And while she quietly sits in the corner
to catch her breath...]
[Kkuk returns with his answer.]
[Team Running Man were so confident of
themselves before the game began.]
[Totally humiliated and befuddled.]
I think it's a hint.
[What special advantage did
the winning team earn themselves?]
[First option]
The more you earn those option tickets,
the better off you'll be at the end.
[Collecting as many of those tickets as they
can will give them an upper hand in the end!]
[Team Running Man vs Team Angel-
Off to their next location.]
[Conversing about Seung Ri's tactic.]
[Complimenting Hye Sun's clear instructions.]
I didn't want the background noise to
interfere with what I was telling you.
So that's why I went off to a quiet place
to talk into the transmitter to everyone.
Who lost the lead to the other team?
It was you, Kwang Soo, wasn't it?
- Let's be honest here.
- I gave us a lead.
[Everyone blaming one another.]
[Team Running Man's chaotic,
and unclear transmitter message.]
[This is the team where every single one
of their members had something to say.]
[Second mission location-
Seoul Civil Administration Office.]
- We need to show them this time.
- It would be humiliating to lose again.
This is nice. Doesn't it feel like we're
building teamwork before we start our drama?
Yeah, this is really nice.
[Their friendships are getting built deeper
as they climb up and down these steps.]
It's a quiz!
Isn't that a quiz setting?
[Bingo!
It is a quiz!]
- We're confident in this game!
- I'll take the entertainment category!
There's a Seoul University graduate
on that team.
- Yeah, you're right.
- I forgot Sang Yoon went to Seoul University.
[They remember that Sang Yoon is
a graduate of Seoul University.]
- Sang Yoon is a Seoul University alumni.
- I recently graduated.
- Must be nice.
- It's okay, because we have Jae Suk.
This round will be a quiz contest to
test the two teams.
[Round two- Quiz Battle.]
It'll be done in an 'All-Kill' method.
[Team Angel is full of intellectuals.]
As you probably all know, the mics in front
of you will blow puffs of air.
If you give the wrong answer, then a puff
of air will be blown in your face.
We'll make sure to get hit in the face
with the air if we're wrong.
[That's what you call 'variety humor'.]
You have to get hit in the mouth.
That looks the funniest.
[Variety veteran, Big-nose, gives them
a quick lesson on how to be funny.]
Since we have the members of
Team Angel here as our guests today...
we have chosen different professions that you
often see in dramas to suit our guests.
[A quiz based on different professions
that you often see in dramas.]
Now you may determine amongst yourselves
who will start off the quiz battle.
- Why don't we start with Hae Hyo?
- We should start with someone smart.
- Like we did the last time?
- How about we start off with Gary?
[First player from Team Running Man- Gary.]
[Gut feelings over brains-
Random Mr. Capable, Gary.]
Gary is good at things like this.
- I'm not good at things like this.
- Rock, paper, scissors?
- Why don't you go out there?
- Should I get a feel for their skills?
Hae Hyo!
[Team Angel's first player- Hae Hyo.]
We love you!
We love you! Good luck!
(Word play with Hae Hyo's name.)
We have to determine the category
and we'll determine it by playing
rock, paper, scissors.
- Okay, I understand.
- Take them all down, Gary!
- Make it easy on everyone.
- Should I just take them all down?
[Gary wins the right to choose first.]
- Go with something you know.
- Singer!
- Singer.
- I'll go with, 'singer'.
[15 years since he made his debut-
Gary chooses the category, 'singer'.]
Singer Gae, fighting!
- It's a singer related music question.
- It's a music question?
- I don't know many singers.
- I just go with my gut feeling.
But if it's an old song,
it could give Hae Hyo the advantage.
[Old pop song could give
Hae Hyo the advantage.]
- Please listen carefully.
- Okay.
- In pansori... (traditional singing)
- Pan?
- Usage of a drum in pansori...
- Answer.
[The question isn't even done
being asked?]
- Usage of a drum in pansori...
- Answer. Go-Soo.
Go-Soo?
I haven't finished asking the question.
- But that's your answer?
- Go-Soo.
No way.
[Team Angel members are preparing themselves
to get shot in the face with the puff of air.]
I know what a 'Go-Soo' is too.
Isn't that the person who gives the beat?
- Is it wrong?
- The correct answer is...
[Correct answer]
[A refreshing puff of air.]
[Hae Hyo starts off with a bang!]
- What was that?
- That was unbelievable.
[Newly formed Kwon Hae Hyo's fan club.]
You have to cut them off
right now, Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- That was unbelievable.
[The ace up their sleeve.
King of Common Sense, Jae Suk on the prowl.]
If I don't cut you off right now,
then it's all over for my team.
- Go with 'Announcer'.
- Yeah, go with that one.
Announcer!
[Jae Suk chooses the 'Announcer' category.]
It could be a Hangeul related question.
Hangeul?
That's hard.
- I know.
- Pronunciation, and such?
- Actors are better with things like that.
- Then I chose wrong.
- You can change the category.
- Then I want to go with 'Athletes'.
- Athletes?
- Athletes.
- We have to cut him off right now.
- Will you be okay with that category?
- Yes, I really love sports.
[King of Common Sense is known
for his love of sports.]
- Here's your question.
- Okay.
The topic is, soccer.
[Topic- Soccer]
- This should be my category.
- He's the one who knows everything about it.
The country where
the 2014 World Cup will be taking place is...
That would be Brazil.
[The question hasn't even been asked.]
[In an extreme state of nervousness with
the King of Common Sense sitting next to him.]
I'll ask the question again.
Yes, Brazil is where the 2014 World Cup
will be taking place.
Where will it take place in 2018?
[Immediate response]
The country where it'll take place in 2018?
Wait a minute, where is it going to be?
[Which country will the 2018 World Cup
be taking place in?]
- Please!
- Three, two, one.
- Wait a minute, 2018?
- Just answer the question.
- Wrong.
- 2018?
- The time's up.
- Is that how you buy more time?
You really are a pro at this.
It's been at least 20 minutes!
[Time over]
United Arab Emirates.
That's not the country?
Team Running!
England!
Wait, where is it being held in 2018?
The location for 2018 games
have already been chosen?
- I know where it is!
- Team Running!
I think... Qatar!
- It's not Qatar?
- No, it's not.
Qatar is in 2022.
- Ah, is that it?
- Qatar is in 2022?
So that's not it either.
- Is it somewhere in Europe?
- They've already chosen for 2022?
- Why are they in such a hurry to decide?
- Just say whatever. Don't worry about us.
We're all ready to get blown
in the face.
Belgium.
Stop saying whatever comes
to your mind.
- I don't think that's the way to go anymore.
- Team Angel.
Spain?
Running.
Italy.
Running!
Norway.
Running.
Denmark.
Sweden.
- That hurts!
- Stop blurting out the wrong answers!
- I have to get the answer.
- Take your time.
- Take a little rest, Jae Suk.
- Which country haven't you mentioned yet?
What else is there in Europe?
Let's see...
Swiss?
Team Angel.
Netherlands?
- Russia?
- What did you say?
[Correct answer]
[A round around Europe,
and finally gets the correct answer!]
[Two wins in a row for Hae Hyo!]
[Remaining players- 7:5.]
They just had the Winter Olympics in Sochi,
and they're having the World Cup too?
Don't you think that you're being
too good at this game?
[We ask that you judge more fairly
during the World Cup games...]
[Hae Hyo eliminates four player of Team RM-
Remaining players- 6:3.]
- Gu Hye Sun!
- Gu Hye Sun can choose the category.
You can choose since you're
the challenger.
- Rescue Team.
- Rescue Team?
[Hye Sun played a rescue guard in
the drama, 'Angel Eyes'.]
She even took classes.
It could be related to that.
- It could be something that she learned.
- Finish listening to the question first.
Here's your question.
When the rescue helicopter is called out
what is the signal that the person in need
gives out to indicate that they need rescuing?
What is the signal?
[Do you know what it is?]
[I don't know either.]
- Neither one of them knows.
- Didn't you play a rescue guard?
- Blank Ji Hyo!
- I'm curious to know myself.
Is it an object that is used?
Either a prop or your own body.
Something you can signal with your own body.
Running.
Hand.
What are you talking about?
[Wave to the rescuers out of sheer joy?]
'X'?
[Seung Ri and his out of the blue
bodily gags.]
No one seemed to be talking, so...
[Lightens the mood with his joke.]
- You're pretty close to the answer.
- Just say whatever comes to your mind.
Running.
'X'.
- 'X'.
- That answer was already given.
That answer was already given!
[Sorry...]
- Angel. '11'.
- '11'?
'11'?
Running.
'Mansei' (Figure of '11'.)
How is that any different from '11'?
What is a person to do
if they've hurt their arms?
Angel!'
'V'?
[Hye Sun wins the round.]
The correct answer is, the sign of a 'V'.
- We only have two players left.
- Who's the next challenger?
That's me.
You dare laugh?
- You're just giving up, aren't you?
- You don't know what you're saying.
They've pretty much given up.
- How about 'Reporter'? Or 'Chef'?
- No, Hye Sun is a really good cook.
[Hye Sun is too good of a cook
to go with that category.]
- Go with 'Producer'.
- Producer?
[But 'Producer' is iffy with
Hye Sun being a movie director.]
How about 'Scientist'?
No, just go with 'Reporter'.
There's nothing I can do.
- Go with 'Reporter'. That's your best option.
- Reporter!
[Time for them to win this round!]
- You should take them all down, Ha Ha.
- That would be awesome.
- You can do it!
- What is Team Running Man so confident about?
We have to be on the show
every single week.
[We've been coming on the show every week
for the past four years.]
You sure are lucky, Ji Suk.
[Ji Suk hasn't shown off his airheaded side
all thanks to his smart teammates.]
The topic is... entertainment news.
[Entertainment]
- We can do this!
- You're all set!
It's a question based on statistics
in the industry.
What is the name of the actor who's made
the most number of appearances
as a foreign actor guest on various shows
on SBS network in the last 20 years?
- Who is that actor/actress?
- You know this one!
Please!
Ki Chan.
[Huh?]
[Could our faraway friend, Jackie Chan,
be the correct answer?]
[The formidable ace in the
entertainment category, Ha Ha.]
[Jackie Chan came in at first place for
having made ten separate appearances.]
Make some noise!
Gu Hye Sun.
- How many of you are there now?
- We have four left.
[Team Angel still has five players!]
I'm going to choose the 'Actor' category.
[Ha Ha has experience in
being in a movie himself.]
You're competing against a man who started
with the movie, 'Not the Hamburger Level'.
[He made his debut 26 years ago in a movie.]
That movie came out
when I was in middle school.
Were you in the movie as an extra?
- Why don't you answer it first then?
- Okay, deal!
Here's the question.
What are the four elements in acting?
- What are the four elements in acting?
- Seriously!
[It seems as though Ji Suk knows
the answer.]
Four elements of acting?
[Four elements of acting.]
[Audience, stage, actor, storyline.]
Second element is...
Stage.
[Huh? Look at this guy...]
There are two elements left, right?
Rent. It's the rent.
[Big-nose is saying the realistic elements
of acting such as management fees, and rent.]
- Management fees.
- Actor.
[Ha Ha has answered
three of the four correct elements.]
I'm sure everyone's shocked with
my answers so far.
- Yes, we're very shocked.
- The last one should be crucial.
It would be so funny if I said it was
the admission fees right now.
Audience, stage, actor...
Stage, audience, actor, entrance.
Entrance.
[Three out of four was correct.
So close...]
Audience, stage, actor, storyline.
[Ha Ha didn't know the final element,
the storyline.]
I had no idea that he'd even know
those three elements.
[Only one challenger left on Team RM.]
[The final challenger of Team Rm- Kkuk.]
- Your brother is a doctor, so go with that.
- My brother is the doctor, not me!
[Very simple, yet logical reason.]
My brother's the doctor, not me!
You don't have any attorneys in the family,
but you do have a doctor, right?
So go with the 'Doctor' category.
Doctor!
[Kkuk chooses the 'doctor' category.]
- Ji Suk needs to go up there.
- No, it's alright.
I want to see Ji Suk go up there.
[The opposing team really wants to see
Ji Suk go up to the stand.]
The topic is... 'Diseases'.
What is it called when a patient is always
diagnosing himself with new symptoms?
- Angel.
- Running.
Obsession.
He did too well in the beginning that we were
fooled into thinking otherwise of Hyung Jin.
Running.
Stalking.
- You definitely are not a doctor.
- Not new 'ideal person', but 'symptoms'.
- State the question accurately.
- Okay.
- It's some sort of illness?
- It's an illness, right?
- Answer!
Answer!
The blues syndrome?
[Players left- 4:1.]
- Where did I hear that from?
- From when your brother was in med school.
- I remember hearing about that somewhere.
- You got it!
Where did I hear that from?
I wonder if it was from a movie.
[Moment of joy is just temporary.
Seoul University Alumni is up next.]
Wait and see which topic
he chooses.
We just need to beat Sang Yoon.
[It's the airhead's turn as long as
they can beat Sang Yoon.]
Don't choose that one.
He was a physics major!
[Kkuk only chose the category because
it was somewhat health related.]
AS soon as we're over this hump,
it's all downhill from here.
It's all downhill!
- Why is it a downhill from there?
- Ji Suk is up next.
- Okay, I got this.
- Think of this as a bobsled game.
[It's an airhead bobsled game
from here on out.]
You have to win this, Sang Yoon.
This is unfair.
The topic is... living organisms.
[Topic- Living organisms.]
- Are you not as familiar with that topic?
- Yes.
That's a relief.
That's a real relief to hear.
Here's your question.
In order for an exoskeleton insect to grow,
they go through a molten stage.
How can you make that the question when
that's the only thing I'm sure he knows?
- Transformation.
- What did you say?
Transformation was your answer?
[That's not in the correct context.]
('Byuntae' can also mean, 'Pervert'.)
In order for an exoskeleton insect to grow,
they go through a molten stage.
What is the terminology that is used to
describe the major difference between
the morphological difference between
the larvae and the adult insect?
- Running.
- Mutation?
- Is it a Korean word?
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook!
- To be more clear...
- You need to settle down, Yoo Jae Suk.
- Jong Kook!
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong?
You can't look behind you.
- It's a Korean word.
- It is?
A butterfly is an example of an insect
that goes through this.
[Halts Sang Yoon out of natural instinct.]
And grasshopper is an example of an insect
that does not go through this.
Is that right?
Butterflies and grasshoppers?
I don't really know much about
grasshoppers.
Answer.
I mean, Running.
I think Sang Yoon's too scared to
even lift up his hand right now.
Abstract metamorphosis?
[What in the world is that?]
- Team Angel?
- Variant metamorphosis.
Answer. Running. Heterogeneity...
heterogeneity metamorphosis.
Angel.
Complete metamorphosis.
[Sang Yoon gets the correct answer.]
[Victor in ease...
and his happy bobsled team.]
[Asking for best out of three.]
Can we just finish up
the remaining categories?
[Team Running Man is not very good
at admitting their defeat.]
How about a one on one between
Ji Suk and Kwang Soo.
Let's let Ji Suk and Kwang Soo
go up against each other.
[Kim Ji Suk vs Lee Kwang Soo-
Super-match round?]
If Kim Ji Suk wins,
then Team Angel wins, no questions asked.
But if Lee Kwang Soo happens to win...
then I'll allow for one more round with
only three players from each team.
- Okay.
- Will that be okay?
- The two teams can decide.
- Should we allow it?
Then we want Kim Jong Kook to come out
and beg us on his knees for his whole team.
- We'll have him get down on his knees!
- Why is that so hard? Look how easy it is!
[A group demonstration of how easy it is
to beg down on their knees.]
We want Kim Jong Kook down
on his knees.
I can get down on my knees.
[Kkuk's self-sacrifice for the chance
for their team to redeem themselves.]
[Thanks to Kkuk, it's now a battle
between Ji Suk and Kwang Soo.]
- I'll end this right now.
- You can do this, Kwang Soo.
I vow to defeat him!
I'm going to win this!
All the categories are
pretty much the same to you.
Rock, paper, scissors.
[Ji Suk wins the right
to choose the category.]
- How about 'Teacher'?
- Aren't you a teacher?
Okay, I will choose 'Teacher',
since I graduated with an education degree.
[Chooses a category related to
his education degree background.]
- Ji Suk has a degree in education?
- I even have a teaching certificate.
Jong Kook is going to kill you
if you lose, Kwang Soo.
- That would be fun.
- I didn't make him get down on his knees.
Just know that you'll be crawling on
your knees until we're done filming.
[Kwang Soo's knees for Jong Kook's.]
Let's take this seriously.
The topic is...
- Novels.
- Okay, novels.
I may not know about anything else,
but I know my novels.
What are we going to do about him?
In the novel,
'Mother and the Love Guests'...
You know that book.
I have a feeling that
Ji Suk may get this right.
Running.
- Potatoes.
- Angel!
[Where did the potatoes come from?]
Eggs... I mean,
two hardboiled eggs.
He's a weirdo himself.
Listen to what the question is first!
Three fried eggs.
Running!
Poached eggs. Poached eggs?
- Listen to the question first!
- Let him finish asking the question!
Running.
Two potatoes, and three eggs.
Hey!
It's not an American style breakfast!
She didn't serve him
an American style breakfast.
[Did she serve her guests an
American style breakfast?]
[Why don't you wait to answer until you've
finished listening to the question first?]
What is the instrument that the mother played
for her customers in the novel?
Running!
[Darn... I was one step too late.]
Gayageum.
Angel.
An organ.
Organ.
[Kim Ji Suk wins!]
[Someone please help me.]
[I can't believe I lost to Ji Suk...]
I wasn't going to resort to this.
[Mission card containing
the next mission location.]
What just happened?
[Team Running Man takes
both the mission cards.]
[Eats the opposing team's mission card!]
- You can't take our card too!
- Just follow our card.
You can just follow our card.
[For the first time in Running Man history,
the victor has to follow the loser?]
Okay, let's follow them.
We'll show you what we're
really made of!
[Second round, Quiz Competition-
Team Angel wins!]
[Their mission location- Soccer Field.]
I wonder what we'll have to do.
- It'll be something physical.
- It can be relay or running of sorts.
The last time I was on the show,
we did acupuncture mat jumping.
- It was so painful.
- Did it really hurt?
But the funny thing is, the day after...
after I got a full night of sleep...
When I got up the next morning...
My skin... my skin was practically glowing.
It really improved my blood circulation.
- I wondered how it could be good for you.
- So it really helped improve your health.
I felt like it opened up all my veins
for better blood circulation.
[Those fond memories...]
[We'll make you relieve them again.]
[May not what this is all about,
but it's a gigantic acupuncture mat setup.]
[This has to be a dream.]
Your next match is a physical competition.
[Round three-
Acupuncture mat competition.]
[A world where whatever they say
becomes a reality.]
It's the acupuncture mat again.
[Since the weather is so cold,
we'll allow you to keep your socks on.]
[Onto the mat with your sock-clad feet.]
It still feels the same!
[Feel the healthy benefits flowing
through their thin socks.]
Maybe I should put on two pairs of socks.
Wearing these socks aren't making
any difference for me.
[Acupuncture mats that they can't even fathom
having to face in dramas.]
- It's a teeny bit better.
- It really hurts! It makes no difference!
Song Ji Hyo's wearing men's formal socks.
You must've left your house in a hurry,
and just bought a pair from the store.
We can't take too long with this game even if
we wanted to because of the level of pain.
I bet Ji Suk's true nature will come out
during this round.
[Acupuncture mat competition- Start!]
I'm coming.
- We have to win this time.
- I know.
[The shortening gap between the two teams.]
[Jae Suk seems to be their first target.]
Don't step on my foot!
Why are you stepping on my foot?
[Everyone's stepping on each other's feet.]
[Discouraging the opponents by
stepping on their feet.]
[The more you get stepped on,
the bigger the health benefits.]
[If someone becomes too much of a liability,
then abandoning them is the answer.]
[Goodbye...]
[Team Running Man 6 vs Team Angel 7.]
[Once lost, then it's time to abandon.
Jae Suk's elimination shows their true color.]
[This team is in celebration mode.]
- Why didn't you save me?
- We couldn't!
[Team Running Man 6 vs Team Angel 7.]
My feet hurt!
[Back to hunt for more.]
Tell Suk Jin to come out here.
[Seung Ri is starting to shed tears
from the pain of being on the mat.]
Just make it quick.
Beat them, or lose, just do whatever.
[Attack by stomping on their feet?]
Get in there!
[The mat is prohibiting them from attacking,
so it's only a verbal attack!]
Come on!
Take your time and come over here.
[Seung Ri- Out!]
[Tiger is about to be unleashed.]
[Putting their faith in the tiger
to shout out in fierce battle cry.]
If Kim Jong Kook wasn't there,
we'd seriously...
Come on!
[Martial art-like hand moves.]
Nice, Gary!
[Got him!]
[Human tug-of-war.]
[In the midst of all this... Ha Ha is ousted!]
[I'm... Running Man's Mr. Capable!]
[An enormous round of elimination!]
[This is Tiger Power!]
[In a blink of an eye,
it's reduced down to three against two.]
Four of them fell off all at once.
You come here.
One on one?
[Kwang Soo vs Hae Hyo.
One on one battle.]
[Leg tripping?]
[Eliminates the Giraffe in one
smooth move!]
- He is allowed to do that?
- Why can't he?
I love you, Kwon Hae Hyo!
I don't know what to do about this.
I really am a huge fan of his.
[Hae Hyo seems to be practicing
the drunken martial arts move.]
- We're losing right now.
- I've seen every drama that he's been in.
- I'm serious. Every single one of them.
- Hae Hyo's putting on an act right now.
He's acting right now.
He used to practice martial arts!
- He really knows martial arts.
- He used to be an action star.
[Former action star's trickery.]
[Continuing to sway back and forth
so that Jong Kook can't get a hold of him.]
- He really knows the martial arts?
- You need to be careful, Ji Hyo.
[Action star lowers his stance.]
[Going face to face with the tiger!]
[Everyone enjoying being
a spectator to this showdown.]
Just eliminate him
so that he can rest in peace!
[Former action star's disgrace.]
Don't you think that you've gone too far?
- I'm so sorry.
- No, it's okay.
[Jong Kook and Ji Hyo vs Hye Sun.]
[Slowly crawls out to make his exit.]
[The angelic actress
pulls out her claws to attack.]
[A full body acupuncture mat massage.]
Ji Hyo, if you don't end it right now,
Jong Kook will lose to her.
- You have to get this done!
- Want me to help lift her?
[The last survivor, Hye Sun,
is also ousted.]
[But she still shocked everyone
with her courageous attack.]
It's been a while since I've seen anyone
attack Ji Hyo like that.
So they can beat us as long as it's
a simple physical competition.
[Team Running Man wins the third round-
Acupuncture mat competition.]
[Team Running Man finally wins
a Priority choice card.]
[They finally arrive at
the final mission location.]
I remember having been here before.
What is all this?
Look at that.
They have a huge set built over there.
Don't people jump off of those things?
[The final stage to determine who will
be the ultimate rescue team.]
This is your final mission destination,
which is the Firefighter Academy.
This is your final competition.
Final competition to choose which team
will become the ultimate rescue team.
Currently, Team Angel has 2 and Team RM has
1 priority choice cards from previous rounds.
[Fire extinguisher vs Bucket;
Rope vs Hands; 5M vs 7M.]
[Team Angel gets to choose
two of those cards.]
When we did our last race
with the university students
the teams that got to choose first
were the last ones to come in.
- Yes, that's right.
- Who knew the blanket boat would win?
- How about we go with the hand one?
- Okay. Okay!
We've made our decision.
Between the fire extinguisher and the bucket,
we'll go with the fire extinguisher.
- Come on, the bucket would be much better!
- We're sure it'll be extinguishing a fire.
And in case of 5M vs 7M...
we're going to go with 5M.
- Let's go with the rope.
- Okay, we choose the rope.
- So everyone's made their decisions.
- Are we going to have to climb something?
But we still don't know if it's a good thing
or a bad thing yet.
You guys mentioned the Han River crossing
mission we did recently a little bit ago.
That idea for that mission was given to us by
the world's oddest paper boat competition.
Our final competition of the day is also from
an 'oddest world competition' that goes on.
Can't you just get something
from a regular competition?
Instead of from an odd competition?
Why are you always looking for something odd?
- Then what is this competition about?
- This odd competition is about...
This is from the world's oddest
firefighter competition.
- That sounds okay.
- That actually sounds pretty cool.
[Firefighter Olympics which determines
the best firefighters in the world.]
[ A competition to determine the best of
the best through a series of games.]
We tweaked the games a bit to
suit us better
and seven members on each team will now play
the game as the real firefighters would.
Here are the rules of the competition.
There are a total of six obstacles.
First course- First runner will slide down
the pole to run over to the second runner.
Second Course- First runner will run over to
the second obstacle
with the second runner on their piggyback
for the second obstacle course
which is the barefoot fire walking course.
Fire walking?
It is just like it sounds.
You'll have to walk on fire.
[Walk barefoot on hot coals and stones with
the first runner on their piggyback.]
Here's the third mission.
You'll have to utilize either the bucket or
the fire extinguisher that you got to choose
to extinguish the fire roaring
in the steel over that you see over there.
[Third obstacle- Fire extinguishing.]
Fireman standing by will ensure
that the fire has been put out completely.
Only once the fireman has deemed it okay,
will the next runner will be able to go.
For the fourth obstacle,
the fourth runner will climb up the roof.
And for this course as well,
you will have to use either your hands or rope
as you've chosen from the options
that you were given earlier.
[The team that chose the rope is
cheering with joy.]
For the fifth course, fifth and sixth runners
will have to combine their efforts together.
The two runners will have to combine their
efforts together to work the fire hose.
The two must work together to aim and
knockdown their target from its position.
Team Angel chose 5M and
Team Running Man chose 7M.
And here's your final obstacle course.
the seventh runner must climb up the wall
to ring the bell located up near the top.
The first team to ring the bell
will be today's winning team.
This is a relay where the previous runner will
have to stick the name tag on the next runner.
That's how this relay will be played.
[Time to practice their moves.]
- Just slide down like this.
- Is it hot on your hands?
- No, it's not hot.
- I'll give it a try.
[Gary is teaching Ji Hyo how to
slide down the pole.]
- There you go. Good job.
- Like this?
- Did I do okay?
- Yeah, great job.
- You did good.
- Ouch, that hurts.
You're our Ace, who can do anything!
[For Team Angel, Seung Ri is in charge
of sliding down the pole.]
- You have to stick on my name tag, okay?
- Okay.
[But... how am I going to manage that?]
How am I going to put
the fire out with just a bucket?
Putting that fire out isn't going
to be easy.
You have to just hold on to the bottom
when you pull out the safety pin.
There's a lower and an upper handle,
but hold onto only the bottom portion
and you'll be able to pull out
the safety pin just like this.
- Do you understand?
- And just press the handles together?
Yes, I understand.
Thank you.
[Sang Yoon and Jong Kook.
Competing at the roof climbing obstacle.]
It's not easy.
- Wow, this is really slippery.
- This isn't easy.
[Sang Yoon barely manages to
pull himself up onto the roof.]
Sang Yoon's good at climbing up there,
but he doesn't look all that cool.
[He's going to exhaust himself out
from all that practicing.]
[But he seems to have gotten
the hang of it.]
[Fifth course-
Knock the target down with the hose.]
We have to do it forcefully?
It's all the weaklings over here.
[Predicting a fierce battle
between the weakest links.]
When the two partners come up here
together once everything's been setup
then one of you will have to look over to
that person, and yell out, 'water'.
[Learning how to work the water hose.]
If you open it too much,
then it'll go all over the place.
So just open it up slightly?
Open too wide, then it's like this,
and open a little, and it's a narrow stream.
It's just like when we would play with
the garden hose when we were kids.
I shouldn't have taken on this course.
- Have you ever done this before, Ha Neul?
- Me?
- For about a year and a half?
- That's cheating!
You doing this is cheating!
But I forgot how to do it.
It's been so long.
I shouldn't have said I was
going to do this.
What was I thinking?
Is it too late to change my mind now?
- The fire feels so warm.
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
- Want to do my course?
- Why?
[Hoping for a chance to swap out his course
after being fitted for the equipment?]
Why are you suddenly asking me that?
- I was wondering if you'd be interested.
- But you have such long legs.
And did you see the shoes?
You need climbing shoes.
- Your shoes are very important.
- Do you have climbing shoes?
- Right now?
- Yeah.
- Don't you carry them around?
- Who would carry them around?
You should always carry them
around with you.
You always have to carry certain pairs of
shoes around with you in this industry.
[Don't you know the basics
of the variety industry?]
You should always be ready for anything.
- When would I ever go climbing?
- What's your shoe size?
- 290mm.
- Then mine wouldn't even fit you.
- You have a pair with you?
- Of course! We all have them with us.
You have to carry all sorts of shoes,
such as bowling shoes at all times.
[Unbelievable]
You never know when you'll need them.
Nothing we can do about today.
Just do it without them today.
But let's go to this store I know and
get you a pair for next time.
Let's get you a pair for you
to take around.
[I guess you're going to have to buy a few
things if you want to stay in this industry.]
You need to get yourself a pair.
[The final competition]
[Ultimate firefighter competition.]
[First obstacle- Pole sliding.
Ji Hyo vs Seung Ri.]
[A fierce battle where the pride of the variety
and drama departments are riding on the line.]
[Second obstacle- Fire walking.
Gary vs Hyung Jin.]
[Third obstacle- Fire extinguishing.
Jae Suk vs Hye Sun.]
[Fourth obstacle- Roof climbing.
Jong Kook vs Sang Yoon.]
[Fifth obstacle- Hit the target.
Suk Jin and Ha Ha vs Hae Hyo and Ji Suk.]
[Sixth course- Rockwall climbing.
Kwang Soo vs Ha Neul.]
Get ready.
[Which team will take home the honor?]
[Ji Hyo vs Seung Ri.
First course- Pole sliding.]
You're doing great, Ji Hyo!
Please!
[Neck and neck!]
[Almost at the same time!]
They're so close!
[Ace Ji Hyo doesn't lose out to any man!]
It's neck and neck!
Neck and neck!
[Second obstacle- Fire walking.]
[Third obstacle- Fire extinguishing.]
[Team Running Man- Bucket.
Team Angel- Fire extinguisher.]
[Double bucket action.]
[Hye Sun is struggling
to pull out the safety pin.]
[The fireman must lift up his flag in
acknowledgment for them to pass.]
- You have to put it all out!
- Put it all out!
[Jae Suk continues to run back and forth.]
[Just then... Hye Sun succeeds her mission.]
[Team Running Man also succeeds the mission
right in Team Angel's footsteps.]
[Both teams rush off to the fourth obstacle-
Roof climbing.]
[Jong Kook and Sang Yoon
get on their way simultaneously.]
[This roof climbing obstacle could determine
which team comes out the winner!]
[Team Angel- Hands.
Team Running Man- Rope.]
[Tiger power in full effect!]
[Kkuk climbs up onto the roof in
a blink of an eye with his rope.]
What's taking Sang Yoon so long?
[Maybe he exhausted himself out
too much during practice?]
Sang Yoon looks so uncool right now.
[His grunting is his only reply.]
[Oh no...]
Sang Yoon!
[Even the opposing team
starts to cheer him on.]
I don't think I can climb up there.
It's way too high.
[Meanwhile, Team Running Man is about to
get started with their fifth course.]
- Hurry up and stick it on.
- Got it. Let's hurry!
[Big-nose's hose rolling skills.]
[Fireman Big-nose gets it done right!]
[Team Running Man has to knock down
their target from 7M away.]
[Sang Yoon, on the other hand...]
[He's still battling with the rooftop.]
Just a little bit more.
There you go, Sang Yoon.
You got it.
You need to hurry!
The other team got through the roof!
- Grab it over here.
- Water!
[Team Angel is right on their heels.]
[I can't be the cause of our team's loss...]
[Ready to take aim.]
Hold it steady.
[Must knock down their target with
the stream of water to pass.]
[Will it be knocked down?]
Aim it higher!
You have to aim higher!
[Team Running Man-
Passes through the fifth course!]
[Only one final obstacle left to go!]
Lee Kwang Soo, fighting!
- Lee Kwang Soo, fighting!
- I'm sorry, but I don't think I can do this!
This is too big of a burden on me!
Water!
[What?
It's a rainbow shower.]
If you open it up too much,
then it'll spread sideways.
[He definitely told them
not to open it up too much.]
[So this is what he meant by that...]
[The two firemen are battling the water hose.]
- Stick it on his back!
- Go!
[The final obstacle- Rockwall climbing.]
Okay, we've got this!
We can win this thing!
[Everything is now riding on
Kwang Soo's shoulders.]
[Must ring the bell, which is placed
10m above his head to win the competition.]
- You can do this!
- Take your time!
[Team Angel finally figures out how
to work the water hose properly.]
- A little bit higher.
- Okay.
[Wow! Succeeds the mission in
record time!]
Hurry!
- Kwang Soo!
- He has a lot of experience doing this.
Kwang Soo's having a hard time with this.
Come on, Kwang Soo!
You're doing good!
[Ha Neul is climbing
the wall like Spiderman.]
Ha Neul is just very good at this.
Ha Neul took lessons in Rockwall climbing.
[A little faster...
and he may take over the lead?]
- You have to move faster, Kwang Soo!
- I don't know where to grab!
[Ha Neul is right on his trail!]
[So close, yet so far.]
Just ring the bell and drop off!
[Just who... will ring the bell first?]
[With the pride of drama
and variety department on the line!]
Come on, Kwang Soo!
[Team Running Man wins the competition!]
[Drunk in the euphoria of their victory!]
- That's disappointing.
- We were so close.
The final winner of this competition is,
Team Running Man.
[Team Running Man wins the competition!]
[Golden envelopes to the winning team.]
- There's really something in there.
- As stated earlier, you get both envelopes.
There's real money in there.
I thought there would be another mission card,
but it's real money in there!
I guess I'll go out to a nice
barbeque dinner.
[You should invite us along!]
Thanks to our guests for joining us, and
we wish you the best with your new drama.
[We hope that your new drama
is a huge hit!]
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is the 1800's,
the gold rush era in Australia.
[Running Members are off to
find their gold.]
[One day, they come to discover
a mysterious book.]
[Only one person can be the star
of Running Hills.]
[Carry out the missions that are hidden
throughout the town...]
[And only the one who possesses the most number
of 'R' badges will be the ultimate winner.]
[The ultimate battle during
the gold rush period.]
[Just who will become
the man of Running Hills?]
[The star of Running Hills-
The ultimate showdown.]
[Next week's Running Man-
Star of Running Hills.]