(Card Sharks 2:
The Return of the Gamblers)
Card Sharks Two,
The Return of the Gamblers.
(About 6 months ago)
I have a feeling
something huge is going to happen.
Eight card sharks from all over
the country were gathered.
And they held the first
Card Shark Association Meeting.
They elected the first chairman...
of the Card Shark Association
who gets enormous power.
Ji Suk Jin was elected the first
chairman of the association.
But the chairman failed
to dominate the association...
and resigned from the position.
Yoo Jae Suk!
Yoo Jae Suk was elected
the second chairman.
Form a single line.
But as soon as he got elected,
he changed abruptly
and imposed strict rules.
(But as soon as he got elected, he
changed abruptly and imposed rules.)
Pay your association fees.
What?
Then he started to extort
association fees from the members.
(Then he started to extort
association fees from the members.)
Give me two caramels.
If I give you two,
and you go sit there...
- I won't sit there. Don't worry.
- Really?
Even after he went bankrupt,
he kept collecting association fees.
All right.
And the chairman ended up
laying hands on the association fee,
and it upset the members greatly.
It's done.
He lost all the association fees...
- and got kicked out with no money.
- I told you not to come.
The first Card Shark
Association Meeting...
came to a devastating end like that.
And a few months later...
(The chairman called the members
together deep into a mountain.)
(The portrait of the chairman
is hanging on the wall...)
(to show his character.)
Hi, I'm Sally. My name is Sally.
Call me Sally.
You've got your own character.
(You've got your own character.)
I've prepared this for a whole week.
It took me a long time
to put these stickers on.
(It took me a long time
to put these stickers on.)
The New Year's Party
of the Card Shark Association?
(She's totally immersed
in her role.)
My husband is on a business trip.
(Chewing gum noisily)
That's why I'm here.
(My husband is on a business trip.
That's why I'm here.)
I'm Sally. Oh, hey.
Hey, Laura.
- Hi, Laura.
- What are you doing, Sally?
We're having a New Year's party.
Where are you from?
- Is the gum part of your character?
- Yes.
(Laura, aka Song Jeoktoma)
(Sally, has stickers
all over her body)
Hey.
- Hello, Jong Kook.
- Who's Madam Jeong?
(A man in a black leather jacket)
(Kim Grand Award,
the Punch of the association)
I'm Sally. Hello.
Hello, Sally.
- Nice to see you.
- Hello.
My goodness.
(Two members are coming in
with their long mullets.)
- Hey, Kka Chi.
- It's an homage.
(An homage to Jo Kka Chi
from Tazza 3)
(Yang Kka Chi, the fake,
Jo Kka Chi, the original)
It's an homage.
- Why are you copying me?
- An homage to Kka Chi from Tazza.
I mean, I'm grateful, but...
- this feels weird.
- Jong Kook.
I got back-hair extensions
at a beauty salon.
You put so much work into it.
- Come closer.
- My goodness.
- It's the Card Sharks' special.
- Kka Chi.
- It's nice to meet you.
- I'm Sally.
Sally, it's good to see you.
Gosh, are you MacGyver?
- Actually, this is Lee Kwang Soo.
- Hello.
- I'm Sally.
- It's nice to see you.
(A petty thief imitating the thieves
from Home Alone)
What are you supposed to be,
a thief?
- Why? Don't I look okay?
- You look like a thief.
You should do better than this.
- What's wrong with this?
- I can see your underwear.
You look like a thief.
- Hello.
- Oh, gosh.
- Who is this?
- It's Im Ha Ryong. Hello, sir.
Hello, Ha Ryong.
(Senior Card Shark, Has many
nicknames including Im Ha Ryong)
- Who is he supposed to be?
- He really is a senior card shark.
Is he Corporal Pyeong?
What? He doesn't look like him.
- I'm actually Corporal Ji.
- Corporal Ji?
- Yes, I'm Corporal Ji.
- He insists.
- "Stop right there."
- He's Ha Ryong.
You look like Sopa Bang Jung Hwan.
Can you call yourselves
real card sharks?
(A time warp placed this old
card shark in the wrong place.)
- What is that?
- Don't do that.
He's not here yet.
He's the chairman.
- This says...
- What is this?
- Is he dead? My goodness.
- No.
- What?
- What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
- Isn't he dead?
- There are no ribbons on the frame.
- Are you sure he's not dead?
- What are you talking about?
So when is the chairman coming?
- When is he coming?
- He's not here yet?
Let's have a seat.
We still have time.
He'll be here in 30 minutes.
Gosh, who elected him the chairman?
- He's so arrogant.
- Actually, no one elected him.
- My goodness.
- So where is he now?
Why is the couch so low?
Gosh, it's so flat.
What is this?
It's flat as a sitting cushion.
My goodness. It's so flat.
This is like a sitting cushion.
- Gosh.
- He loves that it's comfortable.
- Yes, but it's...
- Suk Jin loves it.
Why do you look like
you're from a historical drama?
- Come on.
- Are you from "Rustic Period"?
- Why did you draw this?
- Maybe he's Sirasoni.
You really look like
you were on "Rustic Period".
- You little kids.
- I think there was a role like him.
- Why did you draw a mustache?
- Kim Young Tae.
You're a bully, aren't you?
- His name is Jo Kka Chi.
- You're perfect for the role.
"Don't you know me?"
- By the way.
- Jo Kka Chi.
You know what?
Maybe it's because
of his long mullet.
But your mouth
seems to stick out more.
Don't you think so?
Like he's wearing
special effect makeup.
- No. I only extended the mullet.
- Really?
- I know why he grows the mullet.
- Why?
Because it warms
the back of the neck.
- Yes, it does.
- Seriously.
(So it's not a neck warmer
but a hair warmer.)
And the back of your neck
doesn't get sunburned.
- You're right.
- I'm sure.
Have you done
your hair like this before?
No. I've never.
You've stolen a bike
with that hair before, right?
What? No.
What's wrong with this hair?
What does his hair
have to do with stealing a bike?
I think I've seen a guy
who looks exactly like you.
(The visual of a bike stealer
with a long mullet)
What are you, a detective?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm a gang member.
- You're always a gang member.
- Actually,
no matter which movie theme we have,
I look like a gang member.
So you're like a problem solver.
I play the same role every time.
- By the way.
- What?
You look good. Maybe it's because
you've won the Grand Prize.
("2020 SBS Entertainment Awards,
Kim Jong Kook wins the Grand Prize")
(At the 2020 SBS Entertainment
Awards ceremony)
Kim Jong Kook from "Running Man"
and "My Little Old Boy".
Congratulations!
(Kim Jong Kook
won the Grand Prize...)
(at the 2020 SBS
Entertainment Awards.)
(With the encouragement of
his younger colleagues...)
(and the embrace of
his older colleagues,)
(he won the Grand Prize
of 2020 Entertainment Awards!)
I didn't think I would
feel this way because...
(I didn't think I would
feel this way because...)
(No one's ever seen
Jong Kook's tears in 10 years.)
Actually, as I see the other members
of Running Man...
Seeing the other members
of Running Man was overwhelming.
(The members who encouraged him
for the last 10 years)
You all did a terrific job.
They should take a lot of
the credit for this award.
So I'd like to thank them.
- Don't do this.
- Kim Jong Kook!
- We should toss you into the air.
- No, don't.
- Here we go.
- Don't!
I said no!
Don't!
Don't do this!
- We should.
- Don't!
- Don't toss me.
- Why not?
Just don't do this.
We're six people.
And we can't toss one man?
- We can do this.
- I said no.
Come on. We can do this.
- Let go of me.
- Come on. Let's do this.
- Stop this.
- It's so funny.
- Why toss me?
- What's wrong?
Why can't we congratulate you?
- My goodness.
- Don't congratulate me.
- What's this?
- Don't do this.
Listen to me. Like I said before...
I always had to consider
the next winner,
which was the Grand Prize.
So I always had to
cut my acceptance speech short.
- I see.
- But this time, I was at the end.
So I wasn't used to
a longer acceptance speech.
- It was burdensome.
- Yes, it was.
- But you were the last winner.
Because you won the Grand Prize!
Kim Jong Kook!
- Don't do this!
- Kim Jong Kook!
I said no!
- This won't work.
- Darn it!
(Darn it!)
Why is this so hard?
Tossing you isn't that difficult!
Do you think we'll drop you?
- What's the big deal?
- My goodness.
- By the way, Yang Se Chan.
- What?
You only cried
when Jong Kook won the prize.
- You cried?
- No, I didn't.
- Come on. You did.
- I didn't.
But you didn't cry
when I won a prize!
Come on. I didn't cry.
- He cried.
- No...
- No, I didn't.
- Well,
- it's okay to cry.
- I've never felt that way.
Watching someone I know
feeling overwhelmed made me...
- feel like crying.
- I know.
I was so overwhelmed at that moment.
I saw you holding back tears too.
- Right.
- You saw it too?
I was holding back tears because
you guys looked overwhelmed.
Because I was watching all of you.
Wait a minute.
There are other members
who won prizes.
Yes, that's right.
("Haha from 'Running Man'
wins Top Excellence Award!")
- Let's toss him.
- Yes, let's!
- Let's toss him in the air!
- What are you doing?
- 1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3!
(He just lets them toss him.)
- Gosh, this is great.
- Here you go.
Haha is light.
- He almost went flying.
- Yes, and he let us throw him.
- I should apologize to Ji Hyo.
- Why?
- I was so bewildered.
- I know.
So I mentioned the members
I could see in my acceptance speech.
But Ji Hyo wasn't
where I could see her.
- She had to go present an award.
- I know.
I'd like to thank
the members who supported me.
Jong Kook, Jae Suk,
our youngest members
who brought us luck...
So Min and Se Chan.
And I'd like to thank Kwang Soo too.
I'd also like to thank
my role model, Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin, Jae Suk, Jong Kook,
Kwang Soo, So Min, and Se Chan)
(But he didn't mention Ji Hyo
in his long acceptance speech.)
I'll keep trying my best. Thank you.
(His acceptance speech ended
but Ji Hyo's name wasn't mentioned.)
But Ji Hyo wasn't
where I could see her.
- She had to go present an award.
- I know.
So tell everyone
that you're okay about it.
What?
- Ji Hyo.
- Should I?
- People are texting me about it.
- Really?
They're asking me if we had a fight.
- Why didn't you mention her?
- We're the Mapo Siblings.
- Why would I? Tell them it's okay.
- Yes, do that.
- Say that you're not upset at all.
- But you know what?
- I'm a little upset.
- Hey!
(I'm a little upset.)
- That's it. Kill him.
- We're not the Mapo Siblings.
- Hey!
- Just kill him!
You know what?
Even if she wasn't there,
- you should've mentioned her name.
- He's right.
But actually,
- she mentioned us in her speech.
- Yes.
But she mentioned the older members,
Se Chan, and So Min.
- That was it.
- He's right.
You're right. She did.
- I wasn't going to say this.
- You're right.
I was so upset about it
that I almost cried.
With the older members,
So Min, and Se Chan...
I will keep doing my best.
Thank you.
(Ji Hyo, what about me?)
I was so upset about it
that I almost cried.
I said, "the other members,
Se Chan, and So Min".
Didn't she say, "younger members"?
She said, "older members"!
- No, I didn't.
- Kwang Soo is younger than you.
- Say you're okay with it.
- Yes, say something.
I'm really upset.
(So upset)
I can't even sleep...
because I'm too upset.
It's only natural to mention
all members' names...
- in acceptance speeches.
- You're right.
- Yes.
- That's why...
I listened very carefully
to your acceptance speech.
- You mentioned us as "our members".
- Yes, he did.
Yes, as "our members".
He also talked more about
"My Little Old Boy" than our show.
- I even timed it.
- No, I didn't.
- You're so right.
- That's not true.
- I'm so upset!
- It's not true.
What are you talking about?
And there's another hot topic.
The 2020 SBS Entertainment Awards
presented another prize.
It's called
the Worst Reaction Prize.
- Who? Suk Jin?
- Yes. Suk Jin.
Congratulations, Suk Jin.
- Here we go.
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Why me?
(Suk Jin won
the Worst Reaction Prize!)
- Why me?
- Suk Jin had the worst reaction...
- when he was on camera.
- You're right.
Once he was massaging his hands.
- He acted indifferently.
- Yes, you're right.
- Every time.
- Who was the camera director...
- who got me on camera?
- Why do you ask?
It was strange.
I was focusing on the ceremony.
But when I do something else,
they caught me on camera.
(Doing something else)
(Doing origami)
(Getting into the rhythm)
It was whenever he was doing
something else.
Everyone stood up to give applause.
And Suk Jin sat back down
a bit earlier than us.
Right then,
they got a full shot of us.
Everyone was still standing.
- But Suk Jin was sitting down.
- The worst reaction.
(Suk Jin just sat down quickly.)
I was so surprised when I saw that.
Legendary celebrities
were being awarded.
I only sat down
faster than the others.
But suddenly we were on the camera
at that moment.
Fortunately, you're as old as
those celebrities.
You're in the same age bracket
as they are.
So they were okay about it.
You can continue the conversation
when the chairman arrives.
- All right.
- Why isn't the chairman coming?
We're holding the 2021 Card Shark
Association New Year's Party.
Like you did last time,
you'll have a fierce competition...
- over caramels.
- Gosh, caramels again?
- I see.
- We're doing it again?
Like we did before, we'll elect...
- the chairman of the association.
- All right.
But right now,
the chairman of the association...
is Yoo Jae Suk,
the one who was elected last time.
The chairman will arrive
30 minutes later.
Until then, you will discuss
whether Jae Suk should get to...
keep his position
as the chairman or not.
And if you put 20 caramels
in the box here,
We should submit caramels.
you'll remove him from the position
and elect a new chairman.
So what was the benefit?
- It's not about benefits.
- He can arrange the matches.
And he took all our caramels.
- That's right. He was...
- He took all our caramels...
all of a sudden.
Why did he do that?
Can he do stuff like that?
We can dismiss him
with three caramels each.
We have to submit our caramels.
He will extort them from us anyway.
I put my caramels
in his box by mistake,
and he just took them.
And he placed another bet
with the winner's tip.
- He can't do that.
- That's ridiculous.
He was supposed
to eat or something with it.
I didn't like it when he extorted
caramels from us.
- Right.
- He was like a bully.
He got his own way.
We have to remove him
from the position.
We have to dismiss him.
- Let's get rid of him.
- He always gets his own way.
All right. I'm sure
I'll be the chairman again.
(He was hiding in an attic room
before the members arrived.)
What am I doing here?
- Jae Suk.
- Yes.
As you know, you're the chairman
of the Card Shark Association.
Am I the chairman?
You abused your power
as the chairman.
I didn't abuse my power.
You did.
And you're still the chairman.
You are still in the position.
But do you see the seven
card sharks gathered together there?
I see them.
They think the chairman is...
arriving in 30 minutes.
And they will have a discussion...
about your second consecutive term.
- In there?
- Yes.
I'm sure they will fail
to gather 20 caramels.
If they fail to collect 20 caramels,
you will be the chairman
for another round.
(He can serve two consecutive terms
if they fail to gather caramels.)
(The chairman has been
watching the whole thing.)
(They can dismiss Jae Suk
with 20 caramels.)
Three caramels each?
3 times 7 is 21.
I just need 1 person
who doesn't submit 3 caramels.
For your information, the new
chairman will get more power.
We have to dismiss him
no matter what.
Then we should
elect Suk Jin chairman.
- Okay.
- You should pay 10 caramels then.
- Right.
- And we will support you.
Isn't it a good idea?
They will put up...
an easy person to deal with
as the candidate.
- I will support you.
- Isn't it a good idea?
You should submit 10 caramels.
Suk Jin will be
the puppet chairman.
- And Jong Kook will control him.
- The puppet chairman?
- Hey.
- Is he Jong Kook's puppet?
He's a puppet.
You are dressed
like a puppet chairman.
I don't like it.
- I want to be the real chairman.
- You can be the real chairman.
- You're the real chairman.
- It's okay as he doesn't know.
Jae Suk never listens to me.
It really upsets me.
- We will support you.
- We're here to help.
6 times 2 is 12.
You should submit 2 caramels.
I'll submit 8.
- Eight caramels?
- Yes.
- 8? Hang on.
- Just go with 10.
- Submit 10 caramels.
- The numbers don't add up.
And one of us will submit
no caramels.
Whether you submit 5 or 10,
you'll lose them all anyway.
Just give us 10 caramels now.
It's better to submit them now.
At least you will
look cool this way.
- You will look generous.
- You can be generous this way.
- Okay. I'll give 10 caramels.
- Okay.
Good.
- I love it.
- I'm going to teach him a lesson.
Put your caramels in the box.
- We will split the rest.
- Okay.
- Submit 2 caramels each.
- 2 caramels?
- Wait. I want to see him pay.
- One of us don't have to pay.
We have to decide who it should be.
I have a feeling...
that I will lose 10 caramels
and the plan will fall apart.
- Gosh.
- That's not going to happen.
That's not how we want
to start the new year.
I just feel like you won't
submit your caramels.
It's our promise.
We have to keep our words.
- You have my word.
- It's time for action.
- Okay.
- Then...
Suk Jin will be the hero
of our first episode...
- in the year 2021.
- Sure.
It's very meaningful, Suk Jin.
You should be the hero.
It's 10. Let's go.
- I'm submitting 10 caramels.
- You're the best.
Hey!
(As soon as he walks out
with his caramels,)
(the caramel thieves raid his bag.)
I didn't take any.
- I didn't do anything.
- My gosh.
You punks.
I'm not doing it.
I don't want to do this.
- He doesn't want it.
- I'm not doing this with you.
I don't want to be the chairman.
- Why are you sulking?
- I'm not doing this.
- It's just...
- I don't want it anymore.
As if we planned it all together...
We are really mean.
I took one caramel.
- Give them back.
- I didn't take any.
- I didn't take your caramels.
- Me neither.
- 2, 4, 6...
- I don't have his caramels.
- I swear I didn't take any.
- 2, 4, 6, 8...
- I was going to, but I failed.
I'm not doing this.
- Why are you sulking?
- I don't want to do this.
Jae Suk should be the chairman.
What is it that you don't
want to do? This show?
You don't want to be the chairman?
I'm not submitting 10 caramels.
Actually, I want to be chairwoman.
Of course. Honestly,
So Min deserves to be one.
I want to try it.
Let's go with So Min then.
So Min is a little tiring though.
No. I'm... You know what?
I'm like that
when I'm just a member.
But if I become the chairwoman,
I will be nothing but fair.
- Will you submit 10 caramels?
- If I do, can I be the chairwoman?
- Sure.
- We have no reason not to.
You should submit 10 caramels then.
- And we will submit 2 each.
- Sure. You submit 10.
- Can I really trust you guys?
- Of course.
- Let's give it a try. It's good.
- Today?
- I'm serious.
- But my camera...
- Your camera?
- Your camera is over there.
- Say hello to it.
- Do you see it over there?
- It's right there.
- Say hi.
Hi. It's right there.
Even the cameraman waved at him.
- He's so kind.
- I was looking for it.
I will submit 10 caramels.
Make sure to elect me chairwoman.
- We promise.
- We're serious.
I'll submit two caramels.
Whoever it is, we need
a new chairperson.
Make sure to elect me as chairwoman.
- You're so cool.
- These are 10 caramels.
- She sounds bold.
- Okay.
I gave 10 caramels.
Make me the chairwoman.
(Letting out a sigh)
Hang on.
(Chairman Yoo is doing something.)
Se Chan.
(Se Chan, I'm watching
you guys now.)
(If I become the chairman,
I'll take good care of you.)
And Kwang Soo.
Are you sure you gave 10 caramels?
- Did you put in 10 caramels?
- Sure.
I can't tell you that.
Seriously, I put in 10 caramels.
Gosh, this is...
- Here are two caramels.
- Make me the chairwoman, Se Chan.
So tell me about your plans.
Kwang Soo didn't put in caramels.
Gosh, seriously.
(Pretending to put it in,)
(Jo Kka Chi deceived everyone.)
Gosh, seriously. You can't do this.
- Don't be like that.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo.
(Before he gets his hand cut off,
he puts it in again.)
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Kka Chi, please.
(He submits 1 caramel
against his will.)
- I submitted mine, seriously.
- He didn't.
You will see it later.
Kwang Soo, if you don't
submit your caramels,
- I did.
- we can't get a new chairperson.
You can check the box later.
(What about Se Chan
who got Chairman Yu's message?)
You put in only one caramel.
(He submits only 1 caramel.)
- I put in 2.
- No, it was only 1.
- He submitted only 1.
- I submitted 2.
I didn't know So Min would do this.
So Min is stepping up.
(Chairman Yoo feels betrayed
by So Min.)
(The other three are done
submitting their caramels.)
I never lied.
Please trust me. I will show you...
a fair and beautiful world.
I will announce the results
once Jae Suk arrives.
Kwang Soo, are you sure
you submitted your caramels?
- I did. I'm serious.
- You have to do this.
I really did.
I have only 18 caramels now.
- You are...
- Don't fake it.
I'm putting in one caramel.
- I'm telling you, So Min.
- Hey, Suk Jin!
(He steals caramels from the box.)
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- What are you doing?
Why are you taking the caramels?
Stop it.
- Don't do it.
- Put them back in.
You're really strange.
You can't steal them.
This is mine. It's mine.
You can't steal the caramels.
He doesn't even have skills.
It was so obvious.
- Obviously, he was taking caramels.
- It was obvious.
He's like a man who steals
tithings from church.
What are you doing?
- I have 10.
- He's here.
He's here.
- Hello.
- He's Yoo San Seul.
- Is he Yoo San Seul?
(He shows up
looking like a trot singer.)
- All right.
- Hello.
- Have a seat.
- I'm Sally.
(He shows off his power
extending his hand for a handshake.)
Congratulations.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- He's wearing an armband.
- The chairman is really...
- You look great today.
We have to change the world.
I've been abroad for a while.
Where? We can't go abroad.
I was in self-quarantine
for two weeks.
That's how I came back.
Who copied whose mustache here?
- Who was the first?
- You look like twin brothers.
This is my real mustache.
Do you want to see
who copied whose mustache?
The two look like...
(He tries to remove
Suk Jin's mustache.)
- Don't do that to him.
- Get off me.
(He can't even fight against it.)
- It's gone.
- The mustache is gone.
- Hey.
- It's gone.
- He's a copycat.
- I did it with a lot of care.
- He looks so dull.
- He's a copycat.
- All right.
- Look at them.
Now you can see who copied whom.
Now I know.
How dare you...
He copied Jae Suk.
- Let's sit.
- Okay.
The award winners should sit here.
Don't be like that.
- Why are you doing this?
- Don't say that.
- Stop it.
- Why are you sitting in a corner?
What? Why?
Did you win an award?
- I didn't.
- Then sit over there.
Why does it even matter?
He won the reaction award.
- He won the Worst Reaction Award.
- The Worst Reaction Award.
Just fire him.
- We have the Grand Award winner.
- My goodness.
- Come over here.
- Okay.
- That's enough.
- We have the award winners.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- It never happened to us before.
- This is what we have to do.
I'm sitting here as the chairman.
But why is the sofa so low?
- This is a sitting cushion.
- Is this a sitting cushion?
This is called a cushion sofa.
Are we in a Korean restaurant
or what?
- What?
- This is nice though.
My gosh.
I don't know
what you guys were doing,
but I heard a babble of voices.
We were talking about you.
I'm Sally today.
We have Se Ri here.
- Pak Se Ri?
- Pak Se Ri.
- He's Pak Se Ri.
(He talks about Jong Kook's
doppelganger every once in a while.)
- We will finally win
(Mr. Se Ri can't take his socks off
because of his muscles.)
- I really like your show.
- Take off his socks.
All right.
Today, with Chairman Yoo Jae Suk,
we are having the 2021 Card Shark
Association New Year's Party.
Before the chairman got here,
the members had a debate...
on Chairman Yu's
second consecutive term.
- There were a lot of complaints.
- I'm very disappointed.
It was meaningless though.
I'm disappointed.
Actually, Chairman Yoo Jae Suk...
was watching and hearing
the whole thing.
- Really?
- Yes. And...
(Really?)
He watched and heard
what you did and said.
That's right. I did.
By the way,
I didn't know that So Min would...
- step up so enthusiastically.
- I see.
- You saw all that, right?
- Yes, I saw everything.
- I was taken aback, to be honest.
- I see.
- I don't know how it'll turn out,
- The one who dreams to be a king.
but please remember
what I tried to do.
You see,
I know what you guys think
as I've worked with you for so long.
The person whom you want
as the chairperson is...
a puppet type.
- You're right.
- That's true.
- Someone not like a chairperson.
- Yes.
- A puppet chairperson.
- Exactly.
- And the most suitable person is...
- Someone who's easy to control.
Seok Sam, you know.
- I know. However, you know what?
- Yes?
- It scratched my pride.
- I know.
- You saw how they robbed me, right?
- Yes, I saw that.
I couldn't trust them,
- so I withdrew my candidacy...
- Yes.
- and recommended another puppet.
- Did you?
Anyway, you will probably be
removed from your position.
(Declaration of war)
- Me?
- Yes. You'll be sacked.
- What if he keeps his position?
- I understand.
We don't know
how things will turn out yet.
Whatever happens,
I can assure you of one thing.
- If I get elected again,
- Yes.
- I'll consider what I saw...
- Of course.
- when I treat each of you.
- Absolutely.
- Of course, you should.
- You saw everything, right?
As soon as I find out
that I'm re-elected,
my revenge begins.
Do you understand?
I didn't even turn in any caramels.
- Is that true?
- Yes, I didn't turn in my caramels.
- Hey, how could you...
- Jong Kook...
- If I get re-elected,
- Yes.
- That won't happen.
- those who voted for a new one...
will have to turn in two caramels
as an association fee.
- All right!
- Sounds great.
- Hey.
- You never let us down, sir.
- You're brilliant as always.
- Do you understand?
- You fools!
- I'd give you mine just for you.
- Trust me. He'll be fired.
- You're amazing.
- Do you understand?
- We don't know that.
I bet we turned in 20 caramels.
You'll definitely be fired.
- It's hard to predict.
- I know who voted earlier.
I promise I will give
those who voted more caramels.
- All right.
- Yes.
We'll find out the result.
If there are 20 caramels in here,
the new chairperson will
automatically be elected.
- Please. I used half what I had.
- If not,
Jae Suk will serve another term
as the chairman.
I took five caramels out.
- Please. There should be 20.
- Yes.
- 10 of those are mine.
- I told you to turn in some more.
- You didn't turn in any, did you?
- I did.
- I turned in three caramels.
- The current number is 11.
You heard him, right?
Haha said he had turned in three.
- He turned in three caramels.
- Did he?
- I was just saying, you know.
- Ms. Chairwoman.
I think there are more in the box.
Ms. Chairwoman.
(Suk Jin is going all-in
on So Min.)
14 caramels so far.
- We need only six more.
- Why are there so many?
Please.
17 caramels so far.
- Just three more caramels.
- I really want to be a chairwoman.
(They need only 3 more caramels
to replace the chairwoman.)
Three more caramels, please.
19 caramels.
- Just one more, please.
- Really?
(Just 1 more caramel will make
the anti-Jae Suk group succeed.)
- Please. Just one more.
- Who turned in so many caramels?
(What could be the fate
of the Card Shark Association?)
There's no more. I'm relieved.
- No more?
- 19 caramels in total.
(The final result, 19 caramels)
Congratulations.
We'll toss you up. Ready. 1, 2, 3.
- Hooray! Hooray!
- Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
- Hooray!
- Thank you.
Congratulations
on being elected again.
- Thank you.
- It's because...
- Why are there no more caramels?
- Congratulations.
Who didn't turn in caramels?
- I was worried a little bit.
- Despite the tense situation,
I openly supported you.
- Thank you for that.
- You know that, right?
- You still have all the caramels?
- Of course, I do.
We did as we were told.
I turned in just one caramel
because I had no choice.
- Please have a seat, everyone.
- Thank you.
Oh, my. My dear Jae Suk.
Move to the other side.
Ha Ryong... Ha Ryong will...
- Ha Ryong. Ha Ryong, you...
- Why did you push me?
- Ji Ha Ryong.
- Why did you push me, sir?
- Mr. Ji Ha Ryong.
- You pushed me...
My gosh. They needed only one more
caramel. That was unbelievable.
First of all, the new members...
- Just as I announced,
- Yes.
- please pay your association fee.
- Right.
Each of you should turn in
two caramels.
- You should pay the fee.
- You should.
- Now?
- Why must we pay the fee?
- I already told you.
The chairperson
of this association...
- has absolute power...
- This is...
- Hey! You little...
- Darn.
(He slapped him in the face.)
(Jo Kka Chi versus Ji Ha Ryong)
Stop it.
(The fateful fight
over the caramel tax)
(Suk Jin feels humiliated as he got
hit on the head with his own bag.)
- That's enough.
- Look at that.
- How dare you?
- He's actually kicking him.
He's actually hitting him.
(Even the chairman can't stop
their childish fight.)
Suk Jin, we're filming the opening.
- Save it. The shoot just began.
- They're actually fighting.
Stop it, guys. That's enough.
- Hey! How could you...
- Pay your fee.
- Pay your association fee.
- Pay it for now.
- Give me back those.
- Calm down.
- Give me back my caramels.
- Please sit down.
- Give me back mine!
- I'll give them back to you.
- Please sit down.
- If you're drunk...
Excuse me. If you're drunk,
you should go home.
Please go home.
My precious caramels...
(The old man can't get it together
when he's drunk.)
By the way, you have 20...
You still have 20 caramels.
Why did you say you voted?
I received 30 caramels.
Oh, I see.
Give me two caramels for now.
If I turn in two caramels...
Suk Jin, your mic fell off.
- Who will get them?
- Oh, his mic?
Don't worry about it.
He won't be saying anything.
(He won't let him talk either.)
Oh. Mr. Yu, that's impressive.
- You even sorted that out too?
- He's amazing.
- That was impressive.
- You won't even let him talk?
- Of course, I should do it.
- Look at So Min's face.
Isn't her fake smile so funny?
Gosh. Stop it.
I thought she was wearing the mask
we put on at the awards ceremony.
She looked like she was wearing it.
- Make it just one, please.
- Her eyes look so sad.
- And those who supported me,
- Yes.
- I'd like to...
- Yes, sir.
- give you one for each of you.
- Oh, my. Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Thank you for looking after us.
- He's so cool.
- He's the best. Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
- Do you guys have no pride?
- Do you have no pride?
- That's right. We have no pride.
- For a mere caramel...
- Right.
- Please sit down.
- Okay.
Jae Suk, please say New Year
greetings as the chairman.
All right.
- Mr. Yu, you dropped this.
- 2021...
- My, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Please put it on.
You sure are the winner
of the Grand Award.
- You're elegant and sophisticated.
- He's different.
- You speak so elegantly.
- Of course.
- Suk Jin, sit here.
- The year 2021 has come.
- That's okay.
- The new year has begun.
- I insist. You might get piles.
- Yes.
Shut it, you punks!
(Shut it, you punks.)
The chairman is speaking.
- Have you lost your mind?
- That's enough.
- Stop it.
- You little...
Gosh, seriously.
- Anyway...
- Hey, calm down. Take it easy.
- I can't believe them.
- I know.
But we should treat him
as our elder today.
- 2021 has come.
- Yes.
In 2020,
we all struggled
due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
I hope all our viewers' lives...
will return to normal
so they can be comfortable again...
in 2021.
- Also...
- He won't stay seated.
- we're going to...
- Sir.
(As the chairman's
boring speech continued...)
- Sir.
- My gosh.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Gosh.
The chairman is giving
his speech now.
Can't I even drink water?
- His speech...
- I am...
- saying greetings to our viewers.
- Exactly.
- He was saying something important.
- I mean...
- He drives me crazy.
- I'll use violence next time.
- Drink it.
- I'll slap you next time.
- It's okay.
- They can edit it out.
- Calm down. It's okay.
- Gosh. Stop it already.
- What are you doing?
- Go back to your seat.
- It's okay.
- Gosh. Why you little...
- What are you doing?
- Suk Jin, go ahead and drink it.
- Mr. Yu.
- Dear viewers,
- happy New Year!
- Happy New Year!
(While Suk Jin is drinking water,)
(they made a deep bow suddenly.)
They're getting a full shot.
- They got a full shot.
- Exactly.
- He put only one hand on the floor.
- That's right.
- Go ahead and drink it.
- Hey.
Why did you do it
while I was drinking water?
What's wrong?
I'm always grateful
to our viewers too.
- You can thank them any time.
- Absolutely.
- My gosh.
- Oh, wow.
- That was perfect.
- Yes.
It's the Year of the Ox.
Was anyone born
in the Year of the Ox?
- I was.
- Kwang Soo was.
Oh, Kwang Soo was born
in the Year of the Ox.
- He was born in 1985.
- In 1985, the Year of the Ox.
- I see. You were born in 1985.
- Yes.
To celebrate the start
of the Year of the Ox...
(He's finishing up hastily.)
- But...
- Yes?
Won't you make
any well-wishing remarks?
Last year was the Year of the Mouse.
I was born in the Year of the Mouse.
You're not the only person
who was born in the Year of the Ox.
- My mom was born in the Ox Year.
- So were a lot of other people.
- Really? Your mother was?
- Yes, my mom was.
Why don't you move to Hoengseong?
Why would I move to Hoengseong?
- Imitate an ox at least.
- That's nonsense.
How about you go by
Lee Hoeng Seong...
just throughout this year?
Lee Hoeng Seong.
- That makes no sense.
- I like the idea.
- How about Lee Beef?
- Lee Beef.
- That sounds great.
- You should go by Lee Beef.
- Lee Beef.
- That's a good name.
How about Lee Sirloin?
"Lee Sirloin"?
(Lee Sirloin got mad
because it's not "Ribeye".)
- Lee Sirloin sounds great.
- I like that name.
- Sirloin isn't the only part.
- I like the name.
- Why would you say that?
- I like the name too.
- Why "sirloin"?
- How about "ribeye"?
He'll be called Lee Sirloin
this year.
- His nickname has been decided.
- Why "sirloin"?
It's a great nickname.
Lee Sirloin.
- This is ridiculous.
- Sirloin is a perfect name.
- I agree.
- He was born in the Ox Year.
- Today,
we're going to do a race
to celebrate the new year.
It's the 2021 Card Shark Association
New Year's Party,
The Return of Gamblers.
Every one of you begins the race
with 30 caramels.
- But I have only...
- You can obtain more caramels...
through the missions.
The more caramels you have
at the end of the race,
the earlier you can leave
as well as receiving a prize.
- My goodness.
- That's a great reward.
- The bottom three...
- That's tempting.
will receive a penalty
and be the last to go home.
- Oh, boy.
- That's the worst.
- We're in Yangpyeong.
My house is three hours' drive
away from here.
If you get stuck
in rush hour traffic...
- During rush hour,
- It'll take three hours...
- during rush hour.
- It'll take three hours.
- I should do a really good job.
- The chairperson...
has even bigger power
than the last time.
He will divide you guys into teams
and decide the order of the teams...
- to carry out missions.
- That's great.
Also, for each mission,
he gets to add one rule
and use it for his own benefit.
- He has such a privilege?
- Really?
Being the chairman is awesome.
Absolutely. Congratulations.
- It's awesome.
- You have such a great privilege.
He's practically a king.
But if the members don't like
the chairperson,
you can put 20 caramels
in the proposal box...
before the next mission begins
to replace him with someone else.
- That will never happen.
- If you turn in 20 caramels,
you will elect a new chairperson
after the mission ends.
- I bet you won't be replaced.
- Today,
- the winner can go home early.
- Exactly.
So we should save
as many as caramels...
- Don't worry. We hold more chairs.
- I know.
A few of us already
fell out of his favor.
- Why would we do that?
- You fools.
- You should join us.
- I'm not worried at all.
- Do you two want to ally with me?
- Let's form an alliance.
- The three of us together.
- Ji Hyo, make up your mind.
She'll definitely ally with us.
- Are you with us?
- You should be.
Why are you forcing
an answer out of me?
- I'm not forcing anything...
- They're falling apart.
- We're outnumbered.
- Let me think about it.
- Did you pay the association fee?
- I did.
Well, they didn't.
- They received caramels instead.
- Okay, I hear you.
I love it. They're arguing
at the beginning of the year.
They must be looking
to win Best Couple in 2021.
Let me pass on the rules.
The new chairperson
won't be put to a vote.
The former chairperson
will write down five names...
on a roulette wheel
with eight blank spaces.
Spinning it will tell us
who the new chairperson is.
- I get it now.
- So it's like this.
The opposing team
may want a change in leadership,
- but one of us could be selected.
- Right.
It won't be easy to make a move.
He'll write down
four names from that side...
and only one from this side.
Then let's head out
to the location...
where the first game
will take place.
- All right.
- Let's go!
- Everyone.
- Yes?
- Gather around.
- Got it.
- Coming.
- We'll be right there.
Unbelievable.
Our fans provided us with beverages.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
We all enjoyed them.
I'm not joking when I say...
that we should be the ones
giving back to our fans,
but they're the ones
sending us coffee.
Thank you for being generous
when we haven't done much for you.
- What the...
- What was that?
Then do something for them.
- Please do something for the fans.
- Be more sincere.
(Suk Jin gets an earful
for chiming in unnecessarily.)
Don't kill the mood.
Act on your words then.
Do something for the fans.
- You and your empty promises.
- I'm always...
- grateful.
- He doesn't seem to mean it.
After the 2020 SBS
Entertainment Awards,
he complained about
it taking too long.
But then when
the chief director came by,
he said, "The ceremony was a blast!"
What a bootlicker.
- With his thump up.
- What a bootlicker.
- You're now making things up.
- So personally...
Don't just talk the talk anymore
and...
The proposal box
will always be in the room.
Hyeong Gu, why are you
eating the caramel?
(The assistant director was hungry
and ate a caramel.)
(They get agitated by the news
that he ate their money.)
You shouldn't eat that.
Hyeong Gu!
- You shouldn't eat that.
- Don't eat that.
- Why would you eat that?
- He ate a caramel?
Shouldn't you be watching
your weight for the wedding?
- Hyeong Gu...
- The wedding was postponed.
- His wedding was postponed.
- Still...
The January wedding...
- was pushed to July.
- July?
You got a few more
months of freedom...
hence the chubby cheeks.
Hyeong Gu,
you seem happy to have it postponed.
six months is a long time.
- How...
- They can register the marriage.
Is it better to quickly
register the marriage?
- If I'm being honest...
- Yes?
You should wait a year...
- To see how things go?
- Yes.
- Have you yet to register yours?
- After all this time?
It's about time you did it.
How else could I have added
my kids to my family register?
- I didn't know better.
- What on earth are you saying?
- I didn't know.
- Suk Jin,
- register your marriage.
- I already did!
- I didn't know.
- We might end up doing it for you.
But I already did.
(The coffee break ends with
his point of view on marriage.)
The first mission...
will only let the brave
win caramels.
- This is No Room for Cowards.
- This won't be easy.
- No Room for Cowards?
- No Room for Cowards.
Each round will see
three of you compete.
You'll sit under
two water balloons each.
In turns, you will
be able to launch an attack.
After betting
the desired amount of caramels...
- See those 12 lines behind you?
- Sure.
Only six of them are the real deal.
- We must cut one at a time.
- You will cut one.
The balloon that pops
could be yours, someone else's,
- or none of the above.
- I could pop my own balloon.
There's a chance
that nothing could happen too.
If you cut a line that leads...
to no balloons popping,
you will receive
the amount that you bet.
So it's still a win.
If you pop a balloon
above someone else's head,
you'll receive double.
- Double?
- Yes.
If your balloon pops,
you'll have to pay double.
(They will lose double the amount
if their balloon pops.)
The one whose balloon pops...
will end up paying double
the amount.
That'd be huge.
However, you're allowed
to jump out of the way.
If you think your balloon will pop,
you may move out of the way.
- We must say it in advance.
- If you're right,
you'll receive the amount
that was originally bet.
If you're wrong,
you'll have to pay up that amount.
It's all about trusting your gut.
Stay seated if you're brave enough.
- I'm not a coward.
- Neither am I.
Jump out of the way for no reason
and you'll lose caramels.
Then I'll lose two, right?
You're eliminated when
both your balloons pop...
and the round ends there.
The chairperson...
will split you into groups of three.
One must play twice though.
- Please keep that in mind.
- Participating in two rounds...
It could be an advantage
but also a disadvantage.
- Right.
- Only if you win caramels.
I'll have to see
how the round progresses.
Guys, can you all
take two steps back?
- 1, 2.
- You're allowed to give out orders?
- Then...
Stand at the far end.
- Move!
- Don't stand in the center.
Off you go.
Can you believe him?
I see.
Who you compete with
will be crucial.
Of course.
It's all up to you, Mr. Yu!
- Then...
- I hope you'll be generous.
Sure, I'll try to be fair.
- Jong Kook...
- Sure thing.
- Those will be the groups.
- Okay.
Kwang Soo, announce
how many you'll bet...
and cut a line.
It's nice and simple.
- This is nerve-wracking.
- Kwang Soo,
betting the right amount
is everything
Give up if you're scared.
(What?)
He didn't convey
any emotion with that.
- It was mechanical in a way.
- He said the line with no feeling.
- All right.
- If nothing happens,
I'll earn the amount
that I bet, right?
Right, the same amount.
If no balloons...
Just do it already!
- Bet your caramels.
- Bet five and be done with it.
- Don't be a coward.
- Just do it.
I'll bet five.
- 5?
- Yes, 5.
- That's quite a lot.
- Good.
Please announce
the number of the line you'll cut.
I'll...
(Kwang Soo must choose
which line he'll cut.)
I'll cut line number eight.
Would anyone like to step away?
Would anyone like to
move out of the way?
Not me.
You're never successful
at these games.
I'd like to take this chance.
There's a good chance
that yours won't pop.
There's more of a chance
of a balloon not popping.
- Which one's number eight?
- I'll receive double...
if someone else's balloon pops.
- Let's go!
- Let's do this.
- Please let it pop.
- I'll cut it then.
(Will Kwang Soo's bet pay off?)
- I'd love for it to pop.
- Number eight?
Please let Kwang Soo's balloon pop.
I think you should
move out of the way.
- Let Kwang Soo's balloon pop.
- Do it.
Let's go!
(Just please don't let it be mine.)
(A balloon popped!)
(Jong Kook loses 10 caramels.)
He earned double the amount.
You earned double.
How did he know?
- The chances were low.
- I earned 10 caramels.
Kwang Soo receives 10 caramels.
This is fun.
- He did it on his first try.
- No way.
I popped a water balloon
on Kim Grand Award's head!
- Unbelievable.
- Gosh.
- Right?
- He made it happen though.
I now have 10 caramels.
Suk Jin, how many will you bet?
He'll go for 10.
- Yes, 10.
- My gosh.
- 10 caramels?
- I was like this the whole time.
It's all about reading
the staff's intentions.
Number eight was attached
to a water balloon.
- Then...
- Can you head out...
and mow the lawn?
- What?
- Please mow the lawn.
I'll choose line number 11.
- The veteran entertainer...
- Line number 11.
Would anyone like to
move out of the way?
If I do,
but my balloon doesn't pop...
- You'll lose caramels.
- I'll lose 10, right?
- Right.
- That's too much.
It's a better choice to stay seated.
- It's hard to take that chance.
I'll stay seated.
- You already earned enough, so...
- You'll stay?
- What about you?
- I'll stay seated.
- Okay, here we go.
- Cut the line.
I think his balloon will pop.
I hope Suk Jin's will pop.
It'd be most entertaining
to have Suk Jin's balloon popped.
- That'd be hilarious.
- Let's do this!
(Suk Jin will lose 20 caramels
if his balloon pops.)
No balloons popped.
(He cut a line
that wasn't attached to anything.)
No balloons popped.
(Suk Jin earns 10 caramels
which is the amount he bet.)
You earn an additional amount
of 10 caramels.
An additional amount?
- Okay!
- Nice one.
- All right.
- That's not bad either.
- No way.
- Good job, Suk Jin.
It's all about probability.
There's a higher chance
of mine not popping.
Hyeong Gu's been given a big role.
- Look at him.
- Way to go.
Hyeong Gu, congratulations
on your big role.
- You were on TV.
- The camera was on you just now.
You're playing a big role.
Just don't eat the caramels
while you're there.
(Hyeong Gu's being accused
of eating all the caramels.)
- I should go just as big.
- Right.
- I'll bet 10.
- Of course.
My gosh.
There's a low chance
of my balloon popping.
Line number one's too taut.
Could that be on purpose?
Jong Kook is at it again.
- He's sharp with these things.
- He's being perceptive.
Line number one
is tighter than the others.
Spoken like someone
with an AB blood type.
- Line number one?
- Yes.
I'll step away.
- Kwang Soo, go ahead.
- I'll step away.
- I doubt his will pop.
- He's onto something.
I highly doubt it.
(If Kwang Soo's balloon pops,
he'll earn 10 caramels.)
- I think he made the right choice.
- I agree.
All right. Can I cut it?
- Sure.
- What if Kwang Soo's pops?
(Was it wise for Kwang Soo
to step away?)
(He cut it!)
Nothing happened.
Poor Kwang Soo.
(If nothing happens,
you lose the amount you bet.)
- Too bad.
- Kwang Soo ruined his chances.
Nice!
(He lost 10 caramels
by pretending to be intuitive.)
What did I tell you?
- What he earned earlier...
- Kwang Soo loses 10...
while Jong Kook earns 10.
You lost the amount
that you earned earlier.
- Give me 10.
- Oh, no!
It serves you right for showing off.
You seemed like a loser just now.
- I'm glad.
- It was all for nothing.
It's your fault for saying
the line was taut.
I just mentioned how weird it was.
It was too taut...
which made me believe
it wasn't attached to anything.
The balloons will now start to pop.
They probably will.
It's all about
stepping out of the way now.
I'll bet 15.
My gosh.
Stepping away might
make you lose big time.
Betting at least this many will...
- Right, we can't step away.
- We'll have to stay seated.
My goal...
is to pop someone else's balloon.
- Right.
- Of course.
The round will be over
if mine goes off.
The balloons will now
go off left and right.
Right?
Sounds intriguing.
(The spectators are thrilled
to be watching the game.)
- Which one will it be?
- Let me see.
Let me see.
One should know when to step away.
- Number 9 or 7...
- The chance that mine will pop...
I doubt that would
lead to yours popping.
They must not be placed
consecutively.
You don't know that, you punk.
- Why would you swear at me?
- Hey.
How would you know?
It's not like you are...
one of the staff members, you brat.
(Kim Grand Award became sensitive
as 15 caramels are on the line.)
- Hey, Grand Award.
- Why?
- Kim Grand Award.
- It's not like that.
- Mr. Yu, he's being unreasonable.
- He suggested...
a groundless assumption.
- That's how we play this game.
- You didn't make any sense.
You should've come up
with something reasonable.
- Gosh, Kim Grand Award.
- Kim Grand Award.
You just blabbered nonsense.
- I'll finish him.
- You'll finish me?
- Lee Sirloin! Lee Sirloin!
- Sirloin, hurry up.
- I choose...
- You can do it, Sirloin.
Okay. I choose number two.
- I think it'll make one pop.
- I'll go with number two.
- Number two will pop.
- I think so too.
- Good choice.
- You won't move, right?
- 2 or 8.
- I won't move.
- I can't because I bet 15.
- Let's go for it.
A man doesn't fear getting splashed.
- I never turn around.
- I won't move.
I'll get 30 caramels if I succeed.
Number two?
It's taut.
- It's taut.
- Sirloin, you can do this.
(The 2 of them are hoping
their balloons won't pop.)
I think the red one will pop.
(A balloon popped.)
- Number two?
- I think the red one will pop.
(Suk Jin's balloon popped.)
(He gained 30 caramel
as someone else's balloon popped.)
Good job!
(Suk Jin lost 30 caramels since he
stayed and his balloon popped.)
He's good at this game.
- He bet 15...
- Nice.
(He hit his head on the frame.)
Nice slapstick comedy act.
- Okay.
- He got lucky.
- Kwang Soo got lucky.
Did he bet 15 caramels?
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
- Kka Chi.
- That was cool.
- Then will I lose mine?
- Yes.
You should give Kwang Soo
30 caramels.
- I...
- You should pay double.
- 30 caramels?
- Yes.
Okay. It's over.
He's broke already.
- Will he get a loan?
- That's a lot.
30 caramels?
- He's broke already.
- The bankrupt man.
- He's broke now.
- Really?
- As you must know,
- Here are five caramels.
when you use up all the caramels
you have,
you should go out
to the snowy field.
- You know that, right?
- He'll roll around in the snow.
Yes, he'll roll around in the snow.
- Did I give you 3 or 4 times?
- 5 caramels each time.
I think he'll have to
get a loan soon.
- Can a bankrupt person go home too?
- He should find a loan shark.
You gave me the right amount.
Can I get a loan?
- We'll give you a loan.
- Okay.
I can't bet just one caramel.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
You should pay your association fee.
- That was unexpected.
- Pardon? But I...
- I supported you.
- When you earn a lot of caramels,
- Hold on a second.
- you should pay the fee.
Don't you remember me?
You should pay your association fee
no matter what.
- He's right, Kwang Soo.
- You should pay it.
- We're using water and everything.
- Exactly.
- It will all be...
- But earlier...
- It'll be used for the association.
- That's how we get the supplies.
- But I already paid one caramel.
- That's not how it works.
- 2 caramels per 10.
- Wait.
You have to pay five caramels.
Why did the fee go up
to five caramels suddenly?
- You have to pay five.
- Why did it suddenly change?
You earned a lot.
You just gained 30 caramels.
The interest is 2 caramels
per 10 caramels of principal.
- What?
- Two caramels.
Give me 20 caramels.
I should go big. This won't work.
I'll recover my funds.
- I will use this money...
- Wait, Suk Jin.
to help out members
who struggle financially.
- It's like a tax, right?
- Sounds great.
Yes, you can say that.
- Those who struggle financially...
- Wait.
- Why?
- Never mind. Continue.
- What is it?
It's nothing. Continue.
How dare you cut the chairman off?
We were...
(Here comes the bootlicker.)
(Our chairman is speaking
right now.)
- Hey, hey!
- What's that?
(What he did made everyone frown.)
- I can't believe him.
- What's wrong with you?
Those are new pants.
That brat.
- Gosh, seriously.
- My gosh.
I'm sorry.
- Gosh, that brat.
- Why did you do that?
I'm so sorry.
He spilled coffee on his new pants.
- My goodness.
- He's unbelievable.
- Gosh.
- Go back to your seat.
I apologize for what he did.
Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- You asked for 20 caramels.
Why did you leave
when I gave you only 10?
- Well, he...
- He's hopeless.
(Sadly, the slow-witted Suk Jin
miscalculated.)
He's going to lose anyway.
- I'm worried about him.
- How could you deceive me?
(Here's how he left when he received
only half what he asked for.)
(Suk Jin clearly asked
for 20 caramels.)
(The staff meant to give him
10 caramels twice.)
(But he left after receiving
a handful of caramels.)
(Walking away)
- Gosh.
- I'm worried about him.
- How could you deceive me?
- I didn't.
- How could you deceive the cast?
- You should have done it.
Why would you try to deceive us?
He deceives himself
and feels satisfied.
Exactly.
(Suk Jin who made a fool
of himself will bet this time.)
Moving on, it's Suk Jin's turn.
I will go all-in.
- Seriously? How many do you have?
- I have 21.
- Are you serious?
- That's too risky, Suk Jin.
- But this is...
- I can't move this time.
But if you bet all you have...
- I have a chance...
- You should think carefully.
- You might go broke.
- Listen to me.
You might end up in the snowy field.
- No, I won't.
- You'll have to get another loan.
I was defeated once.
So I should get back at him.
There's a high probability...
that their balloons will pop
or none will pop.
I'll most likely win this time.
But it's too risky.
You know, a thought just
crossed my mind.
- What is it?
- Are you trying to go home late?
- I mean, he might have planned...
- He made a meticulous plan.
No wonder why he left his bag open
as if he wanted us to steal it.
- It's odd.
- Hang on.
I miss my wife at this very moment
although I'm shooting a show.
(If you say so.)
- Are you referring to Chaser?
- Yes, I am.
I miss my Chaser so much.
- You do?
- Ms. Chaser.
Yes.
You mean, Ms. Chaser?
My dear Chaser.
Don't worry. You'll find yourself
naked in the snowy field...
in 10 minutes.
Without wearing pants.
- The staff didn't tell me that.
- Reporter Yang Se Chan.
Yes, this is Yang Se Chan.
- Tell us the next news.
- Up next,
Ji Suk Jin is rolling around
in the snow with no pants.
(Sighing)
It is assumed that he took off
his pants of his own accord.
That's all.
Are there any signs
that someone else did it to him?
No, there's none.
With caramels stuck in there...
It sounded...
like it was actually happening.
- When you're ready...
- Hurry up and cut the string.
I choose number five.
- Number 5?
- He chose number 5.
- I'll have to give you 42 caramels.
- Yes.
Well, I have no choice.
- 21 caramels.
- Okay.
I'll clear my debt
with what I earn this time.
- Okay.
- In the next round...
- The interest is four, right?
- Yes.
(What could be the fate
of line number 5?)
(It was a fake line!)
Okay!
(As no balloon popped,
Suk Jin keeps the 21 caramels.)
- I get caramels too, right?
- Okay!
(Relieved)
(He beat the odds
and picked the fake line.)
I can't believe no balloons popped.
- I think the staff members...
- That's amazing.
I think the staff members
find it weird.
- What? Why?
- Why didn't any of them pop?
Was one of them supposed to pop?
- But... Hold on.
- Okay.
- It's weird.
- Can you all stand up?
- Why?
- Something went wrong.
Did something go wrong?
(They're standing up carefully
as the staff asked.)
(Standing awkwardly)
- Are you grabbing the line?
- Please step aside.
- Pardon?
Move to the side, please.
- Move to the side.
- I bet something went wrong.
- You're holding the line, right?
- Hang on.
(He's holding the line?)
- Right. He's stepping on it.
- Move your foot.
(As soon as he moved his foot,
he got splashed by water.)
(His underhanded foot skill
shocked everyone.)
- Gosh, seriously.
- Gosh.
- Oh, yes!
- That brat.
- He's a swindler.
- Let's go.
(He stepped on the line
before the line was cut.)
(When the line he was stepping on
was cut,)
(he maintained his poker face.)
- He's a swindler.
- Gosh.
- What a swindler.
- He was stepping on the line.
- No wonder, something felt weird.
- That swindler.
- It was impossible to happen.
His balloon was supposed to pop
when I cut line number five, right?
That punk is a swindler.
- Gosh, that swindler.
- He was stepping on the line.
Can't we report him to the police?
- Shouldn't we report him?
- Shouldn't he be arrested?
This is really serious.
- He cheated.
- Give me 40 caramels.
- I mean, 42 caramels.
- I owe him 42 caramels?
2, 4, 6, 8...
Give me one more.
- Congratulations, Suk Jin.
- Have one.
- Thank you.
- You shouldn't give them away.
- Why? Why?
- Give me all five of them.
Kwang Soo paid
the association fee too.
- What kind of chairman he is?
- Give me...
- Give me three more caramels.
- He's like a hunter.
- Why?
- You see...
- You should pay the interest.
- The interest? Four, right?
- I'll help you out...
- if you struggle. Don't worry.
- Here are four caramels.
You should pay the principal too.
- Pardon?
- The principal of 20 caramels.
- Should I give you that too?
- Of course.
(He forgot about the principal.)
- You must repay what you borrowed.
- What are you trying to do?
You want to pay only the interest?
Not the principal?
He doesn't want to pay it.
Here you go.
Gosh. I forgot about the principal.
Gosh, seriously.
It's neck and neck.
- It'll end when one of them is out.
- Okay.
I'll go all-in,
but I don't know how many I have.
Please!
(He cut the line he chose
with his heart throbbing.)
None popped.
- None popped.
- Gosh.
Decide whether or not you want to
move out of the way.
- I won't.
- I'll move.
- You'll move?
- Yes.
It's taut.
- Oh, boy.
- Okay!
Kwang Soo gained 26 caramels,
and Suk Jin lost 26 caramels.
And Jong Kook lost 13 caramels.
Good game.
- Nice.
- We'll begin the second round.
- Now?
- Yes.
Se Chan, Haha, and So Min.
In this order.
I'm getting nervous somehow.
I'm the 1st one to go. I'll bet 20.
Betting 20 is normal.
- Personally...
- I would bet 30 at the start.
- You should go all-in.
- You should've bet all you had.
- Exactly.
- You're a man.
- I choose number nine.
- You should stay.
- Okay.
- Go, Yang Kka Chi.
- Please!
- Go, Yang Kka Chi!
You will all stay, right?
- Yes, we'll stay.
- Is this number nine?
There's no way any of them will pop.
- Exactly.
- Right?
- You can't move if you bet 30.
- I thought the same but failed.
1, 2, 3.
(So Min's balloon popped.)
(Yang Kka Chi succeeded
in attacking.)
- It ends if I make hers pop too.
- I wish I had gone all-in.
The balloon over this seat popped
in the previous round too.
You should give him 40 caramels
as he bet 20.
I have only 18 caramels.
Can I get a loan?
- You have 18?
- Yes.
You shouldn't have tried to
become the chairperson.
We'll lend you 30 caramels.
- 30 caramels?
- They charge a 20 percent interest.
You have to pay 2 in interest
for every 10 in principal.
It's ridiculous.
Which line should I pick?
Excuse me for a second.
- Here.
- Well...
- Mr. Yu.
- Se Chan.
I'll give you five caramels now.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
You pay the fee
for the association's sake.
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
You guys have experience.
What should I do?
Haha, how many bullets do you have?
- I have 30 now.
- 30?
Why would you call it a bullet?
It's a caramel.
- It's a caramel.
- Oh, right.
- I have 30 caramels.
- Why would he call it a bullet?
- Don't bet too many at the start.
- Is it like professional lingo?
But one balloon popped.
- It increased the probability.
- Your turn will come again.
- Right.
- Bet a large amount next time.
Then shall I bet just 10?
- You should bet 30 caramels now.
- That's too risky.
There's a 20 percent chance
your balloon will pop.
I would bet 30 if I were you.
- Okay. I'll bet 20 like he did.
- Good. You should bet that much.
(He mustered up the courage.)
(He decided to bet 20 caramels.)
Number one.
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's go.
Please don't let it be my balloon!
I think number one is yours.
I have a strong hunch.
Please.
- I can't change it now, right?
- That's right.
(You will lose 40 caramels
if you get hit with a balloon.)
(Whose line is number 1?)
So Min is in danger.
Will it be me again?
If it's me,
I will be incredibly unlucky.
- It can't be you.
- What a way to start 2021, right?
For goodness' sake.
(An unlucky man)
- There you go.
- Nice!
This is the worst way
to start the year.
I am completely broke!
What did I tell you?
- I told you to wait for a round.
- I told you.
- Seriously.
- Why didn't you listen?
I had a hunch.
This is the worst way
to start the year.
I told you.
I told you to wait for a round.
- I had a hunch.
- Why didn't you listen?
Seriously.
I can't believe this happened to me.
- Hey.
- Give me 40 caramels.
- I told you that it's yours.
- 40 caramels?
I told you to wait for a round.
- He is so unlucky.
- Seriously.
2021.
- 10.
- I will loan you 10 caramels.
You need to lend me more.
I plan to bet everything
on the next round.
Lend me as many as you can.
- How many can you lend me?
- Haha.
Haha, get a hold of yourself.
Haha! Haha!
Let go of me, you jerk!
Haha!
Let me play one more round!
Haha, please don't do this!
- Come on.
- Give me the caramels.
Haha! Get a hold of yourself!
- You can receive them over there.
- 40 caramels.
- Hey.
We won't be able to change
the chairperson...
if we go broke.
- Give me 50 caramels.
- We need to save them up for later.
It looks like I will continue to be
the chairman.
We won't be able to change
the chairperson.
It looks like I will continue to be
the chairman.
This is So Min's chance.
I will bet nine caramels.
Would someone lend me one caramel?
So Min, I will lend you 10 caramels.
If you win caramels, give me some.
- Okay, okay.
- Let's bet five caramels each.
- Forget it.
- Listen, everyone.
As the chairman, I will tell you
that you aren't allowed...
- to make investments.
- No?
- Why not?
It's a common practice.
- It isn't allowed.
- We need to replace him.
- It's a common practice.
- It isn't allowed.
Let's collect 20 caramels.
- I only have nine caramels.
Take out a loan then.
I have 9 caramels left
from the loan of 30 caramels.
- Did you take out a loan already?
- Yes.
Had it been the last round...
- So Min.
- I am done.
So Min, I have caramels
from the association.
Seriously.
(Rummaging)
I will give you nine caramels.
- Nine caramels?
- Thank you.
If you win more caramels,
pay the association fee.
- Move out of the way.
- Of course. Thank you.
What?
I can't believe you.
When I wanted to invest...
These caramels belong
to the association.
- Hold on.
Didn't you take these caramels
from us?
- Hold on.
- Give me back five caramels.
Didn't you take these caramels
from us?
- Hurry up.
- Hold on.
- I mean...
- This is absolutely ridiculous.
I turned in five caramels earlier.
Let's change the chairperson!
- Hold on.
- You didn't let me invest.
- Seriously.
- Why didn't you let me invest?
You acted all benevolent
with our caramels.
Listen.
You can do the same thing
when you become the chairperson.
- Listen.
- Is it so hard to understand?
- Let's change it.
- What?
- "It"?
- It.
- "Let's change it"?
- Hold on. "It"?
- "It"?
- What's wrong with "It"?
- Grab him!
(Grab him!)
- What?
- "It"?
Hey, aren't you upset?
I will beat him up.
- "It"?
- Be careful.
- Be careful what you say.
- All right.
- Don't call him "It".
- I am still the chairman.
All right.
- Gosh, this won't do.
- I will give you...
nine caramels.
20 caramels went in.
If I fail again,
I will have to roll in the snow.
Number two will be a good choice.
I will pop the number 11.
- Number 11.
If you pop your balloon,
I won't have a chance.
It's pulled tight. Here I go.
Here I go.
Get up as soon as you cut it.
- Yes!
- Okay!
(She succeeded to have her revenge.)
(So Min acquired
twice the caramels she bet.)
- That was incredible.
- Nice, nice.
Congratulations.
- Sir.
- All right.
It was my idea,
- so please give me some caramels.
- All right. Take a seat.
You need to turn in 40 caramels.
- 40 caramels?
- Yes.
The five caramels I turned in...
Jae Suk, hold on.
- Did you see that?
- Give me back the five caramels.
- Why?
I am broke. Jae Suk.
- Five caramels.
- I will take care of it...
once I get back what I invested.
I don't have any caramels left!
- Suk Jin, you earned a lot, right?
- No, I didn't.
No? You did, right?
- I am in the negative.
- No, I didn't. Jong Kook did.
- Did you earn a lot?
- No.
Who took all the caramels?
Four caramels.
Five caramels.
Did the chairman take
all the caramels?
- What?
- No one profited.
- Everyone is in the negative.
- What kind of a game is this?
- Who took all the caramels?
- What?
- Seriously.
- Jae Suk took all of them.
Who profited?
After each round,
you will see that no one profited.
- That's how it is.
- It's so fascinating.
Only the production crew
and I are profiting.
- Why is the chairman...
- You need to turn the tables.
- 20 caramels?
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- Take out a loan.
Take out a loan of 20 caramels
and bet everything.
Can I take out a loan now?
- Of course.
- I will take out a loan.
Bet everything.
How big of a loan can I take out?
How many caramels?
20 caramels.
Kwang Soo will stand surety for me.
- 20 caramels.
- Stand surety for me.
- Is that a thing?
- Give me 10 more caramels.
If Se Chan fails to pay back,
you must pay back twice the amount.
- Kwang Soo.
- For goodness' sake.
You can get a loan of 20 caramels.
- Okay. 20 caramels.
- Bet all of them.
- Bet 24 caramels.
- I will bet 40 caramels.
Excuse me.
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
How many caramels will you give me
if I invest eight caramels?
You can't make...
- a personal investment.
- You can't do that.
Only caramels from the association
can be invested.
- Caramels from the association.
- We need a new chairperson!
Suk Jin, I will give you 3 caramels
if you give me 8 caramels.
No, thank you.
- I won't give you any then.
- Sit down.
All right. Which line will it be?
Which line made my balloon pop
earlier?
Which numbers remain?
Number 1... No, numbers 2, 3, 5...
You were number 11.
It would be best...
if Se Chan pops
Haha or So Min's balloon.
That's right. It would be best.
- Something in the middle.
- No, no.
- No.
- The numbers go up to 12, right?
- Okay. Something in the middle.
- Let's have another round.
Out of the numbers...
(He sticks out his mouth
and decides on a number.)
- We should have another round.
- Number six.
There you go.
- Number six is dangerous.
- It's a good number.
- It's in the middle.
- A balloon will pop.
If I were you...
- I hope it isn't my balloon.
- Please.
(What will be the fate
of line number 6?)
Two.
(What will be the fate
of line number 6?)
(He got a fake line.)
It isn't half bad.
Be glad you took out a loan.
- That's right. It isn't half bad.
- See?
- 20 caramels.
- 40 caramels.
He got a lot of caramels.
- Do I get all of these?
- Of course.
He doesn't know the rules well.
He became rich.
(1 caramel drops.)
(Picking up)
He went all-in.
16 caramels.
Hey, beggar!
(Hey, beggar!)
Bring it over here.
How could you call me a beggar
just because I don't have caramels?
Bring it over here.
How could you call me a beggar
just because I don't have caramels?
Bring me the caramel you picked up.
This is the world of caramels.
You said it so awkwardly.
I am proud of him.
That's how you do it.
That's how you bet.
Who is next?
- So Min.
- Okay.
- So Min, bet everything.
- I will go all-in.
- She needs to go all-in.
You can't help but go all-in
when you play this game.
It's highly unlikely...
that I will be terribly unlucky
and pop my own balloon.
(In that case)
So Min, I will give you
some caramels from the association.
- Really?
- It's a dangerous investment.
Let's do this.
- Really?
- Okay.
I don't know how many there are.
This way, all of us can win.
- Don't you agree?
- Jae Suk, don't bet so many.
- Let's bet everything.
- Take some out.
Hold on. Hey, are those yours?
These aren't your caramels.
- Hold on.
- How many are there?
Get lost, you jerk.
Hold on.
This is the association fund.
- Don't act all benevolent...
- You are embezzling.
- with the association fund.
- Listen.
If you need help, throw a caramel.
Then I will take care of the matter.
He is a problem solver.
- I have a question.
- Throw a caramel.
Here you go.
- These are mine.
- How many are there?
These are mine.
15 caramels.
I will add these to 15 caramels.
I will go all-in.
This has to go well.
- Number five.
- I think a balloon will pop.
- Someone's balloon will pop.
- Of course.
- Guys.
- The odds are good.
- Number five.
- This could be interesting.
I invested the caramels
at the right time.
It was a good decision.
- Here I go.
- You invested at the right time.
- I will dodge.
- Will you dodge?
- But So Min is quite unlucky.
- Will he dodge?
I will dodge. If I get hit,
I pay twice the amount.
- But...
- I might not get hit, right?
If you don't get hit,
you will pay the exact amount.
- Let's go.
- Here I go.
Someone's balloon will pop.
It will be interesting.
(Will it be Haha,
the one who dodged?)
(Will it be Se Chan,
the one who didn't dodge?)
(Will it be So Min herself?)
In that case, the two of you...
(Is it Se Chan again?)
(So Min is Se Chan's killer.)
- Yes!
- That was incredible.
- Nice.
(The chairman's investment
was successful as well.)
For goodness' sake! What is this?
This is a good result
for all the members.
Thank you.
It was a good investment.
(The caramels go
into the chairman's pockets.)
Who will play the last round?
- Me! Let me play again.
- There is an opening...
- for one person.
- Me!
Haha doesn't have any caramels.
Let me take out a loan.
You should stop.
Please let me play one more round!
One more round!
- Listen.
- Get a hold of yourself!
One more round!
The association has
a lot of caramels, so...
Please let me play one more round.
- One more round!
- I could go again.
- Excuse me, Mr. Kim.
- Yes?
- Drag out the two of them.
- Okay.
Come here.
One more round!
- You jerk!
- One more round!
Stop it.
I had over 100 caramels.
You should know when to stop.
Do you want to play a round?
Yes, I do.
This is insane.
I really want to play a round.
- I will do it.
- I want to send him...
- out to the snow.
- I will do it.
- He should experience the cold.
- I really want to play a round.
- What's wrong with you?
- I will bet my life on this round.
- Come here.
- Okay.
Come here. I will give you a chance.
Let's do this.
I will bet my life.
I want to play one more round.
I will take out a loan
and bet everything.
Going all-in is the way to go.
- The odds are the best.
I will go all-in.
- The first try is the best.
- Yes.
- He can come up with a rule, right?
- That's right.
- You haven't made one yet, right?
- I haven't made one yet.
- You can go twice that way, right?
- He can do what he wants.
Can he make a rule...
- after something occurs?
- He can't do that.
He can say, "Let's redo it."
- Can he say that?
- I knew it.
- He has an advantage.
- What?
Can he say, "Let's redo it"?
- That's...
- Let's go.
(Round 3 begins.)
He poured them in.
(Both Ji Hyo and Jae Suk had
1 balloon popped.)
I will use the association fund
as well.
- Why would you use that?
- It's the association fund.
There is nothing wrong
with using the association fund.
- It's an investment.
- It's the association fund.
How many caramels do you have...
as the association fund?
- There must be about 50 caramels.
- There are a lot.
Can't you reveal
how many caramels there are?
I can reveal it.
- I haven't used any of them yet.
- Okay.
Everyone,
I will bet these caramels.
I will use the chairman's chance...
- and make a rule.
- Really?
Will he ask
for twice the amount he bet?
(He is as powerful as ever.
Which rule will he ask for?)
- Can you tell me the numbers?
- Yes.
(Does he mean the numbers
behind the balloons?)
The numbers?
Can he do that?
This is ridiculous!
What is this?
(The chairman's power
makes their jaws drop.)
- What is this?
- The numbers?
What do you mean?
It's the chairperson's rule.
The chairperson has too much power.
He has too much power.
(Jae Suk gets the numbers
from the production crew.)
(He saw all the numbers
as the chairman.)
He will remain the chairman.
(He knows what could happen.)
I am torn. If they dodge...
This is a match of the brains.
A psychological game.
You have to put on your poker face.
This is hard.
Will he get Ji Hyo or Suk Jin?
Will he end the game?
I decided whether or not
I will dodge.
One of them will end up in the snow.
This is bad.
(44 caramels are on the line.
What will be Jae Suk's choice?)
In that case,
I will skip this turn.
- What?
- I choose number seven.
"I will skip this turn"?
("I will skip this turn"?)
- My goodness.
- That's something we didn't expect.
- This time,
- "I will skip this turn"?
I will skip the turn.
- Since Kim Grand Award is...
- You will skip the turn?
- Yes.
I will skip the turn.
- He is playing a trick.
- Shall I go ahead and cut a line?
No. Hold on.
Will you listen to him or...
That means he won't cut
one of our lines.
That's right.
But...
I think he will cut
one of our lines.
I will dodge!
He said he will skip the turn.
- Number seven.
- I will win.
Ji Hyo, aren't you going to dodge?
(If Suk Jin's balloon doesn't pop,
he must pay 44 caramels.)
I...
It's too late now.
1, 2...
(Ji Hyo decided not to dodge.
What did Jae Suk's words mean?)
1, 2...
(Silent)
- Did he really skip the turn?
- He skipped the turn.
(I told you that I will do it.)
Suk Jin needs to pay up, right?
- Good job.
- He needs to pay up.
Did you really skip the turn?
- Good job.
- All right.
I skipped the turn.
It's like playing rock...
- after saying, "I will play rock."
- I am amazed.
- Suk Jin got fooled.
- He caught 2 birds with 1 stone.
- He won caramels...
while Suk Jin lost caramels.
Suk Jin's line still remains.
- It still remains.
- That's right.
Why didn't you believe my words?
Jae Suk, should we throw him
into the snow?
Not yet. The game is ongoing.
He might turn the tables.
I was winning.
What is Suk Jin going to do?
This is...
This is incredible.
- "I will skip this turn."
- The game is still ongoing.
- I will give you two caramels.
- Why?
Please give me a number.
He can't do that.
(She begs for a number
with 2 caramels and a smile.)
- She wants to know her number.
- He can't do that.
- I am sorry.
- Jae Suk knows the numbers.
- Jeoktoma.
- I am sorry.
- I will give you two more caramels.
- He can't do that.
- I can't do that.
- She is cute.
- She can't do that.
- It's understandable.
- I am sorry.
- You had the right approach.
My goodness.
But...
I...
- 10 caramels?
- 10 caramels. Hold on.
- Decide on the number first.
It's my business.
She got mad at Suk Jin.
- It's your business.
- Yes.
I just got absorbed in the game.
(The two of them become
overly sensitive.)
Would you recommend me a number?
He can't do that.
Number five.
- Number five?
- Yes.
Number five? I will dodge.
This is a psychological game.
I need to use my brain.
It will be unbelievable
if Ji Hyo's balloon pops.
- I think your balloon will pop.
- It will be okay if it doesn't pop.
What?
She is out.
For goodness' sake.
Ji Hyo will end up in the snow.
- Hey.
- No, no!
(There is a place
for the broke gamblers.)
She is getting sent
to the snowy field.
- Gosh, Ji Hyo.
- No.
Come on.
(Ji Hyo gets dragged
to the snowy field.)
Stop it. I am in the snow already.
(Rolling)
- Go.
- Get lost.
- Don't come back here.
Let me join you guys.
- Get lost.
- Let me join you guys.
She rolled in the snow.
(The brothers come back
after finishing the task.)
Gosh, I didn't know.
- I need a bigger bag.
- Jae Suk.
- Put some in the safe.
- This is no joke.
We need to change the chairperson.
We need to change the chairperson
and use the caramels.
I put some caramels
in the proposal box.
- Me too.
- Darn it.
The thing is,
all of us have
only a handful of caramels.
- They are our tear-soaked caramels.
- I know.
- We need to take his caramels.
- It's better to switch it.
Guys.
- Yes?
Are you trying to get
a new chairperson?
- No, no.
- No. What are you saying?
- Of course not.
- I am very satisfied.
I respect you.
They have gathered around...
- to come up with a scheme.
- That's right.
- There is no other explanation.
- No, no.
- The first mission is complete.
- Okay.
Let's check the proposal box
before the second mission.
Dealer, please announce
the number of caramels.
(If there are 20 caramels,
the chairperson will be replaced.)
(How many caramels
are in the proposal box?)
In the proposal box,
(Please!)
there are 20 caramels.
Did you put in caramels?
20 caramels?
- Really?
- Who put them in?
- Exactly 20 caramels?
Who put them in?
(Jae Suk's tyrannical behaviors
upset the younger members.)
I will put in five caramels.
(So Min put in 5 caramels.)
(Kwang Soo put in 5 caramels.)
(Se Chan put in 5 caramels.)
(So Min put in 10 caramels.)
Since there are
20 caramels in total,
the chairperson will write down
the five candidates.
- Okay.
- When did everyone turn them in?
The former chairperson will put down
five names...
in the roulette with eight slots.
- Trust me and write my name.
- You can trust me too.
The new chairperson should be
someone without many caramels.
I don't have any caramels.
I will write down Ji Hyo's name.
- Remember me.
- Jae Suk.
- Think of me as a parrot.
Jae Suk, earlier...
You should write my name down,
don't you think?
Listen.
You know how much I supported you.
I know that, but...
His tone is too rebellious.
Okay. I will write your name.
- You are making it hard.
- You should write it.
You won the Grand Award.
- You supported me well.
- That's right.
- Jae Suk, I am the one...
- At the beginning...
who supported you from the start.
- I will write your name, Se Chan.
- Okay!
Kwang Soo, talk to him. Okay.
- The thing is,
- You know what I did.
I supported you from the start.
- I don't have many caramels.
- I am begging you.
Kwang Soo put caramels
in the proposal box.
Come on.
You put caramels
in the proposal box.
- He did that.
- Me?
- He put a lot of caramels.
- I didn't do that.
- I received a tip-off...
that you put in caramels
in the proposal box.
- I can't write your name.
- That's right.
- Isn't that right?
- So, I...
I got a loan, so I don't have
any money.
I swear that I saw So Min put it in.
- I also saw Se Chan do it.
- It's not me.
- I don't have any.
- Okay.
- There are five people.
- Is that it?
- Let's go.
- I'm satisfied with one spot.
- It was done fairly.
(The nomination for the next
chairperson is complete.)
- You can only do it one time.
- Let's do it once.
But you...
Did you put a caramel in
but didn't get in the candidates?
- Did you put it in?
- But...
I put it in.
He hid it.
- I paid all the association fees.
- Okay.
- But...
I didn't gain anything.
Okay, let's go then.
- Let's go.
- I'm going to start.
- Who will succeed me...
- Please...
as the next association chairman?
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- I just want to do it once.
- Honestly, I have no greed.
- I...
(The roulette is spinning.)
But the association chairman is...
- The chairman is really powerful.
- The chairman is...
- really powerful.
- The chairman has strong authority.
Do you have any objections?
It's me.
- Kim Grand Award.
(The next association chairman is
Kim Grand Award.)
- Kim Grand Award.
- Don't do it.
- Come here.
- Kim Grand Award.
- Yes.
- I made you the next chairman.
- This is...
I didn't...
Go away!
- He's mistreating you.
- Yes.
- Kim Grand Award.
- I just touched him.
- Today...
- This is the world I wanted.
- I said I didn't want anything...
- Kim Grand Award.
- Gosh.
- I'll take him away.
- It would have been me...
- What are you doing?
- if it stopped one step further.
- He's out.
Who is that guy?
What does he do for a living?
You disloyal punks!
Let me go. You disloyal punks!
- Roll him around.
- You disloyal punks!
- Hey.
- That's enough. Let's go.
- Let's go.
You disloyal punks! Hey!
Gosh, those punks...
You disloyal punks!
- Chairman.
We got rid of the rotten part
of the past.
- Close the door.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Close the door.
(He's suddenly considered
a deep-rooted evil.)
Hey, you two with the mullets.
- You're the one who likes snow.
- Oh, my.
- Kim Grand Award.
- Yes?
I made you the chairman.
I know it.
- You know it, right?
- Yes, I know it.
He even drew a mustache on
with a permanent marker.
I can't believe
I ended up like this.
Yes, let's see how you do.
I'm going to rise again.
- I'm going to rise again.
- That's enough.
So Min, can you give me one?
- I have 0.
- Do you have 0?
I'll give you the rules
for the next mission.
For the next mission, if you get
the least number of members...
in a room,
you will get more caramels
- It's a cozy meal.
- This is driving me crazy.
In a moment, you will move
one person at a time.
You will go into 1 of the 3 rooms.
Each person will take turns
to choose a room.
The members who chose the room
with the least number of members...
will get three times
the amount they betted.
(The room with the least members
gets 3 times the amount of the bet.)
(If they just choose well, they will
get 3 times the amount of caramels.)
- Three times?
- Yes.
I'm curious. Can I get a loan?
I don't have any.
- I only have debt.
- I also only have debt.
I'll give you a loan of 20 each.
- Okay, give them to me.
- What will you give 20 each?
- It's a loan.
- Okay.
- Why are you so excited?
I also wanted to get it.
- He wants more caramels.
- He's sensitive.
It's because I'm so upset.
- This mission is really good.
- Yes.
- I can get a lot at once.
- That's right.
Hey, you can do this.
You can go to room 1 and say,
"Don't come to room 1."
"Hey, you can do this"?
- "Hey, you can..."
- Roll him in the snow!
- Come here.
- I mean...
- Isn't "Hey, you" too informal?
- Yes.
- You're the chairman.
- That's right.
(Breaking News, "Ji Suk Jin rolls
around in the snow with no pants")
Up next, Ji Suk Jin...
is rolling around
in the snow with no pants.
- Yes.
- Roll him.
It is assumed that he took off
his pants of his own accord.
That's all.
He's a funny man.
Are you really going to live
like that?
- "Hey, you" was too informal.
- It was.
- We took care of him.
- As a matter of fact...
My title is the chairman.
- But Kim Grand Award,
- Yes?
I'm a little upset.
- I made you the chairman.
- Hey.
- You're amazing.
- Attention!
How dare you
lean on one foot like that?
- What are you doing?
- Roll him.
How dare you lean on one foot?
- He leaned on one foot.
- How dare you!
- I was really surprised.
- Are you okay, Jong Kook?
I never saw someone
lean on one foot.
(The mullet gang is back on the move
because he leaned on one foot.)
How dare you lean on one foot?
Get lost.
I'll do something about them.
I'm so mad.
He will never be able to lean
on one foot again.
(He comes back
while flipping his mullet.)
- We scolded him good.
- That was really...
Gosh, these mullets are really...
- "Mullets"?
If I become the chairman,
I'll do something about you.
(Kwang Soo provokes Jae Suk
by pretending to spit on him.)
(A hand-to-hand fight breaks out.)
- Jong Kook, he used violence.
- Violence?
- You used violence.
- Oh, my.
Oh, my.
These are hair extensions.
(He timidly punishes
the mullet gang.)
- Gosh, they're really...
- I'm sorry,
but why do you keep
standing next to me?
You're warm.
- You're warm.
- Mustache Brothers, just leave.
What?
- You Mustaches...
- You Mullets...
- You'll fight with the Mullets?
You Mullets...
(The kiddie fight started again.)
You Mullets are really...
- You...
- Mustache Brothers...
- Okay, good.
- Good job.
- Did my mustache get erased?
- How dare you touch my mullet?
- No, it didn't get erased.
Okay, first...
For the order,
I think the ex-chairman...
should start first.
Please put me at the end.
- He talks too much.
- Do you want this to be your end?
- What do you want to do?
- Okay.
- He should go second then.
- Yes.
That's right.
- The two Mustaches should go first.
- He should go second.
- I'll go first.
- I put almost 10 caramels in.
- Really?
- Yes.
I really hate lies.
Do you know that or not?
- I really put them in!
- Violence and...
Hyeong Gu, tell him for me.
First...
He's third then.
You should go third.
- The fourth is...
- Conscientiously, I'll go next.
I'll go next conscientiously.
- I like things like this. Okay.
- Thank you.
I'll go next.
(He wasn't aware of it.)
(Drop)
(He got his bag strap cut off
with his eyes wide open.)
(He's really happy.)
- Gosh.
- That's unbelievable.
He cut it off.
- Why did you cut it off?
- What did he do?
- I saw this on the news.
This is like...
What is this?
This is...
Last time, Tae Hyun...
He's really a piece of trash
if he did that.
- What?
- I can't believe it.
- I don't know.
- What is he going to do?
Okay, good.
- We will start with number one.
- Yes.
Tell us how much you will bet,
and just go by yourself.
- I'm in trouble.
- Can we see how much he bets?
Yes, we will start right away.
This is all luck.
Okay, all-in.
- All-in.
- How many do you have?
(Jae Suk goes all-in.)
Wait a minute, but this is...
If we put all of them in,
we can't change the chairman.
Wait a minute. The chairman... Okay.
- Okay.
- So let's put all of them in.
- I heard you.
Okay, I will start then.
Gosh, this is all luck.
We can't do anything about it.
(He needs caramels to get back
the spot of the chairman.)
- Where is it?
- Take this lunchbox,
and go to the second floor.
- So do I choose 1 room?
- Yes, there are 3 rooms.
(Jae Suk goes first.)
(He has to predict a room where
the members will go the least.)
(Thinking carefully)
(After deep deliberation,
he chose...)
(room number 1 which appears
right away on the 2nd floor.)
Please...
- I'll put 20 in.
- Okay.
Ji Suk Jin, please get going.
- There's a proposal box.
- Yes.
Here.
(He dreams of reclaiming
the spot of chairman.)
(Suk Jin turns in 12 caramels.)
Let me be chairman one more time.
We need to change the chairperson.
(He has to avoid the room
Jae Suk is in before everything.)
Room number 2 and 3...
(His hands become polite at
the sound of Suk Jin's footsteps.)
(It's a mission that will get them
three times more caramels.)
(He's in the middle of a lonesome
high-degree psychological warfare.)
People will skip number one.
(This person didn't skip number 1.)
Will you make a decision?
People won't go in number one.
- Gosh, I really can't believe it.
- Gosh.
(A grand failure of
the psychological warfare)
- Why did you choose number one?
- Why are you here?
Gosh, you're really
driving me crazy.
You should have skipped number one.
How could you go in number 1
when you started 1st?
- It's over.
- Gosh.
I can't believe it. It's okay
if no one else comes in.
How could you...
You're really driving me crazy.
(Kwang Soo enters third.)
Hello.
(He also aimed for a big one
and bet 20 pieces.)
All right.
If there is one more person,
the possibility will be slim.
(Will he be able to
escape being unlucky...)
(and get a big fortune of caramels?)
(Kwang Soo stopped
in front of room number 1.)
(Will Kwang Soo also
go into room number 1?)
It's okay to knock, right?
I won't talk.
(He starts a knocking game
with room number 2,)
(walking on eggshells.)
(He's also knocking on the hearts
of the Mustache Gang.)
(After knocking up to
room number 3...)
I choose this room.
(He seems to have made
a decision. Where did he head to?)
(Kwang Soo also chose
room number 1.)
- Gosh, seriously...
- Gosh.
Hey!
What is really wrong with you?
Are you out of your mind?
Are you really out of your mind?
- We're over.
- I chose the wrong room.
I turned a lot of caramels in.
How many?
- I turned 20 in.
- Me too.
I went all-in.
- It's already over for us.
- It's over for us.
But didn't number one
just feel right for some reason?
Yes, I felt drawn to it strangely.
That's impossible.
- Is this possible?
- Gosh.
(The room with the least number
of people will win.)
(What are the choices
of the remaining 5 people?)
(The fate of the card sharks...)
(depend on a single choice.)
(The final match of the card sharks
starts properly now.)
(They have nothing to lose now.)
(It's a betting war
with their pride on the line.)
You can't see anything, can you?
(The last match of the gamblers.
What will the ending be?)
(And...)
(The production objective of Running
Man remained the same for 10 years.)
(There's a need to change it.)
(The members' characters also
remained the same for 10 years.)
(He's the dad of three kids.)
(He's an old fossil now.)
This should really change.
(That's why they will write
their own characters.)
- I thought it was like this.
- What?
(The last program of Yoo Jae Suk
who is facing his retirement...)
(after 21 years of his career?)
(Open your eyes.
Fun on a big scale will come.)
(Open your mouth.
Laughter on a big scale will come.)
That's good.
(They wrote the production objective
according to their preference.)
"He has a lot of greed
hidden behind his appearance."
(Amid the exchange of well-wishing
remarks, they even wrote...)
(the member's introductions
according to their preference.)
(Only 1 of their production
objectives can be chosen.)
(In whose hands will the 10-year-old
production objective get changed?)
(Production Objective Race:
Running Man Rewritten)