Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(The warm autumn sunlight welcomes the sunny morning.)
It's fall now.
The weather is warm though.
(The members gather enjoying the autumn weather.)
It was cold in the morning.
This is the typical fall weather.
(Pleased)
- There are dragonflies. - Like high sky and plump horses.
They say it's the season of high sky and plump horses.
(Proud)
- Ji Hyo. - Yes, Haha.
(Ji Hyo runs in wearing a scarf.)
I like your scarf.
- Did you go to the beauty salon? - It goes well with fall.
Why do you go to the beauty salon so often these days?
(Interested that she's going to the beauty salon more often)
Did you go there again?
Stop going there. You don't have to go.
(Laughing)
They just criticize her whatever she does.
Your hair looks...
(Ji Hyo has become more elegant in the fall.)
- It looks neat. - Your hair looks much better.
Because it's fall.
The weather is perfect for an outing.
(Even the sky is clear.)
The weather is nice. The sky looks like that of LA.
(It looks like the sky of LA?)
Why do you keep saying that it's like LA?
This is the Korean fall weather.
(An LA lover forever)
Hey, this is obviously Korea. Why do you say it's LA?
(Korean sky)
This is the season of high sky and plump horses.
I wonder if LA is doing well.
This is the best compliment for him.
"You look like a person from LA."
- He does say that. - "This is LA style."
(Jong Kook's "It's LA" means...)
- "You look like a native of LA." - I heard...
(it's good, satisfying, glad, and desirable.)
(He uses "LA" as an adjective.)
that the weather is nice in LA.
But we're in Korea now. Why would you compare it with LA?
I wonder if it's doing fine.
- Who? - His daughter.
Your daughter? I see.
(His daughter in LA only exists in his imagination.)
- Is she doing well? - In LA...
He just nods his head now.
(He plays along with any joke that has "LA" in it.)
- He admits it. - Was her name Britney?
- My gosh. - My gosh.
(Why isn't So Min here?)
Where's So Min?
I didn't see So Min today.
What happened?
Do you remember? She was going to get a penalty.
- Oh, right. - The penalty.
- Right. - From the Precious Sisters Race.
(That's right.)
Jeon So Min. I sincerely congratulate you.
(Last week, Precious Sisters Race)
Both of them are good, but So Min pulls them off well.
(So Min was picked to get a penalty at the last moment.)
(They said she'd get a special penalty during the opening.)
- I wonder how she will look. - I'm looking forward to it.
(So Min's surprising penalty will be revealed soon.)
I just went to the restroom earlier.
(Kwang Soo shares his story that happened before shooting.)
I said hello to the staff on my way and went inside.
(Kwang Soo went to the restroom in the building earlier today.)
Some people were sitting in there,
so I greeted them and got out after using the restroom.
It turns out, it was someone's house.
It's not an accommodation we booked for the shoot.
(He visited the owner of the house who let us use his lawn.)
- Really? - Hey.
- I felt terrible. - How could you do that?
- We already told you... - Hey, listen.
(Criticizing)
- Why did you barge in their house? - It wasn't a waiting room.
I thought it was our waiting room.
- You must have lost your mind. - I entered the house saying hello,
but they only stared at me without greeting me back.
(I knew it was weird.)
You can't just barge in like that just because you're a celebrity.
(He's got something on him.)
I'm really sorry. I didn't know.
We must make sure no celebrities misbehave themselves...
Don't go too far.
I went in there because I didn't know.
(He's excited to have this thing on him.)
- Just because he's popular... - And I apologized.
- I mean, this is... - He's always so arrogant.
(Teasing)
This is a whole new level of a power trip.
It's trespassing.
- Trespassing? - It's a power trip.
(Taken aback)
- He's not even that popular. - Exactly.
- It wasn't like that. - What's this hand gesture?
(He becomes unpopular for going to the bathroom once.)
- He's not that popular. - He doesn't care about anything.
- "I'm a star, so let it slide." - He doesn't care.
He peed in someone else's house just because he's a little famous.
(Popularity)
"I am Lee Kwang Soo!"
(They all have something to say about his story.)
I thought we were going to be filming in there.
- "I go wherever I want." - Exactly.
- "I'm a star." - Gosh, seriously.
(Moving on from Kwang Soo the star)
Now, let's meet today's guests.
(There are guests on Running Man this week?)
- Let's do that. - Okay!
- Please come out. - Okay.
See? Jong Kook hates it when we do this.
(It's always embarrassing to make that sound.)
He's excited. It's weird when...
(Who could be today's guests who are showing up amid cheers?)
Oh, my.
(Surprised)
(Hello, everyone.)
Oh, my. Hi, guys.
- Are they BLACKPINK? - Hi, guys.
(K-pop star BLACKPINK is back with "Lovesick Girls".)
- Awesome! - My goodness.
- Hi. - Hello.
(They dominate the K-pop history.)
(The global artists on another level)
(They swept the Billboard Hot 100.)
(The global star, BLACKPINK, is here.)
It's been a while.
How long has it been?
- BLACKPINK is here! - Hello.
(All members of BLACKPINK)
- They're all here! - It's been a long time.
- Why today? - Come here.
(Not this day)
I wish I had dressed up and had my hair done.
Guys, we should've dressed up for today.
(Se Chan is sad that he couldn't go to the hair salon today.)
Now, I see why Ji Hyo went to a beauty parlor before coming here.
(Ji Hyo looks neat in front of BLACKPINK.)
BLACKPINK, please say hello to our viewers first.
(Today's guest, BLACKPINK!)
- BLACKPINK. - I'm so excited.
- Hello. We are BLACKPINK. - Hello. We are BLACKPINK.
- Hello, BLACKPINK. Welcome. - Oh, yes!
- All right! - I'm overwhelmed.
(Getting excited)
- Let's watch their performance. - Okay.
(BLACKPINK's performance of the new song)
- Sounds great. - That would be awesome.
I can't believe I get to see their performance in person.
The weather is nice, and we're surrounded by beautiful scenery.
(Even the weather is perfect as BLACKPINK will perform outside.)
It's perfect weather for BLACKPINK.
("Lovesick Girls" by BLACKPINK)
Come on!
(Clenching his fists)
(You can't end my love just as you want)
(BLACKPINK's dazzling performance...)
(makes everyone want to mimic them.)
(The hip dance move that reminds us of jump rope)
- Why is she... What is she doing? - What?
(At that moment...)
- What? Hang on. - What is she doing?
(What is that?)
My gosh. What's going on?
- Gosh. What is this? - What's going on?
(So Min walks out from the back.)
- What is she doing? - What? Hang on.
- Gosh. What is this? - What's going on?
(Jeon So Min, one-day BLACKPINK member, the loser to get a penalty)
Why did she come out?
(BLACKPINK is dancing, )
What a surprise.
(and So Min is standing behind BLACKPINK.)
- What is this? - My gosh.
Why did she come out?
(I learned from this part.)
What a surprise.
- What is this? - My gosh.
Get out!
- What are you doing? - Get out!
(Doing the dance she learned after arriving 1 hour early)
- Are you out of your mind? - I said, get out.
This is ridiculous. Stop it!
(He hates it.)
Get out!
(He asks her to leave.)
I said, get out!
- I can't believe this. - Get out!
(She practiced too hard to stop now.)
- I said, get out. - Get out!
(Even the part she's confident in)
- Hey! - I said, get out!
- I actually got goosebumps. - What's that?
(So Min is the one getting the penalty, )
- That's embarrassing. - What are you doing?
(and the rest of the members suffer with her.)
- Get out. - I said, get out!
(She's enjoying the penalty.)
Hey!
Get out!
(Among 4 members of BLACKPINK, )
- Get out. - How dare you dance with them?
Get out!
(So Min, who lost last week, )
- Get out. - How dare you dance with them?
(joined BLACKPINK as a one-day member.)
- Get out already. - Get out.
(So Min's penalty time ends.)
- What was that? - Good job.
- Get out. I said, get out. - Haha.
Get out!
- She's so annoying, Haha. - How dare you?
(The members are irritated, )
(so she charges toward the staff.)
- My gosh. - That's so embarrassing.
Get out now.
(They can't react.)
- She suddenly came out... - Get out.
She must have lost her mind.
(She finished up her penalty while enjoying it.)
- You see... - This is ridiculous.
- It was so funny... - You did a great job.
(She joins BLACKPINK as if she belongs there.)
that while they were performing their trendy dance,
(BLACKPINK's...)
So Min was dancing in an old-fashioned way.
All I could see was So Min.
- Only So Min was... - Because she stood out too much.
- That was funny. - Your dance was like retro.
(Revisiting Se Chan the hardcore fan)
Why did you dance like that?
Hey, go away.
(Giggling)
- Hey. - Sweetheart.
Don't call me that.
My, that was so funny.
(So Min's penalty ends for real.)
- She ruined it. - My goodness.
Our four guests,
(After the intense penalty, )
(they meet BLACKPINK properly this time.)
the members of BLACKPINK!
They look so sophisticated.
- Oh, my. You're right. - You all look so cool.
(The real guests put smiles back on their faces.)
- Indeed. - They're so cool.
- I agree. - They're cool city girls.
(City girls)
- "City girls"? - Look at them.
- How sophisticated. - Please say hello individually.
Jisoo, you go first.
Hello. I'm Jisoo.
(Feeling great)
Hello to you too.
- She even says hi differently. - Next up is...
Hello. I'm Jennie.
Come on.
Let's move on.
Hello. I'm Rose.
- She has such a beautiful voice. - And next...
Hello. I'm Lisa.
- Lisa! - Lisa!
(He's on cloud nine.)
Hello.
(She's trying to say hello as a member of the group.)
- I'm Jasu... - Shut it.
- I have my own stage name too. - What is it?
Jasu as in embroidery.
(Jasu also known as So Min)
(Her hobby is embroidery, and her role model is Jisoo.)
- Jasu? - Jasu as in embroidery?
"As in embroidery".
- Stand with them. - No.
Stand in the center now.
(After the self-introduction of Jasu...)
Above all,
whenever BLACKPINK joined our show,
- they created legendary scenes. - Absolutely.
(BLACKPINK creates legendary scenes every time they appear.)
The clip of Jennie in the haunted house...
(Remembering)
- went viral. - It's still popular.
(Jennie's haunted house experience was sensational.)
It's still all over the internet.
Are you confident? If not, I'll go first.
(2 years ago, Running Man, Episode 409)
(She entered the haunted house with confidence, )
Oh, my gosh!
(but she wouldn't stop screaming.)
Gosh! Jennie. Jennie.
Jennie, calm down.
Hey, she's crying.
(She even cried.)
She's crying.
(Scared and upset)
- Jennie, calm down. - I said...
(Unluckily, she paired up with Kwang Soo who gets scared easily.)
Hey, stop it!
Stop it!
(Jennie got out of the haunted house with her face covered with tears.)
It's okay.
- I heard I wouldn't be startled. - It's over. Who said that?
- Are you okay? - Yes. I'm okay.
(Scared Jennie looked so cute and made everyone her fan.)
People try to scare me often since then.
- Really? - Yes.
She's just like me.
- She's just like you? - So I...
- You just get scared easily. - That's not true.
- You're just a scaredy-cat. - The noises scare you, right?
(He makes up something they have in common.)
You're just a scaredy-cat. She's not like you.
(Cute Jennie is different from a mere coward.)
- Stop trying to use her fame. - Exactly.
- Anyway, BLACKPINK is here. - That's right.
They're top stars who we can't see often.
(BLACKPINK isn't a group that you can see often.)
Unlike Kwang Soo who we can see very often.
(Here...)
Is he a star too?
(Lee Kwang Soo, a common star, went to the bathroom this morning)
He trespassed someone's house...
- to urinate. - I didn't trespass.
It wasn't trespassing.
- Even international stars... - Really?
(Telling her what happened to Kwang Soo)
- wouldn't do such a rude thing. - Is someone living there?
I mean, he's not even that popular.
I said that's not what happened!
- I had no choice. - He barged in a stranger's house.
(The petty star explodes.)
- I thought that was... - He entered someone else's house...
- to pee. - I thought we would...
- Why would he do that? - Why?
Your trousers look... What's this?
- It looks unusual... - It's a jumpsuit.
- In front of BLACKPINK... - How nice.
(The BLACKPINK members found his jumpsuit fascinating.)
- How nice. - It's a jumpsuit.
- I think it's a jumpsuit. - Do you think it's cool?
- Do you think it's cool? - I guess...
(He'd be happy to show how it looks to see their reactions.)
I like how they reacted.
- Don't do that. Kwang Soo, come on. - I'll take this off.
(I guess they like this look.)
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo, what's wrong with you?
(Taking his vest off)
(As he took off his vest, )
(they reacted enthusiastically.)
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo, what's wrong with you?
Awesome.
(I know I'm cool.)
He's so annoying.
(Showing off his skills for BLACKPINK's reactions)
Kwang Soo, you look cute. That's cool.
(Incomprehensible)
- You look so cool. - Gosh. He's annoying.
- You look cool. - Indeed.
- Gosh. He's so annoying. - Look at him.
(Edgy)
- Posing like a fashion model. - That's cool.
(She's covering her eyes while saying he looks cool.)
This is crazy.
(Proud)
- That was good. - I heard that Lisa...
- will show us the hipster dance. - Really?
(Lisa prepared the hipster dance.)
"The hipster dance"?
- What is the hipster dance? - What is it?
- What's the hipster dance? - You prepared this?
- Oh, gosh. - What's that?
(As the music started playing, )
- What's the hipster dance? - You prepared this?
(she started dancing.)
- Oh, gosh. - What's that?
Is this the hipster dance?
Good. I like her facial expression.
Oh, gosh.
(The city girl is looking for something with a keen eye.)
She found something.
Oh, she's looking at something.
(Taxi!)
- She's trying to get a taxi. - Oh, she's trying to get a taxi?
(The desperate body gestures to get a taxi)
- I like her lines. - She looks...
(This is Lisa's taxi dance that plays with the beat.)
She looks like a doll.
- Awesome. - She dances so skillfully.
She's so cute.
- There's a story behind it. - She has long arms and legs.
(Jasu is also amazed.)
Actually,
Jasu will...
- Jasu as in embroidery. - Jasu.
(So Min's penalty time is back. She'll try the taxi dance.)
Jasu will...
- Jasu as in embroidery. - Jasu.
- She has her own style. - Jasu.
You saw Lisa's dance, right?
(Trying the taxi dance in her own version)
- Come on out and try it. - How did she start?
You walk out to the street and try to get a taxi.
(She has to walk up indifferently and start.)
- Warm up a little like this. - When will the penalty end?
When will the penalty end?
(Dancing to the beat)
(Way to go!)
Good.
Her dance is a bit different from Lisa's.
(The hipster in her 20s looking for a taxi)
I like her facial expression.
(The woman in her 30s who has done it many times before)
(Same dance, different feel)
So Min, look here. There's a taxi here.
Look at the taxi. So Min, look.
Look at the taxi.
(Jasu's taxi dance reeks of alcohol.)
Look far away. Good. Find a taxi.
- That's good. - So Min.
- Now, hail a taxi. - So Min.
(Jasu is focused on reinterpreting the dance, not getting a taxi.)
- Hail a taxi. - So Min, wave at me.
- Wave for a taxi. - Like this.
Here. Se Chan is driving a taxi here.
- Wave for his taxi. - Wave for it.
(Taxi!)
Wave for it.
(For hire)
(Hired)
(Where is your destination?)
(Lisa, who invented the dance, is also satisfied.)
- That's good. - It's here.
- You should get in. - Hop in.
(A taxi comes after hardship.)
- Hop in. - You should get in.
(She gets a taxi thanks to Driver Yang.)
- Get in the taxi. - Here we go.
- Get in the taxi. - Hop in.
- That's good. - That's hilarious.
(Jasu and Driver Yang's performance enchanted everyone.)
- That was good. - Great job.
- That was hilarious. - They did such a good job.
(Awed)
She has good dancing skills.
(Her dancing skills tell us she's experienced.)
- She's a good dancer. - Indeed.
(They feel proud of pulling off the hipster dance.)
We pulled off the hipster dance.
Today,
you must avoid a penalty by rolling the dice.
(They must avoid the penalty by rolling the dice well today.)
It's Save Us From Probability.
(Save Us From Probability)
- I see. - Oh, boy.
Among the 12 of you, 3 people with the least penalty rice cakes...
(The 3 members with the least penalty rice cakes get a prize.)
will receive prizes.
(The 3 members with the most penalty rice cakes get a penalty.)
The bottom three with the most penalty rice cakes...
- will get a penalty. - Three of us?
(Earlier today, before the shoot began...)
- One of them is a normal dice. - I see.
(The members have been given 3 dice.)
This dice has 2 sides of numbers 1, 2, and 6.
(A normal dice, 1, 2, 6 dice, and 0, 10 dice)
1, 2, and 6.
(The rice cakes will be given based on the results.)
This has 3 sides of 0 and 3 sides of 10.
Is it better to have bigger numbers?
(Whoever earns more rice cake is more likely to get the penalty.)
No, bigger numbers will put you at a disadvantage.
Disadvantage?
(It's best if you get lower numbers in a dice.)
You get as many penalty rice cakes as the number on your dice.
I don't want to risk it.
- I will pick the normal dice. - The normal dice.
(Ji Hyo doesn't choose a normal dice.)
- No, I will have the 2nd one. - The 2nd one.
(She chooses 1, 2, 6 dice.)
- Can I try? - Yes.
Two.
(She gets 2 penalty rice cakes.)
You get two penalty rice cakes.
I'm not that adventurous,
(Jong Kook also chooses 1, 2, 6 dice.)
but this is the risk I'm willing to take.
All right.
Gosh.
(He gets 2 penalty rice cakes.)
- This isn't bad. - You get two rice cakes.
Okay.
(Haha thinks hard about 0, 10 dice.)
Hang on. This is...
I guess the tiger moths will pick this dice.
(Lee Kwang Soo, Tiger Moth, I go for 0, 10 dice.)
I pick this one.
- Are you sure? - Definitely.
(Haha was right.)
But it also has 10s.
(He picks the 0, 10 dice with no hesitation.)
I should do this at the beginning...
so I can decide which way I'm going today.
(He easily let fate determine his destiny today.)
Whether I try to win the race...
or sabotage it.
(Kwang Soo tempts his fate with the first dice.)
- No, I practiced it just once. - No.
(He gets 10 penalty rice cakes.)
Why are you laughing so much?
I will show you...
how to sabotage the whole race today.
(He got the most rice cakes even before the race began.)
Gosh.
- I'll pick the dice with three 10s. - Okay.
(Another tiger moth chooses 0, 10 dice.)
I'm hoping to get the good one like how I practiced.
(So Min also gets 10 penalty rice cakes.)
Gosh, hang on. Can I roll the dice again? Just one more time.
(The tiger moths are suffering misfortune from the morning.)
I'll go with it.
(In the end, Haha also chooses 0, 10 dice.)
Why would I hesitate? I can get zero.
That's it!
(He gets zero rice cakes.)
I was too loud.
(Oh, no.)
All right. Gosh, I'm doomed.
(BLACKPINK also rolled the dice.)
This is good, right?
(Rose 1, Lisa 6)
(Jae Suk 2, Jong Kook 2, Ji Hyo 2)
(Suk Jin 10, Kwang Soo 10, So Min 10, Jisoo 10)
(Haha 0, Se Chan 0, Jennie 0)
For your information,
you get extra five rice cakes...
(They also got 5 penalty rice cakes on top of the current counts.)
with the ones you got from rolling the dice.
You're getting five more rice cakes than the number on your dice.
I see.
So you will play one on one during the race,
(They will complete missions in teams.)
but you will play teams for each mission.
And you will get more penalty rice cakes according to the results.
(They'll get more penalty rice cakes based on the results.)
For those with many rice cakes,
we have this rice cake box where you can get rid of your rice cakes.
(There's a rice cake box.)
That's good.
You can put your team sticker on your rice cakes...
(Put the team sticker on rice cakes...)
and put them in the box before the race ends.
(to cancel out the individual rice cake count.)
But the team with the most rice cakes in the box...
(However)
(But the team with the most rice cakes in the box...)
will get the penalty together.
(will get the penalty together at the end of the race.)
- The whole team? - Yes.
I should never team up with Kwang Soo.
(Discard the rice cakes for an individual win, )
- That's not true. - He should never be on my team.
(but it puts the team at a great disadvantage.)
Kwang Soo's team will definitely lose.
He always brings others down with him.
(It'll be tiring to be on the same team as tiger moths.)
- Can I give mine to others? - You can't.
But you can eat your rice cakes.
(They can eat the rice cakes to get rid of them.)
- We can eat them? - You can eat the rice cakes.
I've divided you into teams for the missions.
(It's time to announce the teams.)
The first team is...
Jae Suk, Suk Jin, So Min, and Jennie.
(Not so happy)
(His face brightens as soon as he hears "Jennie".)
We have Jennie.
You just heard So Min's name, right?
(Jae Suk)
- Come here, Jasu. - Jae Suk.
(There's also Jasu.)
Jae Suk, you only heard Suk Jin and So Min, didn't you?
(Nodding)
When he heard Suk Jin and So Min,
(His face darkened after finding out he is on the same team as So Min.)
he seemed quite disappointed. Then he heard Jennie's name.
- Still, we have Jennie. - We have Jennie on our team.
- What matters is we have Jennie. - He almost didn't hear it.
(So they are divided into three teams.)
(Team Jennie, Team Rose and Lisa, Team Jisoo)
- Jennie. - It's been a long time.
What should I do with the rice cakes?
I guess I can eat one rice cake.
I can eat it, right?
(The rice cake has the shape of a watermelon.)
- This is smaller than I thought. - It looks delicious.
(The rice cake is smaller than expected.)
This doesn't taste like the bar rice cake we had before.
(I'll eat them.)
It tastes so good.
(So Min is going somewhere with her rice cake.)
- This is good. - I'm thirsty.
This is really good.
(She forces her cameraman to eat the rice cake.)
(Shaking his head)
- Open it. - No.
Just have a bite. This is really good.
(It's very So Min, where she kills two birds with one stone.)
You can eat this while working. You must be tired.
(That's So Min.)
(I want to eat this with some water.)
Thank you for your hard work.
(They are busy eating up the rice cakes.)
Should we put the rice cakes in the box...
even after eating them?
- No, you can just eat it. - Once you eat it, it's gone.
- I see. - If you still have too many,
(It's gone if they eat it.)
(They can put away the remaining rice cakes inside the box.)
you can put them in the box.
With a sticker on it.
(Understood)
- The team sticker. - With a sticker on it.
So, Jennie...
- All right, Kwang Soo. - I got it!
She got it.
So if you...
(She stops him from talking.)
- All right, Kwang Soo. - I got it.
She says she got it.
(How can you do this to me?)
- I understood. - You're being like this too?
(I understood the rules.)
- How many rice cakes do you have? - This is so funny.
- A lot. - It's so funny.
(In addition to Jae Suk who loves to tease Kwang Soo, )
When Kwang Soo was about to talk, she said, "I got it!"
(it's Jennie who likes to tease Kwang Soo.)
"I understood."
You know what? Someone kept touching my hand.
So I was upset. Suk Jin kept touching my hand.
(Suk Jin touched So Min's hands?)
So I turned around, and it turns out it was the ear.
(Looking)
It kept touching my hand.
- Suk Jin wouldn't do that. - I'm not that kind of person.
(Don't misunderstand.)
- But it was so unpleasant. - You're so...
(She almost misunderstood him due to the ear on his bag.)
- Come on, Jasu. - Why would I touch your hand?
- Gosh, she thinks I'm... - One day,
- on the plane, they... - Stay quiet.
But this is a funny story!
- Stay quiet. - But this is a funny story!
(He cuts him off.)
Do you not want to hear my interesting story?
- That's enough. - Scold him some more Jae Suk!
(Kwang Soo's story is locked up forever.)
- That's just your story. - That's not important.
- We have BLACKPINK here. - Right. You should stop.
Who do you think you are?
You're not that popular anyway.
(He explodes.)
- Stop it. - Right. I'm just a bedwetter.
Why would you brag about your petty popularity?
(Past Asia Prince, Current Bedwetter)
We have global stars here. Will you be modest?
(He shouts with BLACKPINK's support on his back.)
I shouldn't have gone to the restroom.
(I regret it.)
- Guys, this is the first mission. - What is it?
It's called Kill This Turtle Egg Tag.
(Kill This Turtle Egg Tag)
We have one Team Turtle who's supposed protect eggs...
(Team Turtle must protect eggs...)
and two Team Rabbit who are supposed to steal eggs.
(while two Team Rabbit are supposed to steal eggs.)
I see.
In 10 minutes, Team Rabbit...
(Team Rabbit must find as many ping-pong balls as they can.)
should find as many ping-pong balls as you can in this place.
Meanwhile, Team Turtle can rip off the name tags of Team Rabbit.
(Team Turtle can rip off the name tags of Team Rabbit.)
But Team Rabbit can say freeze.
(But Team Rabbit can say freeze.)
And we will randomly pick two Dragon Kings...
(They will pick 2 Dragon Kings randomly.)
who can unfreeze frozen players.
(Dragon Kings can release frozen players.)
Even the Dragon Kings can freeze,
(Even the Dragon Kings can freeze.)
but they need another Dragon King to be unfrozen.
So if both Dragon Kings freeze at the same time, the race is over.
(If both Dragon Kings freeze at the same time, the race is over.)
They can't be unfrozen.
(It's best if someone quick becomes the Dragon King.)
- So they should be fast. - Right.
Team Jennie will be Team Turtle first.
(Round 1, Team Jennie is Team Turtle.)
- Jennie, have a seat. - Okay.
(Team Turtle prepares for Round 1.)
Jasu.
Are your members strong?
Rose and Lisa are strong.
(Rose and Lisa are strong.)
Really?
- They are on the same team. - Jisoo is easy to defeat.
(Jisoo is weak.)
- Really? I should deal with Jisoo. - She's so slim.
- I call dibs on Jisoo. - You can defeat her right away.
(I call dibs on Jisoo.)
Hang on. Then...
- The queen? - No, the Dragon King.
(It's not Queen, it's Dragon King.)
- "Queen"? - Dragon King.
Weren't you there when we heard it?
- The Dragon King... - What's wrong with you?
(I'm getting worried.)
We need two Dragon Kings.
(Additional lesson)
- Can we do that? - We will pick them randomly.
Two Dragon Kings?
So I'll be running. And they will...
(Trying to recap)
- If they freeze me, I should stop. - No.
(Why would the tagger freeze?)
- Isn't that it? - Hang on. I can't do this.
I can't play with him.
- Hey, Jasu. - Who will freeze then?
(He doesn't understand the rules.)
- Am I supposed to say it? - No.
(Team Jennie has a long road ahead.)
I see.
- Very simple. - Yes.
Oh, my goodness.
Everyone, gather here if you're ready.
(Team Rabbit finished changing clothes.)
- We need to pick the Dragon Kings. - Dragon Kings.
I'm number one.
(Haha is number 1.)
- It goes this way. - I'm number five.
We have numbers from 1 to 8.
Jong Kook should be the Dragon King.
(The 2 Dragon Kings can release the frozen players.)
- Right. - I know.
(Who's the first Dragon King?)
(Number 1)
- Me? - Number one.
(It's Haha.)
Darn, it's me.
What?
He's just useless.
(He suddenly speaks the truth from his heart.)
Useless? That's funny.
(Useless)
We need one more.
He's useless.
(Picking the second Dragon King)
Will he be able to unfreeze us?
Three. It's Jong Kook.
(It's Jong Kook.)
- Good. - Yes!
(Useful Jong Kook is the Dragon King!)
How did it happen?
All right. You're given 10 minutes.
- The race starts. - Let's go.
The race starts.
Let's go.
Come here. Follow me.
(Team Rabbit must find as many ping-pong balls as possible.)
- Can we go around together? - Come here.
Turtles will be here soon.
- There they are. - There are a lot of rabbits.
(Team Turtle must eliminate Team Rabbit as fast as possible.)
They are coming. The turtles are coming.
- Let's go. - They're up there.
(Turtles are running.)
- I'm going to catch the rabbits. - I see a lot of rabbits.
(Eager)
(Cornering rabbits)
- There they are! - Look at the rabbits.
I'll catch Rabbit Jisoo.
I'm going to catch the rabbit.
(Rushing to Rabbit Jisoo)
(Frightened)
(Jumping)
What do I do? I think my hair stands out too much.
There's Rabbit Rose.
(The novice turtle lets everyone know her location.)
She's over there!
I'm so tired. I can't go up there.
(Rabbit Lisa is already tired.)
There's Rabbit Lisa.
(Rushing to Rabbit Lisa.)
Jae Suk, she's here.
(However...)
Hang on. Are we going up a hill?
(Exhausted)
Turtles are coming.
(Rabbit Jisoo evaded Jennie who got tired easily.)
(Right at the moment!)
(Suk Jin's surprise attack)
Freeze.
What? Who's out then?
(Who's out when she freezes?)
Am I frozen now?
(He doesn't understand the rules.)
(Laughing)
No. The Dragon King should come to unfreeze me.
(She kindly repeats the rule to Suk Jin again.)
If she freezes, she has to stay still here.
(Jennie chimes in.)
Freeze.
(Arrogant rabbit?)
Then are we frozen too?
(He still doesn't understand.)
No. We should just go.
- I can move, right? - Yes, you can.
(Not sure)
My gosh.
(Rabbit Jisoo is frozen until the Dragon King comes.)
That's quite useful.
I'm frozen.
She wants to be unfrozen? Where is she?
(Dragon King Jong Kook discovers Jisoo.)
I give up. I want to give up.
(Jennie gives up.)
(At that moment...)
(She sees Jong Kook running to Jisoo.)
He's going to unfreeze Jisoo!
Jong Kook.
(Before Jennie comes...)
- Unfreeze me. - Are you frozen?
Unfreeze me.
(Jong Kook releases Rabbit Jisoo.)
She's weak. Right.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
(She is out of her breath.)
I have no energy to chase them.
(I have no energy to chase them.)
(She gives up again.)
I can't do this.
I'm in trouble.
(Rabbit Ji Hyo is looking for ping-pong balls.)
How far should I go?
(At the moment!)
(A surprise attack)
How far should I go?
Gosh, Jennie.
(She rips off Ji Hyo's name tag immediately.)
I ripped it off.
(She's so excited.)
- My gosh. - I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
When did you come?
I sneaked up on you.
(Ji Hyo was a lucky break for tired Jennie.)
Gosh, she didn't even make a noise.
(Amazing!)
(Exhausted)
I can't do this.
Hey, Lisa.
(Jae Suk spots Rabbit Lisa.)
(Chasing fiercely)
(She's caught.)
Hey, Lisa.
(Why isn't she freezing?)
Lisa, hold on.
She's super strong.
(Startled)
Suk Jin! Gosh, she's strong.
(She decides to stall them as they're weak.)
Here. Rip her name tag off.
- She must be the queen. - Eliminate her.
(Irrelevant)
(She starts to hold out.)
What...
Rip her name tag off.
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin both try their best.)
- What... - Hold on.
- She's too strong. - She's really strong.
(Astonished)
(Lisa holds out for a few more minutes...)
(before she's eliminated.)
- Sorry, Lisa. - We're sorry.
(Lisa with superhuman strength)
- Let's go. - Sorry, Lisa.
The race is over.
(Round 1 ends.)
You can freeze only once.
(Round 2 begins with Rose and Lisa as taggers.)
- So as fast as possible... - Who?
We should go out and get them to freeze.
(Discussing their strategy reflecting on their experience)
Can we rip the name tags off?
- Yes, but be careful. - Why...
- don't we... - It's so itchy for some reason.
- Can we rip the name tags off? - Yes, but be careful.
(I...)
It's so itchy for some reason.
- Let me see. - I'll go after them quickly.
- From the get-go... - We...
From the get-go,
- we should go after them. - Yes, that's better.
- I wanted to say... - Just don't.
I've been opening my mouth...
for about 15 times just to say this as well.
I tried to talk, but you said your skin was itchy.
Then you said something in English.
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
I guess you have that effect on people.
(Interesting)
- Why's that? - We made eye contact,
(Kwang Soo's shouts can't reach other people.)
- and you said your skin was itchy. - Sorry about that.
- We should chase after them fast. - So what now?
(While Team Turtle plan their strategy, )
- Let's get them to freeze. - Exactly.
- As fast as possible. - Sure.
We'll see who the Dragon Kings are.
(Team Rabbit chooses the Dragon Kings.)
- Don't let it be four. - I'd like to be the Dragon King.
- Number 2. It's Jae Suk. - Nice, it's 2.
(Jae Suk becomes a Dragon King.)
- Number two. - It's Jae Suk.
- It was 2. - It's number 6 this time.
(The second Dragon King is...)
- Number six. - It's you.
(Ji Hyo becomes a Dragon King.)
- Me? - Nice, Ji Hyo.
- This is good for us. - You'll be good at this.
(They've chosen their Dragon Kings.)
- Just keep running. - I'm glad.
I should've been the Dragon King.
(Disappointed)
If you were, you'd die on the spot.
(Speaking nonsense)
- You'd die. - Will he be burned to death?
- He'll just drop dead. - You don't know what that means.
- He doesn't know. - He said Suk Jin will be burned.
Of course, I know what he meant!
You're just as mean, you know.
So many people cross the line with me now.
I didn't mean that he'll be burned.
(That doesn't mean he'll burn.)
Well, I didn't...
(It was a slip of the tongue.)
It's the same as starving to death.
Of course, of a stomachache.
(The rabbits who cannot die on the spot...)
Has it already begun?
(go to find the ping-pong balls.)
- We need to get running. - Yes, let's.
- Yell when you eliminate someone. - Got it.
(Team Turtle departs as well.)
Where's their base?
Where do they start the race?
(Right here.)
(She makes a run for it.)
(Jong Kook starts chasing after So Min.)
(She runs toward the back of the van.)
(Startled)
My gosh!
(Dragon King Jae Suk is already there hiding.)
What the...
(At that moment, )
(Jong Kook followed So Min here.)
What the...
(Dragon King Jae Suk and Rabbit So Min)
- Freeze. - Freeze.
Over here. I got two of them.
He followed you here!
(So Min...)
Two of them are frozen here.
(I'm sorry, Dragon King.)
I can't afford to be frozen.
(I'm a Dragon King.)
Why did you do it then?
(Team Rabbit faces a crisis from the beginning.)
Why on earth did you come here?
I was just as startled to see you.
I didn't know you were here.
- Where... - I got two over there.
(Jong Kook suggests they watch them in case a Dragon King comes.)
Lisa, one should keep an eye on them.
- I'll be right on it! - Let's go.
(Lisa heads over to keep an eye on them.)
They probably went up the hill.
(The others chase after the other rabbits.)
Hello.
(I'm here to watch you.)
- Hi. - Goodness, Lisa.
(Asking the other Dragon King for help)
Are you guys chilling here?
Hello, guys. Hi.
(But...)
(she's chilling with the puppies instead of watching them.)
Hi, there.
Lisa, what are you up to?
What?
(Flustered)
I was asked to keep an eye on them, so here I am.
Focus!
(She switches on to the meerkat mode.)
I'd love to find at least one ball.
(She takes a bite out of her rice cake.)
(Jennie's monodrama, "SOLO")
Would there be a ball up here?
Can we come out this far?
Over there.
(Startled)
(Jennie's monodrama, "SOLO", production stops.)
Can you please crunch down as though I'm not here?
(Meanwhile, Rose spots someone.)
Over there.
(He instinctively runs.)
Get him!
(Kwang Soo helps with the rabbit hunt.)
Jong Kook!
Get him!
(Jong Kook blocks him.)
(He runs as fast as he can, but...)
- Get him! - Freeze.
- There. - Freeze.
(Now, Se Chan is frozen too.)
Gosh.
Can you tell me at least where one is?
(Jennie's monodrama resumes.)
I just can't find any ping-pong balls.
(She's about to cry.)
(Hold on!)
Is that it? Is that a ping-pong ball?
(Did she finally find her first ping-pong ball?)
A ping-pong ball...
My gosh, it's Jong Kook!
(The tiger hunts the rabbit.)
It's Jong Kook!
(Charging toward his prey)
Okay, fine. Freeze!
(You're too scary.)
(She was scared to death.)
I've never been more scared in my life.
We got everyone up here.
(Team Turtle already made 4 people freeze on the spot.)
(Meanwhile, Rose heads somewhere.)
(Glancing around)
Isn't he the Dragon King?
(Where is Rose headed?)
(The table of rice cakes bags)
(What is she up to?)
(She pulls out a rice cake from her case.)
(Detective Yang records the scene of the crime.)
What are you doing?
(Video evidence)
Rose was caught red-handed!
This will disrupt your whole team.
(Se Chan's camera)
I was just too hungry, that's all.
(Changing her attitude)
Okay, fine. I'll keep your secret.
(Rose was caught red-handed by Detective Yang.)
I can't trust you though.
I won't tell anyone.
I'm watching Se Chan!
(Changing her plan)
- You... - I'm watching Se Chan!
(Her plan is to pretend to watch him so that they won't suspect her.)
Rose, stay there.
Sure thing.
(Jong Kook trusts Rose and passes by.)
Let's go.
(She waits for the right time to discard her rice cake.)
(His 2nd attempt at collecting evidence)
Okay, I'll keep your secret.
(He promises to keep it a secret.)
I won't take out my phone again. I'll keep your secret.
You have to help me once later on though.
If you don't, I'll show people this.
Anyway, go ahead. It'll be our secret.
(The deal is closed.)
Go ahead. Now's the time.
(After making the deal, )
(she discards her rice cake.)
Dragon King!
(Jennie's monodrama: She's currently frozen.)
The Dragon King must not be coming.
(Sobbing)
(Dragon King Ji Hyo appears as she heard Jennie's cry.)
Jennie.
Ji Hyo!
Let's go.
(Jennie is unfrozen.)
(She grabs the ping-pong ball in front of her.)
I see one.
- Jong Kook, it's a rabbit. - Right.
(Jennie is running as fast as she can.)
(She locks eyes with the tiger.)
- Wait. - No!
(Help a rabbit!)
I can't run away. Please!
(Ripped off)
(Rabbit Jennie is eliminated.)
10 seconds! 10, 9...
- I was held by a concrete block. - 8, 7...
(Shivering)
(Round 2 ends.)
The race is over.
Rose?
Don't you have something to say to me?
Se Chan!
(He promised to keep her secret...)
- All right. - No, Se Chan!
(and tries to reveal it.)
- Okay. - What is it?
- Don't! - I hear you.
(Rose's teammates swarm in.)
- Se Chan, please. - What is it?
You see, I farted by mistake.
- What... - You see, I farted by mistake.
(She tries to cover up what she has done.)
You don't have to tell us those things.
- Don't. - Se Chan was going to tell!
Don't worry. You don't have to say that.
- Rose... - You jerk!
(Acting enthusiastically while lying about a fart)
- I farted and... - Se Chan!
It's okay.
As if you don't fart!
(Her adult fans protest.)
How dare you.
- You jerk. - It's okay, Rose.
(That was good, Rose.)
- You... - It's okay.
(Rose's fan club)
- You must've heard wrong. - I was so nervous.
- Can you believe it? - It was probably you who farted.
(She succeeds in hiding the fact that she discarded her rice cake.)
Okay, fine. I hear you, Rose.
(The result of the first mission)
The first round is over,
and the team who secured the most number of eggs won.
(The team that lost the least amount of turtle eggs is placed 1st.)
- Right. - Turtle eggs.
A total of nine.
(Team Jennie lost 9 turtle eggs.)
- Us? - You had nine eggs stolen.
- They were stolen? - Yes.
(They did well with Suk Jin on the team.)
Team Jisoo...
(Team Jisoo lost 8 turtle eggs.)
- You had eight stolen. - We must be in first place.
(We'll place 1st.)
Jong Kook's team must be in last place.
- That's right. - They lost a lot.
(Team Rose and Lisa lost 23 turtle eggs.)
Your team lost 23 eggs.
It's because they were all together.
(We're at the bottom.)
You lost 23 eggs, so you must roll the dice twice.
(None, once, and twice)
You only have to roll it once...
while the winning team doesn't have to.
(The number they roll will be the number of rice cakes they gain.)
(They make a big fuss.)
(They celebrate in front of those who lost.)
(Let's dance too!)
Why are you dancing when we lost?
- Don't copy us. - From now on...
(Losing the game can't hold back Rose and Lisa.)
Let's do it too.
(Humming)
Hold on a second.
Did you hear what Suk Jin was humming?
(The melody was old and too simple.)
So Min seemed like an obedient daughter just now.
- She seemed so sweet. - Didn't she?
(Jasu's father and daughter trip with music)
Like an obedient daughter.
- I just did it for him. - She wanted to do it, so...
So your team must roll one of the three dices.
(Team Rose and Lisa will pick 1 out of 3 dice and roll it twice.)
The one with 1 to 6, the one with 1, 2, and 6,
or the one with 0 and 10.
(They must share as many rice cakes as the number of dice.)
- 0 and 10. - Of course.
- Right. - 0 and 10!
(Recommending 0, 10 dice)
0 and 10? Isn't that...
Okay, let's go for it. Even though we roll a 10,
it's to be divided anyway.
(They choose the 0, 10 dice and aims for 0.)
If we roll a zero twice, we'll be in the lead.
- Okay. - Let's do this.
(Rose rolls the first dice.)
- It's too high. - Nice one.
(How many rice cakes will be added to their pile?)
This will be fun.
- Nice! - Okay!
(We rolled a 0!)
- Nicely done. - All right.
- Good one. - No way.
(Team Rose and Lisa has a happy occasion thanks to the bold bet.)
They rolled a zero.
I can't believe they rolled a zero.
We're starting off with a clean state now.
(But they have to roll it once again.)
Now, we're at the starting line with them.
So would we need to gamble again?
(We already have a 0.)
- Right. - Then the one with 1, 2, and 6.
It's better to play it safe.
(They choose the 1, 2, 6 dice for the 2nd one.)
- But Jong Kook... - Where's the fun in that?
- It's better to gamble. - Right.
(Tossing the 0, 10 dice to Kwang Soo)
Kwang Soo has good luck today.
- But if he rolls a 10... - He rolled it!
- No, this isn't it. - He rolled it!
(Kwang Soo threw the 0, 10 dice?)
- He rolled it. - He rolled it!
(Flustered)
- No, this isn't it. - He rolled it!
Nice!
- This isn't it. - Nice!
- Nice! - This isn't it.
(Are they getting 10 more rice cakes because of Kwang Soo?)
(Insisting)
- We didn't decide on it. - You rolled it.
- I was only checking. - You rolled it.
(Kwang Soo tries to get out of it.)
- But you rolled it. - No!
- You rolled it. - Come on.
- He's right. - You rolled it.
Are you being a snob?
- Exactly. - You rolled it.
Isn't this special treatment?
- That's right. - Are you going to be biased?
- Exactly. - Nicely said.
I didn't think much of it when I threw the dice.
(Feeling victimized)
Jisoo, did he roll the dice or not?
(Jisoo's decision)
- Of course, he did. - Her voice flipped just now.
(He totally rolled it.)
"Isn't this special treatment?"
She said you rolled the dice.
(As Jisoo who also judges the stars fairly, )
- I knew it. - You take four.
(Team Rose and Lisa gets 10 additional rice cakes.)
I knew it.
This happens when you team up with Kwang Soo.
(The bathroom superstar picked the wrong day.)
She said you rolled it.
- There he is. - Where?
(Jae Suk sees someone and moves.)
We're sorry about earlier.
We're sorry.
(Earlier...)
Kwang Soo startled you, didn't he?
I was... It's just...
(The owner of the house appeared through the window.)
- Sorry about that. - I didn't know you lived here.
- We're sorry. - I'm so sorry.
Unbelievable.
(Apologizing together to the owner who let us use the lawn)
What a fun scene to see in a weekend variety show.
(An interesting scene that a weekend filming created)
- It's a first for me. - Unbelievable.
A surprise visit by a celebrity.
- He won a date with a celebrity. - A wrong trip to the bathroom...
(Lee Kwang Soo, the bathroom star, regretting going to the bathroom)
- We'll go with the 0 and 10. - 10.
(Team Jennie also chooses the 0, 10 dice.)
- It's only 10 anyway. - Let's go.
(Getting herself together)
Let's go. Jennie, let's do this.
- Jennie. - I can roll a zero.
(How many rice cakes will they end up taking?)
Okay, okay.
- Okay, okay. - Let's see.
- Okay. - Yes!
(0 penalty rice cakes)
(Great)
Okay.
(Objection)
- It hit the sketchpad over there. - No.
- Haha! - I get it.
(Result)
So I'll give 10 of them only to this team.
(Team Rose and Lisa gets 10 penalty rice cakes.)
We didn't have to get them.
- Shall we play rock-paper-scissors? - In my opinion...
(Sharing)
You and I should have 3 each and give 2 to each girl.
- Wait. - Here. Take them.
- I can have them, - Give them to me now.
but do you think they'll stay with me?
(It seems like they'll go into the rice cake box right away.)
(Reaching the limit of his patience)
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Hey!
- Give them to the girls! - Slapped with a rice cake.
- He was slapped with a rice cake. - Where did it go?
Gosh, Lisa said...
he was slapped with a rice cake.
- Hey, you jerk. - Slapped with a rice cake?
(Summarizing the situation with accurate words)
- Lisa... - Her Korean is really good now.
(Lisa's Korean skill, five stars)
- She's good. - Slapped with a rice cake.
She even knows what being slapped with a rice cake means.
Now let's move on to the second mission.
(What's the second mission with the members of BLACKPINK?)
- Okay. - Let's go.
(Current rice cakes, Team Jennie, Team Rose and Lisa, and Team Jisoo)
Lisa, do you want to eat rice cakes?
(Preparation time before the second mission)
Gosh, my legs hurt.
- Are we still on the same team? - My legs. It's done.
(Team Jisoo trusts the teammates the most.)
- The green one. - I feel relieved.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - I heard that...
(Just now...)
the other team members are betraying each other so much.
(The other team members betray each other a lot.)
- They are, right? - No one is more honest than us.
- You're all honest, right? - Hey.
(One person can't smile to hear Jisoo's innocent question.)
(30 minutes ago)
(While everyone is looking for ping-pong balls, )
(Se Chan was just focusing on discarding his rice cakes.)
Wait. I want to give you one more.
(He betrayed his team not once, but twice.)
Unfreeze me!
Then we have a chance of winning.
(Looking far away as he's sorry)
The second mission is...
(The second mission will start.)
about suppressing your instinct as much as possible.
It's called Instinctively Ddu-du Ddu-du.
(The second mission, Instinctively Ddu-du Ddu-du)
- What's that? - Ddu-du Ddu-du.
- Ddu-du Ddu-du - Ddu-du Ddu-du.
It's a device that detects a change of emotion...
(It analyzes the brainwave from the wearer's frontal lobe...)
- using brainwaves. - Brainwaves?
(and expresses his or her mental state through the ears.)
When you're calm, the ears droop and don't move.
(The ears will be still or droop when he or she is calm.)
but if you get nervous, excited,
(The ears will move if the wearer is nervous or excited.)
or interested, they're pricked up.
Wow, it's incredible.
If you feel extremely excited,
the ears keep moving nonstop.
(You can tell the wearer's mind by the moving ears.)
They move like crazy?
- That sounds fun. - Goodness.
(Already worried)
I can't believe there's something like that.
A member of each team will join,
(1 member of each team will play with the cat ears.)
and they will be asked questions for 100 seconds in turn.
(They'll take turns to answer questions for 100 seconds.)
The two will ask as many questions as they want,
and all the other has to do is answer.
(We measure the time the ears have moved during 100 seconds, )
We'll measure the time when the ears are pricked up,
(and the team with the least total length of time wins.)
and the team with the longest time will lose the game.
(They have to stay calm so the ears move as little as possible.)
- My heart is pounding already. - Okay.
(List of matches)
Let me tell you who will fight with whom.
The first match will be...
among So Min, Rose, and Se Chan.
- Okay. - Okay.
Rose.
- Bang, bang. - Then the second match will be...
(The lineup of Round 1 is already looking good.)
The first round will be fierce already.
Wow, it's fascinating.
(This isn't product placement.)
- Do they really move? - Wow.
- Are they moving? - They really move.
Oh, they're moving.
(The ears reading brainwaves make the idol singers nervous.)
They're moving.
Are you extremely nervous?
(Pricking)
- Gosh, how did you make them move? - What is it?
What did you do?
Do they move if I think of strange things?
(The ears move more if you're excited, interested, or focused.)
- He must be thinking hard. - What are you thinking?
(He gets excited instantly.)
Hey.
- I'm scared of that. - Why are you blushing?
(He feels naked.)
- If you keep thinking about... - Why did his face turn red?
- What are you thinking now? - Why is Se Chan's face red now?
(Se Chan, what are you thinking about?)
Try to hold my hand.
(Your hand?)
(Se Chan and So Min hold each other's hands.)
(Twitching)
(It responds as soon as he holds her hand.)
Everything will get caught.
(Embarrassed)
- So funny. Come here. - There are things I want to hide.
(Do you get nervous when you hold my hand?)
Come here and hold my hand.
(He wants to run away.)
(He smiles and his ears get busy when he holds her hand.)
A lot of your gums are showing today.
I hate it because it shows everything.
(He blushes as he's ashamed.)
Is only mine moving like this?
(Jennie, the next contender, is already worried.)
All right, So Min goes first.
(So Min will go first.)
- The other two can ask questions. - Okay.
(Se Chan and Rose can ask her anything for 100 seconds.)
- It's 100 seconds. - Okay.
(What questions will she ask to stir So Min?)
Ready.
Go.
(100 seconds start.)
Honestly, when you were practicing earlier,
you thought you can replace one of the BLACKPINK members, right?
No.
(Twitching)
(So Min's brainwave fluctuates as soon as she says no.)
I guess she did.
- It moved like this. - Like this.
(It twitched immediately.)
No, I didn't think so. It's true.
(She says no, but...)
- It twitched. - It twitched.
(She couldn't hide her brainwave.)
It moved.
(Jasu, the 5th member, briefly dreamed of becoming a regular one?)
You had that in mind? Gosh.
- So Min, now... - Do you want to go on a blind date?
- I do. - I know a nice guy.
(Please introduce him to me.)
(The degree of the excitement is level 2.)
I really want to. Let me do that.
(She opens her ears as soon as she hears it.)
Gosh, the ears are pricked up so high.
I mean it.
- They're pricked up so high. - Please.
(You're not just saying it, right?)
- I want to do that so much. - Gosh,
if you go on a blind date in groups wearing this,
(Recommending this game for those in their 20s on blind dates)
- your feelings will be revealed. - It signals your emotions.
(A guide to women for inexperienced men such as Jae Suk and Se Chan)
- It absolutely signals them. - It does.
Let's not ask any weird questions.
So Min, you fancy him a lot, right?
(Rose asked this question even without a warning.)
I don't fancy him.
(Twitching, twitching)
(She fails to hide her brainwave again.)
(A romantic drama unexpectedly starts to air.)
- Look at that. - They keep moving.
- They move continuously. - Hey.
- They move slightly. - They twitched.
(The onlookers are even more excited.)
Let me ask a question.
Se Chan, now is the time.
Hey, do you fancy me?
- No, I don't. - What?
(What's going on between them?)
What's going on?
(So Min's ears responded cluelessly to Se Chan's daring question.)
Will it be okay?
(The romance lovers fulfill their wishes today.)
- What's going on? - What is going on?
- Look. - They're moving like crazy.
(Her pride is hurt.)
Moving like crazy.
(So Min)
They really are.
What are you going to do this evening?
(Encouraged)
(He gets confident...)
(and asks her masculinely.)
Are you available?
I'll be at home.
- She wants to stay home, and why... - Why are yours...
(She just said she'd stay home, )
I'll be at home.
(and he got himself excited.)
- Why are yours moving? - Quiet.
(The magic spell, )
- Why yours? - Hey.
("I'll stay home," invites Se Chan to his imagination.)
- You're... - Why are your ears moving?
- You're a jerk. - No.
(What's the matter with my ears?)
- Why are you excited? - She'll be at home. What about it?
- She'll be home. Why do they move? - Why did your ears move?
(We can't even imagine what goes on in his imagination.)
- What's wrong with staying home? - Ask questions away.
(They need to shake her up more as there isn't much time.)
- Se Chan, ask away. - 20 seconds left.
- So Min. - Yes?
Can I go to your house...
to eat ramyeon with you this evening?
(He daringly asked if he could visit her place even if he's embarrassed.)
No.
(Pricked up)
You're ridiculous.
(So Min's ears allowed it again.)
- No. - You're ridiculous.
My goodness.
(The love affairs of the friends of the same age are getting serious.)
You're ridiculous.
(It's a battle of pride now.)
- The ears are moving. - You have to check if they move.
- The ears are moving. - The ears are pricked up.
(The 100 seconds end.)
Mine didn't move.
Out of 100 seconds,
they moved for 52 seconds.
(So Min's ears moved for 52 seconds.)
- Did they really move? - Next, please.
(It's time to ask Rose.)
They got pricked up so high.
- Next up is Rose. - Let's go!
Ready. Go.
Rose, out of the BLACKPINK members,
you think you're the prettiest, don't you?
Of course.
(Rose's ears are completely calm.)
Oh, she means it.
- They don't move at all. - She meant it.
(Rose thinks she's the prettiest in BLACKPINK.)
- They don't move. - She meant it.
(Even if the other members are glaring, )
Hey, Rose.
She meant it.
(Rose keeps calm.)
- What do you think about Se Chan? - I think...
(What will Rose think about Se Chan?)
What do you think about Se Chan?
I think...
he has a lot of teeth.
(A forced compliment)
I've never heard anything like that.
I have a lot of teeth?
(He's also rich with teeth.)
- Teeth? - Don't we have the same number?
Look at his ears.
Everyone has the same number of teeth.
(Don't all humans have the same number of teeth?)
His ears are drooping.
The number of our teeth is the same.
- Do you like rich people? - Rich people?
Well, yes, not bad.
Look. They're moving a lot.
Kwang... What's wrong with my ears? What's wrong?
What's wrong with my ears? What's wrong?
I don't have that many teeth!
(He gets excited after she said she likes rich people.)
I don't!
Goodness. It has an error.
- It's crazy. - Don't get excited.
(It's not the same "rich"!)
- They're moving like crazy. - It has an error.
(No matter how many times he tells himself, )
- I need to calm down. - Don't get excited.
(he can't hide his expectations.)
- Take a deep breath. - Don't be excited.
- It's okay now. - Gosh.
What's the matter?
(He barely gets calm.)
Let's continue.
Are you swayed by what Rose just said?
(Wake up, Se Chan.)
Do you think Kwang Soo is good-looking?
(Managing to ask)
Well, he is good-looking.
- They started to move. - Stay still!
(The ears show that she's lying.)
- Idol... - Stay still. Wait. Sit.
- They moved a lot. - They were saying no.
(Her brainwave strongly disagrees with "Kwang Soo is good-looking.")
- They moved a lot. - You should've rather said no.
Why are your ears pricked up?
(Rose's time ends with Kwang Soo's false hope.)
- I can't attack her. - Right. Don't do that.
It's 37 seconds.
(Rose's ears moved for 37 seconds.)
- What? It's too short. - 37 seconds.
- It's okay. - Se Chan.
(Now it's time to ask Se Chan.)
Se Chan is in big trouble.
- It's Se Chan. He'll be almost... - Se Chan.
(Se Chan's ears will shake for a single question.)
I think mine may explode.
Ready. Ask him questions.
(How will he do during his turn?)
Go.
What time did you wake up this morning?
What?
(His brainwave reacts right away to a simple English question.)
They're moving. They started to move.
What did she say?
What did you say?
(He suddenly became polite.)
Honestly, you really want to go to her place to eat ramyeon, right?
No.
(Twitching)
(Se Chan is...)
(really planning to go there to eat ramyeon tonight.)
(They started this game just for fun, )
(but the ears move just at the right moment every time.)
(An unexpected romance...)
(of a guy with many teeth on a Sunday evening)
Hey.
- Pull yourself together. - Hey.
- My brains. - Hey.
- My brains. Pull yourself together. - Hey.
(It's so interesting!)
Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - It's fun as long as it's not me.
(So Min's turn to ask a question)
So Min, make a move.
(So Min beckons him instead of asking a question.)
Give me your hands.
(Trying to make a decisive move)
Is she touching him?
(Holding his hands tight)
His feelings are real!
(Pricked up)
(He's extremely excited.)
His feelings are real!
(The sirens are wailing.)
Please save me.
(Se Chan gives way.)
(He sends an SOS with his brainwave.)
(You lost, Se Chan.)
(So Min who seized a chance to win...)
(keeps pretending to be fatally attractive.)
My goodness.
- Please save me. - They're moving like crazy.
- Goodness. - Like crazy.
(A warm touch...)
(overloads Se Chan's brain.)
- Hey, what was that? - Gosh.
I don't know. I think the device is malfunctioning.
(He blames the machine as he's embarrassed.)
- Rose, you hold his hands too. - What?
- Why don't you hold his hands? - Try it.
(Se Chan reacted instantly to So Min's hand.)
- I don't think they'll move. - Yes, they will.
They're not moving. There is only one person in his heart.
(It's not moving for Rose's hands?)
So Min, you should try holding his hands again.
(However...)
- So Min, you should do it. - They're moving.
- So Min, you should do it. - Why are...
- Why are my ears moving? - Rose, why are your ears moving?
Tell your ears to stay still!
(Rose's heart is fluttering?)
- Stay still! - Tell them to stop.
- She likes men with a lot of teeth. - There's no way.
- She likes men with a lot of teeth. - She's getting more excited.
Hey! Stop lying.
You like him?
(Rose, did you...)
- Rose. - No. I don't.
(This teen drama had a strong twist.)
- No, So Min. It's not true. - Rose.
- What's with Rose? - He's yours.
She said I'm hers.
- This love triangle is fun. - Don't misunderstand it.
Ask a question.
(Amidst the love triangle, they start going after Se Chan again.)
Do you really like me?
(Yes.)
Hey, you.
Do you really like me?
(Se Chan's brain waves shyly surrender to the carpet bombing.)
Hey, you.
(His pride is hurt.)
- This is amazing. - Why can't you just tell her?
Hey.
(He's rich in brain waves.)
- Just tell her. - Seriously.
This is driving me crazy. What's wrong with this?
(The drama ends with Se Chan's defeat.)
- He really likes her. - What is with this thing?
You hid your true feelings all this time, didn't you?
(However...)
- This is... - He really likes her.
Everyone is having fun, but he isn't.
Don't worry about me.
(Kwang Soo is really nervous.)
- Continue playing the game. - I feel bad for him.
What's wrong with you?
(Meanwhile, Jennie will also go up next against Kwang Soo.)
Jennie's ears are moving a lot.
(The ears are moving a lot even before the game.)
- What should we do about this? - Jennie's ears can't stop moving.
- I can't sit next to her. - What are you thinking, Jennie?
- They keep... - What are you thinking about?
(She emits brain waves...)
- What are you thinking? - I was practicing,
(to every question that wasn't meant for her.)
but my ears are out of control.
What should I do?
(Se Chan's session is over.)
It's over.
- How long did mine move for? - 58 seconds.
(Se Chan's ears moved for 58 seconds.)
- My gosh. - Goodness.
You can't hide anything with these.
- The next group will come up. - Jennie. Hey, come on!
(Round 1 is over, and it's now Round 2.)
I can do it!
No cheating!
(It's now Jisoo, Jennie, and Kwang Soo's turn.)
I think Kwang Soo is in trouble.
Why is he up against these two?
- Kwang Soo's ears will move a lot. - He's in trouble.
You'll go after Jennie first.
(Jennie's trying to calm herself down.)
- Have my ears gone down? - They're going down... Oh, my.
(Her ears move immediately.)
You can't control these.
- You can't. - Your ears are standing up.
(They ask questions as soon as she calms down.)
- Right now. - She's calm now.
- Start. - She's calm.
You froze earlier because you didn't want to run, right?
Yes.
(Her face is calm, but her ears aren't.)
- Because it was hot, right? - They're very accurate.
Yes, very.
When So Min danced earlier, it was a bit of an eyesore, right?
(What does Jennie think about BLACKPINK's Jasu?)
No.
(It's definitely a lie.)
- What's wrong with them? - Why are they moving so much?
They're moving a lot.
- They're moving a lot, Jennie. - What's with her?
I think I've gone crazy.
Who has the messiest room?
Lisa.
(She doesn't think about it before saying Lisa's name.)
Jennie tells us everything.
(She gets insulted while listening.)
- She's telling us everything. - She is.
- The game is important too, but... - Jennie...
(They're impressed...)
(how Jennie answers to every question they ask.)
I thought she wouldn't be able to answer.
Jennie tells us everything.
- What is this? - How long is her turn?
Do you think you're the prettiest in BLACKPINK?
(Do you...)
(How pretty does Jennie think she is among the members?)
Do you think you're the prettiest in BLACKPINK?
- Do you think you're the prettiest? - His mouth went up.
Yes.
(Her ears calm down as if she's telling the truth.)
They're not moving.
(No, they didn't.)
Do your ears even go down?
There's someone prettier.
(Her ears start to move again.)
There's someone she thinks is prettier.
- This is chaos. - It is.
They can't calm down.
(What's wrong with them?)
What's wrong with them?
(Her ears moved for 50 seconds when they didn't ask anything.)
- Why do they keep moving? - It's incredible.
What's up with Jennie?
I must be going crazy.
Shouldn't she calm down before we can ask her questions?
- Ask her questions. - Hey, Jennie.
Calm down.
- What are you thinking about? - I'm thinking about you.
(You're thinking about me?)
You're not the one on the spot. Ask her questions.
(Lost focus)
Why are your ears moving?
Don't try to collect your thoughts.
(Kwang Soo forgets it's a game and starts to get excited.)
- Why is she thinking about me? - Hey. Calm down.
(I need to calm down.)
- Calm down. - He froze in his spot.
He froze when she said she was thinking about him.
(The brain wave game seduces many people.)
Calm down.
Go after her.
Is there a guy you're interested in right now?
(He resumes his question.)
- Right here. - You.
Kwang Soo?
(Me?)
My gosh, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo?
(Both his ears perk up.)
My gosh, Kwang Soo. Don't ask questions like that.
(Jennie likes me?)
- It's for his benefit. Stop it. - This is good.
(Satisfaction with the answer)
- This was good for us. - I'm in trouble.
Jennie's turn is over.
(Jennie's time is up.)
- Yes! But wasn't I too excited? - They moved for 82 seconds.
(Jennie's ears moved for 82 seconds.)
- What? - 82 seconds? Nobody can beat that.
82 seconds?
(It's the worst record.)
I'm sorry.
I was too excited.
- I'll do a good job from now. - Kwang Soo is next.
- Okay. - Who will go next?
- Kwang Soo? - Kwang Soo? Okay, then.
(It's time to ask Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo.
Is Sun Bin doing well?
(Kwang Soo's brainwaves begin fluctuating at the strong question.)
- They're moving. - She's good.
- She's good. Look at her face. - Keep going.
(Nodding)
Is Sun Bin pretty or is Jisoo pretty?
(He refuses to answer.)
(Brain, please pull yourself together.)
- Jisoo, hold his hands. - They each have separate charms.
- Make physical contact. - They each have separate charms.
They each have separate charms.
He didn't answer it out loud, but the answer crossed his head.
(The brain answered before he can answer with his mouth.)
They each have separate charms.
(He emphasizes on how everyone has different charms.)
- Not answering is weirder. - She's good.
Who's the prettiest member of BLACKPINK?
(His ears start moving at the thought of BLACKPINK.)
I...
(What is Kwang Soo's answer?)
Personally, I like Rose.
(She's happy.)
He's telling the truth.
Jennie. Why...
(I see.)
Jennie. Why are your ears moving suddenly?
I'm sorry. It's just my personal...
(Is Jennie getting jealous?)
You asked me the question, so I had to answer.
(How could you say that in front of us?)
Jennie. Hey, Jennie.
All of a sudden... Jennie.
(Kwang Soo is doing well.)
Why are your ears moving all of a sudden?
Do you keep watching the video of my acrostic poem for you?
(Do you remember the acrostic poem Jennie made for Kwang Soo?)
Let's be honest. It's time for Mr. Yang to give me permission.
Kwang Soo,
shall we have a drink together?
Shall we have a drink together?
(There may be people who haven't seen it, )
Do you keep watching the video of my acrostic poem for you?
(but there aren't any people who have only seen it once.)
(He watches it.)
Gosh.
He watches that legendary scene in secret.
She's very good.
- I watch it occasionally. - She's good.
- His ears can't stop moving. - Jennie is good at this.
(With Kwang Soo's shy confession, )
(Kwang Soo's time is up.)
- Jennie is good. - My gosh.
(Kwang Soo's ears moved for 37 seconds.)
- How long did mine move? - 37 seconds.
- Really? - I did well.
(He actually did well.)
Well done, well done.
- I guess I should target her. - Okay.
(The next target is Jisoo.)
Ready, start.
Who is your ideal type?
Kwang Soo.
(I'm your ideal type?)
Me?
(Kwang Soo's ears move whenever they mention his name.)
Why are you happy?
This is so funny.
No, I... I...
(Do BLACKPINK members like me?)
(Jisoo's strategy is to answer everything with Kwang Soo.)
- Is she telling the truth? - You have to attack her.
Kwang Soo is just like a chance card.
(Idol's easy answer is always Kwang Soo.)
If she answers with Kwang Soo, she remains calm.
- She looked at me when she said it. - Hey.
What's going on?
It's hard living with the members, right?
(Her ears move first.)
I love it.
(Then she gives a thumbs up.)
"I love it." That's what happened.
(It must have been really tough for her sometimes.)
I'm sure there are hard times.
(Until the end)
I love it. I'm happy.
Do you miss when we were roommates?
I do.
(Perking up)
(I guess you don't miss it.)
- She doesn't miss it. - No. They're not my ears.
Jisoo is a machine.
(Jisoo doesn't hesitate even for a second.)
- She's an answering machine. - I do miss it.
Were you stressed because of me?
No, I wasn't.
(Perking up)
Just say that it's true.
(Jisoo...)
She's a machine.
(Even the people looking at her ears get embarrassed.)
- It keeps you on your toes. - Who made this thing?
It's better to say yes and have them move.
(Was it really tough for you?)
Who made this thing?
(Flustered)
(Jisoo's turn is over.)
Yes! That was the last question.
32 seconds.
(Jisoo's ears moved for 32 seconds.)
I did too poorly.
(She is in the 1st place among the three of them.)
- I did it! - Good job.
- It's okay. - I'm sorry.
(Jennie feels bad after recording 82 seconds.)
- Jennie, it's okay. - It's okay.
My ears were excited.
- It's okay. - We'll move on to the next group.
(Round 3 is over with Suk Jin's 39 seconds, Lisa's 31 seconds, )
- My gosh. - Everyone's so mentally strong.
(and Ji Hyo's 24 seconds.)
Mine is moving a lot. This is weird.
(It's the final round among Haha, Jae Suk, and Jong Kook.)
Okay. Ha Dong Hoon. I got this!
Jae Suk. Show us what you've got.
- Of course. - Show us.
- Please bring about a twist. - Hey.
A game between the Running Man members is bound to be intense.
There's nothing to talk about here.
(Intense)
- I suddenly feel... - I'll show you.
(Jong Kook is nervous too.)
- Mine moves a lot. - Make sure Jong Kook's move a lot.
Haha, just ask strong questions from start to finish.
This is the last round. Jong Kook.
(The first target is Jong Kook.)
- Jong Kook is good at these games. - Listen.
(Jae Suk abruptly asks the question first.)
- Don't worry. - I'll be direct.
You think that if you are determined,
you can make any woman fall for you, right?
No.
(Perking up)
(His answer is modest but his ears aren't.)
Do you think that?
- No? - No, I don't.
I don't think that.
Have you ever dated one of our guests?
Why are your ears moving? Did you really date one of them?
(Peek-a-boo)
Why are your ears moving?
Did you really date one of them?
(Screaming)
(The time has come.)
Why are your ears moving?
Did you really date one of them?
(Feeling betrayed)
(It gets out of control as Jong Kook doesn't deny it.)
You can deny it. Why?
- We'll leave it at that. - I haven't answered the question.
(Making excuses)
Okay. We understand.
(I didn't name anyone.)
I didn't say anything. I just said they were a guest.
The woman you dated...
(This is my chance.)
I know her too, right?
(Yes, you do.)
(This must be true.)
Please just tell us her initials.
(I'm curious.)
He's usually really good at games like this.
(He breaks down at the mention of the past relationships.)
He's going to pull himself together.
- Yes, of course. You know her. - Pull yourself together.
(His turn is over after he collects himself together.)
It's over.
Jong Kook, you did well.
(Jong Kook's ears moved for 49 seconds.)
- It wasn't bad? - No, it wasn't.
- Look. I'll show you... - Jae Suk.
(Next target is Jae Suk.)
what it means to be composed.
(He is the master of composure.)
- Show us your experience. - I'll show you my composure.
Jae Suk might fly off because of his ears, so you have to hold him.
- Hey. - He might fly because of his ears.
(Beware of any take-offs)
They will flap around like this.
Do we need to secure him with a safety belt?
Bring it on. I'll show you what it means to be composed.
Imagine that your wife...
goes on a trip...
with the kids...
for a month. How would that make you feel?
I would be so sad.
(His ears are moving.)
(It's certainly a sad thing.)
(But his ears were so insensitive.)
(Jong Kook knows exactly what married men want.)
- Look at that. - For a month?
(A glimpse of a quiet home crossed his mind.)
- I can't even imagine that. - He might fly away.
- Look at that. - Grab him.
- Look at his ears. - Grab him now.
(He's really excited.)
He must be really happy.
- I would be so sad. - Grab him.
- His ears are dancing. - If that happens,
(What happened to the composure?)
- I would be so sad. - Hold him.
(Moving back and forth)
- Oh, no. - Jong Kook, don't say such a thing.
- Let's try one more time. - Don't say such a thing.
- They're still moving. - The thought alone makes me sad.
- Jae Suk. - I feel so sad.
You must be so happy seeing that you always...
- tell me to get married soon. - Of course.
(It's like a reflex.)
- I always tell you that. - Yes.
Who made you want to get married?
- You did. - Exactly.
(He hopes everyone else can feel the happiness in marriage.)
Why do you think I told you guys to get married soon?
They won't stop moving.
Could it be broken?
- Could it be broken? - Jae Suk, you might fly away.
(Worried)
I think it's broken.
- Go and wash your face. - Stop moving!
Jae Suk, you must be so happy...
(It's the biggest challenge for a man with 14 years of marriage.)
Jae Suk, your married life...
- Jae Suk. Hey, listen. - Jae Suk.
(Exhaling)
What are you doing?
- We don't have to say anything. - What's going on?
- My gosh. - It's over.
(It's done after just one question.)
We don't have to say anything anymore.
(He lost all of his other characters.)
You lost your calm because of a single question.
(Today is just Yoo Jae Suk, who's been married for 14 years.)
- They might explode at this rate. - What's going on?
- We're going to lose. - Goodbye.
- They might explode at this rate. - Life experience, my foot.
I think they're broken.
(He now blames it on the machine.)
This machine must be broken.
- Jae Suk, please calm down. - Just throw in the towel.
- Do you want to give up? - Hold on.
- Listen. I... - I won't say a word.
(He's going to fill all 100 seconds.)
- I won't do anything. - Hold on.
- Why... - I won't say anything.
- Why are you so nervous? - Stop murmuring.
It's because I have anxiety issues.
- That's why. - Anxiety issues, my foot.
(He always gets nervous in variety shows.)
- Okay? - Pull your hair back.
What's wrong with you?
(Jae Suk's time is up.)
- Time's up. - What's my record?
- 75 seconds. - Why...
(His ears moved for 75 seconds out of 100 seconds.)
- Gosh. - 75 seconds?
I think we'll be the last place team.
(Haha successfully defended himself with 29 seconds.)
This isn't right. We should get rid of them.
(Mission 2 Final Results)
142 seconds in total.
Team Jisoo came in first.
(Team Jisoo wins with 142 seconds.)
- Okay. - I didn't expect this.
- We're doing so well. - The team in second place...
(Team Rose and Lisa wins 2nd place...)
- with a record of 154 seconds... - We must be the last place team.
(with 154 seconds, which is 12 seconds behind.)
- is Team Rose and Lisa. - Okay.
- And... - It's not bad.
- Second place is not bad. - Good.
(It's not that bad.)
- We can still roll a dice. - I will...
(Although they're in the last place, they can still win in the dice.)
- We still have a chance. - Let's pick the 0, 10 dice.
- We'll go with the 0, 10 dice. - Yes.
(They chose 0, 10 dice.)
- Here you go. - Really?
The 0, 10 dice.
(Team Jennie must roll the dice twice.)
Jennie, just do as you did earlier.
- They're taking a risk. - Jennie.
- Go, Jennie! - Zero!
(They really need to get 0.)
- You can do this. - Zero!
- I'll just throw it freely. - Get zero both times.
- Let's go. - Zero, please.
Jennie, get zero both times.
(The dice fell on the floor while they're hoping to get zero.)
(It kept rolling.)
- Zero, please. - Oh, no.
(And it stopped.)
(They got 10 pieces of penalty rice cake.)
It hit the tray before it stopped.
- He's right. - It hit the tray and stopped.
(I can't accept it.)
- That doesn't matter. - This doesn't count.
(They all object.)
- No. - It hit the tray.
- It hit the tray and stopped. - No.
- It hit the tray and stopped. - It hit the tray.
- Hey, listen. - It hit the tray.
- You said that doesn't matter. - No.
(It's just 10 rice cakes.)
- The dice hit the tray. - You saw that too.
- It hit right here. - It hit the tray.
- It stopped after hitting it. - It hit the tray.
- Only if it falls on the tray. - It didn't fall on the tray.
(He got carried away and used violence.)
It hit the tray.
- That doesn't matter. - Throw it again.
(The two members are far from composure.)
- No. They said... - Let's do it again.
You have...
- another chance. - You have one more try left.
(After a physical fight, they accept 10 rice cakes.)
- Okay. 10. - It's okay.
(It's now time to roll the second dice.)
Our rankings will change this time.
- Jennie, it's okay. - Gosh.
There's no way we'll get 20.
- That won't happen. - Exactly.
Let's go. Get 10 again.
- Stay focused. - If we get 20...
- I hope you get 10 again! - 10 again!
- 10 again! - 10 again!
(Everyone hopes they'll get 10 again.)
(Will they get 0 this time?)
- Okay. - 10 again!
(If they get 10 again, they'll receive 20 pieces of rice cake.)
- 10 again! - 10 again!
(They thought it wouldn't happen, )
- Okay. - 10 again!
(but they got 10 twice in a row.)
My goodness. I can't believe it.
(Devastated)
(Team Jisoo widened the gap by 20 pieces at once.)
- I'm so sorry! - Great.
- We... - Which dice will you throw?
(Team Rose and Lisa, who is in the 2nd place, )
- The 1, 10... No, the 0, 10 dice. - We'll pick the same dice.
(also chooses 0, 10 dice.)
- The 0, 10 dice. - Here you go.
You see, Lisa decided to overcome it.
(Lisa...)
She'll change her luck today.
(Lisa is determined to change her luck today.)
That's right. She'll change it today.
- Lisa... - Tell me I can do it.
(Actually, )
"R" will work too.
(at the shoe throwing game, Lisa...)
- "R"! - Or a black box. "R"!
- I think she'll get that one. - I hope so.
It'll land in "R".
(had a 2 percent chance of failure, )
(but her shoe fell in the penalty box.)
- Unlucky hand, unlucky hand. - Lisa.
- Unlucky hand, unlucky hand. - Lisa, get zero.
- She whispered, "unlucky hand". - I hope you get zero.
(She's been known as the unlucky one in the group.)
She should get 10.
- Get 10, Lisa. - It's going to be a festival.
- Get 10. - Let's do this.
(Will she be able to change her luck...)
Do you like 10? Just as you thought.
(despite their sabotage?)
- Okay. - It's going to hit the tray.
(Please.)
- Do you like 10? - Just as you thought.
It's going to hit the tray.
That doesn't matter.
(She got unlucky this time again.)
(The other teams got excited.)
- I told you so. - It's okay.
(Unlucky)
(They can't even get mad because it's Lisa.)
- Let's go! - That was great.
- My gosh. Lisa did it again. - Go, Team!
(Only Team Jisoo in the 1st place is at a great advantage.)
They benefited a lot.
- She rolled it. She didn't throw. - They benefited a lot.
- 20 pieces of rice cake. - We didn't get any.
(Team Jennie gets 20 rice cakes, Team Rose and Lisa gets 10.)
- These are 20 pieces. - That's a lot.
We'll move to another place for the final mission.
- Okay. - I'll eat one.
What is it? Whose is it?
(The rice cake box is always on standby.)
- Are you serious? - I got two pieces.
- Yes. Jong Kook got three pieces. - Wait. I have a question.
(Slowly)
Where is he? There he is.
(Rose discards rice cakes...)
(when no one is looking.)
Wait. I have a question.
- Rose. - Yes?
- I just saw you... - What did you do?
- Nothing. - What did you do?
- I put them in here. - Wait.
- You can't... - You saw that, right?
(She jumps after discarding her rice cakes.)
- Hey. - She did it when we were all here?
(Even Kwang Soo is surprised at the speed of her actions.)
- Hey! - She's unbelievable.
Rose put them in the box right away.
- Yes. I saw her doing it. - That's not true.
(She's saying nonsense.)
You took three, right? Where did you put them?
- Forget it. I'm in shock. - I saw that.
Kwang Soo.
(That's how Lisa learns about how Running Man works.)
I thought we were on the same team.
- Kwang Soo, please. - I got two.
Lisa, why are you taking so many pieces of rice cake out?
I'm going to eat them.
(Shameless)
- Excuse me. - Five pieces.
What?
- One more piece. - Okay.
(Even during breaks, the box is very popular.)
(These are the two VIPs of the rice cake box.)
(He quickly gets rid of the rice cakes.)
(Kwang Soo does the same.)
I'll close the door. We'll be off.
(They move to the last mission place.)
The rice cake is bigger than I thought.
I heard that they have 50 million subscribers to their channel.
(BLACKPINK)
- Who? - BLACKPINK.
(They have the 2nd most subscribers after Justin Bieber.)
- That's incredible. - That's no joke.
- 50 million subscribers. - That's so cool.
Can you send me just 100,000 people to my channel?
(Genuinely envious)
- At the opening... - Can you just...
(Haha's Youtube Channel)
mention "Haha PD" just once?
- We'll do that. - Hey.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
(It's the generosity of the global idols.)
- We'll really do that. - Really?
Can you mention "Jiseokjin World" just once as well?
(Suk Jin's Youtube Channel)
- We'll do that. - "Jiseokjin World"?
- That's a promise. - I promise.
- He acted so pathetically. - Thank you.
(Dumbfounded)
The name of his channel is "Jiseokjin World".
(Everyone's begging for subscribers.)
- "Jiseokjin World". - Isn't it funny?
- "Jiseokjin World". - That's lame.
(Please mention it once.)
Please mention it just once.
And stop calling us while broadcasting.
(Embarrassed)
Come on. Help me out.
(Let's help each other.)
You said you would never do that to attract subscribers.
(Suk Jin finds an easy way to boost his subscribers.)
Just help me out.
But "Haha PD" is easy for foreigners to catch,
(Jong Kook gives an honest opinion about Suk Jin's channel.)
but "Jiseokjin World" isn't.
(The channel's name is too difficult for non-Koreans.)
- It's hard to pronounce. - Indeed.
The English title is "Jiseokjin World".
Even the English title is hard to catch.
(The name is hard even in English.)
- I know. I agree. - It's hard to catch.
(He solemnly admits it.)
- "Haha PD" is simpler. - It'd be hard to get subscribers.
Besides, there's no reason for foreigners to watch your videos.
(Breaks his heart with the truth)
(1. The channel's name is hard, 2. It's hard even in English.)
You just punched him three times in a row.
(3. Non-Koreans wouldn't watch it.)
- Jong Kook is amazing. - They have no reason to watch them.
(Conclusion: No one will watch it.)
- My gosh. - You know I'm right.
He just knocked you down three times in a row.
- Why would they watch his videos? - I believe...
Keep your promise, Jisoo.
- I didn't make any promises to you. - Keep your promise, Jisoo.
(Suk Jin made a promise to himself.)
I didn't make any promises to you.
She didn't promise you, did she? When did she do that?
(When did Jisoo make a promise?)
- No one promised you anything. - What promise did she make?
- That was good. - I'm dizzy.
- Rewind it to see if I promised. - I'm dizzy.
(Can you check?)
Jennie made that promise.
Jennie, now is not the time to sleep.
Jennie is sleeping. Keep it down. She's sleeping.
(Jennie is sleeping.)
- Jennie, you can't sleep now. - She's sleeping, Suk Jin.
(Jennie escapes Suk Jin's clinginess by sleeping.)
- Why is she... - She's sleeping deeply.
She's sleeping when we're this loud?
When you called her...
(She falls asleep as soon as he calls her name.)
Jennie, don't forget. It's "Jiseokjin World".
(Until the end...)
(Sleeping)
Anyway, I'm so happy...
because I became close to the BLACKPINK members.
Seeing that Jisoo made such a joke to me...
- It wasn't a joke. - She was serious.
- She was serious. - A joke, my foot.
(Suk Jin happily reflected on the illusion he created.)
She feels comfortable around me.
- Suk Jin, it wasn't a joke. - You're wrong.
- She feels comfortable around me... - She always means what she says.
- I always mean what I say. - Exactly.
(A little flustered)
- I'm serious. - My goodness.
I was so happy that you were pretending to sleep.
(He changes to Jennie.)
- Why? - That means we're close now.
(He brainwashes her on how close they are.)
- Why does that mean you're close? - I'll go back to sleep.
- You have a positive mindset. - I'm serious.
- I'm really happy. - Hey.
(Positivity is the key to Suk Jin's youth.)
I'm just glad that...
Suk Jin didn't cry about it.
- He's supposed to cry. - I admire him.
He should be crying over this.
(Positive Suk Jin is not daunted by the attacks.)
- We should go, "Don't cry." - "Don't cry."
I think Suk Jin is...
fighting against nine people.
- You're right. - Right.
(Suk Jin the lone fighter)
- Gosh. - Jisoo.
I respect myself for this because...
(He is very used to bullying.)
"I'm so respect." Because...
- He said, "I'm so respect." - "I'm so respect"?
(What is he talking about?)
What does that even mean?
"I'm so respect", "I'm so respect".
I'm so respect.
Gosh, I'm so respect.
(Suk Jin doesn't back down.)
Gosh, BLACKPINK.
You don't become a global star overnight.
(He doesn't care.)
Suk Jin's talks and his activities are...
just so terrible.
But he still manages to push things ahead.
(Although he's not doing too well, he can push his way through.)
- My goodness. - Amazing driving force.
- Amazing force. - What day is it today?
(Abruptly)
- Why are you checking your phone? - I'm checking the date.
I'm checking because it's the day I got close to BLACKPINK.
Is that so?
It's October 6.
(The day he got close to BLACKPINK only in his imagination)
Gosh, this is worse than...
crying over it.
- He's about to cry. - It's worse than crying.
(His positivity makes everyone on the verge of tears.)
- This is as bad as him crying. - Gosh.
Everyone, I got close to BLACKPINK on October 6, 2020.
(They arrive at the mission site...)
He's amazing. He's great.
Yes, I respect him.
(as Suk Jin declares the day memorable by himself.)
- Okay. - He's got guts!
What is this now?
(It's a big set for the last mission.)
- It's a slide. - Of course.
We're supposed to slide down?
(What is this big slide?)
This is your last mission.
After this mission, you're going to throw dices again.
(They'll roll the dice again for the last time...)
(after this mission.)
We should win this time.
- We're done if we lose again. - The three bottom members...
(The team with the most count of rice cakes will get the penalty.)
and the team with the most rice cakes will get the penalty.
The box is filled with rice cakes.
So we had to empty it once.
Who is it? Who?
That many rice cakes?
(Shameless)
- We had to empty it. - Seriously?
I can't believe it.
(She is the leading cause.)
That's too much.
They shouldn't do it when the camera isn't rolling.
(Who is it?)
It's the last round that determines the number of penalty rice cakes.
(It's the final mission over the last rice cakes.)
It's called, Jump Like It's Your Last.
(Jump Like It's Your Last)
All right.
There will be a women's match and a men's match.
(It's a match between women's team and men's team.)
- You will have two matches. - Okay.
Two members from each team will hug each other,
(The two members will come down the slide together.)
and all six of you will come down the slide.
Then you should throw your opponents over the hurdle.
(Then you must throw your opponents over the huddle.)
- What? - Throw them over that?
- Can they go under the hurdle? - But...
(It's about using strength.)
What if I have to throw Jong Kook?
We'll see which team survives longer...
(The rank will be decided based on the time...)
to decide the winner.
(they survived and adding the scores together.)
- Gosh, this is... - We'll be crushed.
Teaming up is important.
That team is too strong.
(Team Jennie and Team Jisoo try to form an alliance.)
Our team is too weak.
- Toward the end. - Jong Kook, we should...
(Team Rose and Lisa are very relaxed.)
- win this one. - I know. Let's do our best.
(Determined)
(Rose and Lisa are already getting ready.)
Okay, okay.
I'm scared of them. They're really strong.
- Jennie, I'm very weak, you know. - You are?
I can't protect you.
Let's start with the men's match.
- Just like that? - Hey.
(A flush of anger)
Hey, you. Don't stand there...
and make a face looking charismatic.
(Charismatic)
You're annoying.
Kwang Soo, you're our target.
(Declaration)
- Our score is so bad... - We're going to attack you.
(He teased them with Jong Kook in mind, but now he's the target.)
- Now you should go up the slide. - I have my target too.
Let's go.
There's nothing much to life. Let's just do it.
(Suk Jin approaches the bag with a sudden theory in life.)
- Let's just go. - Let's.
(Picking up two pieces of rice cake)
Take off your glasses.
(He puts on the sticker after lying about it.)
Try harassing the opponents.
Suk Jin, what are you doing?
(Caught red-handed)
What are you doing?
Look at him.
(Embarrassed)
What are you doing?
I was going to do it, but I didn't. Are we good?
(Suk Jin talks back even though he betrayed the team.)
Why did you put the rice cake in there?
I didn't. Not yet anyway.
Come on.
(He habitually betrays people.)
(Haha and Se Chan went up the slide.)
This is scary.
(They get scared after going up there.)
It's scary. It'll be scary for me too.
Like it's your last How does the dance go?
Like it's your last.
(What was that?)
(Embarrassed)
- Ask Lisa. - Show us.
Lisa, how does the dance go with "Like it's your last"?
(Dancing right away)
Like it's your last dance Ta-da.
(So cute dancing together)
(Just like old drunken guys)
(Jennie is very kind.)
So cute.
- While we go up... - We should go down?
(Men's match, Round 1)
- Throw them over the hurdle. - Got it.
Shouldn't we decide who stands where?
(We'll be attacked if we stand in the middle.)
Yes, that's important.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - You stand in the middle.
We really have to win.
- We haven't won once. - Us too.
- They're the only ones. - Right.
(Telling on)
- They should stand in the middle. - All right.
- You stand here. - Okay.
- You can't win again. - We should join forces.
Just listen to them, you punk!
- There a reason. - He's right.
(He instinctively acts submissive for his survival.)
Jong Kook heard what you said.
- Gosh. - Why is it so steep?
(Pale)
It's amazingly steep.
We'll go down later.
(Haha and Se Chan will join them later for the attack.)
You want us to go first and wait for you?
1. Be a man! 2, 3!
- Three! Go. - You go first.
(How dare you! Go down first.)
- You go first. - No, wait.
(Not going well as they planned)
- Let's go. - We should defend ourselves.
Let's defend.
You're so cool.
(What? I'm cool?)
(Excited to see BLACKPINK's reaction)
(Old guys are so excited.)
Let's go now.
(The rest comes down too.)
Let's go. This is our chance!
(Attacking Jong Kook as soon as they arrive)
(How dare you attack me?)
- No! - No, don't!
(His thigh muscles are on fire.)
No!
- Jae Suk, don't stand there. - Be quiet!
- Come here. - Okay.
(Two weak teams are joining forces.)
Watch it.
No!
(But Jong Kook doesn't budge.)
(Grabbing)
(After conquering the old guy, )
Well done.
- It's okay. It's okay. - Separate them.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo come together.)
- Take Kwang Soo off of him. - It's okay.
(Jong Kook...)
(He tries to separate Kwang Soo with an arm bar.)
I'm not letting him go. Never!
Come on.
(Will you still not separate?)
Take Jong Kook off then.
- Take Jong Kook off. - Take Jong Kook off!
(It's an unexpected deep cleansing of the face.)
Oh, my gosh.
We're done if we don't do this.
Come on, hurry.
Kwang Soo, Jong Kook should go.
Why are you telling me that?
(We're on the same team.)
- Kwang Soo. - No!
No!
(They drive a wedge between them and now Jong Kook is mad!)
(Hunting down persistent Jae Suk)
Don't do this.
(Please.)
- No. - We have amazing teamwork today.
(As Jong Kook catches his breath, )
That's it.
(Suk Jin barely extends his life.)
We can make it.
(It's very unexpected.)
He's doing well.
(This won't do.)
Save me.
No way.
(Jong Kook changes his target to the oldest Suk Jin.)
No! Don't!
No!
(He's about to throw Suk Jin!)
(Kwang Soo even helps him.)
(No!)
(With a single cry, he is pushed aside.)
Come back in!
Suk Jin is out!
(Ji Suk Jin is out.)
(Well, I didn't expect him to be better.)
- No, not me. - Don't attack Se Chan.
(Se Chan is his next target.)
Not me!
(Grabbing and lifting)
(Gosh, no!)
(Se Chan is still hanging in there!)
Se Chan is holding out.
(BLACKPINK is watching me!)
(It's an equal match!)
Oh, my gosh!
(So exciting to watch this up close!)
Se Chan!
(Hang in there!)
Haha, save me!
(Punching)
Why are you attacking me?
(Kwang Soo helps out with his foul play!)
(Jae Suk was attacking Kwang Soo.)
- Come on. - No!
Get Jong Koo off of me!
(Betraying right away)
No, Se Chan!
(Tried to stop their attack alone...)
Se Chan is out!
(Se Chan is out due to Jae Suk's betrayal.)
(Join forces? Is that something you can eat?)
Oh, no.
I want to give up.
- Just let me live. - I want 2nd place.
(It's now 1 versus 1 versus 2.)
- Give me 1st place. - Jae Suk.
They should come in last.
(Haha's team)
They won too many times.
Okay, let's get rid of them.
(Is it my turn?)
All right.
(Haha is chosen as the scapegoat.)
- Come. - Tornado!
(Using his killer move!)
- Oh, my gosh! - Tornado!
(What is that?)
What are you, a chicken?
You're doing good!
(You're doing good!)
(Escapes the crisis with his ultimate skill)
(Shocked)
(Adults are irritated by Jae Suk's childish technique.)
(Teaching the child with physical punishment)
Stop kicking me.
Give him a break, he tried his tornado move.
(Please give him a break.)
(Finally, he's dragged by furious adults.)
Tornado!
(He doesn't have any strength left to do the "Tornado".)
Come on, do the tornado move.
I can only do that two times a day.
(He can use the power only two times a day.)
(Exceeded daily usage)
- Did you do that? - No, no!
(Get up, Haha.)
I used all the power.
(Out of Tornado)
Haha is out.
(Haha and Se Chan's team loses.)
Jae Suk, you can stop now!
(Jae Suk is the only one left.)
(That tickles.)
Jae Suk, give up.
(It's a heartrending battle between 2 against 1.)
- Jae Suk. - Jae Suk.
(Feeling sympathetic)
- Just give up. - Stop.
I can go back in time!
(Punching)
What was that?
- I'm alive. - You are?
Can he do that?
(He has lost his mind after all the tornado attacks.)
You brats.
- Stop. - Jae Suk, stop.
I will show you my power.
(Be quiet!)
You can stop now.
(Please.)
You brats.
Tornado!
(His tornado isn't strong enough to take down a leaf.)
(His sound is the only thing that's loud.)
- Tornado! - You're like a first-grader.
(It's really childish.)
(Lifting up)
- What are you doing? - My goodness.
(The novice tornado maker shows his ugliness.)
(He couldn't even try using the tornado move.)
(And he's out!)
It was amazing.
(Team Rose and Lisa wins the men's match!)
We can never beat Jong Kook.
- Gosh. - It was amazing.
(Now it's the women's match.)
This is really scary.
- What do we do, Jennie? - So Min.
Other BLACKPINK members are all really strong.
- Right? You told us so. - They are, especially Lisa.
(The strong members are coming.)
(Intimidated)
It's cold. Be careful.
If you hold out longer, you'll be able to change the result.
(The rankings will be decided based on this game's result.)
- All right. - Go for it.
(Let's form an ally.)
Let's join forces.
Get ready.
(Okay.)
Set, go!
- Let's do that. - Go down now, you guys.
(Rose and Lisa take off confidently.)
You should scatter.
- Okay, good. - That's better.
(The two weak allied teams also take off.)
They all came down.
Jennie. So Min.
(Rose and Lisa unite from the beginning.)
(So Min goes after Lisa.)
- They're starting with Rose. - No.
(Ji Hyo and Jisoo go after Rose.)
Lisa. Lisa!
(They aren't fooling around.)
Look at Ji Hyo.
So Min is good.
(Jennie is being crushed to death by Rose.)
- Hold on. - Rose, you need to come and help.
(Lisa is in danger as it's 3 against 1.)
(She escapes with her strength.)
Are you okay? Lisa, grab onto to me.
- She's really strong. - No.
(Lisa...)
They're going to run out of energy anyway.
I want to participate in the game too!
(She's buried.)
You won't be able to.
(A desperate cry of the weakest team.)
Let go of me.
Hug me. Hold onto me.
(So Min takes her socks off.)
Who took off my socks?
Why did you take off her socks?
(What's the point?)
(The weakest team tries to cheat to compensate.)
Jennie.
(Jennie already lost her mind.)
This can't be aired.
(What are you doing Jennie?)
You have to get rid of the other team first.
- Come on. - Oh, no.
(This time, Rose is in danger as is 3 against 1.)
- You have to do it. - Push!
(Ji Hyo uses all of her strength.)
- No! Grab onto someone! - No. Hold on.
- Grab onto someone! - No. Hold on.
Hey!
(She listens to Jong Kook and is holding on.)
Hurry up and go.
(Jisoo is in danger!)
(Ji Hyo grabs by the collar.)
- My gosh. - Hey, Jennie.
(Jisoo barely escapes thanks to Ji Hyo.)
- I'm sorry. - What just happened?
Rose, you're doing great.
(Rose tries to fight back.)
Goodness.
Why am I doing this?
(Crying)
(Reality hits her at the sudden headlock.)
Rose, hold on!
Lisa!
Oh, my gosh.
(Rose fights back until the end thanks to Lisa.)
- Gosh. - Good job.
Good job. Nice.
- Rose. - Hey!
Jennie, that has no effect.
- Tickle, tickle. - Stop it!
(The attack is no use.)
Good job, Rose. You're doing great.
(Rose, you're doing a good job.)
(While Rose holds on, )
- Rose, hold on a bit longer. Good. - I'm sorry.
(So Min joins.)
- No, that's Ji Hyo. Not her. - I'm sorry.
(Why is she attacking Ji Hyo?)
- It's not her. - Your target is Rose.
- You have to push Rose out. - What's wrong with her?
(She runs away in vain.)
- What are you doing? - Come here.
- Ji Hyo is mad. - Good.
- Push So Min out. - Push her out.
(Ji Hyo targets So Min.)
- No. - Help her.
This is your chance.
(Rose and Lisa join her.)
- Get Jennie. - Push her.
(Low kick)
(Crazy So Mi is blinded right now.)
- Why are So Min's feet so big? - You got this.
(Anyway...)
- No. - She's holding on with her toes.
- Push her. - It's not working.
(The big-foot So Min holds on with her toes.)
(She barely escapes the danger.)
(The next target is Rose after So Min escapes.)
Come here. This is our chance.
Lisa!
(While everyone is involved in the desperate fight...)
- Over here. - I have a cramp in my foot!
I have a cramp in my foot!
(Her frog toes get a muscle cramp.)
(They really don't care.)
Hold on. I have a cramp in my foot!
- Hold on. - So Min.
(Tapping)
- What is it? - Hey, So Min.
(What's wrong?)
My toe looks weird.
Something is wrong with my toe.
It's because you grabbed onto the mat with your toes.
(It's the result of overworking her toes.)
- It's because you grabbed onto... - She has a cramp.
- the mat with your toes. - She has a cramp.
- Go in now. - This is never going to end.
(She rejoins after Jae Suk's emergency treatment.)
Again?
(She's exhausted after her last escape.)
Push her out.
- Push her out. Okay. - Rose is out.
(Rose is out after the allies' persistent attack.)
- Rose is out. - Rose is out.
- Rose is out. - Good job, Rose. It's okay.
It's okay, Rose.
(Next target is Lisa, who's now left alone.)
I'll take her out with me.
- What? Don't leave me alone. - So Min.
- Let's come in second place. - No.
- They just went out. - Let's come in second place.
- Then we'll be in last place. - No, no.
(Cold)
In the meantime, look at Rose. She's incredible.
Good job.
(As soon as she gets out, she blatantly goes to her bag.)
Look.
(She gets rid of 2 rice cakes.)
In the meantime, look at Rose.
- She's incredible. - Good job.
(Then she returns as if nothing happened.)
(While Rose throws away her rice cakes...)
So Min!
(Lisa is about to be eliminated.)
- I'm getting mad. - Push now.
So Min!
- Push her! - No!
- Lisa is out. - Lisa is out.
(Lisa is finally eliminated.)
- Good job. - Good job.
My gosh.
(It's now 2 versus 2.)
This is nice. I'm comfortable.
This is nice.
(She uses her secret weapon, the pickaxe.)
(She has finished calling on Bully Ji Hyo.)
(Even her teammates are shocked.)
What is this?
- Am I seeing things? - Is this right?
(Intimidated)
- You're seeing it right. - How many people does Ji Hyo have?
(Bully Ji Hyo shows off her power for the first time in a while.)
- Hold on. You should go. - They're incredible.
What's the prize?
Is the prize worth all of this?
Goodbye, So Min.
(Good-bye.)
So Min is done.
(So Min, who stayed in for a while, is out.)
- Bye, Jennie. - My gosh.
- Jennie has fainted. - She gave up.
- She's sleeping. - What's this? Are you hurt?
(She gives up.)
- I'll push you out. - Jennie is done.
(Everyone is out including Jennie.)
Good job!
(Team Jisoo won the women's match.)
(This is a festival!)
(What is the final rank with the combination of the men's match?)
Who was it?
We calculated the time that both people got out.
(They calculated the time that both people got out.)
We added 3 minutes to each person who came in 1st place.
(They added 3 minutes to each person who came in 1st place.)
It was a great fight.
The team in 1st place with 25 minutes and 26 seconds is...
Help me! Tornado!
(Is it Team Rose and Lisa, who came in 1st place in the men's match?)
(Or is it Team Jisoo, who came in 1st place in the women's match?)
Help her.
- Tornado! - Jae Suk, that's enough now.
(Or is it Team Jennie, who constantly came in 2nd place?)
The team in 1st place with 25 minutes and 26 seconds is...
(The team in 1st place in the final mission is...)
It's Team Jisoo.
(Team Jisoo)
(They won 3 consecutive missions.)
- It is them. - Really?
(Team Rose and Lisa, 24 minutes and 59 seconds)
- See? - It was close.
(Team Jennie, 23 minutes and 45 seconds)
They did really great.
(We're in the last place again.)
- This is disappointing. - They won every mission.
(They're very excited to have won 3 consecutive times.)
I told you.
This isn't fun.
We came in second place.
(It's no fun when you've never won a single mission.)
- This isn't fun. - It isn't.
I'm not going to watch the show this week.
- I'm not going to watch it! - This isn't fun.
(Jong Kook, 45 years old, It's only fun when you win.)
- Jong Kook's mad. I can't help you. - This isn't fun.
- Tune in. - Tune in.
(It's a twist of Team Jisoo, who was thought to be weak.)
They came in first place for everything. This isn't fun.
- Who will go first? - Should we start?
(Team Jennie must roll the dice 2 times.)
- We'll go first. - We have to get 0 or 10.
(There's nothing to lose. They chose 0, 10 dice.)
- Let's get zero 2 times. - We have nothing to lose.
- I'll hit it with my head. - Okay.
- Good. Let's get 0. - This is 0.
(They threw the 1st dice haphazardly, )
It's about time for them to get nothing.
(and they got 0.)
Is it zero?
(It's the lucky 0 they got at the very end.)
- Jennie. - So Min!
- 1 more time. - It's over if they get 0 again.
(If they get 0 again, )
(they'll get no additional rice cakes.)
- Let's do it one more time. - This is a miracle.
- Do it with your head. - Good.
(Jennie got 10 in the last 2 missions. What about now?)
It's going.
Yes!
(They were hoping for something else, but she got 10 again.)
- It's okay. - It's okay.
(Crying)
Nothing is going right for me.
- 10, 10. - 10, 10.
(Team Rose and Lisa chose 0, 10 dice too.)
(The fate is in Kwang Soo's hands.)
10, 10.
(He gets 10.)
(We have a comrade!)
Ours bumped into something too!
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, )
- This won't do. - Ours bumped into something too!
(the two teams get 10 additional rice cakes.)
Put these in each of your bags.
(He's walking on eggshells while holding 10.)
- This is yours. - I'm glad everyone worked hard,
but I'm not trying to nitpick, but...
Who was the one that lost earlier?
(In the race...)
(He wants them to take the rice cakes.)
- Or... - They did their best.
No, let's do this.
(Team Jennie is also dividing up the rice cakes.)
- Face up or down. - Face up or down.
- I'm sorry, Jennie. - Jennie.
I'm sorry. We're cold-hearted.
(There are no privileges in the face of competition.)
- Okay. - Take them.
Okay, open up your bags and count your rice cakes.
(It's time for the final count.)
We'll start with Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk discards 6 and is left with 9.)
- I have 9. - 9.
- Nine? - Next, So Min. Open your bag.
(So Min's bag contains...)
- Two? - What?
(only two rice cakes?)
What?
- I didn't have many from the start. - This is crazy.
(So Min discards 17 and is left with 2.)
- Why... - Why did you put water in?
In case someone picked it up.
(She was afraid that someone else will lift it.)
My goodness, she's unbelievable.
- Suk Jin has a lot. - I have five.
(Suk Jin discards 20 and is left with 5.)
(Jennie discards 11 and is left with 6.)
I have six.
Jennie has six. Next up is Lisa.
(How many does Lisa have?)
Hold on.
- Lisa has a lot. - Why do you have so many?
(Full)
- Lisa is so nice. - Lisa.
(Lisa's moving team spirit.)
- 11, 12, 13. - 11.
(11, 12, and an ambiguous 13.)
- Eat it. - What was that?
Just eat it.
(Lisa didn't betray anyone, so Jong Kook eats it right away.)
(She got rid of 5 and has 12 in the end.)
- He's so cool. - Next up is Rose.
(What about Rose who was targeting the rice cake box?)
I had 12?
Goodness.
(Empty)
- She doesn't have any? - What?
(She got rid of all of them?)
Hey.
(She discarded 14 and is left with 1.)
- It's okay. Rose doesn't have any. - I have one.
Rose has one? Good. Gosh, you were really acting before.
(She's like Lee Kwang Soo of BLACKPINK.)
- Next is Jong Kook. - I should have a lot.
(How many rice cakes does Jong Kook have left?)
I have a lot.
(Jong Kook is very loyal.)
- This team is so loyal. - 2, 3.
(Jong Kook discarded 2 and is left with 13.)
He has a total of 13.
Goodness.
- Next is Kwang Soo. - I hope Kwang Soo doesn't have any.
(Can Kwang Soo show a twist and be loyal?)
- No. - Kwang Soo's have stickers on them.
- How many do you have? - He has three? Gosh.
You're the worst.
(Kwang Soo discarded 21 and is left with 3.)
- I didn't start off with a lot. - I didn't have a lot either.
Next up is Jisoo.
(Next is Team Jisoo, who don't have many rice cakes.)
We started with 15, so why do I only have 3 left?
(Ji Hyo has 3, Jisoo has 3, Se Chan has 1, and Haha has 0.)
I didn't have a lot from the start. I only have one left.
- I have three left. - I don't have any left.
The people who will get a prize are Haha...
(The final winners are...)
Rose, Se Chan.
(Se Chan with 1, Rose with 1, and Haha with 0.)
- Let's dance. - Let's dance.
(They celebrate for winning together.)
(Screaming)
Let me join too!
(We're so excited.)
Rose, when did you get here?
She's happy despite the fact that we're sitting here.
Is this how Rose is?
(Rose is like Lee Kwang Soo of BLACKPINK.)
- One of us will be in last place. - Is this how Rose is?
We'll give you the prize that you've all been waiting for.
(It's time to hand out the prizes.)
- What is it? - What is it?
(It's the prize that lives up to the status of the guests.)
- Is it a cake? - Is that a robot vacuum cleaner?
(Very elegant customized rice cakes)
- It's a cake made of rice cakes. - What is this?
Yes!
- What is this? - Yes!
(It's for the winners who didn't get a taste of the rice cakes.)
- It's a cake made of rice cakes. - What is this?
My gosh.
- That's a lot of carbs. - They'll be so full.
(It's my first time not being jealous of the prize.)
- I'm so jealous. - We ate it all day today.
- Is this for us? - I'm so jealous.
I'll give them to my kids.
Here are the bottom three.
(The 3 people with the highest number of rice cakes)
- Jong Kook in last place, - Gosh.
(Jong Kook, 13)
Lisa in 11th place,
(Lisa, 12)
and Jae Suk in 10th place.
(Jae Suk, 9)
The three of you are set.
- My gosh. - It's Jae Suk again?
(Laughing)
The number of rice cakes in the box is...
(The total number of rice cakes inside the box)
Team Jisoo has a total of 15.
(Team Jisoo has 15.)
- What? - That's a lot.
(Is that a lot?)
- Isn't that a lot? - Why?
- That's not a lot. - That's not a lot.
(It's not that many. I put it a lot.)
- Team Rose and Lisa has... - Kwang Soo put in 15 himself.
(The total number of rice cakes inside the box)
- No. - Team Rose and Lisa has 42.
(Team Rose and Lisa has 42.)
- What? - What?
- What? They put in 42? - Rose put it all in.
(There was another person who acts like me.)
How many did you guys put in?
(Team Jisoo is exempted from the penalty.)
I'm losing my spirit.
- They want to die together. - The difference is huge.
(The total number of rice cakes inside the box)
- Team Jennie has... - I should've put more in.
- 55. - What?
(Team Jennie has 55.)
Okay.
(Jae Suk, who was likely to get the penalty, )
(brightens up at the news that his team will get the penalty.)
- This is... - Jae Suk said okay.
Gosh, Jae Suk.
(Everyone in the last team will get the penalty.)
- My gosh. - They're in last place anyway.
(I told you.)
- Gosh, Jae Suk. - This is all because of Suk Jin...
(The two who discarded the most put their heads down.)
- Good job. - and So Min.
Jae Suk, it's better to let it explode.
So the candidates for the penalty are these four,
(The final candidates are Jae Suk, So Min, Suk Jin, and Jennie.)
Lisa, and Jong Kook. The six of you are candidates.
(The final candidates are Lisa and Jong Kook.)
- Okay. - If you look over here,
you have to choose a number from 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
(They'll have to choose a bucket.)
- One of them has black paint, - Okay.
(One has black paint and another has pink paint.)
1 has pink paint, and 4 have confetti.
(The rest is filled with confetti.)
Gosh, you get a chance.
- Trust our fate. - Yes.
- We're BLACKPINK. - Yes, we're BLACKPINK.
We can do this.
- So Min, are you number three? - Yes.
(So Min chooses number 3.)
Jong Kook, number five?
(Jong Kook chooses number 5.)
Then I'll pick number one.
(Jae Suk chooses number 1.)
Number one is for Jae Suk.
(Everyone takes the seat after choosing a number.)
I pick number four.
- Number four for Jennie. - Please hold this.
- I'll count to three. - Pour it as I count to three.
(Who will be the two to be covered with black and pink paint?)
- One... - Is it a stone?
Two.
Three.
(Lisa is safe.)
(Jennie picked confetti too.)
Three.
(They won.)
My gosh.
- Oh, no. - Congratulations!
(They even won against Lisa and Jennie, who are usually unlucky.)
The two of them did it.
(It's the rebellion of the two oldest members.)
They picked the paint.
(Unbelievable)
Is it really number six? Let me see.
- It's really number six. - Look.
(It's the odd fate of the two oldest members.)
It's number one.
I can't believe this.
(Jennie breaks into laughter.)
Number 1 and 6 were paint.
(Mixed feelings)
This is unbelievable.
This is ridiculous.
Jae Suk, you're wearing sunglasses.
- Sunglasses. - They look fashionable.
- I know. - You look good.
(He can't see anything with the sunglasses.)
They look like the sunglasses of hipsters.
- It's splattering. - My gosh.
(The master of composure, The master of respect)
Our team is the best.
Today is the best day.
I had a great time with BLACKPINK. I think we became closer.
I even picked pink.
(Me too.)
Thank you.
BLACKPINK forever.
Gosh, I'm so pink.
(Thanks to BLACKPINK, )
"I'm so pink."
(who worked really hard despite their busy schedule.)
- A mysterious world. - Isn't this expensive?
(An ancient tomb full of treasure)
(This is where the incident started.)
You're right. My gosh.
- You look like a thief. - You guys are experts.
(Unidentified criminals are coming together from all over the country.)
- I stole this. - A petty thief.
I'll work on it.
It's a bike.
(The genius grave robbers heard about the crimes.)
- Je Hoon. - It's Won Hee.
- Je Hoon, you've still got it. - Won Hee.
(Lee Je Hoon, Im Won Hee)
Gosh, the petty thieves...
(The crime they are planning...)
- smelled the money. - They are grave robbers.
(is tomb robbery.)
- Okay! - Hang in there, Won Hee!
(They fight fiercely to get a chance to rob tombs.)
I guess there are only 1 or 2.
(With the gut feelings of tomb robbers, )
- I'm sure this is genuine. - What should I steal?
(they have to find as much treasure as possible in a given time.)
I think some of us are the police officers.
(They have to elude the police to get the treasure.)
- What? - Are you the police?
- Hang on. - Tell me if you're the police.
(They have only one chance.)
I'll betray them.
(Will you betray...)
- I'll betray them. - Aren't you the police?
(the tomb robbers or the police?)
No, I'm not. I'm serious.
(After a series of betrayals, )
- It's begun. - Catch him. Rip it off.
(who will end up with the treasure?)
You're indeed a tomb robber.
(Robber versus Robber: Faceless King of Tomb Robbery)