- Hello, you're here.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Are you all right?
- How are you feeling?
- He sprained his ankle.
- I've never...
- Is it swollen?
- sprained my ankle...
this way before.
Is it swollen or not?
The swelling isn't that bad.
Let's not play soccer in this show.
Jong Kook just gets carried away.
(He can't hold back his desire
to win when he sees a ball.)
In Running Man, I think a day
like today is a good chance for me.
Because Jong Kook is injured?
- Today is the day.
- I just can't help it.
Today...
I don't know why we're
being like this. I know it's bad.
- But I just can't help it.
- His upper body is just fine.
It's not like I'm dying.
In fact, it's not a good chance.
You just can't beat him.
This is crazy.
You've got an invitation card.
- What is it?
- Would you like to open it?
- Isn't So Min coming today?
- So Min is coming.
She's coming back today.
So Min planned something.
What is she doing now?
- What is So Min up to?
- Seok Jin.
- What's wrong with your face?
- What about my face?
Did you get hit or something?
What's going on?
I'm tired from yesterday.
I was sound asleep on my way here.
"What's wrong with your face?"
That's hilarious.
- What happened to you?
- I mean...
The thing is...
Earlier today, Seok Jin...
kept talking about his face,
but Jae Seok didn't care.
And he suddenly started talking
about it as the camera is turned on.
That's what I do.
- Hey.
- Right. He didn't say anything.
Why would I talk
when the camera is off?
You're up anyway.
- That's right.
- I know.
You're so healthy.
- I sprang up in my car.
- Okay.
It says invitation.
"Hi, guys. I've got
a life-changing chance."
"There's this fantastic land where
I can dig up huge diamonds."
"The town even has
the Immortal Heart..."
"which is the world's
most precious diamond."
"Isn't it amazing? Let's go fall for
the charm of the diamond together."
- What is this?
- It's like So Min's handwriting.
(It's like So Min's handwriting.)
What? Hang on.
What are you talking about?
- It's obvious that it's typed out.
- It's just typed out.
Just let it go.
His eyes are all puffy.
Look at his eyes.
Everything he says is fake.
- Seriously.
- What's your true face?
- I got goosebumps.
- Oh, dear.
The person who invited you guys
is waiting in there.
- Really?
- Isn't it So Min?
- You'll find out once you get in.
It must be So Min.
- Bo Pil wouldn't tell us yet.
- Stop it.
We know that already.
It'd be strange
if I pretended not to know it.
You don't have to pretend
not to know about it.
Just don't talk about it.
It's stranger that you said
it's So Min's handwriting.
It gave me goosebumps too.
I'm still half asleep.
This feels awkward.
It feels like
I'm starting all over again.
It feels like the first day
I joined Running Man.
(Who's the mysterious woman
waiting for the members?)
What should I do? I'm so nervous.
Why am I feeling nervous?
My heart is pounding.
(The members are slowly
coming to So Min.)
They're here.
(And So Min waits for them.)
(She tucks her hair
behind her ears.)
This is it. So Min, why are you
sitting with your back against us?
- So Min.
- Hey, So Min.
(As soon as they get here,)
(she goes over the top.)
(What are you doing?)
- So Min.
- Hey, So Min.
Have you been doing well?
So Min's back.
- It's So Min.
- So Min.
(They are happy to meet again.)
Hey, So Min.
- You look much better now.
- You look healthier.
- You look a lot better now.
- You look better.
She really does.
- Hey.
- You did something.
Why do you keep drawing
your hair back over your ears?
Women become prettier
when they are sick.
- Is that it?
- Sure.
- Hello. Hi, Ji Hyo.
- It's nice to see you again.
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
So Min is back.
It's so good to see you again.
There are celebrities here.
They all are celebrities.
- You guys look like celebrities.
- So Min.
Your hair has grown a lot.
Your face has got smaller.
- I lost a lot of weight.
- Your hair has grown a lot.
- You have hollow cheeks.
- All right then.
You should say hello
to our viewers first.
- It's been two months.
- It's been a long time.
It feels really awkward.
I didn't know
there were so many cameras.
- It's always been like this.
- You just took a short break.
- He's right.
- What are you talking about?
So Min, you know we won't be
welcoming you like this for long.
I don't want you
to pay attention to me.
- I feel really uncomfortable.
- Just say hello then.
Hello, everyone. Well...
- Say hello to them.
- Hello.
- What are you doing?
- She feels awkward.
- She's feeling awkward.
- Just say it.
If you feel awkward like that...
What's wrong with her?
Those who are watching us...
might want to change the channel.
- They'd feel awkward too.
- Right.
Hello, viewers. I'm Jeon So Min.
(She says hello cheerfully.)
I heard So Min has changed...
- the course of her life.
- Is that true?
I'm born again.
Like how?
- I think...
- It'd be fun to watch it.
- It won't last for long though.
- That's not true.
What's the change
in your mental attitude?
People don't change easily.
I realized the importance
of my acquaintances.
Now I can tell who truly loves...
and cares about me.
Is that it?
What has changed?
You just sound terrifying.
- You mean people around you?
- Even in this group.
In this small group, there are
people who care about me,
- and...
- She has a list.
- She has her own rankings.
- I told you before.
She's got Death Note.
I checked who called
or texted me how many times.
- Hey.
- The frequency doesn't show...
how much we care about you.
We just call you
on a periodic basis...
only when we are
truly worried about you.
- Sure.
- It's different.
I also remember...
who called me a lot at first
and let up later on.
- I won't mention the names though.
- She's specific.
Look at her.
- It's interesting.
- I know.
A certain someone called me
less and less as time went by.
Are you looking at that person?
(So Min's eyes are fixed
on that certain someone.)
By the way,
Se Chan said the other day...
So Min did all five things women do
that give men the wrong idea...
- I saw it.
- to him.
You saw it? What did you think?
(So Min did all five things to me.)
(So Min did all five things
that give men the wrong idea.)
(Se Chan argued that's why
he ended up getting the wrong idea.)
When did I do those things to you?
- We can find it.
- You're mistaken.
- Everything was filmed.
- I never did those things.
You did all those things
while shooting Running Man.
- So Min, you did those things.
- What I did is...
just smile at him.
But from his point of view,
I must look like this.
I've never given him
a big smile once.
- This is driving me crazy.
- The thing is,
he must look at me
through a filter or something.
(Video assistant referee)
(Sometimes, she acted
like a big sister.)
like a girlfriend.)
(Little by little, Se Chan
got used to this forced romance.)
(So Min calls Se Chan's name
in a nasal voice.)
(The video assistant referee
proves Se Chan's innocence.)
Did you ask Se Chan,
"Are there any guys like you?"
- You did.
- Did you?
You said, "Set me up
with a guy like you."
I did, but I didn't say that
to you only.
I said that to all the other guys.
- But you did say that to me.
- I said that to Jae Seok too.
Have you ever asked me,
"Are you up?"
Have you?
- I have.
- Right?
Why did you say
you never did those things to me?
- You did all those things.
- She did.
- I say that to my friends too.
- Still...
- You gave me the wrong idea.
- Of course.
You guys appreciate each other
more now. That's what's important.
(Teasing)
- Of course.
- There he goes again.
- He's at it again.
- You know...
Even when things are going well,
Haha can ruin everything.
- He ruins everything.
- Definitely.
Ji Hyo called you a lot, right?
Ji Hyo...
called me and texted me
really often.
More often than anyone else.
The funny thing is,
after the articles...
about my break were published,
we talked on the phone,
and she said,
"So Min, why are you not here yet?"
"When are you coming?"
I thought, "Hold on."
(Ji Hyo never checks the news.)
I realized that Ji Hyo really
doesn't use the internet often.
You should understand her.
I called her six days ago,
and she hasn't called me back yet.
It's been six days,
We even shot together after that,
but she hasn't called me back.
Ji Hyo sometimes surprises me.
But when you're sick,
she's really nice to you.
- Right.
- When I injured my leg,
I had to protect my cast
in the shower,
- Gosh.
- and she sent me something.
I thought you said
she helped you take a shower.
Why would she?
- Why would she?
- He did this.
- In the shower...
- I mean she sent me a cast cover.
I didn't understand what he meant.
I mean a cast cover.
- She sent it to me.
- "Turn around."
She didn't help me take a shower.
If you want Ji Hyo's attention,
you should get sick.
- If you want her attention...
- She's like Nightingale.
Can we talk about
the invitation now?
- Oh, what is that?
- Oh, right.
Who sent it? We can find diamonds?
The invitation is
from So Min, right?
- Yes, that's right.
- Are you into fantasy now?
- I mean...
- Hey.
- I saw this.
- What's that?
This flyer...
- This is why I called you here.
- Read the flyer.
- What's this?
- Gems?
- Gems are buried in the ground?
Gujeon Village?
"There is a village where
gems are buried in the ground."
"Find the world's most valuable
diamond, Immortal Heart,"
- "and your life will be fantastic."
- Really?
If you think of a scarecrow
in a golden field,
a village will come to your mind.
It's Gujeon Village.
It is the only village in
the country where gems are buried.
There will be a local festival
this year too.
Also, the world's most valuable
and mysterious diamond,
Immortal Heart, is supposed to be
buried in the ground too.
That's why the village is visited
by so many people every year.
Why don't you visit the village...
and try your luck?
There are gems
buried in this village.
Gems?
So what is this?
Simply put,
it's a local festival.
The gems you dig up...
- will be exchanged with money.
- Really?
- With money?
- Do you mean real money?
- Real money?
- It's supposed to be a bonanza.
Yes, we're giving out cash today.
- We can get cash?
- Can we have it?
Yes, you can get cash.
- Really?
I don't believe it.
- These days...
- We can dig up gems?
It's called the Immortal Heart.
- I'm getting interested.
- Does this make sense?
Let me see.
Since everyone is here,
we prepared a nice brunch.
- Really?
- Enjoy.
- As soon as we start?
- We can already eat?
- It looks nice.
- Look at this.
- It's salmon.
- It's chicken breasts.
- It's my favorite.
Thank you.
Oh, my.
This looks delicious.
- Thank you.
- Unbelievable.
There are pizzas too.
They must be fresh out of
the oven. They look delicious.
- Let's eat.
- This is nice.
- This is delicious.
- This tastes so good.
This feels weird, right?
I was taking a shower with
Seok Jin and Se Chan after soccer,
and Seok Jin's showerhead
kept turning to the side.
- He could just turn it back.
- Right.
But he just followed the water...
until his bottom almost touched me.
He obviously wanted me to move.
- He came so close to me...
- Seriously.
instead of turning his showerhead.
- He could just turn it.
- He didn't?
He didn't.
I'm disappointed in him.
His body almost touched me.
At his age, it's hard to change.
It is.
Unless he's born again...
(Seok Jin can't refute.)
I don't think he'll be born again
as a human.
I want to be born
as a poisonous mushroom.
Aren't mushrooms fungi?
Why do you want to be born again
as a poisonous mushroom?
Then I won't die alone.
(Creepy)
- So Min hasn't changed a bit.
- I have.
- She hasn't.
- Didn't you say you'd be different?
- It's not like that.
Then you won't die alone?
She's become so mean.
Everyone was quiet for two seconds.
- You scared me.
- But she has a point.
Ji Hyo, what do you want to be
in your next life?
- Me?
- Yes.
I want to be a rock.
(I want to be a rock.)
(Ji Hyo wants to be a rock
in her next life.)
- A rock?
- I won't ask why.
- It suits you.
A rock?
She's a bit like a rock
in this life too.
- That was so funny.
- A rock?
She wants to be a rock?
That's hilarious.
- But you didn't laugh.
- I laughed a lot.
I can't believe him.
Please be honest just once.
You didn't even laugh.
Why do you say it's hilarious?
- He confuses me.
- I laughed a lot.
Nothing he says is true.
He didn't laugh at all.
This is a bit too cheesy.
You've been only eating cheese
the whole time. Why do you say that?
You've been only eating cheese.
- In the morning...
- Cheese...
I like eating cheesy food
in the morning.
Of course.
Of course I laughed.
Let me try this.
Didn't you say
the food was too cheesy?
- What are you really thinking?
- He only eats cheese.
You confuse me.
Please make me like you.
(What does Seok Jin really think?)
By the way, why are they
feeding us so much?
- This is all we'll eat all day.
- Because we work hard?
So Min, did you plan this episode?
- What?
- Did you plan this episode?
No, I just read the flyer.
- Really?
- I thought you invited us.
This is strange, right?
(There's no way they'll only
dig up gems on Running Man.)
- I love this, but...
- Because we work hard?
We're going to dig up gems?
- It's crowded in here.
- Yes.
- Right.
- Right?
Did you find something?
(Kwang Soo reads the flyer
carefully.)
- We're to find the Immortal Heart.
- The Immortal Heart.
What could this be?
There must be hints hidden here.
Try reading it vertically.
I've already tried it.
- "Ground, ground, world..."
- Try reading it vertically.
"Ground, ground, world..."
Why are these words colored?
- This...
- Gems...
- Why is "gems" colored?
- Right?
The Immortal Heart...
- So Min, why did you take it?
- Why did you take it?
It's mine.
You said you'd be different.
It's not like that.
- We were reading it.
- I'm different.
- Why did you...
- Why did you become so mean?
You're getting greedy again.
- I'm nice now.
- I already...
felt it while talking to her.
- I'm nice now.
- She hasn't changed a bit.
- Why...
- So Min, are you having fun?
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
- I'm excited.
- Let us read it.
You can read it.
- Why can't I read it?
- I can read it?
- Kwang Soo can't read it.
- Why not me?
- Move.
You're out.
Why not me?
- Yesterday...
- I'm the only one who can read it.
- Why are you doing this?
- I'll read it later.
- Yesterday...
- Why not me?
Yesterday, I realized that So Min...
Guys, did you feel it too?
I'm talking to myself.
No one is listening.
No one is listening to Seok Jin.
It's okay.
They're talking.
I shouldn't have cut in.
- I think it's your fault too.
- It's my fault.
The ones who called me often
get to read it first.
- Okay.
- I think it's your fault too.
- Thank you.
- Why are you doing this?
- This is driving me crazy.
- You let Haha read it?
- Show us too.
- That brat?
So Min, you're going to
betray us again, right?
What are you talking about? Today...
We all...
- It's supposed to be a bonanza.
- Really?
Don't you want to start
digging already?
We'll find so many gems.
- In movies,
- Okay.
people often die one by one
in a remote place.
- That's right.
- There are many movies like that.
I think the first one to die...
will be either Haha or Seok Jin.
(Haha or Seok Jin will die first.)
That's when the movie starts
for real.
I think I'll be
the 2nd or 3rd person to die.
Also, couples always
go deep into the mountains...
- to kiss and die.
- That's right.
- They die as soon as they kiss.
- And...
I know how Seok Jin will die.
He dies while doing
something forbidden.
- Right, he'll do that.
- You know what I mean?
"I don't care. I'll do it anyway."
- Bang!
- Exactly.
- Or while peeing alone.
- Right.
Ms. Rock will survive the longest.
Right, because she doesn't
say anything.
- She could be a criminal too.
- Right.
It's so funny
that she wants to be a rock.
Right, it suits her.
I laughed so hard.
I want to be born again as me.
- One more time?
- Yes.
As you?
That's incredible.
- You want to be yourself again.
- That's so cool.
Kwang Soo, what about you?
A basketball player.
- A spoon worm.
- A spoon worm?
- Who wants to be a spoon worm?
- You'll definitely be a spoon worm.
- You'll be caught in Busan.
- A spoon worm?
You'll then be eaten by me
at a sashimi restaurant.
- Right.
- Must you put it that way?
Why not?
Nice and chewy.
- A spoon worm?
- A spoon worm.
- I'll enjoy it too.
- Spoon worms are good.
(After a 10-minute ride,
they arrive at the village.)
What now?
- Over there.
- What's that?
- "Kim Sang Yeob"?
- There's something here.
- I'm getting a headache.
- What's this?
They don't waste any time, do they?
Must we start digging
the moment we exit the van?
- I'm already getting a headache.
- What's going on?
- As soon as we got here...
- I'm already getting a headache.
I wonder what's here.
(It seems like
an ordinary rural village.)
(However, an eerie vibe
can be detected.)
(Padlocks can be seen everywhere.)
(The village seems ordinary,
but it isn't.)
(What events will take place here?)
Wait, what's this?
- Why are we here today?
- Hello.
- It's a village.
- Hi.
- Digging up gems...
Hello and welcome.
- Hi.
- We're at a village.
- Hello.
- Welcome to Gujeon Village.
- The village head.
- Is he the village head?
- I'm the chairman of the youth.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you.
(Park Cheong Nyeon, chairman
of the young village people)
(He shows visitors around who
are here to dig up the gems.)
(He's the youngest resident
of this village.)
- Chairman of the youth?
- Yes.
- Did you hear that?
- Are you sure?
Yes, that's right.
You should first
sanitize your hands.
Are you here to dig up the diamonds?
I heard that
there are diamonds everywhere.
That's right. Every time you dig,
- you'll find a diamond.
- Really?
(Dozens of diamonds
are supposedly buried in the field.)
The most valuable gem...
- is the red diamond.
- Red?
- The one called the Immortal Heart.
- It's called the Immortal Heart.
So you already know.
Word got out that the diamond
could change your life.
(Finding the Immortal Heart
will change your life.)
Anyway, our proud gem field
is that way.
- There are some people digging.
- Right.
You can get digging too.
Why aren't you also
digging with the others?
- I mean...
- You must already have a lot.
I may not have the touch
because I'm never lucky.
- I see.
- So it's not easy.
- They're not easy to dig.
- It's not easy at all.
- You need a bit of luck.
- Yes, exactly.
Can we get digging then?
Yes, you can.
Once you dig up the gems,
you will take them to the pawnshop.
(Pawnshop)
- There it is.
- Right.
- So there...
- We can cash them in?
- Yes, straight into cash.
- Really?
If you get hungry
or thirsty while digging,
you can head to the stall
to buy snacks.
- Got it.
- Now, please take your tools.
- You can then get digging.
- Sure.
I can't believe this.
I don't know what to expect today.
(Will they be able to find
the Immortal Heart?)
There are a lot of people here.
- Look at all these people.
- Now I'm getting greedy.
- Hello.
- I'm getting a weird feeling.
Are the gems randomly spread out?
- Hello.
- Goodness, hello.
Have you dug up any gems?
- Did you find the red diamond?
- Have you gotten lucky?
- What does it look like?
- We haven't seen it either.
Please let us see it
if you come across one.
- Exactly.
- The red diamond.
- Have you not dug it up?
- The Immortal Heart.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- I doubt there's anything here.
- They haven't gotten lucky.
Are you residents of this village?
- No.
- Are you outsiders?
- We came after hearing the rumors.
- Where are you from?
- We heard about the diamonds.
- So you came to dig them up?
- Yes.
- You all have name tags though.
Are you sisters?
- Yes, sisters.
- You four are all sisters.
(Kim Il Nyeo, Kim E Nyeo,
Kim Sam Nyeo, Kim Sa Nyeo)
(Four sisters, non-residents)
(They all dig in order
to find the diamonds.)
There must be
a few things buried here.
It's getting hot though.
But it was chilly all day.
We were told to dig
because there's something here.
- There probably is.
- How deep should we dig?
Let's see.
Are you sure
there are diamonds here?
Are they even here?
I thought we just had to dig?
There's nothing here.
Are you sure they're buried here?
- Right?
- Did you find something?
Hold on.
What is it?
It's nothing.
- Why?
- What is it?
Did you find something?
(It's just a rock.)
- It's only a rock.
- Seriously?
Hey, you found Ji Hyo.
A rock. That's you, Ji Hyo.
Look how big it is.
I was startled too.
(What's Ji Hyo doing here?)
Ji Hyo!
(She said it to a rock.)
That's huge.
Can't you guys just leave me alone?
Ji Hyo's everywhere.
(Ji Hyo's buried everywhere.)
This is odd though.
Are you sure there are gems here?
It doesn't make sense that
gems would be buried here.
(Not even the 4 sisters
have been successful.)
- What's this?
- My gosh!
(My gosh!)
- He must've found one.
- I found one.
- Really?
- He did!
(He finally finds a gem.)
- It was there.
- They really must be buried here.
- Let me see.
- They're really buried here.
- It's true.
- Let's get digging.
- This wasn't a hoax.
- Look at him.
- You've all gone crazy.
- It's red!
They're really here.
Anyway, I'll head to the pawnshop.
- The rumors were true.
- I wonder how much it's worth.
It was really here.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
What do you have for me?
(Jeon Dang Po, a master haggler)
- I found a gem.
- Really?
Let me take a look.
(His hopes are up.)
- But it's quite big.
- You're not kidding.
Since you're my first customer,
I'll give you a good bargain.
(A chance to change one's life)
(How much is this gem worth?)
- Three dollars.
- What?
- But it's a gem.
- Three dollars.
- I'll take it then.
- Good.
- Here you go.
- Got it.
Thank you.
Bring me another and
I'll give you another good bargain.
I mean...
Three dollars for a gem?
(It's too cheap for a gem.)
(He's pleased to have
found a gem though.)
- How much was it?
- What?
Did you cash it in?
You'll be surprised
by what it's worth.
- Really?
- You'll be shocked.
I'm switching to a pickax.
I see you're all busy digging.
My body will
ache all over tomorrow.
I'm going crazy now that
I know there are gems here.
This is why
we were fed this morning.
(It's why they were
given breakfast.)
- Found it!
- Really?
- Where?
- I found one!
- Where was it?
- I found a gem.
Many must be buried over there.
- Nice!
- Are they all over there?
- Was it buried deep?
- No.
(They couldn't be more jealous.)
You don't have to dig that deep.
Really?
Is that the pawnshop?
I want to check out the stall first.
And then I'll head to the pawnshop.
Hello.
- Welcome.
- Do you only take cash?
And the gem must be cashed in
at the pawnshop?
- Are you here to dig up the gems?
- Yes.
- You can get anything you want.
- I'm just here to look.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- They're on the pricier side.
- Really?
- Anyway, I'll be back.
- Sure.
(Kim Ga Ge, stall owner,
doesn't intend to sell anything)
Was it buried deep?
You don't have to dig deep.
- Found one!
- What?
- I...
- It's blue.
I bet you haven't seen
a blue one before.
It's a real gem.
It's also known
as an angel's teardrop.
- An angel's teardrop?
- That's not it.
It's the Immortal Heart.
You have your chance now.
- Hurry over to the pawnshop.
- Get going.
- Here.
- Let me see.
I bet you haven't
seen one like this before.
- What is it?
- It's a diamond,
also known as an angel's teardrop.
- Isn't this the Tear of Yondu?
- It isn't.
- Hold on.
- It's blue.
You brought me a precious kind.
- It's quite valuable.
- But it's covered in scratches.
- Look at the scratches.
- Since it's a precious one,
I'll give you a dollar for it.
He said a dollar.
It has too many scratches on it.
But that's not my fault.
You should've brought me one
without any scratches.
Off you go.
Get digging again.
I was hoping for a lot
since it's a gem, but a dollar...
(Kwang Soo can't seem to walk away.)
What can I do with a dollar anyway?
Where's the stall?
(He heads to the stall
with a dollar.)
- What?
- Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo!)
Are you here to dig up gems too?
(Someone seems happy
to see Kwang Soo.)
- The Immortal Heart.
- Yes?
- Isn't that what you're after?
- Yes, the red diamond.
(Kwang Soo talks to a mystery woman
for quite some time.)
Thank you.
(Then he heads to someplace.)
The pink container building?
The pink container building...
Why is he running over there?
- Where is he going?
- Where... Hey!
(They detect that something is up
and chase after him.)
He must have new information.
Is this the place?
(He finds a new field
behind the pink container building.)
- Must I dig again?
- Let's follow them.
Don't bother.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
Let's get over there.
- But wait...
- I'm heading over there.
- Come on.
- Come with us too.
Don't force me.
- Let's go.
- I'm going to keep digging here.
What's going on?
Why did they head over there?
Kwang Soo suddenly ran over there.
(Kwang Soo starts digging.)
Jae Seok.
How did you know to follow me?
You don't know yet, do you?
- Know what?
- The Immortal Heart is buried here.
- Really?
- Yes.
(The Immortal Heart is buried here.)
- Really?
- Yes.
A local resident told me.
It's no use digging over there.
What is it?
- Hurry on over.
- Get digging.
(Se Chan joins them.)
Whoever finds it
must split the money though.
- Of course.
- Now everyone's here.
- We'll dig too.
- We're here to dig as well.
Promise that
you'll split the money though.
If only there's anything here.
Until when must we dig?
Jae Seok, Kwang Soo
talked to a woman earlier.
- What?
- She told me...
that the Immortal Heart was here.
She was wearing a white hanbok.
- A white hanbok?
- Yes.
Her name is Kwang Ja though.
- She had a name?
- Really?
I wonder who she is.
(Jong Kook was on
his way to the pawnshop.)
(He spots a mysterious woman
and sees her name.)
Kwang Ja? That name...
Kwang Soo!
(Just like Jong Kook saw...)
(The mysterious woman's name
is Lee Kwang Ja.)
Her name is Kwang Ja though.
- She had a name?
- Really?
- Is she your sister?
- Is she family?
Who's Kwang Ja? Tell us.
I don't know who she is.
She said she lives here.
I find Kwang Soo strange.
He was with her.
I swear it's not me today.
I swear it's not me.
Why is her name Kwang Ja then?
I didn't see her name tag.
I didn't know she was Kwang Ja.
I find it so strange
that you didn't see her name tag.
That's strange.
That's the first thing I saw.
- Okay.
- Right?
- Anyway...
- I didn't see it.
Kwang Soo made us
all come here, right?
Is it possible he lured us here...
- so that he can do something else?
- That's true.
- Maybe there's nothing here.
- No way.
- What is it?
I'm not certain either,
but she told me.
- She lives here.
- She was Kwang Ja.
He's avoiding our eyes.
(Name: Lee Kwang Ja, occupation
and characteristic unknown)
There's nothing.
- There's nothing here.
- There's nothing.
We kept digging,
and there's nothing.
- That was false information.
- We went deep.
- What is it?
- He found it.
(He found
the Immortal Heart gem box!)
He got it.
- He knew the location.
- I'm sure.
- There must be a gem for real.
- It's okay.
- What's this?
- It's a red diary.
This is the Immortal Diamond.
It's a red diamond.
- You found it?
- Can I see too?
- Hold on.
- It's a red diamond.
Please don't get close.
Can I touch it?
Get closer.
- Don't touch it.
- I won't.
- We'll watch.
- Hurry.
- I saw something shiny.
Open it with the key.
- There's no key.
- There isn't.
If it's a real gem, you get
good energy when you touch it.
- If it's a real gem?
- Really?
- Oh, no. Wait.
- Don't touch it.
I'll only touch it.
- Show us.
- Touch it.
- I can't open it.
- Find it.
- If you touch it...
- They said...
- you get good energy.
- Just by touching it?
- Come here. Let me touch it.
- Let me touch it.
- No, wait.
Did you find it?
Let me touch it.
You get good energy
when you touch it.
What do you think?
Do you feel energized already?
- I'm not sure.
- Let me touch it.
- Why?
- My gosh.
- Do you feel it?
- We found it.
- Don't take it.
- Hey!
(At that moment!)
(Kim Sa Nyeo steals the box
and runs away!)
Sa Nyeo!
What is she doing?
You can't take it.
She's a thief!
- What are you doing?
- She's a thief.
This is good, so I want to
bring it home for my husband.
- Why did you take it?
- You can't!
- I want to let my husband touch it.
- Kwang Soo found it.
You can't take it.
Why?
Fine.
I was just fooling around with you.
- We just wanted to touch it.
- She was fooling around with you.
- I'm sure.
- There's no key.
We have no key.
- Il Nyeo,
- Why do they want this?
- let's so somewhere else.
- Let's go take a rest.
- Let's go somewhere else.
- We have no key,
- so there's no point having this.
- I know.
He met Kwang Ja
in front of the supermarket.
- Let's go there.
- Let's go over first.
- Let's find out why.
- Ji Hyo, hold onto this.
But I found it.
It doesn't even matter.
Still.
- I found it.
- That's true.
- Sure.
- There's a supermarket.
We have to meet her to resolve this.
- There she is.
- There's a supermarket.
- Kwang Ja is over there.
- It's her.
Hello.
- We found it.
- You're back.
We found it.
What's that?
- We found it.
- Can I have it?
- Maybe not.
- She's Kwang Ja.
- She talks weird.
She sounds just like you.
I sound like her?
What are you talking about?
- You sound like her.
- Do you know about the key?
Do you know where it is?
Well, I don't know much,
but the village head
knows everything.
Where's the village head?
Where is he?
The village head is over there!
Over there?
There must be a village head.
We have to find him.
- Thank you.
- Thanks a lot.
Their names are so similar.
Lee Kwang Ja.
It's a coincidence.
She's not related to me.
Hey, she won't do that
if she's not related to you.
The village head. Village head!
- He's over here.
- It's him!
He's over there.
Mr. Choi!
(Name: Choi Yi Jang)
(Characteristic: village head, knows
most secrets, has early dementia)
Mr. Choi?
- What's wrong?
- Mr. Choi.
- Mr. Choi!
- He's in a wheelchair.
- Is it you?
- Hello, sir.
Who are you?
- We're visitors.
- Are you guys visiting?
Yes, sir.
We're here to find gems,
and we dug this up.
Do you know where the key is
by any chance?
What is that?
Do you not know what this is?
That?
Isn't that a brand name chocolate?
- It's not chocolate.
- It's not.
- You know about the field, right?
- It's a gem field.
- There's a gem field.
Who said that?
I don't know anything about it.
Sir, do you know any of us?
(Glancing)
He looked at you.
He looked at Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin, he looked at you.
- He looked at you.
- It was him.
- Why are you pointing at me?
- Is he your friend from school?
- Elementary school friend?
(Elementary school friend?)
- Say, "Nice to meet you, friend."
- Do it.
- "Nice to meet you, friend."
I don't know.
Nice to meet you, friend.
(Nice to meet you, friend.)
- Goodness!
- He's not.
(They're not school friends.)
Then sir.
Where can we find the key?
My memory is faint.
- I don't know.
- I'll give you some gems.
My gosh. What's wrong with you?
I can't, right?
Every word you say is awful.
Hey, this is not that kind of world.
Stop bothering me! Go away!
He didn't answer anything.
- But this...
- I already told you.
I don't know,
so I have nothing more to say.
- Okay.
- We'll get going.
- We're leaving.
- Excuse us.
There's something.
There's nothing!
Why is he so angry?
You get angry once every minute.
- He's strange.
- It's bad for your health, sir.
- We'll get going.
- We're leaving.
- Thank you, sir.
- Mr. Choi.
- Good luck.
- I wish you good health.
- He's the worst.
- Why would you say "Good luck"?
Why would you say "Good luck"?
I wish you good health, sir.
(They leave without obtaining
any useful information.)
Should we divide ourselves
into teams?
Let's split and look.
- I'll go with Kwang Soo.
- No, I will.
I'll go with him.
Wait. Why am I so popular?
- I have nothing!
- Let's go.
- Kwang Soo.
- Then...
I'll go with one of you.
- I'll go with you.
- Let's go.
- Leave!
- Okay, I'm going by myself.
(Se Chan is looking for the key
by himself.)
What's the R mark?
(What's the R mark?)
I can hear them. What?
(What?)
(He seems to have found something.)
- What is it?
- It's nothing.
- Why?
Stop being so cheap.
(He goes somewhere in a hurry.)
- Stop being so cheap.
- What's this?
What's this?
(He finds
a mysterious gem box.)
What's this?
What's that? He found something.
- Hey!
- Don't speak so loudly.
- Don't say it!
- I have to carry it around.
- I have no key.
- I'm curious.
Let me see. I'm only going to look.
- Haha!
- Look at this, Haha.
- What's that?
- We don't know.
- He found it.
- Where did you find it?
- Down there.
You two are amazing
when you're a team.
Here he goes again.
Love power?
(Is this love power?)
I knew you were going to mention it.
- He found it by himself.
- Hey.
Hold her hand. Stop running off.
There's something over there.
- Where?
- Up there.
- By the scarecrow.
- Did you see it?
There's something up there.
Don't do it.
Inside...
What's this?
Did you find something?
Let me see.
- "I had fun with my friends today."
- "With my friends today."
- "He watched us pleasantly."
- What?
(I had fun with my friends today.
He watched us pleasantly.)
Remember the gems from earlier?
They had colors.
Right?
They were all different colors.
Right. There were purple,
- pink, and yellow.
- Right?
These match the colors of the gems.
- Right, Ji Hyo?
- You're right.
Right? These are the colors
of the gems.
- Gems from earlier.
- Red too.
The writing.
Let's get going, Ji Hyo.
There's a scarecrow here too.
Is this the children?
- It's not, right?
- I don't think so.
There's a scarecrow over there too.
Where?
(There are scarecrows
all over the village.)
Is this pink?
What's the color of this hat?
There are too many colors.
- On this hat.
- There's nothing.
It looks kind of frightening.
Why are the pants down?
Is that Kwang Soo?
He takes his pants off all the time.
Maybe it does have something to do
with Kwang Soo.
(They are suspicious of Kwang Soo
for several reasons.)
- There's a safe.
- Where?
- This is a safe.
- There's a safe?
(Meanwhile, Se Chan and So Min...)
(find a safe...)
It's on the right.
(on the 2nd floor of
the village head's house.)
- My gosh.
- So Min.
- What?
- We need a passcode.
- It's locked.
Don't press random numbers.
You'll get locked out.
You'll lock it.
What are you doing?
- Sorry?
- We did nothing.
Are you thieves?
- No, we're not.
- No.
Why are you in my house?
- I'm sorry.
- It's the old man.
Get lost before I kick you out!
Okay. Sorry, sir.
(Is the safe keeping a secret?)
He's mad.
So Min.
Sir.
Why do you think...
I can't sell this?
The pawnshop won't take it.
What's this?
It's a gem.
I dug it up from the field.
It's chocolate.
Se Chan...
- Se Chan.
- It's chocolate.
- It's chocolate?
- Yes, it's chocolate.
- It's chocolate.
- Se Chan.
- I'm using the bathroom.
- There's something strange.
He keeps looking for chocolate.
(Se Chan, there's something strange.
He keeps looking for chocolate.)
(He mentioned chocolate
earlier too.)
- How much do you have?
- What?
- I have one gem.
Should I get chocolate?
I'll get chocolate.
- But it's two dollars.
- What?
- It's two dollars.
- I'm going to exchange it.
- No, you need money.
- Do you have money?
- Hold on.
- Let's go together.
He keeps looking for chocolate.
Is the scarecrow hiding something?
This is strange.
(Seok Jin searches
around the scarecrow.)
Seok Jin, shall we go
into the building?
- Let's go inside the building.
- Let's do that.
Even if we find the key...
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
Just tell me the truth.
What are you up to today?
- I'm not doing anything.
- Are you sure?
Really?
(They go into the house
looking for the key.)
- Why?
- What's this?
(Kwang Soo found a box that
looks like what Se Chan found.)
This is amazing.
Let me keep this with me.
Seok Jin.
We are on the same boat.
- Sure. We're a team.
- Seriously.
- Okay.
- You know what I mean.
- Gosh, this is...
- We should never be apart.
- Feeling! Intuition! Cross!
If you and I work together,
we will definitely win this race.
Seok Jin, we should
have one of this each.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
What is this? There are things
here and there in the house.
There are a lot of things.
What is this?
I guess it's just a sheet of paper.
I think it's a clue.
How should I open this?
I need a key.
(And Kwang Soo watches him
look for the key.)
(Shouting)
(Seok Jin suddenly cries out.)
(Ripping)
(And the thing that's left
in the spot where Seok Jin was...)
(Victim)
(Meanwhile, Haha is...)
It's not working.
It doesn't work.
(Haha is doing something
with the gem boxes.)
(By the way, does he have a key?)
(What's the key that Haha has?)
- But we don't have money.
- I have gems.
You can't use the gems.
(Se Chan and So Min go to buy
chocolate for the village head.)
Gosh, what is this?
What's this?
They're not here.
- They're gone.
- Victims?
- Are they dead?
- They're the people we met earlier.
Who tore off the name tags?
Who's doing this?
(Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, Sa Nyeo are gone
with their name tags left here.)
Is someone tearing off
the name tags?
I guess so.
There are victims.
(Their name tags say victim
on the other side.)
Hang on.
Someone's running around
tearing off the name tags.
- Take them.
- They are the ladies...
- we met earlier, right?
- Yes. Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, and Sa Nyeo.
The three of them
lost their name tags.
Where's the rest?
Right. Sa Nyeo.
- No, Sam Nyeo is not here.
- It's Sam Nyeo.
We don't have Sam Nyeo's name tag.
(Sam Nyeo's name is not here.)
(Sam Nyeo was left alone while
the other three went to Kwang Soo.)
Let's go, So Min.
(Where did Kim Sam Nyeo go?)
Excuse me.
Did you see Seok Jin?
- Who's Seok Jin?
- Oh, right.
(Screaming)
What's going on?
Why? What's wrong?
Gosh, what's that?
Haha!
What is this? What's going on?
(Kwang Ja is lying on the ground,
and Haha is there.)
- She tried to rip off my name tag.
- Haha!
- Who is that?
She kept trying
to rip off my name tag.
(Kwang Soo sees Kwang Ja lying
on the floor without her name tag.)
She tried to tear off my name tag,
so I took hers.
(She tried to tear off my name tag,
so I took hers.)
She kept following me around.
- Why did you do that to Kwang Ja?
- It has nothing to do with you.
What's the deal between
Lee Kwang Soo and Lee Kwang Ja?
- I've never seen her before.
- Then why do you even care?
It's just strange.
- From up there...
- Mr. Choi kept watching you.
- I have nothing to do with her.
- It's just strange.
I have nothing to do with her.
- Later, you will...
- Why would you care about her?
I don't care about her.
You just took her name tag off.
- I don't know.
- You better watch out.
I don't know anything.
- Kwang Soo, did you find anything?
- Jae Seok.
- No?
- The thing is...
Haha eliminated Kwang Ja.
What?
Haha just eliminated Kwang Ja.
She was lying on the ground.
Why did he eliminate her?
I don't know.
She's lying on the ground now.
- Why did he eliminate her?
- Did you find anything?
I don't know.
Apparently, Kwang Ja attacked
Seok Jin and Haha.
- Really?
- Yes.
Where have you been?
Actually, there was...
- Hey.
- I was...
- What?
- I wasn't going to say this,
but you're being strange now.
I understand it looks suspicious.
But I don't have anything.
And...
- just now...
- Why does it have to be Kwang Ja?
I don't know that either.
So...
Jae Seok.
- You're going the wrong way.
- What are you up to?
I didn't do anything. I'm nothing.
I have nothing to do with
this village. I've never been here.
And in the pension
next to this building...
Get lost.
(Upset)
Okay. You're so doomed.
I don't know what it is,
but if there's a penalty,
you will definitely get it.
You'll get all wet.
I just said it involuntarily.
I just can't help it
when I see your face.
Do you want me to tell you?
- You know I didn't mean it.
- Okay.
I just said it before I knew it.
- Do you want me to tell you?
- Tell me.
I stopped it.
(He stopped his right hand
with his left hand.)
Before I knew it...
- You do a lot of strange things.
- I didn't mean to do it.
I just did it involuntarily.
I stopped it.
(I stopped it. Tell me, Kwang Soo.)
Tell me, Kwang Soo.
- Do I have to tell you this?
- Just tell me.
In the next building,
Seok Jin and I found a box.
- Really?
- There's another gem box.
- And does it need a key?
- Yes.
It's locked.
And it looks totally
different from this.
Actually, I found a photo here.
Look at you.
(What photo is it?)
(A little while ago)
(What?)
What's this?
(A group photo of villagers)
It looks like a family photo.
Kwang Ja is looking the other way.
(And what is Kwang Ja staring at?)
I guess there's a secret
about this village.
What's this?
Kwang Ja is looking the other way.
You're right.
- They are the villagers.
- He's the pawnbroker.
- This is Park Cheong Nyeon.
- Cheong Nyeon.
And she's the supermarket owner.
- And this is...
- He's the village head.
(What do Kwang Ja's eyes mean?)
Isn't this your house?
Why would it be my house?
Isn't this your village?
What are you talking about?
There must be something.
What's the thing Seok Jin found?
Why is Kwang Ja out?
- She didn't go there.
- Kwang Ja is lying down there.
Haha eliminated her.
It's not like that.
- Why did you eliminate her?
- Listen to me.
- Why did you do that?
- I'll tell you why.
She kept coming to me.
She shook a flower at my face...
and tried to tear off my name tag
as I turned around.
I was going to buy her something.
But she tried to tear it off.
So I took hers off.
- And she's out?
- Yes.
- She fell down when you did it?
Then he came to me.
- Do you know what he said to me?
- What did he say?
He sounded
as if I harmed his family.
"Why did you do it?"
It didn't sound anything like that.
"Why did you do that to Kwang Ja?"
- Why would you think that way?
- He kept talking to me like that.
- His family...
- No. That's enough, Haha.
I figured it out.
What are you doing?
What's up with you?
Why are you pretending
to be so sharp?
I'm the protagonist of this episode.
(I'm the protagonist
of this episode.)
- Why?
I feel like I should unravel
the whole mystery here.
We should eliminate him.
Isn't it strange?
(While they have
an exhausting conversation...)
Haha.
- We almost figured it out.
- What?
Did you see this, guys?
What's that? What's a victim?
The ladies are gone.
- Did you take them off?
- No. I found them on the ground.
- What's this?
- Haha, we need something sweet.
You and I should...
- get the village head something.
- To whom?
- You got money, didn't you?
- To the village head?
- If we get him some chocolate...
- He will give us a hint.
- What?
- We need chocolate.
How much is the chocolate?
It's one dollar.
One dollar? Thank you.
- Really?
- Excuse me.
How come you're all out
of tissue boxes?
Tissue boxes?
It's because of the virus.
People buy a lot of tissue
these days.
But I didn't get extra.
It's the only thing that's sold out.
- Why is it sold out?
- I told you.
It's because of the virus.
My gosh.
(Something's strange.)
What is this?
(Se Chan and So Min find something
on their way to the village head.)
- What is this ddakji?
- What's that?
(This ddakji is...)
(what Kwang Ja played with.)
It's a letter.
It says something. Let's go.
Read it.
(The letter says...)
"May 1, 2019."
"If what I found out is true,"
"those who were
tempted by the diamonds..."
"will soon be eliminated by him."
"Figure out a way to eliminate him
as soon as possible..."
"and share it with people."
(It's a reporter's note
about the elimination.)
- Does this say anything?
- No.
Then...
We will get eliminated
if we become greedy.
It says "those who were
tempted by the diamonds".
Jae Seok, I found a letter.
(I should tell them quickly.)
Who is it?
- I'm sure someone's here.
- There's someone.
- My gosh.
- What?
What's that sound?
- My gosh.
- What?
(Kwang Soo found...)
- Jae Seok.
- What?
(Seok Jin's name tag.)
Why?
(Is Seok Jin eliminated?)
What's that?
- What happened to Seok Jin?
- Look at this.
- What? Seok Jin.
- What's going on?
Seok Jin is a victim.
- Jae Seok.
- You mean Seok Jin?
I was right about that.
What I said in the car is right.
It's just like a movie.
- We will die one by one?
- I said we'd die one by one.
I told you.
Seok Jin or Kwang Soo would die.
(His joke is coming true.)
- The balloon.
- I found this letter.
"May 1, 2019.
If what I found out is true..."
Look at this.
It means there's someone.
We don't have time.
What is going on?
(There's someone who's going
after the members' name tags.)
I think there's a secret
about this village.
I'm sure our routes overlap here.
(I should be careful
not to be eliminated here.)
(Se Chan is back at the village
head's house with chocolate.)
Sir.
I brought chocolate.
(He suddenly grabs the chocolate.)
(The village head takes
the chocolate.)
(Is chocolate the key
that will open his mouth?)
Do you have anything to say?
(Do you have anything to say?)
(Shaking his head)
Was it just an ad-lib?
But chocolate...
Sir. Did you just want
something sweet?
(The village head simply wanted
something sweet.)
- Is that it?
- I don't know anything.
- Gosh, my dollar.
Mr. Choi.
(So Min also brings chocolate
for the village head.)
Se Chan.
(I hope this chocolate will unlock
the secret.)
Chocolate.
(I hope this chocolate will unlock
the secret.)
(He ran out of ad-libs.)
- So Min.
- Yes?
It was an ad-lib.
(It was an ad-lib.)
(The village head is low
on sugar and ad-libs.)
(He got me.)
- Hey.
- Mr. Choi
You and I got fooled.
- Grandpa.
- I give up.
- Did you simply want chocolate?
- I don't know anything.
- Is it unrelated to the plot?
- I don't know.
My wife likes it.
(Laughing)
- Are you sure there is nothing?
- There is nothing.
This is hard.
Kwang Ja disappeared.
(Haha ripped off Kwang Ja's name tag
in this garden.)
What is that?
(Kwang Ja disappeared.)
That's Kwang Ja's name tag.
(Only Kwang Ja's name tag remains.)
- Isn't that Kwang Ja's name tag?
- Yes, it is.
- Haha...
- What?
What is it?
(There is something
on the back of the name tag!)
What is this?
It's a children's song.
(There are lyrics
on the back of Kwang Ja's name tag.)
(Haha ripped off Kwang Ja's name tag
and saw the hint.)
(Why did Haha hide the hint?)
Does Kim Ga Gae's name tag have
a clue as well?
(The owner of the stall)
- Could that be the case?
- Right?
People in the photo
must have hints in their name tags.
Kwang Ja and...
Should we remove
Kim Ga Gae's name tag?
Let's go.
I don't know if we can tell
other people about this.
- You are back.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Jae Seok, will you buy something?
- Well...
Do you want a fish cake bar?
- How much is coffee?
- It's a dollar.
- A dollar?
- Yes.
It's hot.
(Ripping off)
Why did you rip off her name tag?
(Kwang Soo ripped off
Kim Ga Gae's name tag.)
(What's behind the name tag?)
- Kwang Soo ripped off her name tag.
- Whose name tag?
The stall owner.
- "Sold out".
- "Sold out"?
(The hint behind her name tag is
"Sold out".)
What does that mean?
Why does it say "Sold out"?
Why did you rip off her name tag?
- Jong Kook.
- What is up with the two of you?
What is going on?
Hold on.
- What's sold out?
- Sold out?
- What?
- The tissue box is sold out.
Here it is.
Hold on.
We don't have time to do this.
(These greedy ones
are undisciplined.)
Where are you going?
They are so greedy.
There must be something inside.
The sign read
that the tissue box is sold out.
What could this be?
(They hide in a corner
and look for a hint.)
- Is there anything inside?
- There is nothing inside.
This has to mean something.
The sign read
that the tissue box is sold out.
How strange!
(He searches thoroughly.)
Tissue box was the only one
that was sold out. What?
(A hand?)
(Jae Seok suddenly slaps Kwang Soo.)
(Why did you slap me?)
- What was that?
- I got back at you. We are even.
My goodness.
- There is nothing.
- Does this mean nothing?
Why did the hint say "Sold out"?
For goodness' sake.
Let's visit the village head
one more time.
(They have no choice but to move.)
Is there a different approach?
(He sends Jae Seok away.)
(Kwang Soo searches the stall
thoroughly.)
(However)
(There is a note
deep inside the tissue box.)
(The witness' number)
(The witness' number is written
on the note.)
(His eyes go wide.)
What?
It's the witness' number.
Hold on. I should call this number.
(Kwang Soo doesn't want
to share the information.)
(He finds a safe spot.)
(He tries calling
the witness' number.)
(He hears the ringtone.)
- Hello?
- Hello.
Hello. Are you the witness?
Who are you?
I told the reporter everything.
Should I tell you
what happened again?
Yes, yes. Please tell me
what happened again.
My friends and I visited
Gujeon Village two years ago.
One friend found a gem box.
(One friend found a gem box.)
We were looking around the village
in search of a key...
when we suddenly heard
my friend's scream.
When we ran over,
someone was attacking my friend.
That person was strong enough
to rip off the name tag at once.
(A strong person who can rip off
the name tag at once)
I couldn't get a good look
since that person was so fast.
When we ran away in surprise,
that person didn't follow us...
despite being fast enough
to rip off my name tag.
I just remembered something.
(The witness remembered something.)
My friend didn't even let us touch
the gem box.
Perhaps it was unlucky.
(Did her friend want the gem box
for herself?)
(Everyone tried to touch
the gem box earlier.)
I don't want to think about it.
I am hanging up. I am sorry.
But... Hello?
(The witness gets scared
and hangs up.)
(Ji Hyo is looking for hints
by herself.)
What is this?
Is it a hint?
(She comes across a camera.)
What?
(Inside the camera...)
(are the photos
of various parts of Gujeon Village.)
(What do these photos mean?)
What?
(Screaming)
(Ji Hyo disappears with a scream.)
(Victim)
(Two members are eliminated
without a sound.)
Where is everyone?
Why is no one around?
Kwang Soo, what are you doing?
(He acts like nothing has happened.)
Did you poop?
Why would I poop?
- Why would I poop on the camera?
- But you were like...
I was just sitting down.
I didn't pull down my pants.
Did you find something?
- I have something.
- What is it?
Give me a hint.
What I found is really important.
I will show you.
Let's take it out at the same time.
(They agree to take it out
at the same time.)
- Will you show me? Is it important?
- Yes.
1, 2, 3.
(Here is chocolate.)
- What is that? It's important.
- Forget it. Hey.
- It's important.
- What is that?
Go ahead and tell me.
What is that chocolate?
What is that chocolate? Tell me.
- It's really important.
- What is it?
- The village head kept saying it.
- What did he say?
"I will eat chocolate."
"I will eat it later."
- What are you playing at?
- I am serious. Go to him.
I am serious.
You haven't changed at all,
have you?
You have no intention to cooperate.
The village head said,
"I will eat chocolate."
- "I will eat it later."
- In any case...
He is eating so much chocolate.
He won't leave his spot.
I think we should join forces
and solve the problem at hand.
- Really?
- Let me tell you one more thing.
It's about Kwang Ja.
On her name tag
is a children's song.
- A children's song?
- Yes.
The lyrics of a children's song.
Which one?
I am sure you know it.
The faces of angels and fairies
- I know it.
- What was the title?
"Hill".
"I go up the hill
to look up at the blue sky..."
(Meanwhile,
at the house of the village head)
- You read it, right?
- Yes.
Haha, you didn't read
the note, did you?
I didn't get to read it carefully.
It talked about...
how you will become eliminated...
if you fall for the diamond.
(Those who fall for the diamond
will get eliminated.)
We came here...
because So Min invited us.
Hey.
Is So Min the one
who is seducing us...
with the diamond?
It says invitation.
(So Min sent them an invitation
to Gujeon Village.)
(There's this fantastic land where
I can dig up huge diamonds.)
(So Min lured them
with a promise of diamonds.)
When someone makes a comeback,
he or she prepares a special...
- Everyone does it for a surprise.
- That's right.
Yes.
So Min is acting like
she isn't behind this.
She is acting like
this is a mistake.
- "I don't know anything."
- To be honest,
what I said back in the car
was directed at So Min.
- Really?
- That's right.
Jae Seok, don't lie.
- Don't pretend to be sharp.
- Why...
Why did you interfere
when Se Chan almost fell for it?
Keep your mouth shut!
He knows you too well.
- Se Chan was like, "Oh?"
- I was like, "Oh?"
- For goodness' sake.
- Hold on!
(Hold on!)
Does the password have six digits?
Sitting there
won't help you find the password.
When is So Min's birthday?
- They wouldn't have used it again.
- Gosh.
You are a bit...
You have no basic skills
in deducting.
He hasn't been in a lot of
those shows, so he doesn't know.
They wouldn't use
the same information again.
Come on down.
(Why are you guys so expectant?)
Why are you guys so expectant?
(Their eyes were about to pop out.)
I thought it might open.
Why are you guys so expectant
to see it open?
I think So Min is behind this.
- There is something about So Min.
- I know.
I don't know what this hint means.
- Why...
- What does "Sold out" mean?
Why does the tissue box... What?
The tissue box is sold out.
There is an open one.
Jae Seok and I looked inside,
but there was nothing.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Yes.
(She suddenly attacks Kwang Soo.)
What?
What? What are you hiding?
- What's inside?
- What?
- There is nothing inside.
- It's my bag.
- Then why can't I see inside?
Why can't I look inside?
Do you want
to get your name tag ripped off?
(Do you want
to get your name tag ripped off?)
Rip it off. Rip it off.
Rip it off. That has happened
many times.
Why can't I look inside?
You said there's nothing.
What's that note? I have seen it.
Isn't it a reporter's note?
- A reporter's note?
- That's right.
Isn't it the one from earlier?
- No.
- Let me see it.
Come on. Don't be like that.
What is it?
Why are you hiding it?
(She continues to go
after Kwang Soo.)
- I don't have anything.
- Hey!
Why did you put it in there?
- I don't have anything!
- Why did you put it near your butt?
I don't have anything!
Why won't you show me the note?
I don't have anything! What note?
What is wrong with you?
- What is wrong with you?
- Why won't you let me see it?
I don't have it.
I don't have it!
Then why did you touch your butt?
Why did you put your hand in there?
It's a habit.
- You put your hand in there.
- Hey!
What are you doing?
What is up with them?
What's going on?
(Kwang Soo tries to trip her.)
Stop it. Stop it.
(So Min grabs Kwang Soo
by his hair.)
- Give it to me.
- I don't have anything.
- Hurry up.
- Let go.
- Show me.
- Let go. Let go first.
- Let go.
- Let go on the count of three.
- What do you have?
1, 2, 3.
(The negotiation falls through!)
(So Min became so healthy.)
Show me. Why won't you show me?
Let go.
What are you doing?
I can't believe you guys.
Let go. I can't show you
unless you let go.
- I can't show you.
- I let go.
- Let go.
- Slowly.
Okay.
Get your hands off me.
- I don't have anything.
- Why won't you show me?
Why are you doing this to me?
He put a note in his underwear.
- Jong Kook.
- So Min, you said you changed.
This is ridiculous.
She put her hand in there!
Where?
He put a note in his underwear.
Then you should give up,
not put your hand in there.
- Don't be like that.
- You should give up.
Why won't you show me the hint?
- What is it?
- She touched his butt.
I didn't do that!
- She hasn't changed at all!
- That's not true.
- So Min.
- He hid a note near his butt.
- For goodness' sake.
Listen, Jae Seok.
In the shrubs over there,
he was sitting down.
He came outside like this.
I asked him about the note.
Did you poop in the shrubs again?
- No!
- Did you?
Why would I poop
when the camera is on me?
You need to break out of that habit!
- The toilet is right there.
- Jae Seok.
When I asked him what it was,
he put it near his butt.
- He put it in the underwear.
- She kept trying to take it.
It isn't a good hiding place
since your butt is flat.
It must have fallen out.
since his butt is flat.
- Look for it. Look for it.
- Since his butt is flat.
(Annoyed)
Look for it. Look for it.
Look for it, okay?
So Min, So Min. Here is the thing.
- When you come back from a hiatus,
- That's right.
- you receive an important role.
Also, you need to keep this in mind.
So Min is the one
who invited us here.
- That's right.
- I don't know anything.
Isn't So Min acting strange today?
That could be the case.
- Why did you bring us here?
- It's like that most of the time.
So Min, did you come up
with this scheme?
No, Jae Seok.
- I am not that smart.
- She sent us the invitation.
I saw the flyer
and sent you the invitation.
(Ripping)
(Se Chan...)
(ripped off So Min's name tag!)
(She is back on the show
after a two-month hiatus.)
Hey!
Were you determined
to rip off her name tag?
- Is she out?
What does it say?
(So Min was a victim.)
Hey, I am back in a long while.
My goodness.
I am sorry.
- I am back in a long while.
- I am sorry.
I fought with you,
but I didn't do this to you.
So Min.
So Min, I didn't do this to you.
Why didn't you leave So Min be?
Let me earn some money!
- I am sorry.
- She is back after a long while.
- Is So Min out?
- I am out.
- That startled me so much.
- Hey.
(Victim)
Inside the tissue box,
- I found a note.
- You little...
(Inside the tissue box,
I found a note.)
- You little...
- Why didn't you say so earlier?
How dare you?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
You little punk.
- I won't tell you.
- Come on.
- I won't tell you for real.
- Please tell us.
This is a hint
you can't get anymore.
- All right.
- Please tell us.
- Share the information with us.
- Don't be annoyed.
We were simply reacting.
- Just go with the flow.
- Tell us.
- There was a phone number.
- What?
(There was a phone number.)
And?
A witness' number.
What? Did you call the number?
- Yes. When I called,
- Who picked up?
a woman picked up.
(He heard a witness account
over the phone.)
(The witness visited
Gujeon Village,)
(and her friend found a gem box.)
(She heard her friend's scream.)
(Someone was attacking her friend.)
That person was...
very fast and strong.
(The attacker was
very fast and strong.)
I think he is setting me up.
- No, no.
- He could have made this up.
No, no.
The witness really said that.
Her friend who got eliminated
didn't let anyone touch the gem box.
- Her friend who got eliminated?
- Yes.
Fast and strong?
Someone who is fast and strong.
(The truth of Gujeon Village
is shrouded in mystery.)
Let's scatter and find more hints.
(They decide to look
for more hints.)
What on earth is going on?
(Jae Seok searches for more hints.)
(What is this place?)
Gosh, you startled me.
(The only survivor
among the four sisters,)
(Kim Sam Nyeo is here.)
You startled me.
Mister, please save me.
- What?
- Please save me.
What are you doing here alone?
I was hiding
because I became so scared...
upon seeing my sisters
get eliminated.
Who eliminated them?
You know,
Jeon Dang Po disappeared.
That's right. Jeon Dang Po was
nowhere to be seen.
Now that Jeon Dang Po disappeared,
I think that person might come
to me.
That's why I am hiding.
This village seems to have a secret.
Well, I...
I don't know anything!
(He attacks Kim Sam Nyeo.)
- I don't know anything!
- Gosh, hold on.
What are you doing? I don't know...
(He ripped off her name tag!)
I don't know...
(Is there a hint
on Kim Sam Nyeo's name tag?)
She's just a victim.
(Detective Yu killed
an innocent citizen.)
You killed an innocent citizen.
Excuse me.
But...
(I have more lines.)
Did you pass away?
(Jae Seok became speechless.)
I am sorry.
Sam Nyeo's name tag
doesn't have a hint.
(He killed off
innocent Kim Sam Nyeo.)
For goodness' sake. This is hard.
(He thinks about
Kim Sam Nyeo's last words.)
Where did Jeon Dang Po go?
Today's mission is so hard.
(He finds Jeon Dang Po!)
You are here.
What brings you here?
- Sir.
- Yes?
Kim Sam Nyeo said...
you were acting a bit strange.
- She said you had disappeared.
- What?
(Jeon Dang Po was with the sisters,
but he suddenly disappeared.)
You aren't related
to the village head, are you?
No, I am not.
- No?
- No.
What are you doing?
(He attacks Jeon Dang Po
this time!)
Gosh, my head hurts.
(There is a hint!)
"It's the darkest under the lamp."
What does this hint mean?
(What does this hint mean?)
(Pawnshop and lamp...)
"It's the darkest under the lamp"?
Is there something at the pawnshop?
(Is there another hint
at the pawnshop?)
(He looks underneath.)
(What?)
What is this?
(He finds a mysterious cell phone.)
What is this cell phone?
Who is "Big Brother"?
("Big Brother" is the contact
that is saved on the phone.)
(Jae Seok tries calling
Big Brother.)
(Someone answers the phone.)
- Hello.
- Where are you?
Who is this?
This is your little brother.
Where are you?
I'm at the pawnshop.
What?
Where?
(The voice sounds familiar.)
Where are you?
Isn't this Haha's voice?
(Big Brother turns out to be Haha.)
Where are you?
(What does Haha have to do
with this village?)
It's Haha.
Haha must be hiding something.
He asked me where I was.
That means there's someone else.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook is searching
the rest of the houses.)
What? There's a picture.
(There's a picture of two men.)
(The man on the left is Haha.)
Haha?
(Haha's arm is around
a mysterious man.)
Haha must be hiding something.
Who is the man next to him,
by the way?
(Haha is hiding a secret.)
- Did you find anything?
- Jae Seok.
- Come here.
- Why?
I found a picture.
(A picture of Haha was
among pictures of the villagers.)
It's Haha.
- Who is the other man?
- Who is he?
- Gosh.
- What?
What is it?
I found this cell phone.
You found this?
What is it?
- Someone is saved as Big Brother.
- "Big Brother"?
- So I called this number.
- Okay.
And Haha answered the phone.
(All the clues are
pointing to Haha.)
Who...
Where are you?
(He's been keeping a distance from
everyone and eliminated Kwang Ja.)
It's Haha.
Is this guy his little brother?
- Is he?
- I don't know.
(Does Haha live in this village?)
We should...
drive him into a corner.
Mr. Choi!
(Meanwhile,
at the village head's house...)
I know you're not sick.
(Haha is arguing
with the village head.)
Why are you doing this?
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook walk in.)
I have all the evidence.
(The village head and Haha are
getting into a fight.)
Stop trying to find out more.
(Staring)
Why are you asking me that?
- Hey.
- It's because you...
- What's going on?
- The village head...
Hold on. I'm serious.
You probably don't trust me, but...
Please stop him.
- He just yelled at me.
- He's trying to harm me.
I mean it.
He just yelled at me.
He's always angry.
- He's always angry.
- Mr. Choi is always angry.
- Did you answer the phone?
- What?
(Jae Seok asks Haha about
the person saved as Big Brother.)
- Did you answer the phone?
- What?
- Yes, I did.
- Show me your phone.
- Why is your number saved here?
- Give it to me.
(They call Big Brother again.)
(The number is saved as
Little Brother in Haha's phone.)
Sit down first.
Are you suspecting me?
Of course.
(Did Haha eliminate
all the members?)
- Guys.
- We'll sit down.
Stand over there.
I have something unbelievable.
- I'm serious.
- Show us.
I'll play it for you.
(When he is about to be caught,
Haha takes out a voice recorder.)
- What is it?
- I'll play it for you.
- The village head...
- Hurry up.
(Haha plays something
on the recorder.)
It's you, Dong Sik, right?
(Village head:
It's you, Dong Sik, right?)
You stole my keys, didn't you?
I knew it was you.
Why did you pretend
to have Alzheimer's?
Your keys...
What are they?
You're going to die soon anyway.
So give me back my keys.
Where are they?
- So what's the cell phone?
- What is it?
My little brother is called...
- Dong Sik.
- And?
He asked me...
to come to this village
and settle his grudge.
You heard the village head tell him
he couldn't leave the village alive.
- That was your brother's voice?
- Yes, that was his voice.
(Haha's true identity is revealed.)
Haha, there's a letter for you.
(A few days ago)
Please read it out loud.
(Haha got a letter.)
What's this?
"Dear Haha."
"Is everything all right?"
"I've been staying in a village
for a month now."
"Once I'm done learning about
the special diamond here,"
"I'll write an exclusive news story
about it."
(Dong Sik, Haha's brother, was
writing about Gujeon Village.)
"Tomorrow is D-day."
"I still have to do one last check."
"But I think I'm getting close..."
"to the Immortal Heart,
which I've only heard about."
"But this whole thing is
pretty dangerous."
"If you stop hearing from me,"
"you'll receive this letter and
a key by this time next year."
Did something happen? Did he die?
(Dong Sik sensed danger
and wrote this letter last year.)
"Don't trust anyone too fast."
"Please keep this a secret."
"I love you, Brother."
(Giving a key to Haha, Dong Sik
asked him to finish the story.)
(When Kwang Soo found
the Immortal Heart...)
(I should try opening it
with my key.)
(While Kwang Soo was distracted,)
(Haha tried to open the gem box
but failed.)
It won't open.
I can't open it.
(He tries opening other boxes too.)
It doesn't fit.
(He hasn't found a lock
that opens with the key.)
Are you looking for
your little brother?
(Beware of those who
try to get in your way.)
- Did you just try to rip it off?
- "If you find those,"
"please get rid of them."
(Haha eliminates Lee Kwang Ja,
who has been hovering around him.)
(Was Kwang Ja trying to
get in my way or not?)
(A hint was hidden on the back
of Kwang Ja's name tag.)
Grapes, stars, trees...
(Haha examines the bench
that Kwang Ja used to play around.)
A hill?
(He finds Kwang Ja's hill.)
This is just like the lyrics.
I'm up on the hill now.
(Following the lyrics, Haha goes up
the hill and looks up at the sky.)
There are angels.
(He finds angel figurines
in the tree.)
It's the password for the safe.
(Thanks to the angel figurines,
Haha finds the next safe.)
I found the password
for the safe. Unbelievable.
(He finds the safe
hidden in the village.)
(The safe is open.)
What is this?
(He finds a voice recorder
and the conversations on it.)
I knew it was you.
It was the village head.
(That's why Haha was
questioning the village head.)
Are you saying the village head
harmed your brother?
- Yes.
- Is that what you found out?
(Haha was an innocent outsider.)
Does that mean
that the village head has the key?
No, we have to rip off
his name tag first.
I think there's a secret
hidden under his name tag.
- Mr. Choi.
- We have no choice.
Don't!
(The village head's name tag
is ripped off immediately.)
- What is it?
- Right?
(His name tag was hiding
the password for the safe.)
- It's the password for the safe.
- Where's the safe?
- It's 940...
- It's upstairs.
- Let's go upstairs.
See? I'm innocent. Trust me.
- I mean it.
- Is it okay to rip off name tags?
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan
are searching another house.)
Who eliminated Seok Jin?
I don't know.
Hold on. Could it be Jong Kook?
- What do you think?
- The whole thing?
Isn't it possible?
The culprit
is supposed to be strong.
(According to the witness,
the culprit is strong and fast.)
- Who could that be?
- You're right.
It must be Jong Kook.
(Shocked)
- Did you memorize the password?
- Start.
- Yes.
- It's 940302.
(Without knowing what's going on,
they open the safe.)
What's this?
It's another box.
Are these Russian dolls?
- Gosh.
- How many are there?
I'll be honest. I have a key.
- Why didn't you tell us earlier?
- I mean...
It's because you didn't trust me.
- What are you talking about?
- I can't believe you.
Fine, I'll try opening it.
I get it. Trust me.
What is this?
We just need to find the key.
(They find a piece of paper
in the trash can.)
What is this?
"A man mysteriously goes missing
in Gujeon Village..."
"after finding the most expensive
diamond, Immortal Heart."
- Hey.
- I'm not supposed to have it?
I think you're doomed.
Look at this.
(Whoever finds the gem box...)
Someone went missing
after finding it.
- You found it too.
- Hold on.
I got goosebumps.
Whoever finds the gem box...
You'll disappear too.
Can you hold this for me?
- Wait!
- Gosh, you startled me.
(Just then)
- There's another picture here.
- Let me see.
- It's a different picture.
- No, it's the same...
- Why is she looking that way?
- She's looking the other way.
(The new picture,
the previous picture)
(The pictures were taken...)
(in the yard next to the house.)
Let's go there.
(Is there an important hint
hidden in the yard?)
- Hurry up and open it.
- Open it.
(The key fits in the lock.)
- It's open.
- Unbelievable.
There's something inside.
Let me see the picture again.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan look
around the yard in the picture.)
This is the place, right?
- Goodness.
- There's something.
I can't believe you.
- You brat.
Gosh, I have no idea.
(This yard is supposed to hold
an important clue.)
What is this?
- What does it say?
- "To ward off misfortune..."
"and enjoy prosperity,"
"honor the scarecrow
as your guardian..."
(To enjoy prosperity, honor
the scarecrow as your guardian...)
(The scarecrow grabs
Kwang Soo's name tag.)
"and offer him a sacrifice
every year."
(They have to offer the scarecrow
a sacrifice every year?)
(Kwang Soo is eliminated
immediately.)
"Whoever touches
the scarecrow's gem box..."
"will be offered up as a sacrifice."
"The scarecrow will take away
everyone's name."
(The secret of Gujeon Village
is finally revealed.)
(Every May, Gujeon Village attracted
outsiders to their festival.)
(Blinded by their greed, the Running
Man members attended the festival.)
(The villagers were
very happy to see the outsiders.)
(Every year, outsiders have been
lured to the village.)
(The first one
to find the Immortal Heart...)
(was Kwang Soo.)
(That's how the Immortal Heart
got uncovered.)
(When sacrificial victims
touched the Immortal Heart,)
(the scarecrow, which they thought
was a mannequin,)
(started hunting.)
(Everybody touched the gem box.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo found
the most decisive lead.)
(She was looking through
the pictures in the camera.)
(The scarecrow eliminated her.)
(The hunter is stronger
than anybody,)
(and he's lightning fast.)
(He eliminated Seok Jin after that.)
(Kim Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, and Sa Nyeo
were eliminated as well.)
(Any outsider who touched
the Immortal Heart...)
(gets sacrificed.)
(Last May, Dong Sik investigated
and found out about everything.)
(While hiding the Immortal Heart,
he got eliminated by the scarecrow.)
(The materials he collected...)
(were locked away by the villagers.)
(Ha Dong Sik)
(Each villager kept a secret.)
(He was the one...)
(who kept an eye
on the village children.)
(He's a silent assassin
who was watching the whole village.)
(Scarecrow)
(He eliminated Kwang Soo
before he could resist.)
What was that? Hey!
(There's only one way to
break the curse of the scarecrow.)
(You must burn his straw hat.)
(If you burn his straw hat,
the curse gets broken.)
Let's burn the straw hat.
(Burn the scarecrow's hat
in the incinerator.)
Jae Seok!
- Jae Seok!
- What?
- Who?
- Jae Seok.
In the picture,
it wasn't the scarecrow.
- It was a person.
- It is.
(They finally hear about
the identity of the scarecrow.)
- The scarecrow...
- Wait, let me see the straw hat.
We have to remove this straw hat.
(Once they burn this hat,
the scarecrow gets eliminated.)
Let's go catch him.
- There are four of us.
- We can do it.
- He moves so fast.
- Really?
- Over there...
- He's coming!
- What?
- He's coming.
What is it?
(The scarecrow
starts attacking them.)
What is it?
What? What is it?
Who are you?
(Scarecrow versus Jong Kook)
Hold on.
(He comes up fast
and attacks Jong Kook.)
What was that?
(Jong Kook is out.)
What was that? Who are you?
(Why is he so strong?)
- He's so strong!
- My gosh.
- What was that?
What was that?
What was that? My gosh.
- What was that?
- Jae Seok!
Shouldn't we help him?
What was that?
(He starts hunting the other members
before the cameras catch up.)
What was that?
I'm so scared.
- What was that?
- I'm scared.
(The scarecrow caught up
with Se Chan who was running away.)
I'm scared. Wait.
I'm scared.
I'm scared!
That was so scary!
(Jae Seok and Haha are
the only members left.)
(The scarecrow is strong and fast.)
Jae Seok, we have to work together.
Who is this person?
- See? He's out already.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Together. We can do it together.
- Is he out?
- Where did he go?
(The scarecrow disappeared
in an instant.)
Where did he go?
Don't run away.
He's over there.
Jae Seok, he's there.
(Scarecrow versus Jae Seok and Haha)
- Let's do it together.
- From above.
From above.
(They fight 2 to 1,
but the scarecrow defends himself.)
- He's so fast.
- Why is he so fast?
(He's driving them crazy.)
(Haha grabbed the straw hat!)
- Good job.
- What was that?
(But he only ripped some straws.)
What was that?
(This is a volatile situation.)
Who is this person?
Come here!
(Will the scarecrow rip their name
tags or will they steal his hat?)
Hey, hey.
(He stole the straw hat.)
Burn it.
(Haha narrowly stole the hat.)
(He sprints to the incinerator.)
(The scarecrow can't see well
because of the mask.)
(If he manages to burn the hat,
both members win!)
This is hot.
(He put the straw hat in the fire.)
(The curse has been broken.)
(Gujeon Village doesn't need to make
sacrifices anymore.)
(They also obtained the key to the
Immortal Heart that was in the hat.)
Everybody, today's race was
the Secret of Gujeon Village.
This village was protected by
the Almighty of the scarecrow.
- And then?
- Outsiders who touch the gem box...
all get sacrificed
and get eliminated by the scarecrow.
- I touched it.
- The gem box.
People who touched it
got eliminated.
You were all probably wondering
who the scarecrow was.
Who was it?
- Let's invite him here first.
- Okay.
- Scarecrow, come on out.
- He scared me to death.
- He was no joke.
- Really?
- He was so fast.
- He's so fast.
- He was great in ripping name tags.
- He's scary.
Who is it?
You were all probably wondering
who the scarecrow was.
(Jong Kook was surprised at his
strength and speed. He is...)
He...
owns a channel. It's Kim Gye Ran
of Physical Gallery.
It's Kim Gye Ran?
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Wow, friends.
- I watch his videos a lot.
- I'm the bald man.
- The bald man.
(He's extremely athletic as a former
member of the UDT.)
(He has a muscular physique
and is stronger than most people.)
(Kim Gye Ran)
I'm the bald man.
- The bald man.
- Hello.
Jong Kook.
(The workout masters meet.)
- I wanted to meet you the most.
- The bald man!
- I wanted to meet him the most.
- Really?
I really like him.
Jong Kook was never this happy
with any other guest.
- He's so excited.
- He's so happy.
- I love him.
- Okay!
I really like him.
I trust his workout channel
the most.
- I know.
- Kim Gye Ran?
I watch your videos too.
Haha managed to burn his straw hat.
- You stole it from me.
- Narrowly.
The scarecrow got eliminated,
and here's the gem box.
(Winner Haha gets the real gem box.)
Don't you die if you touch that?
No, I broke the curse.
(The prize gets revealed.)
What is it?
- Goodness.
- It's the Immortal Heart.
It's the Immortal Heart.
This is useless to bring it home.
- Does he have to take that?
- Your kids will like it.
You'll get eight dollars from it.
That's the gem of this village,
the Immortal Heart.
That's the Immortal Heart?
- This is insane. I'm envious.
- That's amazing.
(You can't list a prize for
the Immortal Heart.)
This is amazing.
I'm envious!
We usually give the prize
to the guest.
It's fine.
- Haha, you can't do that.
- Gye Ran.
- That's unnecessary.
- Take it home.
Since you're on Running Man.
Can I just take a picture with you?
- Just a picture.
- We'll take a picture.
- Great work.
- Thank you.
Great work.
(TWICE is back as a whole group.)
(Return of the popular group, TWICE)
(It's TWICE.)
(Check out their unexpected charms!)
(They rip name tags
without hesitation...)
(and can do slapstick comedy.)
(She is a bigger traitor
than Kwang Soo.)
(Is she the new traitor?)
(They're tempted...)
(by the captain role.)
(Once you become the captain,)
(you can lead the team
however you want.)
(Form alliances and betray them
to throw off your teammates.)
(Build solid trust...)
(and find your guarantor!)
(A war ensues to obtain
the captain's privilege!)
(Captains of Running Man)