- Hello.
Hello. Hi, guys.
- Hey.
- This place is nice.
- I changed my pants.
- The weather is nice.
- Why are you guys being so...
- It's windy.
- What?
- It's a lovely day.
It's chilly in the morning.
So Min says she doesn't feel cold.
But she has a hot pack on her back.
- A hot pack in May?
- What?
Why would you
need a hot pack in May?
The weather is nice today.
There are Jong Kook and his manager.
I guess he's got a new manager.
- Isn't he the guy who does origami?
- He looks like a mischievous boy.
They never wait for me.
It's him. Hello, we're "boogers".
Is he today's guest?
- He's the origami guy.
- Mr. Origami.
I'm a big fan.
Can I get your autograph?
He's the guy who teaches us origami.
- It's him.
- We saw him a lot in childhood.
They called me the origami guy.
- We're boogers.
- He's from the TV show.
- Hello.
- I was a big fan.
- It's the origami guy.
- Wow.
Mr. Ji Young Man.
He's our guest for today.
- Hello.
- Hello, Mr. Origami.
It's him.
- Hello.
- It's been a really long time.
Hey, how could you call me
the origami guy?
What?
It's Suk Jin!
What happened?
- It's Suk Jin.
- Hello, kids.
It was Suk Jin.
Your outfit is too extreme.
It's not extreme.
You seemed quite close
with him over there.
- How could he be like that?
- You're the same.
You're being extreme too.
Everyone changes
in front of cameras.
You're being extreme too.
The seven of us are
attacking him all at once.
It's okay.
He's like...
- Shirasoni.
- Shirasoni of a variety show.
He fights against several enemies.
"Bring it on!"
- He beats us all.
- He takes blows well.
He's tough.
All right.
- What's that?
- What is it?
- What about Ji Suk Jin?
- What's that?
You said this
in "You Quiz on the Block ".
I see. It just came up.
Don't say that. We're not
your best friends for life.
- We are best friends for life.
- We just live our own lives.
I mentioned those two because...
I know what you mean.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yes.
I wasn't disappointed at all.
They are the people
whom I can control.
- You can control them?
- We're not disappointed.
- You all are my best friends.
- Sure.
To put it bluntly, we're like
his well-trained dogs.
(A best friend means
a well-trained dog.)
- Well-trained dogs.
- That sounds rough.
- To put it bluntly.
- That's not true.
You're like his pet dogs.
Hey.
Do you know
whom you can't control here?
- Who is it?
- It's her.
If you call her, she will
call you back a week later.
- "Did you call me?"
- Ji Hyo?
I have no intention to control her.
I texted her after our first
shooting of Running Man,
but she hasn't texted me back.
It's been 10 years,
but she hasn't replied yet.
- She's Cavewoman Ji Hyo indeed.
- Cavewoman Ji Hyo.
Let me introduce our guests
who will join today's race.
- Okay.
- Do we have guests?
- This is exciting.
- They are there.
(There are four guests who will
make today's race special.)
Who are they? He's pretty tall.
- It's Chang Wook.
- Oh, hello.
Hey.
- Chang Wook.
- Have you been doing well?
Hello, Yoo Jung.
Chang Wook, it's been a long time.
(Ji Chang Wook, a clumsy
but good-looking manager)
(A whimsical part-timer,
Kim Yoo Jung)
(An unpredictable romantic comedy,
"Backstreet Rookie")
(Han Sunhwa and Do Sang Woo
are in the middle of the story too.)
(The 4 protagonists
of the drama are here.)
They are the protagonists
of the upcoming SBS drama.
"Backstreet Rookie".
Are you their manager or something?
- What are you talking about?
- Are you their manager?
- Why would you say that?
- They are supposed to talk.
- Stay out of this.
- The title is "Backstreet Rookie".
- Hang on.
- "Backstreet Rookie"?
Sunhwa, are you going
somewhere after the opening?
- She brought her bag.
- Why did you bring your bag?
- What's that bag?
- It's for my fashion.
- It's a fashion item.
- I see.
It looks like she's going somewhere.
After shooting the opening.
Yoo Jung, you're dressed
comfortably. You look nice.
Yoo Jung is dressed comfortably,
- but what's wrong with you?
- Mind your outfit.
- It makes me dizzy.
- You know the origami guy, right?
- The origami guy.
- We are boogers.
- Yoo Jung wouldn't know him.
- I'm trying to look young...
because of Yoo Jung.
You look even younger than her.
You're dressed like a newborn baby.
Are you opening a sushi bar
or something, Sang Woo?
You look...
It also looks like
a taekwondo uniform.
- I know.
- It looks like a uniform.
- Martial arts uniform.
- I know.
Good. We have Chang Wook here.
There are many celebrities
who have Ji as their surnames.
- And he's one of them.
- He's very handsome.
He's my junior from high school.
- Really?
- In Anyang.
We went to Shinsung High School.
Shinsung High School?
(He suddenly starts to sing
the school song.)
Nice.
- We went to the same school.
- Was it a school song?
Yes, it was.
(He's being childish.)
I thought that's what you said.
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
It just sounded like that.
Is it your real name?
Yes.
- The Chungju Ji Clan?
- Yes.
Maybe I should trace my genealogy.
You'll get some colored paper today.
(You'll get some
colored paper today.)
(Booger Chang Wook will
get some colored paper.)
Because he's the origami guy.
He will get a hundred
origami cranes.
Or origami turtles.
Have you been in a drama
with So Min before?
- No.
- Not even once?
No. I don't think we've met.
- Is this your first time?
- You haven't met before?
I did a drama with him.
- With Kwang Soo?
- What was the drama?
It was "Bachelor's Vegetable Store".
(We did the drama called
"Bachelor's Vegetable Store".)
- You were the vegetable man.
- Yes.
- Right?
- "Bachelor's Vegetable Store".
(They've found the prey.)
- Right?
- Yes.
You were the eggplant.
- Vegetables.
- You were the cucumber.
He was a vegetable.
No, he was a dried radish.
(Spitting)
(The vegetable man
explodes with anger.)
- He was a dried radish.
- He was a Chinese yam.
- Vegetables.
- That's what he was.
At a vegetable store...
He was a bamboo shoot.
- Green onion.
- An apple box.
A shishito pepper.
A shishito pepper?
I hate it when the three of them
are standing together.
- I feel much better now.
- Celery.
- That's what he looks like.
Celery tastes good though.
Be patient.
- Patient?
- Corn that's gone bad.
Please tell us about your new drama,
Yoo Jung and Sunhwa.
It's been a long time, Yoo Jung.
The title of our new drama is
"Backstreet Rookie".
I play the manager there.
The manager.
- What about you, Yoo Jung?
- I'm a part-timer.
She's a part-timer.
It sounds about right.
I work at the head office
of the convenience store chain.
What about you, Sang Woo?
I'm the director at the head office.
- I see.
- He's the director.
- So who's the rookie?
- The rookie.
Isn't it obvious? Gosh.
It's obvious who the rookie is.
- Hey.
- Suk Jin.
You're dressed like a rookie today.
You're the rookie.
It's the rookie look.
- You're dressed like a rookie.
- Hey.
Hey, kid.
He seems to like it.
He's the rookie.
All right.
Please give the four of them
a big hand then.
Before I explain the rules,
you will decide your teams.
- Please bring in the mats first.
- Mats?
What?
Everyone.
There will be 4 groups of 3 members.
The guests will wait in the square.
And the members will jump into
the square of the guest they want.
Once three of you get together,
you're a team.
- What if we bounce off?
- If you bounce off,
you will have to try again
at the end.
- At the end?
- Okay. Please stand in the squares.
Which team should I pick?
All right then. Ji Hyo
and So Min will go first.
So Min, you go first.
- Me?
- So Min.
What should I do?
- Whom should I pick?
- I know.
I feel uncomfortable to go first.
Can we ask who they want
for their teams?
Gosh, it's so old-fashioned.
Mr. Origami!
You're dressed
in an old-fashioned way.
I just don't know where to go.
Does anyone of you want me
to be your team?
- Yoo Jung wants you.
- Yoo Jung.
- Cool.
- If they raise their hands...
- You keep staying...
around Chang Wook.
You were there only for a moment.
She wouldn't go over there.
You keep staying around him.
Don't pretend to hesitate.
Just go to him.
Just go.
I want you two to play
rock-paper-scissors.
Why? It doesn't even matter.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Sang Woo wins.)
You don't even care who wins.
Are you going to the winner?
He won. He won me.
I should go to him.
I feel bad for him.
He won me.
- I should go to him.
- What?
I should step on the square.
You can push her
if you don't like her.
I'll go to Chang Wook.
You can push her out.
- He didn't push me.
- This is only the beginning.
- He can't push you.
- Right.
- He can't do it from the beginning.
- Who's next?
Jong Kook goes next.
(Next up is Jong Kook.)
Who would push you out?
- I know.
- You can just hold out.
Okay.
I was going to pick
my high school junior.
Chang Wook is fine with it,
but Ji Hyo doesn't want you.
Ji Hyo doesn't like me.
He wants to take care
of his junior from Anyang.
But Ji Hyo is about to kick you out.
Gosh, I think Ji Hyo
is going to kick me out.
I'm interested in the sushi bar too.
- It's a nice place.
It's not bad.
I think Sang Woo...
How should I explain this?
- I think he's like us.
- Right.
Judging from the way you look,
I think you'll be like us.
- And he looks a bit clumsy.
- I know.
- He does.
- He looks...
a bit like Maeng Gu.
He's a handsome version
of Maeng Gu.
I know what you mean.
- How can Chil Deuk say that?
- I already feel close to him.
He does remind me of Kwang Soo.
- I like him.
- First...
- Are you going there?
- All right.
This is good.
So Min...
(Jong Kook is pushed away.)
(So Min panics,
and Sang Woo holds Jong Kook.)
- She pushed him away.
- That's not it.
And Sang Woo caught him.
So Min pushed him away,
but Sang Woo caught him.
(What?)
- I mean...
- Okay, I get it.
You said you wanted Jae Suk
on your team.
So Min is
in an awkward situation now.
She got caught.
All right.
- Go.
- It's my turn now.
- You're choosing between the two.
- I'm choosing between...
- Yoo Jung and Sunhwa.
- I know.
- I'm not even looking at the guys.
- I can't decide.
Are you sure
you don't need any knee pads?
- You might hurt yourself.
- Put a helmet on him!
Guys, as soon as I join a team,
I'll manage the team closely.
- Who do you think you are?
- I'll manage the team closely.
Keep that in mind.
I'll manage my team very closely.
I choose Yoo Jung.
(The strict man chooses Yoo Jung.)
- You're not pushing him away?
Okay!
All of them are so nice.
- You're the first person, so...
- Okay.
I've made myself clear.
- Gosh, I'm the last one.
- It's my turn.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
- Se Chan...
- I'll jump...
Please don't feel hurt.
What's with...
his outfit today?
- Is it me now?
- No.
Is this the problem?
- That looks better.
- This looks better?
Let me have a word with Yoo Jung.
- Gosh, I can't stand him.
- Okay.
- Did she decide?
- Yes.
That role suits him so well.
Jump, jump, jump...
(Strict defense)
(Se Chan is pushed away.)
Who are you to push me away?
Yoo Jung was okay with you,
but I don't like you.
You pushed my mouth!
I didn't mean to...
(What?)
(What? Jae Suk got pushed out?)
Jae Suk got pushed out.
Nice!
- Good job!
- We should decide together.
- I said I like Se Chan.
- I can't believe this.
- You didn't even let me catch him.
- You said you like me?
- Jae Suk!
- He was only pretending.
(Yoo Jung is even stricter
than Jae Suk.)
- I mean...
- Suk Jin.
- I'll go for Sunhwa.
- We should choose Sunhwa.
- We should.
Otherwise, she'd feel hurt.
I'm coming.
Leave a spot for me.
- Well...
- Now?
- Sunhwa, leave a spot for me.
- Sunhwa.
Don't feel hurt.
They only chose Yoo Jung
to be funny.
- Don't feel hurt.
- They were trying to be funny.
- That's why.
- We just wanted to be funny.
It's not your fault.
- I feel even more hurt now.
- Sunhwa.
I was feeling okay.
I didn't feel hurt.
Why are you doing this?
- Sunhwa is the best.
- Sunhwa.
- They were just trying to be funny.
- I'm coming, okay?
We have to go to Yoo Jung
to be funny.
- Sunhwa likes to have space.
- I'm doing great.
I'm the one who made her a star
on "Star Golden Bell".
- Who?
- Sunhwa.
You did?
You didn't become a star
on that show yourself.
What are you talking about?
(Suk Jin was the only one
who didn't become a star.)
- Seriously...
- All right.
(Suk Jin is getting ready to jump
to Sunhwa.)
You don't look so happy.
(Right then...)
It's not like that.
(Suk Jin's T-shirt stretches.)
(Jumping)
(This is how you make it funny.)
- That was hilarious.
- The situation was funny.
How did he jump like this?
- That was funny.
- He jumped 3cm.
(Instead of choosing a team,
Suk Jin only made people laugh.)
Go back to your place.
Let's do this again.
- Let's do it again.
- I failed?
He failed?
You failed.
(Annoying)
(How long will this go on?)
This is never going to end.
Oh, that's the wrong direction.
He went to Yoo Jung instead.
(Jae Suk tries
Yoo Jung's team again.)
- Sunhwa would feel hurt.
- "Oh, that's the wrong direction."
I was going to push him away.
- You were going to?
- Gosh.
- He's annoying, right?
- I jumped in the wrong direction.
I'll definitely choose Sunhwa.
- Jump, jump, jump.
(Se Chan jumps into
Sunhwa's box.)
She didn't push him away.
- Next up is Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
(Is it my turn now?)
Here comes celery.
- He's only interested in two teams.
- A shishito pepper.
Hey, no one is getting nervous.
No one cares.
(Which team will Kwang Soo choose?)
(Jae Suk slaps his face.)
(It becomes funny again.)
(Where did Kwang Soo land?)
You're in.
No, I'm not.
I'm not in.
- You're in.
- I'm not.
- No.
You're in.
- This is not okay.
- Good job.
You landed right in there.
(I saw it.)
- You're in, Kwang Soo.
- You went right in.
- I wasn't even considering.
- You're in.
I like this team too.
I like this team too, but...
Is it my turn?
Here we go.
(It's Haha's turn.)
(I didn't get pushed out.)
- Good.
- Then I'll join this team.
- Hold on. What?
- He got pushed out.
- Why did you push him out?
- He was in.
Let's just end it here.
Didn't we agree to push him?
I get kicked out and that's it?
- You're in.
- Haha!
- Is Haha by himself?
- We're sorry.
- Don't worry.
That was a mistake.
I thought it was Suk Jin.
(Team Selection Result)
With today's guests, who are playing
convenience store employees,
we'll have Convenience Store
Hot Item Race.
The four guests will be
the branch manager of each team.
- They're the branch managers.
In today's race,
you have to guess
the most popular items...
sold at convenience stores...
and try to get as many of them.
There are top 15 items...
and 25 randomly chosen items,
and they have different points
according to their sales rankings.
After each mission,
you get to choose items.
At the end, the points from
each item will be added up,
and the two teams with
the highest score will win prizes.
One more thing. There are...
- two brokers among you.
- What?
- Brokers?
(There are two brokers among them.)
Hey. Are you a broker?
- Stop acting.
- A broker?
You're not a broker, are you?
I can't believe you.
We're going to choose
the two brokers randomly.
- Really?
- It's not decided yet.
- We're going to choose them now.
- I'm sorry.
- See?
I saw the old look in her eyes.
Gosh.
She's scary.
- What's with you?
- The two brokers...
will carry out hidden missions...
and propose a deal
to a team of their choice.
After each mission,
the proposals will be announced.
If the team accepts the deal,
they can choose an additional item.
At the same time, the broker
will win another item too.
If the team turns down the deal,
they get no additional item...
but can win a hint about the broker.
If a team manages to catch
a broker using the hints,
they'll get a chance
to turn the game around.
- We'll have to make a choice.
- If we turn down a deal...
So there are 2 brokers and 4 teams.
They'll compete against each other,
and the top two teams
will win prizes.
Let's choose two brokers now.
- We choose them randomly?
- Yes.
- We choose them?
- Each of you will draw one.
- Let's start.
- Two of them will say, "Broker".
(They choose two brokers randomly.)
I usually choose the one left.
I want to choose the one left.
(Even the brokers don't know
who the other broker is.)
(They have to compete
against each other too.)
(The two brokers are given
hidden missions.)
All right.
(Which of them are the 2 brokers?)
- I'll see you at the next spot.
- Okay.
(They change and move
to the next mission spot.)
Who could be the brokers?
I know they're not on my team.
So Min, I think the broker thing
is too complicated.
What do you mean?
If the broker's deal is accepted,
he or she wins another item.
What if it's turned down?
But what are you worried about?
As a broker, you just have to
propose a deal.
Gosh.
(Shocked)
- You're scary.
- Right?
You're scary.
You are a broker.
So Min. Seriously...
How can you be so shameless?
You're a broker.
- How dare you?
- You're scary.
You're scary.
Even innocent people
are suspected here.
You haven't been on this show
in so long.
You're really scary.
You are a broker.
Ji Hyo.
- Something didn't feel right.
- Sunhwa is a broker.
- She's a broker?
- Yes.
No, I'm not.
But Se Chan and Haha...
That sounds tough, right?
They're on her team.
What are they like?
(Ji Hyo sighs.)
Don't trust them.
Don't let them sweet-talk you.
- You think so?
- Yes.
Don't trust So Min.
- I can't trust anyone?
- I'm different.
- So Min is the most dangerous one.
- Are you buckled up?
- Yes.
- They'll shoot us eating too?
- Sunhwa, are you buckled up?
- Yes, I am.
Those cup noodles looked so tasty.
- Chapaghetti too.
- I want Chapaghetti.
I'm sure they're
some of the top-selling items.
Definitely.
The numbers are from 2019...
- and this year.
- 2019?
- They're from the past year?
- That's recent.
And we're talking about
the number of units sold.
- The number of units sold.
I'd guess Yoo Jung goes to
convenience stores often.
- I do.
- Right?
Young people go there a lot.
What's the first thing
you pick up there?
- Bottled water.
Many people buy bottled water
at convenience stores.
- I often buy bottled water.
- They do.
Or Coke.
- Ice cubes in cups.
- Coke?
Packed meals, triangular gimbap,
ramyeon...
- Triangular gimbap, definitely.
- Definitely.
You can only get it
at convenience stores.
I'm sure it's in the ranking.
You could even say,
without triangular gimbap,
convenience stores wouldn't be
where they are now.
Convenience stores were
made by companies.
(Jong Kook disagrees.)
- What's with you today?
- Hey!
There's an item I'm thinking of,
but I'm not going to tell you.
- Tell us. Come on.
- What is it?
- I'm sure it's near the top.
- Tell us.
- Sausages.
- Sausages?
- Sausages...
- That's just what you like.
They sell more than you think.
I think hangover drinks
sell a lot too.
- Gosh.
- Hangover drinks. That's right.
That's the only place
where hangover drinks are sold.
Yes, you can only buy them
at convenience stores.
- You're right.
- That's what I also said.
Hangover drinks.
Ji Hyo knows it well.
Everyone's just pointing out
what they mostly buy.
- Sausages, fish cake bars...
- Ramyeon...
Suk Jin, what do you think?
Isn't he more used
to union sales shops?
(Isn't he more used
to union sales shops?)
(People his age would be
more familiar with that.)
Is that the actual name?
I bet you called for barmaids.
(Should I play along with this?)
- Barmaid!
- I'd order rice and soup...
before climbing the mountain range.
How long would
your straw shoes last?
They'd wear out
after walking up two hills.
(I can't believe
he's playing along with this.)
Instead of coins or actual money,
we paid with shells.
- Really?
- With shells?
- Didn't you have currency?
- No, it was before that.
- He's playing along.
- Clamshells?
Have you seen
a royal insignia before?
(Will he play along with this too?)
Didn't I tell you about this?
A good friend of mine from school
became a secret inspector.
- A friend from school?
- Yes.
I felt betrayed because
we'd play together all the time.
But he still managed to study hard.
- He studied at night.
- Without you knowing?
He studied hard behind my back.
- Unbelievable.
- That's insane.
Anyway, I was surprised to see
how he turned out.
Did Shim Chung exist in real life?
- What about Chun Hyang?
- Did you ever get to see her?
Chun Hyang? Well, I had
only heard rumors about her.
What about Shim Chung?
- What about Shim Chung?
- That inspector is my friend.
- Really?
- What?
- No way.
- Are you kidding me?
- He's my friend.
- The puzzle pieces come together.
Exactly.
What does the poison taste like?
- What?
- The poison.
I didn't die by drinking it.
He said he never died.
Didn't you once drink it
until you were full?
(Ji Suk Jin, the immortal)
I heard that you ate rice
with your poison.
No way.
Suk Jin will be
exhausted after this.
You're draining his energy.
Suk Jin, you won't
have enough energy for later.
As you know, back then,
we weren't able
to meet with women freely.
- But I saw Chun Hyang.
- How was she?
- Was she pretty?
- She didn't have double eyelids.
Magistrate Byun? He was pure evil,
so don't get me started on him.
- There weren't photos back then.
- Exactly.
- Someone drew a picture.
- A drawing.
- How can it be trusted though?
- I know.
- Can this be aired?
- No way.
It sounds too fake
to even be a joke.
Jae Suk drew an X.
- It'll never air.
- But it sounds true...
coming from him.
We all pitched in at first,
but we sneaked out one by one.
It became boring
once Suk Jin found it funny.
Jae Suk's analysis is funnier.
Jong Kook's jokes
shouldn't be returned so easily.
It lost its appeal
because Suk Jin found it funny.
He played along too easily.
Jong Kook kept going
to see who would give in first.
I heard that Magistrate Byun
was quite handsome though.
- You have no idea.
- Really?
(Wasn't it over?)
He could even be better looking
than Chang Wook.
- Better looking than Chang Wook?
- Yes.
- I feel bad for you now.
- Can you please stop?
- This isn't a pretty sight.
- Please stop.
- Jong Kook, please stop.
- But it's funny.
- It's funny though.
- Jong Kook...
- Did you hear him or not?
- You're exhausting him.
He's only doing this
to entertain you, Jong Kook.
- But Suk Jin...
- This...
- I was bored.
- He kept going for you.
Gosh, what is this?
What's this for?
Are we doing something in secret?
- Also...
- Yoo Jung, you can sit here.
There must be some sort of mission.
There must be.
- It's a convenience store.
- What?
Is this security camera footage?
(What kind of game will they play
at the convenience store?)
The first game is called
Sweet Combinations.
- Sweet Combinations?
- Right.
Each team will go in turns.
You are to successfully
make and bring back...
the three customized items
that have been pre-ordered.
We must make them?
Four members of the staff
already placed their orders...
to us.
One other team...
will enter blindfolded
but with a toy hammer.
If you get hit by the hammer,
you will be out.
- No way!
- We'll be driven out.
The ones remaining
must make the dishes themselves.
- We shouldn't make noise.
- So you must stay quiet...
and make the dishes fast.
You will go in turns.
The team with the fastest record...
- will win the game.
- Got it.
The teams will now
choose a member of the staff.
Please show it to the camera.
1, 2, 3, and 4.
Did Sunhwa choose number three?
Good.
When Team One enters,
Team Two will follow
with toy hammers.
- Jong Kook's coming for us.
- We'll go after Team Four.
- Gosh.
- It's his team?
- Are you Team Two?
- It'll be doomsday.
All right. Team Two will enter...
- and get ready with the hammers.
- Unbelievable.
Yoo Jung...
Jong Kook will be a tough opponent.
He'll use his strength to stop us.
Then go ahead and hit him.
We need to take these.
They'll be making the dishes
on a table.
- Right?
- How can we possibly miss?
Will we have to wear blindfolds?
Of course.
Right? We must be blindfolded.
Isn't that obvious?
I knew it wouldn't be that easy.
Why would you even ask that?
The microwave is over there,
so that's where they'll go.
Right?
(Microwave 2, Drinks, Microwave 3)
(Snacks, Ramyeon, Gimbap and Drinks,
Microwave 1, Counter)
They'll have to come over here.
This is where
the ramyeon and other things are.
- We should... Yoo Jung!
- Yes?
We'll each take an aisle.
We're responsible for one lane each.
One each? I'll take this one.
Someone from Team One
will step forward...
and pick a staff member.
- Team 1, go ahead.
- Team 1?
- Let me see.
- Sure.
(The orders made
by the members of the staff)
Go Ji Yeon, the youngest director.
Kang Chae Ra, the floor director.
Kang Chan Hee,
the director of photography.
I choose Mr. Kang Chan Hee.
I doubt he knows...
a lot about what you can make
in convenience stores.
- He wouldn't mix things.
- It won't be too complicated.
- I'm not sure about this.
- He'd keep it simple.
- Are you sure?
- There's a lot written down.
"Heat in the microwave
for 30 seconds..."
- What's the menu?
- Let me read these to you.
A peeled triangular gimbap...
that's been heated up in
the microwave for 30 seconds.
A cup of grain latte made from
a grain snack and grain milk.
A sandwich made from
a cheese bun and potato salad.
(He can't believe his ears.)
But...
You're quite picky, Mr. Kang.
- That's what you enjoy?
- Those aren't easy to make.
I had no idea
that he enjoyed grain latte.
I like his recipes though.
The grain snack
would be delicious though.
I'd like to try them.
- Did you have to pick number one?
- Sang Woo...
No, you did great.
- They're here!
- Are they here?
They're here!
(The soldiers are ready
with their toy hammers.)
They haven't entered yet.
Actually, I have no idea.
- What do we do?
- Actually, I have no idea.
Make sure you don't hit the stands.
They could be in here already.
(Team Sang Woo enters covertly.)
- Are they inside?
- Are they in here?
- Can't you tell us? Who's there?
- What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
They don't know
that Team Sang Woo entered.
(Thump!)
- Is someone there?
- No, I hit something else.
(While Team Yoo Jung
wanders around...)
(They spot a triangular gimbap.)
- Is someone there?
- No, it's just the stand.
I'm...
(They pick up a triangular gimbap.)
- But...
- I'm checking the back too.
The microwave is over there.
They won't even let us know
if they've entered.
(Suk Jin is standing guard.)
Who's this?
- Are they not...
- Who's this?
- Aren't they inside yet?
- They're over there.
- Team Sang Woo is already inside.
- Already?
Really?
(Suk Jin's right
next to Jong Kook.)
(But Jong Kook has nowhere to go.)
(Jong Kook tries to slide past him.)
We need to locate them.
(Jong Kook gets past Suk Jin
undetected.)
I can't see a thing.
- Where are they?
- It's not easy.
We should keep in mind
that they don't make any noise.
Help me.
Did you hit someone or not?
(Jong Kook squeezes through.)
There's someone here!
(The old man waves
around his hammer.)
I sense someone.
Where?
Over here.
Where? Someone ran past me.
(Sang Woo, distract him for me.)
- Hold on.
- Someone threw something.
Someone's here!
- Where?
- I heard something.
(So Min and Sang Woo
have nowhere to go.)
- Where?
- Charge!
Where?
(So Min quickly
makes an escape too.)
Where are they?
I heard them over here but...
I can't tell where they are.
(Beeping)
- The microwave!
(Busted!)
(Jong Kook is surrounded
by Yoo Jung and Suk Jin.)
- Where are they?
- By the microwave.
(He sees an opening
and manages to escape.)
- Where are they?
- I heard someone over here.
- Is there another microwave here?
- Where?
- Where are they?
- By the microwave.
- Where?
- Over here.
- Gosh, it's just me.
- Where?
- Where are they?
- I'm sorry.
- Someone's here.
- Hold on a second.
- Here.
- I heard the microwave beep.
- Who is this?
- Who am I hitting?
- It's me.
- Yoo Jung, is this you?
- Who's this?
- It's me you're hitting.
- I found someone.
- Where?
- Who is this?
- Who are you?
- I'm the cameraman.
- The cameraman?
- I'm sorry.
Are you sure?
Someone should stay behind there.
Don't stay here.
(Jong Kook heads to
another microwave.)
(Beeping)
I heard something!
- Right?
- There are two microwaves.
- There are two microwaves?
- There's one up front.
Wasn't it the microwave
beeping just now?
- There's one up front?
- Really?
Hold on a second.
I heard something.
- What's this?
- It came from the left.
Over there.
I heard it again!
(The moment the microwave beeps,)
(Jong Kook comes flying forward.)
Over there.
I heard it again!
It's the microwave.
- Where?
- The timer's up.
(Jong Kook's surrounded though.)
The timer's up.
(He makes a run for it
through the small opening.)
- Where?
- The microwave is done.
I definitely heard something.
It came from the left.
- It came from across the store.
- I can smell the food now.
- Suk Jin, stay there.
- Okay.
(They only have to leave
the store now.)
Hold on.
(Will Team Sang Woo be able
to safely exit the store?)
(Sang Woo makes it out first.)
(Jong Kook also
makes it out safely!)
The dishes will
be evaluated outside.
Hold on. Someone just poked me.
Really?
- Here...
- Unbelievable.
- I hit someone.
- You did?
Yes, I just did.
Didn't I hit anyone?
Are they done already?
- I had a blast.
- Did you make all the dishes?
You have to go back in
if you didn't follow the recipe.
- Really?
- Sang Woo,
- what kind of milk did you use?
- Good job, So Min.
It was...
normal white milk.
You got the menu wrong,
so you have to make it again.
- Again?
- You have to make grain latte.
Grain latte?
- What's this?
- Is that grain milk?
- What's that?
- Grain...
Quick, Sang Woo. You messed up.
(He checks the recipe
one more time.)
I don't hear anything.
Did they take their shoes off?
I don't think they left yet.
They're still inside.
(Zombie Yu has
neither reflex nor wits.)
(He gets the ingredients again.)
(While Sang Woo picks out
the ingredients...)
(Hitting)
(So Min tries to confuse him.)
What are they doing?
Somebody just hit me.
(Sang Woo throws a trap as well.)
(Screaming)
(He strikes Suk Jin's belly.)
Hey!
(The toy hammer got his sides.)
(They find the blunder hilarious.)
Who makes that sound
after getting hit by a toy hammer?
It made full contact.
I hear footsteps. Footsteps!
(What's he doing by himself?)
I hear footsteps. That way!
Where?
Ahead of me.
(They just have to get out
to complete all items on the menu.)
Where are they?
(This is a bait.)
Hey.
- It's me.
- Is it you?
(Team Sang Woo completes all items.)
How many times did you hit me?
- This fell off.
- The mission is over.
- Suk Jin.
- Jae Suk keeps on hitting me.
We thought you were going to die.
- Why?
- They keep fighting.
Jae Suk hit you too many times.
Why did you hit me so many times?
You made weird sounds.
I stood next to you
for the longest time.
- How?
- Right in front of you.
You were like zombies
in front of the microwave.
I turned on the microwave,
and you were all there.
There were two microwaves.
Gosh, the microwave.
You were like zombies.
It's our turn next.
We should do well.
Try Go Ji Yeon,
the youngest director.
You have to microwave it
for a long time.
Please get back.
(Tteokbokki microwaved for 1 minute,
cocktail with plain yogurt...)
- This is better.
- What?
(and orange juice,
ice cream with chocolate snack)
Let's turn off the microwave.
- When they come.
- Jae Suk.
Look. It's this button.
Increase the time or turn it off.
How did they do it so perfectly?
Which team is inside?
I think Jae Suk is good
at this game.
Are they inside?
- They're inside.
- They're inside!
(She's nervous.)
- Go. Go around.
- Are they inside?
(She patiently picks out
the ingredients.)
- Are they inside?
- Go around.
(Tteokbokki microwaved for 1 minute)
I'm off.
(She gets tteokbokki and backs off.)
(He's on full alert.)
I hear footsteps.
(Ice cream with chocolate snack)
- They're inside, right?
- I think so.
(Yoo Jung makes tteokbokki
in the corner.)
They're inside. It's this way.
Where?
(While Haha turns away,)
(he gets the ice cream cone.)
I heard them.
(He strikes with his toy hammer.)
(That was close.)
I don't think
they're coming this way.
- Over there.
- I heard them.
(I heard them.)
It's this way. I heard them.
- Where are you?
- Where?
(Inching slowly)
- Who's this?
- It's me.
Welcome.
(What are you doing over there?)
I think somebody is over here.
- Come this way. It's me.
- Where are you?
- Corner them!
- Left side.
- Did you touch them?
- Didn't I hit them?
Didn't I?
- It's me.
- I can't see anything.
What was that?
They're nowhere.
(Sniffing)
(He follows the smell
and reaches the microwave.)
What's this?
Somebody microwaved food.
They did?
It smells sweet. What's this?
I think it's triangular gimbap.
(It's the triangular gimbap
Jong Kook failed to remove.)
I'll put it in my pocket.
Se Chan.
(He keeps the inheritance
Jong Kook left.)
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- Did they microwave something?
- They did but couldn't take it.
Really? Take it out.
- I did. It's in my pocket.
- Is it?
(Ice cream with chocolate snack)
I found it.
- I heard a sound.
- Here.
- Se Chan.
- Did you get them?
I opened the microwave,
and I smelled ramyeon.
(Suk Jin and Yoo Jung get away.)
(Jae Suk gets cornered!)
I heard a sound.
(He uses his sense of touch
and hearing.)
It's over here. This way.
(He's a psychic
who uses his five senses.)
I don't know where they are.
- I hear a sound.
- Haha.
Come this way.
(He covers his mouth.)
(The situation is
about to escalate.)
- Who are you?
- No one's here.
Hey, Jong Kook!
(Is this the cameraman?)
Haha, does the cameraman
have a microphone?
Hey!
(I caught you, rascal!)
Who are you?
- Did you get somebody?
- Jae Suk is out.
- It was Jae Suk.
- Good job.
Who did it? Good job.
- My gosh.
- Haha.
Please return everything.
I smelled him.
He smells so good.
Wait.
Oh, my gosh.
(He exits
without getting anything done.)
- They're coming this way.
- It's me.
Hey.
- Yoo Jung is out.
- Yes!
Suk Jin is out.
- Is Suk Jin out?
- Is he out?
How am I out?
(While Se Chan was
going after Yoo Jung,)
(he gently touched Suk Jin.)
- Is everybody out?
- Yes.
Okay!
- Really?
- How am I out?
Was it me?
Gosh, Jae Suk.
How did he get caught?
- I smelled him.
- You smelled him?
He smells good.
Move that way.
We have to make sounds
for each other.
You have to keep moving.
With potato chips.
- Oh, gosh.
- We're done for.
- I always get caught.
- With cheddar cheese.
Nacho? Microwaved.
Where are you?
I'm over here. I'm by the door.
- By the door?
- Yes.
We won't know when they come in.
(Kwang Soo is already nervous.)
- Oh, dear.
- What was that?
- What was that? What did I hit?
- Are they inside?
- I don't know.
Did I break something?
Where was that?
I don't think they're here yet.
(This team looks sloppy already.)
What's this? I can't see.
(They pass by Kwang Soo's territory
rather easily.)
(They see Chang Wook
waiting in ambush.)
- Where are they?
- They're inside.
They're inside.
(He stands up.)
(He's making way for them?)
- Are they inside?
- Are they?
(Grabbing)
(Canafe with vegetable tuna
on crackers)
- We have started.
- They're inside.
(Pear ice cream is in here.)
- What's this?
- Over here.
- Where?
(Kwang Soo is worked up.)
- Here.
- Where?
Here. The freezer is open.
Who is this?
- Where?
- Here.
(Se Chan is getting cornered.)
- Where?
- Over here.
- Here.
Where?
(Bang! Bang!)
Don't break things!
(He plays a warning alert.)
Somebody took ice cream.
Hey.
- Who are you?
- Are you okay? Me.
It's you.
- Where are you?
- Wait.
They're not here.
(He gets an item easily
from Kwang Soo's territory.)
Snacks!
- It's me.
- They're not here.
(He tries to get ice cream again.)
- Here. Ice cream!
- Where? Which one?
(He runs away in a hurry.)
Which one?
They got away.
(These two dummies can't even
block the freezer.)
- This is open.
- I know.
They need something from here.
(They're like automatic doors.)
- They left.
- I heard the bell.
They left? They're already done?
- This is not the camera.
- What?
(He bumped into something.)
- Where are you?
- No, I'm in pain.
Wait, the microwave is done.
(Chang Wook, I'm coming to help!)
Where was it? I smell it.
(Zombie Ji smelled money
from the ATM.)
Is this it? Is this the microwave?
It's open. They can't take it.
(He finds tteokbokki
that was being made.)
(He's eating it with his hand?)
Kwang Soo, you can't eat that.
(This is a new way of defending.)
This is hot.
What are you eating?
This is hot. It's a rice cake.
What are you doing?
What's this?
(She felt something.)
What? Did they eat something?
(He holds his breath.)
(She can smell a man in his 30s.)
(Hitting)
Hey.
I got them!
- I got Se Chan.
- I was almost done.
- Se Chan is out.
- I got him.
(He was almost done.)
(There are 2 items
and 2 people left.)
They're over here!
(Chang Wook almost had him.)
- Where?
- Kwang Soo!
They got away.
- Who was it?
- By the door!
- They're getting away.
- Who was it?
(He runs away like a coward.)
- Where did he go?
- My gosh.
- What did you have to make?
- What is it?
- One person is out.
Chang Wook. I smell something.
I smell something.
It's hot. I'm eating right now.
Kwang Soo, what are you eating?
(It's actually good.)
- I think it's tteokbokki.
- They're over here.
Ice cream!
(They're over here. Ice cream!)
- Ice cream!
Please don't hit too hard.
- Where are they?
- Over here!
- It's me.
- This is good.
- What are you having?
- I want it too.
- I finished it.
You finished it?
Is it cheese or pizza tteokbokki?
(He enjoyed the food
without doing his job.)
(She's not even hiding,
and nobody is stopping her.)
(She's relaxed.)
(She finished the drink without
anybody interfering with her.)
- Hey.
- I heard a sound.
It's me! It's me!
- Hey, it's me.
- Where?
Hey, it's me.
- You brat!
- Where? My bad.
- Are you okay?
- Where are you?
Everybody, the mission is over.
They must be gone.
(Team Chang Wook used up
their energy for nothing.)
I heard something.
(Team Sang Woo is here
to block them.)
This is like cardio.
(This is like cardio.)
(Kwang Soo comes in ambitiously.)
- Who is this?
- I got someone.
Who is it? Who did you catch?
(He gives Chang Wook some tips
as he leaves.)
Gosh, I'm out already.
Okay.
Why is he holding a real hammer?
Isn't it a real hammer?
(Team Chang Wook's turn
ends in vain.)
Let me announce the results
of Sweet Combinations.
Team Sang Woo won
without getting caught...
for 7 minutes and 49 seconds.
They're in 1st place.
(Team Sang Woo won 1st place with
a record of 7 minutes 49 seconds.)
We're the best.
Team Sunhwa who finished
the mission with two members out...
in 10 minutes and 12 seconds
won 2nd place.
- Good.
- This is nice.
Team Chang Wook and Team Yoo Jung
are all out.
Team Chang Wook who held out for
11 minutes and 6 seconds is the 3rd.
Okay.
Team Yoo Jung is the 4th
with a record...
- of 5 minutes and 45 seconds.
- Only 5 minutes?
- That's a big difference.
- We were very quick though.
Let's move to the next place...
and pick the first item.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Well done.
- Okay.
(What's the popular convenience
store item they will pick?)
Do we have two spies here?
- Brokers.
- What do brokers do?
- What's the deal with the brokers?
- What are the brokers for?
What do they do?
The brokers...
already threw...
their offers many times
while performing the mission.
- Really?
- What?
- They threw their offers?
- To whom?
When did they do that?
(The two brokers were told
to offer their proposal earlier.)
(Take a picture of the name tag
or write down...)
(the name of the person
you want to propose a deal to.)
(During the mission, the brokers
approached the production crew.)
They offer their proposal
to the production crew?
To the production crew? I see.
What happens
if we catch the brokers?
If you find out the brokers,
you will get
a doubling sticker per each.
You can double your points
with the sticker.
It's a good one.
- If you fail to find the brokers...
- We should catch them.
Who are the brokers?
Suk Jin just said that
when he doesn't even care.
I thought he was
talking in his sleep.
Chang Wook, are you the broker?
(He yells at Chang Wook
all of a sudden.)
- He just yelled out of the blue.
- I didn't even say anything.
- Who is it?
- What's wrong with you?
I think...
this is what Suk Jin can do.
I think so. It's no big deal.
- It's not that big a deal.
- I know.
- It's a small role.
- Even if he gets caught,
- it doesn't ruin the whole race.
- I know.
- Suk Jin sounds right for it.
- That's what Suk Jin can do.
It doesn't affect the whole race.
- He seems so happy to be suspected.
- It's you, right?
Yes. Sure.
- How did you know?
- It can't be him.
- It's not him.
- My gosh.
I shouldn't suspect him.
- Chang Wook.
- Yes?
Who do you think the brokers are?
I think it's either Sunhwa...
I agree.
Can you tell us the truth,
swearing on our drama?
- You're the broker, aren't you?
- No.
She even mentioned her drama.
They sound serious.
Why would you say it on our drama?
Can you swear on our drama
that you're not the broker?
That's not what we do.
What will you do with your drama?
- It's just...
- What if you're lying?
We will leave the drama.
- Leave the drama?
- Leave?
- What?
- Leave the drama?
- Do you have to do that?
- Why would you quit it?
He's right. We should enjoy.
It'll be funny if you quit the drama
because of Running Man.
(Sunhwa leaves the drama because
of her promise with Running Man.)
"I have no choice. I made
my promise with them."
"What's the reason?"
- "In Running Man..."
- I was the broker in Running Man.
"I have no choice. I made
my promise with them."
"I hid the fact
that I was the broker."
Is the mission for the brokers
something like this?
- Hey, Bones. Stay quiet.
- Bones.
- Me?
- Which one?
- He has bones.
- He has bones on his shirt.
I see. That's what he means.
Why did you put this on?
Dream can't go out because of you.
(As Jong Kook makes
a slight joke,)
(they burst into laughter.)
You're wearing Dream's shirt.
Do you know what's funny here?
Only his two underlings
laugh at his joke.
No one else laughed.
(While everyone is quiet,)
(only the two of them
burst into laughter.)
- Only the two underlings.
- Hey.
(The original underling
studies Jong Kook's face quietly.)
- Why would you call us underlings?
- No one laughed.
Use good words. Like subordinates.
Only his underlings...
Only his subordinates are laughing.
No one else laughed.
Why did you not laugh?
You're his underling number four.
Because...
(She bursts into laughter
as if she was waiting.)
(Our captain is so funny.)
He's really funny.
Good.
Jong Kook, your underling
number five is not laughing.
- He's laughing now.
- He's laughing quietly.
He was laughing quietly.
I'm number four.
- He says he's number 4.
- "I'm number 4."
Suk Jin is...
You guys are mistaken. He's a mole.
(They head to the next destination
ranking the underlings.)
Everyone.
It's time to pick
your first hot item.
Team Sang Woo won
the convenience store mission.
You get to pick one item you want
and put it on your table.
There are two kinds of water.
The big one and the small one.
What matters is how many of them
were sold.
There are many kinds of water.
For your information, the brokers
might want to pick bad items...
on purpose for the competition.
(The brokers might induce
their members to pick bad items.)
Can we pick three items?
- No, only one.
- We get to pick one.
- Triangular gimbap?
- Triangular gimbap.
- I should pick triangular gimbap.
- Let's do that.
- Triangular gimbap?
- Isn't this it?
Hang on. What if
triangular gimbap is sold out?
If you pick the most popular item,
you will get 15 points.
And 14 points
for the second popular item.
You get 1 point for the 15th item.
All right. I guess this is it.
- Triangular gimbap?
- No.
- Is it over?
- Are you done?
Yes. We picked triangular gimbap.
- Okay.
- It's triangular gimbap.
Who's next?
There are a lot of popular items.
- This is red bean jelly.
- Hang on. I think...
it's either cup noodles or water.
No. Just trust me this once.
All right then.
Let's go with that.
- I guess he's right.
- We picked this.
- Is that what you got?
- Okay.
Are you sure?
(Team Sunhwa picks cup noodles
as Se Chan insists.)
They picked cup noodles.
I'm sure about this.
It's a 500ml bottle of water.
(They pick 500ml water
in confidence.)
- Do you have any idea?
- Sausage.
- But people don't eat it a lot.
- No, it must be sausage.
- I don't think so.
- Suk Jin.
- But...
- I'm telling you.
- Is he the broker?
- I don't think it's popular.
- No, I'm serious.
- It doesn't sound right.
- People don't eat it a lot.
- Do people really eat it a lot?
I read something.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
No.
- Isn't it soda?
- I'm sure this is it.
- Are you sure?
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- What about chewing gum?
I don't think so.
- Are you sure?
- What about ice cream?
Are you serious?
Do you not want to pick ice cream?
He's the broker. He's being strange.
(Jae Suk picks sausage
despite the strong opposition.)
- We eat ice cream even in winter.
- You're the broker.
I'm telling you.
Jae seok is the broker.
- I think he's the broker.
- You're the broker.
(Jae Suk is being suspicious.
Is he really the broker?)
I'm sure about this. Listen to me.
Why would we listen to you?
You're unreliable.
You can't pick what you like.
Jae Suk, you don't even
go to a convenience store.
We don't have anything else to pick.
Just listen to me this once.
- Come here.
- What about ice cream?
What about fish cake bar?
- What do you mean?
Just come here, Yoo Jung.
(They are all done
picking their first items.)
You guys made your choice.
Now I will reveal the offers
from the brokers made in Round One.
(The offers from the two brokers
are revealed now.)
The first broker, A...
made an offer to Team Sang Woo.
(Broker A made an offer
to Team Sang Woo.)
- I didn't hear it.
- And Broker B made...
an offer to Team Sunhwa,
Yoo Jung, and Chang Wook.
Even to us?
I guess they tried to confuse us.
- Broker B is...
- We can catch them.
Oh, my.
Now you should think about it.
If you accept the offer,
you can pick one more item.
(If they accept the offer,
they can pick one more item.)
But if you accept it,
the broker will...
also get one more chance
to pick an item.
- What's the offer?
- What if we don't accept it?
You can't pick an extra item,
but you can get a hint
about the broker.
- Let's not accept it then.
- Okay.
We'd better get a hint.
- I think getting a hint is better.
- If we pick one more item...
Let's get a hint.
Let's just accept the offer.
We should accept it.
- No. Are you the broker?
- I'm not.
We should find out
who the brokers are.
- Do you want to get a hint?
- We can double our points.
Let's accept the offer.
- What do you want to do?
- We should accept it.
- I'm thinking about it.
- We should get it.
Do you want to get a hint?
It will be over if our team wins.
If you're not the broker,
you won't accept the offer.
(Team Chang Wook wants
to accept the broker's offer.)
Captain Kim, we will
follow your opinion.
- I think it's okay to accept one.
- Okay.
Our captain, Yoo Jung,
wants to accept the offer.
- Are you accepting the offer?
- Yes.
We want to accept the offer too.
- We will accept it.
- We will accept the offer.
They accepted it before you did,
so they get to pick first.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Captain Kim.
- We made a good choice.
The brokers can pick
the same items later.
- This is about the number of sales.
- Exactly.
Do you want ice cream?
(Captain Kim wants
to pick ice cream.)
Do you want it? Okay.
- Wait. Ice cream and...
- This isn't right.
That's what she wants.
- Captain Kim, bring this.
- What?
She picked ice cream.
- It's just the color of your shirt.
- That's what our captain wants.
- They picked only strange ones.
- It matches their shirt.
We picked this.
Corn tea?
But you wanted this.
I didn't see this coming.
Okay.
- What did you say before?
- We'll pick Chapaghetti.
- Let's take the risk.
- We will accept the offer.
(Team Sang Woo accepts the offer
and picks a lighter.)
- A lighter?
- Yes.
The brokers must be excited.
(The brokers get to pick
more items as well.)
- We all accepted the offer.
- All right then.
All the four teams
accepted the offer.
Let's move on to the second mission.
(Hot Item Selection Status)
The second mission is...
Your Fate in Your Hands
where you control...
the fate of your own team.
Do you see the water balloons
over your heads?
They have water in them.
And it has 10 layers of balloons.
We will give you
an eyebrow razor later.
You can cut it carefully,
you can survive 10 times.
If you do it wrong,
it will burst immediately.
- I'm scared.
- I know what it is.
If we do it right, it won't
burst for 10 times.
So this is what you're going to do.
The production crew
will present a question.
And you will name a member
to the question.
The rest of the members will hear it
and guess what the question is.
If your balloon bursts,
you will get one more balloon.
You get two balloons.
The first team to pop the two
balloons will lose the game.
- Okay.
- And the 2nd one is in 3rd place.
- I want to win.
- Then you should decide...
who will answer the question.
So Min.
But So Min is quite imaginative.
Pick one question...
and tell them your answer
to the question.
Tell them your opinion.
This question is tricky.
- The question is too hard.
- Is it hard?
What is it, So Min?
- It's not about love.
- Is that so?
- It's about the opposite sex.
- Okay.
(Who does So Min think is top 1
regarding this question?)
It's about the opposite sex.
The answer is clear.
- Anyone would have chosen him.
- Who?
Jae Suk.
(Top 1 is Jae Suk.)
- I am serious.
- Let me answer.
(Haha is ready to answer
right away.)
- The person who is ugly in my eyes.
- No.
- I didn't try to throw people off.
- The answer is clear.
- Did you think of him right away?
Other people just don't fit.
There is only one possible answer.
Yoo Jae Suk.
You are Michael Jordan
of this question.
Had this been an encyclopedia entry,
- his name would have been there.
- Really?
The man who shouldn't take off
his glasses before women.
Let me answer.
The man who thinks
he is popular among women.
- Incorrect.
- The man who is delusional.
You are nowhere near the answer.
- Jae Suk...
- I can't get it right.
The production crew agrees
with So Min's answer.
- Really?
- Everyone agrees.
The answer has to be Jae Suk.
Even if I choose the top two,
the gap would be too big.
Jae Suk is way up there.
- Really?
- Is he way up there?
It must be something
about appearances.
- Is it about being rich?
- Appearances?
Is it about being rich?
Why would it be about being rich?
You lack in so many ways.
- It's hard to choose one.
- Why would you say that?
- It's true. You lack...
- Let me answer.
The man whose child
must take after his or her mother.
Incorrect.
Is it a good thing or a bad thing?
It's a good thing...
because you are Yoo Jae Suk.
- Is it a good thing?
- If there is someone like him...
who isn't Yoo Jae Suk,
it would be really bad.
Someone like him
who isn't Yoo Jae Suk?
- Then it would be really bad.
- Yes.
You are saying it's a good thing
that he is Yoo Jae Suk.
It's a good thing
Would you give us a motion hint
that fits the situation?
- This is hard.
- Right, give us a motion hint.
A motion hint?
Hello, everyone. I am Yoo Jae Suk.
Today...
(Fans cheers upon seeing Jae Suk.)
- Jae Suk! Let's shake hands.
- Let me answer.
The man who should be glad
that he became a celebrity.
(Incorrect)
It's close to the answer.
- Right?
- Is it close?
- Yes, it is.
- I knew it.
Okay, okay.
Come on, guys.
Let me answer.
The man who wouldn't have succeeded
if he weren't a celebrity.
The man who wouldn't have married
The man who would be a celebrity
even in his next life.
The man who is popular among women
only because he is a celebrity.
Yes!
(Correct)
How could you say that?
(They finally understand why
Jae Suk is top 1 by a landslide.)
(Jong Kook gives a ceremony
with a man who avoided misfortune.)
Thank you.
- So Min, that was neat.
- Thank you.
- That was neat.
- I chose the right one.
It hit me.
"Only because he is a celebrity"
was like a wakeup call.
It's true.
Let's start with this team.
Slash the balloon once.
Should I do it?
How much do we need to slash?
While it can be small,
at least one layer must come off.
- This is scary.
- Do it like this.
- Slash lightly.
- Do it lightly.
There you go.
- There you go.
(One layer came off
when she put the blade against it.)
It came off so easily.
That was no joke.
- It's a different color.
- She barely touched it.
- It was so scary.
- Team Ji Chang Wook.
- Who wants to go first?
- Do you want to go first?
- Hold on.
You need to sit down and do it.
- Do I need to sit down?
- Of course.
- This is insane.
- Do it gently.
Give it a small poke.
A small poke.
I can't do it. Hold on.
Do it the second time.
- Go first.
- Okay.
- A small poke.
- I'll try my best.
- I will slash it here.
- A small poke.
- Hold on.
- You need to slash it.
This is nerve-wracking.
How did you do it?
(The blade hasn't even touched
the balloon yet.)
A small poke.
The blade touched the balloon,
but it wouldn't pop.
The blade...
(They are overreacting.)
- The blade touched the balloon.
- It didn't touch the balloon.
What's wrong with you guys?
Hey, this is...
(Chang Wook gets too scared
and tosses it to Kwang Soo.)
Give it a light poke.
It isn't working.
- Kwang Soo, drive it in there.
- Come on.
Drive it in there.
(It popped!)
I did it really gently.
- Hey.
- I did it really gently.
- Good job.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
You really slashed all 10 layers.
I just put the blade gently
against the balloon.
- How did you do it?
- Sunhwa did a great job.
- I did it gently.
- How did she remove one layer?
I did it really gently.
- Yoo Jung.
- All right.
Let's go.
This is fun.
(She succeeded to remove one layer.)
Good job.
(She is surprised.)
(Jae Suk makes a big fuss.)
It was so nerve-wracking.
(Captain Yoo Jung
succeeded courageously.)
Good job.
The second team should pick someone
who will answer the question.
- Let's keep it simple.
- Se Chan.
- Okay.
If it's about ugliness,
the answer is Kwang Soo.
That goes without saying.
- Se Chan.
- Watch me.
I will be able to guess the question
once I hear the name.
- That's right.
- Let's go.
I will figure it out right away.
Who is it?
Hold on.
- Let's hear it.
- The question must be vague.
- Sit here.
- Keep it simple.
- No one fits it perfectly.
- That's right.
- Don't lie.
- I won't.
- I will figure it out right away.
- Let's go.
(After much deliberation,
he chooses...)
- Sunhwa.
- Me?
- This is hard. Sunhwa?
- Sunhwa?
- I...
- Let me answer.
The person who can lie the best.
Let me answer.
The person who is a scatterbrain.
(Incorrect)
Let me answer.
The person who is ignorant.
That was forever ago.
- I don't watch TV.
- You are stuck in the past.
Let me answer.
The person who has never dated.
- What?
- Sunhwa?
- I have dated a few men. My gosh.
- Is it a compliment or what?
Please reveal the top 2 and 3
as a hint.
- The top 2 and 3?
- Okay, that will help.
- I will get it right.
- This is hard.
- Then I choose Yoo Jung.
- If he mentions Chang Wook...
Yoo Jung?
And Chang Wook.
I see that sex doesn't matter.
It's related to our job.
- Our job?
- Yes.
Let me answer.
- If Se Chan were to meet someone...
- That's right.
- It's too long.
- in the industry...
Is that your guess?
- If Se Chan were to meet someone...
- What are you talking about?
That's not how you play this game.
- Is it incorrect?
- It's incorrect.
Let me answer.
The person who is the worst
at investing.
Let me answer.
Being a celebrity,
we have many worries and...
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- That's ridiculous.
- What did I do wrong?
- Your answer is too long.
- It wasn't too long.
- Let me answer.
The person who has given
the most amount of autographs.
- No, that's not it.
- Let me answer.
When you are
in the entertainment industry,
you come across people
who haven't...
- Hurry up and answer.
- What are you doing?
Are you a doctor?
Can't I guess?
- It was ridiculous.
- Can't I guess?
For goodness' sake.
Give us a hint.
- Would you like a motion hint?
- Yes.
(Rubbing his eyes)
Let me answer!
(Confident)
- I haven't done anything yet.
- The person with bad sight...
- Incorrect. Let me keep going.
- It's incorrect.
- I am not done yet.
- He hasn't given a hint yet.
- I will keep it simple.
- Don't show unnecessary motions.
I got confused because you did this.
- I wanted to bring out the detail.
- Why did you rub your eyes?
I wanted to bring out the detail.
- I will keep it straightforward.
- Let me answer!
- Sunhwa was faster.
I was faster.
She was faster.
The person who looks up
his or her name the most.
That's it!
(Correct)
I rubbed my eyes to express
doing so on a search engine.
- Good job.
- So that was the answer.
I did think of that.
Then why did you sit still?
I said "Let me answer" too late.
Team Sang Woo, go first.
Team Chang Wook, you are out
if you pop this balloon.
What? Out?
We only get two balloons.
You will do well.
Sang Woo will do it.
Do it gently. Relax your wrist.
Just put the blade on the surface.
- It will pop if you push.
- Pop.
Pop. Pop.
- Just put the blade on the surface.
- Yes.
Gently.
- Why isn't it working?
- Scratch it.
- No.
- It isn't...
- There you go.
(He succeeds to slash 2 layers.)
- Two layers.
- My goodness.
How many layers did you slash?
Two layers? That's a lot.
- Team Yoo Jung.
- Shall we go first?
Yoo Jung.
- Yoo Jung, we believe in you.
- She is...
a professional.
Come closer. If it pops,
we should get wet together.
That's right.
Suk Jin, move your head.
Yoo Jung, we believe in you.
- Yoo Jung, please.
- You can do it.
- Do it gently.
- Come on.
- Yoo Jung, do it gently.
- There you go.
- Gently.
- It's in.
- That's enough.
- My goodness.
- You are practically slicing it.
- Hold on.
- For goodness' sake.
Yoo Jung, you need to ignore them
and do it.
- I am sorry.
- Just do it.
- I can't concentrate.
I couldn't help but talk.
- We will keep quiet.
- Okay, okay.
The balloon doesn't pop easily.
- That's right.
- Don't listen to them.
(She manages to slash one layer
this time as well.)
Yoo Jung.
How are you so good at it?
You are a genius.
It peeled off so fast.
If you pop this balloon,
you are out.
All right.
Do it gently. Do it gently.
- Do it gently.
- Gently.
(Gently)
Rub it back and forth.
No. Keep it on the same spot.
Hold on.
- I am sorry.
- You keep blowing air...
into my ear.
I am sorry.
Stop blowing air into his ear.
Why would you blow air into his ear?
Do it gently.
(He covers his ear.)
- Gently.
- Keep it on the same spot.
- It pops very easily.
- Hit it lightly.
- There are 10 layers, so it's okay.
- No, no. Don't listen to him.
(Hitting)
- Don't listen to him.
- Seriously.
- How could you listen to him?
- Keep your ears closed.
Don't listen to anyone.
Do what you want to do.
- Just keep your touch gentle.
- Let's focus.
He will do it now.
Chang Wook.
Hey, that's...
(Shaking)
- There you go.
- Hit it lightly.
- Hey, hey!
- Hold on!
- There you go.
- Hit it lightly.
- Hey, hey!
- Hold on!
- I can't do it.
- You should do it.
- Do it gently.
- Do it as if trimming your brows.
It's almost done.
- Okay. I got it.
- Give it a try.
Do it gently.
- Do you want me to do it?
- This is our last chance.
- Hold on.
- Don't hit it.
That tactic won't work.
Jae Suk...
(Popping)
(They get a splash of water.)
(She failed to control
her strength.)
My goodness.
That happened
because you kept scratching.
Okay!
I am so annoyed.
- They did the worst job.
- Okay.
You shouldn't have scratched
the surface.
Other teams removed 1 or 2 layers.
You are in no place to say that.
I told you to do it gently.
I couldn't keep my touch gentle
since I was too annoyed.
They are terrible at it.
- Okay.
- Team Chang Wook is the last place.
They are out.
You can still answer the question.
Shall I give a question?
Can we get the answer right?
No.
Just enjoy the game.
- What?
- Just enjoy Running Man.
Are we only allowed to give
the question?
Yes. Give them your answer.
Who is it?
You can sit down and do it.
I bet he will give a strange answer
on purpose.
- Who is it?
- I bet he will throw us off.
It's what I think.
- I am going by the person's image.
- Hurry up.
- Sunhwa.
- Why?
- Sunhwa?
- Her image?
- What is this about?
- Let's hear more about it.
- Sunhwa.
It's about dating.
- Dating?
- It's about dating.
- It's about dating, right?
- Dating.
- Let me answer.
The person who would break up
in the coolest fashion.
No. I am not cool about a breakup.
Is it about two-timing?
The person who gets obsessive...
- Is it about dating?
- Is it a good thing or a bad thing?
Well, it's not a good thing.
- Really?
- Is it about a breakup?
Is it about a breakup?
A breakup.
It's related to a breakup.
- Really?
- Let me answer.
The person who would break up
the fastest.
I am sorry, but this could be
a bit worse than that.
- Is it worse than that?
- Then why did you give my name?
It's not something that comes
after a breakup.
- I see.
- Then during a relationship...
Who is the top two?
Is it So Min?
Why would it be me?
He said it's something bad.
- We are the same.
- That's exactly why it's you.
Why do people choose me
for all the bad things?
You are a bit...
So Min is within the top three,
right?
The top two is...
- Haha.
- What?
(Am I the top 2?)
- Really?
- Let me answer.
The person who swears
when he or she breaks up.
It's not something that comes
after a breakup.
- That's right.
- He said that before.
This is something that comes
during a breakup.
The person who doesn't pay
for the date.
- I pay a lot.
- I...
I practically sell the house.
I can't help but explain myself.
- "I am not like that."
- It's about...
dating someone...
(That's what it says
on the cue card.)
There is a word, "The other".
(It's a big hint.)
- The other?
- Yes.
Let me answer.
The person the other would tire of
the fastest in a relationship.
(Correct)
Come on!
Why is it Sunhwa?
Why is it me?
- Explain.
- Why is it Sunhwa?
- I mean...
- How could you do this to me?
- It's not like that.
- Come here!
Take this!
- Why is it Sunhwa?
- I had to pick someone.
I'm not saying you're like that.
What do you know about Sunhwa?
I am already hurt
because of my past relationship.
Seriously.
Don't misunderstand.
How could you be so mean?
- I had to choose someone.
- My relationships...
- last long.
- Is Haha the top two?
Why am I the top two? Explain.
- My relationships last long.
- It's...
What do you know?
My ex-girlfriends
still have feelings for me!
The celebrities you have dated
always say...
they are sick and tired of you!
- Look at yourself objectively.
- I know that, but...
I just went with my feeling.
I got confused
because he picked Sunhwa.
No one would have thought that
about her.
Seriously.
My relationships last long.
I know that. I am sorry.
I had to pick someone.
The two teams will take turns
to slash the balloon.
I don't know why
we need to sit down and do it.
No, no. It's a rule.
- All right.
- We need to sit down.
I will sit down.
- I hope their balloon pops.
- We need to do it, right?
It's so frustrating.
No, no. Hold on.
What?
Move the blade sideways.
- That's right.
- Move the blade sideways.
Move it sideways.
(She removed 4 layers.)
(In any case, she succeeded.)
- Did you see that?
- Good job.
You did a good job.
This is how you do it.
I will stay close.
(Bursting)
(She took out her anger
on the water balloon.)
The water splattered everywhere!
(Sunhwa slashed
without holding back.)
- You...
- I did it gently!
She is angry because of you!
- I am sorry, Sunhwa.
- She is really angry.
I picked you
because I had to pick someone.
- Come back to your senses.
- I could have done...
- better.
- Okay.
- Come back to your senses.
- Sunhwa, let's go.
Someone from Team Chang Wook.
Give us the name.
(Chang Wook checks the question
this time.)
- Whom will you choose?
- Well...
- Why is he looking at me?
- Whom will you choose?
- Suk Jin.
- Me?
Let me answer. The person
who doesn't act his or her age.
(Incorrect)
- Me?
- The person who is cold-hearted.
The person who frequents the toilet
at night because of residual urine.
Don't say something that's true.
- Residual urine!
- He frequents the toilet at night.
Residual urine!
Let me answer.
The person who says he peed...
even though you didn't hear
any sound.
(Incorrect)
There was no one else.
(The silent toilet)
Chang Wook must see Suk Jin
differently from us.
- That's right.
- Chang Wook, tell us...
how you see Suk Jin.
Since he has a way with words,
- Really?
- I think...
he will do this
when he has a conversation.
A conversation?
Let me answer.
The person who laughs
at his own joke.
That was perfect.
Let me answer. The person
who isn't serious at all.
(Incorrect)
The person who has been punched
during a conversation.
(The person who has been punched
during a conversation)
That's correct.
That's perfect.
Chang Wook, give us a motion hint.
During a conversation, he would go,
"Hey, I..."
Let me answer.
(Upon seeing the motion hint,)
(Jae Suk yelled out.)
The person who brags about
the celebrities...
- he knows.
- Let me answer.
(Correct)
(Who would brag about
the celebrities he or she knows?)
My goodness.
Brag about how well-connected I am?
I don't do that.
- Chang Wook.
- But...
you bragged too much earlier.
Chang Wook.
You started
from Magistrate Byun and...
- He did that.
- Magistrate Byun.
- I am sorry.
- The former classmates.
I bragged too much earlier.
That's right.
- That's right.
- Okay.
Slash the balloon.
So Min, do it.
- Should I do it?
- She is Dr. Romantic.
I don't know if I would be able
to do it again.
She is Dr. Jeon.
Dr. Jeon, I believe in you.
It's over for them.
- Dr. Jeon.
- It's okay if I fail, right?
Dr. Jeon, it's okay. Go ahead.
(She brandishes the scalpel.)
What was that?
- What?
- What was that?
- It fell.
- It's on the floor.
- What happened?
- We are still in.
We are still in.
- How did you do it?
- We are still in.
It looked like
a turtle was laying an egg.
So Min is good.
- She is daring.
- It didn't burst.
I will try again, but there is
a good chance it will burst.
I bet Kwang Soo will burst it
with his hands.
I wouldn't do that.
Don't be ridiculous.
- In that case,
- I am nervous.
cut his finger.
Come on. I will just hold it.
Keep your fingers relaxed.
- Okay.
- Let's do it.
- Don't press it!
- All right.
All right. I will just hold it.
I am simply applying force.
- Why would you do that?
- Action and reaction.
I will stay still.
Why did you bring up
action and reaction?
(Why did he bring up
action and reaction?)
Be careful.
(Will So Min be able to succeed?)
I did it.
(But...)
(Kwang Soo's action
and reaction came into play.)
- What was that?
- It didn't burst!
- I did it.
- It was Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo pressed it.
He got water all over him.
- He is stupid.
- So Min succeeded.
Are you okay?
- I succeeded.
- Team Yoo Jung takes first place.
- Okay.
Yoo Jung, you did it.
Yoo Jung made all the difference.
Starting from the winning team,
you will choose an item each.
Yoo Jung, let's go.
A packed meal.
A packed meal is popular.
All right.
- Pick an item, Sang Woo.
- Wet wipes.
Okay.
- Okay.
- A hangover drink.
We choose an energy drink.
- Okay.
- That can't be popular.
You have an offer from a broker.
- What is it?
- Team Sunhwa,
will you accept it?
- What should we do?
- Let's turn it down.
- Turn it down.
- What happens if we turn it down?
- We receive a hint.
- What happens if we accept it?
- Then we can catch the brokers.
- A hint?
- Two hints.
- Don't do that.
You are a broker, right?
- No, I am not.
- That's why...
We aren't brokers,
- so we want a hint.
- We won't be able to find them.
No, Haha.
- Don't be like that.
- Are you a broker?
- We need a hint.
- Everyone.
I will give you a crucial hint.
The top 1, 2, 3 items
in terms of sales are still here.
Really?
(The top 1, 2, 3 items
in terms of sales remain.)
Really?
- Then let's accept it.
- Let's accept it.
No way.
Could chewing gum be one of them?
- I don't think so.
- People don't buy it often.
I think they're around here.
I think they're drinks.
I think banana milk is
one of the top three.
- I agree.
- Banana milk, definitely.
- Let's go for it.
- It's very popular.
- We've made our choice.
Guys, a broker
just proposed a deal...
to Team Yoo Jung.
- Make up your mind.
- We'll accept it.
- We'll accept it. Let's go.
- What?
- Why?
- We have to accept it.
- Don't we need a hint?
- Isn't it better to get a hint?
- Do you want a hint?
- Let's get a hint.
- I think that'd be better.
Okay, let's get a hint. Yoo Jung.
What could be the top three?
Brokers, propose deals to us too.
Brokers, propose deals to us!
I have no idea.
What's that?
- Here's a hint.
- What?
- What's this?
(They receive a hint
from the staff.)
The broker wrote it.
- It's the broker's handwriting?
- The broker wrote it?
(It's the broker's handwriting?)
Is the handwriting the hint?
- Goodness, that's unbelievable.
- This...
- It's a label from clothes.
Is it from the broker's clothes?
- Is this the same?
- This...
No, they're different.
Where is it from? Let me see.
- It's from a towel.
- It's from a towel?
A towel... Let me see.
- A towel...
- I know.
The broker is not among us.
Do you know why?
- We didn't use any towels.
- None of us are wet.
- The towel was the hint.
- When did the broker write it?
(The broker is
one of these nine people.)
I think there's a broker
among you guys.
Propose a deal to us,
and we'll accept it.
- Propose a deal.
- Let's propose a deal.
- Let's do it.
- Do it.
- Let's propose a deal.
- Please.
- Propose a deal to us too.
- We'll accept it.
- Do you want it first or...
- We want it first.
- We'll accept it.
We'll propose a deal to this team.
You have to...
(Are these two really brokers?)
You have to signal the staff.
- It has to be done the proper way.
- We'll do it.
Start.
- We are the future
(We are the future)
(The two childish brokers
are proposing a deal.)
(What were we expecting from them?)
- That was the brokers' sign?
- Yes.
Why haven't I seen it before?
(The 40-year-old broker
is trying hard.)
Gather up, everyone.
- The broker is incredible.
- The broker is so quick.
Good job. That was so quick.
- When did the broker do it?
All right.
Let's get ready
for the last mission.
- Okay.
(Hot Item Selection Status)
(The last mission to win hot items)
(A refreshing water-sled race
with the brokers)
(The third mission is finished.)
Let me announce the results
of the last mission.
Team Sang Woo is in 1st place
with 11 points.
(Team Sang Woo in 1st place)
Team Sunhwa is in 2nd place
with 10 points.
(Team Sunhwa in 2nd place)
Team Chang Wook is in 3rd place
with 8 points.
Team Yoo Jung is in 4th place
with 7 points.
That's a shame.
Please choose your last item.
- Are we choosing 1?
- Yes, choose 1.
- We choose Coke.
- Let's go for Coke.
Really?
(Team Sunhwa chooses stockings.)
- All right. Let's choose stockings.
- Okay.
- I vote for tissues.
- Tissues?
- Tissues.
- Okay, tissues.
(Team Chang Wook chooses tissues.)
(Team Yoo Jung chooses
ice cubes in a cup.)
Ice cubes in a cup?
This is what I buy most often.
- Yoo Jung.
- Let her choose.
I think we should choose
a fish cake bar.
Yoo Jung, you get to decide.
I think she's a broker.
- Trust me.
- That's a surprising choice.
- I know.
- Gosh.
Let me announce
the brokers' last proposals.
Broker A proposed a deal to
Team Yoo Jung and Team Chang Wook.
(Team Yoo Jung and Team Chang Wook)
Broker B proposed a deal
to Team Sang Woo.
- Broker B.
- Should we get a hint?
- We didn't get any proposals?
- No.
(Team Sunhwa is the only team
that didn't get any proposal.)
I think...
(They have to decide
whether to accept the deal or not.)
We should accept the deal...
- and win another item.
- Right.
- Let's do that.
- I know one of the brokers.
What did you see?
I saw the broker...
write something and submit it.
- I saw it clearly.
- Really?
I saw it with my own eyes.
- Yes.
I know who it is.
(Does Chang Wook really know
who the broker is?)
We want a hint...
- It's a hint about Broker A, right?
- It's about Broker A.
- We want the hint.
- Let's have a look.
- Just a second.
We won't swipe.
- What's that?
- Is that a hint?
It's from the broker.
- The broker took this picture?
- Yes.
Think of what's going on
in this picture.
- Where was this?
- So the broker is...
The broker is not
one of the people in the picture.
- Where was this?
- Isn't that me?
- No.
- That cap is mine.
- No, it isn't.
- It isn't?
- No.
- No?
It's Sang Woo.
Why are they looking at you?
- Why are they looking at me?
- They looked at you.
It must be a picture.
(Sang Woo has no idea.)
- The broker sent this picture?
- Yes.
To choose the team?
What do the other teams want?
- We want a hint.
You want a hint about Broker B.
We have no hints,
so we'll have to take a guess.
What's this?
(A hint about Broker B
for Team Sang Woo)
The broker submitted this
to choose us?
Is this how he proposed a deal?
Try to think of the situation and
guess whose handwriting this is.
- Kwang Soo and Jae Suk were...
- Kwang Soo was wearing gloves.
He was, right?
(A moment ago)
(Kwang Soo was wearing
gloves the whole time.)
(Is Kwang Soo Broker B?)
- Let's see.
- How big is it?
- Well...
- The broker has big hands.
The bottom of my hand is here.
This is a lot bigger than my hand.
(The glove is a lot bigger
than So Min's hand.)
- Spread your fingers.
- Why?
(So Min examines Kwang Soo's hand.)
(Like the prince looking for
the owner of a glass slipper,)
(So Min is looking for
the owner of the glove.)
(Laughing)
- It's a man, right?
- It is.
- Right?
- Because...
the fingers are so long.
Look at this.
This is where the fingers bend.
Is Kwang Soo a broker?
Why? What's the hint?
- Kwang Soo, are you a broker?
- No.
All right.
- What do you want to do?
- We accept the deal.
- You do?
- Yes.
Then choose an item.
(Team Chang Wook chooses
an additional item.)
I want to choose coffee.
Coffee?
- Canned coffee?
- Let's do this.
All teams are done choosing items.
(Team Yoo Jung, Team Sunhwa,
Team Sang Woo, Team Chang Wook)
(Both Brokers A and B
made 3 successful deals.)
(It's time to catch the brokers.)
First, you'll catch the brokers.
If you choose to catch the brokers,
you have to guess both brokers.
You can put
a "multiply by two" sticker...
on as many items as the number
of brokers you catch.
- On the items we choose?
- You'll also put...
a "divide by two" sticker
on as many items...
as the number of brokers
you fail to catch.
- "Divide by two"?
- We have to catch both brokers?
Yes, then you'll get
two "multiply by two" stickers.
- What if we catch only one?
- You'll get one of each.
(They get "multiply by 2"
and "divide by 2" stickers.)
Also, the brokers will lose...
as many items...
as the number of teams
that catch them.
- We'll...
- We'll stay out.
We have no hints.
We'll stay out.
Team Sunhwa stays out.
- Do you want to catch the brokers?
- Yes, we do.
- We want to catch the brokers.
- Let's try.
- Okay.
Three teams want to catch
the brokers.
Discuss for a minute
and tell us your decision.
- Come here.
- Since we know...
- We know one broker for sure.
- We know one.
Who is it?
- One of them is Kwang Soo.
- Me?
- Right?
- It's not me.
(Chang Wook suspects Kwang Soo.)
Right?
What are you talking about?
I thought so too.
(Kwang Soo follows them.)
I saw it.
Shut it.
(Kwang Soo is cornered
and swears at Chang Wook.)
(When the brokers were
being decided...)
(You're a broker.)
(Take a picture of the name tag
or write down...)
(the name of the person
you want to propose a deal to.)
(Kwang Soo was chosen as a broker.)
(While everyone was busy
carrying out missions,)
(he wrote down names
on all kinds of things,)
(including a blindfold
and a ramyeon seasoning bag.)
(The glove was Kwang Soo's too.)
(Han Sunhwa, Ji Chang Wook,
Kim Yoo Jung, Do Sang Woo)
(He wasn't afraid to propose
a deal in any situation.)
(In the end, he was witnessed
by Chang Wook.)
(Is Kwang Soo a broker?)
- I saw it.
- Shut it.
(The broker tries to
shut Chang Wook's mouth.)
(Kwang Soo, you're busted!)
Shut it before the other teams
find out.
Can't we just guess one broker?
- You have to guess both.
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
I told you.
I'm not entirely sure
whose handwriting this is, but...
- Who do you think it is?
- I think...
this is...
Chang Wook's handwriting.
(It's Kwang Soo's handwriting.)
- Can't we make him write something?
- It's similar.
(Yoo Jung makes a wrong guess.)
- You've seen his handwriting?
- Yes.
- I've seen it.
- Really?
I'm sure.
- Let's do it.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
Chang Wook, who do you think
the other broker is?
(Chang Wook and Ji Hyo know
one broker for sure.)
- The brokers were chosen randomly.
- Yes.
(If they guess both right, they get
2 "multiply by 2" stickers.)
I should try to catch
the other broker too.
(Kwang Soo joins the investigation.)
- The other broker took a picture.
- The other broker...
sent a picture.
Who used a phone?
I'm suspecting
Sunhwa and Yoo Jung.
Yoo Jung kept hovering around there.
(Is the other broker
one of the two?)
- Yoo Jung?
Kwang Soo!
We're done.
Let's just write it.
(Team Sang Woo and Team Yoo Jung
have made their choices too.)
I'm not sure about that one,
but it's probably right.
Right?
Everyone is suspecting everyone.
Let me announce
the three teams' choices first...
- and then who the brokers are.
- Okay.
Team Sang Woo chose...
Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.
Me?
- And...
- Why me?
He sounds surprised.
Team Yoo Jung chose...
Chang Wook and Jong Kook.
- Me?
- Yes.
Team Chang Wook chose...
Kwang Soo and Yoo Jung.
- They picked one from their team?
- I'm speechless.
I don't know.
I kept saying it's not me,
but they won't listen.
- Kwang Soo came out as a broker.
- True.
- They were whispering behind me.
- Hey.
That's not why.
I caught him.
- What are you talking about?
- What?
- He was passing off a memo...
- Shut your mouth!
(He explodes.)
- Really?
- It is you.
- What? It's not me.
- It's you.
It's not.
Let me announce the brokers.
The brokers are...
(Kwang Soo got exposed,
and there's one more.)
(Unlike him,
Broker A is still a mystery.)
The brokers are
Kwang Soo and Chang Wook.
(The brokers are
Kwang Soo and Chang Wook!)
That's what I said!
This is unbelievable.
- It was so obvious.
- Hey!
- See? Chang Wook acted weird today.
- That's what I said!
(He feigned innocence
and exposed Kwang Soo.)
(There's nobody you can trust
in the world of brokers.)
I have to look by myself.
(When the brokers were
being selected...)
(Take a picture of the name tag
or write down...)
(the name of the person
you want to propose a deal to.)
(Chang Wook was selected
as the broker.)
(He approached them quietly...)
(and took pictures.)
(Chang Wook was
a silent photographer.)
I caught him.
(When he realized what Kwang Soo
was, he diverted attention.)
(That's how Broker Ji Chang Wook
gained everybody's trust.)
I did catch you though.
You're Broker B, right?
I was right!
She guessed it right.
Yoo Jung said
it was Chang Wook's writing.
That was good, Chang Wook.
Where did they go? Crazy people.
I did catch you though.
- They're fighting.
- It was them.
Hey, you...
(Cursing and grabbing him by
the throat after being betrayed)
Did he lose?
Chang Wook exposed Kwang Soo.
We're both brokers,
and he ratted me out.
Kwang Soo, you got arrested,
so you can choose one item.
Chang Wook, you can choose two.
Only two? Rather than that...
See? We're in first place.
We might win.
- See? We're in first place.
- That's true.
We might win.
Three teams,
please add "multiply by two"...
and "divide by two"
on items you want.
That was close.
Yoo Jung, you can put
"multiply by two" wherever you want.
Brokers, please decide.
Do they steal our items?
Go ahead.
Do whatever you want.
This is the ice cream.
We have to put "divide by two"
on an item with a low score.
- Low score.
- Something that'll sell the least.
Let's choose the packed meal.
Brokers, please use items as well.
- I'll choose canned coffee.
- Canned coffee?
What about you, Chang Wook?
I'll choose stockings...
and ice cream.
- Ice cream?
- Ice cream.
(They put the stickers on.
Brokers chose their items as well!)
I'll announce the final rankings.
I really want to know.
- You never know. We might win.
- I know.
- Should we open this?
- Yes.
1, 2, 3.
(How were the convenience store
hot items ranked?)
I see the large bottle of water.
A cup of ice is in first place?
- We're first!
- It's us!
Is this in first place?
I told you it was ice.
- Look at second place.
- We got it.
See? There's banana milk.
Banana milk...
How is
the large bottle of water here?
It's what we said.
- People buy water a lot.
- Exactly.
- We were right.
- I suggested it.
- Where are the stockings?
They're not here at all.
- This was unexpected.
- This is not what we thought.
Yoo Jung, you did great.
Yoo Jung.
Here are the scores.
First place is...
(Which team got 1st place?)
Team Yoo Jung with 30 points.
Yes!
(Team Yoo Jung with 30 points)
(They won with the cup of ice,
with points multiplied by 2.)
No way. Only if it wasn't
in first place...
We were in last place
the whole time.
We won hands down because of her.
- How did she think of cup of ice?
- It was just one item.
We would have won with that.
How did she think of cup of ice?
- I didn't think of it at all.
- 2nd and 3rd places...
were 2 points apart.
It's us.
2nd place is Team Sunhwa
with 22 points.
- We did well.
- Good job.
3rd place is Team Sang Woo
with 20 points.
- Are we in third place?
- That was close.
At least we're not in last place.
Team Chang Wook,
Ji Hyo earned 13 points,
Kwang Soo earned 4 points,
and Chang Wook earned 0.
(Brokers Chang Wook and Kwang Soo
earned 0 and 4 points.)
- This is fun.
You darn brokers.
- Brokers.
- Serves you right.
The prizes are 10 popular items
from the convenience store...
- Really?
- and convenience store gift card.
- There's a gift card?
- I'm envious.
(We would like to thank
Chang Wook, Yoo Jung,)
(Sunhwa, and Sang Woo for joining
us in the early summer heat.)
- Great work.
- Thank you.
I'm scared.
(There are three kinds of people
in this world.)
Ji Hyo!
(Those on top,)
(those on the bottom,)
What's going on?
(and those who betray)
(This coin sharing is to test
the loyalty of Running Man members.)
(United we stand
and divided we fall!)
(It's an intense race where people
without their trust get eliminated.)
(Viewers' reports
finally get revealed.)
(From Jae Suk's first kiss...)
(to seeing him at the sauna)
Can this be on TV?
A woman who lived overseas.
(Will Jong Kook's love story get
revealed for the first time?)
So Min was in front of
the waiting room with somebody else.
(Does So Min's past make her
put her head down?)
Who was it?
(The viewers' eyewitnesses
add substance to the revelations.)
(Is there no loyalty?
You can look forward to next week!)
(Running Man Loyalty Race:
Sharing Playbook)