- Hello.
Hello.
What? Why are you
wearing denim jackets?
I don't know. I just put it on and
realized Kwang Soo's wearing it too.
Are you two running
a shopping mall together?
Gosh, no.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Why do you look
so mischievous today?
What did you say?
Hello, Suk Jin.
You guys go ahead and talk.
I'm putting on the microphone now.
Why are you yelling at us?
- Why are you so upset?
- What's so upsetting?
- We were complimenting your outfit.
- What made you upset?
He wouldn't even say hello to us
without a microphone.
He's really ridiculous.
Once I put on the microphone,
my work begins.
(His work hour begins
with the microphone.)
Suk Jin wants to join us,
so he keeps leaning forward.
He can't wait to talk.
It's not done,
but he wants to talk already.
- I know.
- He can't wait to come here.
Dogs find it hard to wait.
Jong Kook, isn't that
what you wore last week?
These are my own clothes.
It's cold outside.
Why are you
wearing your own clothes?
Why do you have your stylist then?
Why is she coming with you?
Just to show off.
I see.
That's 1 of the 5 world's
greatest mysteries.
You got your hair done.
- Why did you not change?
- Why is Ji Seon here as a stylist?
Just to show off.
Suk Jin, you are wearing
Cheon Young Rock's glasses.
- It's from the 1980s.
- He looks young, right?
- The glasses...
- He looks younger.
I wore them the other day,
and people liked them.
- You look a lot younger.
- I see.
- You look younger.
- That's not why I'm wearing them.
There is a limit
to how much younger he can get.
What limit?
You look like 54.
There is a limit
to how much younger he can get.
It's just a couple of years at most.
I'm healthier than you, though.
It's not like he looks younger.
He looks less old.
- Exactly.
- Hey.
- He can't look young.
- That's...
the best we can do.
Hey.
My friends my age
are going to kill you.
- Who's going to kill us?
- My friends my age.
Do you think my friends
will let it happen?
Do you want to fight?
- You're no match for them.
- My friends born in 1972...
My friends won't let this slide.
I will bring my friends together.
Seriously...
It will be hard for Suk Jin
to bring his friends together.
- It's hard.
- They rarely get together.
For Suk Jin,
I think four would grab him
by the collar, to begin with.
Why would they grab me
by the collar?
- They will.
- No, no. Why?
Why would they?
We're having a conversation.
He's not a good fighter.
But he's wiry.
- And he's resilient.
- Right.
Do you want to know how he fights?
He just lets his opponent
hit one side of his face.
He just offers them
to hit his cheek.
- His cheek.
- I say, "Just hit me."
But I never pass out.
He says he never passes out.
I never pass out.
- I feel bad for him.
- You know what?
It's like we're
on "Lee Suk Jin Show".
What? Why would you say that?
Can we just hit you
and wrap this up?
- No way.
- Come on. Just one punch.
- Why would you hit me?
- By the way...
- I should hit you and wrap this up.
- Stop it already.
Your face turned red.
It's because it's hot in here.
Now Suk Jin's all warmed up.
We can finally begin now.
- Let's do this.
- Yes, let's do this.
- This feels good.
- Hello, everyone.
Hello!
Hello, everyone.
Let's do this.
This is our last episode this year.
- Is that so?
- Really?
Really?
I just hope this year ends soon.
Yes, I hate this year.
It was the worst.
- Yes, it should end soon.
- Yes.
I would rather turn 50. My goodness.
- You're right.
- You're 50 soon.
- Yes.
- You'll be 50.
We'll enjoy the year-end
with some chips.
It's red chili flavor.
(Product placement advertisement
is on.)
It goes better with Coke.
Is it crisp both
on the inside and outside?
Stupid both
on the inside and outside.
Come on. This is an ad.
How could you say that?
- You are...
- How could you...
- How could you say that?
- You said so yourself.
I said it's crisp
both on the inside and outside.
Yes, stupid
Can I take this home with me?
Just taste it first.
(Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo!)
We're doing the ad on condition
that you don't talk about this.
What are you talking about?
Please enjoy.
- Can someone take this card?
- All right.
"Running Man Year-End
Feelings Settlement".
"This is the last episode of 2020."
"Go into each booth that has
each member's name tag on it..."
"and write what you were upset about
each member this year."
- Gosh.
- What I was upset about them?
I wasn't much upset about anything.
Do we have to write it
in every booth?
No, you don't have to.
- Only a few?
- For the ones you were upset with.
- Only for those I was upset with?
- You're right.
What should I write about?
Well, there's nothing much...
(Heartwarming)
- Right, there is nothing much.
- There's nothing much.
- There's nothing to write about.
- Right. Because...
everything is understandable.
(Jae Suk is not upset, but he
goes into Suk Jin's booth.)
- Gosh.
- What are you going to write about?
- Excuse me.
- Hey!
Excuse me.
- Is someone in there?
- What will you write about?
- Someone is in here.
- Oh, I see.
- Someone's in here.
- I should write something.
My goodness.
(It looks like Suk Jin's booth
will be packed.)
I have some things
to say to Se Chan.
I have some things to say
to you too.
I have something for Se Chan.
Really?
(Already very scared)
I even have something
for Jae Suk too.
- What?
- Me? What is it?
- I'm upset because of you.
- Why?
Then I should write one for you too.
What am I upset about?
(Remembering the grudges
they have against each other)
What is it, Jae Suk?
What is it?
I can't believe it. I just can't.
It's anonymous, right?
- Yes, just write down the content.
- Kwang Soo.
Right. There's one for Ji Hyo too.
(As they hear it's anonymous,
they all get up.)
Gosh, my legs.
I'm remembering things
now that I've started.
My goodness. People are lined up.
Wait a minute. Is that my booth?
- You can't line up there.
- I'm just here like everyone else.
- Then what should I do?
- All right then.
- Someone's in there?
- Yes.
I wrote for Haha.
(What is he so upset about Se Chan
that he had to wait in line?)
(Ji Hyo said she's not upset
about anything, but...)
I don't have to write one
if there's nothing, right?
(But she's writing something down.)
Gosh, I don't have anything
to write about.
Ji Hyo, were you upset with So Min?
What are you doing?
- Were you spying on me?
- Why were you in there?
- I did nothing.
- Ji Hyo, what were you doing?
I did nothing.
Why would you go in there?
No, I'm just checking something.
I mean, why would you go in there?
I wrote something for Se Chan and...
They're writing
all sorts of stuff now.
They're writing about their flaws.
They are...
Maybe there's nothing else
to write about.
They're all writing
about the members' flaws.
Not what they're upset about.
It's just a slander.
That's so funny. Our flaws?
It's not what they're upset about.
- Excuse me.
- Now everyone should come out.
(Finishing it
before they hurt their feelings)
All right.
- It's what you wrote for Jong Kook.
- All right.
I wonder what you're upset about me.
Here it goes.
- It's completely anonymous.
- All right.
"He doesn't know
how to control his strength."
- It's something to be upset about.
- I'm sure.
- It's possible.
- Yes, everyone will agree.
I recognize the handwriting.
- I know who wrote that.
- Really?
I'm not so sure though.
- Why are you nervous?
- You're not sure?
Why are you so nervous?
- Are you really sure?
- Next.
"He gets dubious without thinking."
"I'm sick of it."
- This person's sick of it.
- Sick of it?
I understand.
Yes, it's understandable.
"Whenever I'm the spy,"
"I want to get rid of him."
It's getting dubious too.
He doubts too much.
It's not me.
- It's Haha.
- It wasn't me.
Next.
"He only likes his daughter."
What's that?
Here we go.
This person wrote without thinking.
"He only spends money
on his daughter."
(He only spends money
on his daughter.)
People will think it's true.
The next one says,
"Se Chan speaks ill of you
behind your back."
What?
What is this?
- It's so obvious who wrote it.
- It's So Min.
I think it's So Min.
Next says... This is funny.
"When he's the spy,"
"he uses his strength
to prove otherwise."
(Everyone has an experience of it.)
- This is so true.
- It's something to be upset about.
- He really does that.
- So you've all been upset.
Here are the things Suk Jin did
that made us upset.
"He doesn't speak to us
unless the camera..."
"or the microphone is on."
(He doesn't speak to us unless
the camera or the mic is on.)
- "Even if we say hello,"
- It's something to be upset about.
"he doesn't speak to us."
- I'm really upset about it too.
- Yes, you're right.
- It's so true.
- Do I really do that?
Once I knocked on his car window
to say hi,
but he didn't even lower the window.
- I guess he's a professional.
- Yes, he's a pro.
- He's a professional.
- He acts when the camera rolls.
(Laughing)
- This is the worst.
- What is it?
"He pretends his family's precious."
(He pretends
his family is precious.)
- Of course this upsets us.
- Yes.
- It's the worst.
- The worst.
- And it upsets us.
- Gosh.
- So Min, you did this.
- It wasn't me.
- You wrote all three comments.
- This is funny too.
"He pulls a string of hair
that grows on his ear."
(He pulls a string of hair
that grows on his ear.)
What was that again?
"He pulls a string of hair
that grows on his ear."
Don't pull it.
I don't have
hair growing on my ear!
- Yes, you do.
- Let me see.
I don't!
You should water it.
- You wrote it, right?
- I didn't.
I don't have hair on the ear.
- Water the hair.
- This is so funny.
Now, here are the things
that Kwang Soo did that upset us.
- "He's gotten ugly."
- What?
- "His fashion sense is excessive."
- Right, people ask me this a lot.
They ask me why you're getting ugly.
"He contacts me
only when he's drunk."
"His back hair is too long."
"His forelock is too short
compared to the back hair."
It's not like I can grow
my forelock down here.
Isn't it natural to have...
- longer back hair?
- Is it something to be upset about?
Of course the forelock
is shorter than the back hair.
I was serious,
but this person wasn't.
Why is this person
upset about my hair?
This is just a malicious comment.
Okay, next.
"I don't like his face
especially when he smiles."
"His face is crooked."
(I don't like his face especially
when he smiles. It is crooked.)
- Wait a minute.
- It's nothing to be upset about.
This person's upset
because my face is crooked?
- This is too much.
- Why does it make you upset?
- What if that's my weak point?
- This is...
- So funny.
- Because my face isn't symmetrical,
this person is upset?
"He's gotten even taller."
"I think he's as tall as
a two-story apartment."
"I think he can grow as high as 3m,"
"but he's not trying much."
(I think he can grow as high as
3m, but he's not trying much.)
Who wrote this?
What's this? This is ridiculous.
- This is so funny.
- How can this person say that?
Yes, you can be upset about it.
- You can grow up to 3m.
- That's right.
- You can, so why aren't you trying?
- We're upset about it.
How should I try harder?
We're upset, so work harder.
Why aren't you trying harder?
You can be taller.
- Why should I be taller?
- Work harder.
Okay, next.
"When you had drinks
with the younger members,"
"you hesitated to pay for it."
Seriously, he makes it too obvious.
(It was you, wasn't it?)
- Come on. It wasn't me.
- Hey, hey.
It wasn't like that.
- I had my reasons.
- Hey, you're so stingy.
- I didn't hesitate.
- He never spends money.
- Seriously.
- I didn't hesitate.
I do spend money.
And I didn't hesitate.
- Things you're upset with me.
- All right.
"You always try to
hang up the phone."
"I'm bored of your hairstyle."
"Your mouth protruded even more."
"Too bad you're not
handsome enough."
- Gosh.
- What is this?
Too bad that I'm not
handsome enough?
You could be upset about it.
"I'm upset that
your teeth aren't even."
Yes, I'm also upset
that your teeth aren't even.
- This person really meant it.
- Yes, you could be upset.
This upsets me.
My teeth aren't even?
- Yes, it upsets me.
- Right.
It'd be funnier
if I get some braces.
- No, you'll look better.
- My goodness.
Look at Se Chan.
- He straightened his teeth.
- Yes.
You'll look better.
Well, I don't look better though.
Yours are straightened,
but they're still protruding.
- Yes, they're protruding.
- Right.
- Straightened but protruding.
- Yes, straightened but protruding.
- Gosh.
Gosh, straightened but protruding.
- Both on the outside and inside?
- Yes, stupid on the inside.
Next is Song Ji Hyo.
"After my first filming,
I texted that she did a good job..."
"and that I hope to be good friends
with her."
"But she still hasn't replied."
Since the first filming?
- You should reply to people.
- Isn't that 10 years ago?
- Ji Hyo.
- Gosh, this is upsetting.
No, Jae Suk. That's not true.
"I can never reach her."
"I want to see your clear eyes
at least once."
It's because she's Song Sleepy.
"An ad to shoot together. But she
wrote her name first on the card."
What does this mean?
It's nothing. Just pass.
- What is it?
- What does it mean?
Well, it's...
This is no fun.
- What is it?
- Gosh.
(Dozing off)
- What is it?
- It's nothing. Let's move on.
- Really?
- It's a joke. It means nothing.
It's a joke,
but it's not funny at all.
(Straightforward)
Be easy on him.
- Don't be so mean. Be easy on him.
- Hey.
- Are you upset?
- You don't know what's it about.
Are you upset?
I'm not upset, but you don't
even know what it's about.
You're not upset, right?
You don't know what it's about.
It sure isn't funny.
What we're upset with Haha.
"He said we should
get together sometime,"
"but he never called.
I guess it was a formality."
(Embarrassed)
Yes, that's what he does.
- He does that.
- Hey, let's get together sometime.
- He asks to have a drink.
- Hey.
- It's been years.
- Let's have a drink.
- I've never had a drink with him.
- Yes, he does that.
- He asks to have a drink.
- He does that all the time.
- Why would he ask then?
- So don't ask us.
- A drink and half-dried herring?
- He does that all the time.
- He wasn't like that in the past.
- Seriously.
- Come on, Haha.
- You can't help it.
He doesn't talk casually
on the phone.
He always says this when I answer.
"Hello, Mr. Lee Kwang Soo."
It's just business.
It's all about work.
"Mr. Lee Kwang Soo, please
say hello to our viewers."
- He's always like that.
- Seriously.
"When I was a spy, he said he'd let
me off if I told him the truth..."
"when there was no camera around."
"So I told him, but he spread it
everywhere and removed my name tag."
That's so pathetic.
He's unbelievable.
- We should have a drink together.
- It's not me.
There he goes again.
- This is the worst part.
- He just opens a group chat room.
This is for Se Chan.
"He says he's at a meeting
for 'Comedy Big League'..."
"and never calls me back
for over two hours."
He's being strange these days.
I think he's seeing someone.
- I know.
- Exactly.
"When we went climbing together,"
"he obviously gave me
the wrong directions..."
"and told me to go before him."
Isn't it that he tried to kill you?
I bet it's So Min.
- Really?
- He tried to kill you.
It was really close.
It could've been dangerous.
"He looks like cuttlefish."
Hey, what's that? Cuttlefish?
- Cuttlefish.
- This is just a slander.
Cuttlefish is expensive.
Gosh, this one is
quite straightforward.
"He likes So Min, but he never
tells her about his feelings."
I'm sure it's Haha.
It's definitely him.
I was very disappointed.
- Why?
- Why didn't you tell her?
This is why I come to Running Man.
Okay.
This is about So Min.
"She lies a lot."
- Who wrote that?
- "She doesn't trust me."
She keeps questioning me.
I think this is Haha.
- It's Haha.
- I really meant it.
- Because you always lie to me.
- That's not true.
"She promised not to do it,"
"but she doubts me every time
we get a new mission."
Why do you keep doubting me?
"It's been six months since the
promise, but she hasn't changed."
"I will never trust you again."
Isn't this a letter to her?
Is that from one person?
"She keeps trying to make
things look romantic."
- You spelled it wrong though.
- Se Chan.
- It's wrong.
- Did you write it?
- Se Chan.
- You spelled it wrong.
It's really embarrassing.
(Ji Hyo is the one
who spelled it wrong.)
There's a hidden secret...
- behind those messages.
- What?
Each message you got today...
is converted to minus 100 points.
What are you doing?
And your scores will be accumulated.
Kwang Soo got a lot of messages.
We all wrote a message to him.
The more messages you have,
the more points you will lose.
(The results of 2020
Year-End Feelings Settlement)
(So Min: Minus 800,
Ji Hyo: Minus 900)
(Jae Suk: Minus 1,000,
Haha: Minus 1,000)
(Se Chan: Minus 1,100,
Suk Jin: Minus 1,200)
(Jong Kook: Minus 1,400,
Kwang Soo: Minus 1,400)
But members who lost a lot of points
still can turn the game around.
- I see.
- That's good.
While you were writing
down your complaints,
- our guests for today wrote down...
- Guests?
good things about you.
Good things about us?
I guess they are someone we know.
(And each message will be
converted to 100 points.)
- This is hard. What should I say?
- What should I say?
- Their merits?
- Their merits.
(Back on Running Man after 7 years,
Lee Yeon Hee)
(Kwang Soo's close friend,
Yoo Yeon Seok)
We should be honest.
Right.
(New on a variety show, Yoo Teo,
A variety show pro, Choi Sooyoung)
Kwang Soo?
(What does Kwang Soo's best friend
think Kwang Soo's merit is?)
He's tall.
(What are the merits of the members
that the four guests think?)
He's tall.
Everyone, we will bring in
our guests...
who wrote about your merits.
Please come on in.
Who are they?
(The 4 special actors are
here on Running Man.)
- Oh, hello.
- Hey.
(Their entrance gives an impression
of a warm year-end party.)
There's Sooyoung.
(They are glad to see the guests.)
- What?
- Hello.
(They're here to introduce their new
movie for 2021, "New Year Blues".)
(The movie is about four couples...)
Have you never dated anyone?
(who want to be happier
in the coming new year.)
When I'm with you, I feel so small.
Have you been feeling
that way the whole time?
(Today's special guests, Yeon Seok,
Yeon Hee, Sooyoung, and Teo)
We have four actors
from the movie, "New Year Blues".
- It's "New Year Blues".
- "New Year Blues".
Are you starring in the movie?
- No.
- How do you know it then?
Then stay quiet.
What did I do?
People would think
you starred in the movie too.
Kwang Soo knows the movie.
Yeon Seok, this is
your first time...
to join our show officially, right?
This is my first
official appearance.
- With Haha...
- He was Kwang Soo's...
That's right.
I had to shave my beard
as soon as I met him.
(Running Man Episode 293 in 2016)
(He asked Haha to shave his beard
on their first meeting.)
(You're bleeding!)
(He even saw Haha's blood
on their first meeting.)
Right.
- But...
- Kwang Soo made me do it back then.
- Right. He did.
- I did.
On our first meeting.
He just shaved my beard
while laughing.
I even bled.
He was bleeding here.
- Right.
- Now I remember that.
(And he's back on Running Man
after 4 years.)
It was really...
What? Did Yeon Seok and Yeon Hee
prepare a tango performance?
- Are we doing it already?
- Really?
- Is it from your movie?
- Are they dancing the tango?
- Are we doing it already?
- Really?
(Wait. Are we doing it already?)
- No.
- This is crazy.
Did you prepare a tango performance?
Why are you being like this?
The tango I know?
No, in our movie...
- Thank you for doing this.
- It's not like that.
We should watch it then.
- No, it's just...
- Go ahead and show us.
- We prepared...
- Show us what you prepared.
I'm so grateful that
they want to perform for us.
Go ahead and do it.
- They did it in the movie.
- I've never seen tango before.
All of a sudden?
Actually, this is what we thought.
"Did Yeon Hee and Yeon Seok dance
tango in the movie?"
"Then can you show us a little?"
I thought it would go like this.
- We wouldn't do that.
- That's not what we do.
We don't say things like that.
- We get to the point right away.
- To the point.
Do you dance the tango? Show us.
- Right away?
- Yes.
So this is Yeon Seok
and Yeon Hee's tango performance.
Hang on.
This is...
- Can you make it look less abrupt?
- So...
The thing is,
they really want to show us.
- It's not like that.
- You want to talk more.
Let me tell you. In Argentina...
Boo, just go ahead and dance.
Just show us.
Let's just do it.
We will make it short.
- Then we can talk about it.
- Just dance first.
We'll talk after you dance.
With no explanation.
- I want you to lead.
- I don't know what to do.
- Let's go.
- But...
They strike the pose right away.
Gosh, this is tango.
But Yeon Hee...
(What would
their tango dance look like?)
(Wriggling)
(They wriggle together for a while.)
(Then they start to dance.)
(It's just the basic steps
from the beginner's tango class.)
(They don't know how to react.)
(But the two actors
are dancing seriously.)
(Crossing at a crosswalk?)
(Laughing)
(What is this?)
(A sudden finish)
Oh, no.
(They clap their hands anyway.)
You haven't done this
for a long time, right?
I just told you.
It's not that we prepared this.
- I can tell it's been a long time.
- We didn't prepare it.
I get it.
It's not that they were
unbelievably good.
They looked good together though.
The movie has a scene
where we dance the tango together.
We did it a year ago.
Ask him this question.
Why did he want to dance?
(Why did you want
to show us the dance?)
Will you stay quiet?
- I'm just curious.
- Will you stay quiet?
I'm just curious.
Aren't you curious?
- I didn't want to dance.
- So this is...
an important scene. I see.
But why?
Why did you want that so much?
Gosh, no one would
want to watch our movie.
So you wanted to dance.
- So it has the tango scene.
- I see.
I bet it looks different
in the movie.
It's not easy to show something
that you did a year ago.
- I know.
- But why did you want to do it?
(Why did you still want to try it?)
- I was...
- I guess he was really determined.
Yeon Seok, you must
love tango a lot.
He loves to tango.
I heard you are still
taking tango lessons.
Next up is Yoo Teo.
(Next up is an actor
of proven ability, Yoo Teo.)
He looks amazing.
I heard you were born in Germany.
- He was born in Germany too.
- Really?
- Were you born in Germany?
- Yes.
- In Stuttgart.
- Really?
- Which part?
- Cologne.
- Where?
- He doesn't know it.
- Really?
So Cologne is in Germany.
- You don't know where it is.
- Speak some German.
Do you speak German?
I'm fluent.
You should ask Haha
some questions then.
- Ask him questions.
- You're from the same country.
(Have a talk in German.)
- Say things like this.
- Ask him a question.
(Speaking German)
He's really good.
(The German kid answers
with his body language.)
- What? Why?
- Answer the question.
I know.
What do you know?
His German is really good.
So he's from Germany.
I lived in Germany until I was 21.
- His German is really good.
- He's a native.
That's why you have an accent.
I see.
He speaks good English too.
- Does he speak English as well?
- English?
Gosh.
Stop asking me
to speak foreign languages.
- They weren't going to ask you.
- There's more.
Stop asking me
to speak foreign languages.
(We weren't going to ask you
to speak more.)
- No one was going to.
- Because we don't...
get to see someone
who speaks German a lot.
Right. This is my first time.
Please give the four actors
a big hand then.
It's so good to see you.
As I told you before,
the guests wrote down your merits.
They wrote about our merits.
Those who know you
wrote the merits they know.
And those who don't know you
just wrote what they thought.
- I might not have anything.
- It's 100 points per merit.
- 100 points.
- We wrote about flaws.
Let's see what they wrote.
I don't think they wrote about me
because we're not acquainted.
- Right. We're not acquainted.
- Me neither.
This is empty.
- Right? This is...
- Gosh.
Hang on. What is this?
What does this mean?
"It hurts"?
Please read it for us.
I often spell things wrong.
- I got it wrong again.
- I know what it means.
Okay.
This is for me.
"He's always thoughtful
and considerate toward his guests."
- "He's the best."
- My gosh.
"He takes good care of himself."
"He's the best variety show host.
He's cool."
Jong Kook.
"He's very thrifty and frugal,"
"so he makes me reflect on myself."
"He looks scary even when he's
standing still during a race."
"He seems to be good at sports."
- "Will you be my training partner?"
- I know who wrote it.
One of the messages sounds
like it's automatically translated.
- This is Suk Jin's.
- Like a translation device.
This is for Suk Jin.
"He's an experienced veteran."
- "He's warm."
(It's obviously Teo's message.)
Yeon Seok.
"I worry about him
both when I see him on TV..."
"and when I shoot
a TV show with him."
(He's worried about shooting
a TV show with Suk Jin.)
Who was that?
It's supposed to be a compliment.
Who was that? Is that a compliment?
- He worries about you.
- I guess it's Sooyoung.
Haha's. "He greets me
with excessive reactions,"
"but I'm not sure
if he really means it."
Why would you say that?
It must be someone you know.
We should have a drink together.
Who is it?
You should reflect on yourself.
- It's someone who knows Haha.
- Let's drink together.
There you go again.
"He has a loud voice,
so I can hear him well."
Who is it?
They are forcing themselves
to say something good.
Gosh, this feels really good.
The compliments...
You all will end up in paradise.
I guess it was really hard for them
to find something meritorious.
- Someone squeezed out the comment.
- It's easy to hear his voice.
- They reluctantly wrote these.
- They had no choice.
- They saw us on TV...
- The compliments of Ji Hyo.
"She's so good at games.
She's both charismatic and pretty."
These also sound...
- half-hearted. Don't you think?
- Absolutely.
- Because they don't know us well.
- They were just being polite.
- It means they're not close to us.
- Exactly.
Right? Let's move on to Kwang Soo.
"He's a superstar
in Southeast Asia."
- In Southeast Asia?
- Yes.
- Who wrote that?
- Specifically in Southeast Asia?
I suppose this person saw Kwang Soo
only on TV.
- But... Why...
- So they're not acquainted.
- Why am I disappointed?
- Not a superstar in Asia?
- Let's move on to So Min.
- That's weird.
"I found out that she goes to
the same beauty parlor as me."
"I guess she has good taste."
Is this supposed to be sarcastic?
It sounds a little sarcastic.
- Is it sarcasm?
- It means they have similar tastes.
- It sounds like...
- Oh, I see.
He's just not good
at writing Korean.
These are about Se Chan.
"He's as funny as his teeth."
- "I don't know him. Who is he?"
(I don't know him. Who is he?")
- That's so funny.
- It sounds so half-hearted.
- There was nothing to write.
- None whatsoever.
- Okay. I won't forget this.
- Jae Suk...
It seems to me that they wrote
in this order from here.
- So they were tired at the end.
- They got tired.
- Their comments got much shorter.
- They still had to write something.
- Okay.
- The handwriting...
But he's getting more famous
as So Min's boyfriend.
He's getting more famous
Today, it's the 2020 Year-End
Feelings Settlement Race.
We tallied the scores you received
from the other members and guests...
from the complaint and compliment
surveys.
- I'll announce your scores now.
- Okay.
The members
in the first place are...
Ji Hyo and So Min with 500 points.
- Really?
- Nice.
Kwang Soo's score is
minus 1,100 points.
Minus 1,100 points?
Now, you'll be divided into
4 teams of 3 people.
The tallied score of team members
will be your team score.
You will receive scores according to
the result of the mission.
The 1st 2 teams that gain
2,020 points will win.
- 2,020 points?
- Yes.
If 2 members have minus 100
and minus 300 points,
their team score is
minus 400 points.
When your team score is
2,020 points, the race ends.
Oh, 2,020 points. I see.
The 2 winning teams will receive
1,000 dollars as New Year's gift.
- Really?
- 1,000 dollars?
And the team with the lowest score
will receive a penalty.
Let's decide teams now.
Bring the gifts here.
We'll begin the first mission
after you change your clothes.
- Okay.
(They're gathering at the place
for the 1st mission 1 by 1.)
- Gosh. It's so cold.
- It's really cold here.
You're shaking because of
the mere cold.
- Jae Suk.
- You're cringing your fingers.
You seem to be feeling very cold.
He's so cool. He looks cool
even when doing his warm-ups.
You can tell he works out regularly.
- Whom are you talking about?
- Teo.
I didn't realize earlier, but he...
He has such a muscular body.
Teo, how old are you?
- I'm 40.
- I'm sorry.
Are you serious?
He's 40.
- Teo, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- My goodness.
I'm sorry. I thought you were
younger than me. I'm sorry.
- Why?
- I didn't know.
I asked him, "How old are you?"
Teo, I'm really sorry.
- Pardon me?
- I apologize.
- He thought he was older than you.
- I thought I was older than you.
- That's why talked like that.
- That's okay. Don't worry.
- It's a good thing.
- I thought he was younger than you.
He looks much younger than
his actual age.
- Teo is 40.
- I thought he was younger than me.
- He's 40.
- He has a babyface.
- I thought the same as Se Chan.
- Me too.
- Right?
- Please sit down.
This will be fun.
- Yutnori is easy.
- We'll play yutnori.
- Okay. One of them is different.
- Yutnori!
Yutnori requires some skills.
- I'm good at yutnori.
- You need good sense.
Exactly.
- The first mission is...
- I'm really good at this.
Bomb Yutnori, the upgraded yutnori.
- What is it?
- It sounds fun.
It has the same basic rules
as regular yutnori.
However, each team will receive
one normal piece...
and one bomb piece.
When your normal piece is back
at the starting point, you're done.
And you'll receive different scores
according to the result of the game.
As you can see,
we have five yut-sticks.
- What's the extra stick?
- The dark brown stick is...
the bomb yut-stick.
There are bombs drawn
on the other side.
- So?
- If that side is up,
you get to place your bomb piece
anywhere you want.
- Anywhere we want?
- It's like a landmine.
- It explodes when we stop there.
The bomb explodes,
and the team that placed the bomb
gains 100 points.
(The team that stops at the bomb
goes back to the starting point.)
- We should place it wisely.
- Okay.
- It's good.
- It's like the famous board game.
Instead, you can't catch other
teams' pieces with your piece.
You can only catch them
with your bomb.
- Even if you stop at the same spot.
- Okay.
When you get yut or mo,
you get to throw sticks again.
But you must move your piece
before throwing the sticks again.
If you stop where there's
a bomb is, you lose the chance.
- Okay.
- We must move our piece first?
Correct. You can't move your piece
after throwing the sticks again.
- We can't add the moves later.
- We must stick to the order, right?
- You must move it right away.
- Okay.
Yeon Seok stands out so much.
Come on. Don't be like that.
It's not because of me.
- It's not just Yeon Seok.
- It's not because of me.
(Yeon Seok stands out,
and Kwang Soo denies it.)
- I think...
- Jae Suk,
Yeon Seok stands out among them,
but Suk Jin also stands out.
He stands out so much.
He's our grandfather.
Team Green.
He wants to blend in by any means.
He put on a pink cap
to blend in with his team members.
He looks like an old man
with his grandchildren.
- In my entire life...
- Grandpa, happy New Year.
Stop it. Gosh.
- I wish you a long, healthy life.
- They look like good grandchildren.
He stands out too.
The same goes for your team.
Teo stands out so much.
- Who?
- Teo.
- Teo looks even more handsome.
- Teo stands out?
He looks even younger.
Jae Suk, don't act like
you didn't expect that answer.
Did you think she referred to you?
Okay. I admit it.
He became so shameless.
- Okay.
- Shall we decide the order?
Let's do that.
Let's sit in the order. 1, 2, 3, 4.
How about you sit in the order?
The first team should sit here.
- We're the 3rd team.
- The 1st team should sit there.
The first team is here.
The first team, sit over there.
Team Mint Green.
This is the worst.
That side...
- looks so gloomy.
- The atmosphere is so bad.
Hey, you look like braised monkfish.
- Braised monkfish?
- Yes, braised monkfish.
- You look just like it.
- I have all sorts of nicknames.
That's too mean.
- He looks like braised monkfish.
- Father, that's enough.
You look like braised monkfish,
not even monkfish soup.
Stop it.
I can see how different we all look.
Now that I saw you closely,
I realized your gums are
so pink and pretty.
- I can't believe him.
- He has pretty pink gums.
- I'm surprised.
- It's pretty pink.
- It's the color of pork belly.
- The color is so pretty.
I know, right?
I'll give you some later.
No wonder why I craved soju
when I saw his face.
His gums are pretty pink.
- Let's begin.
- This team goes first.
- Okay.
- Sooyoung, throw the sticks.
- Me?
- The yut-sticks.
- Team Mint Green will go first.
- Go ahead.
- Shouldn't we spread it properly?
- He's right.
Is it out if only part of a stick
goes out of the mat?
Of course, it's out.
- No.
- Isn't it okay to be partially out?
It's in as long as a part of it is
on the mat.
- It's in if a part of it is on it.
- Like this?
- Well...
- We can stand in the front.
You can throw the sticks over there.
No. Let's draw a line here.
- Everyone should stand here.
- She sounded so firm.
- We should throw the sticks there?
- No.
- It's too far.
- I can't throw them there.
- All of them will go out.
- That's not necessary.
- But... I mean...
- Don't people...
throw the sticks over the mat?
- You don't know the rules, do you?
- Listen.
- I mean...
- The game won't end that way.
- We draw a line in my neighborhood.
- Where is it?
Cheongdam-dong.
Do they have such a rule
in Cheongdam-dong?
- Many of us live there.
- There's no such rule there.
Is that how they play this
in Cheongdam-dong?
Everyone throws
from a different distance.
- That's up to you.
- That doesn't matter.
What if I throw them
right in front of the mat?
- That's okay.
- That's how it's done.
- Really? Is it okay?
- But you must throw them high.
- You shouldn't roll the sticks.
- Above your head.
- When you're in a sitting position.
Then the lower your body is,
the easier it gets.
- Go ahead and try it.
- Why must this be so complicated?
- Have you never played it before?
- Just try it.
That's not the point of the game,
Sooyoung.
Just relax.
I was afraid you might complain
about how I throw them.
- We won't.
- I promise we won't.
- Okay. I'll do it as I want.
- Yes. Go ahead.
What if it falls like this?
- It's in.
- That's okay.
- It's in?
- Yes, it's in.
- Okay.
- It's out if more than half is out.
- You're quite meticulous.
- More than half?
Whom have you been playing
this game with?
It always causes a fight
in my family.
- It happens a lot.
- Exactly.
- Your family fights over this?
- It happens a lot.
You're taking too much time.
Okay. I'll do it now. 1, 2, 3.
- Good.
- That's good.
- It's out.
- Look at Jong Kook's face.
Look at Jong Kook's face.
(It went out?)
- It's out.
- He's so excited.
Jong Kook is in shock.
You're so cheeky.
I hate you the most.
- Jong Kook is shocked.
- I'm happy.
- Good job, Sooyoung.
- Yeon Hee.
- Gosh. She wouldn't stop talking.
That stick went completely out
of the mat.
Hey, Yeon Hee. Yeon Hee.
You should throw them high
so we can see your hands move.
- I'll throw them like this.
- Good. That's acceptable.
- That's how it should be done.
- That's good.
- It's out.
- I knew it.
- It's quite hard.
- Move.
- Come on out.
- It goes out if you throw high.
Both of them failed. I get it now.
Here comes a handsome man.
We just have to move our piece.
- That's right.
- Because they all failed.
- Let's see.
- Anything would do.
- Can I begin now?
- Of course. Go ahead.
- Let's move our piece.
- Throw them high.
- It's out.
(He can't move the piece
as it went out.)
- What was that?
- This is a mess.
- Why did you throw them there?
- Why did you do that?
- Why did everyone fail?
- I don't believe this.
He practically threw the sticks
on the floor.
- I didn't know it was so hard.
- I think the mat should be larger.
- Let's spread it a little.
- Is it hard?
Let's spread the blanket
a little wider.
Yeon Seok came out,
and confidently said,
"We just have to move our piece."
You shouldn't have been
so confident.
What they did wrong was...
- You should throw from a distance.
- Exactly.
Don't act like you're good at it.
You failed so many times
the last time we played this game.
- Shut it.
- You failed so many times.
You just have to throw as high as
your eyes lying on the side.
- Good. That's a good stance.
- Like this.
He reminds me of an uncle
who hasn't gotten married...
that you meet when your relatives
gather on holidays.
- Wearing sweatpants...
- Exactly.
- It's the only time they can brag.
- and picking a fight with everyone.
Watch me.
- Only on holidays,
- What are you doing?
- they meet other people.
- Shut it, will you?
- Watch me.
- It's the only time they show off.
- Just as high as your eyes.
- I'm 100 percent sure it'll be out.
- Out.
- It's out.
- It's still in. Oh, gosh.
The mat is too small.
- No one got them on the mat.
- It's too small.
- It's out.
- Let's spread it.
- Shall we?
- Okay.
- It's too small.
- Why can't we do this?
Hey, we can discuss things
and move on like this.
This is why...
Can I say something?
- Go ahead.
- It's too small.
- I told you earlier.
- About what?
If we draw a line and...
- We already refused to do that.
- We won't do it in your style.
- Why would you do it like that?
- Let's just do it normally.
- Wait. I'll show you.
- Let's just follow normal rules.
If we throw the sticks here,
we'll keep failing.
- It'll be out.
- Okay. Show us.
- We draw a line and throw them...
- Here?
- The tone of your voice...
- in our own ways.
- I see.
- In our own ways?
- Just as you want to do it.
- Okay. I like it.
- It seems better.
- Shall we fold a little?
- Yes, just a little.
- Okay.
- And then...
- Wait. You should flip it over.
- If it goes out of here, it's out.
- Flip it over.
- Fold it and flip it over.
- Gosh. Why is this...
- When are we going to begin?
Gosh, seriously.
(He kicked the blanket.)
Go. Get out.
- Everyone, just go home.
- Leave. Get lost.
- You go first.
- Get out of my house.
- This is my house.
- You go first.
I'll watch a movie,
so all of you, get out.
(I'll watch "New Year Blues",
so get out.)
It might take us three hours
to set up the rules.
- As expected...
- Gosh. This is just a game.
- The couple...
- We're good.
- And now...
- Just do as Sooyoung says.
- Right.
- She'll state the rules.
We'll follow Sooyoung's
Cheongdam-dong Rule.
- Right.
- Of course.
Okay, 1, 2, 3.
Okay, good.
- Geol.
- It's a geol.
- Geol with no bomb.
- Geol.
- Here.
Let's go catch that.
Yeon Hee, let's get them.
Hey, look.
- Nice one.
- Nice.
We caught that team.
- No.
- It's not like regular yutnori.
- You'll be placing a bomb.
- We can't catch the others?
- So we move alongside them?
- We occupy the same spot?
- The bomb.
- Where should we place it?
It should be where they might land.
How about here?
That's not a bad idea.
- Yeon Seok, don't roll a gae.
- Don't roll a gae.
- Because of the bomb?
- Just don't roll a gae.
- Geol would be ideal.
- You'll roll a gae.
A gae, gae, gae...
- Hold on a second.
- Gae, gae, gae...
You're Yoo Yeon Gae.
- Yoo Yeon Gae?
- Seriously?
- Then Gae Yeon Seok.
- Are you kidding me?
Gae Yeon Seok?
I'm wishing for him to roll a gae.
- Don't mind him.
- Gae...
- I mean...
- Suk Jin even shocked himself.
- He keeps saying "gae."
- Gae Yeon Seok.
- Gosh.
Yoo Yeon Gae.
Roll a gae. Come on.
- Geol.
- Gosh.
- And a bomb.
- It's a gae!
- It's a gae.
- No, a geol.
Gae. How is this a geol?
- Of course, it's a geol.
- It's a geol.
This should be ignored.
- What do you mean?
- Just look at it.
- It's a geol.
- Shouldn't this be ignored?
- Do, gae, geol.
- How is this a geol?
- How is it not?
- It's a geol for sure.
- Unbelievable.
My eyes have been
deceiving me lately.
So do, gae, geol.
- This is the turning point.
- It's easy to land here.
- Like this.
- See?
- But we could land on it too.
- A turning point.
- Is it possible to set off ours?
- Of course.
So we shouldn't do that.
Since it's your turn,
you choose where to put it.
Sure.
(They let Yeon Seok decide
where to place the bomb.)
But...
- Hurry up.
- You're placing it up there?
(Yeon Seok places the bomb
ahead of his team's piece.)
- He placed it.
- You're placing it up there?
(Yeon Seok decided
to block all 3 teams.)
- You can't move it.
- But what about us?
You can't take it back.
But we could land on it instead.
- We'll just not land there.
- We're doomed.
Let's roll a geol!
Can you move? It's our turn now.
Gae Teo.
- Gae Teo.
- No, Geol Teo.
- Just roll them.
- Don't mind him.
- Gae Teo.
He rolled a gae!
- It's a gae.
- A gae.
- Gae.
- Yes, this is a gae.
We're the only team
still at the starting line.
- Nice.
- Okay.
- So we get 100 points?
- Let's speed things up.
Is this allowed?
- Next is So Min.
- So Min!
Gosh.
- It's a gae.
- A gae.
Okay, that's good.
(So Min rolled a gae.)
- Okay, that's good.
- I didn't roll a bomb though.
We made it.
- Where do we go?
- No, we landed on a bomb.
You landed on a bomb.
(They landed on a bomb.)
Nice, it's our bomb!
(Team Yeon Seok
receives 100 points.)
It's the bomb that I placed.
Right.
- It was a great choice.
- Geol and gae mostly get rolled.
- Right.
- Okay.
Gae... We can roll
just about anything.
- Another bomb would be nice.
- Life's all about one lucky punch.
A bomb and a geol.
- No, a gae.
- A gae.
We'll move two steps.
- Today...
- They get to turn directions.
Let's place it here.
They could make a run for it.
Just don't roll a do.
- Braised monkfish.
- Just don't roll a do.
- Go for it.
- Roll a do.
Nice!
- Nice!
- One rolled out.
It doesn't count.
- Kwang Soo...
- You just killed our momentum.
- I'm sorry.
- Haha.
- Are you kidding me?
- What now?
- That's what he rolled.
Let's do this!
You just killed our momentum.
- A gae.
- Gae!
Nice one. It's not bad.
- Darn it.
- Here.
- We were on a roll.
- Is ours in black?
- Next is...
- Jong Kook.
- There are bombs everywhere.
If only we were able
to place a bomb.
- There...
- You get your wish.
I know, you're getting your wish.
- What do we need?
- A yut.
- Anything will be great.
- Except a yut?
- Right.
- Roll a yut.
It's a yut!
He rolled a yut!
(Back to the starting line,
Plus 100 points)
- Nice!
- He rolled a yut.
- Everyone, he rolled a yut.
- A yut!
- Yut, yut.
(Let's celebrate.)
It's a yut.
You can still place a bomb though.
- Can we place a bomb though?
- Yes, you can.
So much for rolling a big one.
(They must place it
where it'll hurt the others most.)
This line wouldn't be bad.
- How about right here?
- Okay.
- So Min, good choice.
- If they roll a geol...
- That's right.
- We can roll anything but that.
How about we place it at the center?
Sure, the center.
Sure, roll a geol.
I can roll anything but that.
Geol Suk Jin.
- Roll a geol.
- Geol Suk Jin.
Geol Suk Jin.
(The chant's childish
but addictive.)
Does the "geol" mean beggar
in his case?
- Geol Suk Jin.
- Ji Seok Geol.
- Okay!
- It's a do.
- A do.
- Do.
- A do at this part of the game?
Do.
They just have to roll a gae next.
You're right. It's better this way.
We'll place bombs in its path.
- They could still roll a geol.
- Go, go!
(They'll target Team Yeon Hee
by making a minefield.)
- Let's do this.
- Gae.
You...
- Roll a gae.
- Just roll a bomb.
You talk a lot for someone
who only rolled a gae.
- You are so talkative.
- I've been the best on this team.
Are you good at yutnori?
- Yes, I'm a professional.
- Get back here.
The Young Master of Mapo-gu.
- Just don't let it roll out.
- Come on!
- Nice!
- One rolled off!
(One rolled off the mat once again.)
- Move.
- It doesn't count.
- Nice!
- Seriously?
- The mat's not even far away.
- Kwang Soo failed!
- Kwang Soo Out!
- I didn't mean to.
- Just watch.
- Watch how I get it done.
- Okay.
Okay.
- He tossed them forward.
- Nice!
- A yut.
- I rolled a yut!
- Okay.
- You get another roll.
Does he get another roll?
- Give me a yut.
- Must he be so sly?
- Good.
- Nice one!
- Gae.
- Gae and a bomb.
- Right, a gae and a bomb.
We need to catch this team,
so this is where it should go.
- Do, gae, geol.
- Target the team in the lead.
They'll land on a bomb
if they roll a gae or a geol.
- Gae.
- Darn, we're doomed this time.
They're doomed.
We're in big trouble.
(They make a minefield
that blocks Team Yeon Hee's way.)
- Let's do this!
- It's a minefield.
Yeon Hee, you're next.
- No...
- The bombs are in one line.
No, you should do it...
- since this is an important moment.
- Look at all those bombs.
Yeon Hee.
Yeon Hee, look.
You can't roll a gae or a geol.
All right, a gae or a geol.
(Will they be able
to avoid the bombs?)
One rolled out!
- Gae or geol.
- What on earth?
- It's a yut!
(A yut!)
- Seriously?
- It's a yut.
- How is she so good at this?
(They jump over the bombs
thanks to Yeon Hee.)
- How can this be?
- It's a yut.
- They jumped over them.
- All of them.
- No way.
- You get another roll.
The game's nearly over then.
- No way.
- Go ahead.
They're masters at this.
- Please go out.
- One went out!
- Okay.
- One went out.
One rolled out.
It would've been another yut.
Yeon Seok, we need to block them
by placing a bomb.
- What...
- This is our last chance.
- Come on.
- We need to move forward too.
- We mostly need a bomb.
- Right, we need a bomb.
We need to stop the other team.
I bet one will roll out.
- I'm sure of it.
- Please roll a gae.
- One will go out.
- I agree.
One will roll off the mat!
(It's their 4th time already.)
You guys are good
at missing the mat.
Seriously?
- Yeon Seok.
- You're the worst.
- Yutnori...
- He's the weakest link.
- He's terrible at this.
- It isn't even funny anymore.
- Yeon Seok's the weakest link.
- It's our third time already.
It's their third time.
- It doesn't matter though.
- It's their third time.
- Lower your torso.
- Get out of his way!
Lower your torso.
- What do they need?
- Just throw them.
- Let's go.
- Let it roll off the mat.
- Geol. No, it's a yut.
- It's a yut!
(They roll a yut with no bomb.)
- Yut pops up often.
- It's a yut.
(They already make it past
Team Sooyoung.)
We'll be strict with the rules
from now on.
Okay, I'm loving the stance.
- Good.
- That's how we all do it.
Go ahead.
- Let's see.
- All right.
- It's not bad.
- A gae and a bomb.
This is actually better.
A gae and a bomb.
Where...
Let's make sure
they won't follow us.
Following us along this line
will lead to their demise.
Do, gae...
We're not your enemy at the moment!
Guys, just look.
- Take a look at this.
- We rolled a gae.
Nice. No one's bothering
to block our way.
Let's just stay quiet.
It might end up
blocking their way too.
That team will roll
before you do, right?
It's better to target them first.
Sooyoung's right.
- What if we land on it?
- Yes, I'm right.
Still...
- A gae?
- Yes.
- Let's roll a geol.
- It's all right.
- Geol.
- Gae is rolled most often.
- Gae.
We can't even
take part in the conversation.
- We are not even close to them.
- How many times has he done this?
It's like we're invisible.
I've lost interest in the game.
(Team Yeon Seok
seems to be on the sidelines.)
- Gae.
- Roll a gae!
- Gae So Min.
- Roll gae and you're done for.
- Woof, woof!
- Did you hear that?
Why on earth are you
excited by that nickname?
Being so will prevent me
from rolling a gae.
- Woof.
- Jeon So Gae.
- Get a bomb too while you're at it.
At least set up a bomb.
- Out, out, out, out
- Out!
(She lets the rhythm sink in.)
- Hold on a second.
- Out, out, out, out
Just keep quiet
so that she can roll them.
- All right.
- I'm begging you.
- Don't excite her like this.
- Got it.
- But I want to have fun.
- All right.
- But you...
- I can't believe Yeon Seok sang it.
Out, out, out.
I want one to roll off the mat!
- Just let her be.
- I want one to roll off the mat!
Don't provoke her.
Out So Min.
- Jeon So Out.
- Stay put, will you?
Why can't I do what I want?
I just...
- They're at it again.
- It's just something I want to do.
- Suk Jin's upset.
- Their show has begun.
- But So Min was enjoying it.
- Still...
She was having fun,
but so was I.
We were all having fun, right?
Jong Kook, just let the two
have some fun.
- He's right.
- Roll a gae
Gae So Min rolls a gae
A bomb and a geol.
- A geol!
- A bomb and a geol.
- Okay, good.
- She rolled a bomb.
I said we should assume
that they'd roll a geol.
(They jump past Team Teo's bomb.)
- Nicely done.
- Nice!
- Is it good for us?
- Of course.
Geol or a gae?
- What do we do next?
- A gae or...
- What's better for us?
- A gae.
- Exactly.
- So here.
- I agree.
- Me too.
We're finally joining
the game, right?
- Let's move forward now.
- At least roll a bomb.
- You can do it.
- Yeon Seok, don't worry.
- We need to roll a bomb at least.
- Right.
We at least need a bomb.
Just make sure they stay on the mat.
(Yeon Seok solemnly
straightens out the mat.)
Look at Yeon Seok.
You're straightening out the mat.
I'll just make sure
none rolls out of the mat.
- It's actually our turn.
- What?
Our team's next.
I see.
- What...
- Yeon Seok, it's not our turn.
(He's straightening out the mat.)
- It's not our turn.
- It isn't?
- It's not our turn yet.
- It's not our turn?
- Yeon Hee said...
- Get it together.
When will our turn come?
- Let's keep it together.
- Is it Yeon Hee's turn?
- I see.
- It's not hers either.
- Okay.
- Where's Ji Hyo?
Here comes Jeoktoma
- She'll crush you all
- Jeoktoma! Jeoktoma!
- No!
- It's out.
- It's in.
- It's on the mat.
We'll call this as out.
- Okay. It's out.
- It's out.
- Me?
- Yes.
- If it goes out this time...
- Make sure it won't happen.
- I'll do that.
- Just avoid getting out.
- Stay focused.
- Okay.
- Out, out, out
- Team Gray is still there?
The sticks rolled out of the mat
repeatedly.
- We couldn't move our piece.
- We never got a bomb.
- Out, out, out
- Earlier...
Out Se Chan, Out Se Chan
Out Se Chan
- Out Se Chan!
- I am braised monkfish
Gosh, seriously.
The small serving, 25 dollars
I am braised monkfish,
monkfish, monkfish
- All right.
- "The small serving, 25 dollars"?
- Out Se Chan ate an octopus again
- Out Se Chan
- I hope the sticks will slide out
- I just have to avoid getting out.
- Out Se Chan
Se Chan never let any sticks
roll off the mat.
- Out Se Chan
- Out, out, out, out, out
- Focus.
- Out Se Chan
- Throw them high
- It'll go out
- It's out!
(It's out!)
(The team failed to move forward
for the 5th time in a row.)
- It's out, it's out, it's out
- Gosh.
- I'm sorry.
- What's wrong with you?
- I don't know. I couldn't do it.
- I know you can do better.
- They keep getting out.
- I'm sorry.
- Move.
- Okay!
Gosh. This is annoying.
- That was...
- Even I'm annoyed too.
- This is so boring.
- They're really bad at this.
- It's not fun anymore.
- It's not fun at all.
- I'm frustrated. What are we doing?
- My gosh.
I hope we get 1 yut. No, 2 yut.
- Yut, yut.
- It doesn't match the drawing.
- Geol, geol.
- Yut, yut.
- Geol, geol, geol.
- Please stop there.
- Geolster, Geolster.
- Geolster.
- Hey.
- I thought I misheard it.
- I didn't know you'd say that.
- It sounds fun.
- That was unexpected.
- It suits him.
- It suits him well.
- Geolster?
- Haha.
- Geolster.
- Yut.
- Yut, yut.
- Geolster, Geolster.
- Please get a geol.
- Geol.
- Get a geol.
(Haha's team will lead the game
if he gets anything but a geol.)
- Geol.
- Geolster.
- It's a geol.
- It's out.
(Swarming)
- It's a geol.
- No, it's not.
- It's out.
- You're wrong. It's a geol.
- It's a geol.
- It's out.
- It's out. It's out. Say it.
- It's definitely a geol.
- It's out.
- No, it's a geol.
- Check the camera.
- It's definitely out.
- We came to a conclusion.
- We discussed it.
- It's in.
- We concluded it's in.
- It's a geol.
- All right.
- Okay.
- They stopped here.
- They landed on the bomb.
(They landed on a bomb and went back
to the starting point.)
There's a team behind us now.
- There's a team behind us.
- Let's stay alert.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
We still have a chance.
Gosh, that brat.
Jae Suk.
- They don't jibe with each other.
- It's not like you did well.
- They can't be on the same team.
- Did you do well?
- Just break up already.
- You didn't do well either.
- We're back at the starting point.
- They never jibe with each other.
- Gosh, that brat.
- I've been too nice to you.
We never jibe with each other.
She knows much about variety shows
as she has a lot of experience.
She knows much about variety shows.
- Good.
- It's a yut.
- Let's move our piece.
- How does she throw the sticks?
- It's a yut.
- We can move four steps.
- We're almost there.
That team is almost done.
- They're almost done.
- We're done for.
- Okay.
- Wait. She just put them down.
- What?
She just put them down
instead of throwing them.
- This doesn't count.
- People at Cheongdam-dong are...
- so underhanded.
- Fine.
- She didn't throw them.
- She never throw them properly.
I'll throw them properly this time.
- I guess after the shoot,
- Make sure to bend your arm.
we won't see each other
for a while.
- I'm so upset right now.
- Bend your arm.
This will be my last appearance
on Running Man.
- So I'll throw them hard.
- Sounds good.
- That's good enough.
- It's a yut.
It's a yut!
- That's great.
- Oh, yes.
Didn't she throw them too lightly?
- Go ahead.
- She threw them properly.
- They're almost there.
- We'll end it.
- It was acceptable.
- It's a do.
- Do and a bomb.
- We got a do and a bomb.
- We passed the finishing point.
- Okay.
And then...
- They passed it.
- Where should we place the bomb?
Where shall we place it?
(The other teams will fight
for the 2nd place.)
- We finished it.
- We won fairly.
- Fair and square.
- I've never won fairly before.
Fair and square.
Let's get 2 yut and 3 mo.
- Let's move on.
- Okay.
- Yang Gae Chan.
- You can do it.
Yang Gae Chan.
- It's a yut!
- Yut!
(Finally, they got their 1st yut.)
- Let's go.
- It's a yut.
- They might land on a bomb.
- Exactly.
You can land on a bomb anytime.
- A do would be perfect.
- Right.
A bomb would be nice too.
- Where is it?
- A bomb, please.
- A bomb! And a yut!
- It's a yut! It's a yut!
(They got 2 yut and 1 bomb
in 2 attempts.)
- It's a yut.
- He just drooled.
Yeon Seok drooled.
(After he checked the result,)
(he got so excited he drooled.)
- He drooled.
- Yeon Seok.
Yeon Seok.
- He drooled.
- Yeon Seok.
- My gosh.
- Stop it already.
- I'm so happy.
- He drooled!
- Yeon Seok, are you that excited?
- Hey, pretend you didn't see it.
Pretend you didn't see it!
- Yeon Seok just drooled.
- I'm so happy.
This is so sweet.
- Getting 2 yut is so sweet.
- He got too excited.
- Drooling Yeon Seok.
- My gosh.
- I can't believe he drooled.
- Drooling Yeon Seok.
- Are you that happy?
- Yes.
- Yeon Seok is so funny.
- Are you excited?
This is so sweet.
- He's so down-to-earth.
- My goodness.
- We should avoid a geol.
- I hope you get a geol.
- Is it Yeon Seok's turn?
- Yes, he'll throw them.
- Throw them hard.
- Geol, geol.
- It will be a disaster
(It will be a disaster, my darling)
- What's that song?
- It's "Girl" by Aspirin.
(They're getting better at choosing
a song to distract another team.)
(Team Yeon Seok can avoid a bomb
if he avoids a geol.)
- Geol, geol, geol.
- Mo, mo.
- Geol.
- Good.
- Geol, geol, geol.
- Mo, mo.
- Geol.
- Good.
- Oh, yes!
- It's a geol.
(They got a geol.)
- Oh, yes!
- It's a geol.
Oh, yes.
What is wrong with him?
(Team Yeon Seok landed on a bomb and
went back to the starting point.)
- He's so bad at this.
- We were so close.
He made me lose interest
in the game.
We were so close.
- Yeon Seok is so bad at this.
- Okay.
We could be in second place.
- You see...
- Save it.
I don't know
what the penalty will be.
You'll most likely receive
the penalty.
Anyway, you will...
get the penalty.
(Because of Yeon Seok's
terrible mistakes...)
- We won!
- Oh, yes!
- My goodness.
- We're in second place.
(Team Yeon Hee came in 2nd place
10 minutes later.)
Gosh. It's not working out
well for us.
It's okay.
- I'll announce your scores.
- Okay.
The team in first place received
1,000 points.
(Team Sooyoung
gained 1,000 points!)
- And the 2nd place?
- The team in 2nd place gained 500,
the 3rd place gained 300,
and the 4th place gained 100 points.
- We gained 300 points.
- We gained 100 points.
500, 300, and 100 points?
- There aren't large differences.
- Okay.
- We'll move to the next location.
Gosh. I'm so upset.
(Team Sooyoung: Minus 400 points,
Team Yeon Hee: Minus 400 points,)
(Team Teo: Minus 900 points,)
(Team Yeon Seok: Minus 1,200 points)
I didn't know Yeon Seok was
so bad at the game.
It turns out he's not good
at yutnori.
He was so bad at it.
He did even worse than we did.
I shouldn't have teased Kwang Soo...
for being lousy at games.
I only got humiliated.
Yeon Seok got so excited
that he drooled.
- Just because we got a yut...
- That was unforgettable.
- We got 2 yut in a row.
- He drooled...
I got so excited
when we got our second yut.
- He was exhilarated.
- He rarely drools like that.
Exactly.
(He was overly excited
and saliva came out of his mouth.)
- Everyone.
- Yes?
- We'll do the last mission shortly.
- Yes.
- And we'll play a simple game now.
- Okay.
To celebrate the year-end,
we'll reflect upon ourselves...
at the age of 20 when we were
full of hopes and dreams.
It's When I Was 20 Years Old.
When I Was 20 Years Old.
- It makes me tear up.
- Okay.
We prepared the 10 songs that were
popular when you were 20.
(The top 10 hit songs
when they were 20 are prepared!)
And we'll play one of the songs
randomly.
You'll listen to the song
for three seconds,
and guess who was 20
when the song was popular,
- the song title, and the singer.
- Okay.
For example, you can say, "Jae Suk,
the singer, the song title".
- I see.
- I feel emotional.
- It's touching.
- I get it.
How do we know the songs that were
popular when Suk Jin was 20?
- It's Suk Jin if it's a folk song.
- Exactly.
I think it's disadvantageous to you.
Se Chan, are you and Kwang Soo
the same age?
- I don't remember.
- He's the same age as So Min.
I'm one year younger than Kwang Soo.
- You're one year younger than him?
- Yes.
You appeared
on many variety shows, right?
- It's because you're rude.
- No, that's not it.
When people who don't know us
see us, they think...
It's because I look older
than my age.
Kwang Soo is one year
younger than me.
- You were born in 1984.
- Yes.
How much older are you
than me, Yeon Hee?
- I was born in 1988.
- She's younger than you.
(He thought she was older than him.)
- Really?
You speak casually to people
who are older than you.
- I thought she was older than me.
- You talk formally to younger ones.
That was discourteous of you.
- I thought she was older than me.
- Right. It was so rude of you.
- I'm sorry.
- Se Chan.
- Earlier, you asked Teo...
- I did the same thing Teo.
- "Teo, how old are you?"
And he said, "I'm 40."
Teo, I'm sorry again.
- What's with you?
- I keep guessing wrong.
- "How much older are you than me?"
- Exactly.
Yeon Hee looks like she's only 23.
- Suk Jin, that's enough.
- That's enough.
- Suk Jin must feel uncomfortable.
- You're making her uncomfortable.
- You should know when to stop.
- She's on my team.
They're arguing again.
I'll meet Jong Kook privately later.
I've been waiting for the day
when you call me out.
Suk Jin, if you are to roll
on the ground, go to a snowy field.
- After it snowed a lot.
- I'll treat him to a nice meal.
Let's hear from our correspondent.
Se Chan.
Yes, this is Yang Se Chan.
Tell us what happened.
Something absolutely shocking
happened here.
- He's good at it.
- Comedian Ji Suk Jin...
was rolling on the ground
without wearing trousers.
in the snowy field.
He wasn't wearing trousers?
- He wasn't wearing trousers?
- No, he wasn't.
It doesn't seem like
he did it of his own accord.
It seems that someone else
robbed them from him.
That's all.
(The prime suspect for stealing
his trousers is Mr. Kim.)
All right. Here's your
first question. Cue.
Cue.
(The 1st song will be played.)
- Haha.
- So Min.
(As they heard the familiar intro,)
(everyone got excited.)
- So Min.
- Haha, say the answer.
So Min, S.E.S, "Dreams Come True".
She wasn't 20 at the time.
- Wrong.
- Let me answer.
Yeon Seong...
- "Yeon Seong"?
- Wrong.
- That's wrong.
- What was that?
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
- How could you not know his name?
Ji Hyo, S.E.S, "Dreams Come True".
- Wrong.
- Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo was faster.
- Kwang Soo, go ahead.
Haha, S.E.S, "Dreams Come True".
- Correct.
- Okay!
- Really? I didn't realize it.
- Haha.
- "Dreams Come True".
- My gosh.
What a shame.
- It was when you were 20.
- Dreams come true
Was he exactly 20 years old?
("Dreams Come True" by S.E.S
was a hit song of 1998.)
(The song made the hearts of
all men flutter including Haha.)
So it was when Haha was 20.
- What a shame.
- The song was very popular.
- Here's the second question.
- It was Haha.
Cue.
- Let me answer.
The answer is...
- Suk Jin...
- Oh, right.
- Suk Jin, Kim Wan Sun...
- That's correct.
- Wait.
- 3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer!
- Let me answer.
- I said it first.
- So Min, go ahead.
Suk Jin, Kim Wan Sun,
"The Pierrot Smiles at Us".
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
(She was certain,
but her answer was incorrect.)
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
- Suk Jin,
Kim Wan Sun,
"The Piroro Always Smiles at Us".
- Piroro?
- Let me answer.
(What? Piroro?)
- Piroro?
- Let me answer.
- What is Piroro?
Suk Jin, Kim Wan Sun,
"The Pierrot Smiles at Us".
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
- The answer was correct.
- Is it me?
- It must be you.
- Jae Suk,
Kim Wan Sun,
"The Pierrot Smiles at Us".
- Correct.
- Okay!
(Team Yeon Seok
got 2 questions right in a row!)
- Whose song is it?
- Yours.
Is it mine?
Is it his? Isn't it mine?
- You were 20 years old.
- Did the song come out in 1991?
(The masterpiece caused a sensation
when Jae Suk was 20 years old.)
Team Yeon Seok
got two questions right.
This is a team competition, right?
- Yes, it is.
- All right.
Good job. Yeon Seok.
- They got two questions right.
- Good job.
Kwang Soo keeps stealing answers.
Here comes the next question.
(It's the third question.)
Se Chan!
What is this song?
Se Chan, Buzz, "Coward".
(Se Chan, Buzz, "Coward")
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
- So Min.
- You are right.
- Kwang Soo, Buzz, "Thorn".
- It must be Kwang Soo.
No.
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
Yeon Seok.
- 5, 4,
- Buzz,
- three...
- "Coward"...
- Is it Yeon Seok?
- So Min.
- Incorrect.
- I told you it's incorrect!
(He explodes.)
What is wrong with him?
- He drives me crazy.
- What are you doing?
Did you tell me it's incorrect?
- Ji Hyo.
- Yeon Seok,
- Buzz, "Coward".
- Is it me?
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
Yeon Seok, Buzz, "Coward".
- Incorrect.
- Is it wrong?
Let's listen to the song a bit more.
It's "Coward".
Maybe it isn't Yeon Seok.
- It's a song by Buzz.
- That's right.
Yes.
(Everyone sings along naturally.)
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo, Buzz, "Thorn".
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
Kwang Soo, Buzz, "Thorn".
It's correct, isn't it?
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
- I tried that answer.
- Jae Suk tried that answer.
Is it "Thorn"?
- He gave the exact same answer.
- Se Chan, did you try "Thorn"?
I tried "Thorn".
(This song is...)
("Thorn" by Buzz
which was released in 2005.)
(Every man must have copied
Min Kyung Hoon's head voice.)
The right combination
hasn't come up yet.
- Really?
- Let me answer.
- Jong Kook, Buzz, "Thorn".
- No.
- Incorrect.
- Yeon Seok, Buzz, "Thorn".
- Let me answer.
Yeon Seok, Buzz, "Coward".
- Incorrect.
- It isn't "Coward".
Maybe it isn't "Coward" or "Thorn".
- Isn't it "Thorn"?
- "Thorn".
- Is it a song by Buzz?
- Let me answer.
- Jae Suk.
- Is it "Thorn"?
- Yeon Seok.
- So Min, Buzz, "Thorn".
- Correct.
- What?
- No one said it.
- Didn't someone say my name?
No one said it
with Buzz and "Thorn".
Did no one say
"Se Chan, Buzz, 'Thorn'"?
- Didn't you say it?
- I thought I did.
- "Thorn".
- I thought it was "Coward".
"Thorn".
(Suk Jin is singing "Coward".)
(This is the answer.)
(They loudly sing the song
everyone sang at the karaoke.)
- Next question, cue.
- Okay.
- I will answer it.
- Let me answer.
- 3, 2.
- Teo.
Teo, Uhm Jung Hwa, "Pupil".
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
Ji Hyo, Uhm Jung Hwa, "Poison".
- Incorrect.
- Yeon Seok, Uhm Jung Hwa, "Poison".
Incorrect.
Let's listen to it some more.
It isn't "Poison".
All right.
- Let me answer.
- I figured it out!
Yeon Hee! Yeon Hee!
- BoA.
- "Atlantis Princess".
"Atlantis Princess".
- Incorrect.
- It is a song by BoA.
- Sooyoung!
- All right.
Yeon Seok, BoA, "Atlantis Princess".
- Correct!
- Yes!
(Nice!)
She pronounced it strangely.
- No, I didn't.
- She said "Tiramisu Princess".
- "Tiramisu Princess".
Sooyoung, say the answer clearly.
- Atlantis.
- "Atlantis Princess".
- I was so close.
- It gets confusing.
- I know.
- She got it right.
- "Atlantis Princess".
(Yeon Seok was 20 years old
in 2003.)
(The star of Asia,
BoA released this masterpiece.)
- We will have two more questions.
- Okay.
- Yeon Seok, answer one.
- Let's go.
- Look at Yeon Seok.
- I will answer.
- Yeon Seok, concentrate!
Don't look outside the window.
Figure out who was 20 years old.
Song title and singer too.
Let's go.
(Let me answer.)
Let me answer.
god, "Lies"... Hold on.
Who was 20 years old then?
- 3, 2...
- So Min.
- Incorrect.
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo, god, "Lies".
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
Yeon Seok, god, "Lies".
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
- So Min.
- Ji Hyo, god, "Lies".
- Correct.
- It was Ji Hyo.
(Was it me?)
Really?
- Was it me?
- "Lies" came out a long time ago.
(The song made god
the national idol group...)
(and made everyone sing,
"Goodbye, don't go.")
They were young back then.
- I had no idea.
- god.
- Now comes the last question.
- Okay.
That was close.
- Yeon Seok, get it right.
- Yeon Seok,
just yell, "Let me answer."
- Yeon Seok, help out your team.
- Okay.
Let's go. Music, cue.
(The last song plays.)
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
- The answer is...
3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer.
Hold on. Yeon Hee should go first.
Kwang Soo,
Kim Hyun Jung, "Bruise".
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
- Yeon Seok.
- Hold on.
- Let me answer.
- "Bruise"?
- Kim Hyun Jung...
Hold on. Yeon Seok said it first.
- Yeon Seok.
- Okay.
Jong Kook, Kim Hyun Jung,
- "Bruise".
- Incorrect.
- Let me answer.
- What?
Jong Kook.
I will play it again.
- What is it?
- It sounds familiar.
I can't hear it.
- "Farewell Again".
- Let me answer.
- What?
- I think it's "Tears".
- Jong Kook.
- That isn't it.
- R.ef...
- 3, 2, 1.
- He only knows his songs.
- Incorrect.
- It goes like this.
(The song has a familiar melody.)
Listen to the lyrics.
How do the lyrics go?
It's an old song.
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
- Haha, Kim Hyun Jung,
- Go ahead.
(Haha, Kim Hyun Jung)
- "Breaking up Alone".
- Incorrect.
The lyrics contained the title.
- Sooyoung.
- Go ahead.
Who was it? Haha, Kim Hyun Jung,
"Breakup with Her".
- Correct!
- That's right. "Breakup with Her"!
(Correct!)
(She succeeded to get
the last question right.)
That's right.
- "Breakup with Her".
- We were so close.
We messed up from the start.
- It was Haha.
- It was me.
- "Breakup with Her".
- That's right.
(People who could hit high notes
attempted to sing this song.)
(The song with high notes in which
her belting cleansed the eardrums)
"It was my fault."
That's the song, right?
"I didn't forget."
- Everyone...
- Here is the result.
- Team Sooyoung took first place.
- Yes!
- Did they take first place again?
- We got many questions right.
Team Yeon Seok took 2nd place
with 2 questions right.
- Okay!
The other two teams
are at the bottom.
We will give
500, 300, and 100 points.
- Okay, okay.
- In that case,
- we won points.
- Do we have plus 100 points now?
Is there a game that uses the body?
The next mission uses the body.
Before we begin the last mission,
I will announce the current points.
In first place is Team Sooyoung
with plus 100 points.
- Plus?
- They placed first in both games.
They placed first in both games.
- Every member is good at games.
- Yes.
Team Yeon Hee, minus 300 points.
Team Teo, minus 800 points.
- Are we still in the last place?
- Team Yeon Seok,
minus 1,100 points.
- But we...
- We...
- We received points.
- The current score reflects that.
Are we still in the last place?
- I mean...
- From minus 1,400 points...
(Why are we still in the last place
when we worked so hard?)
Why are we still in the last place
when we worked so hard?
Do you guys keep receiving
minus points?
- I don't know.
- The thing is, Yeon Seok...
- isn't contributing at all.
- Seriously.
(The thing is, Yeon Seok
isn't contributing at all.)
Seriously.
We started at minus 900 points.
You should have written down
more merits.
Yeon Seok really is bad at games.
- You are right.
- He is the worst.
- I wasn't going to complain, but...
- He is suited for variety shows.
If Yeon Seok ages well,
he will become Suk Jin.
- That's right.
- He hates it.
- Yeon Seok hates it.
- He is devastated.
- He hates it.
- It's true, Yeon Seok.
Suk Jin loves games,
but he is bad at them.
Oh, no.
"Oh, no."
I am sorry, Suk Jin.
I mean...
- Suk Jin became sullen for real.
- It's okay.
He became sullen for real.
It's just that I want to be
at games.
Suk Jin met the right team.
He didn't do anything,
but his teammates saved him.
Yeon Hee was really good.
Yeon Hee played diligently.
- I didn't know she was so cheerful.
- Seriously.
- She is competitive too.
- My throat hurts.
The last mission...
is the Push and Pull Car Racer
for 2021.
(Push and Pull Car Racer)
While wearing a blindfold,
you will come down a slope in a car.
You succeed...
if you step on the brake
and stop the car...
as close as you can to the edge.
(A success)
Before you go,
you can bet points.
- Your points?
- Yes.
Let's say you bet 100 points.
It can become minus 200,
minus 100 points, etc.
You can win up to
five times the points.
No matter how many points you bet,
we will give you 300 points
if you fall into starch.
We win 300 points
if we fall into starch.
You can press the brake only once.
(You can press the brake only once.)
Teammates can yell, "Stop."
(Teammates can yell, "Stop.")
The 1st and 2nd teams
that get 2,020 points will win.
If no team gets 2,020 points...
even after the fourth round,
the final scores
will determine the rankings.
- This is our only chance.
- Okay, okay.
- Let's go.
The first player of each team
should go up.
(The 1st player of each team
on standby)
Be careful.
(The king of curiosity
checks out the cart.)
- It doesn't fit.
- I see.
(He gets on the cart.)
You can't practice.
You can't do it.
- Why are you practicing?
- Catch him.
(He goes down the slope.)
(Flustered)
- Stop.
- No, no.
- Jae Suk, stop.
- Catch him.
- He is at the bottom.
- Why are you practicing?
(He fails to hit the brake.)
- What are you doing?
(He falls off the edge.)
(He went down unexpectedly
and dove into the starch.)
- What was that?
- Why is he so flippant?
What was that?
Hey, hey.
I wasn't going to go down.
You are so mischievous.
He always breaks the rules.
He is a comedian
through and through.
- It wasn't intentional.
- He is the best.
- Gosh.
I will go fourth.
Once it speeds it...
It takes time for the cart to stop.
Let's go!
So Min, tell us
how many points you will bet.
How many points will you bet?
Do I choose?
Bet 1,000 points.
Shall I add 1,000 more points
to that?
(She bets like
there is no tomorrow.)
Get a hold of yourself, So Min.
- Put on a blindfold.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
(She could win 5,000 points
or lose 2,000 points.)
I am so scared. Hold on.
Push gently.
- Let's go.
- Push gently.
I'm pushing.
- So Min, are you ready?
- Okay.
(How will she do?)
Not yet. Not yet. Not yet.
(It's a tense moment.)
It won't go down.
- Did you hit the brake?
- I didn't.
- Hold on, hold on.
- Oh, no. So Min.
So Min, press it!
(Kwang Soo pushes the cart.)
- Hold on, hold on.
- Oh, no. So Min.
- So Min, press it!
- Stop!
(Despite her teammates' cries,)
(she lands in starch.)
- Hey!
- She should have pressed...
- the brake.
- You jerk!
- It's your fault!
- The cart had stopped.
I only helped her.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- I only helped her.
- This is hilarious.
I only helped her.
So Min, are you okay?
So Min, it's a ski resort.
- Are you okay?
- So Min, it's a ski resort.
Kwang Soo.
(Sneezing)
Who pushed me?
- Kwang Soo.
- It wasn't like that.
It wasn't like that.
The cart had come to a full stop.
- Fine.
- I had to help.
- Kwang Soo.
- Let's go.
Kwang Soo, how many points
will you bet?
- I will bet 1,000 points.
- Okay.
Okay. 1,000 points.
Kwang Soo, we will tell you
when to stop.
- Where should he stop?
- Hold on.
Shall we tell him to stop at the
"multiply by minus one" mark?
Let's tell him to stop
at the "multiply by zero" mark.
1,000 points.
I am in the right position, right?
Okay.
- Let's go.
- I am in the right position, right?
- Yes.
- Am I...
(Kwang Soo sets off with hopes
to escape from the minus points!)
- Stop!
(Will Kwang Soo be able
to stop in time?)
(He crashes into starch!)
(He fiddled with the brake
belatedly...)
(and crashed.)
Is this how it's done?
- No one is succeeding to stop.
- Hey.
- Did you run a simulation?
- Yes.
Were you able to stop?
We were able to stop.
- I don't think the brake works.
- The teammates should help.
You know...
The teammates should help.
He flew off like KTX.
It's impossible to stop.
I don't think the brake works.
- Shall we give a demonstration?
- Yes.
Why would you give a demonstration
at this point?
- You should have done it sooner.
- You are done.
(He gets angry with a pale face.)
(They put the cart back in place
for demonstration.)
Suk Jin, help me with this.
Don't just leave.
Carry this with me.
- We will give a demonstration.
- Okay.
Let's see a demonstration.
(The representative
of the production crew comes up.)
- Try it.
- Okay.
Try it with this cart.
(He checks the brake expertly.)
(The simulation team
has gone through countless games.)
Stop before you go off the edge.
(To make a safe and fun game,)
(the best driver has ridden the cart
dozens of times.)
(The ace member sets off
to quell their complaints.)
Let's see it.
Will he succeed?
Come on. Come on!
(He stops the cart in less than 1m.)
Hey!
(He should be embarrassed
about the distance.)
Hey!
Why did you send a coward?
He is a coward!
He didn't even go halfway down.
- He is a coward!
- This is impossible.
Even a staff member can't do it.
(Being under pressure made him stop
as soon as he began.)
(A moment ago,)
(the simulation team could stop
as they wanted.)
(Proud)
- Let's go.
- Let's bet 1,000 points.
1,000 points. He is confident.
1,000 points.
- Here we go.
- Stop him.
(The cart moves
before he gets into position.)
Stop, stop.
Hey.
What was that?
(He pressed the brake
as hard as he could.)
(He got thrown into starch.)
This game is no fun.
(The flippant man had it coming.)
- Hey!
- The brake is broken!
He pressed it early on,
but it didn't stop!
- Hey!
- The brake is broken!
- He pressed it right away.
- It doesn't work!
He pressed it right away,
but it didn't stop!
What is this nonsense?
Listen.
After it speeds up,
it should be halted
halfway down the slope.
Why are you running a simulation
with us?
- Why?
- We tried it many times.
Can we take off our blindfolds?
We did wear blindfolds, but...
- Let's start over...
- From the next round,
- without the blindfolds.
- we will take out the blindfolds.
- All right.
- Teo is determined.
He studied everyone carefully.
He is serious.
Jong Kook tends to succeed
when he plays games like this.
I bet Jong Kook will succeed.
(He checks the cart.)
How many points will you bet?
- Bet 1,000 points. 1,000 points.
- 1,000 points.
- 1,000 points?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- 1,000 points.
- I will push you.
- Okay.
(He refuses to be covered in
what isn't even protein powder.)
(The protein monster sets off
with determination!)
(Screeching)
What?
(After 2.5m,)
(the cart stops.)
- "Multiply by minus two".
- Okay.
- Yes!
- "Multiply by minus two".
- Minus 2,000 points.
(Team Sooyoung loses 2,000 points.)
- It works!
- "Multiply by minus two".
- The brake works well!
(The protein monster gets angry
when he is embarrassed.)
- Nice!
- Okay!
- Minus 2,000 points.
(The cart halted quickly
because he used his muscles.)
- Okay. This cart stops well.
- They are at the bottom now.
- Listen.
We could wear blindfolds.
The brake works well.
- Minus 2,000 points.
- We could wear blindfolds.
We could wear blindfolds.
The brake works well.
It's a party!
Jong Kook, you are a coward.
Had you gone off the edge,
you would have gotten 300 points.
The cart moved this much
when the others hit the brake.
- So I did it early on.
- Jong Kook, it was fun.
- The sound was so petty.
- It was fun.
It was fun.
Yeon Seok, you saw how it's done.
Hit the brake around here.
- Let's go.
- My goodness.
- Wear the helmet.
- Yeon Seok, you must do this.
Okay. 2,000 points.
I won't play around this time.
- I will do it with seriousness.
- Yeon Seok.
- You failed all day, okay?
- Succeed just this once.
- Show us your cool side.
- Okay.
We don't know
what the penalty will be.
(I won't fail anymore!)
Even if you stop at yellow,
we will be set.
Okay.
I will succeed.
- I will put an end to failures.
- Okay.
(He gives his words of resolution.)
I will put an end to failures.
Hold on. No!
What is he doing?
- What is he doing?
- No one pushed him.
(No one pushed him.)
(What is he doing?)
What is he doing? What is he doing?
(After an unimpressive ride,
he falls in a fancy way.)
- What is he doing?
- What was that?
- What is up with him?
- What are you doing?
- You're talking nonsense.
- Hey...
What is wrong with him?
Why did you look back
when no one pushed you?
- What is wrong with him?
- Did you see a ghost?
- Gosh.
- What is wrong with him?
- What did he do?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- What is wrong with him?
- I thought someone pushed me.
Who would push you?
- Who would push you?
- There was no one behind you.
- I just...
- No one paid attention to you.
(He only ended up
extending his life.)
I thought Jong Kook pushed me.
(Failing Yeon Seok became
covered in starch.)
That was so funny, Yeon Seok.
Yeon Seok, it's okay
since you were funny.
- Gosh.
- It's okay since you were funny.
It's better to brush it hard.
(Lee Kwang Soo, Starch expert,
It's better to brush it hard.)
I brushed hard to brush
the starch off.
(I'll also brush it off you then.)
What are you doing?
(Altruistic cheek-slapping...)
(where the slappers are dying
to brush off the starch)
That's heartwarming.
The year-end is so heartwarming.
- Yes.
- You can help each other out.
- That's right.
- Our company is running...
so darn well.
Yes, your company is really...
(Heartwarming)
Our company is running
so darn well.
(The two starch King Kongs are
showing off a special friendship.)
- Hey.
- Oh, my.
(I think only good things
will happen in 2021.)
We're starting again.
- It's Teo's turn.
- Teo!
(It's Teo's turn
to bet on 1,000 points.)
- Let's go.
- You can do it.
I think he can do it
for some reason.
You only have to do it once.
It's 10,000 dollars.
There's a ghost next to Ji Hyo.
- What?
- Me?
(A 2.4m tall ghost that looks pale)
- He's just standing like that.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Why is he standing there?
He's just standing like that.
- He's scary.
- What's happening?
He's taking off.
He accepted the challenge.
Do your best.
(Teo takes off.)
(Think of the autobahn you
experienced when you were young.)
Okay, go.
- No way.
- Nice!
(It's a cowardly riding...)
(that you can't see in Germany.)
- Okay!
Nice! That's double minus points!
- What are you...
- I'm not in last place anymore!.
- He's a coward.
- Gosh.
- This is...
- Yoo Teo, "Coward" by Buzz.
Teo.
Give this to me again.
- That's it.
- It's not locked completely.
(They're trying hard
to fix the brake.)
Kwang Soo, just come out
if you can't do it.
It's going to break.
(He succeeded at once.)
- He did it.
- It's working now.
(Oh, so that's how it's done?)
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
It's over if I just press this once.
- Wait a minute.
- Just go.
What is wrong with you?
What is wrong with him?
- You need to take off quickly.
- I'm getting ready.
- During the test...
- Lean to the back.
- From here...
- No.
I'm going to go fast.
- He's going to go fast.
- I'm going to go fast.
Look. I will stop when I lock
the brake around "multiply by two".
- Will you speed?
- I will.
- He's heavy, so...
- So now...
- Let's go.
- Let go after you tell me.
(The speed helper forces
a fast take off.)
Wait, it's broken.
(Wait, it's broken!)
(He fell forward after making
a lot of noise from the brake.)
You said you would go fast.
- You...
- This is impossible.
You said you would go fast.
- I'm going to take off.
- Just go.
- Haha. Teo.
- Do your best!
I'm going to aim for 2,000 points.
- 2,000 points. Deal!
- Take it and double it.
He's voluntarily going to
the underworld.
Okay, I'll take off.
(The fate of their team depends on
the fingertips of the troublemaker.)
Good.
(Creaking)
He did it!
- It's "multiply by one".
- Okay.
(He successfully stopped
at "multiply by one".)
(The troublemaker
who always caused trouble...)
(made his teammates proud
for the first time.)
- "Multiply by one".
- I should've gone a little further.
(He gained 2,000 points
with an amazing control.)
- You were really awesome!
- I should've gone a little further.
- Yes.
You gained 2,000 points!
- I should've gone a little further.
- We could've gotten 4,000 points.
(Bitter)
- Okay, then. This team won.
- Gosh.
- We won?
- Yes.
- We won!
Yes, but we will continue until
we have a team in second place.
(Even the winners are
puzzled by the news of winning.)
(We did it!)
- What are they doing?
- I think we will be in last place.
- This is unbelievable.
- After that...
- This is incredible.
- Didn't they have any minus points?
Didn't they have any minus points?
Weren't they in last place?
(Are you sure that team is
in 1st place?)
They didn't win, did they?
(Murmuring)
They were?
- Everyone.
- Look at this.
I'm sorry.
You have 1,820 points right now.
You need 200 more points.
- Come on.
- 1,820?
(They need 200 more points to get
the winning score of 2,020 points.)
You need more points.
- 1,820 points?
- You need more points.
- Tell us why you did that.
- Hey.
The atmosphere was nice just now.
- We did ceremonies like crazy.
- You should've kept it going.
(There's an exchange of joy and
sorrow because of the reversal.)
- It's not over yet.
- We need more points.
It's not over yet.
If I just land in the starch
and receive 300 points...
- You will succeed then.
- Okay.
- Teo.
- Yes?
- Just land in the starch.
We get 300 points if we land
in there. You'll look cool.
- Just land in the starch.
- Okay.
(They start to murmur again.)
Everyone, I'm really sorry,
but you had minus 2,200 points.
That's right. They had
a lot of minus points.
So you have minus 200 points now.
- I'm sorry.
- What is he talking about?
I'm sorry.
There's still a long way to go.
Why are you causing such a fuss?
Goodness.
- I'm sorry.
- There's still a long way to go.
(The staff continues to make
embarrassing calculation mistakes.)
- I'm sorry.
- You should get beaten up first.
I'm really sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
I thought the game was over.
(He thought the game was over
because they caused such a fuss.)
Did they just reach
minus 200 points?
Are you kidding me?
- You didn't win yet.
- Gosh.
- Hey.
- We're even done doing ceremonies.
- Did you just reach minus 200?
- What are you doing?
- What is happening?
- We're even done doing ceremonies.
- Okay.
You had minus 2,200 points earlier
because of Yoo Teo.
You earned 2,000 points just now.
(His brain is in full operation.)
We bet 2,000 points though.
- So you earned that.
- And they got "multiply by one".
- You ended up with that.
- Will we get minus zero...
if we get "multiply by 0"?
No, it's just zero.
Just cut it out.
What's the difference
between 0 and 1?
Zero means that
you won't earn anything.
- We gave you 2,000 points.
- He can't even win.
- Hey.
- Haha.
Dumb Haha, just come here.
2,000 times 0 is 0.
Why do you keep complaining to him
when he's highly educated?
- He said you're highly educated.
- Why do you keep acting up?
- He will lose just like that.
- Gosh.
- He lost.
- He's returning.
I'm sorry for the confusion.
Multiplying it by zero
obviously give them zero points.
Doesn't he know how to multiply?
This is the last round.
- It's Jae Suk's turn then.
- Will Jae Suk do it?
- Me?
- We're in second place now.
How many points do we have
right now?
- Please tell us exactly.
- Aren't we in second place?
(1st, Team Yeon Hee 300,
2nd, Team Yeon Seok minus 100)
(3rd, Team Teo minus 200,
4th, Team Sooyoung minus 2,200)
I think Jae Suk will do it.
But this is...
(Jae Suk aims for 1st place
while betting 1,000 points.)
(Jae Suk has the highest record,
and it's his last try.)
We will prepare a ceremony.
Do your best.
(Will Jae Suk be able to repeat
the miracle that happened earlier?)
That's it.
Trust your instincts.
(He pushed the brake.)
- It's a minus.
It's a minus.
("Multiply by minus 1" equals to
a 1,000-point deduction.)
You're in last place then.
- Earlier...
- You're in last place.
- What happened?
- Since it's multiply by minus one.
Jae Suk.
(Now there's a possibility for them
to end up in last place.)
Seriously...
- Try pushing it in the beginning.
- Okay.
- Will you bet 2,000 points?
- Yes.
(She's in last place anyway.
She daringly bets 2,000 points.)
(If she gets "multiply by 5",
her team will end up in 1st place.)
(If she gets a minus,
her team will end up in last place.)
Sooyoung, you can do it.
Do your best, Sooyoung.
You can do it.
I think you should push the brake.
Push it.
(Sooyoung pushes the brake after
safely passing the minus zone.)
- Push it.
- Gosh.
- That's it.
Sooyoung, good job.
I pushed it.
- Good job.
- It was too late.
Why do I keep going backward?
- That's not how you do it.
- Push with one foot.
- We will push it for you.
- Hey.
No, you can't do that.
- Stop.
- What happened?
(But...)
- It's "multiply by one"!
- What?
Stop.
- What happened?
- Yes!
(She stopped for now.)
It's "multiply by zero".
(She stopped exactly in between...)
("multiply by one"
and "multiply by zero".)
- It's "multiply by zero"!
- No, it's "multiply by zero".
- Isn't it "multiply by one"?
- It's "multiply by zero".
The front wheel is
on "multiply by zero".
- I'm certain.
- It is, judging from the sideline.
- Right here.
- It's "multiply by zero".
- "Multiply by zero".
- How is this "multiply by zero"?
- It is "multiply by zero".
- The wheels...
It's based on the wheels.
Yeon Seok, just land in the starch.
Yeon Seok.
- Yeon Seok.
- Push it when you're here.
If you succeed here, you will win.
- If he succeeds?
- Yes.
(Team Yeon Hee is currently in
1st place with 300 points.)
(Team Sooyoung is currently in
last place with minus 1,900 points.)
(Team Yeon Seok can also be in
1st or last place.)
You need to go a little fast.
That's good. That look
in your eyes is good.
Okay, let the best man win.
Let the best man win.
(The last cart took off heroically.)
- This is a match.
- He keeps asking that.
- What are you doing?
Why?
- What is wrong with you?
(He set off fully determined, but he
cowardly stopped after 1m.)
- What are you doing?
- What is wrong with you?
Hey, you...
(His teammates
have finally exploded.)
- The slope isn't even that steep.
- You should've at least come here.
Hey.
- You're in last place.
- He was so serious though.
Gosh.
That's what happens
when he does it seriously.
You're showing a lot of
different sides of you today.
- This stops too easily.
- Yeon Seok.
- What is wrong with you?
- You've been doing this all day.
I told you to push it here.
- Everyone, we have the result.
- Yes.
The team in first place is...
Team Yeon Hee.
- Yes.
- Did we win?
The team in second place is
Team Teo.
(Team Teo ended up in 2nd place
by luck with minus 1,200 points.)
- This is unbelievable.
- Gosh.
3rd place and 4th place have
a 200-point difference.
200 points?
Then we still have a chance.
- I think we're in last place.
- That was so close though.
(With a 200-point difference,
4th place will receive the penalty.)
Okay, third place is...
Third place...
(3rd place will avoid the penalty
with a 200-point difference.)
It can't be...
Third place...
- Team Sooyoung.
- Wow!
Fourth place is Team Yeon Seok.
(3rd place Team Sooyoung,
Last place Team Yeon Seok)
(These three men will receive
the penalty.)
Why would you make us expectant?
Yoo Yeon Seok...
- He made them lose at one go.
- Hey.
Yeon Seok did everything today.
Was the game turned around
because of Yeon Seok?
- Really?
- Yes, with "multiply by minus two".
That's incredible.
It's our first time having a guest
ruin their team like this.
- I'm serious.
- He's terrible at games.
I've never seen anyone
this terrible at games.
He's really...
He even beat
Kwang Soo and Se Chan.
- This is driving me crazy.
- He really...
For the teams
in 1st place and 2nd place,
we will give you gift certificates
to use at traditional markets...
worth 1,000 dollars
as a new year's gift.
- I can't believe it.
- You can share them now.
- Take these.
- 1,000 dollars?
- Yes.
- That's nice.
They're traditional market
gift certificates.
It's my 1st time being in 1st place.
You can use this like cash.
- This is like cash.
- Okay.
Divide them among yourselves.
What is the penalty for today
and who is in the last place?
The penalty is...
for you to get rid of the old grime
of 2020...
and have a fresh start in 2021.
You will make a copy of your face
by applying ink on your face.
- Yes, that's good.
- What are you talking about?
- Bring in the materials.
- This is the worst.
You must apply it completely.
You forgot his nose.
Apply more on the lips.
- Gosh.
- It's really...
You really look like a fish.
- It turned out well.
- What is that?
- Do it for Kwang Soo too.
- It turned out well.
- Right now...
- Do it now.
- Should I press it?
- It really looks...
(They even completed Yeon Seok's
copy that's unique for some reason.)
2021 is the Year of the Ox.
We will see you then.
- It's the Year of the Ox.
- Yes, it is.
See you next year. Thank you.
- Thank you
- Thank you.
(Life always...)
(makes you stand in front of
a crossroad of choices.)
(Just die if you're scared.)
(We have a good chance right now,
so we should just continue.)
(Let's start the game now.)
Okay, lock the door.
(The new year, 2021)
(President candidate 1,
Carlos, Ex-president)
(President candidate 2,
Grand Award winner)
(President candidate 3,
Yang Kka Chi)
(President candidate 4,
Year of the Ox, Lee Ribeye)
(President candidate 5,
Senior Hoodwinker)
(President candidate 6, Sally)
(President candidate 7,
Song Jeoktoma)
(President candidate 8, Petty Thief)
(Variety Show Hoodwinkers,
The Return of Gamblers)
(It's the final match
among hoodwinkers...)
(who only know about going all in.)
(They can only depend on
luck and power.)
(The world of experts...)
(became more desperate
and venomous.)
(You're going bankrupt.)
(You're going to end up
on the streets.)
(Breaking news, "Bankrupt
Hoodwinker Ji Rolling in Snow")
(Did the bare hoodwinkers
even visit a pawnshop?)
(The war among gamblers, who have
nowhere to go, will start.)
(2021 Hoodwinker Association
New Year's Party)
(The Return of Gamblers)