(One sunny day,
in a building in Seoul)
- Hello.
- Do you want to be rich?
Yes, I do.
(There's a round table
with 8 seats.)
I love the theme.
Asura balbalta.
(Gambling Rules)
Double or nothing.
- Be quiet.
- Hello.
- What's today's theme?
- Why is it so dark?
- We're going in there?
- You're going to be like that?
- This...
- Okay.
(Amazed)
Is this how we're going to start?
It's been a while.
- A round table.
- "Gambling Rules".
- So we're going to play a game?
- Hey, look at this.
"No violence
under any circumstances."
- Asura balbalta.
- How can you gamble...
- without any violence?
- What is this?
What is this?
"All alliances and strategies
allowed".
I have a feeling
something huge is going to happen.
(Card sharks from all over
the country are gathered.)
- Double or nothing!
- What is this?
Asura balbalta.
- What's he saying?
- Hey, that's...
Do you want to be rich?
Are you singer Kim Jeong Soo?
- I'm Corporal Pyeong.
- In my...
(In my arms)
Ji Hyo.
- Do you know what today's theme is?
- Exactly.
That's Lee Young Ae.
- That's "Lady Vengeance".
- No.
I'm Madam Song
who went to Ewha Womans University.
Does Madam Song dress that way?
- She doesn't.
- Mind your own business.
- Is Madam Song Kim Hye Soo?
Yes.
Who are you trying to be?
I'm T.O.P.
That's just a shirt he has.
- Hey.
- It's his shirt.
- This is a Hawaiian shirt.
Aren't you just wearing something
you recently bought?
It's a Hawaiian shirt.
- From "Tazza: The Hidden Card".
- It's not a Hawaiian shirt.
- It's just a shirt for the opening.
- What?
No, it isn't.
You look like a realtor...
in my neighborhood from head to toe.
Hey, look at this.
I don't usually wear this.
In that shirt, Jong Kook looks like
Trainer Yang.
Isn't he dressed like a real thug?
- Yes.
- That's right.
A thug, a delinquent,
- Kka Chi.
- and a stooge.
A stooge?
He definitely looks like a stooge.
- Are you just an old student?
- I'm...
- Someone who is studying...
- Hey, why are you...
- Are you yourself?
- I'm myself.
Try to get into character.
I'm myself.
- You're yourself.
- He looks kind whatever he wears.
- Right.
- Why does he look so kind?
- Right?
- I'm myself.
- Your outfit is the most proper.
- Yes.
- I'm dressed like Corporal Pyeong.
- Right.
- It suits you.
- I heard the theme is "Tazza".
By the way, you got dissed
on "Comedy Big League".
That you can't paint the big picture
on "Running Man".
(On "Comedy Big League" recently)
(But you can't seem to paint
the big picture alone...)
(on Running Man either.)
(Embarrassed)
(Hey, do you think
weekend variety shows are easy?)
They said I can't paint the big
picture alone on Running Man.
- That was so accurate.
- I know.
- Right.
- I should get back at him.
Ji Hyo's movie, "Intruder"...
- I can't watch it. It's too scary.
- Is it fun?
- Ji Hyo did an amazing job.
- She did?
But this wasn't the best time
for a movie release.
- I know.
- Exactly.
- Still,
- All her movies were successful.
it attracted more than
a million viewers, right?
It didn't.
Suk Jin, don't bring that up.
- It was number one.
- In times like this...
- Hey.
- What's with you?
It will soon.
- It's over. It's not in theaters.
- It's over.
- It's on IPTV now.
- It's on IPTV?
- Yes.
Are you having a good day
or a bad day?
It's either very good or very bad.
What is it?
- You're the worst.
- It's very bad.
I'm just having fun.
Ji Hyo, I paid 11 dollars
for the movie.
Thank you.
- My wife did too.
- Really?
- Thank you.
- I didn't watch it though.
I feel comforted.
- I was upset about...
- I'll wait until it's five dollars.
- Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- Spend some more.
- That's so you.
You're unbelievable.
- Jong Kook.
- He'll wait for a lower price.
Can't you spend that much
for your colleague?
I rarely watch movies
that cost more than 10 dollars.
Just pay 11 dollars.
- You're sweating so much.
- What?
- Are you okay? You're sweaty.
- It's not sweat.
- He just has greasy skin.
- It's sunscreen.
- He has greasy skin.
I don't wear any makeup
other than sunscreen.
Still, your skin looks so healthy.
- Okay.
- He's going at it again.
(Suk Jin is going at it again.)
- Please show us this once.
- He never misses an opportunity.
Please start a conversation
successfully for once.
- Show us what you can do.
- I can't do anything more.
I gave it a try,
but there's no chance.
- It got cut off?
- Yes.
He picked a fight
by saying I have greasy skin.
I did.
- But it didn't offend him at all.
- Please start a conversation.
He couldn't be bothered.
I picked a fight
by saying he has greasy skin,
but it didn't offend him,
so it ended there.
- Of course.
- Look how Jong Kook is sitting.
It means he'll let most things pass.
- But if he goes, "Oh, really?"
- Exactly.
- Right.
- That's right.
- That means he's more engaged.
- "Oh, really?"
- Exactly.
(He always says, "Oh, really?")
"Oh, really?"
(It means he's ready to talk.)
- That's right.
- Exactly.
- That's how I should look.
- Of course.
- That's right.
If I'm sitting like this,
it means I'll let everything pass.
- I can see there's space.
- Yes.
(After 10 years, he finally gets
Jong Kook's signals.)
- Everyone.
- Yes.
You're variety show sharks
from all over the country.
(Variety show sharks from all over
the country are gathered.)
Variety show sharks.
You'll compete in...
War of Sharks.
- War of Sharks.
- We're variety show sharks.
Your currency today is caramels.
- Caramels?
- Yes.
- Caramels.
- The number of caramels...
you have at the end...
will have a huge impact
on tomorrow's shoot.
- Tomorrow's shoot?
It affects next week's episode?
Gosh.
First, you'll be given
10 caramels each.
- Can I eat them?
- Then you lose them.
They're distributed
by a real dealer.
These are tasty.
- I know.
- They're made in the US.
- I want to eat them.
- Me too.
- Thank you.
- I want to eat just one.
I'll save them.
- They're your money today.
- Okay.
Before we start the mission,
you'll elect a chairman.
- A chairman?
- A chairman.
- A chairman has the right...
to decide the mission order
and teams.
- That's huge.
- Really?
There will be a total
of two elections today.
Anyone can run for election,
and all candidates are given
30 bills...
for their campaign funds.
They're given what?
- Bills.
- 30 bills?
The candidates can then
issue their bills...
to win votes.
Each voter is given three ballots.
- Three ballots?
- Really?
That's a lot.
Voters are allowed...
to receive bills from any candidate.
But only the bills
from the winner...
will be exchanged for caramels.
If the candidate
that I support loses,
- Things get complicated.
- I get no caramels, right?
That's right.
- Suk Jin...
- We should support them.
The bills...
that the winner has left
will be exchanged...
for caramels as well.
So think before you hand out bills.
Gosh, that's...
Each candidate is given 30 bills,
which they can use
as their campaign funds.
I want to be a voter.
I'm not very interested in having...
- a high position.
- Really?
If you support me...
(Intrigued)
If you support me, I want to try.
Are you getting interested?
Are you? I think you are.
I bet Suk Jin wants to participate.
- Right.
- My goodness.
I'll support you.
Are you going to run or not?
- Me? I will.
- Yes.
(Of course.)
Just get out of this place.
- What are you going to do?
- I want to run.
How can you say that
without any support?
I want to run.
I'll give each of you
a caramel now.
- Right now?
- Yes.
- Your caramels?
- If you promise you'll support me.
- Promise me.
- I'll support you.
- I'll support you too.
- Who's going to support me?
- Me.
- I'll support you.
- I'll support you too.
- Who's going to support me?
- Me.
(Everyone promises him support.)
I give up.
- Why?
- I give up.
- You all look so mischievous.
- What is this?
- No.
- You look so mischievous.
- What is this?
- You're going to play me.
- No.
- The look in your eyes...
How can you trample on
our genuine support?
You guys all look so mischievous.
I give up.
I want to run for election.
- Suk Jin wants to run.
- Yes.
- Suk Jin.
- I'll run.
The two of us...
I'll run too.
My opponents look pretty easy,
- so I want to run too.
- Hey!
- Are you sure?
- I'll be fair.
- I promise.
- Okay, good.
- It's the 3 of us.
- That's it.
- Okay.
Bills, please.
No more candidates?
All right. If you support me,
- Hey.
- I'll give you five bills.
- Right now...
- Really?
- Excluding the other candidates.
- Okay.
- Five is enough.
- I promise...
I'll divide my bills
among my supporters equally...
and give everyone one more each.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Why? Then what will you have?
- There are 30, right?
(The generous promise
sways the voters.)
If I promise I'll divide
my bills equally,
- who wants to support me?
- Cut it out.
- Just sit down.
- No way.
- Forget it.
- Don't be ridiculous.
I won't support you
even if you give me all your bills.
No. Convince me...
- that you'll divide them equally.
- Even if you give me everything.
- I have to give you first anyway...
- How...
- Okay.
- We take a vote afterward.
- Yes?
- Ji Hyo, if you're not running,
please support me.
I'll divide my bills equally.
Then give me a down payment.
- That's smart.
- She sure is a shark.
That's how you should play.
Ji Hyo will keep her word.
- I always keep my word.
- But...
I'll write your name.
- 30 bills?
- Yes.
This is only the beginning.
I wouldn't be...
- so reckless.
- Kwang Soo, if I support you...
Give me a caramel,
and I'll give you three votes.
- What do you say?
- I...
Two...
- I'll vote straightforwardly.
- Are you serious?
You're really giving me this?
- Gosh, then I'll vote for you.
- What is this?
I have to.
- He gave this to you?
- Yes.
- Really?
- I'll vote for you.
Kwang Soo, look at this.
I wrote, "Lee Kwang Soo". This is...
Put a caramel in this box,
and I'll vote for you.
Put a caramel in here,
and I'll vote for you right away.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
- I have no choice.
- Kwang Soo.
- I'm not that reckless.
- Let me tell you...
- Give me.
- I'll give you three bills each.
- What?
- Really?
- Three bills each.
- I'll give you three each.
- Kwang Soo.
- He's going all-in for us.
- I'm serious.
- He's going all-in.
- I'll give you three each.
- I count on the three of you.
- This is...
How many?
- I'll give you 3.
- 3?
- I'll give you 4 each.
- 4 each.
- I'll give you four each.
- Give us right away.
- Four.
- They're giving away so much.
- They're giving away all they have.
- So Min, you get four too.
- Okay, thank you.
- All right.
- Then I'll change my vote.
- Give me something.
Can you change your vote?
- Give me something, and I'll...
- What can I do?
- vote for you right away.
- I'll give you four, Jong Kook.
- I mean...
- I'll vote for you right away.
(The voters keep changing
their minds.)
(Jae Suk gives Jong Kook 4 bills.)
- You should give me right away.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- How many are they?
- Four? All right. Here.
- Okay.
I'll give you five.
I can't believe this.
- I give you five.
- You're broad-minded.
I will keep my eye
only on the three smart voters.
Here. Five.
Let me check them.
Suk Jin, you can't treat
Se Chan and me as equals.
"As equals"?
- Excuse me.
- What do you think you're doing?
- I have no money.
- I'm the VVIP.
- I still have two ballots.
- You're being stingy.
You can't treat me like him.
- Here.
- Okay.
I almost went into a sulk.
Suk Jin. Suk Jin?
- Here. They are seven.
- Well done.
- Okay.
- Did you get seven bills already?
Gosh, I might go bankrupt.
It's done. Good.
- Done.
- I've made up my mind.
Guys, I will keep my promise.
I will keep my eye
only on the three smart voters.
I'm done. I'll put them
in the box right away.
You will get the caramels
only when I win the election.
Sure. I know.
Hey, you're good at this.
Please remember that I'm the only
one who offered real caramels.
- Yes, you did.
- I get it.
It will eventually
affect the result.
- You'll see.
- I will keep my promise.
- I will do the same.
- You should watch the situation.
These two don't even know
about the concept of bills.
The way I see it,
you should just wipe your buttocks
with them. They're useless.
- They are bills of dishonor.
- Look at him.
You can't paint a big picture.
- What are you talking about?
- You're so...
They are useless.
- Wipe my buttocks?
- Go wipe your buttocks.
I have a bidet in my place.
- Do you have a bidet?
- How dare you...
- For the ballot-counting...
- Let's make this fair.
Ji Hyo will count the ballots.
I have to become the chairman.
All right.
Okay. One vote for Yoo Jae Suk.
All right. Thank you.
- One vote for Lee Kwang Soo.
- Okay.
- Who voted for Kwang Soo?
- Can you believe it?
Did you not vote for me?
What was that?
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- There should be three votes.
- My gosh.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Oh, dear.
(Ji Suk Jin got two votes.)
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Okay!
Ji Suk Jin!
- Ji Suk Jin.
- I won't forget it.
"I won't forget it."
- Ji Suk Jin.
- My comrades.
I won't forget this.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Ji Suk Jin!
- My time has come.
- My goodness.
- I won't forget this.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- My comrades.
- Ji Suk Jin!
- Come here.
- Ji Suk Jin.
Okay. This is good.
- I hope I get a good seat.
- All right.
- Jae Suk got three votes.
- Here's the deal.
Ji Hyo got me three votes.
And So Min got Kwang Soo
three votes.
(Suk Jin is elected with 9 votes.)
Hang on. Why did you not vote
for me after getting my caramels?
- There must be some reason.
- Or So Min...
It will eventually pay off.
- So Min is nice.
- You'll see.
Suk Jin, you are
an investment genius.
Okay.
I have fewer caramels
than my voters, but I'm satisfied.
This is real money.
The first chairman is Ji Suk Jin.
- Hello.
- Ji Suk Jin!
- I will never forget this.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- Let me put this on you.
He's putting on the armband.
It stings!
I can't believe this.
(He pricks Suk Jin's arm
with a pin.)
I can't believe this. Hey!
- He tried to pin it into your skin.
- You should pin it into your skin.
I saw how Jae Suk
tried to make the pin sharp.
I won't let it happen again
in the next election.
There will be another election.
This episode
will continue next week too.
- This is disappointing.
- It went well at the last moment.
- I told you.
- We were quite determined.
I only need three smart voters.
- Chairman Jee.
- Yes?
We're living well off thanks to you.
Don't worry about
getting good seats.
Okay.
Let's begin then.
- Hang on.
- Why are you eating it?
- Why is he eating it?
- What? Are you eating mine?
2, 4, 6, 8, and 10.
2 and 4...
Hey!
(Stealing)
(While Suk Jin was enjoying
the victory,)
(Jae Suk stole his caramel.)
Come here. Hey!
Bring it back, you jerk!
How could you eat my money?
This is my money.
He's into his character.
It seemed so natural that
I didn't even know what was wrong.
Just accept it.
You owe me one. Okay?
Let's move to the first venue.
- Okay.
- It's downstairs.
(Current Number of Caramels)
You can expect to get good seats.
- Okay, Chairman.
- Thank you.
It sounds nice. I like
the world with no violence.
It's not fun since
no violence is allowed today.
- What is this?
- What's that?
- Where do we sit? Can we just sit?
- I think...
- we should sit with the team.
- We should sit together, Jong Kook.
Let's do that. Have a seat.
You can sit with anyone
whom you want to work with.
- All right.
- Have a seat.
- Haha, have a seat.
- Sir.
(Coming quickly)
Go back to your seats.
(They all are coming
to sit next to Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook, let's move
to the seats over there.
(He takes the best seat.)
You can't do this. Go back
to your seat and fight alone.
Sir.
We left your seat empty.
- Gentlemen.
- Come and have a seat.
- Have a seat here.
- Please sit.
You guys are my family.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- I'll take good care of my family.
- I won't forget about you.
- Ji Suk Jin.
If you want to enter politics,
you will need a powerful fist.
- I know that. It means a lot to me.
- Good.
You can expect a good seat.
The beginning of the game
isn't so important.
- Sure.
- Please support me next time.
Good luck with the next election.
There will be a next time.
Please support me
in the next election.
We're divided into two groups.
We should be a team again
in the next round.
We can't have another chairman.
You should run for election.
- If you do...
- You should be the next chairman.
They have more betrayers
in the team.
Exactly.
I just realized this
during the first election.
I'm not good enough
to be the chairman.
- Now you know it.
- I learned my lesson.
That's not true.
The one who's not good enough
is the current chairman.
You think?
(He's got the title
that's too good for him.)
He's become the chairman already.
(Even his supporters can't deny it.)
- Office changes manners.
- Sure.
(He can't help feeling bitter.)
Alliances and strategies are
important for the first mission.
- It's Minority Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- Minority Rock-Paper-Scissors?
The crew member will present a card
among rock, paper, or scissors.
Then each of you will
choose one card...
and open it all at the same time.
And only those who picked
the card of the minority...
will get caramels according to
the result of rock-paper-scissors.
If you beat the crew member,
you get five caramels.
If it's a tie, you get 3 caramels.
If you lose, you get 1 caramel.
But the majority will have to
return one caramel each.
- I get it.
- Okay.
We should win rock-paper-scissors
as the minority.
- Exactly.
- Here's our first card.
- Let's see.
- We're outcasts here.
Your card is scissors.
Our first card is scissors.
The majority will show rock.
- Suk Jin, let's do this.
- One of us should...
Here's my idea.
I think we should show these two.
- Okay.
- That's our plan.
- This is...
- We should blow this.
We should show this.
(Right at the moment...)
- No.
- This one.
We should show this.
- No.
- This one.
You're holding rock and scissors.
- Oh, right. You can see my card.
- What are you doing?
(The paper card is left
on his table.)
- Did you see that?
- What was that?
- Did you see it?
- My gosh.
- He's such a fool.
- When did you see it?
When did you see it?
My gosh, we ended up
in the same team.
That's too bad.
What do we do now?
(Jae Suk Gang starts to talk
about their strategies.)
We should support one person.
We should stop them
from collecting more caramels.
So you should support me.
I have six caramels now.
I think we should
play this randomly.
- You think?
- If things go wrong,
we might be hoist
with our own petard.
Do you know what I mean?
Just show any card you want.
If we come up with a wrong plan...
(Are we playing this randomly?)
Just show any card you want, okay?
Excuse me. Is there
a seat available?
(One member of Jae Suk Gang
leaves the team.)
Hang on. Aren't you a candidate?
- No. It's 4 to 4 now.
- Excuse me.
He was going to leave anyway.
- You know it, right?
- All of a sudden?
- We don't need a close game.
- Do you want to join us?
We have one seat available.
I'm not going there.
Why would I go there?
Let's just do this.
- I'll do this on my own.
- It's 4 to 4 now.
Just wait for the next round.
(Coming back)
Go away. Go over there.
The majority loses.
(The migratory bird Kwang Soo
comes back feeling small.)
Whoever wins, we can
share the caramels.
That's right.
They will mostly show rock.
- That's true.
- So we should blow it.
We should blow it and get
three caramels with scissors.
We're not playing this one time.
- Three will be enough.
- Suk Jin.
So they can't win.
Sure. It's all about
the probability.
- We all should show this?
- Yes.
We should blow it.
Otherwise, the minority will win.
- It will ruin their plan as well.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
We have to be the minority.
Please show your card
as I count to three.
Okay.
One.
(The two gangs have
different strategies.)
Two.
Three.
(Paper, paper, rock, scissors)
(Scissors, rock, rock, rock)
- Which one won?
- Hang on.
- My gosh.
- It's paper.
Those with scissors and paper
will get caramels each.
Okay!
Scissors and paper.
- Okay.
- You said you'd show scissors.
- Why did you not show scissors?
- Scissors and paper.
Those who showed scissors
get three caramels,
and those who showed paper
get one caramel each.
- It's okay.
- Is it all right?
We got one caramel.
We can do this five times.
Okay. Good.
- Did you play it randomly?
- Yes, we did.
That's our strategy.
It's confusing because
they're playing randomly.
- Let's play randomly then.
- Okay.
Let's play randomly.
We can't plan anything.
- I think we should play randomly.
- Let's do this randomly.
- We will share caramels anyway.
- Sure.
We're not sharing caramels.
- We just earn our own caramels.
- Okay.
- All right. Good.
- Let's do this.
Our second card is scissors again.
(The second card is scissors.)
Aren't you planning anything?
We're just playing it randomly.
We have no plan.
Let's just do this.
I'll show rock for sure.
I'll blow this.
Me too.
- I'll show rock.
- You know it, right?
- One.
- I should be the minority.
2, and 3.
This is it!
- Scissors.
- Is there rock?
There's no scissors.
- Scissors.
- Scissors!
- No. Wait, no.
Ji Hyo showed paper alone.
(Ji Hyo showed paper alone.)
(Ji Hyo showed paper alone
and got a caramel.)
- Paper?
- There was paper?
- That's it.
- Ji Hyo.
My goodness.
- That's it.
- There was a paper?
Ji Hyo got 1,
and everyone else lost 1.
Hey. Your throat must hurt.
(Annoyed)
- Your throat must hurt.
- I'm going to choose randomly.
I'm just going to choose randomly
without thinking about it.
- Hey, Song Ji Hyo!
- I'm...
Why are you ruining everything?
- What do you mean?
- It's not Ji Hyo's fault.
- She's just trying to survive.
- But...
- It's not about survival,
- Honestly,
- it's better than us losing...
- Yes?
because it was preplanned.
- Wait, Jong Kook.
- It would make us angrier.
Isn't he the chairman?
I am.
The chairman is trying to talk,
and you're sitting there...
- Nonetheless...
- and cutting him off.
You cut him off,
and he stopped talking immediately.
What is the role of the chairman?
That's just his name.
- His name is Chairman.
- Chairman.
- Ji Hyo. Don't put out a rock.
- Let's do this!
I'll take care of it.
Mind your business.
- Even your outfit is...
- You're...
"Lady Vengeance", aren't you?
- How dare you talk to me like that?
- I'm Madam Song,
and I graduated from
Ewha Womans University.
Did you just talk down
to the chairman?
Be quiet.
How dare you talk back to me?
(She's focused on her role.)
What are you saying?
I'm the chairman.
You're not our chairman.
I'm the chairman!
- This won't do.
- Why did you put this inside?
This won't do. Remove her seat.
Why are you removing her seat?
Because I'm the chairman.
Give it back to me. Why are you
removing someone else's chair?
- Good job, Ji Hyo.
- My goodness.
What was that sound?
My gosh. It's getting more violent.
That was good.
Ji Hyo, you did a good job.
- This was...
- Good job.
Thanks. I had an itch there.
Thanks.
Ji Hyo. You did a good job.
That was refreshing.
It sounded like
a watermelon cracking.
You didn't watch "Intruder",
did you?
You don't know how scary she is,
do you?
I didn't watch it.
I'm never going to watch it.
I'm going to save myself 11 dollars.
My gosh. He's so childish.
- He's so childish.
- I'll watch it when it's free.
Suk Jin looked so cute...
when he was embarrassed
after getting hit by Ji Hyo.
(The chairman ended his tyranny
due to his embarrassment.)
He deserved to get hit.
- Okay, the third is...
- Okay.
scissors.
We have to plan this.
We have 7 to 8 caramels...
more than that team...
- over there.
- Right.
So we should go on the defense.
Let's prevent them from
turning the tables.
We just need to prevent them
from turning the tables.
We have to prevent them from
getting a big one.
- Okay.
- What are we doing? Is it random?
- Hold on.
- Let's split it this time.
- Okay. For this round.
- Kwang Soo.
- What are we doing?
- They might try...
to get everything at the end.
Some of us should get tied
with them.
Let's do that.
- Then...
Kwang Soo and I will
get a tie with them.
(Try to get a caramel by interfering
with their plan to get a tie...)
You will put out a rock.
(and put out one different card.)
You will put out paper.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk...
- is getting competitive.
- He is.
But we figured that out.
Okay. One,
2, 3.
(The two gangs used different
strategies, who will win?)
(Scissors, paper, rock, scissors)
(Scissors, rock, paper, rock)
Song Ji Hyo and Yang Se Chan
who both put out paper.
- Okay.
It's okay. We both got one.
(Those who put out a rock
or scissors will lose 1 each.)
- Good job.
- I didn't get a single one.
I didn't get a single one.
We'll calculate everything
and hand them out.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo, please step forward.
What's with Kwang Soo?
Lee Kwang Soo got five.
- Is Kwang Soo going up?
- He needs to give away three.
I won't take one,
but give one to So Min.
- Or...
- You can give her one.
- Okay.
- Just 1? I can give her 1.
(Kwang Soo got 5 caramels.)
- He got a lot.
- He has a lot.
- That's a lot.
- Five...
- Give us one each.
- After I see how much you get.
- Let's see how many you get.
- I don't get any.
You never know.
We have our eyes on you, Kwang Soo.
We can gather our influence
and make you the chairman.
(Everyone is giving their attention
to Kwang Soo, who is rich.)
Let's get a meal together.
We could have a meal together.
That's not a hard request.
(His traitor DNA is starting
to move.)
Okay. Haha got four.
I got four, right? I knew it.
- It's because they took some away.
- That's right.
We each get one though.
We got six.
Let's leave them in the middle.
- Let's wait.
- Okay.
Jong Kook, please return two.
- Return?
Just give them two from that pile.
- Let's do that.
- Should we do that for now?
- Of course.
- We are one.
- This is nice.
It's because
we played this round together.
It's true.
- Jeon So Min, return two.
- Yes?
- What?
- Return two.
Kwang Soo.
Give them two on her behalf.
- You should do that.
- It's not that.
Give them two on her behalf.
I have the same amount as her
because I won some in this round.
- No, I...
- So Min, return one each.
- Yes, do that.
- Kwang Soo can return one,
- and you can return 1.
- Right, 1 each.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors,
and loser returns two.
Okay, sounds good.
- I like that idea.
- Those Tiger Moths.
Let's do this.
- The loser returns two.
- Okay.
- Okay. The loser returns two.
- Rock...
- Rock-paper-scissors, shoot.
- Shoot.
(Kwang Soo put out paper.)
- Rock-paper-scissors, shoot.
- Shoot.
(So Min put out...)
(What? There are two cards.)
Why would you put out two cards?
This one is in the front.
- My goodness.
- Why would you...
- put out two cards?
- No. This one is in the front.
These two are something else.
- Just put out one.
- I did this. Okay, fine. Just one.
(They re-do the match properly.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
Let me see.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
- Okay.
- Darn it.
(Throwing)
She's returning the ones she owes.
Why is she throwing a fit?
It's not that.
It's hers.
So Min, you were a bit strange
in this case.
So Min.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Don't you want...
- Chairman.
- to become chairman again?
- No, I...
Don't you want to become
the second chairman as well?
Everyone got 9 earlier,
but I only got 6.
Don't you want to become
the second chairman as well?
- Chairman.
- This isn't a comfortable position.
- You should serve a second term.
- I... This...
- You should...
- see it to the end.
- Yes, that's right.
- Hold on.
- Hey.
What do you keep eating?
What's Jae Suk eating?
- Are you eating a caramel?
- It's a caramel.
(What? He's eating a caramel?)
Wait.
Get over here.
- You!
- Is he a thief?
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Gosh, get over here.
I'm missing two.
How many did you eat?
I ate one.
(It's a segment within a segment.
It's Two-Seoks.)
2, 4, 6, 8, 10.
It tastes so good since
it's been a while since I had one.
Let's move on to the second mission.
- Yes.
- Okay!
Okay! Good.
(Current Number of Caramels,
Jong Kook 20, Se Chan 20, Haha 19)
(Ji Hyo 13, Suk Jin 13,
Jae Suk 12, Kwang Soo 12, So Min 9)
There's a soccer goalpost here.
What is this?
- Is it soccer?
Are we kicking balls
with our eyes covered?
"No violence
under any circumstances."
Something's going on. What are the
rules that card sharks must follow?
(A spoiler: This rule will be
ignored in this round.)
In this mission,
you must be able to read the
opposing team's strategy...
in order to prevent a goal
or get a goal.
It is Brain Shoot Out.
(Brain Shoot Out is where you must
read your opposing team to win.)
It is a shoot-out match where...
you will divide into 2 teams of 4
and rotate from defense to offense.
The 4 members of Team Offense
will have 4 tries to hit 10 balls.
They can choose when and how many
balls each member will hit.
Team Defense will put on
blindfolds and headphones...
and take turns as goalkeepers
for one minute each.
We have to wear blindfolds?
After one minute, the goalkeeper
will remove their headphones...
and guess whether or not
there were any goals...
and blow the whistle to
invalidate the goals.
For example,
if Team Offense got 2 or 3 goals in,
but the goalkeeper
blows the whistle,
it will become
Team Defense's goal...
- It'll be invalid.
- as you can see over there.
(If there are 2 goals and Jae Suk
blows the whistle, he gets them.)
- It's a game of wits.
- If he doesn't blow the whistle,
Team Offense gets the points.
If Team Offense didn't get
any goals, but the whistle is blown,
Team Defense must return
one caramel each.
If there were no goals and no
whistles blown, nothing happens.
However,
only 2 of the 4 goalkeepers...
can blow the whistle.
They might not make a goal
on purpose.
Okay, can the chairman come up and
divide everyone into teams of four,
so we can play the game?
- Goodness.
- He's doing his role.
He's finally doing something.
It's time for the chairman...
He finally gets to show off
his role as chairman.
He's playing his role.
I get to play my role.
- Salute.
- Chairman.
I think our family should
continue working together.
Well, I guess...
Family? Who are you talking about?
The people who supported me.
We're a family.
- They supported me.
- I'm dumbfounded.
- Don't you think so?
- That's fine.
- If it's divided like that,
we have to win at all costs.
Of course.
Are you interested in
joining my team?
I've been wanting to join.
(Politely)
(I am always thinking of you,
Chairman Jee.)
I wanted to join,
but there was no space for me.
Goodness, if that's the case...
You have a high chance of winning.
What is this?
I want to join your team.
- Will you give me a caramel then?
- Yes.
You're going to choose Jong Kook
again, right?
Of course. Join our team.
I want to see who you pick first.
- Join my team.
- I want to see who you pick first.
That means I need to get rid of
one person.
- Hold on.
- I want to see who you pick first.
First, Jong Kook is on my team.
- Jong Kook is...
- My goodness.
- Jong Kook is on my team.
He plays dirty.
Jong Kook, come here.
Suk Jin, we were on the same team,
but you're...
- Okay, fine. Haha.
- Let's go.
- Let's team up.
- Okay.
- Okay, So Min!
Will you join and give me one? Okay.
Okay, So Min!
Goodness. He's the worst.
(Chairman Jee,
A monster born out of capitalism)
- What just happened?
- Suk Jin.
Okay. I got it.
We need to get caramels.
So Min.
(Secretly)
We need to get caramels.
- Kwang Soo!
- Okay.
(Smiling)
(Through active lobbying, he's the
last to join the chairman's team.)
Gosh, this is... For this one...
- We're strong too.
- If this is the case...
- Okay.
- We have to band together.
We'll do our best.
Please support me.
I can do a good job.
- I'll do my best. Seriously.
- We need to...
- win.
- The second chairman will be...
- one of us.
- Okay.
- No matter what.
- The second chairman will be...
- one of us.
- Okay.
- We are at an advantage because...
- This is psychological warfare.
the two members who play tricks
are here.
You're right.
We have the two members who
always play tricks on our team.
- We have to do a good job.
- That's right.
- Because we have these two,
the opposing team
will have a headache.
That's right.
Is this how it is?
Let's make Suk Jin regret it.
We'll go on the offense first.
We'll go first.
- I'll block it.
- Okay.
(The first keeper for Jae Suk Gang
is Jae Suk.)
Who's going first?
(There will be 2 rounds,)
(and the score after Round 2 will be
how many caramels they receive.)
They might put in all the balls
at the beginning.
I think that's what they'll do.
I think we have to go with our gut.
We can't tell you either.
Right. There's nothing we can do.
Let's score some goals
in the beginning.
How about four goals
in the first round?
So we divide it into two tries.
- Let's do that.
- Do five.
Okay.
- This is nice.
- We have to put on blindfolds too.
(Jae Suk is ready
with his eyes and ears covered.)
You will have 1 minute in
round 1 of the 1st half.
We will start now.
Turn on the music.
(The first attack will start now.)
This.
Let's divide it into two turns.
(How many goals will Suk Jin Gang
make in the first attack?)
- Should I go now?
- We have to decide...
whether or not to do it.
(Hitting)
(What just happened?)
(Thump)
(Wait...)
- Suk Jin, seriously?
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- Kwang Soo.
- What...
- Where did you aim for?
- I...
- Seriously?
- Kwang Soo, come on.
I know Jae Suk
already has two kids,
but you never know.
(Hold on.)
Why don't we split it
into two rounds?
(She's going after the caramels.)
(While others
are focused on the game,)
(So Min tries
to break the rules again.)
(She holds her breath
as she keeps at it.)
(She manages to steal one.)
(She's surprised
at how good she is.)
(Jae Suk's clueless.)
No way.
(Sweet additional income)
(She makes her way
over to him again.)
(My hip sack...)
(Why is it open?)
(So Min manages
to steal two caramels.)
(Kwang Soo wants in on the profit,)
(so he tries to steal some too.)
(Groping)
(Darn you!)
(Just hand them over!)
(The first act of violence occurs.)
Hold still.
(What's going on?)
(Blinded by greed,)
(Kwang Soo breaks the rules.)
Five seconds.
4, 3, 2, 1.
(Their 1 minute is over.)
No way.
Jae Suk, you're up.
(If Jae Suk blows the whistle,)
(his team will win 4 points.)
One,
two...
(If he doesn't blow the whistle,)
(Team Offense will win 4 points.)
(The whistle can only be
blown twice, so what will it be?)
Three!
(The whistle can only be
blown twice, so what will it be?)
Three!
(He blew the whistle.)
(Jae Suk's hunch was right,
and he wins four goals!)
Jae Suk, you won four goals.
That's four.
(Suk Jin Gang 0, Jae Suk Gang 4)
See? They kicked four in.
- Didn't I do well?
- You did.
I didn't think
he'd blow the whistle.
This is the most important round.
This has turned into a mind game.
Who'll go next?
- Ji Hyo, go ahead.
- Ji Hyo, you're up.
It can be no one else.
We have another chance anyway.
Is it you?
- Is it Ji Hyo?
- Really?
Let's think of how she is.
- I can't read her.
- She's not readable.
- Not at all.
- Ji Hyo's a wild card.
I can't tell how she'll react.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Nice.
- Are you taking a nap?
- What are you doing?
(Is she taking a nap
or blocking the goal?)
Your minute begins now.
(Their minute begins.)
(Dragging)
(Instead of playing mind games,
they drag her away.)
(However...)
I can't believe
you found your way back.
Did you see that? She made it back.
She's back where she started.
How can she get to her spot?
Can she see?
(Relaxed)
She might be able to see.
Maybe not.
Three,
2, 1.
Please finalize your decision.
Are you done?
Wait...
(She gets rid of a ball
by tossing and turning.)
(Kwang Soo's truly flustered.)
- She kicked one out.
- It's over. This doesn't count.
(Only 2 balls remain in the goal.)
Ji Hyo, you're up.
Will you blow the whistle or not?
I have no idea what she'll do.
1, 2, 3.
(No one knows
how Ji Hyo will react.)
- She didn't blow it.
- She didn't blow the whistle.
- This was placed inside the goal.
- I know.
- You did well.
- Good choice.
- Okay.
- But this rolled out.
Se Chan, you're up. You've got this.
- Go, Se Chan.
- We now have a 50-50 chance.
Do we score half
of the remaining balls?
We'll at least win
one of those rounds.
- Or we could go all-in.
- All at once.
- Go ahead.
- Let's go.
- Se Chan, you've got this.
- All right!
Cue, music.
(The third round begins.)
I sense something.
(Se Chan quickly escapes.)
Where are you off to?
(So Min won't leave his side.)
(He touched So Min,)
(but he moves to the side
without pushing her.)
Se Chan can't be cruel.
- He won't even push you.
- I know.
(Se Chan can't seem
to be harsh with her.)
3, 2, 1.
I'm glad he's not on my team.
(How many goals
did Suk Jin Gang score?)
(Only two keepers remain.)
1, 2...
(Will he blow the whistle
or save it for the next round?)
- Three!
- I won't blow it.
(I won't blow it.)
(How many points
did Team Offense score?)
- We scored all the balls we had.
- We knew it.
(They guessed that Se Chan
wouldn't blow the whistle...)
(and scored all of their
remaining balls.)
I love how my teammates...
are all so cunning.
- I got goosebumps.
- It was such a good choice...
to bring on board
two cunning members.
You will play defense this time.
It's a confusing game.
(Suk Jin Gang
will play keepers this time.)
I can't...
I can't ask them
to keep it safe for me...
because they'll only
end up stealing it.
Unbelievable.
- Who do I give it to?
- Look here.
All alliances and strategies
are allowed...
when violence isn't involved.
Sure thing.
But if I keep it on me,
the other team...
will steal the caramels.
This is driving me crazy.
I'll give back what I stole.
- Please enjoy.
- Keep it.
Sweet, isn't it?
- Do we get a minute?
- That's right.
Gosh, that is more than enough time.
All right.
- Your minute...
- Put the blindfold on properly.
(The 4 are only interested
in Kwang Soo.)
- Can we go ahead?
- Yes.
(Anxious)
(Their minute begins.)
- Are we on the clock?
- Yes.
(They immediately bind him.)
(Without even thinking,
they take Kwang Soo's hip sack.)
(What they hear paints the scene.)
- What's going on, Kwang Soo?
- Are you all right?
- Kwang Soo...
(It only took them 5 seconds
to steal his hip sack.)
I think they're busy
attacking Kwang Soo.
- There's nothing here.
- Where did he hide them?
(It's empty!)
(There are no caramels
inside Kwang Soo's hip sack.)
Where did he hide them?
(They immediately
search his pockets.)
- No!
- They'll take everything.
Where on earth did he hide them?
- Did he hide them?
- How long do I have left?
- Where are they?
- How long do I have?
How many seconds do I have left?
- Where did he hide them?
- He hid them?
- Where are they?
- How long do I have?
Kwang Soo never ceases to amaze me.
- No way.
- You have 20 seconds.
Unbelievable.
- Where did he hide them?
- And when?
(They quickly move on to the balls.)
Let's only leave two behind.
(Let's score as many as we can.)
Where did he hide them? Where?
(They leave all 10 balls!)
- Where did you hide them?
- Four.
- I think I saw them.
- 3, 2, 1.
(Their 1 minute is over.)
Wait. Where are his caramels?
Kwang Soo...
(Panting)
(If they succeed,
they'll win 10 points.)
(They can only blow the whistle
twice, so what will it be?)
(What?)
(He immediately blew
on the whistle.)
(What?)
- What happened?
- The game is over.
(Kwang Soo wins 10 points
for his team!)
- The game is over.
- Nice!
(Kwang Soo did it!)
- Kwang Soo!
- Nicely done.
- What happened?
- Nice.
- You're incredible, you know that?
- Just incredible.
- Kwang Soo!
- Where did you hide them?
- Where are the caramels?
And when?
(Are there caramels
near the cameraman's shoes?)
- And when?
- On the floor?
(When did he hide them there?)
- Over there?
- When?
When?
- Just when?
- So that's where they were.
- They're over here.
- When did he hide them?
When you were busy
playing the game.
(5 minutes into the game)
(After leaving a comment,
he went to hide the caramels.)
(Kwang Soo must've known...)
(that he'd be thoroughly searched.)
- Nice one, Kwang Soo.
- He's on a roll.
- See?
Wasn't I right
to choose the cunning ones?
- The cunning ones.
- Nicely chosen.
Do you all have your caramels?
- Yes.
- Of course.
- He's our lucky charm.
- Exactly.
He brought all the luck.
There's still the second round.
This time, Haha will go first.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Just do it.
- No, play rock-paper-scissors.
- It's your turn.
- You're up.
- No, play rock-paper-scissors.
- It is.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- It's your turn.
- No, it's not.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- It's your turn.
No, I've been waiting for my turn.
We'd like it to be someone
with a lot of caramels.
- That's you.
- Hold on a second.
- Hold on. Just wait.
- Just go ahead.
Wait. No, let me go.
- Hey, we haven't even started yet.
- Not yet?
Gosh, you're annoying. Hold on.
(Thinking of his imminent future
only makes him laugh.)
Wait.
(What now?)
- I know.
- Isn't he scary?
(The caramel thief
already found his target.)
(Give me a caramel,
and I'll let you live.)
Hurry up.
Don't you want to steal it all?
(The juicy target
is making him lose it.)
- Hurry.
- Let's play.
How about this?
Give us one each,
and we won't take any more.
- and we won't take any more.
- Good.
- That can be better.
- Give us one each.
- We'll call it a truce then.
- For real.
That could be better for you.
- Wait...
- It could be better.
- What do you think of my deal?
- I love it.
- It's the final round, anyway.
- We'll take it all.
- That would be better.
- Give us one each,
- and we won't take more.
- That's way better for you.
We have others to steal from anyway.
- We won't steal anymore.
- We swear.
Problems are better solved
with money.
That's right.
- All right.
- The choice is yours.
All right, I'll give them up.
- Thank you.
- Here.
Are you really handing them over?
- This is way better.
- Exactly. Give them away.
Did you really hand them over?
I got my caramels stolen...
- at the age of 42.
- No, don't be like that.
It's a logical solution.
It sets your heart at ease,
doesn't it?
We won't take your bag. Don't worry.
- Seriously.
- That's right.
- Hey.
- He is a coward.
You don't need to be scared.
- Take good care of me.
- One minute begins now.
Since he gave us a caramel,
we should treat him well.
That's right.
We should treat him well.
- We should treat him well.
- That's right.
- He gave us a caramel each.
- We need to set an example...
- so that the others will follow.
- That's right.
We want them to give us caramels
when we ask.
- Haha is the nicest.
- It was a good idea...
- to have the cunning members.
- He is the best.
- Seriously.
- I realized that...
the others would give up caramels
only if we set an example.
It's water.
(Go away.)
(Out of fear, Haha refuses
a moist act of kindness.)
You should drink water.
- It's water.
- It's water. Haha!
It's just water.
We are trying to be nice to you.
- Have a drink of water.
- We are trying to be nice to you.
- Drink.
Drink. I said, drink.
We aren't going to do anything.
Drink.
Why won't you drink?
It looks like you have a fugitive.
- No, no.
- Seriously.
All right. Okay.
Why is Haha sitting down
so pitifully?
We were just...
- Shall we stop with five balls?
- Okay.
(Their minute is over.)
- Shall we stop with five balls?
- Okay.
(There are 5 balls in the goal.
Will Haha blow the whistle?)
He might blow the whistle.
All right.
- Haha, make a choice.
- Why did you give me water?
- We wanted to be nice to you.
- We wanted you to drink it.
- You wanted to be nice to me?
- That's right.
- You gave us a caramel each.
I was scared my team members
would take my caramels.
- Why would they do that?
- They are blindfolded.
I was really scared.
(Crying)
You gave them caramels in advance.
It seemed that way.
Make a decision with the whistle.
(Thanks to the good people,
Haha saved his caramels.)
(Will he be able to save the goal?)
One,
- two,
- What will it be?
three.
(Sighing)
I didn't blow it.
Team Offense won five points.
(Suk Jin Gang won 5 points!)
(They got us again.)
- For goodness' sake.
- You should have blown the whistle.
You should have blown it.
- How was I supposed to know?
- We are on a roll.
How was I supposed to know?
We are a good team.
- We have the best teamwork.
- I know.
All right.
Blow the whistle this time.
Let's go.
(Glancing over)
- But to do this...
- Hold on.
Jae Suk, you are so upsetting.
Why did you look at me
as you said "Let's go"?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Suk is chosen to enter
the lion's den!)
Okay!
(The caramel-hungry beasts
are scarier than losing.)
This is the best.
It's a cause for celebration.
I need to go somewhere for a second.
- Where are you going?
- I will be back.
- Will you hide your caramels?
- Jae Suk,
- you don't need to give us any.
- Hang on.
- It will be a treasure hunt.
- Just give us four caramels.
You will end up
getting everything stolen.
I don't have many caramels.
I only have nine now. Hold on.
I will keep them here for a second.
(He hides the caramels
inside the filming equipment bag.)
I will retrieve them later.
Gosh, that hurts.
(They won't be able to find them.)
Just give us four caramels.
and set your heart at ease.
No!
- No?
- No.
- You will get everything stolen.
- Also,
I will hit you if you come near me.
- Keep that in mind.
- Then Jong Kook should go in alone.
- Okay.
- That's right.
- Good luck. Blow the whistle.
- Okay.
All right. Jae Suk. Music, cue.
(Since he hid the caramels,
he plays the game with ease.)
(What?)
Where are they going?
(Where are his teammates going?)
(Jae Suk's 3 subordinates are
off to look for his caramels!)
- Where are they going?
- They will look for his caramels.
(Aren't they on the same team?)
His teammates
will look for his caramels.
- Where are they?
- Where did he hide them?
- Tell us.
- Where are they? Tell us.
- Hurry up.
- Where are they?
(Let's find and steal them!)
(Meanwhile)
- Does he have them?
- No.
(They check if he has
any leftover caramels.)
- He doesn't have them.
- They must be in there.
They must be in his pocket.
(Hitting)
(His vicious front teeth
attack the thief.)
(I told you
that I won't let you be.)
I won't do it!
(Amidst the chaos,)
(So Min gets to work.)
I won't do it! Hey!
(So Min uses this opportunity
to betray him!)
His bag is unguarded.
Hey! Let go!
(The chairman goes after So Min.)
Let go!
(The thug goes after the chairman!)
(It's a complete mess!)
(The caramel food chain)
(The chemistry they built up
over 10 years shine...)
(before the caramels.)
Oh, no. My caramels.
(There is another place
where their chemistry shines.)
Let's share them.
Let's take two each.
2 for you and 2 for me.
(The fellowship of the slush fund
returns with the caramels.)
I feel bad for him.
Oh, no. My caramels.
(He has no idea what has happened.)
10 seconds left.
(Stealthy)
- Five,
- That was close.
four,
three,
two,
one.
Turn off the music.
(Will Jae Suk blow the whistle?)
- Go ahead.
- Let's see.
I will count to three.
Did he blow the whistle?
(He blew the whistle!)
- Okay.
- He blew the whistle.
Team Defense won five points.
- It's okay.
- Nice.
- There we go.
- They need those points.
- Jae Suk.
- All right.
- There we go.
- We gave them those points.
- That's right.
Thus, the second round
came to an end.
Suk Jin Gang won 31 caramels each.
(Suk Jin Gang won
31 caramels each.)
- That's a lot.
- That worked.
(Their investment paid off.)
Jae Suk Gang won
nine caramels each.
- 9 caramels?
(Jae Suk Gang won 9 caramels each.)
We will distribute the caramels now.
Count how many caramels
you currently have.
I got three caramels taken away.
I only have nine caramels now.
When did you get them taken away?
(Will that really be the case?)
They took my caramels!
(My slush fund)
(They got me.)
You took all of my caramels!
I have 14 caramels.
Did someone take your caramels?
(Feigning innocence)
- Did someone take your caramels?
- They took everything.
Your teammates took them.
- What are you talking about?
(He reports the incident.)
They did it.
Did they get stolen
while you were wearing a blindfold?
- Check the amount.
- Was it you?
- Me?
(He feigns disbelief.)
- Me? I was...
- Was it you?
Ji Hyo, what are those?
- Hold on.
- Ji Hyo, what are those?
(Her hands are full of caramels.)
Ji Hyo, aren't those mine?
- Of course not, Jae Suk.
- Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, it makes no sense
for you to have...
- so many.
- Come on, Jae Suk.
It's like a caramel factory.
I won them earlier.
Is theft allowed?
- Is it?
- You did it...
- before anyone else did.
- Anything but violence is allowed.
Okay. I won't forget this.
I won't forget this. It's a war.
(Current Number of Caramels,
Jong Kook 53, Suk Jin 45,)
(So Min 44, Kwang Soo 44,
Se Chan 31, Haha 27)
(Ji Hyo 25, Jae Suk 9)
- Everyone.
- Yes?
We will have the second election
for the chairman.
- The election.
- The time has come.
The process will remain the same.
The vote will take place
after 10 minutes of campaigning.
Someone with a lot of caramels
will have a high chance.
- That's right.
- You can buy people with caramels.
Se Chan, I will support you.
Run for the chairman.
The candidates
will be given bills, right?
I think Se Chan wants...
- Are you running?
- Yes.
If I become the chairman,
I will give bills to three people.
- Really?
- Me.
- 9 bills to 3 people.
(He will give 9 bills
to 3 people each.)
- I held my hand up 1st.
- Jong Kook, you are 1st.
- Me.
- I will give nine bills...
- each.
- Okay.
Se Chan, I will support you.
- Just give me seven bills.
- Oh, okay.
- Kwang Soo.
- I will run.
- Will you run?
- Yes, I will run.
- Do you need my support?
- I support you.
- Support me.
- Okay.
- I will support...
- Go over there.
- Kwang Soo, come here.
- I will support you.
Me too. I will support you.
- The one we support should win.
- That's right.
- I will support you.
- Seriously.
- I swear.
- Promise...
to divide the 30 bills among us.
- I will divide them equally.
- 7, 7, 8, 8.
- Okay.
Let's give five bills
to anyone who betrays Se Chan.
I will give five bills
What? How many bills?
Five bills.
(Kwang Soo's body reacts
to the talk of betrayal.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Will I get paid now or later?
I will give five bills
to anyone who betrays Se Chan.
It's only 5 bills.
I will give you 7 bills.
Listen. That group has
So Min and Kwang Soo.
We will stick together
and vote for Jae Suk.
- You will get caramels too.
- That's right.
- You won't be able to win there.
- You will get five bills...
and caramels.
How many bills
did you promise to give them?
- Seven bills each.
- That's right.
I will give you two caramels each.
- Then you will have 9 caramels.
- 9 caramels.
In that case, give them to me now.
- What?
- Give them to me now.
- I can't do that.
- He will pay after the election.
Go over there then.
Get five caramels.
- I don't care.
- If you come, I will pay up.
If you come, I will pay up.
- The bills will be divided equally.
- Listen.
- If they divide them equally...
- If you stay here,
- Then I will get nine caramels.
- you will get 9 caramels.
- 9 caramels.
You will get nine caramels.
- Why would you settle for five?
- I am not leaving.
- That's right.
- Don't do that.
I will give you
two additional caramels.
(They aren't falling for it.)
How many caramels
will you give them?
Give them 10 caramels.
It's better to be the chairman.
- It's a necessary sacrifice.
- That's right.
All right. Those who come
will receive 10 caramels.
(10 caramels?)
- 10 caramels?
- 10 caramels.
- We will give 10 caramels.
- Then you should go.
- Go.
Go.
Should I go right now?
- We just need one.
- Should I betray Se Chan later?
(Should I betray Se Chan later?)
(Is betrayal the key?)
- Betray him.
- Right now?
- Okay.
- Betray him.
- Okay. Let's have a vote.
In that case... Listen.
- How many bills? Seven?
- A lot.
All right. Don't come right away.
Betray him later, okay?
- Go.
- We just need one.
No, no.
Give us the bills.
I will do that.
Once we exchange them for caramels,
we will give the reward
to the turncoats.
- That's right.
- We will have a vote in 10 minutes.
I am not afraid
of what comes tomorrow.
We will have a vote in 10 minutes.
(The campaigning begins.)
Kwang Soo, come to the warm country.
We will give you money
so that you can settle down.
(What will be Kwang Soo's choice?)
Haha, can we talk for a second?
What do you want to talk about?
- What is this about?
- I just want to talk about...
- some business plans.
- Okay.
If Kwang Soo betrays me,
how many caramels can you take
in total?
I received seven bills.
I will give you eight caramels.
If you betray Jae Suk,
(Candidate Yang makes
a secretive offer.)
I understand.
If I become the chairman,
I will give you a special benefit.
Okay.
- What benefit?
- Look at the big picture.
Se Chan has a higher chance
of getting betrayed.
That's true.
Even if he wins,
he has a lot of people
to look after including Jong Kook.
- I don't.
- That's certainly the case.
That's right. If you think about it,
- this is where our roots are.
- That's right.
That's a given.
(What will be their decision?)
- My goodness.
- You are here.
Candidate Yu, you are here.
- Candidate Yu.
- Well, let's play fair.
Okay. You have some nice members.
Okay.
Please vote honestly.
Let's keep the process clean.
- All right.
I am sorry, but what does it mean
to vote honestly?
It just means
that we should stay honest.
- Honest?
- That's right. Don't betray.
Haha, you kept your distance.
- What?
- Did you change your mind?
It is a complex situation.
Didn't you write the name yet?
No, I didn't.
I didn't write the name yet.
Really?
Why aren't you inserting
the ballots?
- I did.
- He did.
These are bills.
You received bills from both sides.
Yes.
(Brazen)
Did you receive bills?
One candidate's bills
will become trash.
- You got bills from both sides?
Haha could have voted for Se Chan.
It looks like he received a lot.
I can't believe him.
Se Chan gave him some bills.
(Nervous)
It has been a while
since you painted the big picture.
Yes. This is the picture I wanted.
All right. My ballots are in.
The former chairman
will count the ballots.
- Okay.
- Please count them well.
It's sad to see him step down.
You painted the big picture.
Gosh, this is...
I have no idea what will happen.
There is no way of knowing.
Se Chan, you are dressed
like a chairman today.
My outfit gives off that vibe.
(He looks like the new rich
at a realtor's office.)
I will count the ballots.
- Gosh, this is...
- Yoo Jae Suk.
Thank you.
(Yoo Jae Suk got one vote.)
- Yang Se Chan.
- Thank you.
(Yang Se Chan got one vote.)
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Thank you.
This is neck-and-neck.
- Yang Se Chan.
- Okay.
(It's neck-and-neck
in the beginning.)
- Jae Suk...
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- All right.
- He is leading.
(Yoo Jae Suk got three votes.)
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- My goodness.
Gosh, this is...
Yoo Jae Suk.
This person was torn.
Oh, it's Kwang Soo's ballot.
"It's Kwang Soo's ballot"?
Yoo Jae Suk.
Kwang Soo was torn.
Yoo Jae Suk! Yoo Jae Suk!
(Yoo Jae Suk got 6 votes,
and Yang Se Chan got 2 votes.)
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Gosh, what is this?
- It's for Yoo Jae Suk, right?
- Yes, it is.
Whose ballot is this?
- Haha's.
- Haha's?
(Haha, how could you do this to me?)
- Yoo Jae Suk.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
Yoo Jae Suk, Yoo Jae Suk,
and Yoo Jae Suk.
(He gets consecutive ballots
at the end.)
Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- You are the worst!
- Thank you.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
Firstly...
- You dirty punk!
- You know,
no one voted for Se Chan.
- Jong Kook did.
- I did.
You dirty punk!
Everyone switched sides.
- Firstly...
- You dirty punk!
(So Min approaches the chairman.)
(My goodness.)
- I did.
- So Min.
(She cast 2 ballots to Jae Suk.)
We will change Jae Suk's bills
to caramels.
Like I told you before...
- So Min.
- Will you have any bills left?
Not really.
- But I promised.
- You are in a good mood.
How many bills do you have left?
I will give you two bills each.
- All right.
- Two bills?
- What?
- How many bills do I have?
- 2 bills?
- I need 5 bills for myself.
(He is 3 seconds away
from swearing.)
That's incredible.
You need five bills for yourself?
That's not what you promised.
Don't you want the bills?
You said there will be a benefit.
You said you will give me 11 bills
if I betray Se Chan.
- When did I...
- Where are my nine bills?
When did I say
I will give you 11 bills?
- See?
- Give me the bills then.
It's not like that.
For goodness' sake.
We betrayed Se Chan.
- You promised me 11 bills.
- Take 2 bills for now.
Take two bills for now.
Kwang Soo and So Min,
you would have gotten 11 bills...
- had you stayed.
- You would have gotten 11 bills.
So Min, how many bills did you get?
- Two bills?
- Listen.
Did you get two bills?
So Min got two bills.
I knew Jae Suk didn't have
enough bills.
- How many bills do you have?
- 1, 2, 3...
Hold on. This isn't Jae Suk's bill.
It should be this color.
Oh, right. This is trash.
I don't know why I brought trash.
Why do you carry around
so many napkins?
- They are trash.
- One.
Hold on.
(I got you.)
I got you!
Mr. Yang, you painted a big picture.
I can't paint a big picture
by myself.
This is ridiculous.
- 4, 5...
- This is ridiculous.
In any case,
- the chairman has power.
- That's true.
Will you give us...
- an advantage...
- You promised earlier.
- during the mission?
- I will do that.
- You promised earlier...
- Now...
- to take good care of us.
- Don't worry.
- All right.
- This isn't over yet.
Form a single line.
- Okay.
That's a bit...
I am different
from the former chairman.
- I am different.
- There is more discipline.
I will collect
a fee of two caramels each.
- What?
- Hold on.
(He will forcibly take caramels
from everyone.)
- Hold on.
- Two caramels?
Let's bring him down.
I only received two caramels.
- Let's bring him down.
- This is ridiculous.
- I only received two caramels.
- Give them up.
But I didn't vote for you.
But I became the chairman.
- This is...
- Give them up.
This is tyranny!
No, it isn't. Give me the caramels.
I will give them to you first.
(Please know that I am loyal.)
- I was the first one.
- Give them up.
- So suddenly?
- Give me two caramels each.
I didn't even vote for you.
Be that as it may,
I became the chairman.
Please exempt me...
since I was a candidate.
- I was a fellow candidate.
- Give them to me.
We will give you one caramel.
- Please exempt us.
- We will give you one caramel.
I will run things smoothly,
so you don't need to worry.
- I have 3 children.
- Give me 1 caramel.
- Give me 1 caramel then.
- One caramel.
- We elected a weirdo.
We elected a weirdo.
- Give me one each.
- How did this happen?
- We voted for the wrong candidate.
Ji Hyo, give me two caramels.
You have a lot of caramels.
- That's not true.
- Give me two caramels.
Suk Jin, how many do you have?
What? What do you mean?
- How many do you have?
- I can give you two caramels.
It's not a problem.
Give me two caramels.
This chairman is a thug.
What is going on?
- We voted for the wrong candidate.
- How will you use the caramels?
These caramels are
the congratulatory gift...
from you guys.
The congratulatory gift?
You should use them...
for our improvements.
You should use them
for our improvements, not yours.
I had to give up
the caramels I received.
I will use them for a good cause.
I gave up on 11 caramels
and voted for you.
- Don't worry.
- I gave up on 11 caramels.
Don't worry.
Now that I am the chairman,
we need to implement
the sharing economy.
Do you know what that means?
- The sharing economy?
- The sharing economy.
It's a good thing.
This atmosphere is
the sharing economy, right?
The ancestors' wisdom.
I will distribute the caramels...
to those who fall behind.
You will use them for a good cause.
I will use them for a good cause.
It's time for the last mission.
The last mission requires you
to school your face...
and predict the opponent's move.
It's the Card Game of Wits.
Four members will team up
and play the game.
Each member will get
red and blue cards...
with a number from 1 to 10.
You will put a red card
on your forehead...
and check a blue card alone.
Then you will place a bet.
You will win if the sum
of the numbers is the highest.
(The winner will take
all the caramels!)
My goodness.
The real game will begin now.
- The real game will begin now.
- The real game.
When the member ahead of you
places a bet,
you can either
place the same bet, fold,
or place a higher bet.
You listened to the rules just now.
Please explain the rules.
A blue card goes on your forehead.
- A red card.
- A red card goes on your forehead.
A blue card gets hidden.
- Then you school your face and...
- Ji Hyo.
Please explain
the rules of the game.
For goodness' sake.
A blue card goes on your forehead.
- A red card.
- A red card goes on your forehead.
A red card goes on your forehead.
- Okay.
- You check the blue card alone.
- Now, Chairman Yu.
- We need to decide on the teams.
Do we need to pay up
to get assigned to a team?
I will take out my caramels.
Please assign me...
- to a good team.
- For goodness' sake.
- Stop it.
- Earlier,
I gave you two caramels first.
- All right, Firstly,
- Do we need to pay up?
- Kwang Soo should come here.
- Okay.
- They have quick wits.
- It's okay.
I can make...
the best team...
with the members
who are good with numbers.
Jong Kook, come this way.
Okay!
It's a strong team.
I'm good with numbers.
This is a team.
- Yes.
- You will go against each other.
What? Aren't we on the same side?
You said we are a team.
- What?
- Will they go against each other?
I gave you so many caramels!
My goodness.
I wanted to put them
on the same side.
I didn't know. I am sorry.
- It was my mistake.
- Let's go.
Excuse me.
Please help me compete with Ji Hyo.
Let me compete with Ji Hyo.
Okay. I get it.
- I gave you two bills.
- Okay.
- Please.
- Tell me if you want anyone.
Send Suk Jin to me,
and I'll give you three.
It looks like we can win
many caramels in this game.
Tell me if there's anyone
you want to compete with.
- Ji Hyo.
- Four people compete, right?
- Who do you want?
- Ji Hyo.
We're giving
Jae Suk caramels voluntarily.
- She's too popular.
- The problem is,
too many people want Ji Hyo.
(Many people want to
compete with her.)
- She's too popular.
- Then...
- I'll...
- Okay.
Do you want anyone?
How many caramels
is he taking from us?
- His position is amazing.
- He's taking everything.
- Stop taking caramels!
- I should have run too.
Ji Hyo, who do you want?
(Who does Ji Hyo want?)
Four people compete, right?
- Yes. We need two more people.
- What?
You can't ask me
to get you out of the game.
What are you talking about?
- Then just go home!
- She wants to be out?
She wants to be out?
She doesn't want to play?
- She wants to be out?
- She doesn't understand the rules.
How can you say that?
Ji Hyo, you should play too.
You can't ask me
to get you out of the game.
Anyway, Kwang Soo, Jong Kook,
you can sit at the table.
- Okay.
- Should we sit?
- And then...
- They'll be too strong.
- You want to avoid them.
- Give me this.
So Min, sit at the table.
You didn't give him any caramels.
You didn't give me any caramels,
so sit at the table.
Hold on. Haha gave me one,
- I gave you 1.
- Se Chan gave me 1...
- I gave you 4.
- You gave me 4.
- I gave you 3.
- You gave me 3.
I feel hurt. The two people
sitting here...
are the ones you promised
to give 11 bills to.
- Hold on.
- I have to ask.
Why am I sitting here...
- without any caramels?
- I didn't mean it.
- It just happened that way.
- Why...
- I know.
- I'm sorry. Wait just a minute.
Chairman Yang.
- I mean, Candidate Yang.
- Yes?
You go sit there.
- Okay.
- Please sit down, the four of you.
- We don't know how Se Chan will do.
- He'll do well.
In this game, you shouldn't
think too much.
All members of that team...
From Kka Chi,
- the chairman,
- Yes.
and Goni...
- To Madam Jeong.
- All right.
First, please bet one caramel each.
- This is so fun.
- Okay.
Pick carefully.
I've always wanted to try
sitting at a table like this.
There are tables like this
at board game cafes too.
- Really?
- Yes.
Please put one red card
on your forehead.
- Any card?
- Pick carefully.
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- Okay.
Put it on your forehead
without showing it to anyone.
(Careful)
(They pick
their first cards quietly.)
Here?
Is this the front?
- Is it?
- Yes.
(Even the audience
becomes immersed.)
Like this? Is this right?
Pick one blue card
and check the number secretly.
Guys.
I may run out of money,
but I never quit gambling.
Does he think this is for real?
This isn't for real.
Chewing a caramel and all...
I think I've seen him in a movie.
I'm sorry, but this isn't Las Vegas.
(The muscular chairman is
chewing a caramel in Las Vegas.)
Pick one blue card
and check the number secretly.
So Min, don't show it to the others.
Don't show it to the others.
Gosh, this is bad.
I don't know what to do.
- I don't know what to do.
- Don't show it to the others.
(You should keep a poker face
even if you get a big number.)
Okay.
(They try to look calm
after seeing their cards.)
(The player
with the greatest sum wins.)
We'll start with So Min.
- Here we go.
- Go ahead.
- All in?
- One?
Kwang Soo.
I'll bet one.
I'll bet one and...
(Se Chan bets 1 caramel plus...)
- raise the bet by three.
- Three?
- Hey, Catfish.
- I bet big.
Are you sure?
You raised the bet by three?
We should keep a poker face too.
(After thinking...)
I fold.
- What?
- You fold?
My number must be big.
So Min, you have to bet three more.
So Min, either bet three more
or fold.
(With Jong Kook out,
she has to think.)
Gosh.
(They stare at her
with "9" on their foreheads.)
(Should I continue or not?)
(Poker face)
Gosh, this is...
I should have a taste.
This is our first round anyway.
(She is attracted
to the sweetness of the caramels.)
- So Min.
- Of course you should.
- You want to keep going?
- She wants a taste?
- So Min.
If you bet 3 now,
you'll have to bet 10 later.
- For now...
- Call?
- I bet three more.
- Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
- I fold.
- Bet three more.
- What?
- Okay.
You fold?
- Are you done?
- This is our first round.
- Se Chan, this is our first round.
- I should go all in.
This is our first round, Se Chan.
This is our first round.
I raise the bet by six.
(Catfish raises the bet by 6.)
If you're scared, fold.
- Then you don't have to bet...
- Okay. Call.
(Okay, I bet 6 more.)
- Call?
- Okay.
- I could lose too.
- Gosh.
I should have stayed.
- So Min.
- Very good.
Who knows?
My blue card may be very good.
So Min, you look so cute
with that card on your forehead.
Please reveal your cards now.
- The thing is,
- Let's see the numbers.
Se Chan must have raised the bet...
because his card is good.
(Se Chan's number on his forehead
is bigger than So Min's.)
- So Min.
- Should I see the number?
Check your card.
- Gosh.
- It's too small.
(She is disappointed at the number
on her forehead.)
- It's 1.
- My other number is 8.
- Right?
- Really?
- That's why.
- It's nine in total.
(So Min's sum is 9.)
So it was worth it.
- Kwang Soo...
- So it was worth it.
- Kwang Soo, you...
- Mine was nine?
- Yes.
(He didn't make use of
the number on his forehead.)
- What's your other number?
- You should have kept going.
It's two.
(Kwang Soo's sum is 11.)
It's too small,
so I couldn't continue.
- Se Chan's number is too big.
- It's too big.
- I know.
- Guys, my sum is 19.
(Se Chan's sum is 19.)
- Really?
- I should've gone all in.
You should have gone all in.
Someone could have lost big.
- It's 19.
- Candidate Yang.
Are you painting
the big picture now?
You picked good cards.
Someone could have lost big.
I almost turned my life around.
- You're painting the big picture!
- The number on my forehead is 3,
and I picked two.
Good that I folded early.
If this number was smaller,
So Min would have continued.
- It's because of this.
- Please discard all cards.
Se Chan, you can take everything.
We can't use "9" again?
Gosh, I wasted "9" like this?
We don't have "9" or "10" anymore.
Se Chan discarded "10".
We don't have "10" anymore.
But we can still have "10"
on our foreheads, right?
- Yes.
- That's right.
(They can still have "10"
on their foreheads.)
- Please pick your cards.
- Put it on your forehead.
Raise the bet in the beginning.
(They all have numbers
on their foreheads now.)
Check your blue cards now.
(They check their blue cards.)
I can see who is going out first.
So the three of them...
are playing So Min?
(Jeon Pushover)
Is she your target?
She already lost.
(Are you ready to rip her off?)
(I'm ready.)
(I'm ready too.)
So Min.
(What will So Min do,
surrounded by three cheaters?)
I raise the bet by four.
- Already?
- Yes.
- Call.
- Call?
- Yes.
I raise the bet by five.
It's 10 in total.
- That's big.
- Se Chan.
- We can't...
- I don't think I can go on.
Be quiet.
- I fold.
- You fold?
- Yes.
It's between those two now.
You can play one more round.
(It's between these 2 now.)
So Min, you have to bet five more.
(As So Min has "2" on her forehead,
Kwang Soo is sure he'll win.)
(He goes all in.)
(It's exciting.)
Either bet five more or fold.
- I bet five more.
- Call.
- That's it. It's over.
- Let's see the numbers now.
(It's time to reveal the cards.)
(So Min's number on her forehead
is much smaller.)
Mine is two. What's yours?
What's your other number, So Min?
- It's nine.
- Gosh.
It's 11 in total.
(Kwang Soo seems to have
an advantage for now.)
What if his other number is one?
(Kwang Soo will win
if his other number is 2 or bigger.)
(What number is on his blue card?)
It's one.
(It's 1?)
(How can it be 1?)
It's a big number again.
(Kwang Soo raised the bet
to make So Min give up.)
It was 10?
(Even though he wasted "10",
it's a tie.)
What happens now? Do I win?
- No. It's a tie.
- No?
Pick one red card, each of you.
The one with a bigger number wins.
Pick one from the rest.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Pick 1 red card.
- Just a second.
- 1, 2, 3.
Okay.
- It's decided now.
- It's decided.
- What's my number? Did I lose?
- So Min, show me.
- Did I lose?
- Kwang Soo wins.
Okay!
(Kwang Soo wins!)
(Showing off)
The three of them ripped her off.
(They celebrate together.)
Kwang Soo. So Min.
(Disappointed)
What is this?
So Min is in trouble.
She has nothing left.
She lost everything.
- Here we go.
- This is our last round.
- I haven't picked "10" yet.
- Let me see.
- This is...
- Keep a poker face, So Min.
(She picks the card
for her forehead first.)
Let me see.
(So Min picked "10".)
Show me, So Min.
Show me, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo picked "5",
and Se Chan picked "3".)
Okay.
Let's start.
- I'll pick one.
- Go ahead.
(She picks a blue card.)
(She chuckles.)
(She can't help but smile.)
What is it?
Why does she smile right away?
- Hey.
- I fold!
(The novice can't keep
a poker face.)
- So Min is so cute.
- Should I bet?
- I bet all seven.
- All in?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
- 6, 7. All in.
- So Min goes all in.
Okay. Kwang Soo.
(Confident)
- I fold.
- Why?
I fold too.
- Why? Why would you fold?
- Then I fold too.
Why?
Then I fold too.
(The three cheaters back out.)
(Everyone backs out upon seeing
the novice's smile.)
- I'm sorry.
- I almost got hit in the eye.
- I couldn't go.
So Min. Look at your card.
- Look at it.
- I couldn't go.
I couldn't go.
- What are you holding?
- What is it?
I got "1".
(My blue card was "1".)
(My gosh, her blue card was "1"?)
- Then...
- I didn't stand a chance.
I got "1",
but the red card was also "1".
- I had "12"!
- That's "12".
You would've won with "12".
So Min won the bet.
But there aren't very many.
So Min.
This is why the association exists.
Are you sponsoring her?
- Thank you.
- Do you understand?
- This is fun.
- Thank you.
Let's start with the red card.
(They start the second ground
with new members.)
- Shall we choose them?
- Yes.
(Ji Hyo 10, Suk Jin 2,
Jae Suk 3, Haha 8)
Put on your poker face.
We need to choose our blue cards.
(It's time to choose
their blue cards.)
(They are done checking.)
- This is fun.
- Let's start with Ji Hyo.
- Me?
- You can't do that.
I bet one.
(She submits 1 caramel.)
I call one.
He's at it again.
(He said one thing,
and they caught his bluff.)
- Please help him restrain himself.
- But...
I don't like...
- playing for a long time.
- He's incredible.
- I call 1 and raise 4.
- Go easy.
- Four.
- My goodness.
- I call four...
- You'd think he was rich.
- and raise 4.
- He raises 4.
- Okay.
- I'll make it nine.
They're betting a lot of caramels.
I put in 9,
- He put in 9.
- Really?
I don't know.
- He put in nine. What's this?
- 2, 4, 6,
8, 10.
- 10?
- Yes.
Then how much does Ji Hyo
have to put in?
- Ji Hyo needs to put in...
- I...
- 19.
- She needs to put in 17.
17?
- That's a lot.
- Are you going in?
Are you?
(Is Ji Hyo going for it?)
6, 8, 10.
- Really?
- I fold this round.
- I don't have enough.
- Why did you fold after counting?
I counted to see how many
I had left.
How many do I need to put in
to continue?
You have to start at 10.
- You...
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
7, 8, 9, 10.
Goodness. That's a lot of caramels.
I think two people will die
in this round alone.
Isn't it a waste to fold now?
- It is.
They would lose
the caramels they put in.
I think Haha is going to play
until the end.
He has to at this point.
I have 12 left.
- I also...
- I don't know.
I don't like playing a game
for too long.
The chairman is quite bold.
I fold.
- What?
- I fold.
- Is it because you're scared?
- Yes, it is.
- Fold if you're scared.
- Then fold.
- What should we do now?
- We should show the cards.
Do we need to show?
Can't we go another round?
- You can.
- Bring it on.
- Okay. All in!
- How many?
- 12.
12.
12?
(If he has more than 12,
he can counterattack.)
Take one out.
(His voice is loud
compared to what he has.)
- Take one out.
- I'll let it slide.
- Accept it.
- Okay.
Haha must have a high card.
Should we start with Suk Jin?
The sum of my cards is 10.
- That isn't a low number.
- Ji Hyo.
I have four...
- I had a good hand.
- What's Ji Hyo's number?
Ji Hyo has a high number. It's 10.
What was your total?
- 14.
- What were you holding?
- Gosh. She had "14".
- 14.
- This is...
- Let's see Haha's number first.
(A lot of caramels are on the line
in this one match.)
(Who will take the caramels?)
(Jae Suk's card 3, Haha's card 8)
- He had "8". It's high.
- It's high.
I think the card
he's holding is high.
Let's take turns revealing our card.
- Okay.
- That card is weak. It's "3".
(Jae Suk's card 3, Haha's card 8)
(His blood sugar suddenly dropped.)
(The audience is having a blast.)
(If he loses, he goes bankrupt.)
We can only play one round
of something so fun.
- He should've collected 1 or 2.
- This is so fun.
1, 2, 3.
(They must put all their trust
in their blue card!)
1, 2, 3.
It's over.
(Jae Suk's blue card is "10".)
(Haha had "8" on his forehead.)
(He wins if his card
is higher than "6".)
(My gosh.)
Three.
(What is the number
on Haha's blue card?)
Haha had "10"?
(Haha was holding "10".)
(His coolness explodes.)
His total is 18?
- His total is 18?
- I...
He had "8" on his forehead,
- and he kept raising.
- You could've assumed he had "10".
- Jae Suk had "10" too.
- Drag him out. Stop.
- Let go.
- Come out.
- Come out. Come out!
- This was so fun.
Haha.
(Flinging)
- This was so fun.
- Get out!
Don't come back here.
Don't come back.
You should go.
I can't believe...
- I don't want it.
- Go and get something to eat.
(I'm sure you don't feel good.)
Life is like vapor in the air.
Why would you ruin the game?
(He learned a life lesson
through a card game.)
Gosh, I'm so angry.
This is so much fun,
but he only got to play it once.
This is hilarious.
- Excuse me. Mr. Chairman.
- Yes?
Go get me some water.
- I'm thirsty.
- He's moving.
Okay.
It's time for you to pay your dues.
- No way. I'm not going to pay.
- What are you saying?
What is this?
- Association fees.
- No way.
Since when did we have such fees?
- Association fees.
- How much?
5 from the person who won.
- Five?
- He's a thug.
- 5.
- 5?
- The association fee is 5 caramels.
- What are you doing?
Hurry up and give it to me.
You saw me help those in need.
- Just take 2.
- Give me 5. You won a lot.
Kwang Soo. Let's go bury him.
- This won't do.
- Hold on.
- Give me two.
- This won't do.
- What are you doing?
- Give me two.
- No, I helped those in need.
- Are you trying to sit here?
- You can't sit here.
- Don't sit here.
- I'll give you two, just don't sit.
So Min, you lost a lot earlier.
- I'll give you two.
- Okay.
(He steals 2 from Se Chan.)
- This is the fee to help people.
- How many do you want?
- Give me two.
- Since when did we have fees?
- I'm telling you.
If I give you two,
and you go sit there...
I won't sit there. Don't worry.
- He's a gangster.
- I won't sit there.
- Don't worry.
- Really?
My gosh. Goodness.
Okay.
- What?
- Okay.
(He naturally walks over
to the cards.)
(You said you wouldn't sit down!)
- Don't sit down.
- I'll pay you back after I win.
I'll pay you back after I win.
- Pull yourself together.
- What is he doing?
- Go away!
- What are you saying?
Go away.
- What's wrong with him?
- Do you think you can do that?
We don't trust you.
- Get over here.
- Sit over here.
- My goodness.
- This is hilarious.
- This is fun.
- Should we choose our cards?
(The remaining 3 players
start their game.)
- It was so funny how he sat there.
- What's your number?
(Ji Hyo 4, Suk Jin 10, Haha 1)
Okay.
I fold.
Really?
Here's one,
and I'll go all in.
(All in)
I'll go all in.
I'm sorry, but did you just put it
into Jae Suk's name?
- He put it in Jae Suk's.
- It's over.
He put it in Jae Suk's.
It's mine.
- This is mine.
- Put it down.
(An unexpected fortune
gifted by Big Nose)
Why would you put it into
Jae Suk's name?
No.
I'm telling you that it's mine.
- Why would you put it in there?
- Hey! Give it back!
Give it back.
It's Jae Suk's now.
- Why would you put it in there?
- Hey!
- Why are you doing this?
- You put it in my name.
- Hey! It's not yours.
- It's mine now.
- Give it back.
- Everyone's name is written on it.
- Right.
- Why did you put it in my name?
Why would you put it in his name?
How much is he giving
for his association fee?
- All of it is...
- How many did you take?
- I don't know.
- Put it back. There's 25 or 26.
- It wasn't that many.
- What are you saying?
Are you playing games, you punk?
(He lost his temper.)
Why are you cursing at me?
What is this?
You're the one who put it in.
You put it in under my name.
- It's mine.
- You're not playing this round!
That punk.
(He lost his temper
and is using foul language.)
Bring it back.
(They're starting to
chase each other again.)
(They go around and around.)
We're supposed to play like this?
- What is this?
- What are those two doing?
- Okay.
- Are you playing Duck, Duck, Goose?
Then give me 10, and we'll end this.
- Just give me 10.
- Sit down.
Just give me 10, and let's end this.
2, 4, 6, 7.
Did he get more?
Why would he put it in my name?
- Okay. Give me one.
- This is...
- Give me one.
- My gosh.
You found out because
I said something. Give me one.
My gosh,
there are a lot of pests here.
Okay, let's start.
2, 4, 6, 8, 10.
- It's 20, exactly.
- 20?
- Make 20. You need 18.
- That's a lot.
(He intends to make up for it
with this.)
I fold.
(He doesn't think twice.)
(This wasn't my intention.)
(Suk Jin's plan
goes down the drain.)
- Hurry up, Ji Hyo.
- I folded already.
- I folded earlier.
- Everyone folded.
- Just play!
- I folded.
- Hurry up.
- I folded earlier.
Why did this happen to Suk Jin?
- What is it?
- He won.
(I had "10"?)
So does that mean
he only got two?
This is weird.
- I won, but I have fewer caramels.
- He lost 15 and won 2.
- He lost 15.
- He lost in this round.
I lost.
Okay.
You!
This is chaos.
- Can he play this round?
- He did well.
I still have my name on the box.
Why can't I play?
I think you'll end up coming right
back out, so just play.
- I...
- You can play.
got sponsored by a benefactor...
and got the chance to sit
in this seat again.
You're really good
at raising the stakes.
- I'll just go for it.
- Are you all in?
- I'm all in.
- Me too.
- Let's do it.
- I'm all in too.
(Jae Suk 2, Ji Hyo 5)
- The two of you...
- Ji Hyo.
- Shall we choose our cards?
- My goodness.
(Suk Jin 1, Haha 2)
Okay. We chose our cards.
(They're done choosing
their blue cards.)
Let's start with one.
(Suk Jin submitted 1 caramel.)
I call...
(He has a lot of caramels.)
one.
Haha has a lot.
- He really has a lot.
- 2, 4, 6, 8, 10. I raise 10.
Okay. The stakes are going up.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo.
(To continue playing, Ji Hyo
must put out more than 11 caramels.)
11?
There she goes.
- Ji Hyo, are you going in?
- Is it 10 or 11?
- It's 11?
- Is Ji Hyo going in?
11.
- Shall I put in 11 caramels?
- Go ahead.
Yes.
I'll fold.
What? You just counted
your caramels.
- Ji Hyo.
- Are you kidding me?
It's my choice.
That's what I want to do.
We had to wait
while you counted your caramels.
She asked Jae Suk
to leave her out earlier.
I guess she really meant it.
Let's see.
- Let's see how it goes.
- This is...
Let me see.
This is really...
These are 11 caramels.
(He puts in 11 caramels.)
And three more.
- Is that it?
- What?
Hang on. I want
the three of you to stop...
- trying to sound so cool.
- I agree.
I'm sorry, but you're
just throwing in caramels now.
If you have more caramels
in your bag, just take them out.
(They sound like real card sharks.)
All right. I call three.
Suk Jin, why are you blushing?
Why is your face so red?
I'm still upset
with what happened earlier.
I'll fold.
Can I put in another three caramels?
- It's over. He's done.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- What is it?
These two have nothing,
and they're acting cool.
- I'll take this off.
- Okay.
- I'm taking this off.
- Go ahead.
You two should take it off.
- One.
- Do it at the same time.
(Shocked)
The card in your hand
will decide the winner.
1, 2, 3.
(Who will be winning?)
Three.
(Jae Suk's blue card is 2.)
(Haha's blue card is 5.)
(Haha wins.)
- It's done.
- What?
- Hey.
- I beat Jae Suk.
Come here.
I told you not to come.
Sprinkle salt on him.
Sprinkle caramels on him.
- Don't come again.
- My gosh.
- You're bankrupt again.
- It's a dirty world.
- Okay?
- Don't give him any money.
- It's a dirty world.
- Pull yourself together.
- Put it together.
- My goodness.
Get out of here, you punk.
- Jae Suk.
- I'll call the police.
Why?
Why would you call the police?
I'll report you to the police.
This is a healthy card game.
- All right.
- You guys.
We're using caramels.
Why would you call the police?
The third mission
has come to an end.
Please count your caramels now.
I have three.
- What?
- I will...
get back on my feet with these.
My gosh.
You get 10 cents per caramel.
So Jae Suk gets 30 cents.
(Jae Suk gets 30 cents
for the next week's mission.)
- Only 30 cents?
- 30 cents!
(The tragic end with 30 cents
will be revealed next week.)
(Here are the guests who will
join Jae Suk with 30 cents.)
(Soyou, Jang Won Young of IZ ONE,
YUQI of (G)I-DLE)
(Kim Do Yeon of Weki Meki,
Mi Joo of Lovelyz)
(And...)
(Kim Dong Jun)
(There's a girl...)
(who smiles broadly
with all her heart.)
(It's a capitalistic race
with partners...)
(where they have to follow money.)
(The dice is cast.)
(They're ready to do anything...)
(to get more money.)
(The aftereffect of the betting
isn't over yet.)
(It's a war with deep-fried squid.)
(They can be happy only with money.)
(How would the race
with partners end?)
(Capitalistic Race with Partners,
Don't Worry, Be Happy)