(Coming soon)
(A special opening ceremony for
the penthouse resident presentation)
(It's a luxurious opera performance
that anyone can't watch.)
(4 residential candidates
of the penthouse appeared.)
(Ha Do Kwon, Kim So Yeon,
Lee Ji Ah, Eugene)
(Their merciless fight
to join the top club will begin.)
(While the opera performance
reaches its climax,)
(the battle to get the penthouse
becomes fierce.)
(It will be revealed soon.)
(And last week,)
(6 guests joined...)
(the Old Restaurant Race
in Running Man.)
(And they got a mission.)
(They have to find old restaurants
and eat meals there.)
(And they will subtract the years
of their history from the team age.)
(Make your team age 0.)
(Current Team Age)
(To subtract their numbers,)
(they have to complete
their mission.)
(They go through a mission to set
the order to subtract their number.)
(2 members with the most years left
will get a penalty.)
(And the members with the most years
got a hidden mission.)
(They roll the dice to subtract
his and one opponent's age.)
(White for himself, red for
a member of another team)
Jong Kook, which member
will you choose?
(Jong Kook picked Se Chan.)
(3 years was subtracted
from Se Chan's age.)
(Ji Hyo picked Jae Suk.)
(1 year was subtracted
from Jae Suk's age.)
(Team Suk Jin has 64 years left.)
(Team Jong Kook has 82 years left.)
(Team Ji Hyo has 107 years left.)
(Which team will make their age 0
and win the race?)
(Team Ji Hyo: Jongno, 107 years
Team Suk Jin: Seongbuk, 64 years)
(Team Jong Kook:
Myeong-dong, 82 years)
That was good.
Thank you for the food.
It will be hard
to make it 200 years.
It's impossible.
I know.
H restaurant is 80 years old.
Then we will have
only two years left.
We picked the wrong
restaurant earlier, right?
We should've picked
this restaurant first.
This restaurant is
really good though.
Once you try their beef gone soup,
you won't want to eat it elsewhere.
- Really?
- If it suits your taste.
(Once you try their beef gone soup,
you won't want to eat it elsewhere.)
Anyone can say that.
Gosh.
Don't you think?
"If it suits your taste."
You can say that
for all restaurants.
I mean,
some like it and some don't.
People either like it a lot
or hate it a lot.
I get that the food is good.
But isn't it too much to say that
you can't eat it elsewhere?
Let's be honest.
- Don't you think so?
- Right.
I won't want to eat beef bone soup
at other restaurants?
I think it's far-fetched
to say that.
(Sighing)
You're recommending this restaurant
because you liked it.
You should think
before you say anything.
My point.
- That was too much.
- I know, right?
- It's upsetting, right?
- Yes.
It can be misleading.
Hang on. You've been quiet
the whole time, and you suddenly...
Bomi is being nice
because she has a good personality.
- I agree.
- Sure.
If you date someone mean,
she will hang you out to try.
We're just saying that
because you broke up with her.
So...
I just said this place makes
good beef bone soup.
- I know.
- Then do you really have to...
"Why would you say that?"
(Why would you say that?)
(He suddenly starts a skit.)
"What's with that look
on your face?"
"Are you saying I'm strange?
I want to break up with you."
This is what happens.
It can happen.
"Once you try their beef gone soup,
you won't want to eat it elsewhere."
Because I said that...
"My mom runs
a beef bone soup restaurant."
How would I know that?
(He adds some details in the story.)
Do you want her to shut down?
That's not what I meant.
- If you try their food...
- Then I won't eat it.
"You think they are the only ones
who make good beef bone soup."
That's not what I said.
- "Fine."
- My gosh.
I didn't see this coming.
- You should break up.
- That's unbelievable.
We're here.
Put on a mask.
Jong Kook.
It says "Ha" like my name.
(H Restaurant, opened in 1939,
passed down through 3 generations)
(80-year-old traditional
Korean beef soup)
(Beef soup made with beef leg bones,
brisket, and intestines)
(It's a beef bone soup restaurant
with a long history.)
(According to Kwang Soo, it can
ruin you for other beef bone soup.)
This restaurant is
about 82 years old.
It's 82 years old.
- Hello.
- Hello, ma'am.
Is this place 82 years old?
What? 83 years?
I used to come here
to buy take-out beef soup.
Right.
- You remember him.
- Yes.
Ma'am, how old is this place?
(If it's over 82 years old, they
can make their team age 0.)
(What will she say about
the history of this restaurant?)
It's 82 years old.
(The place has a tradition
of 82 years.)
(The age Team Jong Kook has left
is also 82 years.)
That's amazing.
- 82 years?
- It's perfect.
It's perfect.
- We opened this restaurant in 1939.
- I see.
- That's right.
- It's exactly 82 years.
- It breaks even.
- Kwang Soo said this.
If you try your beef bone soup,
you won't want to eat it elsewhere.
That's why
I'm still having a hard time.
Let's order the food then.
We don't have much time.
We will have beef bone soup.
- Just one serving, please.
- Please make it special.
- This is unbelievable.
- I know.
I can't believe it breaks even.
Let's start the mission then.
- We have to hurry.
- Give us the mission.
- Okay.
- I don't want to lose.
How is this possible?
Pyongyang naengmyeon and
hangover soup with clotted blood?
We should go to a place like this.
I bet you feel queasy now.
(Suk Jin wants to go
to the gamjatang restaurant.)
Let's go to the gamjatang
restaurant then.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- What you've had is...
- I know.
- Let's eat something spicy.
Now we're going
to a restaurant you want.
Gamjatang is really good.
It tastes good with rice.
Are there 3 teams or 4 teams?
Why don't you calculate your age?
First, we went to the restaurant
that's 48 years old.
- Then the second one was...
- It was 84 years old.
- 84 years.
- That's crazy.
So it's 132 years in total.
- Then how many do you have left?
- 66.
We have 66 years left.
How old is this restaurant?
- It's 63 years old.
- 63 years?
Then we can finish it
with this restaurant.
- We can finish it.
- We can do that.
We can finish it
if we do things right.
(How would they finish it
when they need 3 more years?)
(1 hour ago)
(He got 1 year deducted
from his age thanks to Ji Hyo.)
(Jae Suk became the oldest member
and found out about the mission.)
(He got another 1 age deducted
with his bad luck.)
(Jae Suk got 2 years deducted
with the hidden mission.)
(They might be able to win the race
with the next restaurant.)
We can finish it
if we do things right.
This is it.
Is that it?
(They arrive at the restaurant.)
(T Gamjatang Restaurant)
(It was open in 1958 and has been
passed down through 3 generations.)
(The restaurant was redecorated,
so it looks neat and clean,)
(but the place still
has its old heritage.)
(Open 24 hours)
Gosh, it smells great.
(The soup is rich
and the meat is tender.)
All right. This is the last mission.
Okay. I have to win this time.
You can subtract 63 years here.
I have to get rid of all of my age.
Otherwise, we might be the last.
Right. We have to win.
If you complete this mission,
you will have one year left.
Okay.
This mission is...
called Finger Fencing.
You will put paint on your hands,
and the one who puts...
more paint on your opponent's face
in one minute wins the game.
So what's important is
whom you fight against.
Soo Yong has long arms.
I want to fight against Chang Hee.
You'll play Palm Face Down or Up.
We play Palm Face Down or Up.
Palm Face Down or Up
(Suk Jin versus Soo Yong)
I'll fight against Chang Hee.
(It's a big match between
two men born in 1966.)
I'm in trouble.
He has very long arms.
- I will win by default.
- It's a done deal.
I will win by default.
- Ready.
- All right.
(Legend of Yeouido High School,
Kim Soo Yong)
(He's a living legend
with magical fists.)
(A real hungry fighter,
Ji Suk Jin)
(He's a man in his 50s
who's quite strong for his age.)
(It's a match between
two rivals of the same age.)
Start.
(The 1 minute begins.)
(Rubbing)
(Suk Jin got paints on his face
only in 5 seconds.)
(He plays an impenetrable
defense with his long arm.)
(Reaching out...)
(to his face)
(Suk Jin is losing
the game helplessly.)
Hang on. Come here.
He told Soo Yong to come.
(Confident)
- Hey, your arm... Move it.
- Look at Soo Yong.
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- Three.
2, 1. Time's up.
- Who won?
- Soo Yong wins.
Why do you even ask?
Isn't it obvious?
All right. Okay.
(Suk Jin will have
a match for 3rd.)
3, 2...
Time's up.
- Who won?
- Nam Chang Hee won.
(Nam Chang Hee won!)
(Suk Jin came in last place again.)
You'll be the last one to eat.
I know. Gosh, you.
- Leave some for me.
- Okay.
This is the final round.
(The long-awaited final round)
- Let's do this.
- Go for it.
(The fast Suyu-ri Locust)
- Let's go.
- Soo Yong is very tall,
so it won't be easy.
I'll use my speed to win.
- Should I stand here?
- I'm faster than him.
(Their pride is on the line.)
Ready, set, go.
(The final round begins.)
It won't be easy, Jae Suk.
Soo Yong has a really long reach.
(Jae Suk is moving quickly
to get closer to him.)
They put some paint
on each other right away.
Jae Suk looks as if he put on
makeup for a show.
The way the paint got
on his face is funny.
(Korea's best MC's mouth
stands out more with paint over it.)
(However,)
(Soo Yong got more paint
on his face!)
Jae Suk is good at this.
Soo Yong, you should attack now.
Or else, you'll lose.
(Soo Yong will lose at this rate.)
(Soo Yong's final attack
with 8 seconds remaining)
Or else, you'll lose.
(Will Jae Suk be able
to block his attack?)
(Giggling)
(Jae Suk barely managed to block
his attack.)
Two.
2, 1.
(The game is over.)
Time's up.
My gosh. I think...
(The comedians from KBS
showed no mercy on each other.)
- Yoo Jae Suk won.
- That was amazing.
Jae Suk won.
Jae Suk was really fast.
That was a great match.
I won...
in my hometown.
(The pride of Yongmun High School)
- You look like you lost though.
- Really?
Don't wash your face.
- Are you okay?
- Darn.
- Starting with first place.
- Where is my bag?
63 years.
(Jae Suk who was the oldest member
removed all his age badges.)
Next, please.
(Soo Yong and Chang Hee also
removed all their badges.)
Can he deduct all the years left?
I think he has one year left.
(Only Suk Jin has 1 year left.)
(If another team wins, he who is
1 year old will get a penalty.)
It's hard to predict.
Everyone.
- You deducted 63 years in total.
- Yes.
(At that moment, an announcement
was made for all the teams.)
Team Soo Yong and Chang Hee won.
(Team Soo Yong and Chang Hee won.)
(This team won?)
(Team Ji Hyo was at their 3rd place
about 10 minutes ago.)
I'll go to the restroom too.
Go ahead.
(And So Min sneaked out alone.)
(She betrayed her team
and completed the hidden mission.)
(She got to deduct 1 year from her
age and another team's member's.)
(And the person So Min chose
to get 1 year deducted was...)
(She picked Suk Jin
without any doubt.)
(So Min chose Suk Jin because he's
the oldest and less threatening.)
- I got my age deducted.
- Oh, yes!
- Exactly one year got deducted.
- Really?
- Exactly one year?
Thanks to So Min and Ji Hyo,
your team was able to deduct
the exact years you had left.
So Min deducted exactly one year
from my age?
- Yes, and your team won.
- That's awesome.
(Team Suk Jin naturally won
thanks to So Min's mistake.)
We won?
I won after a long time.
(Even they're surprised.
Who knew they would win?)
(And Team Ji Hyo heard the news.)
Then... Hang on.
Hang on a second.
Ji Hyo, did you
get all the age deducted?
Two members with the most years left
will get a penalty.
(The oldest two will receive
a penalty.)
Did you see him put on an act?
- This is crazy.
- I saw him. He was smiling.
- I'm the oldest among us.
- I thought we'd win too.
I thought we would win.
Anyway, the youngest three...
on our team won't receive
a penalty, right?
Jong Kook and I are the oldest two.
You're right.
We should've finished the food
more quickly.
(The end of the race and the penalty
will be revealed at the end!)
(And a week later...)
(We haven't seen the makeup team's
tools in a while.)
- Hi, Ji Hyo.
- Hi.
- Hello.
(Ji Hyo still seems half asleep.)
What was it? What should I do?
(She sat in the chair
without any attempt to resist.)
As for that,
- it's kind of...
- Hi, Ji Hyo.
(At that moment,
Kwang Soo showed up!)
(Kwang Soo also seems pretty weird.)
Hi, Kwang Soo.
I totally forgot about this.
- What's going on?
- Are you dressed as Beethoven?
You remind me of "Guardian:
The Lonely and Great God".
You look like Beethoven.
(Why are they getting makeup done
before the shoot?)
(They teamed up and lost 2 weeks ago
in the Jeju Island special episode.)
(And they were chosen as the members
to receive the opening penalty.)
(And today is the day
of their penalty.)
We were told it was a penalty.
- It'll take some time.
- This is how you'll look.
We're going to do this makeup.
- You'll wear a wig.
- We prepared a wig.
Like this.
(Short exclamation)
This is what we're going to do.
We'll only try
the distinguishing features.
We'll do the bright eyebrows,
blush like this,
and heart-shaped lips.
(So Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo started
their makeup for the penalty.)
That makeup suits you.
(The sleepy Angry Bird)
Don't I look like a penguin?
- Will Kwang Soo wear this makeup?
- Yes, the same makeup.
- I'll wear the same makeup?
- Yes.
(He didn't know it until now.)
A man wearing that makeup?
Yes, you'll wear the same makeup.
(Oh, no. I'll wear that makeup too?)
- But...
- You'll look like a musical actor.
We'll make you look good.
I mean...
(I mean... That's not what I meant.)
It's because she's not
wearing a wig.
- She'll look different in a wig.
- She's right.
I don't want to look different.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn
to transform.)
You put on the hairnet
and changed your clothes, right?
(Troubled and bitter)
I'll make you look great.
Because you're not wearing
any base makeup now,
- I'll apply just a little.
- Sure. Go ahead.
(So she started applying
base makeup on his face.)
(And he put on a wig,
which will add elegance.)
Don't I look scary?
(Don't I look scary?)
(Are you sure
this is the right way?)
Oh, gosh.
Did you come from the underworld?
- Are you from the underworld?
- You look so scary.
You look so scary like Annabelle.
Didn't you come from the underworld?
(Even Annabelle is scared...)
(of Kwang Soo's underworld makeup.)
I think I may look better
without that.
People will scream and run away
when they see me.
That's how scary I look right now.
(After an hour of makeup, they'll
perform at the opening ceremony.)
- Are we going to use this umbrella?
- I mean, the level of scariness...
(What performance will
these 2 opera singers give?)
(Everyone else is busy
preparing the opening.)
(The performers from Europe
are standing awkwardly.)
(They don't know what to do.)
I'm so embarrassed because no one
seems to think this is strange.
Ji Hyo looks like a pretty doll.
Why doesn't Kwang Soo?
(You know why.)
Hit us with some extra light.
You look really pretty.
This is driving me crazy.
Will the guests be there too?
- Yes.
Really?
(Really?)
It's so embarrassing that I have to
meet them looking like this.
Hello. Hello.
(He's about to meet the guests
looking like this.)
This is driving me nuts.
I want to go home.
I don't usually feel embarrassed
about things like this.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo feel
unusually embarrassed today.)
- Hello.
(The 1st guest to meet
the performers, Ha Do Kwon)
Hello.
(The 1st guest to meet
the performers, Ha Do Kwon)
(In the drama "The Penthouse",)
(he plays a classical vocal teacher
who bows before the power!)
(The last time
he came on Running Man,)
(I came here to beat
only one person.)
(He challenged Jong Kook
recklessly.)
(His clothes got ripped,
and he only got humiliated!)
(He's back with the other cast
members to redeem himself!)
Hi, Do Kwon.
(We haven't seen each other
in a while.)
- We got a penalty.
- You look...
(But we look so weird right now.)
(Laughing)
(Kwang Soo is lowering his head.)
You guys went to Jeju Island...
and called us here in Paju
when it's so cold.
I like Jeju Island too.
(I like Jeju Island too.)
It was hilarious.
You put her in a headlock
and threw her down.
(He proves that he's a huge fan
of the show.)
Crush them all like you did.
(He's asking her for a favor.)
(He knows so much
about Running Man.)
It was funnier when Jong Kook
threw you down.
Were you all right?
I got acupuncture treatment
for two days. Lying on my belly,
- Really?
- I regretted what I had done.
I don't care about promoting
my drama.
I'll make sure to win today.
(Forget promoting my drama,
I'll make sure to win today.)
(He didn't learn his lesson.
He announced his 2nd challenge.)
Make an appointment at the clinic
for tomorrow.
Since it's my second time here,
I feel more comfortable here...
than on the drama set.
(After greeting Do Kwon
who's like a family to them...)
- And change your clothes...
- Hello.
Hello.
Hi. It's been a while.
- You look pretty.
- This is a penalty.
It doesn't look like a penalty.
(This is her 1st appearance
on a variety show!)
(Lee Ji Ah, the queen of
the penthouse on the 100th floor!)
(She goes back and forth between
her sweetness and intensity.)
(From the national fairy
to a mom with great mother's love!)
(Eugene makes the viewers cry!)
(She got a role as an evil
character after 20 years.)
(And she's pulling it off.
Kim So Yeon, the heartless woman!)
(The cast members of "The Penthouse"
came on Running Man!)
- Hey, you look so pretty.
- I don't know...
So Yeon, you're teasing me, right?
No, I'm not. I mean it.
You really look great in that.
I think you look pretty.
You look gorgeous.
I want to try this too.
(Oh, my!)
I think they really mean it.
- They started the shoot out there.
- Oh, I see.
It's good to see you again.
The guests will go out first.
I'm nervous.
Me too.
(The 4 special guests
who are a little bit nervous...)
(and the calm representatives
get ready to go on stage.)
- What's with your clothes?
- Is this an award ceremony?
I'm so nervous.
I should've taken some pills.
- Should I have taken pills?
- Don't worry, we have Eugene...
and Do Kwon with us.
People from Running Man are crazy.
(What's going on in the hall?)
(The penthouse
briefing session for residency)
It's kind of fancy.
(The penthouse briefing session
seems very luxurious.)
- It's luxurious, isn't it?
- Yes, it is.
- Hello.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you all.
(Well-dressed bidders
have come to the briefing session.)
(Bowing)
- This way.
- Hello.
Join us.
(It seems
he's never done this before.)
- Sebastian, you're here.
- Hello.
I'm not that butler.
- You're not?
- No.
- A son of a wealthy family.
- Aren't you a magician?
- No, I'm from a wealthy family.
- Are you two a team?
Can you make a pigeon appear?
- Yes.
- Here it is.
(A wealthy boy's magic show)
Are you going to...
Are you going to
saw this woman in half?
- Yes, he is.
- I'll cut her in half with a saw.
(While the two in velvet
make a joke...)
When I walked in here,
I almost did a perfect bow
to one of us.
- Why?
- I thought he was Im Ha Ryong.
I thought he was Im Ha Ryong.
(Possessed by Ha Ryong's spirit)
Come on. Hey.
How could you mistake me for him?
- We look totally different.
- You two look the same.
- We look completely different.
- My goodness.
- Come on.
- He didn't look like him at first.
But these days,
he looks so much like Ha Ryong.
This is so funny.
You are the VIPs who want to get
into the penthouse and that's why...
- you came to the briefing session.
- All right.
We prepared an opening
performance for you.
- Is that so?
- Really?
Should we stand over there?
(Can't be sure which country or era
they are from.)
(But the delegation is ready
to congratulate the opening.)
It's the opening performance
for the penthouse briefing session.
- So it's the opening performance.
- I love to be entertained.
It's a briefing session.
- So are we rich?
- Look at the spotlight.
- I guess we are rich.
- They're treating us this well?
What is it?
(The curtain opens.)
My goodness.
(So elegant)
(What is this?)
- What's this?
- What is this?
- What's that?
This is just like Hurricane Blue.
- What is this?
- What's this?
(It's a high-quality performance
for the VIPs, not a costume show.)
What on earth is this?
- My goodness.
- Gosh, what's this?
So they're going to sing a song?
Look at Kwang Soo's lips.
(His awkward shoulder dance)
This is not exactly a penalty
for Jo Hyo.
You look so pretty.
Ji Hyo, you're so pretty.
- You look like a doll.
- Yes, she is.
- It's not a penalty for her.
- She looks so pretty.
(While everyone
is paying attention...)
He didn't practice at all.
He doesn't know the lyrics.
His lips don't match.
- Gosh, he's bad at this.
- His lips don't match.
Seems like the lyrics don't match.
It's just like Hurricane Blue.
Hello, Lee Yoon Seok.
He's imitating Yoon Seok?
He's imitating Mozart.
(What a horrible performance?)
- Don't you think they're good?
- They are good.
She looks like a Russian doll.
(Soon after,
Jo Hyo does her solo part.)
She's like a Russian doll.
(She competes with her looks
not with her singing skills.)
She doesn't know the lyrics either.
She didn't practice either.
Her lips should be vibrating.
Make it vibrate.
Vibrate!
They should be vibrating.
That's it.
- That's it, that's it.
- Yes, she's doing great.
(They've been ignoring Kwang Soo
for the last five minutes.)
That's it. She's good.
So cute.
(It's a lip-synced performance
but it's pretty perfect.)
She's good.
(Kwang Soo, what are you doing?)
(He missed a beat.)
No, no, he missed it.
My goodness, what is he doing?
(It's getting closer to the climax.)
(Performing madness)
(An unprepared delegation
does its best on the stage.)
My goodness.
(An unprepared delegation
does its best on the stage.)
(Finishes the performance
with burning passion!)
Ole!
(Overaggressive stage manners
for the poor quality performance)
Ole!
It's kind of fun.
Don't they both
look better than usual?
- Yes.
- They look better.
- Yes, the makeup.
- Ji Hyo, you look great.
- Wait a minute.
- Ji Hyo looks great.
Ji Hyo, you look great.
Wait a minute.
- You're so pretty.
- Stop talking about her.
- You look good too.
- Yes, you do.
But Ji Hyo really looks nice.
- It suits you.
- Everyone is saying she's pretty.
You're all saying,
"Ji Hyo, you look great."
Kwang Soo, you look
like a dead person.
- What?
- It's like a dead person's face.
A dead person?
He's back from the dead.
Were you trying to
make him look like Jiangshi?
- Jiangshi?
- Is he from "Surprise Mystery TV"?
Isn't he Jiangshi?
He's from "Surprise Mystery TV"?
It's for an opera.
- Were you imitating Han Gi Beom?
- What are you talking about?
- Stand closer.
- This is so funny.
You look better wearing makeup.
Yes, but it really suits Jo Hyo.
I got it.
Jo Hyo really looks nice.
So are we rich people?
- Are we moving into the penthouse?
- Yes, you are rich.
The guests at the backstage are...
- Stop talking, Kwang Soo.
- I should make an introduction.
I should make an introduction.
I don't think so.
You don't have to.
- What are you saying?
- Your timing was wrong.
- Stay quiet, Jiangshi.
- Yes, be quiet.
- Jiangshi.
- He's not even human.
Like I said, all eight of you
are VIPs who came to...
the briefing session
of the penthouse.
Yes, finally.
And some VIPs will join you.
- I can hear them talking.
- Yes.
They're the real VIPs.
I'm sure.
I should enjoy this.
No, no.
Should we make a cool appearance?
- A cool appearance?
- Yes, like this.
Here are the other bidders.
Please come out.
(Leading actors of "The Penthouse")
(Ha Do Kwon, Kim So Yeon,
Lee Ji Ah, and Eugene)
Eugene.
- Ji Ah.
- It's been a long time.
(Good to see you!)
- Hello.
- My goodness.
It's been a long time.
Hello, Do Kwon.
Hey, So Yeon.
- Do Kwon's here with us again.
- Hello.
- Do Kwon.
Do Kwon, are you okay now?
- Jong Kook attacked you before.
- Why are you here again?
- Are you okay?
- Have you been working out?
- Of course.
- Gosh, I can see that.
- Do Kwon, it's good to see you.
- You look great today.
Yes, you look good.
All right. These are the leading
actors of "The Penthouse".
- Please welcome them.
- Hello.
The drama is so hot right now.
- Yes, it is.
- It's hot.
It's very popular.
The story is so interesting
that you can't wait to see the next.
You're so right.
- The development of the plot is...
- Yes, it's so fast.
- Fast enough to draw attention.
- Yes, starting with Eugene.
Why don't you
introduce yourselves for us?
Hello, everyone.
It's been a long time
since I appeared on TV shows.
- So I'm very excited.
- All right.
- She's a fairy.
- It's been a long time.
I'm playing Oh Yoon Hee
on "The Penthouse".
- Yes, welcome!
- Welcome, Yoon Hee!
Yoon Hee!
- All right.
- Yoon Hee.
- I think for Eugene...
- Yes.
this is her first appearance
on Running Man.
- Yes.
- Really?
I didn't know at first.
- But it's her first time.
- I know.
I've never seen
so many cameras in front of me.
There's a reason why
we have so many cameras.
It's because we like to show off.
Yes, we're pretentious.
- Some of them don't even work.
- Yes, he's right.
Four of them don't even work.
- No red lights on some of them.
- Yes.
They're phony cameras.
We also have dolls.
But you know what?
- I've seen her on TV shows.
- Yes.
But I've never met her
in person for the filming.
- Lee Ji Ah is here with us.
- Hello.
Hello.
You don't appear
on variety shows, do you?
No, that's why it's my first time
seeing most of you in person.
- She's right.
- Yes.
- So she's so nervous.
- Yes, I am.
- She's never been on variety shows.
- You're right.
This is your first variety show,
isn't it?
Do you usually enjoy
watching Running Man?
(Do you usually enjoy
watching Running Man?)
(Well...)
No, she doesn't.
(No, she doesn't.)
- Just stay quiet.
- Give her a second.
You should stay quiet.
Can't you guess that?
- You don't watch "The Penthouse".
- I do watch it.
You do? What's it about?
Veiled enmity and jealousy
of the rich.
That's not it.
- It's not?
- It's not about that.
- Veiled enmity and jealousy.
- Maybe you've watched the middle.
They're fighting
to get into the penthouse.
- Isn't that right?
- No, not really.
I guess he read the plot on Naver.
People must've given you advice
on what to do on our show.
What did they say?
They just told me to be myself.
- But...
- Okay, who told you that?
My agency and my friends.
But it's really hard to be myself.
You're right.
People tell you to be yourself.
- Well...
- But it's hard.
I think I need
some time to get used to this.
But when you get used to it...
- Then the filming ends.
- Then I say, "See you next week!"
So you should try
to get used to it faster.
- All right?
- Okay.
I bet she prepared something
to show us her talent.
Show my talent?
- Gosh.
- She's more nervous.
We won't force you.
- We did that in the old days.
- She'll pass out.
So we've talked to Ji Ah.
Now let's talk to So Yeon.
You were on our show before, right?
- No, this is my first time.
- Gosh, it's her first.
- It the first for all three.
- Right.
Yes, this is the first time
on our show for all three of you.
My niece's biggest wish is for
her aunt to appear on Running Man.
Really?
I mentioned it
in my interviews as well.
And she turns 20 next year.
Already?
- How long has it been then?
- I thought, "It's been too long."
So she thought of it first
when she was 10.
Yes, her wish came true in 10 years.
Her dream has come true.
- Yes.
- Many of you won't know this...
- but we have many young fans.
- Yes, it's true.
- Yes, we do.
- Children love our show.
So Yeon, you're playing
the villain on "The Penthouse".
Yes, I am.
Is it your first time
playing the villain?
This is my second. I played
the villain about 20 years ago...
on "All About Eve".
(Courtesy of MBC)
You're incredible.
If you're worried about Woo Jin,
you should go to London.
I grew up watching that show.
- I loved it.
- It was popular.
So you were a young fan
of "All About Eve"?
Yes, of course, I was.
She was an announcer on the show.
Yes, you're right.
(Making a fuss)
She must be so happy.
- This is so exciting.
- Good for you.
You haven't changed a bit.
- Ji Ah.
- Yes.
Why did you laugh...
after watching them
make a fuss about it?
Well, I'm just getting used to it.
- You're getting what?
- I'm getting used to it.
- To our reaction.
- So you're learning how to react?
You can learn
a lot from their reaction.
That's how you react when you're
surprised or glad to meet someone.
She was on "All About Eve".
How would you react?
(Making a fuss)
- I'm a big fan.
- They're here.
I loved your drama.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
I'm such a huge fan.
- All right.
- This is how you should react.
This is what we do.
We'd like you to make a fuss.
"All About Eve"?
("All About Eve"?)
- That's just too much.
- You went too far.
That's ridiculous.
- Oh, okay.
- Kwang Soo.
I just gave them an example.
I was excited
and surprised to see you.
- He passed out.
- That was funny.
That's too much though.
That's just what he does.
He has his own universe.
As you were saying, in the drama...
- you play...
- In the drama,
I'm the head of the art department
at Cheong A Arts High School.
- The head of art department.
- And I'm a famous soprano.
I have everything,
but I always lose to Oh Yoon Hee...
- who's standing right here...
- She gets in your way.
- at critical moments.
- I see.
So I have
an inferiority complex and...
It's just that
she's not good enough.
(Sulky)
They are having a war
of nerves even here.
It was funny when So Yeon did this.
She couldn't deny it,
so she was just...
(She uses her whole body
to express her feelings.)
You know what I mean.
That was funny.
Oh, okay. I did it.
- They are so into their characters.
- She thinks she's better.
Honestly, we are totally
absorbed in our characters now.
I can see that.
She was shooting the drama
until early this morning.
And these two...
- haven't slept for days.
- What about you, Do Kwon?
- I bet he had a sound sleep.
- I had a good sleep.
(I had a good sleep.)
He seems to be in the best shape.
- I can see that.
- He's the only one who looks good.
- He's ready to face Jong Kook.
- I want to run fast...
- since this is "Running Man".
- Ji Ah said...
you're the only one
who looks good today.
- He's in good condition.
- You look nice today.
Your face is glowing.
He had a good sleep.
- Do Kwon is like my soulmate.
- He's finally here.
Do Kwon, were you okay
when you joined our show last time?
You said you came
to catch Jong Kook,
but you just got humiliated.
I got treated with
acupuncture for two days.
I had the bee sting therapy
and cupping treatment.
- It must've been bad.
- You got cupping treatment?
- Yes.
- And you posted...
- some photos on your social media.
- Really?
After the show was aired,
- he posted a review.
- He posted a review.
- This is what he wrote.
- He also added a message.
"I went to shoot "Running Man" with
Kang Doo Ki's uniform yesterday."
It's like his diary.
- I can't read it all.
- It's a diary.
It says "face-to-face
confrontation".
He says he lost the face-to-face
confrontation with Jong Kook.
(Flustered)
It's like his essay.
Do Kwon, this is too long. And
there's no substance in the story.
It says "face-to-face
confrontation".
This is too long.
The point is...
that I should've avoided
the confrontation with Jong Kook.
- I see.
- It's like a little kid's diary.
This is how Do Kwon looks
in the drama.
That's how he looks.
- He's a music teacher in the drama.
- Right.
He looks like Beethoven.
- He's a teacher. But he ran away.
- Tell us about your part.
I'm a vocal teacher.
- He majored in voice.
- Right.
And my character is
a kiss up, kick down.
- What?
- I'm polite to superiors...
and harsh on subordinates.
I'm a teacher like that.
How would you compare it
with your personality?
It fits me well.
(He's a kiss up,
kick down for real.)
What did I tell you?
That was neat.
- He's honest.
- Right.
That's why
your acting was so natural.
- Exactly.
- Anyway,
thank you all for joining us
despite your busy schedule.
- The drama isn't over yet.
- Right. They're still shooting it.
So they have no time to rest.
How is your new movie,
The Pirates" going?
- It's going well.
- Actually,
- he's shooting summer scenes.
- Right.
But it's winter now.
It's been put off a little.
- Oh, no.
- That's why your cheeks are red.
- What?
- Because it's cold.
- This is because it's cold?
- Oh, dear.
- I bet he's cold now.
- I feel bad for him.
- Did you get frostbite?
- No.
It looks like frostbite.
And you have age spots here.
- Stop that.
- It's a mole.
- Is it a mole?
- Age spots?
All right.
Today's race is called
Recruiting Penthouse Race.
You will be playing one on one.
Okay. Today is the day.
The penthouse...
- Suk Jin, stop that.
- Stop being silly.
- What's wrong with you?
- What?
They will have a hard time
editing the video. Don't do that.
- I just...
- You can't just say anything...
- because you're paid.
- That's not it.
- I just can't stay quiet.
- He's like a parrot.
- Should I stay quiet?
- Stop it.
My goodness.
Suk Jin, I'll see you in jail.
(He talks a lot, but he doesn't
understand the rules well.)
You will be playing
an individual race today.
The first four people who make it
to the penthouse...
will be the winners.
- 4 people.
- There will be 4 winners.
- 4 people?
- What? 4 people?
It's first come, first served.
- The four of us should win.
- Exactly.
The 4 winners will get a prize
and the other 8 will get a penalty.
During the race, the mission fund
is very important.
You will soon go through
missions in each round...
and be divided into two groups
of six, top club and bottom club.
And those in the top club...
will get twice the money the bottom
club gets from each mission.
It will make a big difference.
So you should make it
to the top group...
- and save as much money as you can.
- I have to be in the top club.
You can also increase
your mission fund...
at the gathering of each club,
so you should try
to take advantage of it.
(There will be 4 winners,
and the rest 8 will get a penalty.)
We will start the mission
once you get changed.
- Okay.
- All right.
Let's go get changed.
(Who will be the 4 winners
of this race?)
(They get changed
and move to the mission spot.)
I like your eyebrows.
Thank you.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are
still wearing the makeup.)
It was so funny when you lip-synced.
- You were very good.
- You did it well.
- Kwang Soo was terrible at first.
- He was bad.
- It was strange.
- At the last moment,
he just kept opening his mouth.
(Groaning)
(He grabbed Se Chan
by the collar.)
(Upset)
Wasn't it funny when he did this?
He was like this.
Because of what you said...
It was totally out of sync
because of that.
You should've done this too.
- Everyone.
- Yes.
Now you will go through a mission...
to be divided into the top club
and the bottom club.
- Okay.
- This is important.
The members of the top club
and the bottom club...
will be treated and paid
differently during the race.
I see.
Gosh, this is very important.
I have to be in the top club
no matter what.
- I have to make it to the top club.
- We'll be in the top club for sure.
Of course.
I can see who is
not going to make it.
- What are you talking about?
- You are divided already.
Don't say that.
They're standing together.
There will be three missions.
And the male and female
winners of each mission...
will join the top club.
So there will be
six winners in total.
- I see.
- It will be hard.
Here's the first mission.
It's about strength.
- Oh dear.
- My gosh.
(The weak members are
disappointed to hear that.)
Look at Do Kwon.
- Do Kwon seems confident.
- Why are you nodding your head?
- This is a face-off battle.
- He's worked out for this moment.
It's a face-off battle.
What the male members
are competing in is...
the traditional wrestling
of Cumberland, England.
- Wrestling?
- What? Wrestling?
It's a match between
two male members.
They will embrace each other
crossing their arms.
The person who throws his opponent
to the ground wins the game.
It's like ssireum
and wrestling combined.
- This is a little...
- My gosh.
To make it to the top club...
Do Kwon is taking off his jacket.
Do Kwon is...
If you win this match,
you will join the top club
right away.
That sounds great.
Let's go to the top club!
I might be able to win
if I'm lucky with my opponents.
I'm seven.
- I'm five.
- Okay.
- I'm number 1.
- He's number 1.
Okay!
- Number 4.
- I'm number 2.
First, it's Jong Kook
versus Se Chan.
We don't know it yet.
What do you not know?
His girlfriend is rooting for him.
Gosh, stop it.
- Se Chan is strong.
- Hey.
- Are they really dating?
- No.
No? Is it a joke?
- What is So Min doing?
- So Min, wait.
Your girlfriend is rooting for you.
Are you his girlfriend?
(No, I'm not.)
(I'm just working.)
- Like this?
- That's right.
- He should give up.
- Like this?
- Hang on.
- Hold your hands like this.
- Are we doing ssireum like this?
If your upper body touches
the ground, you lose.
You should just lie down.
Ready.
Everyone seems nervous.
Start.
Gosh, stop that.
(Interesting)
Keep your back straight.
- Keep your back straight.
- My goodness.
(After checking up on him,
Jong Kook presses him right away.)
(But Se Chan is holding out.)
My goodness.
(While everyone is watching it
with interest,)
(Do Kwon analyze Jong Kook's moves
with his hawk eyes.)
Can I adjust my grip
during the match?
If you try to hold out,
you might break your back.
Your girlfriend is about to cry.
Oh dear.
(Sad)
Look. She's acting.
(Plopping down)
This is the movie, "Rocky"
(The capitalist couple is
always ready to act.)
(She forces herself to cry
with exaggerated gestures.)
This is crazy.
This is like a scene
from the movie, "Rocky".
- Se Chan, So Min is crying.
- Se Chan!
He wants to show something
to his girlfriend.
- Gosh.
- Good.
(As he sees his girlfriend cry,
he exposes his gums.)
Good.
(But he eventually caved in.)
(You tried hard.)
So how was it?
You held out for quite long though.
- You did well.
- You lost, but you did well.
I exhausted him a little.
It's not like that.
He just fought and lost.
He fought and lost.
He fought but lost.
- He just lost.
- He fought and lost
- Jong Kook.
- Se Chan is strong though.
(Do Kwon just reflects upon
Jong Kook's moves without laughing.)
- It's me and Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
This is meaningless though.
This is a big match.
If I win, I will have to fight
against Jong Kook.
It's okay. I'll beat you up
and fight against Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- He's wearing cotton pants.
Suk Jin works out a lot.
Gosh, his torso is...
His torso is quite thick.
Suk Jin is vigorous
in spite of his old age.
- In spite of his age?
- Don't say that.
- Ready.
- He has a big torso.
Start.
Push him hard.
(Round 2 starts.)
Gosh, it hurts.
(Groaning)
(They're loud,
but they are not moving at all.)
(It looks more like a free hug.)
What kind of fight is so loose?
- Come here.
- It hurts.
(Not an ounce of strength
can be felt.)
They're both squeezing
with all their might.
Why are you only hugging each other?
Hold on.
(Thud)
Did you seriously just hit me there?
(For the first time,
the game gets interesting.)
(He fights back.)
(That hurts...)
(He stumbles across
a viable attack.)
Hold on a second.
Wait.
- You can't use your legs.
- Wait.
But he hit me first.
- You can't kick him.
- He kicked me first.
This isn't how the game should be.
- Isn't this cheating?
- You shouldn't kick.
I'm sorry about that,
but he kicked me first.
You've been given a yellow card.
- You'll go again.
- Can't you use your legs at all?
- Hold on.
- So how do you knock someone back?
Ji Ah...
Ji Ah seems exhausted.
(Spacing out)
She's already tired.
- Ji Ah...
- She's already exhausted.
I can't forget the look on her face.
Have you never seen
anything like this before?
Is it new to you?
This is how we have fun.
What's with that face?
I'm sorry, guys.
I mean...
These are the games we usually play.
Living in a penthouse doesn't mean
you can look down on us.
Suk Jin, come on.
Stop playing dirty, all right?
- You're the dirty one here.
- This is hilarious.
- Ready, set, go.
- Let's do this!
Suk Jin...
Suk Jin doesn't have
any strength left.
- What on earth?
- Jae Suk's...
(Jae Suk seizes the opportunity
to win easily.)
What on earth?
(The lackluster game
ended with no takeaway.)
That would be worth
a full point in judo.
Nicely done.
You drained a lot of his strength.
Are you all right?
- Get lost.
- You drained his strength.
That's the key at the moment.
Nicely done.
What a good game, Suk Jin.
Okay!
It's Ha versus Ha next.
Haha, show him what you've got.
- Don't let him win easily.
- Do Kwon must win to save face.
Your son Dream is watching.
- Grab each other.
- There's a huge size difference.
Wait, where's So Yeon?
- Hold on a second. Wait.
- He's no joke, right?
You won't believe how strong he is.
(Let's see what Do Kwon
has to offer.)
- Ready...
- Distract him.
Hold on a second.
- I doubt...
- Hold on a second.
Wait.
(Do Kwon takes the lead
the moment the game begins.)
Do Kwon, hold on a second.
- Do Kwon's determined.
- Do Kwon, wait.
- Do Kwon...
- You really should calm down.
- Calm down.
- Calm down a bit.
Get out of my way.
(Don't interrupt me!)
(Jong Kook Hunter can't be stopped.)
- Do Kwon!
- I'll just say I'm sorry.
- Calm down for a second.
- I'm fine!
- He's seeing red.
- What's with you?
Hold on.
Okay, fine. We'll say you won.
- He's seeing red.
- What's with you?
(He unleashes his full power.)
(Groaning in pain)
(Like we expected, Do Kwon wins.)
- You...
- Unbelievable.
- Do Kwon...
- Haha, are you all right?
- I saw your eyes flip.
- Haha isn't that weak, you know.
Do Kwon's no joke.
You should've done it
like me and Suk Jin.
This is how I was trained to be.
- His lips are drained of blood.
- My gosh.
Partner,
- crush him.
- Got it.
(I'm amazed.)
I'm looking for payback today.
Kwang Soo advanced by a default win.
Why don't we start
with Do Kwon and Kwang Soo?
Okay, Do Kwon and Kwang Soo.
- This...
- It can go either way.
This sounds like fun.
This is hard to tell.
Haha, it's hard to tell.
- I'll root for the Ha family.
- Kwang Soo isn't weak,
and he also plays dirty.
He plays dirty?
(No one expects this
to be a clean game.)
- He's really strong.
- Wrap it up on your end.
He's really tall though.
Hold on.
(Kwang Soo presses his chin down.)
He's pressing with his chin.
(The game begins
with Kwang Soo cheating.)
Nice.
Kwang Soo...
Are you kidding me?
What's the matter with him?
I said he wasn't an easy opponent.
(The match was dead serious.)
Before I could even...
Do Kwon, why are you
taking this so seriously?
This isn't wrestling!
This is supposed
to be a variety show.
This isn't the Olympics, you know!
- Unbelievable.
- Are you kidding me?
- He only has one goal today.
- Tell me about it.
Are you all right?
He didn't complain about
my chin attack and sent me flying.
- What on earth was that?
- You did well.
- Do Kwon's strong.
- What did I tell you?
He's really strong.
Kwang Soo's not an easy opponent.
(All I'm after is Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook, just you wait.)
He's looking at Jong Kook.
- He came determined today.
- Do Kwon...
He must've counted his days.
- Okay, come on.
- Don't I know it.
Jong Kook has to beat me first.
- What?
- He has to beat me first.
- Just quickly lie down.
- He has to...
- Why don't we...
film how it'll end first?
- With him on the ground first.
- Like this?
- You never know.
- I call three seconds.
- Are you ready?
- Ready...
Go!
(Darn it...)
- Just stay lying down.
- As gently as possible.
So that you won't get hurt.
- He fought and lost!
- You were gently put down.
- It's over.
- Did something even happen?
- You fought and lost.
- Jae Suk...
- I fought and lost.
- Yes, you did!
You fought and lost.
- You fought and lost.
- That I did.
You lost completely.
You fought and lost.
(Is it my turn now?)
- It's now the finals.
- The finals.
The final match.
- Do Kwon, come forward.
- He has awaited this moment.
Finally, Do Kwon...
Do Kwon...
(He took all games seriously
so that he could take on Jong Kook.)
But...
(Jong Kook, I'm back.)
(During episode 515,
he swore to bring Jong Kook down.)
(And then the two
went head-to-head.)
(Do Kwon fought
until his clothes got ripped.)
(During their first match,
he suffered a humiliating loss.)
(He internalized his rage
and came back to win.)
(Even before rage took over,
he scanned Jong Kook's play style.)
(I've waited for this day,
Jong Kook.)
(Do Kwon gets a chance
to seek revenge.)
- Which side?
- He's dead serious.
- What's more comfortable?
- He really wants to win.
- Whatever's comfortable for you.
- I'm good either way.
- Same here.
- How about this then?
Either way is fine.
It's almost intimidating.
Jong Kook...
Do Kwon's just as big as Jong Kook.
Look. Do Kwon's in it to win it.
I know.
(Everyone holds their breaths
to watch the big match.)
(Will Do Kwon get his revenge?)
Be careful.
It'll be different this time.
The legs...
(Do Kwon attacks first.)
(But Jong Kook won't budge.)
Don't use your legs.
Just the upper body.
(They are equally powerful.)
(But right then...)
(The two fall at the same time.)
(Who will be the winner?)
(Do Kwon's back
touch the ground first.)
Jong Kook wins.
(Jong Kook twisted his torso
so that Do Kwon's back...)
(touched the floor first.)
- Jong Kook wins.
Do Kwon's face was pressed hard.
Do Kwon's face was pressed hard!
His face was pressed into the floor.
Are you all right?
Serves you right for taking him on.
You lost again.
- Are you all right?
- We rooted for you.
(He worked out for nothing.)
- You...
- He grabbed the back of his head.
He's now sulking again.
(Sulking)
He sulks every time he loses.
- He just can't win.
- Do Kwon...
- He's now in tears.
- Look at Jong Kook, will you?
- He might call his mom.
- It's just a game, you know.
- And so the winner...
- So much for working out.
is Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook makes it
to the top club.)
We'll now begin the ladies' match.
The game is pull-up bar wrestling.
(The ladies will compete
in a pull-up bar wrestling.)
You will hang from the bar
and knock down...
your opponent to win.
This won't be easy.
So Yeon and Eugene,
haven't you done this before
on other variety shows?
- I don't think I have.
- I see.
Then you'll get your chance today.
(Firmly)
Ji Ah.
I...
Number five gets an advantage.
(Ji Ah heads straight
to the semi-finals.)
Nice, I want number five.
Eugene, let's check your number.
- Number 2.
- I chose number one.
- Then it's you and Eugene.
So Min and Ji Hyo
will also go head-to-head.
- We chose 3 and 4.
- Okay.
Show them the strength
of the Running Man ladies.
(Tournament Bracket)
- So Yeon, head on up.
- Oh, dear.
We'll help.
The rivals go head-to-head.
- You're right.
- Their characters are rivals.
- I got this.
- There you go.
(Eugene sets the tone of the match.)
(She said she hasn't tried
anything like this before.)
(The prima donna of pull-up bars)
You...
She's on the athletic side.
You should hold
the mattress for her.
How...
- Did I get up here too soon?
- I think you did.
Eugene, I'm sorry.
I'll pick up the pace.
- Sorry about this.
- No, it's fine.
So Yeon...
(Dangling)
- Hold on.
- What on earth was that?
So Yeon, please.
What on earth was that?
- We can't even begin the game.
- Are you kidding me?
Can I just advance
to the next round?
- Let me advance.
- The game's as good as over.
- But...
- Eugene wins!
No, please get back up there.
Oh, dear.
I'll get up there first,
so stay here and relax.
- She offered to go up first.
- I truly believe that So Yeon...
should be on variety shows.
- She...
- She's hilarious.
- She really is.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Of course, I do.
- She's so sweet.
- Now...
- She's kind-hearted.
- That's it.
- Eugene, go ahead.
- She's up there.
- She made it up there.
So Yeon's hilarious.
- Okay, good.
- She's up there.
(Meanwhile, without any help...)
I feel like it's already over.
- Eugene's incredible.
- It's already over.
Be careful.
It's already over.
- She can't move.
- It's over.
It's already over.
(The fluttering of her foot
makes no difference.)
- Just go for her legs.
- So Yeon's about to give up.
(So Yeon's about to give up.)
(Eugene is still relaxed.)
(No one knows how So Yeon feels
better than So Min.)
- Eugene...
- It's already over.
So Yeon's about to give up.
(So Yeon drops without
being able to hold for a minute.)
(Eugene wins
with the perfect stance.)
You were like a monkey!
- A monkey.
- Are you all right?
- How nimble of you.
- All you did was hang there.
So Yeon, what happened?
Did you win? Congratulations.
(Did you win? Congratulations.)
- What did you just say?
- Of course, she won.
So Yeon asked if Eugene won.
Congratulations.
Why would you congratulate her?
(After losing,
she congratulates Eugene.)
What just happened?
So Yeon is quite peculiar.
- So Yeon is really funny.
- She's always been like this.
She's doing a great job
on the variety show.
- I can see that.
- Yes.
She couldn't beat her in real life
just like in the drama.
Right.
She can never beat her.
So Yeon does a lot of things
like that.
You know what I mean, right?
She keeps losing.
She makes gestures like this
when she reacts.
She often reacts excessively.
- Just like Americans do.
- Yes.
(Her Hollywood style reactions
seemed unusual from the opening.)
That's so funny.
Are you still laughing?
- She's the queen of reaction.
- Right?
- That was so funny.
She always makes three gestures
in a row.
(It's at least
a triple combination.)
It's so hilarious.
Ji Hyo versus Ji Ah.
- Ji Hyo, step on it first.
- Ji Hyo versus Ji Ah.
- I'm excited.
- After I...
- After I go up?
- Ji Ah, please come forward.
I don't think I can do this.
I'm worried.
Ji Hyo, you and Kwang Soo must win.
- Ji Ah... Ji Ah.
- Yes?
- I have a question for you.
- It won't be easy.
Have you ever done anything
like this?
Never.
When was the last time you did it?
Did you do it when you were a kid?
- She must've tried hanging...
- Kids rarely do this.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- Not many kids do this.
- Do they play dodge ball?
- I've never tried this before.
- Dodge ball?
But I think she's quite strong.
Really? Then we never know.
Let's find out.
She may be quite strong,
but Ji Hyo is extremely strong.
It'd be so funny if she did
a great job on the bar.
She would move like this.
- "Bring it on!"
- Like this.
(Making a fuss)
(Teasing a guest is
the most fun thing to do.)
I don't know. I already feel dizzy.
- Please step up on the mat.
- He never misses a chance.
(They can't stop themselves
from teasing their guests.)
- How should I do this?
- Put your foot on this.
Do you need any help?
Or can you do it by yourself?
Step on it. I'll help you.
- You should pull it a little.
- Gosh.
- Seriously.
- Go, Shim Su Ryeon!
Put your leg over the bar.
- How should I do this?
- That's right.
- Pardon?
- How should I put my legs over it?
- Like a barbecue...
- Like a chicken over the fire.
- We'll support you under here.
- Right.
Gosh, seriously.
- 1, 2...
- This is so annoying, right?
(Cheeky)
It's annoying, right?
(As she sighed unintentionally,)
(Jae Suk read her mind.)
(Maybe Jae Suk was right
seeing that she burst out laughing.)
I know how that feels.
- I know how that feels.
- I know that too.
- You know, right?
- Yes.
- "Why did my agency accept..."
- "Why..."
"the invitation from this show?"
- "I'm so annoyed."
- "Gosh, this is so annoying."
When will you get to do
something like this?
- Where else could you try this?
- "Gosh."
"Gosh, seriously."
- Can you see right through me?
- Yes, I can.
I'm so excited about this match.
Ji Ah, come on.
Wrap your legs around the bar
like this.
- We'll lift your legs.
- Help her out.
- I have no idea.
- It's okay.
- Step on here.
- Step on his shoulder.
- But I can't...
- Step on my shoulder.
Step on my shoulder.
- We'll lift your legs.
- Good.
- Ji Hyo seems so relaxed.
- Like that.
- Done.
- Done. She's ready now.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Okay.
- Good.
- She's ready.
- Ready.
- You can start now.
- I think...
- You never know.
- Gosh. What do I do?
- Ji Ah.
- Yes?
- Well...
- You never know.
You should push her.
Push her, Ji Ah.
(As Jae Suk advised her
to push Ji Hyo...)
Push the black socks off the bar.
- That's good.
- Push her legs off the bar,
and you'll win. That's good.
(Surprised)
- Just push... That's good.
- Ji Ah seems really strong.
- Ji Ah.
- We can't predict the result.
- She's so strong.
- The black socks.
- Ji Hyo shows no mercy.
- My goodness.
(But her opponent is
the merciless Ji Hyo.)
Oh, her leg fell off.
What should I do?
(She got the hang of
hanging from the bar.)
- No!
- Ji Hyo is amazing.
- Push her other leg off the bar.
- I'm impressed.
- Ji Hyo is laughing.
- Ji Ah.
- You can do it!
- She's very strong.
- Push her leg off the bar.
- Oh, my.
Oh, no. Ji Hyo used up
all her energy.
Ji Ah seems as strong as Ji Hyo.
(Ji Ah seems unexpectedly strong.)
Gosh.
- Goodness.
- That's good.
- My gosh.
- Ji Ah.
Keep going.
Gosh. I'm running out of energy.
They could win just by hanging there
without falling.
She's so strong.
(The unexpected tight match
made everyone's jaw drop.)
Wrap your arm around it.
That's good.
You're doing great.
Here she goes.
(Ji Ah started pushing her
with all her might.)
I don't know who's going to win.
This is so fun to watch.
She's doing well
when Ji Hyo is really strong.
Ji Hyo is amazing,
- Ji Hyo won't let her win easily.
- and Ji Ah is amazing too.
- She's really strong.
- Awesome.
(Is she the Ji Ah we know?)
- They're both really strong.
- Look at them.
Ji Ah,
since you're hanging there,
you don't want to lose, right?
(You're right.
I don't want to lose.)
We know...
"This is annoying,
but I want to do my best."
It's hard to give up
although it's annoying.
- You'll win if you hold out long.
- Even though it's annoying...
It's because she's competitive.
(Her arms and legs feel weak
because she's laughing.)
You're almost there. No!
(Ji Ah who has been doing well
lost!)
Ji Ah.
- They're both strong.
- You're almost there. No!
Ji Ah.
(She's expressing her disappointment
with her entire body.)
Are you all right?
Are you all right, Ji Ah?
No.
Please give them some water.
- Water, please.
- Eugene will be at an advantage.
- She ran out of energy.
- By the way,
I find Ji Ah...
- so cool...
- Yes.
because she never lies.
She said no
when I asked if she was okay.
(The variety show rookie is
honest at every moment.)
I think she's overwhelmed
because she hung for so long.
Ji Ah, you're very strong too.
She has good endurance too.
- Gosh.
- You're no joke.
Can't I have another sip?
Of course, you can.
(Jae Suk kindly closed the lid.)
(Can't I have another sip?)
Well... Hey, Ji Ah.
(She's drinking water hastily.)
- Why?
- I didn't try to take it from you.
I just gave her the lid,
and she said,
"Can't I have another sip?"
- She's too obsessive.
- I was...
I was just giving you the lid.
I wasn't trying to take the bottle
away from you.
You can take it home.
People working on variety shows
are not that stingy.
- I don't think I can...
- You can take it home.
I can't stand up.
Of course, she's tired.
While Ji Hyo is
recharging her energy...
Does anyone want a match
to get additional mission funds?
- Between guys?
- Yes. It'll be too hard...
- for Ji Hyo to have a match now.
- Additional mission fund?
- Yes, we'll give you extra money.
- We're going to...
- Do Kwon.
- I bet Do Kwon wants another match.
- With Jong Kook?
- Yes.
(Do Kwon has another chance
to get revenge.)
With me? I don't have to accept it.
I'm already in the top club.
Then I'll have a match
with Do Kwon.
- Okay.
- Have a match with Kwang Soo.
You must defeat Kwang Soo...
- before challenging Jong Kook.
- Kwang Soo is good at this.
Kwang Soo is...
I've never lost in any games
using a pull-up bar.
Kwang Soo has never lost
in any pull-up bar games.
- Do Kwon.
You already have children, right?
I had a vasectomy.
Really? Then you have nothing
to worry about.
- Okay.
- "Okay"?
I'll tell you his nickname now.
Assassin on the Pull-up Bar.
I've never lost.
The winner will get
additional mission funds.
- Okay.
- Yes.
(Ha Face-Off
who always fights head-on)
Ready.
(As the whistle was blown,
the assassin started attacking.)
- Goodness gracious.
- Look at that.
(As soon as the match began,
Do Kwon got the advantage.)
Look at that. I knew it.
(But Kwang Soo won't let him win.)
- Oh, my goodness.
- He's getting the drop on him.
- Do Kwon won't give up.
- He's amazing.
Gosh. He's unbelievable.
(Do Kwon pushed his face
with his foot.)
(The underhanded, dirty fight
began more quickly than expected.)
You can do it.
(His feet got on Assassin
on the Pull-up Bar's nerves.)
Kwang Soo won't let him win.
- Kwang Soo is... Oh, boy.
- Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
Oh, boy. Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo started going crazy.)
(A match between the kings
with world views)
(Do Kwon's short jabs?)
(Or Kwang Soo's long punch?)
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo...
My gosh.
(So Yeon is reacting
most excitedly.)
(Kwang Soo went mad as he's
fighting the person he wanted.)
Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo...
(It's complete chaos.)
Here goes the assassin.
Assassin on the Pull-up Bar...
(The time has come. Assassin
on the Pull-up Bar is here.)
(He started executing him
moving his leg like a straw cutter.)
(He's really incredible.)
(This is even more dramatic
than "The Penthouse".)
My goodness.
(Assassin on the Pull-up Bar is now
using his final weapon, his fist.)
(Do Kwon's legs became wobbly
because of his fist attack.)
(Will he become another victim
on a pull-up bar?)
(Ha Face-Off used his arm strength
not to fall.)
Gosh, that's dirty.
(His arm muscles for hunting
Jong Kook are finally shining.)
(Do Kwon's counter-attack)
It's so dirty.
(He's starting the true
head-to-head fight.)
- This is hilarious.
- It's so dirty.
(Assassin on the Pull-up Bar is
screaming out of joy.)
(The 2 mad men won't give an inch.)
- This is crazy.
- My gosh.
This is really...
(Both are running out of energy.)
Do Kwon is doing
as well as Kwang Soo.
Watching this alone is hard.
- This is crazy.
- My gosh.
- They're both incredible.
Do Kwon...
Do Kwon is fighting dirty too.
(Kwang Soo succeeded in
assassinating Do Kwon in the end.)
He's exhausted.
Do Kwon is exhausted.
Look at him.
Look at Do Kwon.
You, dirty punk.
(It was a great match
full of dirty moves.)
You, dirty punk.
Kwang Soo won
additional mission funds.
- Do Kwon, good job.
- You did a great job.
- Good job.
- Assassin on the Pull-up Bar won.
No one can beat him.
Assassin on the Pull-up Bar...
Even Jong Kook can't beat him
on a pull-up bar.
No one can beat him.
Listen, guys.
- He received only 10 dollars.
- What?
(He earned only 10 dollars
for the arduous assassination.)
- 10 dollars.
- It was so hard to win.
- Hey!
- You're like a beggar.
I have 10 dollars.
You can have it.
- Thank you.
- The beggar received money.
Kwang Soo was so enthusiastic
as if there's no tomorrow.
This is how much he loves
Running Man.
This is the happiest moment
of the month.
Kwang Soo, I want to
give you something.
Give him 50 dollars
out of my paycheck.
Jae Suk.
I didn't say that
to get 50 dollars from you.
- It's a token of my affection.
- Give him 100 dollars at least.
- Give him 100 dollars.
- Should I?
I'll give you 100 dollars
out of my paycheck.
What about you?
You won't do anything?
Give Do Kwon 100 dollars
out of my paycheck.
He asked me
if I wouldn't do anything.
- Give him money out of Suk Jin's.
- Great.
Suk Jin doesn't seem happy.
- He might leave the show.
- Then...
I'll have only 200 dollars left.
(You and your jokes.)
(While they were laughing
and making jokes,)
(someone caught Jae Suk's eyes.)
Look at Ji Ah.
(Look at Ji Ah.)
- What?
- You know,
she watched us in an annoyed state.
(She was having a reality check
at a corner.)
- No, no.
- That was hilarious.
That was hilarious.
(Everyone wants to tease Ji Ah
as she is new to variety shows.)
- This is how we live.
- You should witness it.
Ji Ah, this is how we live.
We have lived this way
for over 10 years.
I am having so much fun.
- I am having so much fun.
- This is fun.
Ji Ah, you don't need to be sorry.
We are really happy
that you visited the show.
- That's right.
- This is fun.
You are showing the reactions
we never give.
- Seriously.
- Her reactions are so unique.
I am laughing so much
thanks to you, Ji Ah.
Shouldn't Do Kwon go home now?
- Are you okay?
- He used up his energy.
- Do Kwon.
- His face turned pale.
His face turned pale.
- Look at his lips.
- He should go home.
A face-off.
- Are you okay?
- A face-off.
We should face him Face-Off.
Face-Off.
- Ha Face-Off.
They had a face-off.
Ha Face-Off.
Now, it's time for the finals.
- Good luck.
- With Eugene's skills,
you don't know what will happen.
- Eugene is incredible.
- Seriously.
She is on another level.
Are you ready?
(Women's final)
(A match between two strong women)
Eugene can go up on her own.
I am excited about this match.
We will begin
as soon as they hang from the bar.
(The winner of this match
will join the top club.)
(Who will be the winner
of the women's match?)
(Ji Hyo is still exhausted.)
- Ji Hyo is...
- Did it begin?
- It began.
- Let's go.
(On the other hand,
Eugene is relaxed.)
Come on.
(Ji Hyo attacks first
in order to end the match quickly.)
(Will she take Eugene down
with a single attack?)
(In her attempt to attack,)
What?
(Ji Hyo exhausts her energy
and falls.)
- What?
- She went back up!
(The prima donna of
the pull-up bar is relaxed.)
(She continues to give reactions.)
(Disappointed)
My goodness.
Ji Hyo wasn't lucky
with her opponents.
- She was already out of energy.
- My arms gave out.
- My goodness.
- I was lucky.
My goodness. Thus, the winner of
the women's match is...
Eugene.
She is incredible.
In the first match of strength,
Eugene and Jong Kook joined
the top club.
Okay, okay.
Now comes the second match.
It's the match of composure.
- Composure?
- I have confidence.
- I can do well in this match.
- I never lose composure.
I have the mental strength.
I never lose composure.
There will be a men's match
and a women's match.
The game will proceed the same way.
When you come out
and put a recorder in your mouth,
another member
will tickle or hit you.
You are out
if the recorder makes a sound.
This has nothing to do
with the inner composure.
I am really ticklish.
I can't stay composed
when someone tickles me.
I won't last a second.
(Go ahead.)
That happens.
How do I hold in the sound?
There must be a way.
(Everyone plays the recorder.)
(He shows off his recorder skills
from the elementary school days.)
(Squeaking)
(The room gets filled
with various notes...)
(and the performance
of "Airplane".)
(The music class must be playing,
"The Netherworld of Recorders".)
Go with the C sharp chord.
Ji Ah looked at the recorder
and went...
(Sighing)
Did she do that again?
She held it and went...
I didn't do that.
- I understand.
- I didn't do that.
"What is this? What is this?"
- "What is this?"
- That's so funny.
(She diligently prepares
for the game.)
Breathing out through your nose
should help, right?
- Give it a try.
- When you get tickled...
- How do you do it?
When you get tickled... Tickle me.
(Squeaking)
(As soon as he begins,)
(he makes a sound.)
- Breathing out through your nose...
- Suk Jin.
- She barely touched you.
- Ji Ah, isn't this fun?
Isn't this fun?
(His instant reaction
makes her chuckle.)
She is incredulous.
This is...
- Try it when I tickle you.
- But this...
Put the recorder in your mouth.
(Try it when I tickle you.
Put the recorder in your mouth.)
- Do it with your nose.
- No!
- Come on.
(Why did he put the recorder
against his nose?)
- Hold on.
- What are you doing?
- Are you stupid?
- Are you nervous?
- You are nervous, right?
- Breathe out through your nose.
- Suk Jin.
I can't put this
back in my mouth now.
- It's your nose. Try it.
- For goodness' sake.
It all depends on who tickles you.
Why don't we go with the order
we chose earlier?
- 1, 2, 3, 4, and so on.
- Yes.
- We decided on it earlier.
- Then I will tickle Se Chan.
- Suk Jin, go first.
- Me?
- Suk Jin.
- Number four.
(The person who will attack Suk Jin
for 30 seconds is...)
- Who's number four?
- I am!
- Kwang Soo is strong.
- He won't be able to hold it in.
- Is it you?
- Jiangshi.
- He is good. He tickles nonstop.
- Is it you?
- Gosh, this is crazy.
- This is crazy.
A clown came. For goodness' sake.
You should know
that I found the perfect tactic.
I learned to breathe out
through my nose.
That's right. Stay composed.
Suk Jin, you will experience pain.
No, no. He won't hurt me.
It will be a disaster
if you wet your cotton pants.
Set.
(The time limit is 30 seconds.)
Go.
(Squeaking)
(He exhaled powerfully.)
0.8 seconds.
That was 0.8 seconds?
Suk Jin,
you are currently in first place.
- Hey.
- What?
- You are currently in first place.
- Why did you rip my ribs?
(He was defenseless
to the attack on his ribs.)
Who is next?
It's Do Kwon. Do I tickle Do Kwon?
- Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk is good at this.
Do Kwon, are you ticklish?
- Are you ticklish?
- He isn't ticklish.
- Hold on. In that case...
- He would pretend even if he is.
You didn't block the opening,
did you?
- Oh, it makes a sound.
- Hold on.
Hold on. I need to think.
The tactic that needs censorship
is your only way.
(They think about cheating.)
Jae Suk, do it our way.
The camera crew should only shoot
his bust.
Let's go
with Assassination Number One.
Let's go with that tactic.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
Get ready.
Set.
Hold it.
(Jong Kook approaches him
from behind.)
(You should do it!)
(Jong Kook attacks instead.)
(But Do Kwon withstands it.)
- He is holding it in.
- He is withstanding it.
(Do Kwon is doing better
than anyone expected.)
I didn't start, Do Kwon.
(I didn't start, Do Kwon.)
(It's a bolt out of the blue.)
Jae Suk needs to start.
Why did you go?
- I was playing around.
- It's Jae Suk's turn.
- Jong Kook, it isn't your turn.
- Jae Suk didn't start.
- Let's start over.
- It isn't your turn.
Jong Kook is so mischievous.
- I guess that wasn't very funny.
- He was playing around.
It's my turn.
- Stop it, Jong Kook.
- All right.
- He withstood it really well.
- I thought it would be funny.
All right. Let's get ready.
Hold on.
- This is...
- They are so serious.
(He puts it in front of Do Kwon.)
Hey.
There is no other way.
(Assassination Number 2:
Set up a screen to hide foul play.)
- We are taking it far.
- Seriously?
I am a guest.
Manners.
- Let's go.
- Our tactics won't work.
He will probably hold it in
even if we stab him with a needle.
Let's go.
(Do Kwon's 2nd attempt
finally begins.)
For goodness' sake.
Attack this area.
- Gosh.
- It isn't working.
He isn't ticklish.
- He is incredible.
- He is holding it in.
- His entire body is tense.
- Nothing is working.
My goodness.
- How is this possible?
- He has no weak points.
(They hear the news
of a strong contender.)
- Let's attack at once.
- Are you okay?
Let's attack at once.
(The onlookers' hands are on him.)
(Rushing over)
(Go away.)
(Do Kwon chases away
the cheating onlookers.)
He is incredible.
Nothing is working.
That was unbelievable.
(The incredibly composed man,
Ha Do Kwon)
He withstood everything.
- He was good.
- Don't you feel ticklish?
Of course, I do.
- Did you hold it in?
- You gritted your teeth.
- He is incredible.
- Is it my turn?
- Is Do Kwon tickling him?
- It's Do Kwon.
- Do Kwon.
(Do Kwon will attack.)
It's time for revenge.
They met again.
Recorder Assassin.
- Recorder Assassin.
- Assassin on the Pull-up Bar.
(Do Kwon wants revenge, but
playing dirty is Kwang Soo's forte.)
(Who will be
the winner of this match?)
Do Kwon is putting his fingers
between Kwang Soo's ribs.
You don't need to use
a lot of force.
Just push a bit.
Do Kwon, it would be better
to aim for the armpit.
- Get ready.
- Really?
- No, no. Ribs are more sensitive.
- Get ready.
- You can do it.
- Go.
- He is holding it in.
(He holds it in!)
- He is holding it in. The armpit.
- He is holding it in.
Hit his armpit.
(If he holds it in for 30 seconds,
he will be in 1st place.)
You should make it painful.
How does he do that?
(Take this.)
(He was forced to breathe.)
Wasn't that the Heimlich maneuver?
(Do Kwon's maneuver
made a clear sound come out.)
Wasn't that the Heimlich maneuver?
8.2 seconds.
- 8.2 seconds.
- What was that?
- I am jealous.
- Do Kwon.
- Do Kwon joined the top club.
- He joined the top club.
- Okay, okay.
- I tried so hard for this.
- Congratulations.
I tried so hard for this.
- Now, the four women.
- Women's match.
The five women.
- Ji Ah is number 1, right?
- Number 2.
- Number two.
- It's So Min's turn.
So Min should go first.
- You will be tickled.
- Will I be tickled?
(She belatedly moves to the center.)
So Min, did you block the opening?
- Let me see.
- No.
Hold on.
- Did she block the opening?
- She blocked the opening.
For goodness' sake.
Hold on.
(She tried to cheat.)
She put the electrical tape
in her mouth.
- This is...
- Listen.
- It's not like that.
- This is...
what you do
when you are playing against us.
- So Min, you went too far.
- Take it off.
- It's not like that.
- Seriously.
- I am really ticklish.
- Let's take it off.
She taped the opening.
- Unbelievable.
- She is unbelievable.
I am really ticklish.
- Take it off.
- The recorder still makes a sound.
- I think...
this show is worse
than "The Penthouse".
Ji Ah said...
this show is worse than the drama.
The drama is fictional,
but this is real.
I am so nervous.
I might pee.
Get ready. Get ready.
(So Min gives it a go.)
Set...
- Don't move. Don't move.
- She is doing pretty well.
She is breathing through her nose.
- Grab her nose.
Ji Ah, grab her nose.
Grab her nose.
(So Min buys time
by breathing through her nose.)
(Squeaking)
(Here comes a steam train.)
- It was 2 against 1!
- I had no choice.
You breathed through your nose.
(Se Chan and Ji Ah's teamwork
took out So Min.)
16 seconds.
- That's a good score.
- She withstood it for a while.
She withstood it for a while.
- Ji Ah, come here.
- It's okay.
Ji Ah, come here.
Eugene will tickle her.
Get ready.
- What am I going to do?
- Set...
- What was that?
- Hold on.
(She bursts out in laughter
instead of playing the recorder.)
- Hold on.
- What was that?
(What was that just now?)
I thought her recorder was making
a strange sound.
It was her laughter.
Hold on. Hold on.
She hasn't gone yet.
- What was that?
- What?
You should play the recorder.
Laughter doesn't count.
Go again.
You can't take the recorder
out of your mouth.
Don't take the recorder
Things are becoming more fun, right?
(She goes over the rules again.)
- Do we start over?
- Do we need to start over?
- You need to start over.
- Get ready.
Take a deep breath.
Catch your breath.
Don't take it out of your mouth.
- Laugh with it in your mouth.
- Get ready.
(Laughing)
Don't take it out of your mouth!
(She bursts out laughing.)
- Hey.
Don't take it out of your mouth!
- Play it!
- Come on!
When you play this game,
you can't take it out of your mouth!
What's the use of the recorder
if you aren't going to do that?
- Seriously.
- We could have gone without it.
- But I...
- Stop with that hearty laughter.
- Don't take it out of your mouth.
- Keep it in there.
Play the recorder.
Should we tape the recorder
on her mouth?
(Eugene suggests
an extreme measure.)
- Come here, Ji Ah.
- Come on.
Keep the recorder in your mouth.
If you want to laugh,
- do so into the recorder.
- That's right.
Every time she gets ready...
Do, re, mi, fa, sol, la, ti, do...
- Why are you holding it that way?
- Is she holding it properly?
It's not like you need to play it.
You don't need to hold it properly.
- Hold it as you want.
- This is so funny.
- She is so diligent.
Ji Ah, you are doing well.
- Should I hold the recorder?
- Okay, okay.
Open wide.
(Be a good girl, Ji Ah.)
She is treating her like a baby.
Here. Let's put it
between your teeth.
Open wide. There you go.
Let's go.
(Baby Ji Ah's
recorder class is over.)
- Let's go.
- Go.
There we go.
- She is out.
- That was refreshing.
(They finally hear
the sound of the recorder.)
(Feeling refreshed)
That was hilarious.
That was refreshing.
(Eugene is up next.)
That was funny.
Eugene.
- Get ready.
- I will laugh in mi.
- Mi.
- I bet she will do well.
- That's a good idea.
- Mi.
- Eugene.
Set...
- She isn't ticklish.
- She is holding it in.
That's how you hold it in.
Isn't it ticklish?
(Ji Hyo continues to tickle her.)
- What are you doing?
- Are you tickling her?
(Ji Hyo attacks her scalp.)
Aren't you going to tickle her?
(Ji Hyo runs out of ideas
as Eugene is impenetrable.)
You are tormenting her.
(Ji Hyo's hands move quickly
to hear the mi sound.)
- She is incredible.
- I think Eugene will swear.
This isn't working.
(Eugene hangs on
until 20 seconds pass.)
This isn't working.
She succeeded.
She withstood everything.
She is strong.
Eugene succeeded.
Ji Hyo became mean
because of that makeup.
- It's the makeup.
- So Yeon.
- Gosh.
- She feels bad.
- What am I going to do?
So Yeon, who are you talking to?
"Gosh." Who are you talking to?
She kept going, "Unbelievable."
She has American reactions.
- You should give us one gesture.
- Okay.
You keep showing us
three gestures in a row.
Unbelievable.
- I can't help myself.
- Okay, So Yeon?
Okay.
- Get ready.
- This is so funny.
- You can put your hands on her.
- Okay.
Set...
What am I going to do?
(Why is So Yeon screaming?)
Why... Why...
- So Yeon.
- Why did you do that?
- You are not the one being tickled.
So Yeon, Ji Hyo didn't blow
the recorder yet.
You need to keep going.
(Screaming)
Why is she acting like
she's being tickled?
Why did she give up?
- So Yeon, what was that?
- Why...
This isn't a difficult game.
- She gets goosebumps.
Why do you get goosebumps?
- Why do you get goosebumps?
- Hurry up and attack!
- My goodness.
- She is crying.
(Screaming)
Why is she feeling ticklish?
- So Yeon.
- Yes?
Your fingers are only doing this.
- I mean...
- Go ahead and tickle...
- her armpit.
- What am I going to do?
(What am I going to do?)
You are doing it wrong. Tickle her.
(Screaming)
My goodness.
Excuse me.
(So Yeon is bad at attacking.)
She won!
(She suddenly announces
that Ji Hyo won.)
What was that?
- "She won!"
(So Yeon saw that there was no hope
and decided to end the match.)
My goodness.
Why are you so funny?
- What was that?
- Her fingers didn't even touch her.
I bet...
I can make her play the recorder
without touching her.
- I...
- 0.1 seconds.
The barest touch will take her out.
Set.
She is holding it in.
- She is determined.
- But...
(What?)
(So Min makes her breathe.)
- Hey!
- What was that?
- Why did you punch her?
You startled me.
So Yeon is out.
So Yeon can withstand
getting tickled,
but she didn't expect
a punch to her stomach.
- She was startled.
- She held it in.
So Min is unbelievable.
- Seriously.
- So Min is unbelievable.
Eugene and Ji Hyo,
play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors
She won.
Ji Hyo joined the top club.
That's impressive.
So Yeon, cross this line.
(They have a match of patience
right afterward.)
(Ji Ah and Haha join the top club.)
Shim Su Ryeon.
Top club and bottom club members,
please line up together.
Okay.
- For goodness' sake.
- We got divided.
I told you earlier...
that the mission fund is
very important in this race.
Each member of the top club
will receive 200 dollars...
and each member of the bottom club
will receive 100 dollars.
The first gathering will give you
a chance to increase the money.
- Gathering?
- Decide...
whether to turn in your money
as the gathering fee...
or to keep it to yourself.
If you choose the latter,
you keep the money to yourself.
The collected gathering fee...
will be doubled...
and divided among the six members.
- My goodness.
- It will be doubled.
For example, let's say...
all six members of the top club
turn in 200 dollars each.
1,200 dollars will become
2,400 dollars...
and each member will receive
400 dollars.
Let's say 1 member turned in
100 dollars...
and 1 member turned in 0 dollars.
Then the total amount will be
900 dollars.
The doubled amount, 1,800 dollars,
will be divided into 6.
Each member will only receive
300 dollars.
The member who didn't turn in money
will take the lead.
We chose the right club.
For now, we chose the right club.
- In the end...
- You know,
we have no reason
not to turn in money.
- There he goes again.
- Don't even start.
You automatically say those things.
We have no reason
not to turn in money.
- I see.
- We have two swindlers.
He says that,
but he won't turn in money.
So Yeon, we need to turn in...
as much money as possible...
- and double it.
- I will turn in money, of course.
Here is what I think.
So Yeon will lose
all of her money today.
- It's bound to happen.
- The results of the next mission...
will change the members.
- The members can change.
- I see.
We could move to the top club.
I won't name any names,
but these two members
will be enough to destroy that club.
Jae Suk, one member will be enough.
One member will be enough.
I will give you the money.
You can secretly turn in
as much money you want to your VJ.
- If so...
- Hey.
I'm going to turn in
everything I have.
- I'm going to turn in everything.
- Okay.
Let's just turn in
a little bit each.
All is too much, so let's just
turn in a little bit each.
- Let's just turn in everything.
- Hey.
I took everything out now.
- I also took everything out.
- Me too.
Let's just turn in
everything we have.
The only way we can catch up
with them is to turn in everything.
We need to catch up.
Can we give it to you right now?
- To be honest...
- Give it to your VJ.
Give it to your VJ.
- Who should I give it to?
- Oh, my.
- Hey.
- Do I have to do it again?
- Say it out loud.
- I'm about to vomit.
- This is his.
Who should I give it to?
Why are you showing it so obviously?
(Will they keep their promise?)
- Can I give it to you now?
- One person...
Okay, me?
I'm going to give you everything.
I will get double back.
(So Yeon turned in everything
she had as promised.)
You have to turn in
everything for this.
(The other people also completed
turning their money in.)
We all promised...
- to give 200 dollars.
- Don't betray us.
- If so...
- I really won't betray you.
We should get
400 dollars back individually.
- That's right.
- If not, someone didn't turn it in.
I'm going to find out who it is
no matter what and get revenge.
Okay.
That's scary.
(They promise to turn 200 dollars
in with a scary warning.)
(What choice will Ji Ah make?)
Didn't we promise
to turn in everything?
What?
- What is happening?
- That's not it.
That's not it.
I told you I'll get revenge
if someone betrays us.
You can't betray us.
You should see what happens
if it doesn't work.
I will get revenge.
if you betray us.
I will turn everything in.
(Scared Ji Ah
turned 200 dollars in.)
(The other 5 people also completed
turning it in.)
I will reveal the amount
of the bottom club first.
- You promised 100 dollars each.
- Yes.
The amount of six people is...
We did a good job
if we get 600 dollars.
- Isn't that right?
- Yes.
- It's 170 dollars.
- What?
(The bottom club's lodge money is
a total of 170 dollars.)
- What?
- Gosh.
- I turned in 100 dollars.
- I turned in everything I had.
- Gosh.
- What?
- That's the worst thing ever.
(He's lying.)
(He's also lying.)
I turned in everything, but you
only turned in 10 dollars each?
- 170 dollars?
- 170 dollars is too harsh.
If you double 170 dollars
and round it up,
- we will give you 60 dollars each.
- That's the worst thing ever.
- What?
- But...
- So Yeon...
- 170 dollars?
- How much did you turn in?
- Someone didn't turn it anything.
I turned in everything I had
in the entire envelope.
So Yeon turned in everything.
Then...
- It's Jae Suk then.
- There are only 170 dollars.
- She didn't turn in anything.
- I really turned it in.
- Did you turn it in?
- I really did.
I'm going to turn in everything.
(He laid a smoke screen
by being loud deliberately.)
We must turn in everything.
(He only turned in 30 dollars.)
(Catching on)
(Se Chan turned in 20 dollars.)
Wait a minute.
(After smiling,)
(he puts on a serious look
right away.)
I won't turn in anything.
(He pretends to turn it in,
but withdraws it quickly.)
(Suk Jin turned in 0 dollars.)
- How much did you turn in?
- 20 dollars.
20 dollars.
(She didn't disappoint us
with her tiger moth-like deeds.)
(Here's another tiger moth who goes
crazy during missions like this.)
(He hides it in his pocket
right away.)
(Kwang Soo turned in 0 dollars.)
If we don't turn everything in
this time,
it will be completely impossible
to turn the tables.
That's the worst thing ever.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- If she paid 100 and you paid 40...
Three people here
didn't turn in anything.
- Oh, my. I got goosebumps.
- People didn't turn in anything.
- It's you.
- Oh, my.
You saw me turn it in
earlier, right?
I turned in too much.
You saw me turn it in, right?
- I don't think I saw it.
- What?
- A lot didn't turn it in.
- Did you only pay 20 dollars?
I will announce the amount
of the top club now.
- 1,200 dollars.
- They had to have gone all in.
I will announce the amount
of the top club now.
- 1,200 dollars.
- They must get 1,200 dollars.
I'm going to scream
if we don't get 1,200 dollars.
They have to get 1,200 dollars.
The top club promised
to turn in 200 dollars each.
They're a strong competitor.
- The total amount is...
- It's 1,200 dollars.
We got that amount unconditionally.
- 1,010 dollars.
- What?
- Who is it?
- 1,010 dollars.
- What?
(Gosh, come out.)
- I swear I turned it in.
- Jong Kook.
- I swear.
I swear.
If you double and divide that,
you'll get 340 dollars each.
- Who is it?
- It's you, isn't it?
- No.
- I really turned it in.
I really did.
- I have an empty envelope.
- You're really...
You saw my empty envelope.
- Did you turn it in?
- I turned it in earlier.
How could you only turn in
10 dollars, not 100 dollars?
(Who survived by themselves
and turned down loyalty?)
It will be hard for this team
to restore trust.
(Top club showing a division
versus bottom club that lost trust)
(But this isn't the end.)
(The top club war is getting
more intense with the mission fee.)
(But at that moment...)
(They started to discover mysterious
delivery boxes one at a time.)
(They suddenly became urgent.)
(Escape from this place right now.)
(The final hurdle
to move into the penthouse)
(Everyone here is a competitor.)
(But is the time they move in
all different?)
(It's war against time...)
(for everyone to move in
from now on.)
(The war for the penthouse sparks.
How will the grand finale be like?)
(The Penthouse Special 2:
Moving In War)
(And the ending of
last time's Old Restaurant Race)
The winning team of today is...
Kim Soo Yong
and Nam Chang Hee's team...
which originally started
as the oldest.
(Suk Jin's team won
with a total of 198 years.)
Ji Hyo and So Min gave one each,
- so it divided evenly.
- Really?
(They were off guard thinking
Suk Jin's team was old.)
I only gave them one.
- We will give you the prize first.
- Okay.
The prize is a set of
wooden tableware for each person.
- Isn't that...
- They're given a gift.
- They're dishes.
- I'm jealous.
- They look nice.
(He's full of energy
since it's about time to end.)
We will tell you the penalty.
The penalty is to take away
from your remaining ages.
1 blow on your forehead
will take away 15 years.
1 blow on your wrist
will take away 5 years.
We won't have to receive
a lot of blows then.
We will only have to receive
one blow on our wrists.
- So...
- Show me your forehead.
- Should I hit like this?
- Yes.
(The weakness of the oldest team
is that they have no strength.)
I didn't hit him properly.
(They finished taking away
years up to Jong Kook's team.)
(Kim Soo Yong, Nam Chang Hee,
Bomi, Namjoo, Hoshi, Mingyu)
- It's over.
- Good job.