(Running High School is known to have unique students.)
- Are we all friends? - Are we supposed to be friends?
- Hello. - My goodness.
(Today, Running High School has school activities.)
Hey, Ji Hyo.
Hello.
(Running High School's beauty, Ji Hyo is the first one to come.)
Ji Hyo, wait for me.
(Husky)
Hurry up and come, Se Chan.
(Next is...)
Ji Hyo. Why are you alone?
(Se Chan doesn't seem like a student who's ready to study.)
- Hey. - Hello, Haha.
(Swaggering)
Are you ready?
He's our leader. Leader Ha.
(He clearly looks like he doesn't study at all.)
- Let's warm up. - Okay.
All right then.
We're Dirty Mustache.
Let's play the music. 1, 2, 3, and 4.
(Dirty Mustache's masterpiece, "Jauji Jangjijiji")
(It's a school band of Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and Haha)
(Empty Head: The youngest member of the band)
(Song Jeoktoma: Vocalist, Dirty Mustache: Bandleader)
Good. You've still got it.
- You're our main vocalist for sure. - She's amazing.
(They've been performing only this song for 3 years.)
- You're our main vocalist. - Shut it!
- Hello. - I can't believe you guys.
(Three students appear by discouraging the band.)
- Are you a returning student? - No, I'm not.
You punks.
- You're here. - What's that?
(Bowing)
- He's just a gangster. - Why do you have a dumbbell?
(They act like a clique boss and his minions.)
You punk.
My gosh.
- Behave yourselves. - We're friends.
(Kind)
Are we friends, you punk?
I repeated the same year for five years.
- Five years? - What?
- He's lying. - It's a lie. It was for 10 years.
You repeated the same year for 10 years.
(He's 29, but he's still in high school.)
- It was five years. - Hey.
They are my friends.
(People of all ages become friends in Running High School.)
- Sure. - What?
Ji Hyo.
What?
You're pretty.
Ji Hyo, you look passionate today.
- Do you have a boyfriend? - The main vocalist of our band.
(Cheesy)
(As the boys are only interested in Ji Hyo...)
I have my own style.
(Pushing a button)
You have your own style? I see.
- Hey. - What is it?
(A song so suddenly?)
What? We're the dance team.
(Jong Kook and Suk Jin's bodies react automatically.)
You're the dance team?
Gosh, what are you doing?
(The band club starts singing.)
(The dance club with no precision)
(The dancer specializing in the Im Ha Ryong dance)
Is this a school for troublemakers?
It's a school for troublemakers.
(No discipline at all)
(Dancing machines!)
So Min's very flexible.
(29-year-old Suk Jin can't seem to keep up with the teenagers.)
This is a school for troublemakers.
Come on. We're the dance team. You should be better.
(Tenacious tiger moth, Big Nose the founder of the team,)
What is that?
(and the protein monster who protects other members)
- This is not a school. - The setting is weird.
(Does this kind of school even exist?)
I haven't done this in a long time.
(Lost in dancing)
My goodness, our dance team is really...
What was that?
(The sound of a whistle?)
What is it?
- What is it? - What is it?
- Turn off the music. - Quiet down!
- Turn off the music. - It's the Apgujeong Whistle.
What are you, a zebra?
(Jae Suk and Kwang Soo turn off the music as they enter.)
Turn off the music.
- He's turning it off himself. - Yes, you do that.
(Which club are they?)
- Student guidance club? - Who are you guys?
What's with the noise so early in the morning?
(Strict)
(Yoo Jae Suk, top student and the leader of student guidance club)
(Lee Kwang Soo, the informer of student guidance club)
- They're the student guidance club. - My gosh, student guidance club.
(They were the student guidance club?)
What's with your hair? Are you out of your mind?
(Hair length regulation)
- What's with your mullet? - Your mullet is weird too.
(The school's hair length regulation is tolerant to back hair.)
- Get a haircut. - Yes, get a haircut.
- Gosh. Hello, sir. - Hello, teacher.
- Good to see you, sir. - Gosh, You're not a teacher?
(Bowing)
I'm not a teacher.
I'm a friend of yours.
- Aren't you the vice-principal? - I'm a friend of yours.
(Suk Jin is in the same grade, though he looks like a teacher.)
Who told you to dance?
I apologize, sir.
- Hey. - We'll control them.
But we're the dance team.
- What? - We're the dance team.
(The leader of the guidance club obeys the school rules.)
But you can't dance in front of the school.
You like to dance too.
I know you're the dance team, but...
Actually, he...
- failed the audition for our club. - You're really good.
(The top student in terms of excitement dances every time.)
- He failed the audition. - What's with that move?
He's doing this because he failed the audition.
(Waving)
How can a student dance like that?
You're really good at this move.
(She learned the travel bus groove at an early age.)
She's our best dancer.
Hey.
I can smell cigarettes on your breath.
- Hey, leave him alone. - Come here.
- Hey. - Let him be.
- Give me your hands! - Let him be!
- Hey! - Give me your hands.
- I didn't smoke! - Give me your hands.
- Just give me your hands. - Hey.
(Slipping)
How could you smoke when you're a student?
(Suk Jin gets weak at the knees after a hit on his hands.)
- I didn't smoke! - Are you out of your mind?
I said I didn't smoke.
(His old person's smell was mistaken as cigarette smell.)
I know you're much older than we are.
(29 years old)
- That's right. - But you're still a student.
(Teenage smoking may accelerate aging.)
- You should listen to us. - Hey.
- What? - Actually, the cigarette smell...
(Trying to frame her)
is from Song Ji Hyo.
Gosh, that hurts.
(Pulling his side hair)
They're tied to my real hair! It hurts when you pull!
It hurts!
(The fluorescent hair is tied up to his real hair.)
It's tied to your hair?
- Hey. - It hurts!
I'm sorry.
- Gosh, it really hurt. - He didn't know.
- I'm sorry. - Wasn't it attached to the hat?
(I thought it was attached to your hat.)
What's wrong with you?
Wait a minute.
Which club are you from?
- Me? - Dance team. We're the dance team.
(I'm in the dance club.)
The dance team.
- Why are you holding a dumbbell? - This?
He's just a bully.
- You're a bully? - Not a dance team member.
(He overpowers his character and returns to being a thug.)
He looks like a bully no matter what he wears.
He always looks like a bully.
As a member of the student guidance club...
you should go talk some sense into him.
Yes, talk some sense into him.
(Staring)
Or you could hit him.
- Talk to him. - What?
(The leader of the student guidance club never meddles in.)
- You were saying? - Talk to him.
Just let me hit you once.
Then when it's all over,
I'll wire 50 dollars to your account.
(As they're intimidated by the thug from the dance team...)
Step by step
- What? - Who is it?
- Oh, baby - Who is it?
(Humming)
Who's that?
Gosh, who's that?
(Who is that?)
Some more bullies are here.
- Step by step - What is this?
(Appearing while singing in his beautiful voice is...)
Oh, baby
(Defconn, a heavyweight dancer from the dance team.)
He's a dance team member.
- Hello. - Loyalty!
(Kim Bo Sung, a student guidance club member...)
Loyalty!
(who lives and dies for loyalty)
- Hello. - Loyalty!
Loyalty!
- Loyalty! - That hurts.
(50 percent of his conversation is made up of "loyalty".)
- It hurts. - That hurts!
I'm sorry.
Brother.
- How have you been? - How have you been?
I've been good.
(I've been well.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Nice to see you too, Defconn.)
- Hello. - It's good to see you.
Why do you look so nasty?
I'm a dance team member.
- Dance team? - You're a dance team member?
- We're the dance team. - You're one of us.
- Yes, you're one of us. - Okay, good.
(Defconn is in the dance club,)
- I'm on student guidance club. - You are?
(and Bo Sung is in the student guidance club.)
Move.
You're a student guidance club member and you have sideburns?
You have a problem with it?
(Throwing his bag without notice)
He's serious. This isn't acting.
- Hey. - What was that?
(You can't predict what he's feeling.)
Gosh, he just turned violent.
Brother.
He reacts right away.
(He moves out without telling anyone.)
Yes, he does.
He doesn't give you notice.
How come a student guidance club member has such a long mullet?
(Can a guidance club member have such long hair?)
Yes, he has such a long mullet and sideburns.
Student guidance club members should set good examples.
(The long-haired members lead the way in liberalizing the hair code.)
How could you both have long hair?
Hey, quiet down.
- It's Gyu Jin. - Hey, Gyu Jin.
(This voice is...)
Gyu Jin's here again?
(Shin Gyu Jin who paints a big picture!)
Quiet down.
(On Comedy Big League,)
Yang Se Chan, when you're alone on Running Man,
you're not able to paint a big picture either!
Se Chan, since you're not able to paint a big picture,
(he gives Se Chan harsh criticism.)
- watch out for Suk Jin. - Who, me?
(And when he was on Running Man to paint a big picture,)
No, no! Bring it here!
- Take that away. - That's real!
(he failed to paint a big picture. Not even a rough sketch.)
Is it okay to escape?
(So he returned to the base.)
- Why is your face red? - He's sleep deprived.
He couldn't sleep.
Have you ever been on Running Man?
I should give Jae Suk a call.
(Then Shin Gyu Jin showed off that he was on Running Man!)
Gosh, it's Gyu Jin.
- Then... - Oh, he's here.
Gyu Jin's here again?
Gosh, it's Gyu Jin.
I thought his role was gone, but he's back again.
He's back again.
(Shin Gyu Jin, the dean of students is very nervous right now.)
- Hey, Gyu Jin. - It's been months.
My goodness. Look at these brats.
(He recites the lines he prepared while feeling tense.)
Gosh, he really is like a teacher.
- What's wrong with you? - He's like a real teacher.
(Interrupting)
It's been a while since we saw you. Why do you look so haggard?
Hey, hey. Be quiet.
- But... - Quiet down.
(Hmph!)
Don't you think you're the same as the prison guard you played before?
- He's the dean of students. - Which prison guard?
(It's not going as he had hoped from the start.)
I don't know what you're talking about.
- His acting is amazing. - So today...
(Whenever he tries to speak...)
What happened to your skin?
It's rotten.
It's because I didn't sleep well last night.
(Telling the truth)
- Maybe the teacher's nervous. - Were you nervous about today?
(The dean suffers from insomnia the day before coming to this show.)
Why can't he sleep the day before coming on Running Man?
(Gulping)
Well, that's not what's important.
(The first line he prepared)
I am here today for a reason.
I'm here because today is the day of dress inspection.
(Today is the dress inspection day!)
The dress inspection?
- He's checking our outfits? - So everyone...
put all your personal belongings on the floor.
(Teachers used to check the students' belongings...)
Put your hands on your heads and stand still.
(and uniforms by surprise.)
- Personal belongings? - Hurry up.
(Grumbling)
I don't want to hear you grumbling.
- Put everything on the ground. - My goodness.
(They strongly oppose as this is a school of delinquent students.)
- Come on. - Stop grumbling.
- Sir! - First thing in the morning?
- This is too much. - You can't do this to us.
Hey, hey.
This school is set in the 80s, so we have corporal punishment.
Corporal punishment?
(He can give corporal punishment as we're in the 80s.)
We're in the 1980s?
- We're in the 1980s? - He can hit us.
- Yes, they hit students back then. - You're right. They did.
(There was corporal punishment at the time.)
We got hit by the teachers in the old days.
(They look like they used to get punished often.)
Okay, then.
- My goodness. - Okay.
(Checking Haha from the band club first)
My goodness.
What is this?
Are you a gangster?
It's my father's.
- Your father? - What's with the accent?
(He's using a dialect all of a sudden?)
- "What does your father do?" - Why is he using a weird accent?
Your father?
(The dean of students looks pleased to role play as he expected.)
My goodness.
- Why is he using a weird accent? - Come here.
What does your father do?
(Confident)
My father is a gangster.
A gangster?
Gosh.
- He doesn't know what to say. - He can't improvise.
(He doesn't know how to improvise after his first line.)
He can't improvise.
- So your father's a gangster? - He can't improvise.
(What should I say?)
- Gosh. - So your father's a gangster?
- Yes, take off your watch. - I've seen this somewhere.
(He stutters without being able to keep it going.)
Sir, you saw him last week.
- What's wrong with him? - The teacher is too nice.
Your hairstyle isn't appropriate as a student.
(Getting back into character)
Well, it's because I'm a band member.
Do you need to have long hair to be in the band?
- But I got permission. - From who?
- From you. - From me?
- Yes. - It's my first day at this school.
So you're new here.
(His second ad-lib barely works.)
You get three penalty points.
My goodness. You didn't pay for these, did you?
(With your money?)
This belongs to Dream.
- Gosh. - Don't mess with Dream.
(It's his family.)
It's the only thing you can't mess with.
(He runs out of things to say for the 2nd time.)
- He has a child. - You can't mess with his kid.
I'm sorry.
The teacher is too kind.
(A kind teacher)
He has no backbone.
(Teacher Shin gave us a big laugh though he's spinless.)
- Gosh, what's wrong with him? - So kind.
It's so easy to convince him.
- Anyway, you get penalty points. - All right.
(Haha gets a penalty point according to the school's regulation.)
- Remember that. - Yes, sir.
Who's next?
(Next student.)
- Hello, sir. - It's been a while.
Yes, it has. You know me, don't you?
(Sly)
- Yes. - Right.
(He met Se Chan on "Comedy Big League".)
- From his previous school? - Yes, maybe.
Yes, I met him at the previous school I went to.
(They're direct senior and junior outside of this improv.)
- I just transferred to this school. - You're a new student here?
Gosh, look at yourself.
- What do I do with you? - What do you mean?
The shape of your hat is ruined!
Make it right.
(His unnatural acting suddenly kills the mood.)
It's becoming slightly corny.
- "Make it right?" - It's like a boring comedy show.
(What do I do now?)
All right, what do you want me to do?
- All right. - Yes.
Let me see.
Doesn't your mom iron your uniform?
He doesn't know what to say.
(The dean isn't giving him penalty points when he clearly seems wrong.)
Anybody would think that his inner shirt is inappropriate.
- That's right. The scarf. - His scarf is inappropriate.
Are you playing favorites with him?
Se Chan, you don't get any penalty points.
- Oh, thank you. - What?
(What? Why just Se Chan?)
- Thank you, sir. - What was that?
- I'll be good to you tomorrow. - Good, good.
- Are you two meeting tomorrow? - No, we're not.
(They're meeting as a senior and junior tomorrow.)
You're filming Comedy Big League tomorrow, right?
- You brat! - Gosh, you can't do this.
This darn world runs on regionalism and kinship.
No, we're not.
Actually,
you can't call it that. They have school ties.
He's right.
(Suk Jin lacks vocabulary.)
- Well, whatever it is... - Suk Jin.
This isn't about regionalism and kinship.
(His academic achievement is really low.)
This is about school ties.
I can work with regionalism but not kinship.
(Se Chan gets 0 penalty points due to the teacher's favoritism.)
Now quiet down.
Ji Hyo is next.
(Warm)
Gosh, what do I do with you?
- Inside your uniform. - She worked hard to look nice.
(Running High School's Ji Hyo plays the role in a great outfit.)
- You tried too hard to look nice. - Seriously.
So you wore a colorful turtleneck sweater.
Yes, but I did because it was too cold.
(Nasal voice)
Of course you did.
- My goodness, what? - What on earth are you doing?
(The dean becomes understanding when Song Jeoktoma uses her cute voice.)
- Sir! - What can you say? She was cold!
It's so cold these days.
(Nasal voice)
All right, Ji Hyo.
(Song Jeoktoma's cute, nasal voice)
Let me see your hair.
What is this? Isn't it inappropriate for a student?
(But getting a perm is against the school regulation.)
- It's funky style. - You can't get a perm.
- I went to a beauty salon today. - Yes.
And they told me it suits my style.
Yes, it does.
(Smiling)
My goodness.
- What's he doing? It's ridiculous. - You do look nice.
(She's avoiding penalties thanks to the biased teacher.)
You should point out her problems.
- Is this your bag? - Yes.
Let me check it.
- Hang on. - Gosh, that...
- Please be careful. - Why?
Nothing.
Am I not supposed to open it?
(You can open it.)
You can open it.
We're going to start it from the Lunar New Year.
What is this?
I'm in the school band.
(What's this mic for?)
I carry a microphone around with me so I can practice all the time.
(I carry it around to practice.)
Are you the vocalist?
- Sure. - Actually, this is a lighter.
Hey, stay quiet.
I'll give you one penalty point.
You are spreading false information.
(For spreading false information!)
You get one penalty point.
(Haha is getting on the wrong side of the teacher.)
Anyway, you have too many colorful pins in your hair,
(He gives 1 penalty point just for the show.)
- so you get one penalty point. - Good.
All right. One point.
Who's next?
(Next is Kwang Soo, the student guidance club member.)
I'm in the student guidance club.
How dare you look down at your teacher?
(Nitpicking)
- I'm in the student guidance club. - All right. Student guidance?
(Opening legs to match the teacher's eye level)
- Sir, he has very long hair. - But he doesn't shower.
(He's in the student guidance club.)
- He's so filthy. - You should cut his hair.
- Gosh. - If you cut my hair,
- I'm okay with that. - What?
Get him some scissors.
Get him some scissors. Where are they?
(Is he really cutting the hair?)
Do you not know the school regulations?
If you want to cut my hair, I'll let you do that.
- Really? Okay. - Yes.
(The student with the long hair is so into the skit.)
If he wants to cut it, I have to follow him.
- Here you are, sir. - It's longer than I thought.
(Suk Jin hands the teacher an actual scissor.)
- Really? - Is he serious?
Isn't this a skit? Are we doing this for real?
We have no choice though.
(They're all framing him.)
- What? - We have no choice.
The movie shoot is over.
- Here you are, sir. - Really?
(Wait a minute.)
Cut it short please.
(This is getting strange.)
- It's too long. - I know.
(The teacher also doesn't know what to do.)
Isn't this a skit? Are we doing this for real?
Cut it short please.
Sir, if you cut it...
(They resume the thrilling skit.)
Gosh, I think you've been growing your hair for years.
- Yes. You can cut it. - Are you okay with that?
(Is it for real?)
- Sure. - I think he's cutting it for real.
(Will he really cut Kwang Soo's hair?)
- He's really doing it. - He's cutting the hair.
- I'm cutting it for real. - I mean... Sure.
I'm not familiar with stuff like this. I'm cutting it for real.
- Hey, he's doing it for real. - This isn't a joke.
(The two are confused between the skit and reality.)
Are you sure about this?
(Is it for real? Or is this a skit?)
- Sir. - It's okay to cut it.
Go ahead and cut it.
(The tensions build up due to the excited crowd.)
He should get a haircut anyway.
Stop hesitating and cut it.
But the problem is...
If you get your hair cut,
Bo Sung will have to do the same.
If you get your hair cut, Bo Sung will have to do the same.
(Me too?)
- Bo Sung should do that too. - So...
You should just get penalty points.
(They finally end the thrilling skit.)
- All right. - You should get penalty points.
(Anxious)
- I get it. - Just cut it.
Give me that.
So I will just...
(Please calm down.)
- Give him penalty points. - I'll give you five penalty points.
(Kwang Soo gets 5 penalty points total for flustering the teacher.)
- Okay. - This isn't acceptable.
All right. Next.
(Next is Kim Bo Sung.)
He's here. He's a member of the student guidance club.
Gosh, his bag is like...
Hang on.
What is this?
Leather gloves.
- What are these? - Gloves.
I know they are gloves. But what's with the bumps?
In case of emergency...
- You're a student. - It's called LA.
The loyalty of an angel.
- I always protect the weak. - I see.
(Kim Bo Sung, the guardian of the angel's loyalty)
I protect the underprivileged.
- It's the student guidance club. - Right.
(The words seem grand, but he's just explaining the gloves.)
You should give him penalty points for his hair.
(Bo Sung also has long hair.)
- Oh, his hair. - He has long hair.
This is too long. What do you think?
You can cut it if you want.
(My back hair)
Hang on. No, I won't...
I don't think I have to cut it.
You have very thin hair.
(The angel's hair is very thin.)
You're being too serious.
- I mean... - Sir, don't make fun of his hair.
- It's humiliating. - Don't make fun of his thin hair.
- You should keep it to yourself. - That's so mean.
(Due to the sudden attack on this thin hair,)
You should show him something.
(he starts to swing nunchucks.)
He's your teacher.
(Swinging them hard)
(Stepping back)
Why are you swinging them at school?
(Hitting his head)
(He hits his head while swinging the nunchucks.)
- He hit his head. - Tidy your hair.
He got hit in the head.
- Are you all right? - It didn't go well.
(Embarrassed)
Why are you swinging them now?
(Why did he take out his nunchucks?)
About your sunglasses. Are those prescribed?
(It's not prescribed.)
- Say yes. - No, they're not.
They're not prescribed?
Then you should get penalty points.
- He's so nice that he can't lie. - He's nice.
- He can't lie. - He doesn't know what to say.
He just can't lie.
(He may be swinging nunchucks, but he never lies.)
- Just say anything. - He's so innocent.
- He just can't lie. - He has such innocent eyes.
We're just doing a skit now.
(The angel's eyes are very pure.)
He's got the eyes of a deer.
Go ahead and say a lie.
(After Bo Sung's turn is over)
He didn't get that many penalty points though.
- Hang on. - Yes?
- Nice to meet you. - Three penalty points.
Already?
I didn't do anything. Why?
You have a tough-looking face.
- What's wrong? - And...
I was born this way. What should I do?
(That's not fair.)
And I understand you are a growing student,
- but you should shave your face. - What is Bo Sung doing?
What is he doing behind there?
(He's training nunchucks all by himself.)
Look at Bo Sung.
(The master martial artist doesn't know the right time and place.)
- Why are you swinging those? - What's wrong with you?
I didn't do it right earlier.
(He still can't get over it.)
- Why do you keep swinging them? - He has regrets.
(I'm usually better.)
All right. Next.
- I will check your uniform anyway. - Okay.
(The teacher checks Suk Jin's uniform too.)
But your headphones are not connected to anything.
- They are in my bag. - Those are hearing aids.
- Really? - Hearing aids?
Hang on. The gold necklace...
It's a health necklace.
This is a health necklace.
(He wears all kinds of health accessories.)
Is it germanium?
Sir, he drives an electric car.
Why are you saying that?
(He owned an electric car since the 1980s.)
- Why? - We're doing this seriously.
- Why can't I say that? - He cares about the environment.
- He cares about the environment. - I do.
He's driving an electric car already.
Really?
(Examination on Earth-loving Suk Jin is now finished.)
- You want to protect the earth. - I do.
Next.
All right.
(Now it's the problematic student's turn.)
- They finally met. - All right.
He's here.
(Hesitant)
(What should I do?)
He's here.
- What is he going to do? - I've been waiting for this moment.
(It's a big match that everyone has been waiting for.)
- Gosh, this is... - He wouldn't budge.
(He doesn't budge.)
- Hey, kid. - "Kid"?
Do you want to pick a fight with me?
Why is your posture so...
What's wrong with my posture?
- You look aggressive. - Sir, he is...
(He has an aggressive attitude for a student.)
addicted to protein.
He is?
- Sir. - Yes?
Make sure you don't run into me on the street.
(The protein addict provokes his teacher.)
He's saying that to his teacher?
(He takes up the protein addict's challenge...)
(without a backup plan.)
- He's taking off his watch. - Sir.
He finally took off his watch.
- Get down. - Get down.
(Encouraging)
Get down.
(The teacher tries to punish Jong Kook with others' support.)
Go ahead and get down.
- Oh dear. - You should punish him.
- You should hit him for real. - It's okay. Go ahead.
(It's fine. Hit him hard.)
- Get down. - Get down.
(Hit him hard!)
You can do this for real.
Let's do this for real.
(The protein student lies down on the floor.)
- All right. - He's got a broad back.
You sound very rude to your teacher.
(He sounds firm,)
There you go.
(but his eyelids are fluttering.)
You sound very rude...
(Things are getting extreme, but no one's trying to stop him.)
to your teacher.
All right. There you go.
(Hitting gently)
- Sir. - Hang on.
(What?)
(He hits very gently.)
- The sound... - Hang on.
- Wait, sir. - What was that?
(The rookie comedian's action is disapproved by everyone.)
He's terrified.
What was that?
- My gosh. Sir. - What are you doing?
(He clearly got hit. He clearly hit him.)
You should be strict.
- I mean... - You're the dean of students.
(Criticism)
You're the dean.
It should have some impact.
- Why did you... - It was just a gentle pat.
(Criticism)
Anyway.
(He wears the meaningless watch again.)
- Give him penalty points. - Okay.
Just relax your chest.
(Jong Kook opens up his chest more after the punishment went south.)
I didn't tighten my chest.
You are threatening enough already.
- So... - He's intimidated.
(It's a tough environment for the rookie comedian.)
You can't button up your jacket, so you get one penalty point.
(He bravely gives 1 penalty point.)
What about his fierce glare, sir?
- The defiant glare. - What? You're still aggressive.
(Glaring)
- He should get down again. - He deserves five points.
(A typical villain)
I should look you in the eyes when you talk.
His glare deserves five penalty points.
- It deserves 5 points. - He should get 15 points.
(The penalty points)
The teacher's authority is damaged.
You have to establish it already.
Sir, show us what you've got.
(The students encourage the teacher again.)
- Sir. - You can do this.
How many penalty points?
(Can I do it?)
- You're right. - How many penalty points?
- Teacher. - Teacher.
(You can do it!)
- Tell him to lie down. - Teacher.
(The rookie comedian gets carried away by their cheering.)
- Teacher. - Teacher.
The teacher's authority has been damaged.
- Get down. - Show us what you can do.
(Do I need to lie down again?)
- This is your last chance. - Get down!
(Reckless)
(At this moment...)
- Tell him to get down. - I'll get punished instead of him.
(I'll get hit on his behalf.)
- Bo Sung. - Go ahead and hit him.
- I'll get punished instead of him. - Go ahead and hit him.
(The angel of loyalty steps up suddenly.)
Bo Sung.
(Even the beneficiary does not understand the flow of this skit.)
Go ahead and hit him.
Teach him a lesson.
- You are a loyal friend. - Loyalty.
- He's loyal. - I'm loyal.
(The loyalty of an angel protects even the strong.)
The loyalty of an angel.
Hit him hard.
Hard?
- I'll hit you just once. - He's so cool.
(A slippery loyalty appeared in the fixed flow of skit.)
- There you go. - You can hit me 10 times.
- I'll hit you just once. - Loyalty.
(How will the teacher proceed with the unexpected situation?)
- All right. - Loyalty.
He's so loyal.
(Hitting)
(Hitting hard)
(Making a fuss)
(He got carried away and lost control of his power.)
Hey, he's in his 50s.
Hey, Gyu Jin.
(He's laughing because he's flustered.)
(It's so hard to be an angel of loyalty.)
Bo Sung is...
Why did you hit me so hard?
(Why did he even volunteer to get hit?)
- I was... - You hit him gently earlier.
You are very loyal.
(The man of loyalty can easily feel the pain.)
You know what? What's really hilarious is...
that there was a puff of dust from Bo Sung's pants.
Let me tell you why I got hit instead of him.
He's really loyal.
In the show, "Mom's Diary"...
If you don't want to get hit again, just come here.
He gave me a padded vest.
- Just come here. - He gave me...
(He's very thankful for the padded vest.)
- a padded vest as a gift. - That's enough.
I'm a giver, actually. Not a taker.
(They bonded over the padded vest.)
He gave me a padded vest.
- All right. Next. - It's in my car.
(It's my favorite padded vest.)
If you do something wrong again,
Bo Sung will get hit again.
- Okay. - Behave yourself.
(Did I?)
- Okay. - Do you understand?
- Yes. - Loyalty!
(He is forced to agree.)
- Loyalty! - Bo Sung is so cool.
He's a loyal friend.
(I shouldn't have accepted the padded vest.)
He's the man of loyalty.
- Hello, sir. - All right. You're very polite.
(It's time to examine So Min's uniform.)
- The turtleneck sweater. - Yes.
(Neon-colored turtleneck sweater)
- One penalty point. - I'm wearing it because it's cold.
(1 penalty point)
Is that because it's cold?
You should try to endure it.
(He sounds shy but firm.)
- One point. - So Min, that doesn't work for him.
- So Min, your wink doesn't work. - Don't fall for her tricks.
(His attitude is different from when he treated Ji Hyo.)
He's as firm as a rock.
What is this thing?
(She is subject to many penalty points.)
The kids in the dance club won't hang out with me...
if I don't wear these.
- She sounds annoyed. - No, I'm not.
(He tries to make her get more penalty points.)
You should care about your dance skills instead.
(She's got great dance skills.)
She's a good dancer.
She does dance well.
(We acknowledge that.)
- She's a good dancer. - She's good.
(The rookie comedian again stumbles on an unexpected skit.)
- She dances well. - You've got good dance skills.
- Right. - You dance well.
- I go to school for... - She's really good.
(Her dance skills make him speechless.)
She's good.
This is how she comes to school.
(Please don't give me penalty points.)
- Is this your jacket? - No, this isn't mine.
- It's yours. - You can throw this away.
- This belongs to Suk Jin. - Is it mine?
(What?)
I think it's Bo Sung's.
- Isn't this yours? - Sir, I saw Bo Sung was wearing it.
That belongs to Bo Sung.
(Is it mine?)
Right. It's Bo Sung's.
- Teacher. - This is yours.
(They try to force him to show his angel of loyalty again.)
- It's not mine. - It's yours. Put it on.
- This is yours. - No.
I've never seen this before.
I saw that too.
(He denies fervently and forgets about his loyalty.)
- I saw him wearing it. - It fits him perfectly.
- It really isn't mine. - It looks good on him.
(For stop being loyal,)
- It's not mine. - He's genuinely flustered.
(Bo Sung avoids the punishment.)
- It's not mine. - He doesn't want to be punished.
I'll let it slide just this once. Now...
(The eventful uniform check is over.)
Let me think. I think that's enough.
I got too many penalty points.
- Thank you, Teacher. - Why did I get so many?
(Penalty Point Chart)
- I got too many... - You got 12 points?
- I got too many penalty points. - You got six points?
(Se Chan 0, Ji Hyo 1, Jae Suk 1, So Min 5, Jong Kook 6)
- Se Chan got no penalty points. - He got 18 points.
(Defconn 6, Bo Sung 9, Haha 10, Suk Jin 12, Kwang Soo 18)
Why didn't you get any penalty points?
(Penalty point)
- I don't know. - Exactly. Why didn't he get any?
- Gosh, seriously. - I don't understand.
(It's my love for my senior.)
Today, we'll find the best club in Running High School.
(Pick the best club in Running High School)
It's The Burning 18 Again.
(The Burning 18 Again)
- "The Burning 18"? - The Burning 18 Again.
You'll be divided into three groups,
(You'll be divided into 3 groups.)
which are the student guidance club, dance club, and band club.
The club that gains the most club fund will win.
(The club that gains the most club fund will win.)
All the members of the winning club will receive a scholarship.
(All the members of the winning club will receive a scholarship.)
- All right. - Great.
Meanwhile, regardless of the club fund,
(Regardless of the club fund,)
there's a penalty point system.
(there's a penalty point system.)
The three students who get the most penalty points...
(The 3 students who get the most penalty points...)
will stay after the shoot to carry out an annoying penalty.
(will stay after the shoot to carry out an annoying penalty.)
I hate annoying penalties.
I hate it the most.
(18-year-olds are the laziest.)
- That's what I hate the most. - I hate it too.
As for the penalty points, just like he did earlier,
(As for the penalty points,)
the dean of students will watch you during the missions,
(it's up to the dean of students.)
and announce the final results at the end of the show.
During the club activity time after each class,
(Club activity)
(You may steal another club's fund.)
you will have a chance to steal another club's fund.
Okay.
If you give school support donations to the dean of students,
(If you give school support donation to the teacher,)
your individual penalty points will be deducted.
(your individual penalty points will be deducted.)
- So use this chance wisely. - It won't be easy.
School support donation? Gosh.
Each club's fund will determine the winning team.
(The club's fund determines the winning team.)
- Let's go to the first classroom. - Okay.
(The penalty points determine who carries out the penalty.)
(They will move to the classroom for the 1st class!)
- Okay. - Yes.
(This is where Running High School's classes will officially begin.)
(The club name is written in front of each seat.)
(What kind of mission will they have here?)
- The dance club is the best! - We're the dance club.
The dance, dance, dance club.
(The dance club members are the 1st to arrive.)
Stay with me
Forever
Haha, the song suits you.
He looks like the singer too.
(The colorful Lee Moon Sae is somewhat similar to Lee Moon Sae.)
Right. He does look like the singer.
He looks a bit like Lee Moon Sae if you cover his eyes.
Not just a little bit. My nickname was Lee Moon Sae.
(Brazen)
- Really? - Little Lee Moon Sae.
Some people confuse me with him.
Mr. Shin, are you going to be with us throughout the shoot?
Yes, Ms. Jeon, to the end.
I see.
(Gyu Jin returns to a rookie comedian.)
He spoke formally to her.
Don't you have a meeting today?
("Comedy Big League")
- Oh, yes, I do, - Yes.
but I play in the same comedy skit with Mr. Yang.
(Polite)
I see you speak very politely in real life.
- I didn't influence the decision. - Is that so?
(He's actually a soft-hearted rookie comedian.)
(Glancing)
(Jae Suk looked aside and suddenly started giggling.)
(Why is he laughing suddenly?)
The stock prices of all the other companies are going up...
(Chuckling)
except for the ones Suk Jin bought.
- What could be the reason? - Suk Jin.
(He feels down.)
Why won't they go up when the market is so rosy?
- Well, I guess... - It's hard to believe.
(Suk Jin's choice of stocks avoided the biggest stock boom.)
And why did he get the blue sign?
He needs a red one.
- He's wearing red socks. - You see,
(His stocks keep going down.)
I'm not joking. Only the ones he bought won't go up.
- What's the reason? - Why is that?
(He has no idea why his stocks go down.)
I don't know. I don't understand. Why...
(Hope one day Suk Jin sees red lights.)
The first class is the subject that you guys are worst at.
(1st period is the moral class.)
It's a moral education class.
- Gosh. - What? I'm good at it.
- I'm really confident in it. - Don't you know that?
(Lee Kwang Soo, Traitor Giraffe)
My name is Moralconn.
I'm such a moral person.
- Moralconn? - I'm Moralconn.
My nickname is Kim Moral.
(Everyone shamelessly shows off their sense of morality.)
The result of this class...
won't just determine...
(According to the result, they'll earn the club fund.)
- your club funds. - Okay.
After the mission ends, Mr. Shin will announce your penalty points.
(After the mission, Mr. Shin will announce the penalty points.)
(Sharp)
You will get penalty points...
if you don't contribute to the team's success...
(Penalty points will be given...)
or if you don't make people laugh.
(based on their performance and how funny they are.)
All those things will be considered.
- We have to be funny too? - Really?
Then do we gain an advantage if we do something really funny?
- Of course, you do. - Is that so?
(As soon as they heard the answer, they started acting funny.)
What song is this?
- I don't know. - All you guys do is scream.
(Laughing)
- That's not funny at all. - Exactly.
(They always shout first.)
- Respect, respect, be respectful - Be respectful
(Perfect teamwork)
Do it with Ji Hyo.
- Respect, respect - She can do it well too.
(They suddenly put their arms around their shoulders.)
It ended when I took my mic out.
Hey, Ji Hyo. That doesn't suit you.
That's not true. What makes you think so? I can pull it off.
(She doesn't want to go along with their childish shout.)
Let's go, Song Jeoktoma.
Ji Hyo is doing it reluctantly.
She didn't know what to do. You didn't know, Song Jeoktoma.
- That was tacky. - "Let's go, Song Jeoktoma."
(As the band club forces Ji Hyo, she joins them.)
- You say that first next time. - By the way,
I want to join the band club.
Right? Didn't it make you feel excited?
(He's attracted to the band club's hyper voice.)
- They seem so energetic. - Defconn.
- Let's do it too, Defconn. - They give off a good vibe.
- That was exciting. - We can do it too.
- We're the dance club. - They're so cheerful.
(Waving)
You're right. We can do it.
(The dance club cannot be defeated.)
- Suk Jin is a dance club member, - We're the dance club.
(Suk Jin)
but he's sitting with his arms crossed.
- Dancers don't cross their arms. - Exactly.
(Suk Jin doesn't move at all even though he's a dance club member.)
- Are you really in the dance club? - Yes, I am.
- He just showed up one day. - Oh, he just...
He joined the club of his own accord.
(The old student joined the dance club by himself.)
Ji Suk Jin is in the dance club.
- Oh, that was what he meant? - Yes.
- He joined us of his own accord. - Loyalty!
(Anyway, Suk Jin looks like he won't dance at all.)
Bo Sung, loyalty!
- Loyalty! - Let's say "Guidance" instead.
Guidance!
- Good job. - That's so him.
He's like a machine. He does everything he's asked to do.
- He's like a machine. - Are you really a human?
(The cheerful loyal guy grants all requests.)
Aren't you a robot?
In the first class, you will learn to be considerate of one another.
(You will learn to be considerate in the 1st period.)
It's Break Up Strawberries with Loyalty.
(Break Up Strawberries with Loyalty)
- Loyalty! - Break Up Strawberries?
The strawberry game.
("Break Up Strawberries"?)
(You have to break up the syllables of "strawberry" to the given beat.)
- Ji Hyun, one. - St-raw-ber-ry
(1, St-raw-ber-ry)
- Jae Suk, two. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
(2, Straw-berry-straw-berry)
Kwang Soo, three.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry - Se Chan, four.
(3, Straw-berry -strawberry-strawberry)
Strawberry-strawberry -strawberry-strawberry
(4, Strawberry-strawberry -strawberry-strawberry)
(They've played it before. How well will they do this time?)
My goodness.
(You understand the rules, right?)
I don't think Bo Sung can play this game.
It must be difficult for Bo Sung,
but Jae Suk is also really bad at this game.
- We'll play the strawberry game? - Yes.
(The student guidance club is worried already.)
- This is driving me nuts. - Strawberry-strawberry
I'm worried about Bo Sung.
However, this time, we'll have a team match.
(This version of Break Up Strawberries is a little different.)
For example, one of you said, "Band, three."
(Band club, student guidance club)
(Band club, 3!)
The first member must begin.
If he says, "St-raw-ber-ry",
(St-raw-ber-ry, St-raw-ber-ry, St-raw-ber-ry)
the other members have to say twice more.
And then you can attack the other team.
(Student guidance club, 4!)
- I get it. - The first member...
(Break Up Strawberries is changed to a loyalty test game.)
It's like the loyalty game.
It's a sort of loyalty game.
If someone says, "Dance, four",
(For example, if one says, "Dance club, 4",)
Jong Kook will begin as he's the first member.
(the 1st player of the dance club, Jong Kook plays first.)
I say, "St-raw-ber-ry".
- And you say, "St-raw-ber-ry". - Oh, I get it.
- He says, "St-raw-ber-ry". - St-raw-ber-ry
- I say, "St-raw-ber-ry". - That's four.
(They say it 4 times together.)
Then I attack the other team. Or he can say strawberry twice.
(After saying it 4 times, So Min attacks the other team.)
- And you say it twice too. - I see. I get it now.
(Okay. Got it.)
What does this game have to do with moral education?
(Absurd)
It's like the loyalty game.
It's a sort of loyalty game.
Can one person do it all at once and attack the other team?
(1st player can say it all and attack the other team.)
Yes.
But the maximum number for 1 person is 4.
(But the maximum number for 1 person is 4.)
Correct. You can say it up to four times.
- Let's do some practice. - St-raw-ber-ry
(Confused)
I'll attack you.
Bo Sung, three.
- St-raw... - No. You're already out.
He just wants to get his penalty points deducted.
(It's a team play.)
- My gosh. - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(It's rare to see Kwang Soo's team play.)
- Just to get his points deducted. - Let's try it one more time.
(Teaching passionately)
- Bo Sung, three. - Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(That's not it.)
- Oh, okay. - Again. Three.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Bo Sung, three. - Bo Sung...
- Bo Sung. - Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
It's so difficult for me.
I'll be honest.
I bet the student guidance club will do worst among us.
Kwang Soo, it's hard to master in one day.
(Break Up Strawberries with Loyalty looks difficult and tough.)
Then there's no way we can win.
Team leaders,
(It's time to decide the order through rock-paper-scissors.)
play rock-paper-scissors to decide the order.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(The club leaders play rock-paper-scissors.)
Won't anyone from that team come out?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Bo Sung, play rock-paper-scissors.
(The student guidance club leader)
No, not with me.
Please keep it together.
- I'm confused. - He can't keep it together.
- You don't play it with me. - Okay. Here we go.
(They're worried about Bo Sung who doesn't know how to play.)
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors - Oh, yes.
(Paper, rock, scissors)
- You didn't win. - She's playing the game too.
(He got excited when no one won.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - You didn't win.
- She's playing the game too. - Oh, right.
(The loyal man's still confused.)
He can't even play this game. How will he play the strawberry game?
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Scissors, rock, scissors)
- Great. - Good job.
(Bo Sung wins by giving a rock consistently.)
- You did well. - You guys go first.
- He won with a rock. - We'll go first.
(Happy)
- Okay. - How exciting. Let's go.
- This is exciting. - Let's go
(The 1st round will begin with the student guidance club's attack.)
Let's go!
I really don't want to let that team win.
Let's begin. Ready. Here we go.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Band, seven.
(The student guidance club is attacking first!)
St-raw-ber-ry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry -strawberry-strawberry
- Okay! - Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Okay!
(Okay. That was good.)
You chose seven. That was brilliant.
(They made a successful attack with 7, a high number.)
- 7! - 7 was a good choice.
That was unexpected.
Haha, I didn't know how many times you said it.
- But... I mean... - Oh, yes!
(Goofball is excited.)
Jae Suk, we needed to do some warm-up first.
(Preheat)
You should've called a number between 1 to 4.
- But you called seven. - I don't care.
(I don't hear you.)
- Seven was a good choice. - It was difficult.
(Goofball is brutal.)
- Let's call 6. - I think 7 is the best.
(What a bummer.)
- Why don't you... - You two...
Bo Sung, just say it once. Or maybe twice?
- Okay. - Say it just once no matter what.
- St-raw-ber-ry - St-raw-ber-ry
(Bo Sung will only say it once.)
- That's all you have to do. - St-raw-ber-ry
- Let's begin. - Don't try anything else.
(Got it.)
- We'll fill the rest. - We'll begin.
- Okay. - We're ready.
(Both student guidance club and dance club get 1 point each.)
- Ready, go. I like strawberries - I like strawberries
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
- Student guidance, six. - Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry
Strawberry-strawberry -strawberry-strawberry
St-raw-ber-ry
(Bo Sung, the one they worried about the most, succeeded.)
(They will succeed if Jae Suk says 1 strawberry.)
St-raw-ber-ry
Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Great. - Why?
- You said... - It was six.
- He said 4 strawberries. - I did 4.
(Exactly.)
- Oh, you said it 4 times. - And he said 1.
- You didn't have to say it. - I thought you said it three times.
- This is driving me nuts. - No, he should've said it once.
(The man going crazy, the man who doesn't know what he got wrong)
Or Bo Sung should've said it twice and attack another team.
(The man with a game fright)
I said it four times.
- Only you know how to play this. - You should have...
(The worst combination for the strawberry game)
- I should've said it once. - That's right.
Bo Sung, keep saying it just once.
(Kibitzing)
Okay.
You say it just once too.
(Who do you think you are to teach him?)
- Okay. - My goodness.
- Is Jae Suk teaching him? - Got it.
(No way.)
- This is crazy. - Just say it once.
(The mouth player is only good at coaching.)
- Take that. - They're all so stupid.
- It's my turn. - Ready, go.
(Both band club and dance club get 1 point each.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Dance, eight.
- Straw-berry - He skipped his turn.
(What?)
Gosh, Jong Kook.
Dance, eight.
Straw-berry
Gosh, Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook skipped his turn.)
- Why didn't you do anything? - Was it my turn?
- He said "Dance". - Why didn't you do anything?
(Suk Jin skipped Jong Kook.)
It's confusing because he called our team name.
(Nice. That was good.)
- Nice! - We're the dance club.
- Let's call a number under five. - Good job.
(He's only good at attacking.)
- High numbers are good for offense. - Okay.
I didn't know we were the dance club until now.
- Relax, everyone. - Okay!
(The elder checked the team name 2 hours after the shoot.)
- The name makes it confusing. - Just relax.
- We're the dance club, right? - Ready, go.
(Both band club and student guidance club get 1 point each.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
- Student guidance, seven. - Strawberry-strawberry
- Strawberry-strawberry - Student guidance, seven.
Strawberry-strawberry -strawberry-strawberry
St-raw-ber-ry
I'm sorry.
Strawberry-strawberry -strawberry-strawberry
(They picked a lot of strawberries.)
I'm sorry.
(He almost drooled while saying strawberry.)
- Nine strawberries! - He's an idiot.
- He's so stupid. - Idiot, idiot.
- Why are you so nervous? - Idiot, idiot.
- All you had to do was... - That was so funny.
(His game fright isn't getting any better.)
- You should've said it once. - By the way,
Bo Sung really does as he was told.
(Bo Sung)
This strawberry game is...
(He quietly plays the given role.)
Bo Sung, are you a robot?
Strawberry-strawberry -strawberry-strawberry
(Whatever number is called,)
St-raw-ber-ry
Strawberry-strawberry -strawberry-strawberry
(this loyal man says only st-raw-ber-ry like a robot.)
St-raw-ber-ry
Bo Sung, are you a robot?
(He's like a vending machine. He's consistent.)
- You should've said it once. - Bo Sung is...
- Bo Sung... - You should count it.
It's too hard to count it while thinking about the beat.
(Overloaded)
- You have no choice. - It's easy if you can count it.
(The last position is too difficult for the game coward.)
- Bo Sung, always say it once. - They're so stupid.
(Clucking)
From now on, if any one of us makes a mistake,
- he gets a slap in the face. - Okay.
(We need a punishment.)
- A slap? - Yes.
(We're taking it that far?)
Gosh. Keep it simple then.
(Feels tense about the scary penalty)
And go.
(The student guidance club attacks first.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
- Dance two. - St-raw-ber-ry
St-raw... Ry
Seriously?
(He ignores the standard beat.)
- Suk Jin! - He wasn't wrong though.
(His team loses as he interprets the beat arbitrarily.)
He only twisted the beat a little.
- It was him being laid-back. - That's not allowed.
St-raw-ber-ry
(He refutes strongly using hip-hop terms.)
- That's not allowed. - See?
- Seriously? - I got confused.
- How can you get this wrong? - I mean...
You said two.
- Only one. - We agreed to do one each.
(What are you saying?)
- 1 each. - Why did I hear 2?
(A problem with his cochleae)
- Unbelievable. - Seriously?
- Hey. - Do it properly, will you?
(I'm going to...)
- You got it wrong too, you know. - What?
(The protein student yells at his classmate.)
You got it wrong earlier too.
- Hey, you. - Did you just hit me?
- What do you think you're doing? - Seriously?
- I'm sorry. - Listen to the teacher.
(I apologize.)
- The teacher's here. - The teacher's with us.
(You brat!)
Hear me out though, sir.
(The victim tells the teacher on Jong Kook.)
We're all allowed to make mistakes.
You made a mistake on an easy one though.
- Jong Kook! - Yes?
You've been making too many mistakes.
Me?
You...
(Then...)
Bo Sung, get out here.
(Bo Sung, on the ground.)
(Again?)
- He's already limping. - But...
Why him?
(Due to his loyalty regarding a padded vest during the opening,)
- Can't you see he's limping? - Just let him be.
(his loyal bottoms get massaged all day.)
- Get on the floor. - Hold on.
I'm not kidding when I say Bo Sung's on the older side.
(Please let him off.)
Bo Sung, you can get up now. I talked to the teacher.
(He gets a pass thanks to his old age.)
- You can get up now. - That's right.
Jong Kook. Make a mistake...
(Warning him strictly)
- and Bo Sung will get punished. - got it.
(Polite)
- Don't intimidate others. - Got it, sir.
(The class becomes amicable again after the teacher's discipline.)
- All right. - Let's go.
Okay, let's get this party started!
- Let's party. - Begin the party.
(The band club is after the cheer points.)
- Let's party. - I'd love to join that club.
(The band club)
We can be just as festive, you know.
(Genuinely jealous)
Let's have fun too.
(The friendly band club is very popular among students.)
- As if. - Just do one. Don't get confused.
- All right. - Why don't we swap seats?
(They switch seats to proceed with the game better.)
Just do it once.
(Bo Sung goes to the front, which is easier.)
St-raw-ber-ry That's all you have to say.
Just the one.
Before we begin,
when they call our group,
start by saying "Loyalty" first.
Let's do this.
(The familiar word has him all confused.)
What are you doing?
- He's messing with me, right? - Of course.
(Of course not.)
- Right? - Just say "St-raw-ber-ry".
Are you kidding me?
(The fiery fists of loyalty)
Bo Sung...
Bo Sung was actually considering it.
(Frightened)
(He tends to react to "loyalty" every single time.)
Se Chan told Bo Sung...
to say "Loyalty" before playing the game.
And Bo Sung actually considered it.
(The innocent man almost fell for the trick.)
Don't say it, okay?
(Never)
- Got it. - All right?
- Don't confuse me. - Got it.
- Don't overdo it. - Got it.
(The ban on "loyalty" to the man of loyalty)
- We'll start with Haha. - Haha goes first.
- Let's do this. - 1, 2,
(The band club attacks first.)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Student guidance, five.
St-raw-ber-ry
(He got confused and missed his beat.)
You had me all confused.
(Because of you...)
The beat was off.
(His plan worked.)
Let's practice, all right?
- St-raw-ber-ry - Repeat after me.
(The private lesson sparks up again.)
- St! - St!
St-raw-ber-ry
(Copying)
- Yes, say just that. - Right.
(The guidance club can't be guided.)
Okay, let's make them lose.
We can't seem to go back and forth though.
(By the way...)
And go.
(The band club and the dance club each get 1 point.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Dance, three.
St-raw-ber-ry
- Why? - Defconn!
- St-raw! - St-raw!
(The strawberry wilts as Bo Sung ambushes Defconn.)
- How is that so difficult? - St-raw-ber-ry!
- Seriously? - St-raw...
(Suk Jin gives him a private lesson.)
St-raw, st-raw.
- St-raw-ber-ry - Do better yourself!
(Who are you to teach someone?)
What do you mean? I'm not doing so bad.
(The team gets divided like somatic cell division.)
Was the beat off?
When Suk Jin was told to do better himself,
he stepped backward saying,
"What do you mean?"
(Stumbling)
- Do better yourself? - What...
(His body flaps in the air.)
- Do better yourself? - Stay behind after school.
- Ji Suk Jin, shut it. - Shut it!
- Shut it! - Shut it!
(Picking it up)
- Get out here. - Shut it.
- Are you kidding me? - Bo Sung!
(He suddenly uses his nunchucks.)
- Why me? - Bo Sung!
(He's truly startled.)
- Bo Sung. - Seriously?
(How dare you mess with Jong Kook?)
- Why... - What's wrong with you people?
Get back here.
(He volunteers for Jong Kook's bodyguard for a padded vest.)
- Why... - Why are you twirling that?
- This... - Why are you angry at me though?
(Shivering)
Is this even real?
Well,
he gave me his jacket, right?
So you were defending me?
(The brotherhood is formed thanks to a padded vest.)
- That's right. - You were being loyal.
- Loyalty! - Loyalty!
(I'll wear it well.)
I should give him one too then.
I'd rather you be better at this game.
St-raw-ber-ry
(He never forgets about saying "Loyalty.")
Okay, got it.
- Strawberry. - Strawberry.
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 3, 4.
(The band club and guidance club get 1 point each.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
- Band, four. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
That's wrong!
(He gets it wrong by saying it 5 times when there were 4.)
- What's wrong with you? - Unbelievable.
- You should've said 1 or 2. - How could you say 3?
(Tutting)
(Exhilarated)
- You said three. - How clueless are you?
When you add 2 and 2, it's is 4, isn't it?
(His friends' lectures strike his ears as if he's being scolded.)
- I said 2, remember? - Why add on 3?
Even Dream would do better!
Why won't you listen to me?
(What did you say?)
Dream is watching, you know.
(Dream's father loses it as he's compared to his son.)
- Unbelievable. - I'm trying to be funny!
Okay, let's go!
(Let's go, band club!)
- Nice. - All right!
(He brightens up the mood by shouting.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Can't we just play the game?
(I'd love to join the band club.)
- What? - Straw, straw, straw!
(I can feel the energy rising!)
I like strawberries!
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(Here we go.)
(He's embodying Lee Bak Sa.)
- I like strawberries - Must they be this loud?
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(Being a member of the dance club, So Min dances to the rhythm.)
- 1, 2. - Seriously?
1, 2, 3, 4.
(But the older members aren't interested.)
- Let's party, guys! - We're the dance club, guys.
Let's do this.
- Just do it already. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Tired)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(He brings up the mood and resumes the game.)
- Dance, four. - Straw-ber-r-y
(The melody falls behind and he misses the beat.)
- Seriously? - Defconn!
Just sit down, will you?
I mean...
- I can't do this. - Are you kidding me?
- What on earth was that? - Is this a joke?
(How dare you groove up "strawberry"?)
- After all that practicing? - Unbelievable.
(Even he's surprised.)
- Come on! - It's st-raw-ber-ry.
Let's not play this game!
Why can't you focus?
(They haven't even made a single lap for 30 minutes.)
- But he... - Let's sit back down.
Didn't you play games like this on "2 Days 1 Night"?
Not games like this.
This is driving me crazy.
- Right. - It's your turn.
- Just give us a game console. - Suk Jin, take his seat.
Can't we play games like Street Fighter?
- Change seats. - Okay, we'll change seats.
(Defconn and Suk Jin end up switching seats.)
The smartest member should go first.
Can you be this bad?
(You're not the smartest.)
I wouldn't be as bad as you though.
(They can only raise their voices.)
You're all so bad.
- Suk Jin, do well. - Don't you worry.
Don't worry.
- He'll be all right. - I'm not bad, you know.
- Are you sure? - 1, 2,
(Suk Jin ignores him and continues.)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries - Why though?
(Asking him out of the blue)
- I like straw-berries - Why though?
(What?)
- I like them all. - But why?
- I just do. - Why?
(He's never thought of why he prefers strawberries.)
- I just like them all. - Why?
- I just do. - But why?
- Sweet, tasty, and sour. - What about apples?
(The reason)
What about apples?
(Changing the question)
Apples?
(What? Apples?)
Apples are tasty but expensive
(He was robbed of his timing.)
- Just do it already! - Strawberries...
How about grapes?
(How about this?)
I hate the seeds!
Strawberry seeds burst pleasantly in your mouth
(Ji-rasoni answers all kinds of questions.)
How about grapes?
Then what about muscat?
Muscat!
Expensive!
- How about grapes? - It's 25 dollars for 3 clusters.
(He likes or dislikes them based on the price.)
- Muscat! - What about geobong?
What if it's made into juice?
(Varying the tune)
In order to make juice, we need a juicer
(The repetitive song is endless.)
Which means I need 50 dollars to buy the juicer
I need 50 dollars to buy the juicer
I have no money, no money at all
("I am not money"?)
I have no money
(Please stop.)
- I'd rather have strawberries! - Game...
(His conclusion)
- Let's change the game to this. - 1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4.
(They finally begin after a lengthy song.)
- I like strawberries - How about apples?
(Wasn't it over?)
How about apples?
Apples are only good in the morning
- I like strawberries - How about kiwis?
(The questions continue.)
New Zealand kiwis are the best
I like kiwis.
4 kiwis at the price of 10 dollars
When on sale, you can get 6 for 10 dollars
- How... - When on sale?
(His creative song gets stranger as it continues.)
Why are they more expensive when on sale?
- When on sale? - Why though?
- They're more expensive on sale. - How's that possible?
(The two idiots of the band club can't calculate.)
I'm proud of you.
Why aren't you starting the game?
(He brings out his nunchucks again.)
Just start the game!
You startled us.
(Just stop it. I'm going to forget how to say, "St-raw-ber-ry.")
Why would you run out like that?
This isn't how you act here.
- No? - Of course not.
(The scene is resolved thanks to Bo Sung.)
He's the one you should be angry at.
So shut it!
- Okay, fine. - It's so funny that I'm crying.
(They're all crying after laughing so hard.)
The game just won't start.
I'll make sure that Suk Jin can never start the game.
I love the strategy.
Shut it. Just shut it!
- I'm proud of you. - He keeps answering me though.
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Suk Jin who answers questions well goes first.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
- Band, four. - Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-straw-berry
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
Why?
(They said it 7 times when it was supposed to be 4.)
What I said made four.
- Really? - Then you should've attacked.
(Haha should have attacked.)
Right, I should've.
(But they lost because Se Chan followed instantly.)
I was going to, but you beat me to it.
- Really? - You idiot!
(Bringing up his son again)
Even Dream could do better.
What did you just say?
(Dream's father explodes.)
(Swearing)
(Jong Kook gets up.)
You...
(You're going to win anyway if you fight him.)
Did it end with you?
Yes, I said enough to make four.
(His nunchucks appear again.)
Bo Sung...
- Bo Sung took out his nunchucks. - Hold on.
- He... - Did you see that?
(His nunchucks appear every time someone challenges Jong Kook.)
Why do you keep taking out your nunchucks?
Why do you keep pulling out your nunchucks?
(Loyalty!)
We're one unit, you know.
What kind of winter jacket did you give him?
(Could he be loyal to the padded vest?)
- Loyalty. - Loyalty!
All right.
The three teams are at a tie.
(The three teams are all tied.)
All right, then.
(No one knows who'll win yet.)
We only need to get it right once.
It's all about who you attack.
(The strawberry robot is doing pretty well.)
Just one. We only need to get it right once.
Right.
The dance club will be called.
(The band club gets ready once again.)
(Haha, the vocal drummer)
(Yang Se Chan, backup vocalist)
(A cappella instrumental band)
- Strawberries - Are you hearing this?
(Envying)
Strawberries, strawberries
(Sing a line for us, Ji Hyo!)
When will they be in season?
(Song Ji Hyo, main vocalist)
When will you begin the game?
(When on earth...)
(Song Jeoktoma's dance break)
- Ji Hyo doesn't want to do it. - She hates it.
- She... - Did you see her?
Just get on with the game!
(Fed up with it)
Stop fooling around and begin the game!
Ji Hyo would probably want to be in the student guidance club.
(Rather than the band club...)
(Guiding students suit her better than singing.)
- We're just as strict, you know. - The student guidance club.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(A surprise attack)
- Student guidance, five. - Straw...
- Student guidance, five. - St-raw-ber-ry
- Why would you say it? - Hold on.
(He called the student guidance club, but...)
(Suk Jin said it.)
Why would you say it instead?
- Why... - Suk Jin, why?
(Flustered)
I killed 2 birds with 1 stone.
(Swearing with his eyes)
Why would you say it...
when he targeted the student guidance club?
(Suk Jin stole the next-door strawberries without realizing.)
The two clubs start with a completely different letter.
- Why didn't you target us? - S and D, right?
(Starting an argument for nothing)
Before...
- I'm not even angry anymore. - But...
Were you hearing things?
Why would you answer...
(Worried about the old man's hearing)
when he targeted the other team?
I'm sorry.
Would you like to go first this time?
Nice.
(Suk Jin and So Min switch seats.)
- But... - Just know...
that this isn't an easy position.
All you have to do is say one.
(What's so hard about it?)
- Just one. - It's not easy at all.
- All you have to do is say one. - Then take the seat.
(The dance club's morale is down due to Suk Jin.)
Just do one each.
(Let's make some noise.)
We're the dance club, so let's dance beforehand.
- I'd rather not. - But we're the dance club!
(They hate it.)
(Bothered)
But we're the dance club.
(The old member of the dance club does not want to dance.)
- What kind of dance club... - Why...
- Straw-straw, straw-straw-straw - Straw-straw, straw-straw-straw
(She's dancing alone in the end.)
- I like strawberries - She's dancing alone.
(Impressed)
- I like strawberries - Hold on a second.
(She's excited.)
Hang on.
This is practically a school talent show.
- Let's dance together. - You guys...
(He's like a grandparent who came to his grandchild's talent show.)
- They look like the parents. - You let her dance alone.
This is not So Min's talent show.
- Why would she dance alone? - Let's dance together.
(Please.)
Strawberries, strawberries Let's dance together.
(They reluctantly get up.)
- Why won't any of you do it? - Okay. Let's do it.
- Let's do it. - Jong Kook won't even listen.
- I'm so upset because of him. - Strawberries, strawberries
(He doesn't feel like dancing.)
- I'm not in the mood for dancing. - Straw-straw
- Straw - I'm so upset.
(He got excited without grasping the situation.)
Straw-straw-strawberry
- Strawberries - How about pineapples?
Pineapples have so many spikes
- Strawberries are the best - Then what about shine muscat?
(This is crazy.)
- Straw-straw, straw-straw-straw - Straw-straw, straw-straw-straw
(They begin the game before it goes on longer.)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
Student guidance, eight.
Guidance-guidance-guidance
(Jae Suk was taken aback.)
Give me another chance. Let me do it over again.
- I was preoccupied. - Only Bo Sung must be at ease.
I was preoccupied.
(He is taken by surprise.)
- The dance club! - Bo Sung's position is the best.
(What should we do?)
- You should focus on the game. - I know.
We're the winning team now.
(With one more question to go, the band club is in 1st place.)
- Nice. - It's hard.
(The real game will be between the two teams.)
- We must not be in last place. - We can do this.
Bo Sung will begin the game.
(The game will start with Bo Sung's offense.)
- Okay. - You can attack another team.
- Attack? - Attack.
Attack the band club, Bo Sung.
- Okay. - Attack the student guidance club.
- Okay. - No, attack the band club.
Why did you say okay? We're the student guidance club.
(Shocked)
- Hey! - Don't say "student guidance".
- Never do that. - Never say "student guidance".
Got it. Understood.
(He almost got tricked by Se Chan again.)
Do you want us to play the cymbals?
- Should we be ambitious? - Straw-berry
(The band club's performance before the final round)
Here goes Jae Suk
(Dancing)
- Come on. - Here goes Jae Suk
We're the dance club, but we never dance.
(The male members do not budge.)
- Chug, chug, puff, puff - Chug, chug, puff, puff
(The strawberry train is about to leave.)
(How exciting.)
(A cheer captain got on the train out of the blue.)
When are you going to begin? Hurry up.
(It's too tedious.)
- Strawberries, strawberries - Strawberries, strawberries
(The final chant is getting close to the climax!)
(3 seconds until the departure of the strawberry train!)
- 1, 2. 1, 2. 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(The last game begins.)
(Bo Sung will begin the round.)
Student guidance, eight.
(The most hilarious finale)
What just happened?
- You should've continued. - You should've said it.
(It was Jae Suk's turn.)
(Bo Sung actually killed his own team.)
- Why didn't you say it? - You should've said strawberries.
- No. They failed. - You should've continued.
(Their plan worked.)
- We won. - No. Hang on.
- This isn't fair. - It's all because of him.
- I mean, he... - My gosh.
(They try to deny it, but it's already done.)
- Just admit it. - No, it's not fair.
You should've said it because he called your team.
I told you that we're the student guidance club.
- No, it's okay. - You could've continued.
(The strawberry robot was too into the cheering competition.)
- It's okay, Bo Sung. - No, we couldn't.
- You could've said strawberries. - The game would've continued...
(The cheer captain was the reason why the team lost.)
if you had said it.
- It's either dance or band. - We would've accepted it.
(He's too funny.)
Exactly. We would've continued the game if they said it.
(The strawberry game ends with Bo Sung's grand show.)
The band club won the game.
(The band club came in 1st.)
The dance club is in second place,
and the student guidance club is in third place.
It's not so bad.
(The student guidance club came in last.)
You will receive the club funds in a little while.
(After a clear-cut ending, they move on to the next mission.)
- Let's go. - It's over. It was nice.
- It's over. - That was funny.
- Good job, everyone. - Thank you, Sir.
(It's time to announce the penalty points.)
Some of you got penalty points while playing the game.
(The teacher gave penalty points as he observed the students.)
- Why five points? - What?
Why did I get penalty points?
Yoo Jae Suk got five points.
(Jae Suk 5, Yang Se Chan 3, Defconn 3)
- Great. - And...
- Why did Defconn get 3 points? - Why did I get 5 points?
(I don't understand.)
Why did I get three points?
First, Jae Suk did such a poor job playing the game.
He did such a poor job playing the game.
(He got penalty points because he was bad at the game.)
- That's true. - He can't deny it.
(That's true.)
I gave him five points because he ruined the flow of the game.
(Speechless)
Then what about me?
(I don't understand.)
Se Chan, you were too sly.
That's true.
You were too sly.
(Staring)
- So I gave you three points. - What about me?
Defconn, you failed to keep your appearance neat and tidy.
But he was like this from the beginning.
(Reason for penalty points: His untidy appearance)
Aren't you just teasing him?
(That's not fair.)
- My appearance has nothing to do... - He keeps saying it.
Does that mean he'll get penalty points in every mission?
(Defconn, Will likely get penalty points all day today.)
Will he get penalty points every single time?
You could cover yourself a little.
- Cover what? - How? What should I do?
(The rules on appearance are quite strict.)
Aren't you just teasing him?
Now, I'll explain to you about the club activity...
(After all penalty points have been distributed,)
- after the lunch break. - Okay.
(it's time for club activities.)
- Each club will receive funds. - Yes.
(Each club will receive funds.)
After that, go to your club rooms,
(They must hide the money in different places in the club room.)
and hide the money in different places in the rooms.
(We need to hide the money.)
However, you must hide all the money you receive.
(However, they must hide all the money they received.)
You shouldn't keep any of it.
You're not allowed to hide the money...
(They cannot hide the money on their bodies.)
- on your bodies. - Got it.
Next, choose one member from your club.
(After hiding, they'll need to pick one member from each club.)
To find the money?
(The person will be blindfolded to guard the club room.)
That person will be blindfolded...
Blindfolded?
and will guard the club room.
As for the other club members...
(I get it.)
They have to go to the other club rooms...
(All other members...)
and find the money hidden in the rooms.
(must find the hidden money from other clubs.)
You can hit them with a toy hammer.
- That means you're out. - Exactly.
(If they get hit by the toy hammer,)
- If you get hit by the toy hammer, - Yes.
- you're automatically out. - Oh, I see.
(they will be eliminated.)
The total amount of the money you steal...
(The money they steal)
and the money you keep safe will be your club fund.
(The money they guard)
(The final club fund)
Also, if you think you got too many penalty points,
you can give me school support donations,
(Each penalty point will be worth 10 cents.)
and I'll deduct 1 point for 10 cents.
(It can be deducted by paying the school support donation.)
- 10 cents? - So...
(The student with the highest point is now tempted.)
if you want to get a deduction, come to see me quietly.
(The student with chronic inappropriate appearance)
- Do you understand? - Yes.
- I'll give you your club funds now. - How much is it?
(It's time to distribute the club funds.)
The club in first place...
(10 cents)
- Only 1 dollar? - 50 cents, 70 cents, and 1 dollar.
(Band club 1 dollar, Dance club 70 cents)
- How much? - 50 cents.
(Student guidance club 50 cents)
Now, you may go to your club rooms.
We should hide our money well and find their money well.
(It's important to hide the club funds well.)
The dance club!
(The clubrooms are decorated...)
The dance, dance, dance club.
(just like the old days!)
All right. Let's hide our money.
(No mullet)
Let's go.
- Think about where to hide it. - Okay.
(They each look for places to hide the funds.)
We shouldn't hide it where they can see upon the entrance.
1, 2. Americano
(The band club members actually started their club activity.)
I like it so much
Americano
I like it
What should I do?
(The singer is only focused on looking cool.)
I only try to make myself look cool.
That's all I care about. Even when I'm so bad at singing.
(Laughing)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(They started playing a song inspired by the strawberry game.)
- I like it - I like strawberries
(They're too busy making themselves look cool.)
- Strawberries - I love strawberries
(It looks like a religious meeting to worship strawberries.)
Gosh, those punks.
They're so loud.
(They're annoying the other teams by making noise.)
I want to perform in front of people.
Like a busker. Although I'm a lousy singer.
(The desire for busking intensifies regardless of their skills.)
Did you enjoy my song?
(He's only trying to look cool.)
Well, I think I haven't even done half of it yet.
- Are you ready to have fun? - Yes!
Next, I'm going to sing a song by the singer you all love...
- Do you know Jason Mraz? - Yes.
I'll sing "I'm Yours".
(Will he really sing this romantic song?)
"I'm Yours".
Give me the beat.
(Here comes the beat.)
(Half air, half scat)
(He turned the song into a scat song without lyrics.)
I don't know the lyrics.
(His weakness is his poor English proficiency.)
(While the band club is too into themselves,)
You may start hiding your money.
(the other clubs started hiding their money!)
We should start hiding the money?
(The student guidance club tries to hide it near the hanger.)
Roll it and put it inside so they can't see it.
(Jae Suk is leading the team as if he has a lot of experience.)
Okay.
(Where should I hide it?)
But you see...
Jae Suk, wouldn't hiding it here stall for time?
(While Jae Suk tries to teach the innocent Bo Sung...)
- They'll find it easily. - Really?
- That's not good enough. - Is that so?
(While pretending to help them, Kwang Soo...)
(abruptly returns to the hanger?)
It might take them a long time.
They might waste their time here.
(He's taking out the money he hid while looking at them.)
(Stealing)
(Kwang Soo stole the money while Jae Suk was looking away.)
How about under the cushion?
(He's planning to use it to get his penalty points deducted.)
You can give me school support donations,
and I'll deduct 1 point for 10 cents.
(Jae Suk and Bo Sung didn't notice it.)
How about under the cushion?
- Shall we hide it under there? - I'm not sure.
(While the members of the 3 clubs are busy hiding their money...)
(Looking around)
Here you go.
(Haha gave a school support donation.)
You got a lot of penalty points.
(A few moments ago)
The team in 2nd place received 70 cents,
(The band member gave him 30 cents for Haha.)
- so get three points deducted. - Okay.
- Ji Hyo, we'll be fine, right? - Okay.
(Haha got 3 points deducted thanks to his loyal club members.)
Here.
You will leave your club rooms in 10 seconds.
You can kill them with that toy hammer, right?
- Of course, I can. - Okay.
- I can hit them with my fist. - 10,
(Jong Kook will guard the dance club room.)
9, 8...
(Bo Sung, the angel of loyalty, will guard the room.)
- Grab them first. - Can I grab them?
- 6, 5... - Keep our money safe.
(Confident)
- Keep our money safe. - Okay.
- Three. - Loyalty!
(Haha is the unexpected guard of the band club.)
- Two. - Loyalty!
- 1. - 1.
Loyalty!
(It's time to search for the club fund!)
- The loyalty of an angel. - Find their money.
- Here we go. We can do it. - Let's go!
(Avoid the hammer and secure as much club funds as you can!)
- Good luck, guys. - Jong Kook, good luck.
- We can do it. - Let's go!
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo are going straight to the dance club room.)
Jong Kook, good luck.
(Solemn)
Are you going to tell me if someone comes in?
(Se Chan already got scared by how he looks.)
(It means he won't let anyone steal even 10 cents.)
(Jong Kook's impenetrable defense...)
(scared them and made them walk out for now.)
Gosh, I'm so scared.
(She's terrified.)
I'm so scared of him that I can't live anymore.
(Bo Sung is swinging the hammer in the air.)
Loyalty!
The loyalty of an angel.
(However...)
(The loyal man can't notice people coming in.)
(They came into the room without any problems.)
(Relaxed)
(The dance club members are targeting the loyal man.)
Has it begun?
Yes, it's begun.
(Following the dance club members,)
(Kwang Soo came into the student guidance club room.)
Let's go. We can do it.
(Kwang Soo left the room with Jae Suk earlier.)
- All right. - Let's do this.
(After giving the money he stole as a school support donation,)
(he boldly came back to his club room.)
(He quickly took out the money hidden in the tissue box.)
Loyalty!
(He starts stealing money for his club.)
(Right then, Defconn spots Kwang Soo.)
It's not here.
(Betraying Kwang Soo is captured.)
(Bo Sung approaches them after hearing the noise.)
- Did you find it? - Loyalty!
- What's this? Who is it? - It's me.
(Hitting)
- Who is this? - Kwang Soo is out.
How can I be killed by my own team member?
- You can! - Kwang Soo is out.
I can kill my team member?
(He's acting brazenly after stealing his own club's fund.)
- You can. - So why are you here?
- But... - Why are you here?
To protect you, of course!
- Why would you protect me? - What's this?
Kwang Soo, you're out. Come this way.
- No, I found this. - Darn it.
(Blinded by penalty points, he goes straight to the hallway.)
Kwang Soo, come here.
Stand here.
(He pays the school support donation...)
Stand against the wall.
You...
(He pays the school support donation even when he's caught.)
I told you to stand against the wall.
- Stand against the wall. - How dare you steal from us?
(Absurd)
That's not it.
Stand against the wall with your hands up.
You have one minute left.
(There's only a minute left.)
(Jae Suk snuck into band club to find Kwang Soo's money.)
(Scared)
(Haha couldn't catch anyone as he was busy making a fuss.)
Let's go, guidance club!
(Bo Sung still hasn't made any valid hit yet.)
He's right there!
(Se Chan found the student guidance club's fund.)
To your right! Over there!
(The club activity ends.)
- He's right there! - Time's up.
Time's up, everyone.
(There's already 60 cents for the school support donation?)
- Is it over? - It's over.
- I couldn't find any. - Right?
(Who else paid for support donation besides Kwang Soo and Haha?)
- I couldn't find any. - I know.
- What are we playing this time? - It's table tennis!
(They meet the next mission with curiosity.)
Wow, it's going to be so fun!
(It's table tennis.)
Let's play a game.
I'm really good at table tennis.
- There he is! The king of... - Come on!
(The table is surrounded by the bluffers already.)
- This is what I'm talking about! - Yes, I love table tennis.
The '88 Olympics generation.
(They begin their practice rally.)
We are the '88 Olympics generation.
It's a rally.
(Swinging)
Bo Sung is not that good.
(You're not good at it.)
- You're bad at it. - You're pretty bad at it.
- Bo Sung's not a good player. - He's worse than I thought.
How strange. I'm usually good.
(Bo Sung's clumsier than they expected.)
No, wait a minute. Let me try again.
(He wants to try again.)
Let me try again.
(Swinging)
Come on. He can't hit a backhand smash.
Which sports are you good at?
- There you go. - Give him a chance.
(He looks sloppy...)
(even after 3 practices.)
- Bo Sung... - My gosh.
- Bo Sung. - You can't just hit randomly.
- He's so bad. - That's not how you hit.
(Even other teams are worried about Bo Sung.)
Are you playing badminton or something?
(Will Bo Sung be able to take a part in this mission?)
Let me tell you the rules of the final mission.
According to the result of the moral education class,
(The club fund was distributed after the first period.)
the band club won 1 dollar as they won 1st place.
(Club fund earned)
- They won 1 dollar? - The dance club won...
- 70 cents as they won 2nd place. - Okay!
The student guidance club won 50 cents as they came in 3rd.
Now, tell us how much you have in total.
(How much do they have left after the club activity?)
- We have 60 cents. - 60 cents.
We have 60 cents.
(The dance club has 60 cents.)
Someone took our 10 cents.
- We also have 60 cents. - We have 50 cents.
(The band club has 60 cents.)
- We have 60 cents. - That's right.
- 60? - Because he found 10 cents.
We have 30 cents.
(The student guidance club has 30 cents.)
We must win this mission.
(Due to Kwang Soo's embezzlement,)
(the student guidance club's in the last place.)
The second class, our last one, is a PE class.
(Can they turn the table in the 2nd period?)
(PE class)
- All right, PE! - I love it!
- That's ours to win. - We're actually a sports club.
You'll be playing table tennis to expand your territory.
(You'll be playing table tennis to expand your territory.)
Expand our territory? What's that?
Unlike the standard table tennis, three people will play on each side.
(3 players will play for each team.)
Each club can designate a member to receive a penalty point.
(If a person from your team receives 1 penalty point,)
(you can add 2 squares in the other team's table.)
In return, you can add two squares to the other team's table.
That means the other team will have a harder time winning.
(That means the other team will be more difficult to win.)
Oh, we must be using these.
- We'll be using these. - Really?
(You can move each square in the table.)
- I think so. - Oh, this one?
- Really? - We can add more space here.
I've never played a game of table tennis like this.
We'll have more space to hit.
(To buy a part of their territory,)
(one of them has to sacrifice.)
But you must choose a member to receive a penalty point.
- It's like hopscotch. - We need to buy a lot then.
(You may purchase the territory anytime.)
You can purchase their territory anytime you want.
Each team will play against different teams...
(Three teams will play against each other.)
to decide the final winner.
If every team has a win and a loss, we'll decide the winner by points.
(If every team has a win and a loss, we'll decide the winner by points.)
The teacher will be watching you in this class as well.
(The teacher's recording the penalty points like in the 1st period.)
- Okay! - All right.
- Let's play against the dance club. - That sounds great.
(Two teams that will play in the first round are...)
Okay, bring it on.
(student guidance club and band club.)
- We want to buy their territory. - Okay!
(The student guidance club wants to purchase the territory.)
Where shall we place it? Shall we place two at the back?
Since we must win,
- we need to buy a lot. - We'll be buying penalty points.
We'll be giving 2 pieces for 1 penalty point.
(It's 1 penalty point for 2 squares.)
Then we'll buy around 20 pieces with Bo Sung's penalty points.
(With my penalty points?)
For the penalty points...
We can only buy up to 20?
- Shall we buy 10 pieces first? - 10?
- We can win this. - It'll be fine if we win.
(They try to purchase it with Bo Sung's penalty points.)
- It'll be fine if we win. - It'll be fine if we win.
- Really? - It's our last chance.
If you approve it, then you'll be getting the punishment.
(When they buy 10, Bo Sung will have to carry out the penalty.)
No, Bo Sung. Don't be tricked by them.
(The protein monster gets up to stay loyal.)
They should also get the penalty points equally.
(Don't give it all to him.)
- You said you can take a lot. - He's being a jerk.
- Is he? - He's a total jerk.
(Gullible)
It's time to flex your muscles.
He's a total jerk.
- You need to flex your muscles. - Yes, I got 17.
(He flexes his muscles right away.)
- You have 17? - Yes, I got 17.
(The angel uses his fist.)
It doesn't even hurt that much.
(He said you're a jerk.)
- He's a jerk. - Bo Sung, you're...
- We must win so that... - Come here, Bo Sung.
(They failed to buy a chunk of territory.)
- You need to divide the points. - Kwang Soo has 17 points.
(The student guidance club still wants to buy territories.)
Then we have Bo Sung receive...
2 penalty points. We'll buy 4 pieces.
(They buy 4 squares, and Bo Sung gets 2 penalty points.)
Only four?
- Let's buy more later. - We need at least eight.
(What a bummer.)
Let's buy four first.
- Kwang Soo, are we set? - Bo Sung, let's use one more point.
(He implores Bo Sung to secure 2 more squares.)
- Sure, that's fine. - Thank you so much!
(Sure, go ahead.)
That's fine.
(They add 6 squares to the band club's territory.)
Kwang Soo, place it here.
Shall we place one here so that it can get in their way?
- Okay, let's place one there. - Sir.
(1 uncomfortable row is added.)
We'll be placing them like this.
Se Chan, how about we put ours on the side?
- Sure, let's put them here. - Let's put them on the side.
(The band club aims to expand the side, which is easy to attack.)
Then we can go after their side.
That's a good idea.
- You're expanding both sides? - That's how you'll place them?
(They make a right-wing zone to attack the side.)
- That won't help anyway. - Let me warn you all.
We won't be this petty. We'll win with our skills.
- We'll use our skills. - Move.
Don't we have to play the standard game first?
(The dance club keeps kibitzing.)
- Of course! - They placed them too early.
It's because they're bad at table tennis.
Whose penalty points are you using?
We'll be using Se Chan's.
What are you talking about? You said we'll play rock-paper-scissors.
(Flustered)
But you have no penalty points.
Let's use your points first,
(The band club persuades Se Chan.)
- then we'll take turns. - Okay.
- You're using 3 points? - Yes, 3 points. Okay.
You should shout out "my ball".
(Both Se Chan and Bo Sung receive 3 penalty points...)
Say "my ball" when you want to hit the ball.
(and expand the territories.)
Can we start now?
(Round 1 serve game)
Let's play a round to decide who serves first.
Okay, let's do that.
- Bo Sung took off his sunglasses. - He did.
(Taking off his sunglasses)
- Now, he's... - Bo Sung took off his sunglasses.
- Show us what you got now. - Okay, sure.
All right, this is a game to decide who serves first.
(The game to decide the first server starts.)
There's no need to rush. There you go.
(The ball stably goes back and forth.)
Slowly. There you go.
(They keep hitting to Jae Suk's side.)
Haha is pretty good.
- All right! - Nice!
(Se Chan missed it.)
Haha is pretty good.
- Nice! - Jae Suk is our ace.
(Ace Jae Suk gets to serve first.)
All right, we're doing great!
- I'm more serious than ever. - This is an important match.
(Serious)
Let Bo Sung join in too.
- Let's go, Bo Sung! - Let's go!
- Show us what you got. - Sure.
(Jae Suk's first serve)
- He's so ugly. - Hit it, Haha.
- Okay! - Yes!
He's so ugly.
- Hit it, Haha. - Okay!
He was so ugly... Isn't it cheating to make an ugly face?
(He missed the ball while watching Jae Suk's face.)
You're supposed to throw the ball before you serve.
(Jong Kook claims that the ball was too low.)
- But he did this. - That's not how you serve.
- If you do that... - No, it doesn't matter.
This should be allowed though.
(It's tricky to receive the surface-adhering serve.)
Since this is a variety show, you should throw it a little.
(They're requested to serve high for the show.)
- Okay, then. - Okay.
You should serve, Bo Sung.
(Bo Sung serves instead.)
It's okay as long as you pass the ball to the other side.
Bo Sung, show us a fiery serve. Shoot a sharp serve.
You can do it!
(Okay...)
You need to throw the ball.
- Wait a minute. - Wait!
He needs to throw the ball!
- You can do it! - You need to throw the ball.
(Using a table-adhering, magical serving method)
He's pretty good.
He needs to throw the ball! What was that?
(He was supposed to serve high, but he presented a weird serve.)
- He did it. - What was that about?
- What's wrong with it? - You can't serve like that.
(As it gets difficult to receive, they complain.)
You should go easy on the guests.
(Give the guest a break.)
Go easy on the guests.
- This is a legit way to serve. - It's his first time playing.
(The student guidance club decides to insist.)
- This is allowed! - We can serve like that?
- This is allowed then? - Yes.
- Okay. - This is allowed.
(It's Bo Sung's serve again.)
- Okay. - You should receive it.
You should receive it.
- Nice! - You should receive it.
(Bo Sung got them again.)
Nice!
- How did he do that? - This shouldn't be allowed.
(Scoring 2 points with a table-adhering serve)
- How do you do that? - All right.
- How does he serve like that? - You just push the ball forward.
- It's allowed. - What is that?
Push the ball forward.
(The angel's serve)
That's a slider.
- No, that's a curveball. - How does he do that?
You're good. You should serve.
(Bo Sung gets to serve again.)
You want me to serve again?
He serves weirdly.
(Will Bo Sung's weird serve work again?)
- His ball is slow, - He hits there.
- but it doesn't stop. - It's better for us if they win.
- Okay! - All right.
(There you go!)
- He should serve again. - It's weird.
(The band club falls for the breaking ball for the 3rd time.)
- He's so... - We need one more point.
(The expert of a breaking ball)
- We need one more point. - That's right.
Let me tell you the official rules as a professional player.
(At that moment, Suk Jin tries to pick on them.)
- You should... - Suk Jin, move.
The ball needs to leave your hand.
- Move, move. - Hey!
(Two men of the same age are about to fight.)
Go away.
- Hey! Bo Sung... - Move.
(Bo Sung doesn't care about loyalty when it comes to winning.)
- Move! - The ball needs to leave your hand!
- All right. - Let's play now.
- The ball needs to leave your hand. - He can't serve from there.
(Bo Sung serves again.)
- He should step back. - He should step back.
- There you go. - The ball hit the net.
(Se Chan's smash)
Okay!
(Se Chan hit the ball right at the territory they bought.)
- There you go. - Okay!
Well done, Se Chan!
(They're heated up after winning a point with a smash.)
- You're good. - Let's bring back the momentum.
- There you go. - I want to play too.
- Okay! - Okay!
(Se Chan smashes again.)
Don't hit the ball to Se Chan.
(No defense in Jae Suk's extra territory)
- Okay, I got it. - You shouldn't give it to Se Chan.
- What about it? - Hit it quickly.
(The band club sustains the momentum.)
Smash it. Okay!
(He succeeds in hitting 3 smashes in a row.)
- Okay! - Hold on! Time out.
- Let us use your penalty points. - We turned the tables on you.
(As they keep losing points, he allows to purchase more territory.)
- We turned the tables on you. - Hang on.
- Let us buy more territory. - In an instant.
- Let us buy two more pieces. - Let us buy more territory.
(With 1 penalty point for Bo Sung, 2 pieces are added.)
How could you get...
(They use Bo Sung every time they're in crisis.)
- smashed instantly? - Se Chan is quite good.
Se Chan. Se Chan is really good.
(Practicing)
Give me the ball.
(Clenching their teeth, they move 4 pieces.)
We're buying more territory.
Whose penalty points are you using?
Bo Sung's.
Stop bullying Bo Sung!
- It's okay. - We're using Bo Sung's points.
Why would you let them take advantage of you, Bo Sung?
(He exceeded the recommended daily loyalty amount.)
I'm ruined already. We need to win first.
It'll be fine if we win, Bo Sung.
(The table is fixed.)
We're all set.
Let's play now.
We must get this.
(It's a tie. They'll take turns to serve.)
Why don't you take turns to serve? Only one person is playing.
- Let Ji Hyo play too. - Okay, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo who hasn't served gets special treatment.)
- Let her play. - But I'm not good.
- It's okay. The ball... - It's okay if you're bad.
needs to hit our table first and theirs.
- So this is how you play. - It needs to hit our table first.
- There you go. That's how you play. - Spike!
No, that doesn't count!
- Spike! - No, that doesn't count!
(A powerful smash)
(Watch. This is table tennis.)
- Hey. - That was...
You can't do that.
All right. We won.
(I can't believe him.)
- We won. - That's so mean.
- Kwang Soo must be upset! - We won.
(I don't care as long as I win.)
- We won. - Good job.
They lost.
- That little... - Kwang Soo must be upset.
(In front of angry Ji Hyo,)
- Kwang Soo is upset. - Okay!
(he provokes her by jumping.)
- He's so annoying. - Ji Hyo must be hurt.
(He's annoying.)
- He's so annoying. - Okay!
Kwang Soo.
(The student guidance club tries to come up with a plan...)
I'll throw the ball, you serve.
(before the next rally.)
(Whispering)
Who should hit the ball? Me or you?
Jae Suk, let Bo Sung join in too.
(A team play of their own)
Let him join in too!
(Peeping)
Why would you leave him out?
- It's not like that. - Let him join in too.
(They look for Bo Sung only when they need a penalty point.)
Are you only using Bo Sung for penalty points?
- Let him join in too. - No.
Bo Sung, I'm sorry.
They only use Bo Sung for penalty points.
(The game resumes without Bo Sung knowing the plan.)
- Yes. - Go.
Okay.
(Ready)
(Is Bo Sung serving?)
That's it. It went in.
(Meanwhile, he even scored a point.)
That's it.
- Wait a minute. - It went in.
(He scores a point by serving.)
- It went in. - It went in.
- But he hit it from here. - It went in.
(He happens to score a point.)
But Bo Sung just did it without discussing it with us.
- It went in. - We were planning something else.
(He doesn't even need to come up with a strategy.)
- But... - He's sly.
- It went in. - That's nice.
What you did had no sense of loyalty.
- Let's stack them. - This won't do.
(The band club in crisis purchases more territory.)
It's too large.
There won't be any outs this way.
(The band club fills the side.)
Just use mine then. How many points is that total?
(At that moment,)
- Yes. - Do you have five penalty points?
(Bo Sung walks away.)
How many are you stacking?
- Is Bo Sung buying more? - You have to buy them.
(Is Bo Sung buying the territory himself?)
- With whose points? - Are you buying them?
(The penalty point)
- With Kwang Soo's points. - Wait a minute, I...
(Cheerful)
(A penalty point is added to Kwang Soo without discussion.)
- You can't add to my points. - I'll do it.
- I didn't agree. - Okay.
(Pretending not to hear them)
- We'll add to Kwang Soo's points. - I have 17 points.
- Just buy two. - What?
- You're buying them with my points? - Yes.
(Even the angel cannot accept Kwang Soo cheating.)
- Wait, I didn't agree. - Let's add 9 and 2 more.
It's funny though.
(As they keep expanding the territory,)
(they keep getting more penalty points.)
It expanded up to there.
(After the expansion, it's the band club's turn to serve.)
You should hit an unexpected ball.
- We don't know who'll hit a serve. - I'll hit it.
(Se Chan and Haha stick together to serve.)
- Come. - Go.
(A copy and paste table tennis ball show)
(Swinging)
Pin the ball down.
- He's out. - He's out.
- He was too greedy. - He should have succeeded.
(Despite the strategy, they lose a point.)
- He has to succeed to survive. - That's right.
I also want to try that.
(They want to copy the table tennis ball copy method.)
- Okay. - My shoulders hurt.
- Let's go to the finals. It's fun. - Let's go.
You will go to the finals? Oh, my. What is happening?
(At that moment)
(What?)
(Their ambush failed.)
- That was really fast. - It's the finals.
(They lose a point after cheating.)
- You shouldn't have said anything. - They won.
- It was the finals. - We won because of that.
(He even fails to cheat due to game fright.)
- If you were going to feint... - I'm sorry.
- If you going for an ambush... - You shouldn't have said anything.
(The game continued.)
If a team scores one more point, the game will be over.
(The team that wins 1 point wins.)
It's okay as long as we win, right?
- Kim Bo Sung, you can do it! - Yes.
(They're reconfirming their determination...)
(since victory is right around the corner.)
(Se Chan's serve)
- Hit it lightly. - Is it the match point?
- Okay. - That's good.
(Se Chan passed the ball toward Kwang Soo.)
- Oh, my. - Nice!
(He hurrahed as a reflex.)
- What did he just do? - What did he just do?
(Kwang Soo avoided the ball, but it settled safely on their territory.)
Nice!
- The band club won the first round. - We won.
(The band club wins the 1st round.)
(The penalty point donator is feeling bitter.)
- They won because of this. - We lost.
I couldn't hit the ball because of this.
(This result was caused by expanding territory only on one side.)
(They won against the student guidance club.)
- Good job. - We did a really good job.
Let's try a rally.
(The dance club guys finally get to play table tennis.)
- Good. - Let's do a rally.
- Let's do it once. - Please let me play.
(Prominent table tennis player)
- Okay, wait a minute. - Wait a minute.
(So Min who looks clearly precarious is playing amongst guys.)
- Wait a minute. - If we have some extra time,
(Refusing to answer)
- we will let you play. - Gosh.
- I... - Do you want to put this in here?
I will give up five of my penalty points to play.
(They're preoccupied with playing table tennis.)
- Gosh, So Min. - Jong Kook.
I will give up five of my penalty points to play.
(No one heard...)
(So Min's wild suggestion.)
I want to play.
- I also want to play. - You're good.
- I will give you five points. - Everyone...
(They don't even listen to the production crew.)
- I also want to play! - Everyone...
- I'm good. - Let's play one more time.
I also want to play!
(Let me play table tennis.)
- So Min, play. - Okay.
- I'll give you five points. - Okay, let's go.
(She finally gets to talk to them after going on a strike.)
- Join in. - And...
(So Min's approved to play. It's time to pick the opponent.)
Please decide who she will play against for the first round.
You Small Fries should come out.
- Yes, student guidance club. - Small fries, come out.
(The dance club plays against the student guidance club first.)
- That'll be a real match. - So Min, you should go first.
- Give up 1 point each. - I'll buy So Min's 5 points.
(They purchase the territory before playing.)
We will serve.
Okay, go first.
- Show them an unexpected ball. - Bo Sung.
- His ball is really unexpected. - It really is.
(Bo Sung's serve is known to be disloyal.)
- It's hard to block. - I'll block it.
I can block it.
(Big Nose who is about the same age is confident.)
(The unexpected ball sets off.)
You can block it like this.
(He succeeds to defend.)
- Okay. - Oh, my.
(Crushing)
You can block it like this.
(Too short)
- Okay. - Oh, my.
(As Jong Kook who was confident performs slapstick comedy,)
- He got caught. - It was too long.
(the nonstop laughter appears.)
- He got caught. - Gosh.
- Hey! - Don't laugh.
(Laughing)
He's really so annoying.
Okay, good.
(He tries to keep a smile on.)
Okay.
(He was like this.)
It's okay.
(Trying to smile)
- He's really enjoying it. - It's okay.
(It's not easy even for Jong Kook to ignore Kwang Soo's sneer.)
Don't be affected by him.
- Don't be affected by him. - I'm not affected at all.
Good job.
(Laughing)
(The dance club lost a point.)
- Good job. - Come here.
- He's not teasing you. - Did you see that, Jong Kook?
(He's about to pass out.)
- Not at all. It didn't bother me. - Hey.
(Trying to stay cool)
- He's not scoffing at you. - No.
(Bo Sung continues with the serve again.)
- That's right! - Gosh.
(It's again too short.)
- It's okay. - It's okay.
- There's a distance, so it's okay. - Okay.
(He shows no loyalty when it comes to the serve.)
(They're discouraged.)
- We can't let them off now. - Spread some more territory.
- You also have Jeon So Min. - Okay.
- So Min. - That's right.
- So Min. - Okay.
(Hitting)
It's okay.
- It's okay. - I was warming up.
(She hit the ball for the first time, but it's out.)
- So Min, just sit down. - It's okay.
- No, I was warming up. - Come to the center.
(She braces herself up by saying it was a warm-up.)
- Good job. - It's funny to see...
So Min make a vain effort.
We just have to score five more points with this spirit.
(The student guidance club is in high spirits now.)
(However)
We scored a lot of points.
- Wait a minute. Time out. - We scored a lot of points.
Jong Kook kept pushing me with his arm to tell me to leave.
- He told me to leave. - No, So Min. You are completely...
(Stealthily)
(He stealthily pushed her again.)
Five more points in this spirit.
- Just be in charge of the corner. - I kept moving to the center,
(A lame excuse)
(Jong Kook creates a useless job to secure the corner.)
- and you said, "Leave." - Just be in charge of the corner.
Just the two of them are playing.
- Where should I stop? - No, right here.
(Where should I stop?)
- It's a match. - Right here. That's good.
(She defends a quiet corner.)
It's a match.
(Guest "Dae Buk Gon" is also excluded from the match...)
- It's a match. - Right here. That's good.
(as much as So Min.)
(The two are too serious for their level of contribution.)
It's a really important match, So Min.
Wait a minute.
Both of them have a sense of pride when it comes to table tennis.
- Can you hit from the side? - Yes?
(The middle-aged men bet their lives on the ball play.)
- From the side? - This is perfect.
If the ball crosses the net, it's yours, okay?
(After assigning So Min to watch the corner, the game resumes.)
- Okay, I understand. - How can I hit it from here?
If the ball crosses the net, it's yours.
(The student guidance club in high spirit serves.)
Wait a minute.
(Did they lose a point again?)
- What? - Okay.
Suk Jin, why did you take your jacket off?
You said you were the representative of something.
(The '88 Olympics generation keeps losing points without one rally.)
- What do you represent? - Gosh.
- I'll stay back later. You... - Are you losing?
- Let's play like doubles. - Try it. No.
- No. - I'm also here.
(Why is it doubles when you have me?)
- I'm also here. - But...
- No, I'm also here. - He said it was a doubles game.
(So Min didn't know about the doubles.)
- The audio isn't being recorded. - No, but...
(He even removed the mic.)
Where is my mic?
- Your mic... - My mic doesn't matter right now.
(She even bought the territory, but she got deceived.)
I added territory here with my five points.
I have a share.
I think we will lose when I didn't even play.
(The guest hasn't even played yet.)
No, I'm sorry, Defconn. It's an important moment right now.
(The members become this serious when they play ball games.)
Be careful of feinting.
(The game begins.)
- Gosh. - Stop saying "Gosh" and just...
- That's good! - Gosh.
(Thud)
Stop saying "Gosh" and just...
(Gosh...)
- Look at that. - Hey.
(Kwang Soo passes out.)
Add more territory.
- No, it's okay. - It's okay.
(Playful Child also passes out.)
Hey, we can't reach it!
(He teases with all his might.)
(It caused rather big damage to just ignore him.)
(He exaggerates with all his might.)
That's it.
(His face turned red.)
- No, it's okay. - Spread some more territory.
(Jong Kook becomes full of humanity whenever he plays ball games.)
It's okay. I can't reach it.
(The nonstop laughter gave his all.)
I'll try it once and then you should try it.
- It's because we both... - Okay.
(At that moment)
- try to do it at the same time. - I got it. Let's try that.
(The outskirt table tennis player penetrated the center.)
She's really incredible.
(Meanwhile, she's doing an intense simulation in the center.)
So Min is really incredible. She tries endlessly.
(They respect her tenacity.)
- She's like a weed. - She's really incredible.
(No matter how much you push her, So Min won't be pushed.)
- She won't die no matter what. - Jeon So Min is incredible.
Spread some more territory.
(The dance club in crisis rushes to buy more territory.)
They can reach it, but we can't.
- It's disadvantageous for us. - We can't reach the short ones.
Anyway, are you angry?
I'm not angry at all.
(Lately, Suk Jin has been showing the human side of him.)
- Angry? I'm smiling right now. - You look angry.
- But after you came here... - I'm not angry at all.
(While the eldest brother was putting his anger aside,)
(the guest is buying territory in silence.)
Bring that over here.
Excuse me... Anyway...
- Just do it. - We should also...
(He tries to talk,)
- I'll receive short serves here. - Okay.
(but no one listens.)
- Okay. - Okay, that's good.
Hit a serve toward here.
- Defconn, aren't you going to play? - Why won't you let him join in?
(Even the other teams try to take care of him.)
- Jong Kook. - Look after the guests!
(But they're all busy talking amongst themselves.)
Defconn is sullen.
Suk Jin, let him play. Let him play.
- Defconn. - What's the point of playing now?
What's the point of playing now when you have ruined the match?
You can be in charge of reactions.
- Reactions, my foot! - Reactions.
(Reactions?)
I will never visit this show again!
I will never visit this lousy show again!
(This guest curses the show on his first visit.)
- We need to win. - Come on.
How dare you treat a guest like this?
(Angry Buk Gon unleashes his accumulated anger.)
It's the producer's job to tell the members to switch!
- Defconn. - You seem younger than me too!
(He's too kind to say anything to the older members.)
I am sorry.
I apologize for my outburst.
(He comes back to his senses.)
You can play in the next round.
(He finally earns the right to enter the next game.)
- All right. Okay. - All right.
Suk Jin told him to show reactions and go home.
(He's a guest.)
"Defconn, show reactions and go home."
(Defconn's mood improves since he can play the next time.)
We have the worst teamwork.
You agree, right?
(So Min goes and tells on the teacher.)
Everyone is playing individually.
Also, Suk Jin is trying to play...
all by himself.
- I could do this alone. - He is like Nolbu.
(Like Nolbu, he is declaring that he would rather play alone.)
- You need to win. - All right.
(Student guidance club 10, Dance club, 4)
You need to do better.
(The dance club tries to rebuild their teamwork.)
- That's right. - For goodness' sake.
Stay there until the ball comes.
- Think of it as doubles. - Jong Kook.
(But it's a match point for the student guidance club.)
- Okay, okay. - Tell me when to come in.
- Let's go. - No, no.
I could do this.
- Come on. - Stay there.
(The game begins.)
- So Min, stay there. - Here it comes.
Here it comes.
(Jong Kook's backhand)
There you go.
- He sent it over. - Hey.
(And again)
There you go.
(Kwang Soo hits it again.)
- Hey! - What was that?
(The match ends because of Suk Jin's mistake.)
For goodness' sake.
Take it off. All of it.
(He didn't get to show off his skills from the old days.)
- What was that? - Suk Jin.
- Loyalty! - We won.
(The student guidance club wins for the first time.)
(Bo Sung played a critical role in the team's victory.)
The last match is between the dance club and the band club.
Let's go!
(The result of the match between band club and dance club)
- All right. - We won thanks to you.
(All three teams have 1 win and 1 loss.)
Since all three teams have 1 win and 1 loss,
(The rankings will be decided by the points.)
we got the rankings by the points.
By earning 1 more point, the 1st place winner became...
the student guidance club.
(Student guidance club wins with 21 points.)
- Okay! - Really?
Why? Did they place first?
- Student guidance club? - Didn't we place first?
The band club placed second.
(Band club is in 2nd place.)
Is it us?
The dance club placed 3rd with 25 points.
(Dance club is in 3rd place.)
- Did they place last? - Did we place last?
- This is great. - The 1st place gets 2 dollars.
(1st place gets 2 dollars. 2nd place gets 1.5 dollars.)
- 2 dollars? - Then 1.50 dollars and 1 dollar.
(3rd place gets 1 dollar.)
Two dollars?
(They need to protect this money in order to win!)
You did well with PE.
(The teacher will announce additional penalty points.)
During PE, I watched everyone...
- and assigned penalty points. - Really?
(The points are based on fun, manners, and skills.)
- Suk Jin, three points. - Why?
Despite being the oldest member, you neglected the guests.
(Despite being the oldest member, he neglected the guests.)
- It's true. - It's true.
It's the oldest member's fault.
He told me to show reactions and go home.
(He forced Buk Gon only to react.)
- It's the oldest member's fault. - I heard it.
- Three points. - It's the oldest member's fault.
Jong Kook, seven points.
(Kim Jong Kook gets 7 penalty points!)
What?
Seven points.
You used your strength to push your fellow club member.
(The word "strength" describes everything.)
He pushed me.
I saw you do that twice,
(He restrains himself from using his strength.)
so I gave you seven points.
(After distributing final support fee and penalty points,)
Se Chan, where does he live?
(it's time for the final activity to decide the winner!)
- Him? He lives in Yeonhui-dong. - Yeonhui-dong?
He lives close.
Jae Suk, 3 points. Haha, 3 points.
(The official penalty points except for club activities)
They tried to make the club members lose points.
(It's time for the final club activities!)
- Bo Sung. - Yes?
Kwang Soo is the most dangerous one.
I think he came in earlier and stole club funds.
(Kwang Soo stole the club fund...)
(to submit as a school support donation.)
(The student guidance club members are worried.)
- Our club funds? - That's right.
This time, we should have Kwang Soo stay here...
in a blindfolded state.
Okay.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
(Kwang Soo will be blindfolded to prevent any embezzlement.)
You will be blindfolded this time.
You should do it this time.
(Freezing)
- I can do it, but... - You should do it.
Isn't Bo Sung the best at this role?
No, no. I tried it earlier. It was so suffocating.
(His excuses don't work anymore.)
You got caught too early on the last time.
- It was so suffocating. - But...
(The members are suspecting Kwang Soo.)
I think you got caught on purpose the last time.
Isn't that right?
(The angel shows off his punches.)
Be honest.
Jae Suk.
Let's forget about the past and start over...
- Forget about the past? - You took all the money, right?
Kwang Soo, you are exactly how you seem on TV.
(Bo Sung won't be fooled this time.)
I am very disappointed in you.
- Give us one each. - I expected more from you.
(He pays up 20 cents.)
(My money too!)
I will give you one each,
but the hammer...
(But...)
You need to hold the hammer.
(Kwang Soo is it.)
If you don't hold the hammer, you will steal the money again.
- Rock-paper-scissors... - No, no.
Kwang Soo will be it.
(They now need to hide the club fund.)
Please hide the club funds.
Kwang Soo, wait outside.
- What? - Come on.
(Kwang Soo is completely outcasted from the beginning.)
How will I find it with my eyes covered?
- Wait outside. - Wait outside.
(Lee Kwang Soo, get out of the room.)
- I am a club member too. - Wait outside.
- Wait outside. - Wait outside?
(The angel of loyalty guides the traitor out.)
- Wait outside. - We should hide the funds together.
Wait outside. Wait outside.
I mean... This is driving me crazy.
(Kwang Soo is now forced to stay out in the hallway.)
13. 15.
(Meanwhile, the band club...)
- How many do you have? - I have six.
We have 21.
(The band club is almost in 1st place...)
We are in first place.
(with the club fund of 2.1 dollars.)
We shouldn't turn in money.
(For the team's victory)
- We shouldn't turn in money. - No.
- You should be it. - I will be it.
(The dance club is in the last place with a fund of 1.6 dollars.)
- Again? - I have done it before.
- Let's go! Good luck! - Let's go!
(They try to turn the tables with Operation: Kim Jong Kook.)
(All three clubs finished hiding their club funds.)
Put it in the same spot.
1, 2, 3, 4.
(The band club finished hiding the money early on.)
From head
("Hot Issue" by 4Minute)
- To toe, I am a hot issue - To toe, I am a hot issue
- Everything about me is a hot issue - Everything about me is a hot issue
(It's a total cacophony that hurts the listener's ears.)
Hot it, hot it, hot it, hot it, hot issue
(The band club gives a ceremony to celebrate their victory.)
Let's begin. Let's go.
(After the performance, it's time to search the other rooms.)
The last club activity will begin.
(The last search starts.)
(So Min searches the student guidance club's room!)
(The student guidance club took 2 dollars,)
(but the money is nowhere to be seen.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo is protecting the band club's room.)
Here. Hurry up!
(Se Chan enters.)
Hurry up!
(Se Chan said they should save up and win.)
(He is stealing from his own club's room.)
What?
(He goes to all the hiding spots he remembers.)
(Haha enters as well.)
(Haha approaches with a thief's facial expression.)
(He steals a small amount of money and runs away.)
(Dazed)
(Thus, the band club faces a crisis.)
(But Se Chan and Haha aren't the only ones.)
(The students grow bold.)
We are getting a lot of school support donations.
(Which club will save the club fund and emerge as the winner?)
I will announce the result.
(It's time to announce the results.)
Show us the remaining club funds.
(The club with the highest funds will win the scholarship.)
We have a thief...
within the club.
(There's a thief among us.)
- They are unbelievable. - I saw it with my own eyes.
Se Chan stole from his own team.
(She finds out about the thief from other teams.)
- Good job. - Hey.
(She shows off her charisma fueled by their betrayal.)
- Don't be ridiculous. - That's the band club.
- The band club. - You are unbelievable.
("Dirty Mustache" teamwork broke down just like its name.)
Haha is the worst.
- Haha is the worst. - No, Se Chan is.
(They blame each other.)
Do you know what Se Chan is like?
- He steals from the staff members. - Ji Hyo is annoyed.
(The band club only has 50 cents left.)
- Don't be ridiculous. - If a cell phone goes missing,
it's his fault.
- All right. - We left a lot of money.
Earlier...
(The dance club's final amount is...)
- 15. - 9 and 6, right?
- 15. - 15.
(1.5 dollars!)
15.
- 15. - 15?
(The dance club's fund remains almost intact!)
Kwang Soo. Where is one?
(It's the student guidance club's turn.)
One.
(Kwang Soo was restrained in the 2nd round.)
- I didn't donate it. - You didn't donate it?
(If they have less than 1.50 dollars,)
(the dance club will turn the table and win.)
We have two.
- 2? - 2?
(From 2.3 dollars, they only have 20 cents?)
- That's 20 cents. - Didn't you hide the funds?
(What happened?)
We have the result of the club activity.
(The winning club is...)
With 1.50 dollars, the dance club won...
(The dance club wins...)
(with 1.50 dollars!)
and acquired the scholarship.
- We won. - Look at this, Defconn.
(The dance club with great bonding wins the scholarship.)
We won in the end.
- That's right. - We won.
(They're actual gift certificates worth 1,000 dollars...)
- I did my best. - These are gift certificates.
(for four of them to share.)
Are those actual gift certificates?
Who gets the penalty is unrelated, right?
(3 people with the highest penalty points will get the penalty.)
Okay. It's my goal to avoid the penalty.
Kwang Soo might avoid the penalty.
- The penalty... - That's right. You never know.
(You can avoid the penalty if you donated to the school a lot.)
This team submitted 15 for the school support donation.
- 10 should have been enough. - Seriously.
(Which 3 members will get chosen for an annoying penalty?)
You never know.
Did you enjoy the classes?
(The teacher returns to announce the penalty points.)
Yes, we did.
I will reveal...
(It's time to reveal the total penalty points...)
how many penalty points each student received...
(before the club activities.)
during the classes.
Check your points.
- 22 points? - 13 points?
(These three members are likely to get the penalty.)
I didn't do that badly.
- 22 points? - 13 points?
(The three members are likely candidates...)
(based on the penalty points.)
I didn't do that badly.
- But this isn't important. - Why not?
(But they all actively paid the school support donations.)
- The rankings changed. - Of course.
(As a result, the rankings changed.)
There are students who submitted lots of school support donations.
(1 point will be deducted for every 10 cents.)
Because of those students,
the rankings changed a lot.
You know that the bottom three students...
(What's the tedious penalty the three must complete?)
have to stay behind and carry out a penalty, right?
- Yes. - We know.
The penalty...
(Today's penalty)
involves composing a written apology...
(Writing a full-page apology letter)
- on a sheet of 400-letter paper. - I hate that.
(They need to write out each word.)
- Really? - That's insane.
- I hate that. - You have to write it.
The written apology...
will go up on Running Man's social media account.
(It'll be uploaded to the program's social media account.)
- What? - You have to fill up the paper.
- I hate it. - But it's my first time here.
(A humiliating experience of writing an apology letter)
This student received the least amount of penalty points.
To be honest, we didn't do anything wrong.
The first place.
I will announce the changed rankings.
(It's time to announce the final rankings.)
The 1st place has 2 penalty points.
(The 1st place has only 2 penalty points.)
Two points?
(It's Jae Suk Yu!)
Jae Suk.
(How did Jae Suk win 1st place?)
He stole 20.
(During the 2nd club activity)
- Put on a blindfold. 10, 9... - Put on a blindfold.
(The duo got to work as soon as Kwang soo put on a blindfold.)
2, 1.
(They stole their own club money.)
Bo Sung, you are out.
- Out! - Bo Sung, you are out.
(While Bo Sung showed his loyal side and held back Kwang Soo,)
(Jae Suk stole 200 dollars from a student guidance club fund.)
I will donate.
(He gave it all away as the school support donation.)
That's 10, right?
I will donate for Bo Sung.
(Half of it went to Bo Sung!)
(Both Jae Suk and Bo Sung deducted 10 penalty points.)
I trust Jae Suk wholeheartedly.
(The angel of loyalty finally shines light in the end!)
It's loyalty.
- 10. - 10?
(Jae Suk placed 1st and became Bo Sung's savior.)
Then he must be in second place.
The second place is...
(Ji Hyo, Haha, Se Chan, Bo Sung, and Defconn are exempt.)
Ji Hyo. Then come Haha, Se Chan,
Bo Sung, and Defconn.
Now comes seventh place.
(1 will survive and 3 people will get the penalty.)
This person is the last one to be exempt, right?
(Only 1 of the 4 will be able to avoid the penalty.)
That's right.
The last one to be exempt is...
(Who will be the last lucky one to avoid the penalty?)
I bet it's Suk Jin.
I didn't have that many penalty points.
Please. I am sorry. Please.
(One member managed to survive as the 7th place.)
So Min!
(So Min is exempt as she wins 7th place.)
I was a good student!
- I was a good student! - That means you didn't donate.
I didn't donate.
(So Min went down to 7th place after failing to donate anything.)
- Seriously. - You are a good person.
Of course I am. Trust me.
(She barely avoids the penalty.)
(Jong Kook, Suk Jin, and Kwang Soo have to compose a written apology.)
- That means you didn't donate. - I didn't donate. Seriously.
The 8th place is Jong Kook with 16 points.
You did it.
No, I got the penalty.
The 9th place is Suk Jin with 17 points.
The last place is Kwang Soo with 18 points.
Do I still have 18 points?
(He still has 18 points.)
In any case, you did well with the classes.
(Everyone can go home except for the bottom three.)
Everyone can go home...
- except for the bottom three. - Thank you.
(Thanks to Kim Bo Sung, Defconn, Shin Gyu Jin for joining us today.)
- Okay. - Running Man, let's go!
- Thank you for your hard work. - Loyalty!
You really need to compose a written apology.
(It's time to compose a written apology.)
I will do it with seriousness.
How could you steal during the first club activity?
(He regrets the day.)
This is insane.
Sometimes, I cheated.
(They squeeze their brains out to fill the paper.)
I should have attacked my own team...
- to collect money. - I should have survived...
(They compose a written apology after decades.)
- by betraying the others. - Jong Kook kept me from doing it.
If I ever have a child...
- A child... Gosh. - A child... Hey!
I will teach him or her at a young age...
(Seducing other students by reading)
to survive...
You are confusing me.
Jong Kook, be quiet.
(They're even more distracted.)
I messed up because of you.
You are confusing me. "At a young age..."
- And... - My dad said, "Be honest."
(They talk about their families as they have nothing else to say.)
"Be honest." Hey.
Hey.
For goodness' sake.
(You can check them out on Running Man's SNS account.)
Come on!
- I only wrote five lines. - I am sorry. I am sorry.
You should walk in the snow.
(Deep in the snowy mountain,)
We are isolated.
(the members seem to be isolated.)
It should be here.
I really don't have it. I don't.
(It seems like they are looking for something.)
- Did someone visit already? - How are we supposed to find it?
(Big sister, help me!)
- Big sister, help me! - Hey!
Do I have a big sister?
- Suk Jin. - Suk Jin lost.
(The strong sister, Kim Jae Hwa)
- Gosh. - She is so strong.
(The cheerful sister, Cha Chung Hwa)
- Let's dance! - She is here to dance.
- She is ambitious. - She is like a delinquent.
(The ambitious sister, Shin Dong Mi)
How dare you challenge the Shin family?
- Do you want to go against us? - Do you want to do this?
- Hey! Your uncle! - Watch what you say.
(The love between the siblings shine.)
(They get the right to distribute the allowance.)
- Hey. - Here you go.
(The siblings' love is put to test.)
- I got this. - Let's trust each other.
Did it make you feel good to steal all the money?
(The younger siblings become obsessed with the allowance.)
- It's a war. - It's a war.
(The families are about to scatter.)
I will end you.
(What will become of the three families?)
- Big sister! - How could you?
(The Charismatic Sisters, The Ugly Siblings)
Big sister!