(Last week)
(Superstars joined
Running Man last week!)
(Hello, So Min.)
(Happily screaming)
(4 cast members from "Secret Zoo")
(Ahn Jae Hong, Kang Sora,
Jeon Yeo Been, Kim Sung Oh)
(The captains must arrive first
with their team members.)
(She's not on his Jae Hong's team.)
(All sorts of scams and tricks
unfolded to obstruct one another.)
(Stealing his phone)
(The two of you are on my team.)
(Come on, don't lie.)
(Hey, let's not do this.)
(At the end of many hardships,)
(they finally formed their teams.)
(Which team will arrive first
for the opening segment?)
(The place of their opening segment
is the SBS building in Mok-dong.)
(The first two teams to arrive
will get a benefit for the race.)
(At that time,
the first team arrives.)
- It's Kwang Soo's team.
- Okay.
(Which team arrived first?)
- Be careful.
- Thank you.
- Goodness.
(The first person to arrive is...)
(Sora.)
(Team Sora
is the 1st one to arrive.)
- We pull out the flag, right?
- All right.
(Team Sora gets a benefit.)
- This does make me happy.
- Okay.
- I see a flag.
- Oh, no.
It's still there.
- Suk Jin.
- Gosh.
(Team Yeo Been
is the 2nd to arrive.)
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- Hello, Yeo Been.
- Hi.
- Hello. Jae Hong.
- They are on your team?
- So Min wasn't on your team.
- My goodness.
- Hello. Hi.
She totally got seduced by Jae Hong.
(So Min definitely was a big help
for Team Jae Hong.)
Didn't I tell you?
You can't trust people
with faces like his.
Come on.
You need to get a grip, So Min.
Suk Jin.
You're wearing shoes
a prime minister in Joseon wore.
(You're wearing shoes
a prime minister in Joseon wore.)
- Are those UGG boots?
- I thought...
- The UGGs Lim Soo Jung wore?
- I mean,
- Hey, didn't she wear those?
- "I'm Sorry, I Love You".
- That's the ones Soo Jung wore.
- I couldn't believe my eyes.
- I was so surprised.
- The prime minister wears them.
- I thought you were wearing a cast.
- My goodness.
- Why are you wearing those?
- What are you talking about?
- Hey, these are warm.
- The prime ministers wore them.
- Prime minister's shoes?
- All right.
Well, actually,
- because of the morning mission,
- Right.
so we didn't get
to say hello properly.
- They filmed a movie together.
- A film.
- "They Don't Bite".
- It's called...
It's not "They Don't Bite."
- Suk Jin.
- What?
If you don't know the title,
just be quiet.
Come on.
- Come on, Prime Minister.
- My apologies.
- It's "Don't Harm Me."
- No.
- Seriously.
It's "Secret Zoo."
- This movie takes place at a zoo.
- Right.
- What is this movie about?
- There are no animals at the zoo.
So the zoo is about to close down.
And the employees of the zoo
put on costumes...
- and pretend...
- You put on costumes.
- to be animals.
- You become fake animals.
- You'll be fake animals?
- Yes.
Do you really think
this is possible?
One of the costumes seems off.
- Let me ask Jae Hong this.
- Okay.
- You have a history with Suk Jin.
- Jae Hong.
- "Candy in My Ears".
- Actually, Jae Hong and I...
talked a lot on the phone
three years ago.
- You were on a TV program, right?
- Yes.
How did you feel after finding out
that Suk Jin was your partner?
The thing is
when the batteries ran out,
- the call ended.
- Right.
- That was what the TV show about.
When the batteries ran out,
the call ends.
So I kept the flashlight on
with the phone.
(So I kept the flashlight on
with the phone.)
(Bursting into laughter)
(I knew it.
The calls ended too quickly.)
- So...
- He wanted the call to end fast.
I really liked him.
- So the battery runs out fast.
- That was funny.
(He kept it on
hoping the battery ran out fast.)
That's so funny.
Everyone here is entertaining.
- Jae Hong has entertaining stories.
- That's funny.
- You can split your legs?
- He's flexible.
Yes, I can do the splits.
- Can you show us?
- I would've never guessed.
I can also split legs.
- Someone else's legs.
- Right.
- That's your area of expertise.
- He won't stop there.
- He'll split everything.
- Everything.
- Why would you do that?
- I mean,
- I was just saying.
- Well, for legs...
- Can you show us?
- The leg split?
If you can't, he'll help you.
- The side split or the front split?
- Either one is fine.
He can do the front and back.
- The front split might be better.
- The front split.
- The side split is harder.
- The side split is really hard.
- I'll do the side split.
- Yes.
- Really?
- You can really do that?
- That's the hard one.
- You can do it?
- You can do it in those pants?
- Don't overdo yourself.
- I'll go easy on myself.
- Okay.
- It's hard in those pants.
- Wait.
- It's hard in the morning.
- Do the front split.
- The front split?
- Yes.
I don't care which one.
Can't you just do it?
(I don't care which one.
Can't you just do it?)
(Struggling)
I don't think he can do it.
(Screaming)
(Wide leg split)
(Surprised)
Gosh, he can do it.
- I didn't think he could.
- He's really good.
- Doesn't that hurt?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Are those your legs?
- By the way,
- Hung Kam Bo was really flexible.
- Right.
- Why did you bring him up now?
- Why would you say that now?
(Suddenly mentioning Hung Kam Bo)
- Listen.
- Why are we talking about him?
- All of a sudden?
I'm saying that
some people are flexible...
- although they don't look flexible.
- Right.
Other people can do the splits.
Why did you bring him up?
That's amazing.
(After Jae Hong
who showed off his flexibility...)
- And Sora is here today.
- All right.
- Pine trees, green pine trees.
Sora, how was it today?
You briefly did a mission.
It was brief, but you said
something was shocking.
The betrayals among the members.
(She sounds cheerful.)
- She...
- That was shocking?
- She was so shocked in the car.
- She couldn't do it.
(It was really shocking.)
By the way, Sora...
- is famous for her selfies.
- She takes a lot? She likes it?
Her fans have a nickname for it.
- Selfie Fool.
- SF.
Gosh, here it is. There.
- That kind of selfie...
- Did you take that photo?
- That...
- Did someone take it for you?
People take that kind of photos
for advertisements.
People don't usually use
these photos.
- You took them and uploaded them?
- Is this how you take photos?
- Yes, I posted it a long time ago.
- You posted it online?
- She's good now.
- Well, that's not too bad.
- I'm good at taking selfies now.
- You took them recently.
She can take these photos now.
Now, we have Kim Sung Oh.
In a way, people are reminded...
- of his intense villain roles.
- "The Man from Nowhere".
He showed us a lot
of intense performances.
- You kidnapped Ji Hyo a while back.
- Yes.
(He kidnapped Ji Hyo
a long time ago.)
- You kidnapped Ji Hyo a while back.
- Yes.
- He did that in a movie.
- What? In a movie?
- You scared me.
- You should mention that first...
- and say that next.
- I thought he did it in real life.
- Come on, be clear.
- No.
- I should've mentioned that first.
- You can't say it like that.
- He did that in a movie.
- But...
By the way, what kind of person
is Ji Hyo in your opinion?
She's the best.
- In what ways?
- What?
We want to know too.
Why is she the best? Why?
Can you tell us in what ways
she's the best?
I said it because we're on TV.
(I said it because we're on TV.)
If you think what I say on TV
is valid in real life,
I can't be on TV then.
Should I be myself then?
- He has a lot of anger inside him.
- Listen.
- You need to be yourself on TV.
- He's angry.
You need to give me
some breathing room.
- You can't corner me like that.
- Listen.
- What did I do wrong?
- Why would you say that?
- I can ask him a question.
- Right.
Yes. You're not supposed
to ask that.
- He's making stuff up.
- You know...
- I can't say only nice things.
- That's not it.
In your movie, "Secret Zoo,"
which animal are you?
I'm a gorilla.
- I can see the gorilla inside him.
- It suits him.
- What about you, Yeo Been?
- I'm a sloth.
- It suits her.
- I can see it.
- It suits you.
- You do resemble a sloth.
- Did you put on makeup for that?
- Your face...
- The director did a great job.
- Me?
- He cast the right people.
- He did an awesome job.
You can totally be the sloth.
You've never seen a sloth in person.
- No.
- We're looking at one now.
- I've never seen it in person.
- We're looking at it now.
- When I see you,
- I can totally picture it.
- You totally fit the role.
- He cast the right person.
- He did a great job.
- She reminds me of a sloth.
- That's amazing.
Today's race is called Reincarnated:
We Won't Harm You.
Among you, two members
who were eliminated...
- Again?
- There's another twist?
- There are spies again?
- Gosh, this is crazy.
- Gosh.
- Come on.
Among you, two members
who were eliminated are back...
by reincarnation.
And two deities of death
are trying to catch them.
I think Sung Oh
probably got reincarnated.
- You got a mission, didn't you?
- Yes.
- He came here early today.
- My gosh.
- It's obvious he's the deity.
- Gosh. Look at his face.
I get it now.
- He's the deity of death.
- I know what to do now.
Okay.
There will be three rounds
in the mission.
If even 1 of the 2 reincarnated
members survives,
they will win.
And if both members are eliminated,
the deities of death will win.
- The losers get the water bomb.
- The water bomb?
- Yes.
- It's really cold today.
The deities can eliminate members
by ripping off their name tags.
Only the deities will have
10 minutes to remove...
the name tags after each mission
when the light is turned on.
If the reincarnated members
aren't eliminated,
the staff members will draw
two balls randomly after each round,
and the chosen members
will join the deities.
(The chosen members
will join the deities.)
And the deities will be informed
about the members on their team.
That can't happen.
There can't be more deities.
- Are you the deity of death?
- Why not?
Why can't that happen?
- If I was, I wouldn't say that.
- Right.
- He'd be the reincarnated member.
- The reincarnated member.
- Suk Jin, you should focus.
- You reincarnated, didn't you?
He whispered this to me.
"I don't get it."
(Suk Jin says, "I don't get it.")
(He wants to be sharp,
but he can't understand the rules.)
So the members who weren't chosen
as the deities of death...
will be on the reincarnated
members' team.
If they are eliminated,
they'll face the penalty together.
Protecting them to survive
in the race will be important.
I'll draw two members
for the deities of death.
- You'll draw them?
- I see.
- So no one was informed?
- The first two will be chosen now.
The first two deities of death
will be chosen now.
(2 deities of death
have been chosen.)
We're done with the draw.
- Did you send the text messages?
- Yes. I did.
(The chosen deities of death
will receive a text message.)
The deities of death must go after
the reincarnated members.
First, I'll give out the advantage
to the two winning teams.
- Okay.
- It's an advantage.
You can put it
on any member of your choice.
It's the penalty badge.
If we get a lot of penalty badges...
If you have a lot of the badges,
regardless of the outcome,
you'll get the stick as the penalty.
Whom should we give this to?
- Kwang Soo.
- What?
I see. Someone on our team?
- No.
- So we'll discuss who'll get it?
- Our team has to choose one?
- For a second...
- They are on the same team.
- Were you trying to give it to me?
(Were you trying to give it to me?)
(Kicking)
Jae Suk and Kwang Soo
are on the same team.
- He tried to give it to Kwang Soo.
- You tried to give that to me?
- Kwang Soo.
- What's happening?
You have no faith in me.
- He really kicked you.
- Right?
(He really kicked you.)
(Culture shock)
He really kicked Jae Suk.
- Of course. We don't fake it.
- Right.
- Jae Hong, this is real.
- We don't fake it.
- We should discuss to pick someone.
- Today...
- You should pick someone.
- Yes.
No, don't make me do it.
Why not? It's all right.
Should we vote? Should we all vote?
Since he looks the healthiest,
we should pick Jong Kook.
Jong Kook?
- Is that a dangerous move?
- It's okay.
- Just now,
- What?
you've been chosen by Sora.
- Me?
- Yes.
- We've never met. Why me?
- Right.
I mean... Have we met?
- You don't know me.
- No, listen.
- Jong Kook. He hates...
- We've never met before.
- this the most.
- Right.
- There's no probable cause.
- Did I offend her in any way?
She said you looked healthy.
- Yes, she has a point.
- Yes.
Just give it to anyone you want,
Actress Jeon.
(It's time for her
to give out the badge.)
- At least, you met her before.
- Relax. There's no pressure.
You won't listen to me.
(Surprised)
(Jong Kook gets 2 penalty badges.)
- What's happening?
- That was bold.
What just happened?
- Me?
- She's trying to undermine him.
We've never met before.
Giving you the stick is better...
- than getting one from you.
- Me?
I won't watch your movie
even through VOD.
(He says something shocking.)
Come on.
You didn't have to say that.
What is this?
She suddenly gave it to me.
- What is this?
- How shocking.
- Change your outfits,
and let's get started.
(The race starts.)
- Let's go.
- All right.
You'll be given a hint regarding
those who have been reborn.
Okay.
For this first mission,
all of you need to succeed.
It's called Rodeo and Juliet.
- Rodeo and Juliet?
The teams will take turns.
If you don't pass 3 out of 5 rounds,
the hint will be revealed.
The deities of death
will try to fail intentionally.
That's right.
One of you will get on the horse
and try to hold out.
One of the other members...
must eat jjajangmyeon
or do the water bottle flip...
in the amount of time the person
lasted on the horse to pass.
- Flip a water bottle?
- Yes, you flip it upright.
- Let's have jjajangmyeon.
- Okay.
(They decide to have jjajangmyeon.)
(They're excited.)
Haha, let's work.
- What?
- Don't goof around.
He wants you to stop goofing around
and work.
- I am. What's wrong with him?
- Did you hear him?
(He's sullen.)
(Se Chan is a tattletale.)
He said,
"I am. What's wrong with him?"
That's what he said.
He said that. Right?
- I'm just reacting.
- Right.
You're working.
Okay. I got it.
Take your hands out of your pockets
when working.
(He retaliates.)
- Work, will you?
- What?
- Be sincere.
- Okay.
- Let me fix your clothes.
- You should wear this.
You should wear this
and give that to me.
- They're the same size.
- Yeo Been.
I know you haven't
gotten to know him yet,
but what do you think
about Suk Jin?
He promised to make me into a star.
- Why would you promise her that?
- I told her so.
- I did.
- What's wrong with him?
I am the star-maker of this show.
- Why would you promise her that?
- Look.
I know she's already famous,
I'm going to make her name
the most-searched word online.
- Which team will go first?
- Let's see.
Let's play a Race of Wits.
- The 1st person to...
- 1!
(The staff didn't say go.)
You need to sit down.
She plays so dirty.
- She's so reckless.
- Two!
- Hold on.
- We haven't started yet.
(She says 2.)
- What's wrong with them?
- They do whatever they want!
Like I said, Sora is
very straightforward.
- She's very determined.
- She's reckless.
- She only does what she's told.
- She just wants to win.
- Whoever loses...
- Goes first?
- Yes.
- Okay.
If we don't do anything, we'll win.
I'm sure.
Get ready, set, go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
- 5.
- 6.
Okay.
(Sung Oh and Suk Jin are out.)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- You should've waited.
- Sung Oh, do better.
- He's being scolded.
- Let's go!
- We overlapped.
We overlapped.
You told us to wait.
- You said we should be quiet.
- What have you done?
- What?
You told us not to do anything,
but you did instead.
He got too excited.
That's what this show is all about.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- Let's do it. Come here.
- Good luck.
- Kwang Soo, come here.
I bet he'll be good.
You look quite stable.
There's a 75-percent chance
he's a deity of death.
I can see the words next to him.
He's not that talkative anymore.
Doesn't he need a helmet?
- Helmet?
- Yes, let's give him one.
He should wear one.
Is it that intense?
- If you hold out for too long...
- It's cold.
Don't use both hands.
Jae Suk!
(Jae Suk slips and falls.)
Don't use both hands.
Jae Suk!
- What's wrong with him?
(The others fall as well.)
- What's wrong with you?
- Come on.
What's wrong with you?
- You almost got hurt.
- Why did this move?
It is quite slippery.
- You almost got injured.
- Why is this slippery?
- You try to be so funny.
- He tries to be so funny.
- I can't believe you.
- Why was that slippery?
- Be careful, will you?
- Did you get that?
- They got it.
- What?
Don't act like it was intentional.
- They got it.
- You got it, right?
- It's slapstick.
- He acts like everything's planned.
- "That's a highlight."
- All right.
- We'll start the timer now.
- I have a good feeling about this.
- Me too.
- Get ready, set, go.
Hang in there.
That's quick.
Look at the angles.
- Look at his gaze.
- You shouldn't be stiff.
- Your body needs to be...
- It needs to be flexible.
Good. Great job.
He looks so sexy.
Good.
(He looks seductive.)
You're looking sexy!
You're doing well.
- He's good.
- He is.
Why does he look so sexy?
He looks sexy.
Good. Nice hips.
What if this doesn't get aired?
That's okay.
You're doing well.
- You're doing well.
- You are.
(He clenches his teeth.)
- He's hanging on.
- He is.
I think they could finish
a bowl of jjajangmyeon.
He may make it look easy,
but that's not the case.
- It's really hard.
- He's the best one I've seen.
You're doing well.
You're doing a great job.
- You're doing well.
- What is this?
If he's going to take this long,
let us stop by at home.
(At that moment...)
He's really good.
(He falls.)
- Okay, okay.
- Are you okay?
How many seconds?
Or were they minutes?
1 minute and 40 seconds.
(This sexy man breathes heavily.)
He's obviously not a deity of death.
You're right.
It didn't matter whether I was
reincarnated or a deity.
- I just wanted to ride it well.
- Exactly.
I watched rodeos often.
- You did well.
- Every time I saw it on TV,
- You wanted to try it?
- I felt like I could ride it well.
- He's flexible.
- He is.
He's good.
So Min and Jong Kook,
please decide whether
to do the water bottle flip...
or eat jjajangmyeon
in the given time.
They could do both
in that given time.
You could have jjajangmyeon
and jjamppong.
- Please make your decision.
- We choose jjajangmyeon.
You have 1 minute and 40 seconds.
- You can have fried dumplings too.
- This is...
- This is too easy.
- You could order them right now.
- You can stop by at home too.
- You may begin once I tell you to.
- Will you eat?
- So Min will eat?
- Yes.
- I doubt...
she will finish it.
I really doubt it.
I have a small mouth.
(The countdown begins.)
You shouldn't eat it like that.
She can't do it. She can't.
(While everyone is talking down
to her,)
(a man comes to hold her hair.)
(It's Se Chan.)
(Oh, my.)
(He looks nonchalant.)
(He approaches her without warning.)
Work, will you?
(She focuses on eating once again.)
I don't think she can do it.
- She won't be able to finish it.
- She can't.
She won't finish it.
She only has a minute
and 40 seconds.
It's too much.
She needs to do it again.
They didn't give her pickled radish.
She needs to eat that.
Why can't she finish it?
She's not even having
double servings.
I could finish jjamppong
and jjajangmyeon.
- She's a deity of death.
- I think she's a deity of death.
Yes, it feels like it.
She's really eating slowly.
I agree.
A minute and 40 seconds
is a long time.
I'm really doing my best.
- Five,
- She can't finish this?
- four,
- She's so suspicious.
- three,
- I could've eaten...
- two,
- another dish.
- one.
- I'm serious.
- She failed.
- You've failed.
She's not giving it her best.
You should've told me in advance
if you were going to eat like this.
It's because she didn't have
any pickled radish.
This is way too much.
Is anyone confident...
- to do better than Sung Oh?
- I know, right?
I think I can.
- Jae Hong wants to try.
- Go on.
- Go, Jae Hong.
- I'm flexible.
- Okay.
- Okay. I have high hopes for you.
Good luck.
- Good luck.
(How much time will he obtain
through his flexibility?)
Go slowly. Okay.
- That's good.
- Loosen up your hips like he did.
- Use your hips.
- Loosen them.
- You look sexy.
- You're doing well.
- Hang in there.
- Here he goes.
It's going fast all of a sudden.
- Sir...
- This is only the beginning.
- Your arms are...
- Hold on.
- No.
- Hang in there.
He's already tired.
He's exhausted.
Sir!
It's too fast.
- It's faster than before.
- Don't give up.
Don't give up.
- Use your hips.
He's going to fall soon.
- No, no.
- Jae Hong.
- He's done.
- No!
(After flailing about, he falls.)
- He's done.
- No!
- See? It's not easy.
- Sung Oh was good.
- This is how most of us are.
- Sung Oh.
How many seconds was that?
- 35 seconds.
- What?
That's not bad.
It wasn't this intense before.
35 seconds.
We need to finish it.
We can do it, right?
Come on. Jung Jun Ha finished one
in eight seconds.
- Just go with the water bottle.
- It's impossible to finish that.
No, it's possible.
- No.
- No. Try it then.
- He can do it.
- Let me check the amount.
He must be full because
he had gimbap by himself.
(Is this why you're unsure?)
Right, he must be full.
He must be full. He ate something
while the others were starving.
Is that why?
- Jong Kook, are you being serious?
- How long will this grudge last?
Are you being serious or what?
- He ate by himself.
- He must be full.
We were all starving.
You need to overcome his scolding.
You're only saying that
to make the viewers laugh, right?
Of course.
- That's a given.
- Ready,
set...
35 seconds?
I doubt you can finish it.
Why would you say that already?
- You're on the same team.
- Don't demotivate him like that.
- Should I not?
- You shouldn't be like that.
10 seconds have passed.
- You can do it.
- He can.
- He'll succeed.
- It's only been 10 seconds.
- It's going to work.
- You can do it.
- Let your stomach do all the work.
- He's going to succeed.
- 20 seconds have passed.
- Haha, you're almost there.
- You can do it!
- One more bite.
- You're almost there.
- One more time.
You have five seconds!
(He's almost done.)
- You're almost there.
- You can do it!
- 30 seconds have passed.
- You have five seconds!
(He needs to empty the bowl
as well as his mouth.)
(Will he succeed?)
- 3, 4,
- He did it.
- five.
(35 seconds are over.)
(Now, it's up for the producer
to decide.)
He passed, right?
- He finished it.
- You've failed.
- He's failed?
- The food isn't inside his mouth.
You've failed.
So why in the world
did you have to eat that gimbap?
Why did you?
I knew we had to eat jjajangmyeon.
That's why I told you not to eat.
- You're just too full right now.
- My goodness.
I saw this coming
ever since he ate that gimbap.
He had an entire roll.
- And it was tuna, at that.
- You're right.
- He gobbled it up.
We should do it.
Okay.
- Sora, you must succeed.
- Good luck.
- Let's go, Sora!
You can do this!
At least stay on there
for 35 seconds.
We can finish the bowl then.
- Don't let it speed up too fast.
- Right.
You said it like
you have authority over it.
He always becomes haughty
when we have guests.
- What authority do you have?
- I just asked.
"Don't let it speed up too fast."
- I'm asking you.
- The guy looked at you...
looking completely annoyed.
Gosh.
- Good luck.
- Just give us 30 seconds.
- Okay.
- Is that enough?
- Of course.
- Ready,
- Good luck!
- The longer the better though.
- Okay, good.
- Looking good.
Sora, you've got this.
- She's good.
- She's rocking to the rhythm.
It's speeding up. Stay on it.
- Sora, you're doing great.
- It's faster now.
Wait, she's swaying too much.
- You're doing great.
- But...
- She's quite flexible.
- She's doing great.
- Good.
- What's with that speed?
(Level 3 begins after 20 seconds.)
(She falls off
right after level 3 begins.)
(That's too bad!)
- How long was that?
- 23 seconds.
- It's not much.
- You did well though.
- Right.
- You did a good job.
- The jjajangmyeon.
- In 23 seconds?
- 23 seconds?
- As you know, Jae Suk...
loves noodles.
- He could do it.
- I know he can.
It's completely possible.
He loves noodles...
and didn't eat any gimbap.
(It's possible because...)
- Right.
- Right?
- The gimbap...
- Seriously?
That's enough!
Jae Suk can do it.
(That's enough!)
Why did you eat it then?
It prevented you from succeeding.
- Because of you...
- Unbelievable.
Gosh.
In 23 seconds?
Hold on. Does he only
have to eat the noodles?
- Must he swallow everything?
- His mouth must be empty.
- He must swallow it all?
- Okay.
- No way.
- That seems tricky.
- It doesn't seem easy.
- Ready,
- Here I go.
- It hasn't gone mushy yet.
- get set...
- Jae Suk, please.
- It's a lot though.
- This is our last chance.
- See? It's not easy.
- Just wait.
- Count the time for us.
- He may be able to do it.
- He's almost done.
- Just swallow it.
- 8, 9...
- There's still a lot of time.
- He's already half done.
- 10 seconds have passed.
- 10 seconds?
- He might be able to do it.
- He might do it.
- He's swallowing as he goes.
No wonder you're like a llama.
- 18, 19, 20, 21...
- No wonder you're like a llama.
- 22.
- He ate all the noodles.
- 23.
- Time over.
(There are no noodles left
in the dish.)
(They only have to check
inside his mouth now.)
He ate it all.
Here. Swallow it.
Go on.
Jae Suk...
(10 years of teamwork
shines at times like this.)
Hey, look!
- He ate it all.
- See?
Please open your mouth.
- There's nothing in there.
- See?
- Okay, you pass.
- Yes!
(The miracle of 23 seconds)
Let's go.
- No way.
- All right.
- Okay!
- I can't believe it.
This is because
he didn't eat any gimbap.
- Right?
- He didn't eat any gimbap.
- Don't you agree?
- If he had the gimbap too...
It's because he was on
an empty stomach.
- That's why.
- I could suck it all in.
I can't believe he did it
in 23 seconds.
- Okay.
- Yeo Been, you're next.
Go, Yeo Been!
- Yeo Been.
- Good luck.
- So she has to succeed?
- Yes.
I'm sure you're aware
of the importance.
We won't succeed
unless you ride this well.
- Okay.
- Good luck!
- Oh, no.
- You can do this. Who knows?
This could reveal
a hidden talent of yours.
I hope it doesn't go too fast.
- What...
- What was that?
(What?)
(What are you doing?)
- What was that?
- Seriously?
- I mean...
- Are you kidding me?
- I didn't expect that.
- What was that?
- We're doomed.
- A slapstick comedy?
She has what it takes
to thrive on variety shows.
In through the front door,
out through the back door.
- What?
- What's wrong with you?
- What is this?
- What are you doing?
- Isn't that a typical...
- This is a slapstick comedy.
This is what the old comedians
used to do.
That's what Kim Yong Man is good at.
- What...
- Look at Yeo Been.
- What's wrong with you?
- Are you kidding me?
- Are you doing this on purpose?
- Of course not.
- What's wrong with you?
- I don't think I can do this.
- Come over here.
- I can't do this.
- I'm not wearing the right pants.
- I'm loving her character!
Me too.
- I can't do this.
- She's a great fit...
- in terms of variety shows.
- What's wrong with her?
(What?)
(Again?)
I don't think I can do this.
- What is this?
- What's wrong?
I don't have
the right pants for this.
Her pants are too slippery.
I'm wearing the wrong pants.
Yeo Been, you're full of surprises.
- There.
- She's good.
- You're set.
- There you go.
Isn't she a deity of death?
- Unbelievable.
- No way.
This type of comedy
was forgotten even among comedians.
- In the past...
- It brought back memories.
- Remember Shim Hyung Rae?
- My pants are slippery.
Your pants must really be slippery.
- It's good though.
- It could serve as an advantage.
- Okay.
- It could benefit her.
Right, it could help her
sway easily to the rhythm.
- That's right.
- Let's go.
- Ready,
- Yeo Been, you can do this.
- Please take it easy.
- get set...
- I'm not sure about this.
- She'll easily fall off.
Gosh.
- It's easy at first.
- Right.
But when it starts to swirl...
Keep your back strong.
- Your back!
- There's no rhythm whatsoever.
- Hold on.
- She's not swaying to a rhythm.
- No way.
- How can one be like this?
- Hey!
- Hang on a little longer.
Please, just a while longer...
- Oh, no.
- Please, just a while longer...
(She drops as soon
as level 3 begins.)
No!
No! How long was that?
- How long was it?
- 18 seconds.
- Gosh.
- That's only enough time...
- for the bottle.
- Exactly.
- There's no other option.
- We have to go for the bottle.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
- No, you did great.
- It was hilarious.
(Suk Jin tries the bottle flip.)
(What?)
(He succeeds on his first try.)
(Startled)
- What now?
- Did he do it?
Call me crazy because
I did it on my first try.
- Okay, good.
- What's gotten into me?
- The timer wasn't set.
- It must be my lucky year.
Unbelievable.
He called it his lucky year.
Ready, get set...
(How will he do in the actual game?)
(What?)
(He succeeded on his first try!)
What?
(It only took him a second.)
Gosh.
(His lower body isn't
as strong as his luck.)
No way.
- My gosh.
- Suk Jin!
No way.
- I can't believe it.
- Seriously?
I thought Suk Jin was going to
collapse from high blood pressure.
- Me too.
- Insane, right?
How I'm on a roll is insane!
Jae Suk, we should have
an ambulance ready just in case.
I thought Suk Jin
was going to collapse.
- Unbelievable.
- He won the game...
at the expense of his health.
Please pick a person to go
from the last team.
Kwang Soo, are you up for it?
- Sure thing.
- Good.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- Make it at least 30 seconds.
- Sure thing.
Can you eat another bowl
of jjajangmyeon?
- Well, Sora...
- He can eat it instead.
Sora practiced the bottle flip.
(While others took a break,
Sora practiced by herself.)
- Kwang Soo, here you go.
- He'll be good at this.
(Se Chan helps Kwang Soo
put on the headgear.)
- Sora practiced the bottle flip.
- He has it on backward.
Kwang Soo,
it's on the other way around.
Just keep it like that.
(Kwang Soo's not an idiot!)
- It's not so bad though.
- It suits you.
- Really?
- You look like a fish.
- That's better.
- It looks better that way.
Doesn't he look like a fish?
- Is it all right?
- Yes.
- It suits you.
- Kwang Soo, you're looking good.
(Kwang Soo confidently walks over
with his headgear on backward.)
- It suits you.
- Nice.
Make sure you stay on
for at least 30 seconds.
Don't do that.
- Ready,
- Giddy-up!
- get set...
- He's too tall for this.
He's at an advantage
with his long arms.
- See?
- Keep it steady.
- Nice.
- Good job.
- That's it.
- You're looking good.
- Good job.
- Nice.
- Go for it.
Okay.
- You have a good rhythm.
- Kwang Soo...
- My gosh.
- You're like a machine.
You were made for this.
- You've got this.
- You'll do better than Sung Oh.
- No way.
- Good job.
- Kwang Soo, you're doing great.
- You were made for this.
- He's good at this.
- Way to go!
- He's like a machine.
- He'll have the top record.
- He's really good.
- He's a machine.
The operator seems flustered.
- You're a machine.
- He's making it angry.
- This was a game for Kwang Soo.
- He was made for this.
(Giddy-up!)
- Okay.
- Nice.
(He provokes the horse too much
and ends up falling off.)
Good job.
- A minute.
- A minute?
- Kwang Soo...
- My gosh.
Sora will attempt the bottle flip.
Nice, she has a minute.
- Bring the bottle.
- All right.
I see she's the serious type.
(Kwang Soo sacrificed himself
to give her a minute.)
You have one minute.
Ready...
Wait, no more practicing.
- Ready,
- Please.
get set...
You have enough time.
- Gosh.
- You're using too much force.
Yes, that's about it.
(Did something just fly by?)
- Gosh.
- What was that?
(Sung Oh steals the show.)
- Wait.
- Are you all right?
What's wrong with you?
- Gosh.
- What's wrong with you?
You can't let it be that obvious.
- Are you kidding me?
- I mean...
- I wanted to watch from this side.
- He laid out flat.
I wanted to watch from this side.
It's slippery.
- What on earth is wrong with you?
- It's slippery.
(While everyone is laughing...)
Hold on.
30 seconds.
It's all right.
You have enough time.
She's not the deity of death.
Look at how focused she is.
Just a little bit more.
That's it. You're almost there now.
Flip it a little harder.
You're almost there.
(Just then...)
(She barely succeeds.)
Nice!
It stood right at
the edge of the table.
- Good job.
- Nice.
(Finally, she's able
to see the others around her.)
You will not receive any hints
about the reincarnated members.
- Okay.
- Nice!
- All right.
- Good job.
(The deities of death
must be frustrated.)
Some of the members
are good at slapstick comedy.
We should call them Team Slapstick.
Especially Yeo Been and Sung Oh.
The guests today are hilarious.
Everyone including Yeo Been.
The guests are fun
but our members aren't.
Right.
Who was that directed at?
- Who did you say that to?
- Hang in there.
- Who?
- I'm taking a break this week.
- Stay strong, Suk Jin.
- He's taking a break.
- A break.
- Suk Jin, hang in there.
- Sure.
Right now, for 10 minutes,
the deities of death...
will try and rip off your name tags.
- That's out of the blue.
- Why?
But we didn't receive any hints.
Only the deities of death
may eliminate anyone.
Over the course of three rounds,
the deities of death
can eliminate two people each.
The race is over If the reincarnated
members are eliminated.
But if a regular member
gets eliminated,
both the deity of death
and the eliminated member...
will receive a penalty badge each.
Even if you're not reincarnated,
be careful not to get eliminated.
It'll become obvious.
Let's start...
- the name tag elimination.
- Right now?
Right here?
- Are we supposed to run?
- What?
Ordinary members can't rip off
name tags, right?
- Are you a deity of death?
- She must be a deity of death.
I'm not.
Are you a deity of death?
- What are you doing?
- What's with Yeo Been?
So Min, what are you doing there?
You want to make it so obvious?
- I'm nothing.
- She's acting strange today.
I'm just sick.
Are you pretending to be sick
because you're a deity of death?
- What is she doing?
- Gosh, you startled me.
Gosh.
(Is Yeo Been going for name tags
because she is a deity of death?)
I know you're not a deity of death.
They wouldn't give you such a role.
You're too weak.
I'm not as weak as you are.
(The weak middle-aged men
are squabbling.)
I'll rip off your name tag.
You're not a deity of death,
are you?
- I'm not.
- I knew it.
If I was, your name tag would have
come off.
I wouldn't let that happen.
(The weakest members
keep squabbling.)
What are you doing? Gosh.
I will not...
What?
(Suk Jin is startled
and slurs his words.)
Go away!
What did you say?
What does that mean?
- I don't understand.
- Go away!
Let's go upstairs.
In the elevator?
(Se Chan suggests to Kwang Soo
they go upstairs.)
(What's on his mind?)
You're not a deity of death‚
are you?
I'm not.
(Kwang Soo follows him carefully.)
(Suddenly...)
(Se Chan grabs
Kwang Soo's name tag.)
I'm not a deity of death.
What's with you?
Why do you look so nervous?
If you're a deity of death,
rip off my name tag now.
I'm serious.
You're not a deity of death,
are you?
I'm not. If you are,
rip off name tag now.
Do you want to be a deity of death?
- I think that'd be easier.
- Okay.
(Both the deity of death and the
member can receive a penalty badge.)
You're not?
(Is either of them
a deity of death?)
Hey!
What happened?
Did you get eliminated?
(Why did Kwang Soo scream?)
- Gosh, this is annoying.
- Who eliminated who?
(What's going on?)
Gosh.
- Did you see that?
- Unbelievable.
(Both their name tags are
barely attached.)
- Gosh.
- I didn't see it.
(They're both claiming that
their name tags got ripped off.)
This is crazy.
So one of you is a deity of death?
- Hey.
- Unbelievable.
(Who is a deity of death,
Se Chan or Kwang Soo?)
(The race is over.)
I can't believe it.
I was at the scene.
- Who is it?
- I'm not sure.
It's one of the two.
- It's driving me crazy.
- Who are they? Tell me.
Guys, listen to me.
Look. They both got a penalty badge.
I saw it.
(Both of them are wearing
a penalty badge on their chest.)
- One of them is a deity of death?
- Unbelievable.
Let me tell you one thing.
One of them is a deity of death.
Se Chan is.
- Jong Kook.
- I'm not.
- Didn't you see me do the rodeo?
- I did.
What about me?
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
It's okay to say
that you're a deity of death.
It's not like I can eliminate you.
What if I'm not?
I can say that too, right? I'm not.
Is it you then?
I did the rodeo
for more than a minute.
- He couldn't be a deity of death.
- For more than a minute.
- He did his best.
- Also,
I would have volunteered
to eat jjajangmyeon.
- Jong Kook, but...
- Se Chan, it's okay to say it.
Jong Kook is doing it again.
- I'm on his radar again.
- Say it.
- It's okay to say it.
- Say who the other is.
(Which of them is a deity of death?)
- Seriously...
- I mean...
- You're so mean.
- What's wrong?
What happens now?
More penalty badges
have been distributed.
The deity of death race
for the first round is over.
I will pick two more
deities of death now.
If the same person
from the first round...
is picked again,
that chance is gone.
Therefore, there may not be
four deities of death.
I'd rather be a deity of death.
Can you turn around for a second?
(Two more deities of death
are picked.)
(Round 1)
(Round 2)
(One person is picked again.)
- All right. I'm done.
- Okay.
(There are 3 deities of death
in total.)
- Sung Oh.
- Come on.
I want to be a deity of death.
(The result is texted to them.)
- They're chosen randomly.
- I've never been chosen.
- I wasn't chosen.
- Me neither.
They're not giving me the role.
The first round is over.
Let's move to another place
for the second round.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- I can't believe Kwang Soo.
Se Chan!
- What is this?
Here is the second mission
for all members.
- It's called Rumor Has It.
- Rumor Has It?
Each round will be played
by six members.
You'll put on headphones
and deliver a sentence...
to the next player.
To win, get the correct sentence
delivered to the last player.
If you get 2 out of 3 sentences
correct, you succeed.
If the mission fails,
all members will receive a hint
about the reincarnated members.
I'm afraid too many members will
act like deities of death.
- Right.
There are many suspicious members.
There are too many.
It's so hard today.
Please choose six representatives.
(The 6 representatives
for the 1st question)
(Jong Kook, Se Chan, So Min,
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, and Haha)
- Try to deliver the main idea.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
The first player should summarize
the sentence well...
- deliver it correctly.
- Right.
I'll do my best.
- Let's show them.
- Seriously.
Let's win a hint.
Let's watch carefully.
Some of them may be
deities of death.
- I'm sure.
- Definitely.
Either Se Chan or Kwang Soo is
a deity of death.
Right. We should watch them.
Here we go. Ready, get set, go.
This is impossible.
- I can't even remember the names.
- I don't understand a thing.
- That's hard.
- That's impossible to remember.
- Gosh.
- This won't work.
It's just impossible.
- I couldn't memorize half of it.
- I've lost all my will.
You'd have to already know
the names...
of the players and coaches
to memorize it.
This is too hard.
Just make it as close
to the original sentence as you can.
(While Jong Kook is memorizing
the sentence,)
(the others are dancing.)
I know this dance.
(They're dancing
pretty much in sync.)
(Jong Kook is serious,
but the others are having fun.)
It's that song.
Let's start.
(Jong Kook delivers
the sentence to Se Chan.)
- Listen, guys.
- "Listen, guys."
- In the Champions League...
- "In the Champions League..."
Sadio Mane scored a hat trick.
- Who?
- Sadio Mane.
- You don't know who he is?
- "Sadio Mane"?
- Yes, Sadio Mane.
- Sadio Mane and...
- "Sadio Mane".
Jurgen Klopp,
the manager of Liverpool...
- That's English.
- Yes.
(The English names
put Se Chan in trouble.)
- Jurgen Klopp is the manager.
- What was the other name?
Sadro Malen?
- It's Sadio Mane.
- "Sadio Mane".
I want autographs of Sadio Mane
and the manager, Klopp.
The player who became a free agent
according to the Bosman ruling...
(It's perfect so far.)
- Samuel Umtiti...
- Oh, my.
(Jong Kooks is incredible.)
Bring him to Camp Nou.
Do you know it?
- Camp Nou.
- I don't.
(Se Chan is about to cry.)
(How can you not know it
when you play soccer with me?)
(I'll make you remember it.)
- Camp Nou.
- "Camp Nou".
Se Chan, hurry up.
Bring him to Camp Nou.
I want him in the back seat
of my six-seater SUV.
(Perfect)
(Jong Kook delivered the 100-word
paragraph perfectly.)
(Jong Kook is amazing.)
(This is incredible.)
- He's incredible.
- All right.
- Listen, guys.
- "Listen, guys."
- Listen carefully, guys.
- "Listen carefully, guys."
- The Champions League.
"The Champions League".
- In the Champions League...
- "In the Champions League..."
- A player scored a hat trick.
- "A player scored a hat trick."
A hat trick. It means
scoring more than three goals.
What? A hat trick?
Cut that out.
"Listen, guys. A hat trick
in the Champions League..."
Okay.
(The next word is Sadio Mane.)
(You have to remember it.
It's Sadio Mane.)
Okay. Simon Murphy.
No, that's not it.
(Simon Murphy)
- Just keep going.
- Simon Murphy...
- Simon Murphy.
- "Simon Murphy".
- There's a guy called Simon Murphy.
- Simon Murphy?
- He is called Simon Murphy.
And then...
- there is the manager of Liverpool.
- "The manager of Liverpool".
- His name is Club.
- "Club".
(His name is Club.)
"Club"?
In addition to him,
there is another manager.
- Another manager?
- I mean...
It's an English name again.
What did Jong Kook say?
(It was clearly an English name.)
(All the English names
paralyze Se Chan's brain.)
Gosh, what was it?
Si... Siranman?
- "Siranman"?
- The manager is called Siranman.
He is transferring.
And he is getting in
a six-seater SUV.
- An SUV?
- Yes.
Who gets in it? Simon Murphy?
Or the manager of Liverpool,
who is transferring?
All of them.
Okay. Liverpool...
A person called Simon Murphy...
and he will get in
a six-seater SUV...
- and leave.
- A six-seater SUV...
- A hat trick?
- A hat trick.
(His brain stops functioning.)
- It's hard.
- This is bad.
Listen carefully, guys.
- The Champion League.
- "The Champion League".
- A hat trick.
- "A hat trick".
- Hat trick.
- That's three goals.
Someone scored a hat trick.
And the Liverpool Club...
- What?
- Liverpool.
Simon Murphy and...
- "Simon Murphy"?
- Yes, Simon Murphy.
And a side trick?
Sidopick?
Is that a name?
Well... Si...
Simon Murphy of Liverpool...
and another man
with an English name...
and Side Trick...
were put in a six-seater SUV
and sent away.
She is a deity of death.
She is definitely a deity of death.
- Why?
- It wasn't that bad.
- Keep going, Kwang Soo.
- Keep going.
- That's what Se Chan said.
- You'll hear it later.
- The English names...
- Listen carefully, guys.
- "Listen carefully, guys."
Liverpool in the Champions League...
"Liverpool in
the Champions League..."
A hat trick was scored by...
Simon Dominic?
(Simon Dominic?)
(Simon Dominc Becomes
a Soccer Player)
Simon, Simon Dominic
And Simon...
Diva.
- "Simon Diva"?
- They...
were sent away in a six-seater SUV.
(They were sent away
in a six-seater SUV.)
- Keep going.
- I want to send you away.
You want to send me away?
- Listen, guys.
- "Listen, guys."
Is it a will?
It's a will.
(It's a will.)
(Where did the will come from?)
It's a will.
This man is dividing his property
on his deathbed.
- Look at Ji Hyo.
- This man is dividing the property.
That's the only thing that comes
out of a will.
- I can't believe Ji Hyo.
- Listen, guys.
It's a will.
In the Champions League,
Liverpool...
is it.
(In the Champions League,
Liverpool is it.)
So that's the will?
The will!
"In the Champions League,
Liverpool is it."
(It sounds strange,
but he focuses once more.)
- A hat trick...
- "A hat trick".
Then there was
some kind of a league.
(The will comes up blank.)
It's a six-seater.
(It's a six-seater.)
(It's the will of someone
who wanted to ride a six-seater.)
The diva of a six-seater.
The diva of a six-seater?
Ji Hyo, that's good.
Ji Hyo got all the key points.
The diva of a six-seater?
- It isn't a will, is it?
- Don't add things!
Listen carefully, guys.
(He tries to make a sentence
from what he heard.)
Europe... The UK...
- The Champions League.
- He doesn't know much about soccer.
Liverpool...
(Listen, guys, The Champions League,
and Liverpool)
I sincerely congratulate you
on six consecutive victories.
(He changes a 6-seater
to 6 consecutive wins.)
(100 words turned into 1 sentence.)
(This is how scary it is
to spread words.)
Did I get it wrong?
It can't be a six-seater.
- I heard a six-seater.
- What?
- Jong Kook memorized it perfectly.
- Really?
- Ji Hyo said, "It's a will."
- I was so taken aback.
Ji Hyo, it was funny.
- This is your last chance.
- The last chance.
Let's change two players.
- Let's do that.
- I will give it a try.
Suk Jin, I am sorry, but...
- I will give it a try. I can do it.
- Suk Jin.
If you want to make Yeo Been
a star,
- you should give her a chance.
- Yeo Been.
Suk Jin, we need to succeed.
(He wants to be more popular
than Yeo Been.)
Let's begin. Here we go.
- My goodness.
- Listen, guys.
(The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment
at Seocho-gu...)
That one is hard too.
- Seriously.
- It must be hard.
It's hard. It isn't easy.
(Will Jong Kook be able
to memorize it perfectly?)
(The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment
at Seocho-gu...)
(Jong Kook to Sora)
- Listen, guys.
- It's "Listen, guys" again.
Listen, guys.
The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment
at Seocho-gu...
should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.
Give the pet armadillo...
and kissing gourami...
to my nephew, Jae Hong.
And...
the monkey...
(He remembers that part.)
What kind of monkey was it?
Donate the monkey...
to the Nairobi National Park
of Kenya.
(He missed "mandrill monkey,"
but it's perfect otherwise.)
(Sora to Jae Hong)
- It's a will.
- A will.
Listen, guys. The Hanmaeum Apartment
at Seocho-gu...
- The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment...
- 142m²?
should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.
Give the pet armadillo...
and kissing gourami
to my nephew, Jae Hong.
And... What was the last one?
What was the last one?
Remember the last one.
(She tries to remember it.)
The pet elephant...
No, no.
Donate something to
the Nairobi National Park of Kenya.
What was it?
(She ends up changing
the monkey to the elephant.)
(Jae Hong to Yeo Been)
What was it?
- It's a will.
- "It's a will."
- Listen, guys.
- "Listen, guys."
The 142m² Hanmaeum Apartment
at Seocho-gu...
should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.
Give the pet armadillo...
and kissing gourami...
- to my nephew, Jae Hong.
- My nephew, Jae Hong.
(What was the last one?)
- The rhino...
- The rhino.
(The rhino...)
The rhino.
(Monkey to elephant to rhino)
Keep going.
Give it to someone.
Give the rhino to someone.
(Donate it
to the Nairobi National Park!)
(Yeo Been to Kwang Soo)
Listen, guys. It's a will.
Again?
Is it a will again?
The 142m² apartment at Seocho-gu...
should go to the 2nd and 3rd child.
The pet armandidorang...
(This is a disaster.)
and kissing gourami...
- should go to my nephew.
- What?
The nephew.
Yeo Been, you are acting strange.
Send them to my nephew.
Send the armandi
and kissing gourami?
And...
the rhino...
Wait, that can't be right.
What was it? The rhino...
Well, the rhino...
It should be released.
- It should be released.
- Release it.
(Release the rhino!)
What kind of nonsense is that?
- I don't know...
- Release the rhino?
how this happened.
- What else can you do?
- That's right.
- But why would you release it?
- What else can you do with a rhino?
- That's the only choice.
- That's right.
- It's not like you can eat it.
- But...
(Kwang Soo to Haha)
Listen, guys.
- Is it a will again?
- How did you know?
(You startled me.)
Are you serious?
It's a will.
- The 142m² apartment...
- Listen, guys. It's a will.
The 142m² apartment at Seocho-gu...
- 23.
- What?
There was something about 23.
I am sure of it. 23.
- The 142m² apartment...
- "The 142m² apartment."
- is on the 43rd floor.
- "It's on the 43rd floor."
Okay.
(The will gets mixed up again.)
The pet armand...
Armand?
Isn't that the name of champagne?
- Champagne?
- I am sure it's a brand name.
Armandor.
(He quickly changes the name.)
Send the pet armandor to my nephew.
- My nephew.
- Release the rhino.
(The last part of the will)
What?
(This person really wanted
to release the rhino in the wild.)
- This is crazy.
- That's exactly what I heard.
(I swear.)
Listen, guys. It's a will.
- A will.
- I give you...
the 142m² apartment...
(Haha gets that part right.)
(He is doing great!)
I don't think
it's on the 43rd floor.
I give you 23 142m² apartments...
(I give you 23 142m² apartments...)
(They finally found out
about the father's secret.)
Our father was a rich man!
- Seriously.
- Our father...
- Our father was a rich man!
- 23 142m² apartments?
That's insanely rich.
(Again, this is how scary
it is to spread words.)
I will give
the 23 apartments to you.
Inside them were...
a cat named Armand...
and kissing gourami.
Give them to the rhino.
(Give them to the rhino.)
(The rhino obtained
Armand and kissing gourami.)
Then the family will be successful
for generations.
I will reveal the answer.
What's the answer?
- The rhino...
- Is there a part about a rhino?
I talked about a monkey,
but Sora changed it to an elephant.
Then Jae Hong changed it to a rhino.
All right.
Since you failed the mission,
I will reveal a hint
on the reincarnated members.
If you are a deity of death,
take note.
The reincarnated members don't have
the AB blood type.
It's not me.
(The hint eliminates So Min.)
- That eliminated one member.
- Seriously.
For 10 minutes, we will play
the name tag elimination again.
A hint on the deities of death
is hidden somewhere in here.
- Okay.
- We have to find it.
Where is it?
(Where is the hint?)
You have to look for it.
(He outright asked
for the location of the hint.)
- "Where is it?"
- Why would they tell you?
- You have to look for it.
- Are you okay?
- I feel dizzy.
- "Where is it?"
That was hilarious.
- Jae Hong, that was original.
- I feel dizzy.
"Where is it?" That was original.
He must be the first person
to ask that outright.
Let's go.
(The siren marks the beginning
of the name tag elimination.)
For goodness' sake.
- Let's look for the hint.
- You are a deity of death.
- No, I am not.
- No?
- No.
- Is Kwang Soo a deity of death?
- Yes, he is.
He ripped off my name tag.
- For goodness' sake.
- I am serious.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Kwang Soo ripped off my name tag.
I am serious.
- Whatever.
- Don't get fooled.
(Is Se Chan really not
a deity of death?)
(He spots something.)
What is it?
Hold on. Why is
the moving camera on me?
This is too much.
Why are there three cameras on me?
Everyone will be out to get me.
Kwang Soo, hold on.
I...
(Screaming)
What was that?
(They suddenly hear a scream!)
(It's a woman's scream!)
What was that?
- I heard someone scream.
- Hey.
What was that?
(They run towards the scream.)
Where did that come from?
- No way.
- Did you get eliminated?
(The person who screamed was Sora.)
(But...)
(she's holding a name tag.)
- My gosh, seriously.
- This is crazy.
- Hey.
- I guess I was wrong.
- Jae Suk eliminated her.
- He's the deity of death.
That means he's the deity of death.
I'm only holding my name tag.
- He's the deity of death.
- Sora is unbelievable.
- Everything happened so quickly.
- She took off her own name tag?
- Yes.
You're saying she took off
her own name tag?
But we ran over here
because we heard a woman scream.
What's going on?
My gosh, Sora is unbelievable.
(They're both busy
accusing each other.)
You're the deity of death.
I'm sure that a woman screamed.
- Yes.
- Yes, it was.
- But...
- But seriously...
My gosh, I'm lost for words.
Whoever screamed
sounded really urgent.
But if Sora's faking this,
it's actually really creepy.
- No, wait.
- Seriously.
I bet she screamed
because it wasn't Jae Suk.
- I swear.
- What's the matter?
- What's wrong?
- This is what people do...
- when they feel upset.
- Who was it?
- Why are you lying down?
- Let me tell you...
- what I think.
- It's not her.
- Why?
I read the hint. It's not her.
Really?
(I read the hint. It's not her.)
- Really?
- What did it say?
- You saw the hint?
- I read the hint.
- What was it?
- The deities of death...
(He shares the hint he saw.)
My gosh, what's this?
(Jong Kook finds a hint
about the deities of death.)
"The deities of death aren't
any of the female guests."
(The deities of death aren't
any of the female guests.)
None of the female guests
are the deity of death.
(That means Sora and Yeo Been
aren't deities of death.)
It's not any of our female guests.
(It's not any of our female guests.)
(Then...)
Really?
- That means it's me.
- I knew it.
(I caught you,
you darn deity of death!)
- Look at him.
- I'm sorry.
What's the matter with you?
- It's these two.
- I'm sorry.
(Deities of death: 1. Jae Suk,
2. Kwang Soo or Se Chan,)
(3. And someone yet unknown)
- My gosh.
- There are two...
- Get lost.
- out of these three.
I swear it's not me.
- This is a misunderstanding.
- It's 2 out of these 3.
You guys are unbelievable.
That was such an obvious hint.
Jae Suk was...
(Earlier, when they picked
two more deities of death)
(The result of the draw)
(Jae Suk got picked
as the deity of death.)
(The picked another deity of death.)
(Who are the other two
deities of death?)
- The actual shoot...
- No, it's not me.
might be over already.
(Shush!)
(The deity of death gets angry.)
Why did you hit me?
Are you kidding me?
The race is over.
My gosh, I can't believe
he was the deity of death.
Before we move on to Round Three,
let's pick two more people.
We're picking two more
deities of death?
I need more allies.
Because the same person
might get picked?
Yes, if the same person gets picked,
it won't count.
(They pick two more
deities of death who don't overlap.)
(With 2 more of them, now there are
5 deities of death in total.)
4 teams will compete in a team of 3
for the final mission,
"I'm Scared You Might Burst
If I Touch You."
Each team will take turns.
Two people will wear an air suit...
and explain a word to their member
using only their bodies.
And that member
needs to get it right.
Whoever gets more right will get
a hint on the reincarnated members.
- The reincarnated members?
- I see.
Please discuss which team
you're all going to be in.
Can't we just stick
to our old teams?
- Yes, good idea.
- That's a good idea.
But if we get something right,
Jae Suk will also find out
about the reincarnated members.
Yes, he'll end up knowing.
Can't we just
leave him out of the game?
Let's just leave him out.
- That's nonsense.
- You're going to tell us who it is?
How about this?
Let's put Jae Suk, Kwang Soo,
and Se Chan in one team.
- Yes, let's do that.
- Come here.
- Let's put them in one team.
- Then we'll know.
- What's going on?
- You're all in one team.
Why should I be on this team?
- I'm not it.
- Why are you...
- doing this to me?
- Good idea.
- I'm not it.
- How about we put Sora...
One of them is a deity of death.
- Yes.
I see you have your arm
around Se Chan's shoulder.
(You have your arm
around Se Chan's shoulder.)
(Does that mean Se Chan
is the deity of death?)
What is the matter with you?
Seriously!
What's wrong with you?
You guys look so close.
I feel so close to you.
My gosh.
Don't let him fool you guys.
His face is red.
I really think it's Se Chan.
This is cute.
Who is this?
(Why is she suddenly hugging him?)
What's wrong with you, So Min?
The gorilla is so cute.
- What's with you?
- He's so cute.
I thought we were just friends.
- What's this?
- What are you doing?
(She suddenly kisses him.)
- You're so cute.
- Who was that?
- Will you cut it out?
- That was So Min.
- Hey.
- I'm just playing.
The gorilla costume looks so cute.
What's with you?
The bear is really cute too.
(She slaps him.)
(They're both cute,
but she treats them differently.)
Hey!
(They're both cute,
but she treats them differently.)
- Why are you hitting him?
- Why are you hitting me?
- The costumes look so cute.
- Kwang Soo, you're done.
- I'll get it right.
- You guys look so cute.
- They're cute.
- Okay.
Okay, go.
Ready, get set...
(How will they do as a team?)
Go!
(First quiz: Heat pack)
(They think carefully.)
(The bear and gorilla try to explain
in their own unique ways.)
What are they doing?
- What?
- He is a deity of death.
(They try so hard to communicate
with Jae Suk.)
It's cold? It's cold?
- Kwang Soo's pretty good.
- It's cold?
(Kwang Soo's pretty good.)
(Kwang Soo is proud.)
His hands are saying so much.
It's cold?
(He uses his cute bear paws
to explain the word.)
A heat pack?
(He gets it right.)
(Second quiz: Rice cooker)
(He makes small movements.)
What? I don't get it.
- Rice?
- He's almost there.
- Stew? Is it stew?
- He's explaining.
A stew?
(The body language of a bear.)
- That's a no.
- He just crossed his hands.
He's so cute.
The bear says no.
A stew? A meal?
A meal? No?
A pot?
Hey, gorilla.
Will you do a better job?
Hey, you need to do better.
(Unlike the shy bear,
the gorilla is dancing.)
Hey, what is he doing?
My gosh, are you serious?
- He's so cute.
- Hey, polar bear!
- Explain!
Polar bear, explain!
(He can only count
on the polar bear.)
The polar bear is so shy.
(He's huge, but he's very shy.)
- Why is he so shy?
- Hey!
Will you please explain properly?
He's so timid and kind.
- That's not the polar bear I know.
- He's so cute.
Why are his arms so short?
Hey, polar bear!
(The polar bear struggles
outside of home.)
Move on to the next one.
You need to explain properly.
(The next quiz: Bidet)
You guys can work together
to explain the word.
(You guys can work together
to explain the word.)
Toilet seat!
Jae Suk is having a hard time
getting it right.
What is it? I don't get it.
- Your costume is getting deflated.
- It's losing air.
(The polar bear looks
very discouraged.)
- It's losing air.
- Look at him.
Jae Suk, you just discouraged him.
It's okay again.
(He seems okay,
but at the same time...)
Look. He's looking down.
Hey! Chin up!
Hold your head up high!
Look at him listening to you.
He's trying really hard.
He's very kind.
- He's so cute.
- He's just a little shy.
(The polar bear is working hard
in a foreign country.)
(And today, he really misses
his family in the North Pole.)
Hey! Are you dying?
- Are you dying?
- It's okay now.
Hurry up.
What is it?
That's not it.
- Why are you guys kissing?
- Waist!
Waist! Hey, wait...
What are you guys doing?
Are you serious?
(They suddenly start
showing too much affection.)
What are you guys doing?
(He punishes them
for being too sexual.)
Come to your senses!
(Come to your senses!)
(We were too focused.)
- What do you think you're doing?
- This is so funny.
- Just move on.
- Next!
- This one is so hard.
- How is he going to get this one?
This one is so hard.
(The next quiz: Instant glue)
My gosh.
(How will the animals
describe the word?)
What's this?
- What?
- What are they doing?
(The bear and gorilla stick together
and don't move.)
What's this?
(The polar bear is
looking far away,)
(and the gorilla has his face
buried in the polar bear's chest.)
What is this?
(The polar bear is
looking far away...)
What is this?
(They're glued together.)
- He really can't get this one.
- This is so funny.
- He can't get it right.
- Next.
This one is hard as well.
What is it?
Look at him.
(He uses his paws
to explain the details.)
(He tries his best to use his paws.)
- Eyes!
- My gosh.
- This is so funny.
Glasses! Contact lenses!
- Contact lenses!
- Yes, he got it right.
- Great.
- That's it.
You guys got five right.
- That's a lot.
- We did very well.
Great job.
Next team, please choose one person.
What's that?
Tent!
- Car!
- No.
Motorcycle!
(So Min puts on the gorilla costume
and explains very passionately.)
Look at So Min.
(So Min puts on the gorilla costume
and explains very passionately.)
(Sung Oh is in a dinosaur costume.)
(Thanks to So Min's effort
to help him get the answers...)
Is she running?
(Thanks to So Min's effort
to help him get the answers...)
Fire extinguisher!
You got all 10 questions right.
- So Min did a great job.
- Nice.
Great job.
Will the winning team
please come forward?
- We'll give you a hint.
- Should we keep it from Sung Oh?
- Why?
- Never mind. Come on.
You can see it too. Great job.
This is a hint
about the reincarnated members?
Yes, the reincarnated members.
(What kind of hint will they get?)
You're going to tell us?
Reincarnated members...
aren't among any of the younger
members of Running Man.
(The reincarnated members aren't
the younger members of Running Man.)
This is confusing.
(Then Se Chan and So Min aren't
the reincarnated members.)
The hint was given.
For 30 minutes, we will have
the final name tag elimination.
- 30 minutes?
- If you don't come to a conclusion,
we will open the stage where
the identities will be revealed.
Three members can go up the stage
at the same time.
If all three of them
are regular members,
the reincarnated members
and regular members win.
If even one of them is
a deity of death,
the deities of death win.
The reincarnated members
can use a special method...
to check the members' identities.
Each of them
can rip off one name tag...
to eliminate a deity of death.
If all reincarnated members are out
before the stage opens,
the race will end immediately.
Please go
to your designated spots...
before the race begins.
(They go to their designated spots.)
(Who are the reincarnated members
and deities of death?)
I don't know if it's Se Chan
or Kwang Soo.
Who could it be?
Maybe both of them
are the deities of death.
(Both of them could be
the deities of death.)
I need to know who
the reincarnated members are.
Who are they?
The one I think is
a reincarnated member...
is Sung Oh.
Sung Oh and Jae Hong.
(He thinks Sung Oh and Jae Hong
are the reincarnated members.)
(Walking around)
(Jae Hong is walking around.)
Sung Oh.
(Sung Oh enters the room.)
(Are Sung Oh and Jae Hong meeting
in secret?)
Sung Oh.
I should pretend to be
a regular member, right?
That's right.
No one is suspecting you.
Whose name tag should I rip off?
Then people will know...
that both of us are
the reincarnated members.
(Are both of them
the reincarnated members?)
(They had a preliminary mission
on the last week's episode.)
to the location of the members.
(Sung Oh's van)
(Ripping off)
Sung Oh,
you are out.
(But I haven't even gotten started.)
I was outside the van.
(He talks nonsense.)
(Jae Hong's name tag
got ripped off too.)
(What are you doing?)
I will put it back on.
What was that?
Am I out?
- What...
- You are a reincarnated member...
who came back to life.
(You are a reincarnated member
who came back to life.)
(Sung Oh and Jae Hong found out...)
(about each other's identity.)
There are more deities of death.
I will tell you how you can check
other members' identities.
Find the name tags
that are hidden...
in the building.
If you collect three name tags,
we will give you...
the number of the deities of death
out of the three.
- Out of the three?
- Yes.
We need three name tags.
From the number,
we can ascertain our guesses
and eliminate the deities of death.
I will rip off Se Chan's name tag.
- Really?
- Yes. I am sure it's him.
Then you should do it.
(Jae Hong is sure
Se Chan is a deity of death.)
This is too hard.
(The race is too hard
for the reincarnated members.)
(He doesn't hide
that he is a deity of death.)
5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
The race starts.
(The race starts!)
The deities of death need to work.
(The official deity of death
goes to the members.)
- Tell me if you are reincarnated...
- Suk Jin.
- Go away.
- Please go someplace else.
Go away.
We don't want to talk
to a deity of death.
Jae Hong, are you
a reincarnated member?
I am a regular member.
- Go away.
- I am serious.
Do we agree...
everyone else except for Jae Suk
is a regular member?
Suk Jin is the one...
- who is the closest to death.
- What? Why?
- His age...
- Don't talk about reality.
Why did you suddenly bring up death?
He could be a deity of death.
What are you playing at?
- He could be a deity of death.
- You could die at any age.
- You can't...
You can't make a guess that way.
(After exchanging curses,)
(Jae Hong is busy
looking for the name tags.)
(He finds the first name tag!)
(Yang Se Chan)
(It's Se Chan, the member
Jae Hong suspects the most!)
I want to find another one.
(He needs to find 2 more name tags.)
Would it be in here?
Keep looking.
(The crew wouldn't hide it
by the switchboard.)
There it is!
No, that's a prop.
Really?
(Sung Oh is bad
at finding the name tags.)
They hid them too well.
Sung Oh.
(What is he doing there?)
(Did she see me
looking for name tags?)
- Sung Oh, what exactly are you?
- What?
You could be a deity of death.
I'm confused.
- You are a deity of death, right?
- I...
How could you ask me that
so suddenly?
- Seriously.
- I am a regular member.
- Me too.
- Really?
(Everyone claims to be
a regular member.)
What are you?
Here is what I figured out.
The production crew assigned...
the reincarnated members,
deities of death,
and something else.
(Something else?)
We need to find the being
between the first two,
Young Gu.
(He brings up Young Gu in haste.)
There is Young Gu
among the regular members?
(There is no way
Ji Hyo would fall for this lie.)
(She falls for it.)
That's what I figured out.
(Okay, I got her.)
If one of us
is a deity of death...
So we need to find the link.
Let's hide first.
There are cameramen.
We can't hide by ourselves.
(Will you have a meeting
without the cameras?)
My kids do that.
(I thought I could hide
by myself.)
My kids hide their faces
and tell me to look for them.
So Min!
- Listen to me for a second.
- Did you figure something out?
Be suspicious of Jong Kook.
- Be suspicious Jong Kook? Why?
- Be suspicious of Jong Kook.
- A deity of death?
- I think he corners me...
- because he is a deity of death.
- What do you mean?
- Why?
- He corners me too much.
The deities of death
know each other.
What did you say?
- What are you doing?
- I am recording. What did you say?
Why are you recording
when there are cameras everywhere?
Come on. What about Jong Kook?
There is a chance
Jong Kook is a deity of death.
That must be why he corners me.
You recorded it...
to see Se Chan
when you miss him, right?
(Is it for personal use?)
Right?
- So Min.
You are so weird on the show.
- A deity of death said this.
- What?
- He is a deity of death.
- He is.
- It's highly likely.
- He is a deity of death.
- Just look at him.
That's it.
Did you film this video
because you like him?
- Hey.
- Stop it.
There is no other reason to film it.
Why did you film it
when there are so many cameras?
- It's not like that.
- It's for personal use, right?
- She will watch it every night.
- She did it...
because she was embarrassed.
(Leave the personal agenda
out of this race.)
(Jae Hong, a reincarnated member,
is looking for the name tags.)
There it is!
(He finds the second name tag!)
(Jeon Yeo Been)
(He obtains Yeo Been's name tag!)
(He continues
to look for the name tags.)
(He finds the third name tag!)
I collected three name tags.
If you collect three name tags,
we will give you...
the number of the deities of death
out of the three.
How many deities of death...
The number is...
(Among the three of them,)
(how many deities of death exist?)
- 1.
- 1?
(Among the 3 of them,
1 deity of death exists.)
I will rip off Se Chan's name tag.
- Really?
- Yes. I am sure it's him.
Then you should do it.
You must know.
- Know what?
- My identity.
Of course, I do.
You are a deity of death.
This is driving me crazy.
You are scaring me.
Go rip off someone's name tag.
- Seriously.
- If you are wrong...
Right now, I should be...
- What was that?
- Why did you rip off my name tag?
(Jong Kook's name tag...)
(gets ripped off!)
- What was that?
- Why did you rip off my name tag?
(What is going on?)
Why did you rip off my name tag?
(He hasn't figured out
what's going on.)
I will get...
- What?
- I will get another badge.
(And)
Why did you rip off my name tag?
(She rips off Se Chan's name tag
as well.)
You can only rip off one name tag.
What was that?
You can't rip off two name tags.
What is going on?
(Sora ripped off two name tags
in an instant.)
Sora.
What is going on?
Did someone rip off a name tag?
- What is going on?
- I don't know!
I thought she was a ghost!
I peed my pants a little!
- What is going on?
- What did you do?
I was getting a bit bored.
- What does that mean?
- Are you a deity of death?
(What is Sora?)
(Sora was a regular member
at this point.)
(Before Round 3,
more deities of death were picked.)
(Kang Sora)
(Sora became a deity of death.)
I might as well rip off name tags.
There isn't much time.
- This has never happened before.
- This is insane.
I was just standing still.
- This is crazy! So you know now!
- Who eliminated them?
Who eliminated them?
- Sora ripped off my name tag.
- That means he is a regular member.
(Se Chan is a regular member.)
- Kwang Soo.
- That means he is a deity of death.
- Kwang Soo is it.
- He is a deity of death.
He is a deity of death.
(Kwang Soo is a deity of death.)
- Hey, you!
- For goodness' sake!
- Hey!
- That's not how you play!
- Why did you do that?
Sora!
(I made so much effort.)
Do you want to be a deity of death?
- I would feel more comfortable.
- Okay.
(Testing)
- What are you?
- I am a reincarnated member.
(He sounds Kwang Soo out.)
Really?
Hold on.
Hold on. I was lying.
I was lying.
I am...
(Kwang Soo thought
Se Chan was a reincarnated member.)
(He put the name tag back on.)
- Hey!
- Things were going too slow!
Why did you rip off
Se Chan's name tag?
What were you thinking?
Sora. For goodness' sake.
I mean...
Jong Kook, I hate you.
Jong Kook.
Where are Sung Oh and Jae Hong?
I mean...
(Sung Oh and Jae Hong
are looking for the hints.)
Where are they?
Jae Hong isn't here either.
Where did he go?
Anyone who isn't here is
either a deity of death...
or a reincarnated member.
- I'm right here.
- I'm sure of it.
- Those who aren't here...
- I'm right here.
- are definitely...
- Jae Hong isn't here.
either a deity of death...
- Or a reincarnated member.
- or a reincarnated member.
I'm sure they're here.
- Jae Suk.
- We need to get Jae Hong.
We need to eliminate Jae Hong
and Sung Oh.
- Hurry.
- Where are they going?
- If we don't do it, we'll die.
We'll die.
- Let's go.
- We need to go together.
- We have to eliminate them.
- This is crazy.
Over there.
Someone's there.
(They find someone.)
This is crazy.
(Jae Hong is looking for a hint.)
(And they run toward him.)
They're running!
- We need to catch them!
(They run after
the deities of death.)
Look!
(Jae Hong runs away
after he sees them come after him.)
(Jong Kook tries to help
the reincarnated member.)
Kwang Soo! Hey!
- Kwang Soo, eliminate him!
- Hey!
- Catch him!
- Kwang Soo, eliminate him!
You need to catch him!
Eliminate him!
(The deities of death
will win the race...)
(if they eliminate
all the reincarnated members.)
(The distance between them
keeps getting shorter.)
Go!
(1 of the 2 reincarnated members...)
Jae Hong, run!
(could get eliminated.)
Jae Hong!
(Jae Hong is in trouble,)
(and Se Chan comes to the rescue.)
Jae Suk!
(He starts defending himself.)
You darn deity of death.
- Come here.
- Jae Suk!
You darn punk!
Wait.
(Kwang Soo is outnumbered.)
- Be careful.
- I'll hold him.
Hurry. Do it.
(He quickly reaches
for the name tag.)
- Okay!
- Nice!
(Swift)
(Kwang Soo, the deity of death,
gets eliminated!)
Jae Hong!
Kwang Soo, the deity of death,
is now eliminated.
He was the deity of death?
- Yes.
- I'm so angry.
I almost had him!
Kang Sora!
(He's angry at Sora
for ruining everything.)
(Jae Hong and Se Chan succeed
in eliminating Kwang Soo.)
(Reincarnated Members,
Deities of Death)
My gosh, it must've been hard.
Seriously.
How did you two manage?
- Kwang Soo.
- Jae Suk.
What happened?
You didn't catch them?
- I got eliminated.
- You didn't get Jae Hong?
(He doesn't know what to say.)
(I can't believe you failed
to get his name tag.)
There's something I didn't tell you.
I could ask about three people.
And I asked about Se Chan, Yeo Been,
- and Suk Jin.
- How many are there?
Out of those 3 people,
1 of them is a deity of death.
So two people are innocent.
- It's either Yeo Been or Suk Jin.
- One of them is innocent.
(Other than Se Chan, who was proven
to be a normal person...)
- Yeo Been, what are you?
- Yes?
- What are you?
- What about you?
- You tell me first.
What are you, Suk Jin?
I'm just a normal person.
- Really?
- Yes.
Should we go together?
Sure.
(Which one is the hidden
deity of death?)
I can't believe you attacked me
from behind.
Suk Jin ripped off my name tag!
Here's a penalty badge for you.
(Suk Jin's name tag is torn off.)
- Yeo Been is a deity of death!
- Suk Jin tried to eliminate me!
- Yeo Been took off my name tag!
- Suk Jin ripped off my nametag!
- I'm serious. Stay away from him.
- Who did it?
- Yeo Been attacked me from behind.
- Stay away from Suk Jin.
- Stay away from him.
- You're lying.
Yeo Been obviously
tried to take off his name tag.
She took my name tag off.
- She's a deity of death.
- I'm serious.
- Stay away from her.
Yeo Been is a deity of death.
- Yeo Been did this to him.
- Look.
- She did it.
- Take a look at this.
- He's putting on an act.
- Yeo Been is a deity of death.
- She's a deity of death.
You're a deity of death.
- What?
- Yeo Been is a deity of death.
- She took my name tag off. Look.
- Really?
- It's Yeo Been?
- She attacked me from behind.
These three are
all deities of death.
- She took it off from behind.
- I'm just a normal person.
You saw that, right?
Right now...
Gosh, this is hard to tell.
Don't go near Jae Suk. Come here.
Sora... Sora's okay for now.
She can't take off any name tags.
- Suk Jin.
- I don't need anything.
- Stay right there.
- I'm totally fine.
- You stay there as well.
- Me too.
Stay there.
Wait.
- Is it him?
- Look at her.
(Yeo Been suddenly starts
running toward Jae Hong.)
- What are you doing?
- Let me see.
- Show me.
What's wrong with her?
- Hold her still.
- She's a deity of death.
Hold her still.
- Stay away.
- Stand back.
She's being weird. Look.
What is she doing?
I'm telling you!
She tore my name tag off!
- Exactly.
- So get over here.
- You're really scary.
- Stay there.
Suk Jin isn't a good actor.
- Hold her still.
- I'm so upset.
He really means it.
- Suk Jin is really angry.
- I'm so angry.
Yeo Been is the deity.
- We can't trust Haha either.
- We can't trust him.
Are you kidding me?
You're unbelievable.
So Min isn't safe either.
- I'm sorry. It's just for now.
- Let's go.
- The deities of death...
- Let's check.
- There's Haha, So Min,
- So Min...
- and Ji Hyo.
- Go away, reincarnated members!
- Go away, go away!
- Go away!
- We want to be treated fairly!
- Treat us like humans!
You guys get all the camera time!
We're working too!
Let us work!
- Let's go...
- That's the deity of death.
Don't come near him. Run away.
Yeo Been, we just got a hint.
Right?
We already know
that you're the deity of death.
(He lies to her.)
(Is she upset
because they're wrong?)
- Right? I'm a normal person.
- Yes.
- No way. You can't go.
- Can I go there now?
- Yeo Been, we already know.
- Let me go there now.
- No!
- Let me go!
- I'm going to go, okay?
- No way!
My gosh, what's with her?
- They trust me.
- No!
No, wait.
(Suddenly...)
- No, wait.
- Suk Jin can't be here.
- Hey, be careful.
- Watch out.
- Be careful. She's scary.
- Suk Jin can't be here.
Hold her tight.
(Ripping)
(Yeo Been's name tag
gets ripped off.)
Hold her tight.
(Sung Oh tears off
Yeo Been's name tag.)
We got fooled.
I'm not the deity of death.
It's not me.
Now, we know for sure.
- It's okay.
- That was a good guess.
(Is Yeo Been really
a deity of death?)
(Or is she just a normal person
who got framed?)
- Are you out, Kwang Soo?
- Yes.
- Me too.
- What?
Normal people
can also get eliminated?
(Yeo Been is a normal person?)
A reincarnated member
tore off my name tag.
- She's a normal person?
- We know the answer now.
Okay, we got it. Hey, Sung Oh.
- We got it.
- She's a normal person?
- Good.
- She's a normal person.
That means Suk Jin
is a deity of death.
- Suk Jin is a deity of death.
- It's him.
It happened a while ago.
(Ripping)
(Suk Jin tore off her name tag
while no one was looking.)
What are you?
A reincarnated member?
- I'm a normal person.
- Be quiet.
Suk Jin just ripped off
my name tag!
I can't believe you attacked me
from behind.
(Sora and Suk Jin
come up with a lie.)
(They make it look like his name tag
was torn off.)
Yeo Been took off my name tag! Look!
(He acts like he was the one
who got attacked.)
The race is over. Please gather
around in front of the platform.
You thought I was
a normal person, didn't you?
- Yes, totally.
- Right?
Everyone's gotten so good at this.
Suk Jin is a great actor.
He was a deity of death?
Seriously.
The race is finally over.
However, the reincarnated members
are still alive.
The reincarnated members
can discuss with each other...
and put three people
on the platform.
- Three people?
- Reincarnated members will lose...
if they pick a deity of death.
If not, they'll win.
We know for sure that Suk Jin,
Jae Suk, and Sora
are deities of death.
Now, we need to choose between
Haha, So Min, and Ji Hyo.
(The remaining deity of death
is among these three.)
- Who do we know for sure?
- But...
It's really not me.
- I swear it's not me.
- If you don't pick me,
you'll really regret it.
I don't care.
(Okay, I don't care.)
I want him to bet
his entire fortune.
We're going to draw
two deities of death.
(In the first draw,)
(her name didn't get picked.)
(And in the end,
her name never got picked.)
Why can't I be
the deity of death as well?
(She shows how upset she is
that he won't believe her.)
- So Min is a deity of death.
- I'm so upset.
(He starts accusing people again.)
- What?
- That came out of nowhere.
- He's doing it again.
- So Min...
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm really not it.
- So Min, stop lying.
- It really isn't me.
- It's really not me.
- You've done enough.
- I promise it's not me.
- This is so upsetting.
This is so upsetting.
I'm so upset.
Ji Hyo came downstairs
and asked me...
why I was all alone.
Then she told me what was happening
and warned me to run away.
Sung Oh, everyone's
gathered together right now.
If you're really
a reincarnated member,
you need to be careful.
They're all targeting you.
(Ji Hyo tells Sung Oh to run away.)
- Why are you smiling?
- What?
- I smiled? No, I didn't.
- Yes.
(He's suspicious of Ji Hyo because
she warned him with a smile.)
I feel like she lied to me.
I didn't lie to you.
And I didn't smile, Sung Oh.
My gosh, this is crazy.
- Are you done now?
- Yes.
We'll choose
after we hear your last words.
- I'm human.
- Why?
Because I'm human!
- That's it?
- Did you treat me like a human?
- Did you act like a human?
- You!
I stood by you when you were
being accused as a deity of death!
He's right. He stood by me.
(Haha was the only one
who trusted him.)
I was the only one
who kept saying you're innocent.
I feel so upset.
- It really isn't me. I swear.
- I feel really upset.
- I'd rather have humans lose.
- I'm really human.
I don't care if humans lose
even though I am one.
The reincarnated members
can have their final discussion...
and put three people
on the platform.
- Go ahead.
- Se Chan.
Okay, please step up.
(Se Chan gets chosen.)
- Jong Kook.
- Finally.
Finally.
I can't get soaked today.
- Me neither.
- Let's be a decent human being.
- You need to make...
- I'll just be a deity of death.
- the right choice as a human being!
- They've begun.
(Who will the reincarnated members
choose as their last pick?)
- Ji Hyo.
- Okay, step up the platform.
(The reincarnated members choose
Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo.)
I swear I'm not a deity of death.
How many times have I told you?
- Okay, then.
- You're mistaken.
Among these three people...
You still have time to cancel.
The deity of death...
Please! You still have time
to change your mind!
You still have time!
Among the three of you...
(They weren't certain.)
(What is the result?)
(Among the three of you...)
there's no deity of death.
(They did it! The reincarnated
members win the race.)
- See? Exactly.
- I'm sorry. I suspected you.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
And for your information, So Min
wasn't the deity of death either.
See?
Say that louder!
Tell them I'm a human!
Say that louder.
Tell them I'm a human. Please.
Please. Say that louder.
The reincarnated members
were Jae Hong and Sung Oh.
They were eliminated during
the preliminary round this morning.
As for the deities of death
who were chosen after each round,
Kwang Soo and Haha were chosen
after the first round.
- Jae Suk and Haha were next.
- Come on.
- You were chosen.
- Suk Jin and Sora were chosen...
after the third round.
I see. So you were a human too.
How many times must I tell you?
He just said that too.
- I'm sorry, So Min.
- Hold on.
(Heartbroken)
It's so weird. Whenever we get
the water bomb, it gets cold.
Is it frozen?
Suk Jin should give the stick
on our behalf.
- Me?
- Yes.
I'm sure you have
a lot of grudges against him.
Can I use the side to hit him?
- The side of the stick?
- Go ahead.
Is it today?
You, punk.
(He doesn't sound scary at all.)
Do it right!
It's about time
Suk Jin taught you a lesson.
- You need a good beating.
- How many?
You need a good beating.
I need an excuse
to hit him hard next time.
(Starting today, it's self-defense.)
You, punk.
(Repeating himself)
Do it right.
Hey, Suk Jin can be pretty strong.
(Striking hard)
(A loud striking sound)
That sounded like it hurt.
That was strong.
Come on, hit me harder.
It only offended Suk Jin.
Gosh. That was my full swing.
That wasn't so bad.
Anyway, I'd like to thank
the cast of "Secret Zoo."
I hope that your movie will be
well-received at the box office.
Thank you.
I hope your movie is a big hit.
I hope it's a big hit.
All right. In 1, 2, 3.
(Splashing)
Good job.
Good work.
(We thank all the guests
for joining us.)
(Running Martial Arts School opens!)
(To become masters of martial arts,)
(four masters came
to attend the school.)
(The master of wind, Park Cho Rong)
(The master of water, Kang Han Na)
(But...)
(is there a possibility
of romance at school?)
(Did the students
follow their hearts...)
(and choose romance
over martial arts?)
(There's no time for that!)
(A secret trade of cards
in the back of the school)
(The master of fire, Keum Sae Rok)
(The master of tree, Lee Joo Young)
(Which one of them will become
a master of martial arts?)
(Running Martial Arts School:
Trade the Cards)