- Hello.
Look at the fall leaves over there.
I think the fall foliage
peaks this week.
I know. It's beautiful.
- It's chilly now.
- They are the best this week.
- But it's quite warm.
- It looks amazing.
Your boots are too much.
- Gosh, I knew you'd say that.
- For this season.
It's too soon
to wear boots like them.
The most awkward part
of So Min's outfit is her boots.
I know. Why are you wearing them?
The edges of the boots are folded
around her knees.
Around her knees,
- they are wrinkled.
- You're bleeding on your knees.
So Min is standing
at the end for a reason.
So stop pointing that out.
- Why are you trying to stop us?
- When a dog wears shoes,
it walks awkwardly.
I'm just like that.
I feel awkward in the boots.
You look like a kid at an elementary
school entrance ceremony.
That's right. I'm dressed like this
to attend an entrance ceremony.
(That's right. I'm dressed like this
to attend an entrance ceremony.)
I'm dressed like this
to attend an entrance ceremony.
I see. That's good.
When he says that...
- You should attack him.
- I have nothing to say.
- I... By the way...
- Say something to attack him.
- Suk Jin, you should hit back.
- Is that what you're doing?
Suk Jin! My gosh.
That's what I thought
when I put these on.
That's perfect.
I'm very grateful.
I was right about that.
I got it right.
Suk Jin read your mind.
Suk Jin is good.
- Suk Jin...
- This isn't what he wanted.
- Just let it go.
- Hey, Se Chan.
Suk Jin is really mean.
He got flustered by what I said.
Then he checked Se Chan's outfit.
(He changed his target.)
(As soon as he failed
to attack Jae Suk,)
(he glanced at Se Chan
to pick on him.)
(And he got caught right away.)
(He leered at Se Chan
to change his target.)
Do you know why
he didn't say anything?
His shirt is similar to mine.
- It has a similar pattern.
- He's right.
I was going to say something,
but it looked just like mine.
He wanted to criticize
Se Chan instead.
It's like looking into a mirror.
The weather is
very nice today, isn't it?
- Yes.
Since fall is the season
of gastronomy,
you're going to enjoy
tasty food today.
- Okay.
- Nice.
And we have six guests...
whom we want to have a meal with.
- Gosh, six guests?
- Yes.
- We will...
- What? There's Bomi.
I really wanted to eat with her.
Bomi.
- There's Namjoo.
- Namjoo.
- Hello.
- She's Namjoo.
- Namjoo?
- It's Apink!
(Running Man's family, Apink
is here to have a meal together.)
(Namjoo got her wings
with her solo, "Bird".)
(Bomi is a charming girl
with a good appetite.)
(Welcome, guys!)
- Hello.
We just showed up
out of nowhere, right?
That's why it's so good
to see you.
- Namjoo.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Namjoo.
- Bomi.
- It's been a long time.
They are gourmets.
Bomi, don't you think
this is too straight?
I've gained some weight,
so I want to cover my face.
- I need to cover it.
- It looks like you ironed it.
How did you do that?
- Namjoo, how have you been?
- A long time ago.
My solo album was released.
- That's right!
- Oh, right.
- You didn't know.
- I know. I watched it.
You had something on here.
I saw you dance alone.
I didn't have anything on.
- You didn't?
- Why would you make things up?
Namjoo came to my gym once,
but I didn't see her afterwards.
- Maybe you told her something.
- You didn't go?
- She said,
- That's not true.
"I'll start working out."
And she didn't come again.
She's here as a guest,
but she's being scolded
that she didn't go to the gym.
Really?
I think people like her
seem more humane.
Those who say they will work out
and never come back.
- I didn't see her again.
- Isn't that humane?
- She is indeed humane.
- Right.
Here are our next guests.
I guess we're having
guests with a good appetite.
- It's Mingyu.
- SEVENTEEN.
Welcome. How have you been?
Have you been doing well?
(Hoshi and Mingyu of SEVENTEEN
are back with "Home;Run".)
(SEVENTEEN is so popular
that they have no time to eat.)
(So the two members are joining
Running Man as representatives.)
(It's nice to see you.)
- All right.
- Mingyu...
- has been in our show many times.
- Right.
But this is the first time
for Hoshi.
- Right?
- Yes.
It's been so long since I met
Hoshi in "Sugar Man".
- In "Sugar Man"...
- I didn't appear in "Sugar Man".
- Gosh, he wasn't there.
- Why are you confused?
- Because...
- He's becoming like Suk Jin.
SEVENTEEN has a lot of members,
so I thought I met Hoshi.
But you weren't there.
Things are not going well
for you today.
- It's okay. Cheer up!
- Cheer up!
- Good luck.
- Get your energy up!
It can happen.
Let's bring in the next guests.
They are the last team.
We have a lot of guests today.
(Who are the last guests
to eat with the members?)
(Laughing)
What is it?
(They burst into laughter
as soon as the guests show up.)
Hello.
- What are you doing here?
- What's happening?
- Hello!
- Hello.
It's Soo-DRAGON.
- What are you doing here?
- Soo Yong is perfect for this.
- Chang Hee.
- Okay.
Okay. He's here.
Gosh. As they showed up...
right after Mingyu and Hoshi,
it's really...
- It feels heavy.
- It is heavy.
Soo Yong and I debuted together
at "KBS College Comedy Contest".
He was number one in Yeouido.
Right. He went
to Yeouido High School.
- Yes.
- He grabbed Jae Suk's shoulder.
It's not that he was
number one at his school.
He says he was a good fighter,
but it's not like there's...
a famous story about that.
I think he was
just a worthless scamp.
I didn't know that about Soo Yong.
- All right.
- My gosh.
How could he do that to Jae Suk?
- To Jae Suk...
- Actually,
he's always treated me like this
since our debut.
- Because he's older.
- When I talk a lot,
he always does this.
All right. Good.
If you don't have anything to say,
we will move on.
I don't have much to say.
Okay.
- We're moving on.
- All right then.
We've moved on.
All right. Every time...
Bomi joined us,
she showed her kicks.
I don't know if she'd do it today.
I want her to kick Soo Yong.
I think Soo Yong is ready.
- Right.
- He can give it a try.
Are you going to be okay?
Are you really okay?
- About getting kicked?
- Yes.
- In the buttocks.
- It's her signature.
It's her signature.
All of a sudden?
(Bomi is under a lot of pressure.)
- We all experienced it once.
- I can do that.
- Are you okay with it?
- Sure.
As far as I know, he's very strong.
Sure. He looks strong.
Are you really okay with this?
Yes. It's no problem.
Can I hit you after you hit me?
- What are you talking about?
- What?
- That's not what we're doing.
- How could you...
- How could you clench your fist?
- That's not it.
- That's not what you're doing.
It won't take long.
- It just stings.
- With your foot?
- Where? In the buttocks?
- Look straight ahead.
Are you going
to do this at full strength?
Yes.
Soo Yong was quite famous
in Yeouido High School too.
- I know. He really was.
- All right.
(Will he be able
to put up with Bomi's kick?)
(Groaning)
(The legend of Yeouido High School
groans like a weak person.)
(A scamp from Yeouido collapses.)
Did you hear his short holler?
Soo Yong doesn't usually
react much to anyone.
- But not to this.
- Yes, this is the first I've seen.
Thank you, Bomi.
Soo Yong doesn't react.
This is the first
I've ever seen a reaction.
You're the only one
who made him react.
Are you okay?
- That was good.
- Yes, it was fun.
(Bomi's single blow made everyone
laugh at Soo Yong's reaction.)
Before I explain the rules to you,
- we'll decide on the teams.
- All right.
- So there are teams.
- We'll divide you into three teams.
Each guest has already teamed up
with the person they came with.
- I see.
- Oh, really?
Now they'll decide
who's going to be on their teams.
Each team will pick a card...
to decide the order
of picking their members.
They will take turns to choose one
they want on their team.
(The result of fixing the order)
1, 2, and 3.
Starting there,
you will take turns...
to choose a member for your team.
We will choose...
Jeon So Min.
(My goodness)
She's grinning.
- She's smiling like this again.
- Yes, because she's so excited.
She doesn't know
how to hide her feelings.
Yes, every week.
- Hoshi and Mingyu picked her.
- She's excited.
Who's next?
We will choose...
(Who will be picked
by Bomi and Namjoo of Apink?)
- Jong Kook!
- Okay!
(They chose Jong Kook.)
- Jong Kook eats well.
- Thank you.
- He eats a lot.
- They want to win.
- Yes, they want to win.
- I can eat a lot.
Okay, next.
I will pick...
(Soo Yong and Chang Hee
will pick...)
(They're whispering to each other
like it's difficult to decide.)
(They chose Jae Suk!)
- We choose Yoo Jae Suk!
- Yoo Jae Suk!
(The scamp kicks Jae Suk's butt
to chose him.)
- Why would you pick me?
- Jae Suk.
I'm not good at talking
so we need you.
- This is crazy.
- We need you.
Okay, next.
We will choose Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Se Chan!
She doesn't like it though.
- I don't want him.
- You don't?
I don't want to team up with him.
You don't want her being happy
on their team, do you?
- Go get her.
- I'll ruin everything for you.
- Come on. Why?
- Just get lost!
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Don't!
Hey, hey, hey. Don't!
(Mingyu and Hoshi got a shield!)
Now it's Namjoo and Bomi's turn.
(She has to choose between Suk Jin,
Ji Hyo, Haha, and Kwang Soo.)
We choose Haha.
- Oh, yes!
- Yes!
I wanted to team up with you!
(Haha leaves with a cheer.)
(It's Soo Yong and Chang Hee's turn
to pick among the remaining three.)
- Who will you choose?
- What?
We will choose Mr. Ji.
- Mr. Ji.
- Hey, hey!
(They chose Suk Jin!)
- How could you choose Suk Jin?
- Hey!
- If you choose me,
- Is this a comedian team?
- we're 200 years old in total.
- You should've chosen Ji Hyo.
What is this, "Old Gang is Back"?
Why did you do that?
- You're all so old.
- What is it, a room for comedians?
Soo Yong isn't
good at talking to strangers.
- He's too shy to talk to strangers.
- Get along with the others too.
This is the worst team ever.
- Can I talk casually?
- Sure.
- No, you can't do that.
- Why not?
- You can't talk casually.
- Why not? Hoshi is younger than me.
- Don't talk casually. No.
- Why not?
- We should talk formally.
- Come on, why not?
Talk formally, all right?
These two keep fighting.
I don't want to be on this team.
She wanted to talk casually,
so I said no.
We are going to talk
formally to each other.
- Come on.
- Be polite to each other.
- He's ruining everything.
- Not today.
- Do not speak casually.
- Okay, now...
- Mingyu and Hoshi, your turn.
- It's our turn.
(It's Mingyu and Hoshi's turn
to choose.)
I choose Ji Hyo.
(He picked Ji Hyo.)
- Give me a five, Ji Hyo.
- This is great.
- You should try to stop Se Chan.
- I should?
- Yes, you should.
- Kwang Soo...
(Kwang Soo...)
(Ji Hyo leaves to join the team,)
(and only one member is left.)
(Deserted...)
Last time, he was picked first.
Last time, he was picked first
but not today.
(Left all alone in the corner)
(He comes in last
even before he joins a team.)
Hey.
Hey, Chalk.
- What?
- Chalk.
- What chalk?
- Blue chalk.
Do you want to be hit by chalk?
Chalkboard eraser.
Gosh, do we have to pick him?
(You don't want me?)
Why, because
you don't have an option?
- You want to have an option?
- No, we want you.
- Hey.
- I really like you.
Is it okay not to pick him?
Oh, come on!
Can Kwang Soo eat alone?
- Why would I do that?
- It'd be funny.
(Including the blue chalk,
they're divided into three teams.)
So today,
you're going to
visit old restaurants...
with more than
30 years of history...
to enjoy their food.
It's called Old Restaurant Race.
More than 30 years?
- We are the old ones.
- If Suk Jin and Soo Yong...
enter a restaurant,
that makes it an old restaurant.
- We are the old four.
- We're like an old restaurant.
- What does it mean?
- Old...
- Old restaurants.
- Right.
Since these two were
young comedians,
they were famous for
eating unappetizingly.
- Yes, he eats unappetizingly.
- I'm serious.
He also has a poor appetite.
These two eat
like the food doesn't taste good.
- I feel bad for Chang Hee.
- Serve them well.
When you look for old restaurants,
you should follow special rules.
First, please add up
every member's age.
- Seriously? Wait a minute.
- Gosh.
Adding up the age of you two
will make it 110 years old.
- I'm 39.
- And I'm 49.
Then it's 70, 80...
- Then it's 98 and...
- 198 in total.
- Our total age is 198.
- 198.
Yes, it is 159.
- 159? 159.
- Yes, 159.
- Se Chan.
- It should be more than that.
- 159.
- It's correct. 159.
I'm 26.
- Add up the age of you two.
- You're only 26?
(Add up Bomi and Namjoo's age.)
(Bomi is 28 and Namjoo is 26,
so adding up their age...)
It's 54.
Okay, 54. I'm 36.
- I'm 45.
- You're 36 years old?
54 and 36 is...
- You can use your cell phone.
- That's right.
- 54 and...
- Yes.
- Add your age to 90.
- 90?
135. Add it to 135.
I wish I could multiply by zero.
- You can't add up the numbers?
- It's 95.
(Team Jong Kook has a hard time
adding numbers of double figures.)
- You can't add up numbers?
- It's 96.
(Finally done calculating)
It's 177.
- It's 177.
- Okay.
We're the oldest.
- We only have 4 members.
- And our total age is 198.
Seriously?
It's 198, 177, and 159.
Until 3 p.m.,
you're going to have
meals at old restaurants you find.
Subtract the years of the place's
history from your team's number.
You win when your team's number
goes down to zero.
- What an original game.
- We should visit many places.
- But for us...
- It's tougher for us.
They should have
at least five meals.
Five meals.
You should subtract numbers
according to the rules.
First, you will find a restaurant
with more than 30 years of history.
You go through a mission to set
the order to subtract your number.
Starting with the winner, you may
subtract as much as you want.
So everyone still has a way to win.
Okay.
You will go through
a simple mission...
to subtract the number of its age
from the member's age.
Through the mission, you will
decide who will subtract first.
And you may subtract
as many as you want.
(Restaurant with 50 years of history
1st subtracts 30, 2nd subtracts 15,)
(4th subtracts 1)
You all start off
with your real age.
I'll show you an example.
This is Kim Soo Yong's Age Board.
You may return the badge to us
as you subtract your number.
- Okay, okay.
- Until you're out of badges.
This one is Mingyu's.
Everyone has one.
Gosh, there are so many.
Their age difference shows
a page full of badges.
A page full of badges.
- He's as old as his father.
- We're at a disadvantage.
Except for the winning team,
the other teams will get a penalty.
Two members with most ages from
the two teams will get a penalty.
I know who will get a penalty.
(You should work hard to subtract
your age to avoid penalty.)
So we're all competitors.
(Catching a glimpse)
Yes, Kwang Soo is on our team.
No, I won't betray.
Everyone, get in your team's van.
- Let's go!
- Yes, let's do this!
- I'm hungry.
- Let's go, let's go!
- Let's have something delicious.
- Let's go, let's go.
Ji Hyo.
Jeon So Min,
I'm sitting at the back.
So Min, you shouldn't
sit at the back.
I know you want to
sit at the back, but you can't.
- You can't.
- Because of Hoshi and Mingyu?
(So Min wanted to sit at the back.)
You think I wanted to sit there
because of Hoshi and Mingyu?
- But you can't.
- Thank you.
- What are you talking about?
- You can't.
They should be
as comfortable as they can.
I understand why you picked Ji Hyo.
But Hoshi and Mingyu,
why did you pick Se Chan?
- It'll be easier when they have me.
- He's funny.
- You think Se Chan's funny?
- Yes.
Yes, Hoshi thinks I'm funny.
Se Chan, you know a lot of
old restaurants?
- Of course, Ji Hyo.
- This is good.
- Here's the basic rule.
- He's the best.
Hear me out.
(Professor Yang Se Chan tells us
how to find old restaurants.)
If you want to find the oldest
restaurants, here's where you go.
- You should go to Jongno.
- That's right.
And if you fail to find one there,
restaurants nearby have a history
of 50, 60, and 70 years.
- I can't believe you.
- I'm serious.
How many years of history do Jokbal
restaurants in Jangchung-dong have?
- Well, many years I guess.
- 50 years, at least.
And there are hangover soup places
near there in Gwanghwamun.
- They have a history of 60 years.
- How about kalguksu restaurants?
- I think we will definitely win.
- Kalguksu restaurants are old too.
Three meals will be enough for us.
- You're right.
- We'll be done quickly.
Here's a list of restaurants
that we prepared.
Please refer to the list.
- You may call them before you go.
- Okay.
- Let's go find these places first.
- This one looks good.
- Which place?
- Give me a second.
- What's the name?
- Wait.
They serve hangover ramyeon.
This is the one.
- Let's go there.
- Why?
- They have 45 years of history.
- Let's go.
Okay, let's get going.
Gosh, ramyeon restaurant
with 45 years of history.
My goodness.
It's good to have ramyeon
as your first meal.
- I love ramyeon.
- I love it too.
So we're playing a game there and...
- the winner gets to subtract age?
- You're right.
- If they have 35 years of history,
- Yes.
you play a game...
and the winner gets to subtract
his or her age as many as 35.
- I got it.
- But you should be...
- loyal to the team.
- Yes, you're right.
(They have the highest chance to win
since they are the youngest.)
I think we have a high chance
of winning.
I'll show you how loyal
I am to the team.
- It'll end soon.
- I can't wait.
So here's what we're going to do.
When we have meals
at the first restaurant,
I think we should even out our ages.
Like I said, I will subtract
Ji Hyo's age first.
Because Ji Hyo is the oldest.
(Old girl)
Ji Hyo, this is a game.
- I'm not saying you're old.
- But you know what?
You are old, but...
- I'm not trying to dis you.
- He's a little...
- condescending.
- They're the rules.
If you keep being that way,
three of us will team up.
- See?
- I might text Hoshi and Mingyu...
secretly to team up with them.
- Within this team.
- But you don't know my number.
- Who?
- You.
- What are you doing?
- I'm just saying.
You can just give me your number.
- But I don't know your number.
- Come on, Mingyu.
- Hoshi, will you give your number?
- Sure, I will.
- Mingyu?
- I will give it to you right now.
- You can, can't you?
- I'll give it to you now.
- Okay. Let's exchange our numbers.
- I'll give it to you.
- This is how we become friends.
- Sure.
So Min, why...
I need your number.
- Se Chan.
- What?
- Do you like tigers?
I really like tigers.
Thank you.
- Do you like tigers too?
- Hoshi.
I was born
in the Year of the Tiger.
(She uses her Chinese zodiac sign
to win his favor.)
I was born
in the Year of the Tiger.
I have a tiger tattoo on here.
I have a tattoo.
(The two women are so into tigers.)
Okay. We all like tigers.
All right.
- Do you like to eat?
- Yes.
- I love it.
- I'm starving now.
I was talking to Hoshi.
Why are you being so mean
to me, Se Chan?
- No, I'm not.
- Do you really like me?
Hey.
Stop that!
Why would you say that
in front them?
He's being strange these days.
He's trying to avoid me.
- Is he playing hard to get?
- Yes.
Is that because
you have feelings for her?
I guess that's what it is.
We are close friends.
Why are you avoiding me?
- Why is that? Why?
- Why is he avoiding her?
- So Min...
- Ji Hyo, I'll stop making jokes.
- She can't.
- When he's like that...
Hey, that's enough.
You can't say such things
when the kids are around.
Why are you raising your voice?
That makes me raise my voice too.
Do you think I can't do that?
(Se Chan's patriarchal voice
is perfect for the skit.)
If they become a couple,
it will be really shocking.
I'll attend their wedding for sure.
I will throw feces at your wedding.
You will?
Once our age is reduced,
the hierarchy in our team
will change accordingly.
If I get my age deducted,
- Then you'll become younger?
- I'll become younger.
- We become younger just as much.
- Okay.
- Then we will...
- Do you understand?
- You shouldn't feel bad about that.
- Sure.
- Is this it?
- I know this restaurant.
- Let's go.
- I know this place.
It must be delicious.
(What would the first
old restaurant look like?)
It says tear gas ramyeon.
It must be really spicy.
- Tear gas?
- Yes.
It must be very spicy.
Okay. Let's go!
- Okay.
- It must taste good.
(Tear Gas Hangover Ramyeon)
- This is it.
- It says "old restaurant".
It means this place is old.
It's been here since 1972.
- Hello.
Compared to this restaurant,
we're so young.
We are young.
- This place is older than us.
- I know.
(The restaurant was loved
by a lot of student activists.)
(It was like a safe house for them.)
(Its signature menu,
tear gas ramyeon,)
(is spicy and refreshing
with Cheongyang chili,)
(bean sprouts, and clams.)
- Hello.
- Hello. Ma'am.
- Welcome.
How old is this restaurant?
When did you open this restaurant?
This place looks pretty old.
I'm sorry for asking this
all of a sudden.
This restaurant opened
in 1972 or 1973.
- Then...
- And you've been here all along?
So it's been 47, 48 years.
Can we have some ramyeon here?
- What is popular here?
- I didn't recognize you.
I'm Yang Se Chan.
What is the best menu?
What's popular?
- The popular menu?
- Yes.
- It must be ramyeon.
- Hangover ramyeon.
Hangover ramyeon?
- Where should we eat?
- We will have hangover ramyeon.
- We'll take a seat.
- Let's sit here.
I'll sit between the members
of SEVENTEEN.
(The old restaurant in Sinchon
shows the time of 49 years.)
I can tell this is
a traditional place.
This restaurant was here
even before I was born.
Was it 1973?
- In 1973...
- It was even before I was born.
Right.
You're in the first restaurant now.
And you can order only one serving.
- Only 1 serving?
- 1 serving?
- Can't we eat it all together?
- We're done for.
- Only 1 serving?
- 1 serving...
Is your signature menu
hangover ramyeon?
- Yes.
- We will have...
- 1 serving of hangover ramyeon.
- 1 hangover ramyeon.
- Please make it good.
- Please make it big.
The winner gets to eat the food
first, as much as they want.
Good.
- So this is like the loyalty game.
- It's the loyalty game.
- I like that.
- I'll show you...
what loyalty is. I'm serious.
I'll relieve my hangover here.
I can't do this though.
I'm hungry now.
I'm hungry too.
Once you finish one serving,
you can deduct the age of this place
from your team age.
This place is 49 years old.
This mission is called
Rubber Band Game.
The person who gets more
rubber bands on the face...
- in one minute wins the game.
- On the face?
On the face?
This might snap.
It sounds difficult. I'm scared.
- Get ready.
- I'm ready.
(The first player is
the old restaurant expert, Se Chan.)
It's not easy for Se Chan
because of his mouth.
It might bounce off. He did it.
This isn't about time.
Like this.
It hurts.
You're flustered, right?
(The rubber bands are too tight.)
It must hurt.
- It must hurt.
- My gosh.
- It hurts.
- He's got fat under his eyes.
Se Chan.
This is no joke.
This is...
This feels really strange.
You have 12 bands on your face.
Should I keep going?
- It's been 30 seconds.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- You look good.
- Your face...
- No.
- Se Chan, you should stop it.
- It hurts.
(They haven't seen anything
so shocking for the past 49 years.)
My goodness.
(Se Chan's turn is over.)
- Gosh.
- It must hurt a lot.
(It's not easy to get rid
of the rubber bands.)
Hang on. I need to put these down.
Wait.
5 and 6.
How do I look? Do I look good?
- Am I handsome?
- Yes.
- You look like Voldemort.
- What about your chin?
I'm done.
This is good for blood circulation.
Good.
I can feel that
my blood is circulating.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
Ready.
(The second player is Ji Hyo.)
- You have...
- There she goes.
plenty of time anyway.
Does it hurt, Ji Hyo?
It must hurt.
This is tighter than I thought.
I know. It's tight.
- It looks painful.
- You should spread them. Good.
- 15 seconds?
- Yes.
That's the last one.
Ji Hyo. You're being hasty.
Gosh, Ji Hyo. No!
- I want to eat ramyeon.
- Two.
One. Time's up.
- It's done.
- Take them off.
Time's up. Grab the bands.
- You should help her.
- My gosh.
Ji Hyo, why are you trying so hard?
No. Please, Ji Hyo.
I think this is good
for the text neck syndrome.
(They discover the virtues
of rubber bands.)
Ji Hyo's record is 33.
- My gosh.
- The margin is only three.
- Oh, no.
- What's your record?
- It's 30.
- I'm going to eat ramyeon.
She put on 33 bands.
- So Min, get ready.
- If you want to do it...
all at once, you should do it
toward the end.
Should I do it slowly?
You can take your time
for the first 15 pieces.
So Min isn't that pretty.
(Staring sharply at him)
(Se Chan's biting remark
upsets the Rubber Band Frog.)
So Min, you look
like a painting by Picasso.
I've seen a person
who looks just like her.
There's a comedienne
who looks like her.
Stop that.
- I won't let this slide.
- She looks artistic.
I think So Min will win this game.
You have 10 seconds left.
It hurts!
My goodness. This is crazy.
Her eyes look funny.
- 5, 4...
- So Min, stop it. Please.
Two.
- That's it. Take them off.
- Time's up.
It counts.
Help me.
Help me!
My gosh. I thought
my eyes would pop out.
You thought
your eyes would pop out?
(Groaning)
(Rubber Band Frog is wailing
at an old restaurant.)
It hurts.
- It hurts really bad.
- That's true.
It hurts.
Do I have to go this far
to eat ramyeon?
How many?
(Rubber Band Frog is leading
with her record of 36.)
Seriously, my eyes
almost popped out.
I can't do this.
- I think I did it wrong.
- It really hurts.
Did I win first place?
Starting from first place,
you will get rid of your age.
- I'll...
- Are we...
- doing this openly?
- No, you should tell me.
Really?
- I'll...
- Okay, So Min.
Let me tell you one thing.
This isn't the last place.
- This is the beginning.
- I'll show you...
what loyalty is.
I can give you my age here.
Okay. Go ahead.
I'll show you what loyalty is.
- Ji Hyo, trust me.
- Okay.
- Seriously...
- I believe you.
- I'll...
- I wonder what she's like.
- I'm excited, So Min.
- Seriously.
We have 49 years.
- So I'll...
- 30 years?
No. I'll remove only 10 years.
- Are you serious?
- Sure.
(Really?)
What's with So Min?
- Okay.
- Hey.
I can't betray you guys forever.
- It's not...
- This is nice. I like the peace.
Hang on. I can
get rid of a lot of my age then.
- What?
- 30?
Here's 10.
So Min deducted 10 years.
Of course. This is...
Ji Hyo, you're up.
- Deduct as many as you can.
- You have 39 years left.
(The age that's left is 39.)
Okay. I'll deduct 20 years.
If I deduct 20 years,
and if he deducts 10...
Then we have only 19 years left.
Ji Hyo is 20 now.
Then Ji Hyo is
the youngest one here.
I'll be harsh
on the youngest member.
I've warned you.
We've already talked about
the age and hierarchy.
- I'm shaking.
- I'll scold her.
If I don't do this,
I'm 100 percent sure
Se Chan will do it.
I'm sure Se Chan will
use up all the age.
- I'm very positive.
- I won't do that.
So I tried to show you.
You wouldn't believe me.
I want to do this in secret.
Se Chan, it's your turn.
(He's doing it secretly
after talking about loyalty.)
- I know what's going on.
- Even if you do it secretly...
I can tell what's going on.
Hoshi and Mingyu are next.
(The age he can deduct is 19 years.)
He wouldn't do that to SEVENTEEN.
He's just mean to us. Right?
See? Do you hear the sound?
He's busy taking them off.
I'm just counting them.
- See? He's like a rat.
- Hey. You rat.
- I'm done.
- Okay.
I did it with my conscience.
I figured out what to do.
I did this openly on purpose.
- I wasn't supposed to do that.
- You have four years left.
Really?
(Se Chan deducted
15 out of 19 years.)
I did it so you'd believe me.
You should remember
that Hoshi is up next.
(Hoshi's age
depends on Mingyu's choice.)
I'll just do this.
(This is real loyalty.
Mingyu deducted only 1 year.)
(Mingyu is now 23 years old.)
You're the last one, Hoshi.
- You have 3 years left.
- 3 years?
Good.
- This is huge.
- Give us ramyeon.
Give us ramyeon.
He left some.
- Is this the tear gas ramyeon?
- Tear gas ramyeon?
It must be spicy.
So this dish is 49 years old.
- I'll...
- We should know that.
I won first place,
so I'll take mine first.
I don't think Hoshi will need
his own dish.
I'll take some bean sprouts.
And she took some clams.
And kimchi.
Okay. Kimchi.
- I like kimchi.
- It looks good.
I also need some soup.
(She takes some soup
out of the bowl.)
Watch your hands.
Pick this up for me.
- Into your plate?
- No, into the bowl.
I don't eat a lot. It's okay.
- Is that it?
- Here.
Take this.
- What do you mean?
- Eat that.
Take this.
- What do you mean?
- Eat that.
Have that. This is for me.
(I see.)
- Thank you for the food.
- Wait.
Then Ji Hyo should
leave some for us.
- She should share that with you.
- You can share that.
This?
(The other 4 members
will share this together.)
That's cool. She sounds tough.
(Slurping)
Okay. So Min, I'll remember that.
Okay.
But when we eat...
I'm being generous. This is a lot.
- That's a lot.
- Here.
- So is this for us?
- Yes.
(Ramyeon tastes the best when you
take a bite of someone else's.)
- It's good, isn't it?
- I should remove it from the shell.
Ji Hyo, you gave them...
Ji Hyo gave them a lot.
Don't get me wrong. It has meat.
You can suck it out.
Don't get me wrong, okay?
Don't get me wrong.
(Se Chan gave the others
1 clam with a generous heart.)
- It'll come out. Trust me.
- So...
I'm not lying. Eat up.
It'll come out.
- That's it?
- You should give him something.
You have to decide whether to eat
the clam or the bean sprout.
I'm done.
It's really spicy.
I'm going to eat
some of the noodles.
- You'll give him the clam?
- It really is spicy.
I knew it. You're giving him
only the bean, not the stem.
Good. How do you like it? Savor it.
(The rich flavor of the clam
and the crunchy bean sprout!)
I could taste the soup
as I chewed the bean sprout.
- It's crunchy, right?
- Try this.
Taste it.
We followed the rule.
- You have something to eat here.
- Can we have a look?
Hoshi, show it to them. It's yours.
"Share even one piece of bean."
6 of us are sharing 1 bowl
of noodles.
- It's good.
- Indeed.
Even the bean sprout was
seasoned well, right?
I don't think so.
- Ji Hyo is younger than me now.
- She's 20 now.
I'm in my 20s.
Ji Hyo is younger than me now.
I'm the youngest among us now.
- Se Chan. Gosh.
- Yes, Hoshi.
Se Chan, why didn't you leave
more food for us?
I'm sorry.
It happened that way.
I ate only one piece of bean.
I'm sorry. But it's actually
Mingyu's fault.
- You did wrong too, you brat.
- I'm sorry.
You should've left more food for us.
I'll make sure you'll eat
more food next time.
You brat, how dare you?
Slack off at the next game.
Of course, Hoshi.
I'll do as you say.
Ji Hyo, did you enjoy it?
Yes, So Min. It was delicious.
- Ji Hyo, did you enjoy it?
- I really enjoyed it.
- Shut it. We're the same age.
- Are we the same age?
You two are the same age.
Treat me as a same-age friend.
Don't act like you're older than me.
- I didn't do that.
- These two are...
It's because I'm intimidated.
- Let's get going now.
- Let's go.
- We're going to...
(Team Suk Jin with the total age
of 198 is leaving.)
Oh, man. This is unbelievable.
This is the worst combination
for a team.
We're all so old.
Why must we search
for old restaurants?
If we just eat something
at a convenience store,
that store would look so old.
Suk Jin, put on your seatbelt.
(The team of oldest members)
I'm putting on my seatbelt,
you brat.
(The team of oldest members)
Good. The third oldest member
should check it.
- Let's go to this restaurant.
- Why?
B restaurant at Namdaemun Market,
Jung-gu.
It sounds like an old restaurant.
- What food do they serve?
- What kind of food?
- Noodles. If they have bulgogi,
- Oh, noodles?
- they have naengmyeon too.
- They serve naengmyeon.
Pyongyang naengmyeon?
It says
it's a 60-year-old restaurant.
Do you like naengmyeon?
Of course, I like naengmyeon.
I'm a big fan.
You can make the noodles
for naengmyeon, right?
How can I make noodles?
That's what Soo Yong's jokes
are like.
- I know.
- What else?
- Strawberry milk.
- How to make strawberry milk.
Make the cow blush.
(How to make strawberry milk:
Make the cow blush.)
So that you can get strawberry milk.
That's how you make strawberry milk.
Even his jokes are old-fashioned.
- Right.
- That's funny.
I used to make people laugh
with my jokes.
(I used to make people laugh
with my jokes.)
People would laugh so hard
that they couldn't keep it together.
Chang Hee is nice, right?
I haven't had a chance
to get to know him.
Chang Hee is much nicer than you.
(Chang Hee is much nicer than you.)
- That means he's really nice.
- I thought so.
He's really nice.
Soo Yong,
you know what I mean, right?
That means he's really nice.
To survive this long
without the ability to talk funny,
you must have a good personality.
- Chang Hee is nice...
- Chang Hee.
and perfect in every way.
- He's also hard-working.
- I see.
But he lacks the ability
to talk funny.
That's okay.
Chang Hee, let me ask you
a question.
- Sure.
- When Cho Sae Ho became popular,
you got a little jealous
of his success, right?
- I'll be honest with you.
- Tell me honestly.
I didn't feel jealous at all.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I was happy for my friend.
- Of course.
- I never felt jealous.
- There's no way he got jealous...
- Soo Yong.
- because he cut ties with Sae Ho.
(There's no way he got jealous
because he cut ties with Sae Ho.)
- They don't see each other now.
- Gosh, seriously.
- They still see each other.
- I'm going to meet him...
- after the shoot.
- Soo Yong.
Have you ever felt jealous
of Suk Jin's success?
Of course, I'm jealous.
(That's a given.)
(Soo-DRAGON won't hide
how he really feels.)
Why? You're jealous too.
Why would he be?
- Jae Suk, aren't you jealous?
- Why would he be?
(Jae Suk, aren't you jealous
of Suk Jin's success?)
- Why would he be?
- He became more successful than me.
You know he's more successful.
- I bet he's jealous despite that.
- No way.
What he just said was so funny.
When Kim Yong Man was popular,
I didn't watch his shows.
I know.
- Really?
- Yes.
- In the early years of my career,
- Yes?
although Soo Yong and I debuted
in the same year...
- You didn't watch his shows, right?
- No, I didn't.
- Of course.
- It because I was upset.
- It's not that I was jealous.
- You wanted to be on TV too.
I was just upset and afraid
I might want to be on the show too.
I understand.
- I didn't want to feel that way.
- You see, Jae Suk would...
If it had not been for "Talk Box"...
If it had not been for that show,
Jae Suk would be running
a business now.
(Jae Suk would be running
a business now.)
It's because he was cast on the show
when his career was precarious.
- It was... It's the same for me.
- That's true.
- I haven't come here in a while.
- Namdaemun Market.
I used to come here often
to buy stage outfits.
You shopped here too, right?
When we were younger,
we didn't work with stylists.
I used to come here
with other comedians...
- That's right.
- to buy a suit.
I haven't been here for a long time.
These stores must have been here
for almost 50 years.
- It's nice.
- We could complete the mission...
- in this area.
- Absolutely.
If we visit
a few restaurants here...
- "B" restaurant. We're here.
- This is it.
- Such places are hidden like this.
- Let's go.
I can see the history
of the restaurant.
(It's a popular Pyongyang naengmyeon
restaurant at Namdaemun Market.)
(The wall is covered
with the traces of years.)
(The vendors have been quenching
their hunger here for a long time.)
My, it's nice.
That bindaetteok looks so delicious.
(Crispy bindaetteok is a bonus!)
They've been running this restaurant
here for 60 years?
- Sanitize your hands, everyone.
- Okay.
Let's eat something.
- You're here now.
- Yes.
- But we did some research.
Three generations have been running
this restaurant...
- for 60 years,
- Yes.
but they registered the business
in 1984.
So it's 37 years old.
- Gosh. That's ridiculous.
- You can't do that.
They've been running this place
for 60 years. Then why...
But we don't have any evidence
to prove it.
They've been running the restaurant
with the same name for 60 years.
- Excuse me.
We heard this is a 60-year-old
restaurant. Is it true?
It's 60 years old, right?
In what year
did you open this restaurant?
(Please tell us it's been 60 years.)
My grandmother-in-law started
the business...
around the time when Korea
was liberated from Japan.
- See? It's been 60 years.
- Back then...
You can prove it, right?
- It's a family business.
- Exactly.
- Then we...
- It's as old as Namdaemun Market.
- Exactly.
- That's what I'm saying.
Then to be fair,
we'll meet you halfway.
- Oh, yes.
- That sounds fair.
- Oh, I see.
- Then 48 years...
- It has a 23-year gap, so...
- We'll settle for 48 years.
- 48 years.
- All right.
If you look at the owner's watch...
- Her watch is from "R" brand.
- Why would you say that?
- That wasn't necessary.
- I'm surprised.
You could've put it this way.
We can tell how successful...
- this restaurant has been...
- Yes.
- only by looking at the owner.
- Exactly.
You can tell how tasty their food is
to attract a lot of customers.
All your children
studied overseas, right?
- What?
- That's what they usually do.
Why would you ask
if her children studied overseas?
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- We'll order food later. Thank you.
- Okay.
You can deduct 48 years
from your ages.
We'll begin the game
to decide the order.
It's Age Based on Physical Ability.
You will take a three-step
biological age test.
I'm not good at things like that.
I don't have a flexible body.
You'll be ranked in the order of
your biological ages.
I'm not good at things like this
because I'm not flexible.
- Same here.
- My body is not flexible at all.
- I can't do things like this.
- Let's begin the first step.
- Oh, gosh.
- Tell them how to do it.
If your elbows are above your eyes
like this,
- you're in your 20s.
- That's too hard for me.
30s up to your nose,
40s up to your lips,
and 50s if your face is invisible.
- If my face is invisible?
- Take turns to try it.
- You don't get to practice.
- Jae Suk.
- Shall I go first?
- Okay.
My body is not very flexible.
- Doing this alone is hard for me.
- Exactly.
Gosh, I can't do it.
- Hey, that's it?
- His arms are apart.
- His arms are apart. Look at that.
(His arms are shaking,
and his face is not visible.)
- I couldn't see his face.
- I can't do this.
- He failed.
- You're in your 50s.
- I'll aim to be in my 40s.
(I think I have a chance to win.)
Okay. I'll aim to be in my 40s.
- Gosh, seriously.
- I'm keeping my arms together.
- Right?
- Yes.
(What could be the biological age
of the confident Suk Jin?)
(Struggling)
I think his biological age
is over 70.
(He can't do any better
than Jae Suk.)
(His arms went up 3cm
and stopped.)
(Laughing)
(I'll get to eat naengmyeon.)
Your arms are apart.
(His biological age is over 70.)
(But he's still a teenager
at heart.)
- He can't lift his arms at all.
- I can't do it.
- You're in your 50s.
- It's because I'm not flexible.
It's a piece of cake.
- Easy-peasy.
- Yes, indeed.
- You try it.
- You can just show your chin.
- Exactly.
- Try it.
Your lips are visible for now.
His lips are visible?
Your nose is almost visible.
- It's hard.
- I think that's the best he can do.
- The lips.
- Over 40?
- Yes, he's over 40.
- Gosh.
- It's Chang Hee's turn.
- All right.
Nam Chang Hee
- I am Nam Chang Hee
- All right.
(Shaking)
What's wrong with him?
His biological age is over 60.
- Wait. Just a little higher.
- Hey.
You're in your 50s.
- My gosh.
- Chang Hee.
I'm disappointed.
I thought you were quite flexible.
I can move fast,
but my body is not flexible.
- You can move fast?
- Yes, I'm fast.
- His biological age is over 50?
- You're over 50, 50, 40, and 50.
- It was the first step.
- My gosh.
- I can't do it.
- Let's move on.
- You came in first.
- Let's begin the second step.
- Why are my arms shaking?
- It's jump rope with your arms.
- I can't do that.
- What?
- I see.
With your hands locked
in front of your body,
you have to pass them
under your legs and hips.
Pass them under my legs?
If you fail at your feet, you're
over 50, at your legs, over 40,
at your hips, over 30,
and if you succeed, you're over 20.
Some of us have a chronic disease.
- I have back problems.
- I was born...
- to be inflexible.
- That's ridiculous.
I couldn't do things like this
even when I was a teenager.
I couldn't do it when I was
in the military either.
- We're not flexible.
- Can we do something else?
They're complaining a lot
because they're quite old.
It's not like that.
- Listen to me.
- Why won't you stop complaining?
- Just do it.
- Fine. Let's begin.
And then legs...
(The youngest Chang Hee goes first.)
Could he pass it under his leg?
What happens if he succeeds?
He's made it to the age group
between 40 and 49.
(His feet went over his arms.)
- He stopped at his hips.
- That's it.
- Can't you pass the hips?
- Gosh, I can't do it.
- You're in your 30s.
- I'm in my 30s.
- It's your actual age.
- Yes, it's my actual age.
I'm in my 30s.
This is how it's done.
If you can't pass your knees...
- If you...
- What is he doing?
What is he doing?
Suk Jin, what's this?
- Put them up!
- I'm trying to make them flexible.
- That's an old-fashioned way.
- Okay.
- I'll give it a try.
- I can only pass one leg.
(One foot easily goes through.)
- Okay.
- A foot is out.
You seem flexible enough.
(If the other foot goes through,
he'll at least be in his 40s.)
Your hands must stay clasped.
(Why can't you step over the hands
that are in front of you?)
It's like watching a baby
walk for the first time.
(With silly movements,
he falls to the floor.)
It can't be done.
Your biological age is in its 50s.
- You try it.
- Unbelievable.
But this...
- My two legs...
- Just you wait and see.
I may be stiff and have a sore back,
- but both legs will go through.
- Gosh, this is...
Since you're on the older side...
- Your foot grazed your hands.
- Hold on a second.
- See?
- You can't do it either.
- He can't do it.
- No way.
Jae Suk, seriously?
What...
(He was confident
up until a minute ago.)
- He can't do it either.
- I should be able to do this.
- He can't do it.
- No way.
Jae Suk, seriously?
- You can't...
- You worked out for nothing!
My gosh.
(He ends up
destroying the property.)
Your biological age is in its 40s.
- This isn't accurate though.
- I'm quite stiff.
- This is about being flexible.
- I'm not flexible at all.
But that adds
to your biological age.
- One must be flexible for this.
- That's true,
- but it's not crucial.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Hold on.
Is Yogi Daniels in his teens then?
- Yogi Daniels.
- Who's that?
He's over 60, you know.
- This is ridiculous.
- Yogi Daniels can do this.
I told you that I'm not flexible.
(His mental age
is probably still in its teens.)
Do I put my leg through?
(Last up is Soo-DRAGON.)
Both legs must go through.
- Like this?
- He'll probably manage both legs.
I guess he can't.
Seriously?
- Hey. Can't you do it?
- In some ways,
this isn't all that bad.
They're all just as bad.
- This is a mess.
- There isn't much of a difference.
In sports events,
there's the group of death.
Meanwhile, this is paradise.
I'm in paradise.
Next, you will hold
the V-sit for 10 seconds.
- Sit with your arms out front.
- Okay.
- Lift your two legs.
- This I can do.
Come on.
See? Look!
- No way. That's not it.
- Let's check our sugar levels.
Or our blood pressure.
- Blood pressure...
- Must we go that far?
You'll shed years off your age
starting with whoever came first.
Soo Yong, you're up.
You won the game,
so take at least 15 years.
You're on the older side,
so you need to shed a lot of it.
Hold on. Soo Yong?
(Nothing can be heard except
the sound of the Velcro tape.)
I hear a ripping sound.
- I know.
- Soo Yong...
Do I rip off at least 12?
6, 7, 8...
You're still only at eight?
It's all right.
What's taking you so long?
- How many are you ripping off?
- 12.
- Just 12?
What took you so long though?
- It's not easy.
- It seemed like more.
- Am I next?
- I only discarded 12.
- I'll tell you how much is left.
- Sure.
I ripped off 12.
(Soo Yong shed 35 years off
a total of 48.)
- I ripped off 12.
- Are you kidding me?
- How sly of you.
- Why?
I'll shed off the amount I promised.
- You know how much.
- 12 years?
You've got to be kidding me.
You're 20 now.
- Not even Kwang Soo would do this.
- Exactly.
The food's here.
Thank you.
In the order
you finished the game in,
you'll take as much food
as you want.
Take as much as you want
with your spoon.
- I mean, with your chopsticks.
- Sure.
- Pass me the vinegar.
- I'm dying to try some.
(Soo Yong is up first.)
I'll only take a quarter.
That's considerate of you.
But it's not much.
- That's a quarter.
- You only get one turn.
Sure.
That's kind of you.
This isn't something you see
on Running Man every day.
(Jae Suk is next.)
- Hey.
- What?
Be considerate.
(A heap)
Soo Yong should've eaten more.
(This is what we
normally see on Running Man.)
- Take a heap.
- Can one scrape the edge?
(He uses a ladle
to secure his noodles.)
- There you go.
- Okay.
Get some of the broth too.
That I can give him.
(Here you go.)
Do you know why
he's being generous?
He doesn't favor
Pyongyang naengmyeon.
Unbelievable.
- I thought he was being kind.
- You probably did.
He's not that kind of guy.
Let's try the broth.
(Jae Suk is a well-known
noodle lover.)
(Thanks to him,
the naengmyeon seems delicious.)
(Meanwhile, Soo Yong is known
to make food seem unappealing.)
(Just so you know,
this is him enjoying the food.)
(Then there's Suk Jin who doesn't
like Pyongyang naengmyeon.)
I can smell the beef broth.
(Then there's Suk Jin who doesn't
like Pyongyang naengmyeon.)
This is delicious.
I'd like some bindaetteok.
(I'd like some bindaetteok.)
- Don't order him any.
- Of course not.
You need to choose
your next destination.
- We...
- Yes?
- We had noodles.
- Since we had noodles,
we should get some meat.
Let's eat a meat dish.
- Pork galbi takes long to cook.
- That sounds good.
- It takes long to cook.
- What do you say?
- Hangover soups.
- How about a hangover soup?
What about this C restaurant?
That's the one...
where people from
the Kim Du Han era used to eat.
- Then it's been around for long.
- The C restaurant...
- opened in 1937.
- See?
- That's the one.
- Let's go there next.
- Since 1937.
- Just so you know,
- it's nearby.
- That's right.
(They call the restaurant first.)
Hello, this is Restaurant C.
Hello, it's a pleasure.
- Sure.
- You see,
we're filming Running Man,
- and I'm Ji Suk Jin.
- Yes, hello.
- Why would he introduce himself?
- She's not excited though.
- Could we perhaps...
film there for a short while
while we eat?
- At this hour?
- Yes.
Let me ask my boss first.
Can you leave your phone number?
My number...
(Failing to ask
the proper questions...)
(leads him to revealing
his own phone number.)
- Just a second.
- Say you'll call back in 10.
I'll call you back in five minutes.
- Sure, in five minutes.
- Got it.
(The minute-long call
was fruitless.)
Are you kidding me?
Who calls a restaurant like that?
- I got to the point, didn't I?
- But...
- That's not...
- I got to the point.
You should've asked
when the restaurant opened first.
- We already know that.
- Ask what dishes they sell.
Also, why...
- would you reveal your identity?
- We'll have boiled pork slices.
Suk Jin identified himself,
but she wasn't that excited
to hear from him.
- She didn't seem pleased.
- She was only being polite.
That's what it was.
I see you don't know.
- "I'm Ji Suk Jin..."
- I'm sure she danced in joy.
She danced in joy?
She must have.
She sounded calm,
but she was dancing with joy.
Suk Jin's hilarious.
It's seolleongtang,
so how can it not taste good?
- It's seolleongtang, right?
- No, hangover soup.
- It's the same.
- With intestines.
- They have it all.
- Seolleongtang?
- Right.
- Then we're good.
- Suk Jin can't eat those dishes.
- What?
He can't eat intestine soup.
- I can't eat clotted blood.
- What a picky eater.
- Suk Jin...
- He...
- He was raised like a prince.
- He's the worst.
- He never ate these things.
- Did I have to be on this team?
- Suk Jin.
- Clotted blood...
It's too disgusting.
Doesn't Restaurant C...
have a kid's meal?
He can have the kid's meal instead.
Or we could order from
another restaurant.
- We'll have it delivered.
- He's the worst.
We'll have assorted
boiled pork slices.
- Sure, let's get searching.
- Think about...
- what we mentioned earlier.
- That's right.
We can find many old restaurants
in Jongno and Myeong-dong.
- Myeong-dong and Jongno.
- Right.
Ever since the Kim Du Han days...
Type in "50 years",
and you'll get a whole list.
Toegye-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul.
Guys, Restaurant M...
- has been open for 50 years.
- See?
- Let's go.
- Let's go there.
- It opened in 1966.
- That's right.
The food there is delicious.
- I love this place.
- Let's go.
So right now, Namjoo is...
- I'm 26.
- Right, 26.
So let's all match her age first.
Must we do it this way though?
- Match what?
- You're being selfish already.
Why should we match our ages first?
You'll only betray us later.
- Why would we betray you?
- Earlier,
as soon as he heard the rules,
he told Jong Kook his idea
while grinning.
- That's what I hate the most.
- That's not the case.
What's the main rule anyway?
- I still don't get the game.
- Me neither.
- All I want to do is eat.
- Guys.
Okay, then. How about this?
- We'll match ours to Kwang Soo's.
- Okay, that sounds good.
Is that okay with you two?
Why do we need
to level our ages though?
Because...
- We don't know the rules.
- Too much of an age gap...
The oldest two
will receive the penalty.
- I see.
- The oldest two.
I'm sorry to say this,
but we've repeated this
way too many times.
- We'll explain it one last time.
- Let me explain.
As you know, we...
- First...
- The restaurant's 55 years old.
Minus nine years,
and I'll be Kwang Soo's age.
- What about you?
- In my case...
- We're 6 years apart.
- Yes, 6.
- That's what you'll shed.
- I have an idea.
Spare us 15 years from 55 first.
That'll level our age
with Kwang Soo's.
Then we'll have 30 years
to share among us.
- We'll share the 30 years.
- Then we'll divide it evenly.
- You two will be safe.
- Only in the first round.
- Only at first?
- We won't challenge you yet.
Let us match Kwang Soo's age first.
- Sure thing.
- Are we good?
- Then 15 years each...
- Yes.
No, not each.
Just 15 years in total.
(Jong Kook's lecture
was all for nothing.)
Let us take just 15 years
in the first round.
We'll match our age
only to Kwang Soo's.
As you know, I like to play fair.
I play fair too when I need to be.
- He...
- I play fair until I'm provoked.
- We'll match ours with Kwang Soo's.
- That will come to bite you.
- Just with Kwang Soo.
- You know how he is.
A weasel like him
makes us all suffer a loss.
- Shedding 11 years each is fair.
- We need to...
level our age with Kwang Soo's.
What do you mean by
shedding 11 years?
The restaurant has been around
for 55 years.
- And there are 5 of us.
- 11 years, 11 years...
- I get it now.
- Hold on a second.
The girls are absolutely clueless.
I'm pretty sure that...
siding with you today
won't benefit me at all.
Just don't do anything, all right?
No matter how much we explain it,
we can't get through to them.
- I get it now.
- You need to understand this.
- I get it now too.
- Just eat whatever is served.
That means we need to compete
against each other.
- That's right.
- 11 years, 11 years...
- I get it now.
- If you can be kind enough to...
Are you still calculating the years?
So 11 years each.
- What...
- No, not 11 years each.
I'm sorry, but can we
stop talking for a second?
I'm getting woozy.
- I want you to trust us.
- I'm curious though.
Why are we even in teams?
- What?
- This isn't some competition.
- It's a single player game.
- How are we competing right now?
We're trying to make sure
the team wins.
- This is just our strategy.
- All right, then.
If we're in it to win it,
please explain the rules
clearly to me one last time.
(Another explanation?)
You've got to be kidding me.
Are you serious?
She really is clueless.
Just eat the food
that's presented to you...
and receive the penalty at the end.
This isn't complicated,
but she just doesn't get it.
Why are you trying...
- to shed years off your age?
- Okay, listen up.
- Why shed the years?
- So our team members...
- have a collective age of 177.
- Unbelievable.
Bomi, why did you come here?
- Do you know this is Running Man?
- To eat.
- She's just pretending.
- I'll explain to you.
- There?
- Deduct 65 years...
(He explained the game rule
only for Bomi for a while.)
You mean, the age badges,
not my actual age?
That's correct.
- It's your actual age.
- But if you don't deduct...
- That's what I said.
(Complaining abnormal symptoms)
I've become claustrophobic.
(He passed out.)
- I'm serious.
- Bomi, seriously.
I bet Bomi is still trying to
figure it out.
- No. I understand the rule now.
- But actually...
I haven't been here in a long time.
- We should put on a mask now.
- Okay.
I haven't come to Myeong-dong
in a really long time.
(Each of them has memories
of Myeong-dong.)
- We're here.
- This is it.
- All right.
- Oh, my.
(Opened in 1966)
(This is a popular kalguksu
and dumpling restaurant.)
(Many tourists also visit the place
as it's located in Myeong-dong.)
It smells so good. I'm excited.
Oh, my.
It looks so delicious.
- Was there a place like this here?
- Hello.
It was easy to find.
Where should we sit?
- You arrived at your first place.
- Yes.
- I'm so excited to eat here.
- This restaurant is very famous.
They opened up another location
in Los Angeles too.
- What's most shocking is...
- Really?
It's also one of the good things
about this restaurant.
You can eat
as much rice as you want.
- It's free.
- That's great.
- Am I right, sir?
- I love rice.
- It's great.
- Only when you order noodles.
- I see. We should order noodles.
- Yes.
I wasn't saying that we'll only eat
free rice here.
- We wouldn't do that.
- We won't just ask for free rice.
Of course, we'll order food.
- We're not that kind of people.
- Why would we do that?
Could you tell us
about the history of the restaurant?
- It was established in 1966.
- In 1966?
(It's a 55-year-old restaurant.
It was established in 1966.)
- Suk Jin was born in that year.
- Exactly.
- It's the same age as Suk Jin.
- That's right.
- In 1966?
- Yes.
You don't know what month it was,
right? I bet Suk Jin is older.
- He was born in February.
- In the beginning of the year.
- When you finish eating here,
- Yes.
you can deduct 55 years,
the age of this place,
- from your ages.
- Okay.
But it's so unfair.
Is being old a sin?
Of course, it's not.
Then why would you come up with
a rule like this?
The idea alone can...
- make older people...
- Must Suk Jin die then?
It can make older people upset.
- I mean, is being old a sin?
- It's okay.
Do you think you will never
be my age?
That's why we're giving you a chance
to get your age deducted.
- What I'm saying is...
- I know.
that the members of our team...
- reached an agreement.
- Haha.
You sound so bossy right now.
- The tone of his voice...
- I am talking right now!
- It's not like that.
- He sounds even bossier than me.
What's with you?
What has gotten into you?
- We'll get 25 years.
- Doesn't his hat look like...
- a traditional hat called gamtu?
- And we'll divide...
the remaining 30 years.
The remaining 30 years.
- What happened to him?
- I can't believe him.
He's so bossy.
He's much bossier than me.
He used to have a young mind.
- We'll let you make that decision.
- Okay.
Then I have no problem.
Wait. What was the rule?
1, 2, 3, and 4.
- No dividing by the same number.
- Correct.
For example, 2, 4, and 8. Or...
Bomi, I think you're explaining it
because you're embarrassed.
No, that's not the reason.
All right. I'll explain...
about the game you'll play.
You'll play the same game
you played on Jeju Island...
and gained the worst result.
It's Half Proverb Quiz.
- It was really difficult.
- Proverb?
We'll tell you the latter part
of the proverb.
You have to complete the sentence
in three seconds.
(They succeed if they complete
the given sentence.)
- This never has a peaceful day.
- That's easy.
- What...
- It's easy.
My family never has a peaceful day.
- Hey.
- What's the answer?
(Even the smart members were
humiliated playing the game.)
- I don't know many proverbs.
- But...
It was difficult.
(It was difficult.)
- I don't know many proverbs.
- But I think I have a chance.
He's right. We have a chance to win.
- The smart ones are not here.
- I think...
- I can beat them.
- We have a chance to win.
- I don't know many proverbs.
- I'm begging you...
- Bomi and Namjoo should go first.
- I don't know any proverbs.
Proverbs...
- Kwang Soo should go first.
- Okay.
- No.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- I don't agree...
- The winner gets to eat, right?
The winner gets to eat food...
- and gets the age...
- Get the age deducted?
Bomi, come on. Please.
I'm done for.
Give me the question.
- Bomi,
- Bomi.
- we'll begin now.
- Okay.
Move to Gangnam.
- 3, 2...
- I move to Gangnam.
(I move to Gangnam.)
One.
(It sounds like declaration.)
- That was good. Next.
- My gosh.
- Gosh. I really don't know.
- That was good.
(Following a friend,
you move to Gangnam.)
This never has a peaceful day.
- Three.
- Well...
- Two.
- I never have a peaceful day.
(I never have a peaceful day.)
Her answer always starts with "I".
- I'm worried. I can't just laugh.
- Kwang Soo, why...
Let's move on. Keep going.
But you don't know
how giyeok looks.
- You look at a sickle.
- Correct.
(She finally got a question right.)
You stay up all night.
- Well...
- During the exam period.
During the exam period,
you stay up all night.
(She took the bait right away.)
- Frying beans.
- "Frying beans"?
- Using cooking oil.
- Two.
"Frying beans"?
(You should use cooking oil
when you fry beans.)
- Beans?
- One.
- You eat and fry beans?
- Wrong.
"You eat and fry beans"?
- I'm relieved that she's here.
- Frying beans with lightning?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Okay.
(He's holding back his laugh
as Bomi seems so enthusiastic.)
It's so difficult
because we hear only the half.
It's confusing.
- It's hard to guess the front half.
- Exactly.
But she did a good job.
- It's difficult.
- Is it Jong Kook's turn?
- Me?
- Yes.
Give me some easy questions.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
And pull yourself together. Three.
- Empty your stomach?
- Two.
(Empty your stomach
and pull yourself together?)
- One.
- Jong Kook.
Are you serious?
I mean...
You won't be the worst.
- 3, 2...
- If you don't say anything.
- Correct.
- What?
The taste of the sauce.
- 3, 2...
- What? The taste of the sauce...
- One.
- The longer you store the sauce...
- Wrong.
- The jar isn't better than...
You break your nose.
- 3, 2...
- Even when you fall backward.
- Even when you...
- There's more.
- 3, 2...
- What did you say?
- One. You failed.
- Isn't that correct?
- A rock.
- "If you're unlucky."
- That's the missing part.
- Oh, right.
- You unlucky punk.
- What?
- That's the missing part.
- Oh, right.
(He used the proverb
that he learned right away.)
- You said the proverb, right?
- Don't act like you knew it.
- That's it?
- Yes.
- How many did he get right?
- Two.
- 2 questions.
- I'm relieved that I got 2 right.
We should stop him.
Haha, you're up.
You knock on the window.
- 3, 2...
- When you're desperate.
(While sleeping,
you knock on the window.)
Wrong.
You can't find any.
When you need medicine as poop...
When you need poop as medicine.
(When you need medicine as poop,
you can't find any?)
- What do you mean by that?
- Darn it.
(Bomi who got 1 question right
turns out to be the ace.)
That's hilarious.
Let's move on.
This is impossible
even for a king.
- 3, 2...
- "Even for a king"?
- Running Man games...
- One.
(Solving poverty is impossible
even for a king.)
(Games on Running Man are
impossible even for a king.)
Next.
With a horseshoe.
3, 2...
The one who feels at ease.
- What's horseshoe?
- I don't what horseshoe is.
- And no man is below others.
- Three.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Two.
Why are you doing this to me?
You never did it before.
Under the sky...
- No man is above others.
- Oh, right.
And no man is below others.
- They were too difficult.
- I think...
- They were difficult.
- The ones in the beginning weren't.
- Those two questions were easy.
- They don't suit me.
Don't mind him.
- The one with "poop" suits you.
- Indeed.
It suits you well.
- I'll announce the result.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo came in first.
- Yes.
- Jong Kook is in second place.
- All right.
Namjoo is in 3rd place,
and Bomi is in 4th place.
Haha is in bottom place.
Haha, thank you.
We'll deduct 15 years
as we planned before, right?
About that...
We should try following the rule
to figure it out.
- Just wait for now.
- You're in bottom place.
- Why did you change your mind?
- You thought that too, right?
- It's not like that.
- I love this about him.
- Am I right?
- I really like this about him.
- Deducting 15 years...
- We should follow the rule.
is against the rule.
But they said we could do that.
It's against the rule.
Who are you, mister?
We're not allowed to do that.
He said that we can do that
if we all agree.
Before the food is out,
you can take off as many badges
as you want...
out of 55 years that you gained...
and give the badges to us.
Let's do as we agreed, okay?
(Kwang Soo will go first
as he's the winner.)
- Shall I step forward?
- They shouldn't...
You should submit the badges
without letting us know.
- Hey. He took off a lot of them.
- I mean...
(He already took off
a lot of badges.)
- I should deduct a few years.
- How many did he take off?
Just a few. I took off only four.
- How many will you take off?
- Not many.
- How many?
- You shouldn't have let him.
How many years will you deduct
from your age, Kwang Soo?
- Don't take off too many.
- Okay.
- You punk!
- He's taking off so many.
How many badges is he taking off?
I think he'll take off
all his badges.
Kwang Soo, don't take off
too many.
Gosh. I can't believe Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
- He's so mean.
(The staff member is trying to
calm him down for a while.)
(The staff members are stopping him
as he won't stop.)
- Stop it.
- Kwang Soo, my gosh.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Deduct 36 years...
The staff members are
trying to stop you, you punk!
Hey.
Kwang Soo, stop it.
It won't be funny if you do that.
Fine. Deduct all the years you need
and get out.
- You can't do it in the beginning.
- Just leave.
I think there will be some years
left at least for me.
Jong Kook, come forward.
You know me, right?
I'm not that kind of person.
I'm a reasonable person.
I'll tell you how many years
he deducted.
Exactly. I need to know that.
- I'll decide based on that.
- I didn't take off many.
- You'll get to deduct some years.
- Really?
He submitted 30 badges.
My gosh. He's a crazy punk.
He took off all the badges he had?
Hold on a second.
You shouldn't have given him
a chance to do that.
I'm shocked.
- You still have enough years.
- He must've lost his mind.
Then... My gosh.
He must be out of his mind.
Then I will...
- So we have 25 years left?
- Yes.
Then I'll take off 20 badges.
(Jong Kook is taking off 20 badges?)
(Jong Kook has finally changed.)
(The icon of trust Jong Kook
is no longer the oldest member.)
Okay. Done.
My gosh. I can't believe this.
I guess there's no year left.
- Why? How many do you have left?
- Gosh, seriously.
How many?
Tell no one else but me,
and I'll tell you.
Can I redeem myself?
(After much thought,
Namjoo submitted age badges.)
I was considerate of you two.
- How many do we have left?
- Really.
I shouldn't expect much.
- Your team gained 55 years.
- Yes.
But the members before you
deducted 54 years in total.
(We have only 1 year left?)
- What?
- That's not the reason.
- You became...
- Do you think it was me?
- You became a pirate.
(Bomi also submitted something.)
But you...
You left me no choice...
because you deducted...
One of them went too far.
- How many do we have left?
- He's like a pirate.
You have none left.
How can we have none left?
I guess they took off
all the badges they had.
- The last person...
- The bottom place has none.
has a low chance of
getting the age deducted.
All other members turned in
different numbers of age badges.
(Haha became the oldest member.)
- Okay.
- Are those leather?
- Are you wearing leather pants?
- What is up with your pants?
What about my pants?
Look at you.
That hat looks like
a traditional hat, doesn't it?
We might be the oldest ones.
- Are you satisfied with the result?
- I am totally satisfied.
I wouldn't say I am satisfied
by 100 percent, but...
All right.
You suddenly became a preschooler.
Can he even walk at his age?
Would it be okay
if I go and change my diaper?
It happened so suddenly.
- It's not that bad.
- It happened in the first round.
Shouldn't he eat baby food?
We will serve food.
- Okay.
- It must be delicious.
- This is it.
- We got one serving.
This is it.
Would it be okay if I eat this much?
- Of course.
- Okay.
I will take two dumplings.
All right. I followed my conscience.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food.
This restaurant has been around
for 55 years.
I vouch for this restaurant.
(They exclaim
as soon as they taste the food.)
You must eat this kimchi.
(The dish is perfect...)
(with the dumplings and kimchi.)
Look up restaurants
with 100 years of history.
(They need to find
the next restaurant.)
Jong Kook.
Pyongyangmyeonok.
It's the perfect restaurant
to visit next.
- It will be delicious.
- Let's go.
- We can go to Hadongkwan next.
- Yes.
- Then we will be done.
Then it will be a happy ending.
- We won't need to fight.
- Exactly.
- Okay.
- Then we will be done.
We will be done.
Let's clap the slate.
1, 2, 3.
(The shoot at the first restaurant
ends.)
(Jong Kook heads somewhere.)
The staff members will move first.
(He approaches the trunk.)
(He takes something out.)
Hold on. Where do I do this?
- Where do I do this?
- You need to find a spot and do it.
- Do I need to do it in secret?
- Yes.
Really?
(Does he need to do something
in secret?)
(He stealthily moves
to the back of the car.)
(Is that a die?)
All right.
How many age badges
do you have left?
I can't show them.
We will find out soon.
I wish I could show you.
(Running Man's hidden mission)
How many age badges did you remove?
A lot?
I didn't remove that many.
(Did the oldest member in the team
get a hidden mission?)
(Every 2 hours, the oldest member
in each team gets a hidden mission!)
(2 dice are hidden at the set
at all times!)
(The white die reduces your age...)
(and the red die reduces a selected
member's age in another team.)
(However, the location of the dice
changes every 2 hours.)
(The oldest members were informed
of the hidden mission.)
(Jong Kook was aiming
for his chance to do the mission.)
(He finally got his chance
to complete the hidden mission.)
I will roll it.
(He rolls the white die
to reduce his age first!)
(3 years are deducted
from Jong Kook's age.)
(3 years are also deducted
from a member of another team.)
- What is that?
- What?
- It's nothing.
(Kwang Soo comes out of nowhere
and catches him in the act.)
What are those?
I found them in the trunk.
(Hitting)
(Kwang Soo resorts to violence.)
What are those?
- What are those?
- I found them in the trunk.
(He gets cornered
for his suspicious behavior.)
You suddenly found dice
in the trunk...
- and threw them.
- I did it without any thoughts.
- Let me try it.
- What?
- Let me throw them.
- It isn't something you can do.
I just...
Is this your secret space?
No, it isn't.
Haha, that's not how you do it.
- Let me try it too.
- I mean...
That's not how you do it.
- What are these?
- Nothing.
1, 2, 3.
(He rolls the die
without knowing anything.)
Six.
Let's go.
(Kwang Soo tries to figure out
the situation.)
- Did you roll it?
- Did I get anything?
(He steals the dice.)
Is this a game center or what?
Why are you doing this?
(He rolls the dice.)
6. 6.
What is this? Is it a mission?
Is it a mission?
Do you know what you are doing?
- No.
- Then why are you doing it?
Will you deduct seven years
from my age?
- What?
- Will you deduct seven years?
- No.
- Is it a mission?
Why did you roll the dice?
I was bored, okay?
(He angrily throws the dice.)
(I am so annoyed.)
(This clueless gambler is annoyed.)
What is this?
Let's hit the road.
Is it really nothing?
(He used his energy
without any gain.)
I think it's a mission
only Haha and Jong Kook received.
I didn't receive a mission.
I just copied Jong Kook.
Why did you roll the dice,
Kwang Soo?
Dice?
- Why did you do it?
- I followed him.
It seemed like a mission.
Haha, why did you roll the dice?
I just followed Jong Kook.
Wasn't it your mission?
- Did you do it without a clue?
- Yes.
(Haha copied Jong Kook
and Kwang Soo copied Haha.)
All right. You rolled the dice.
Jong Kook, which member
will you choose?
- What?
- A member from another team, right?
Yes.
I will choose Se Chan.
Okay.
- Tell us what that was about!
- Why won't you tell us anything?
We feel left out.
It doesn't affect you.
Like I told you earlier...
Did you receive a mission?
Haha and Kwang Soo simply played
with the dice.
Why do you keep saying that?
(The dice will be hidden
at a different location now.)
- Jong Kook, as for you,
- Okay.
your result will be reflected.
(Meanwhile, in Team Ji Hyo's car)
(He receives a text about
a deduction in his age.)
(3 years have been deducted
from Jong Kook and Se Chan's ages.)
(He gets a benefit
without knowing what's going on.)
Did you eat a lot?
I drank some soup.
By the way, So Min,
(By the way, So Min...)
act your age.
Okay? When you are in your mid-20s,
you shouldn't keep food
from the younger members.
Hey, I am older than you.
I am 25 years old.
I know that, but
you shouldn't tell me what to do.
Listen.
Don't stretch out the last syllable.
I don't like it.
- Keep it short.
- Okay.
(Okay.)
(He is
as childish as a preschooler.)
I will keep it short!
Shall I talk like this?
Shall I talk faster?
(He annoys me so much.)
What am I going to do with him?
Call me when you come to Yongsan.
I will buy you a meal.
Okay.
But I don't know your number.
I will give you my number.
- Tell her you will memorize it.
- Just ask.
Don't be ridiculous.
Stop being jealous!
- I am not being jealous!
- For goodness' sake.
It would be nice if he tells you
he will memorize it.
He gets so greedy about
something he won't have.
I am not being greedy!
She is ridiculous.
What time is it now?
It's 12:30 p.m., right?
- If it's 12:30 p.m...
- We need to move fast.
We should hit the road again
by 1:30 p.m.
- At this restaurant,
- We don't have much time.
we really need to move fast.
Otherwise, we will lose.
(Team Suk Jin is close
to the second restaurant)
It wasn't enough food
to fill my stomach.
(Suk Jin complains
because he is hungry.)
This is ridiculous.
Suk Jin has a lot of complaints.
I am still hungry.
Suk Jin's complaints are never big.
They are always small.
I will eat more.
- I will eat more.
- Fathers are like that.
But you should know...
that Suk Jin never goes against...
the production crew's wishes.
He does everything.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Yes.
"Why are you making me do this?"
"This is ridiculous."
When he gets the cue,
he does it without fail.
(He becomes a professional
when the camera comes on.)
- You know people like that, right?
- Yes.
(They are nearing
the second restaurant.)
The thing is,
it's not easy
to hold on to a position for years.
It's not easy.
Working in the show business
for 30 years...
- is hard.
- It isn't easy.
- I...
- There was a crisis.
I told myself,
"I will work until the age of 30."
- Really?
- I didn't know...
- if it was the right path for me.
- You weren't sure about that.
I wondered if it would be okay
to pursue this career.
I told myself that
I will quit if I don't succeed...
until the age of 40.
- And?
- So...
when I hit the age of 40, I said,
"I will quit if I don't succeed
until the age of 50."
I pushed the deadline.
(He failed to become popular
until the age of 40.)
I will hang in there
until the age of 60 and quit.
- You just need to stay healthy.
- That's right.
We saw earlier
that he is in good health.
- I keep pushing the deadline.
- That's good.
- You don't need permission.
- This is the place.
- It opened in 1937.
- Okay.
You can see the history.
(It really is an old restaurant.)
Look at this place.
(Cheongjinok is a hangover soup
place with 84 years of history.)
It's Lee Ju Il.
- Nami.
- It really is an old restaurant.
This is a meaningful restaurant.
This is incredible.
- Seriously.
- This restaurant...
(Hangover soup with clotted blood,
tripe, and radish green is popular.)
This restaurant opened in 1937.
Its hangover soup was picked
as Seoul's future heritage.
Suk Jin can't eat...
clotted blood.
- No, he can't.
- What should we do?
Boiled pork.
Would you like to order boiled pork?
No, no. Hangover soup is
their signature dish.
Why are you being so difficult
when he offered to change the menu?
They could take out clotted blood.
- We need to eat clotted blood.
- We love clotted blood.
We want to eat the original version.
- This is driving me crazy.
- It's just Suk Jin.
- We need their signature dish.
- That's right.
I must do my best with the mission.
I bet I will only get clotted blood
if I place last.
Seriously.
- That will happen if I place last.
- Hold on.
You don't like the taste, right?
You can still eat it, right?
- I can eat it.
- That solves the problem.
I can eat it.
- Let's begin the mission.
- Okay.
Frog. 1, 2...
- "Demetan Croaker..."
- Incorrect.
(A well with a frog)
- I placed second.
- My goodness.
- This makes no sense.
- Turn in the age badges.
21 years each.
I left some age badges behind.
(They go from Chang Hee
to Soo Yong.)
I didn't turn in a lot.
My goodness.
Gosh, I turned in only a few.
Are there any years left
for Jae Suk?
- Are there any years left for...
- Jae Suk, your turn.
- How many years remain?
- One.
For goodness' sake.
(That's a lot.)
(Jae Suk could only deduct 1 year.)
All right. If I place first
the next time...
Just you wait.
We will do this again.
This isn't the end.
Seriously.
Do you know what's a relief?
Even though Suk Jin placed second,
he can't eat clotted blood.
That's right.
I am hungry.
- The soup.
- You know...
- He might just drink the soup.
I will eat rice. I will eat it.
The owner will give
a lot of clotted blood.
Please give us a lot of meat.
(The hangover soup
with 84 years of history is served.)
Thank you.
This is...
(The dish has a generous amount
of clotted blood and tripe.)
It looks delicious.
Gosh, it's...
- Shall we add rice?
- It looks delicious.
- I am sorry, but I placed first.
- That's right.
- You placed first.
- That's how it is.
- I see. That being said...
- What's that in the bowl?
- That's how it is.
- What is this?
- What?
"Due to Ji Hyo's hidden mission,
a year got deducted from your age."
- What?
- Lucky you.
"Turn in an age badge
to the production crew secretly."
Why did you read it out loud?
What is this?
I didn't receive anything.
I received a chance.
Is it okay if I do it?
The die chance.
- Why did you reveal it?
- What?
It's a hidden mission.
Why did you reveal it?
Ji Hyo must have succeeded
in the hidden mission.
(Meanwhile, the 3 of them
are eating.)
There is a lot of clotted blood.
(He takes a ladleful
without the clotted blood.)
Gosh, this seems to be a dish...
that isn't easy for me.
The smell...
- What isn't easy for you?
- This dish.
He is complaining about the smell.
- It isn't easy for me.
- There is a lot of food left.
Is that porridge?
(Suk Jin got forced into a diet.)
He is the worst. I told you.
- Watch.
- It isn't easy for me.
Soo Yong likes to eat,
but he eats in an unappetizing way.
Watch.
He eats in an unappetizing way.
(Jae Suk starts an eating show
instead.)
It's so tasty.
By the way,
why am I eating so much
when I placed last?
(He is having his fill
thanks to a picky eater.)
(He looks around without eating.)
Gosh, this is a dish with history.
(He talks about the history
without any food in his mouth.)
- A dish with history.
- He didn't eat much.
Watch him.
He keeps doing this with rice.
(Pushing the rice around)
Why are you mincing the rice?
Suk Jin,
why are you mincing the rice?
This is a dish with history.
I can feel the Korean spirit.
Do you know what he said?
He can feel the Korean spirit.
- The ancestors' spirit.
- He is ridiculous.
(He feels the ancestors' spirit
without tasting the dish.)
- This is the place.
- When did the restaurant open?
1980.
It says, "100-year-old restaurant".
100 years?
Is it 100 years old?
What is this place?
They even received a medal.
This restaurant serves
Pyongyang specialty.
It's from Pyongyang,
so it must be incredibly old.
- I bet it's 200 years.
- Did it start in Pyongyang?
It was passed down
through three generations.
Three generations?
Then it must be over 100 years old.
- How old is it? 100 years?
- We should ask.
You have arrived
at the second restaurant.
They set up a table in advance.
- We will proceed once you sit down.
- Shall we do that?
- All right.
- Sir.
(They call for the owner
with high expectations.)
(Excited)
- Hello.
Please come in.
It's my first time to meet the owner
of a 100-year-old restaurant.
I heard that this restaurant is
100 years old.
Sir,
how old is this restaurant?
(There was a sign that reads,
"100-year-old restaurant".)
(Is it actually 100 years old?)
It opened in 1984,
so it's 37 years old.
(It's 37 years old.)
- 37 years old.
That's... That's incredible.
We don't mean
this specific building.
We mean...
The brand.
We mean the entire brand,
- not this specific branch.
- In that case,
the grandfather of the owner...
- ran a restaurant in Pyongyang.
- Right?
He ran Daedongmyeonok there.
If you combine that history...
- If you combine that history...
- If I do that,
this restaurant would be
about 100 years old.
(This restaurant would be
about 100 years old.)
(They finally hear "100 years"!)
- I got goosebumps.
- That's Dadongmyeonok.
- This restaurant...
- How old is...
- Pyongyangmyeonok?
- How old is it?
It must be close to 100 years old.
It's 37 years old.
No, no.
The sign reads,
"100-year-old restaurant".
- It's our pride.
- I see.
When he moved to South Korea,
he didn't open the restaurant
right away.
- He did something else.
Will you only count
the history of this restaurant?
- Yes.
- 37 years. Okay.
What should we order?
- Which dish is the most popular?
- Pyongyang naengmyeon.
We should eat Pyongyang naengmyeon.
(Noodles with the aroma of buckwheat
and clean broth complete the dish.)
Please give us 1 serving
that feels like 5 servings.
- That's too bad.
- 37 years.
- I continued to send a signal.
We should hurry up
and move on to the next restaurant.
- That's right.
- Let's hurry up.
We need to go to Hadongkwan.
We should do that.
- This restaurant is 37 years old.
- Okay.
The mission is, Blow Out Candles
With the Entire Body.
With a fan attached to your waist,
you will generate winds.
The time it took you
to blow out five candles...
will determine the order.
When we simulated the game,
men had an advantage.
Thus, we will put the candles
50cm closer...
- for women.
- What?
- Here...
- Will the candles be...
- here?
- Yes.
- Is it even possible?
Since women have a handicap...
If you are against it...
I am not against it.
If I am against it,
will you reflect that?
To be honest, I am against it.
(He is petty.)
(He promotes gender equality.)
- It's too much.
- I am against it.
If it's a small advantage,
I would understand.
It's too much.
How much of a benefit
would you accept?
Move the sticker.
- What is your problem?
- No, no.
- We are on the same team.
- This needs to be fair.
I know that we are on the same team.
Then let's play fair.
Don't give us a benefit.
- No, no. You need it.
- Should we play the same way?
- Come on.
- We aren't that mean.
- All right.
- Move it a little bit.
Move it a little bit.
(Two big hand spans)
That's good.
What?
- Where?
- Just don't give us a benefit.
- We will give it.
- Do two hand spans.
Do two hand spans.
- For goodness' sake.
- Do two hand spans.
(Wriggling)
Do two hand spans.
- You moved your fingers.
- You are heartless.
- No, I didn't.
- You moved your fingers.
That's good enough.
- That's good enough.
- It's close to where it was before.
- It was generous of Kwang Soo.
- Seriously.
Do we put this on our waist?
Haha, it's your turn.
Isn't that what you wear
to work out?
Do I keep going
until I blow out all the candles?
Yes. The clock will keep going
until you blow out all of them.
Don't grab the belt
with your hands.
Get ready.
Set...
(Go.)
(One candle goes out already.)
He blew out one candle.
(He swings as much as he can.)
- Are you timing it?
- The wind is strong.
The flame is coming back.
I think the location is off.
- It worked.
- They won't go out.
It went out.
Haha is fast.
- A bit more.
- I did it!
(He succeeded to blow out
all the candles.)
26 seconds.
- This is difficult.
- Why do my knees hurt so much?
- His knees will get ruined.
- Why do your knees hurt?
- Hey.
You can do it.
Bomi.
We stand closer to the candles.
Can I grab the handle?
No, you can't.
Never.
Don't ever grab it.
- Don't ever grab it.
- We become so sensitive.
- Get ready.
Hey.
- Don't step on the line.
- She stepped on the line.
- I am sorry, but if you do that...
- Hey!
- you will just be out.
- Oh, no.
- It's over if you step on the line.
- Just go back.
You will automatically be
in last place.
- Okay.
- Go back more.
- Don't step on the line.
- That's enough.
I'll accept that.
- Get ready.
- Okay.
- Wait a minute.
- Go.
What's happening?
- What's happening?
- She put them out quickly.
(The candles were put out
as soon as she started.)
(Everyone stood up.)
- She was too close.
- This isn't right.
- Gosh.
- This is reverse discrimination.
- She's good.
- This isn't right.
Everyone agreed.
- Everyone agreed to this.
- Still...
Please decide it again then.
- Let's do it from here...
- This is too easy.
- because she's good.
- I could do it.
- We're much older than her.
- Let's try it from here.
- Let's try it first.
- Gosh.
- But this is...
- Or...
- I'll try it.
Let's try it first,
and if it's too hard...
- Get ready.
- Let's try it.
Go!
(Sabotage)
(Despite of Haha's sabotage...)
- What is happening?
- She's just good.
She's just good.
(The candles were put out
within 3 seconds.)
- How many seconds did I take?
- She only took three seconds.
- She's just good.
- Okay.
Honestly, you must give us
an advantage.
I'm serious.
Do you know how old we are?
That is reverse discrimination.
- The angle is important for this.
- That's good.
- Good.
- Watch your feet.
- Okay.
Okay.
Okay, get ready.
- I'm done.
- You punk!
Go!
(Go.)
- Oh, my.
It's over.
Oh, my. This is just...
(No movement at all)
It's over.
(He got the hang of it now.)
- He's doing a good job.
- That's it.
- No.
- Okay!
- It's back on.
- No.
Hurry!
(The candles look like they
will get put out, but they won't.)
What are we going to do?
- He got it.
- I'm mad.
He got it.
What are we going to do?
- Okay!
- No. Put it out.
(Okay! What?)
- Okay!
- No. Put it out.
(It's a supernatural phenomenon
that only happens to Kwang Soo.)
Is this a prank show? Is it a prank?
Is it a prank?
(Flapping)
He's going to be funny now.
(It's a never-ending desperate
struggle with candles.)
- Okay.
- A new...
It got put out.
(It finally got put out!)
(He gave his all.)
Lee Kwang Soo took 42 seconds.
- This will be hard.
- It's harder than I thought.
- It's hard looking at him do it.
- Did some of them come alive?
- It's Namjoo's turn next.
- It's the fourth person.
Is it me?
Make sure embers are
completely extinguished.
You need to gather your hands
behind your back to do a good job.
- Yes.
- Get ready.
- Okay.
- Go.
(Cheerful)
- She lost her balance.
- She's bad.
- Why is she drawing an eight?
- What's happening?
Is she being serious or what?
- She's serious.
- What is she doing?
(She's putting the candles out
with screaming and laughter.)
Why are you moving up and down?
If not...
(Why is she suddenly moving
up and down?)
I mean...
(No matter how much she shakes...)
What is happening?
- I mean...
- Aren't you going to do it?
- She won't be able to do it.
- She got it.
She got it. That's it.
- Make long strokes.
- Yes.
- She got it.
There's the last one left.
Namjoo, you crossed the line
too much.
- Namjoo.
- It's because...
- It's okay. Make long strokes.
- there's a line.
You just have to make long strokes
like earlier.
- Make long strokes.
- This one won't get put out.
- It's really not getting put out.
That one won't get put out.
- I...
- Oh, my.
That one has a long wick.
Blow it out for her, Haha.
(If Namjoo fans,)
(Haha will try to put it out
by blowing it.)
Blow it out for her.
See? Do it again.
Namjoo, you need to move.
You need to be in sync
with each other.
(Tiki-taka)
- You can't do that.
- Yes!
(They finally succeeded.)
You got it.
Namjoo took 1 minute 41 seconds.
- This is really hard.
- This is hard.
Bomi did a really good job.
- She did a ridiculously good job.
- This is hard.
How did you do it?
- I just shook everything.
- Bomi did a good job.
Is it my turn now?
He got it.
(This is the result of Jong Kook
also shaking everything.)
- What happened?
- He's certainly good.
- Oh, my.
Okay.
(He succeeded at putting
the candles out in 9 seconds.)
- I got it.
- I'm getting stressed out.
I just need to be in second place.
We will start taking away
age from first place.
You can take away
as much age as you want...
from 37 years,
the age of this restaurant.
- From 37 years?
- Yes.
- Wait a minute.
- Bomi, I beg you.
From 37 years?
How many do I have?
(It seems like she's taking away
a lot of things.)
- Okay, she's done.
- You look really light, Bomi.
No, I'm not.
- Kim Jong Kook is in second place.
- Okay.
I'll take a look.
I still have a lot. I'm full.
- These are the remaining years.
- Yes.
(The remaining years
after Bomi took away are...)
There are 10 years left.
(0 and rich)
Really?
I was more considerate
than you thought, right?
(He's really surprised.)
- She's...
- Your face turned completely red.
No, I really didn't take away a lot.
- How serious is it?
- I didn't take away a lot.
I think we should put her
in an incubator.
Does she have to get in
an incubator?
Right now, she's...
- I'm inside my mom's belly.
- Right now, she's...
Is she inside her mom's belly?
Gosh, this is really...
At that rate...
Our team has no sense
of teamwork, right?
- We just have to win.
- Let's not do this.
We can't win if we do this.
(Jong Kook took away 6 years.
He's currently 16 years old.)
There's only this much left?
He just went crazy anyway.
Can he walk or not?
Just tell me that.
He can't walk in my opinion.
(Toddling)
He can't walk. He can't walk now.
(The last person is Namjoo,
who is currently 22 years old.)
- Namjoo.
- Yes?
- Don't go.
- I'm not going to take it away.
Namjoo, you won't be able
to take anything away.
There's nothing left.
Okay.
You got it, right?
There's no other...
- I already knew it.
- Okay.
I guess you can't help it.
- We will give you your meal now.
- Okay.
- It looks good.
- Oh, my.
They gave us double portions.
Okay, I'll eat this much.
(Slurping)
(Kwang Soo, who was 4th place,
takes away some naengmyeon.)
Aren't you taking away too little?
- Let's eat together.
- Okay.
- You should eat a lot.
- Aren't you hungry?
(The younger ones are moved.)
I'll eat this.
So...
- Do you want some more?
- No.
I'm sorry,
but I really like naengmyeon.
- I thought you were full.
- We will also go there next time.
I never thought that a baby
who can't even walk properly...
could eat so much
Pyongyang naengmyeon.
This is different.
Kids usually don't like
Pyongyang naengmyeon.
I didn't know you could eat that
in an incubator.
Aren't you supposed to be breastfed?
- I'm being breastfed right now.
- Gosh.
- You first started with 177 years.
- Yes.
You currently have...
82 years left.
We have a lot left.
Let's go with 90 years.
- This is unbelievable.
- Why?
There's a cafe that has 100 years
of history.
- What?
- It's right next here.
(It's a race against time
from now on.)
(Every team is beginning
to become anxious.)
(It's an old restaurant war
with their ages on the line.)
(Which team will be the winner?)
(And)
(November 2020,
The penthouse resident presentation)
(It's a luxurious
opera performance for the VIPs.)
(4 residential candidates
of the penthouse appeared.)
(Kim So Yeon, Lee Ji Ah, Eugene)
(Ha Do Kwon is also here
to go after Jong Kook.)
(Their malicious fight to join
the top club began.)
(Will they join the top club...)
(or the bottom club?)
(Their war of nerves is tough.)
(There are only a few people
allowed to join the top club.)
(Who will join the top club and
become a penthouse resident?)
(The penthouse is
currently recruiting.)