(Last week, in Running Village...)
(It was a birthday party for
the village elder, Ji Suk Jin.)
(Happy birthday, Mr. Ji.)
(Ji Suk Jin, born in February,
the oldest in Running Village)
(Stay healthy, Mr. Ji.)
(The residents are excited
about Mr. Ji's birthday party.)
(A parade of presents is a must
at a birthday party.)
(A bamboo wife)
(That's a lie.)
(Jae Suk got him a gateball set.)
(Bravo to your
shining variety life.)
(We love you
for the rest of your life.)
(Long life, health, blessing)
(They had some good times together
celebrating his birthday.)
Long life, health, and blessing.
The residents of Running Village
congratulated Suk Jin today.
The village head...
sent a present to Suk Jin,
the oldest resident,
to wish him a long and healthy life.
- This is the real present.
- Seriously.
Why wish for a long and healthy life
when I am in my 50s?
Is it a letter?
It's a letter.
(There's a letter in the gift box.)
"Dear Mr. Ji Suk Jin."
"Happy birthday to Mr. Ji Suk Jin,
the oldest resident of the village."
"Were you surprised
by the empty box?"
I haven't checked the box yet.
"For your birthday,
I prepared a surprise event."
"At a place in the village
that is related to 'House',"
- "I hid the gold I prepared."
- Gold?
(Gold?)
"I hope you will find it well."
"I think it'd be hard for you
to find it by yourself,"
"so I'm giving you..."
"an important hint."
He just took it.
"And you can pick two members
who are clever..."
"and decode the clues
I'm giving you with them..."
"to find the gold."
"The other five members will..."
"look for the gold individually."
Individually?
"If your team finds the gold first,"
"you can share it
with your members."
"The other residents will
find hidden hints."
"The resident who touches
the box that has gold in it..."
- "will have the gold to oneself."
- That sounds fun.
"Those who fail to find my gift
will get a penalty."
"If your team finds the gold,"
"you will get to pick two people
to get a penalty."
"If one of the residents finds it,"
"the winner will pick two people
from your team to get a penalty."
"Good luck, everyone."
- So it's like 5 to 3.
- Right.
That sounds good.
Like the letter says, you will have
a race where you look for gold.
It's called
It's Time to Find the Gold Race.
I see.
Suk Jin, we'd like you to pick
two clever members...
whom you want to be a team with.
We have many members
who are good at petty tricks.
- There are a lot.
- That's right.
- Suk Jin is...
- Haha is good at this.
Suk Jin has gotten penalties
for the past six weeks.
- That's right.
- He needs to end it.
He should break the jinx today.
He's not so lucky.
Who'd be good at tricks?
- So Min is good.
- What about Kwang Soo?
So Min won't even look at him.
So Min, you should look at Suk Jin.
- Why would you avoid him?
- Two members.
I've made up my mind.
(He picks two members
after much consideration.)
Kim Jong Kook and Lee Kwang Soo.
- Darn it.
- Okay.
(They are recruited to
Suk Jin's team against their will.)
Hey. What was that?
- No, that's not what I meant.
- Seriously.
You don't have to do this.
I don't want you anymore.
- Today is a good day.
- Hey.
Hey, Kwang Soo. Hey.
- Try to smile.
- Hey.
Today is a good day.
- What are you doing?
- He didn't answer.
Hey, I don't want you on my team.
I don't need you either.
- I'm really...
- Yes!
I need to break the jinx
of six penalties, Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
Hang on.
Aren't the three of you the ones
who wrote the letter of apology?
- That's right.
- They did.
You three wrote
the letter of apology.
And you flew a kite with me.
That's right.
Why are we doing this
on such a good day?
- He's right about that.
- Okay.
I often meet them at the ending.
Exactly.
So your team is decided.
Before we start the mission,
we will play
the first game for hints.
Like I said,
there are hints
hidden in the village.
Unlike how we normally do things,
in this round,
you will go to a random place
in this village...
where you think
the gold is hidden...
carrying your tracking device
with you.
Once you are done
choosing your place,
the device of the member who's
closest to the gold will go off.
And for the next 15 minutes,
you will look for the gold or hints.
We even have tracking devices.
(The one who stays
closest to the gold...)
(will find out the approximate
location of the gold.)
But even if your device
doesn't go off,
you can still find hints
about the location of the gold.
So you should try
to look for the hints.
- We should find the hints first.
- Now, I want you...
to move to places where you think
the gold is hidden.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
A place where I think
the gold is hidden?
Hang on. Where should I go?
There are many houses.
So...
I should go to a place
where I think the gold is hidden.
- Right.
- Any place in the village.
In this whole village?
The whole place?
We have hints.
- Right. We have hints.
- We can see the hints first.
Let's see the hints
and move separately.
We can go to places that are
more likely to have the gold.
We should think the five of us...
- are on the same boat.
- Okay.
- All right, Jae Suk.
- Us?
- We should scatter away.
- Okay.
(They agree to scatter
and find the gold separately.)
2 will go up, and 3 will go down.
We should scatter in all directions.
It says Haha's House.
(Haha's House near the slope?)
I guess they are all
someone's house.
What's that?
It says House of Dolls.
I'll go to House of Dolls.
- Did you feel that too?
- I felt it.
Will you go that way?
I'll stay here.
Take a look at it. I'll get in...
Will you get in the car?
What's all this?
There's a giraffe.
(What's the house
full of stuffed dolls for?)
Giraffe.
Let's check the hint first.
(Suk Jin and his team
check the hint first.)
"All the houses aren't the same."
(This is an important hint
only for Suk Jin.)
(Don't share it
with the other residents.)
(Hint: All the houses
aren't the same.)
"All the houses aren't the same."
Suk Jin, there's House of Sports.
There are many houses.
(There's House of Sports
right behind them.)
(House of Sports)
(But in other buildings
in Running Village...)
(House of Deep Sleep)
(There are many houses...)
(with different themes.)
(House of Cooking)
(There are many mysterious
houses in Running Village.)
(There are also the houses
of the 8 residents in the village.)
(So Min's House, Ji Hyo's House,
Jong Kook's House)
(Hyeong Gu's House,
Jae Suk's House, Suk Jin's House)
(Se Chan's House, Kwang Soo's house,
Haha's House)
"All the houses aren't the same."
Suk Jin, there's House of Sports.
There are many houses.
I bet the gold isn't
in one of these houses.
- There are real houses.
- Like a doghouse.
- A doghouse.
- Right.
There is a doghouse in the middle.
Will you stay in the doghouse then?
I'm just asking.
That's what the hint says.
Why would I go into a doghouse?
There's a doghouse, a birdhouse,
and other things.
- It should be something like that.
- Things that say house.
"All the houses aren't the same."
(Did the three of them
solve the hint right?)
- Should we go into some house?
- What would it be?
Let's go look for the gold.
We're a team now.
- Okay.
- Okay? Good luck.
- I'm serious about this.
- Let's do this seriously.
House of Books?
Are we on the same team?
Sure. We're a team.
(They should find a place
where the gold is hidden.)
(Scanning)
I don't think it's here.
(He doesn't think the gold is
in a cute place like that.)
I'll stay here.
(I'll stay here.)
I don't think this is it.
The house Jae Suk abandons...
is more likely
to be the correct answer.
I pick this place. I'll stay here.
(Se Chan picks an open space
near the three-way intersection.)
I pick this place.
I'll stay in the center.
I should've put on warmer clothes.
Suk Jin, you're the lead today.
You have two cameras.
That's not true.
- All members are the leads.
- This is so cool.
I'll give you the gold if I find it.
Okay.
(Who will find the gold that's
a birthday gift for Suk Jin?)
We did many important things
around here.
(Kwang Soo tries to find out
the gold based on his experience.)
I personally think it's around here.
Because we did
a lot of things here before.
- Is this your choice?
- Yes.
If I'm close to the gold,
will you tell me that?
Your tracking device will go off.
The one who's closest to the gold.
(This is it.)
(Thumbs up)
- Is this product placement?
- No.
(He just gave a thumbs up
out of habit.)
Is this product placement?
(Is this product placement?)
I could put this on my dog's collar
and let it out, right?
(What else should I say?)
(Ji Hyo even dances with the device
to cover the production cost.)
It might be one of these two.
Suk Jin, it's Ji Hyo's house.
Ji Hyo won a lot of gold.
Ji Hyo won a lot of games
and won gold.
So I bet it might be
in Ji Hyo's house.
All the houses aren't the same.
(Jae Suk is upstairs
in the same building.)
Hang on. Hyeong Gu's House?
(Hyeong Gu's House)
Is there Hyeong Gu's House?
I should stand here.
This is strange.
Hyeong Gu's House
doesn't sound right.
Ji Hyo's House.
(Jong Kook visits Ji Hyo's house
as he guessed earlier.)
(Ji Hyo's House)
Am I supposed to make a guess
with what I see?
There's nothing special in here.
(Right at that moment...)
"When it's big, have a close look."
(When it's big, have a close look.)
"When it's big, have a close look?"
("When it's big,
have a close look?")
(Does the family motto
of Ji Hyo's house mean something?)
I'll stay here.
- Have you made up your mind?
- Yes. I pick Ji Hyo's house.
- I've made up my mind.
- Is that your choice?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(Suk Jin, Jong Kook, and Jae Suk
choose the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd floor.)
I think it's here.
(Haha picks House of Dolls
that he found at the beginning.)
- Have you made your choice?
- Yes. I have a feeling.
The thing you pick first
is mostly correct.
The device of the person
closest to the gold will go off.
- My gosh.
- We're at an advantage.
If Jong Kook's device
or Suk Jin's goes off...
(Whose device will go off?)
(Beeping)
(The person who's standing
closest to the gold is...)
(Yang Se Chan.)
(The gold is
near the three-way intersection.)
Am I the only one who can hear that?
(The gold is
near the three-way intersection.)
(He's caught by Haha.)
What are you looking at,
you old man?
- Haha, my device went off.
- I know.
I told you. It's in the center.
I won't tell anyone.
(They promise that
they won't tell anyone else.)
Haha.
It must be somewhere near here.
(The gold is
somewhere near Se Chan.)
This is amazing. It was Se Chan.
Haha.
It must be somewhere near here.
(Where's the gold then?)
The device of the person
closest to the gold just went off.
Mine didn't go off.
That means it's not in here.
I hope it was Suk Jin or Jong Kook.
- You can continue.
- Find the gold?
Yes. You can look for it now.
(They can look for the clues
for 15 minutes.)
I should go ask them.
Did your device ring?
- Did yours go off?
- I think it was Suk Jin's.
What?
Suk Jin's device went off,
so he's going around alone.
He's acting like the protagonist.
Are we supposed
to look for the gold now?
How would we find it when we
don't know where it went off?
Aren't you going to tell us
where the device went off?
We're not telling you.
We can't find it when we don't know
where the device went off.
(Se Chan and Haha scatter away
keeping the secret to themselves.)
I should smell the gold.
The smell of gold.
Can I go in here?
(Se Chan hovers around
where he stood earlier...)
Hang on. Where was I earlier?
(looking for the gold.)
It must be somewhere here.
There's a strange doll in here.
(Jae Suk is searching
the residents' houses.)
(So Min's House)
"When up high, check down below?"
(There's a family motto
in So Min's house too.)
"When up high, check down below."
(Jae Suk boggles at the phrase.)
What's that?
Does that mean
it's not in a high place?
(He walks down the stairs
to check down below.)
(Jong Kook's House)
"I'm always watching you?"
(I'm always watching you?)
(There's another motto.)
Look at that.
What?
(Kwang Soo spots the same frame
in Jong Kook's House.)
So this is the clue.
(Passing by)
(He leaves Kwang Soo right away
since he's on a different team.)
This is the clue.
(He steals Kwang Soo's shoes
while he's at it.)
(He walks away with
Kwang Soo's shoes smiling.)
(Then Kwang Soo tries to leave.)
(What?)
Those are my shoes.
(He steals the cameraman's shoes.)
No.
(The cameraman follows
the shoe thief in his socks.)
(They steal
each other's shoes in a relay.)
- Oh no.
- What?
Did you find something?
- Did you find anything?
- Were these your shoes, Yoon Sang?
(Yoon Sang lost his shoes
to Kwang Soo.)
Yoon Sang, I'm sorry.
These are Yoon Sang's.
I'm wearing Yoon Sang's shoes.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
I had no choice.
Jong Kook, there's a clue.
"When it's big, have a close look."
- That's the clue.
- Hey.
There's a clue in my house too.
Each house has...
Each room has a clue.
Each room has a clue on the wall.
"I'm always watching you."
(Ji Hyo's House, So Min's House,
Jong Kook's House)
We should put them together.
I will go to my house.
It's around here,
so I guess it's in the house.
It might be in the building.
There are Jae Suk's House...
and Suk Jin's House.
But the problem is...
Jae Suk's House has
a lot of R stickers in it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Haha, the clue is...
Someone in here... Gosh.
- Haha.
- What?
- Did you find it?
- Haha.
- There's something.
- It's just paper.
Well done.
Hang on.
Take a look at it.
What is this?
(What's in the envelope
that Se Chan found?)
I remember what this is.
Isn't this the thing
about the Yoo Family?
We played yutnori here.
- And the room on the right is...
- That's the place.
Suk Jin's room.
I know that.
It's Suk Jin's room.
And the one on the left is...
- What?
- Why?
- It was the same back then.
- Jae Suk's House?
(On the left and right
of the living room in the picture,)
(there are Suk Jin's House
and Jae Suk's House.)
They are steaming songpyeon.
They're making songpyeon.
It says R.
(And there are four people
in the picture.)
(One of them is...)
(Yoo Jae Suk.)
Jae Suk, where... Why...
Nothing.
What's with that mischievous smile?
- I'm just looking around.
- What are you doing?
- What are you up to now?
- I'm just looking around.
What's with that mischievous smile?
(Does he have a secret
that the others don't know?)
(The 1st search is over.)
Time's up.
- Please gather around.
- Okay.
(The first search is over.)
(The place for the first mission
has toy hammers in line.)
(What's the mission?)
This is where I got pregnant.
- What?
- I was pregnant here.
That's right.
You should get over the skit.
(Se Chan and So Min were a newly
married couple...)
(during last year's Chuseok holidays
in Episode 523.)
(Retching)
(So Min was absorbed in the skit
and went too far.)
(Her joke embarrassed
even her husband.)
(Do you have an upset stomach?)
(No. Wait...)
(That's how So Min
came up with the best meme.)
This is where you found out
you were pregnant.
- Right. I was retching.
- That's right.
Happy birthday, Suk Jin.
You keep saying that. That's enough.
Why are you angry?
Can't you be happy?
I'm not angry.
Long life, health, and blessing!
- We should do this when we can.
- That's enough.
We should do this when we can.
My dad came to my room yesterday.
I was wrapping the bamboo wife
for him, and Dad asked what it was.
So I said it was
a birthday gift for Suk Jin.
Then he asked how old Suk Jin is,
so I said...
- he was born in 1966.
- That's correct.
I also said that he's quite old now,
and my dad said,
"Hey, he's still so young."
(Suk Jin is still very young
compared to So Min's father.)
- My dad said...
- It's understandable.
- You're right.
- Her father must feel that way.
"He's still so young."
That's what seniors always say.
- Say hello to your father, So Min.
- "He's still so young."
When elderly people like him see
a man who was born in 1966,
- He's like a baby to them.
- he looks so young.
- He's in the prime of his life.
- He's the youngest in such a group.
(Baby Big Nose still has
a long way to go.)
- Today, you have two missions.
- Okay.
To celebrate Suk Jin's birthday,
we prepared...
missions that would be easy
for Suk Jin.
You must be at an advantage.
I guess we'll play some games
I can win.
Then they're probably not
physically hard...
- if it's advantageous for him.
- We don't have to be strong to win.
We rarely see toy hammer games
on TV shows these days.
- They're all simple, easy games.
- Simple and easy?
- The games we've done before?
Did you really have to
put it like that?
You could've used some other words
like "cute".
You mean some old games?
Good. Let's do this!
All right. Let's do this.
The first mission is...
the upgraded version of
Catching Rats,
the game played in the show
that Suk Jin hosted...
- during his best days.
- I know that game.
Catch rats, catch rats
- It's Daring Rats.
- I remember that game.
- Suk Jin will do it well.
- Catch rats, catch rats
- Squeak, squeak, squeak
- I don't...
- remember the rules clearly.
- He has an advantage.
(This is the young Big Nose
during his best days.)
Okay.
(After the song, the 1st player says
the number of the rats to catch.)
- How many rats?
Three rats!
(Players can say either "Caught it"
or "Missed it".)
(When all the rats are caught,
everyone says, "Hooray".)
(You're out when you do the wrong
motion or miss the timing.)
- Catch rats, catch rats
- How many rats?
For example, you say, "Three rats."
- "Caught it."
- "Caught it" or "Missed it".
After three people
saying "Caught it", we all say...
- "Meow"?
- "Hooray."
- Oh, right.
- Hey, you're still young.
- What's wrong with you?
- I mean, he hosted the show.
- There you go.
- Okay.
- Back then, he was the MC,
- Actually, I...
but he only followed
the staff's decisions.
- I bet he didn't care.
- I see.
- He was like a parrot.
- He was more like an avatar.
- He was an avatar.
- He didn't participate in it.
- That's true. I didn't.
- The directors were Shin Won Ho...
- Oh, right.
- And Na Yeong Seok.
- That's right.
- What?
- He must've been close to them.
- Won Ho and Yeong Seok.
- You worked with Na Yeong Seok?
- And the writer was Lee Woo Jung.
(What a fantastic line-up of staff.)
- They're very successful now.
- Indeed.
All the people who worked with him
became so famous, but he...
- If you think about it...
- Hey!
- Why?
- Yeong Seok,
Won Ho, and Woo Jung...
tend to keep working
with the same people.
- They all have that tendency.
- That's right.
- They always do that.
- Then why...
And the people who worked with them
became top stars.
- It's true.
- Really?
Director Shin hired the same actors
for his new dramas.
- They all do that.
- It's like a shortcut to success.
Suk Jin, what happened?
Did you fight with them?
I'm not the type
who argues with others.
- Do you think I'm that type?
- He's right. He's an individualist.
- He's an individualist.
- I don't argue with others.
(He failed to make
the friendship last long.)
We talk on the phone from a distance
and root for each other.
Who would talk on the phone
when they're close by?
- That's why we use a phone.
- Come on, Jae Suk.
Why?
- Today is Suk Jin's birthday.
- He's still so young.
- It's his birthday.
- He's in the prime of his life.
You see, I'm grateful...
- that all three of them are...
- Yes.
doing so well, and I don't have to
worry about them.
I always cheer for you, guys!
Who worries about whom?
- Won Ho, Yeong Seok, and Woo Jung!
- Right.
- You guys are the best.
- Won Ho, Yeong Seok,
- and Woo Jung,
- Yes.
you have nothing to worry
about Suk Jin.
- He's taking good care of himself.
- I'm doing fine.
- Don't worry about me.
- Of course.
We added a new rule to this game.
You can say, "Caught it",
"Missed it", or "It ran".
- What's that?
- "It ran"?
When a player says, "It ran",
one of the rats that were caught
will be excluded from the count.
That is, there will be one less rat
that you caught.
Oh, I see. We can take one out too?
(In the upgraded version,
they can take a rat out too.)
- That sounds so difficult.
- So we have to catch one more.
If you do the wrong motion,
- miss the timing,
- We do the motion too?
or count the rats incorrectly,
you're out and lose one point.
Gosh, seriously.
Oh, that's so cute. It's a rat.
- There's a song too.
- They play the song too.
I haven't heard this song
in a long time.
- It's an old song.
- Thank you.
After that, we'll hear,
"How many rats?"
What do we do with this toy hammer?
- You hit others with it.
- When someone makes a mistake.
Kwang Soo, what else could we do
with a toy hammer?
- Pardon me?
- Use your head.
- Would we crack walnuts with it?
- Jae Suk.
I never said anything about walnuts.
- Don't waste my time like that.
- Hey!
- He's just nervous.
- He's right.
He's doing his warm-ups.
Gosh, seriously.
Play the music.
(Rat Song starts.)
(From Dirty Mustache Rat...)
I haven't done this in a while.
(To So Min Rat who looks perfect
with the headband.)
(Catch rats, catch rats)
- How many rats?
- Six rats!
- Caught it.
- It ran.
- Hooray!
- No. That's not right. Is it?
- No.
- He said...
- You're all out.
- We didn't catch them all.
- We were wrong.
We had one more rat to catch.
Oh, right. She said, "It ran."
- Everyone was looking around...
- I think we did correctly.
and followed him
as soon as he said, "Hooray".
None of us was sure.
Five.
- We had one more rat to catch.
- Exactly.
But he was the first one
to say "Hooray".
- No.
- You're out.
It wasn't me.
Suk Jin said it first.
- Listen to me.
- No, no.
- The two of them caught rats.
- I was mistaken.
- Forget it!
- Listen. Hey!
- We can't even play the normal one.
- Let's try one more time.
- I can't play the original game.
He was the one who should be out.
- Let's call it a practice.
- Good.
Let's focus, everyone.
(Jae Suk cut Suk Jin off
when he was imitating the siren.)
(Catch rats, catch rats)
- How many rats?
Four rats!
- Caught it.
- It ran.
- Caught it. Hooray!
- Hooray!
No, we caught only three rats.
- Caught it.
- It ran.
(After shouting, "It ran",)
(he said "Hooray"
before anyone else said it.)
We caught only three rats.
I didn't say "Hooray".
- We caught 3, right?
- We needed 1 more rat.
- We had to catch one more.
- What's wrong with you?
- Why?
- My gosh.
- I raised my arms because of you.
- Take him out. It's not fun.
I raised my arms because of you.
- Because of me?
- Yes.
You're so lousy at games!
- He ruined the strawberry game too.
- Okay. Got it.
- We had one more to go.
- Okay.
Jae Suk, you lost one point.
- Why? Why?
- Okay.
You said "Hooray".
- You looked so confident.
- You were the only one.
But they said it too.
I did it because of you.
Raise your hand
if you don't understand the rules.
- Jae Suk, raise your hand.
- No. I know the rules.
These two caught rats, right?
Everyone, let's just not say
"It ran" for the time being.
- We can just not say it.
- That's right.
- Don't say it.
- Right.
- Let's stay safe.
- Don't say it.
- It's a promise.
- Okay. Good.
- Also, about the number of rats,
- choose a small number like one.
- Don't say "It ran".
- Just don't say it.
- Until we get used to this game.
- Never say "It ran".
- Let's get used to it first.
- I won't let it slide if you do.
- I'll make it really easy for you.
- Okay.
- What number will it be?
- How many rats?
- I'll say three.
- Okay.
- Keep that in mind.
- Let's begin.
- 1, 2...
- Say "How many rats?"
- Okay. Ready, go.
- How many rats?
- Three rats!
- Caught it.
- Hooray!
- Three rats!
- Caught it!
- Caught it.
- Missed it.
- Caught it. Hooray!
- Hooray!
- Five rats.
- Caught it.
- Hooray!
- Two rats!
- Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray!
- Hooray!
Caught it.
(He was extremely nervous
from the start.)
(Caught it!)
Caught it.
(He made a mistake
because he was too nervous.)
Why? Why can't you do that?
- Why? Why?
What's the problem?
Why do you always get so nervous?
Why are you lousy at everything else
but hosting a show?
Don't make us play simple games!
He always ruins it.
- He's so lousy at this.
- I'm not good at this.
Why?
I'm not good at playing
games like this.
You should've said
the number of rats to catch.
We didn't even say "It ran".
He said he caught a rat.
- I'm not good at this.
- He caught it.
He didn't even know when to say
"Hooray", so he looked at us...
and followed us.
- We should all say it at once.
- He gets flustered.
Let's try to continue
more rounds without stopping.
(Catch rats, catch rats)
Catch rats, catch rats,
squeak, squeak, squeak
- How many rats?
Seven rats!
- Caught it.
- Missed it.
- It ran!
- Caught it.
(Flustered)
Missed it.
- We agreed not to say "It ran".
- Why did you do that?
What's wrong?
Why did you say that?
Why can't I say it
when the rules allow it?
- We all agreed not to say it.
- But it's allowed.
Why did you do that?
- Why would you do that?
- You were told not to.
- Why would you try to stand out?
- Don't do what you're told not to.
- Just don't do it.
- What did I do wrong?
- What? Don't do it as we agreed.
- We all agreed not to say it.
- We all agreed.
But it's allowed to say "It ran"
according to the rules.
- That's not the point.
- I didn't do the wrong motion.
- But we all agreed on it.
- When will we ever get used to it?
It might take us a few days
to learn how to play this.
Shut your mouth.
You ruined everything. So shut it.
- I ruined everything?
- Hey!
You ruined it.
- Ji Hyo was enjoying herself.
- Hey.
- Right. I'm sorry.
- Kwang Soo.
You start the game.
Say the number of rats.
- And let's not...
- Catch rats
(Jae Suk started singing.)
(Suk Jin tried to be an MC
after a long time.)
(But Jae Suk cut him off.)
Suk Jin, don't talk to the players
like that.
"Hey, say the number of rats."
- What was that?
- Just because it's his birthday.
- He speaks like an old man.
- Also...
- Today is my birthday, you know.
- He's so bossy.
Don't call a big number like seven.
It makes it harder
to play this game.
- Too many rats...
- No more than four rats.
- He's a bossy man.
- Under five.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Don't make it confusing.
And don't say "I couldn't catch it."
- You mean "It ran".
- "It ran."
- Suk Jin, come on.
- Just say "Missed it".
- Don't say it either.
- My gosh.
- Ready, go.
- Say "How many rats?"
- How many rats?
Four rats!
- Caught it.
- Missed it.
- Caught it. Hooray!
- Hooray!
- Three rats!
- Caught it.
- Hooray!
Seven rats!
- Missed it.
- Caught it.
It ran.
- Gosh, you.
- Why?
It ran.
(Ji Hyo punished him.)
- You were told not to say it!
- What's wrong?
I told you not to say "It ran".
(Kwang Soo who said it last time
is punishing him most harshly.)
You should never say "It ran"!
- I told you not to say it.
- What? Why?
- Was it you?
- Why would you hit me?
(The person who said it before
gets punished too in this game.)
Why would you hit us?
It can happen, you know.
A rat ran away.
- On such a happy day like this?
- We all agreed not to say it.
- My rat ran away.
- We all agreed.
Exactly.
Hey, we were enjoying the game
without stopping.
- He's right.
- But you ruined it.
- It was fun.
- Don't act like a know-it-all.
- I was flustered.
- Hey, don't act up.
I had no choice but to say it.
- Ji Hyo could've just moved on.
- Exactly.
But she hit me right away. Gosh.
- That was funny.
- Why did you say it?
- Who was out?
- Ji Hyo lost one point.
- Oh, good.
- Let's begin.
He was the one who was hit,
but she lost a point?
Ji Hyo was the one who was out.
Ji Hyo, say "It flew away"
while doing this motion.
This is not fun at all.
You just say "Caught it".
Okay. I'll do whatever I want.
- I never said "Missed it".
- Fine. I heard you.
It's easy to count.
How many rats?
- Two rats!
- Caught it.
We should sing the song first.
We don't have to sing it every time.
But that's part of the game.
- We don't have to do it every time.
- Yes, we have to.
Catch rats, catch rats,
squeak, squeak, squeak
Why won't you sing it?
(He reluctantly sang the song
with a fake smile on his face.)
(He got upset right away.)
- How could I sing along?
- He sang it in his own style.
Let's take a break.
- Why didn't you sing along?
- What was that?
- What's wrong with you?
- Catch
- Rats, catch rats
- Catch rats
Squeak, squeak, squeak
Catch rats, catch rats,
squeak, squeak, squeak
- How many rats?
- Three rats.
- Caught it.
- Hooray!
Four rats.
- Missed it.
- Caught it.
(Ji Hyo had been fully concentrated
since a long time ago.)
- Caught it?
- Hooray!
(Only she didn't raise her arms.)
- Hold on a second.
- What was that?
- Gosh.
- You were too late.
- Ji Hyo, come on.
- What was that?
You sounded unsure.
Say it confidently.
- Be bold. "Caught it?"
- This isn't a quiz.
- It's not a short-answer question.
- It sounded like a question.
- Understood. I'm sorry.
- Don't make it sound like that.
- Got it.
- Why would you ask a question?
- It's "Caught it" or "Missed it".
- Exactly.
- It's that simple.
- Ji Hyo.
Since you keep making a mistake,
Suk Jin hasn't been out yet.
I won't be out.
- Let's switch seats.
- Let's do that.
I played this game for years.
I will never make a mistake.
- Where should I sit?
- Come over here.
- Suk Jin, sit between us.
- Okay.
If I make a mistake,
I'll let Se Chan hit me
in the forehead.
- Are you serious?
- I'm confident.
That wouldn't be special.
We all get hit in the forehead.
I meant finger flick,
not the toy hammer.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Se Chan can hit really hard.
- Here we go.
Instead... There must be
something I get.
- "Something you get"?
- You'll get to eat later.
Oh, you're right. That would work.
- And you got one year older too.
- You should eat something.
- He got one year older.
- Exactly. You got one year older.
That's what he got.
- Oh, I got one year older.
- Yes, you did.
- I didn't realize that.
- You're one year older now.
- That's good enough.
- Great.
Ready, go.
Catch rats, catch rats,
squeak, squeak, squeak
- How many rats?
- Six rats!
- Caught it.
- It ran.
- Caught it. Hooray!
- Hooray!
- Three rats.
- No. You counted wrong.
- We had one more rat to catch.
- That's right.
- What's wrong with you?
- What's the problem?
Don't be anxious.
We were doing great.
Why did you ruin it?
- Gosh.
- We were having fun.
Jae Suk, it's because
you said "It ran".
- Gosh. What's the problem?
- He said it like he didn't care.
Why did you say it?
What's wrong?
Am I not allowed to say it?
Gosh. He says there's nothing wrong
with it now.
Why did you say "It ran"?
He says it's okay because he did it.
Then let's say you're older than me.
- I'm sorry.
- You're older than me from now on.
That's weirdly convincing.
It makes you feel like
you're wrong.
- My gosh. Kwang Soo will go first?
- Okay.
Catch rats, catch rats,
squeak, squeak, squeak
- Catch rats, catch rats
- Louder, louder!
Louder!
Are we in the military?
(Following Old Fossil Yu,
Battalion Chief Yoo appeared.)
- Is this a boot camp?
- Be quiet.
I'm just saying you should
be more excited.
- Right, It wasn't cheery.
- You were frowning.
- Boost your cheery energy.
- Sing it louder.
- Move your shoulders up and down.
- Hey, be more excited.
Catch rats, catch rats,
squeak, squeak, squeak
- How many rats?
Six rats!
- Caught it.
- Missed it.
- Caught it. Hooray!
- Hooray!
Four rats!
- Caught it.
- It ran.
- Caught it. Hooray!
- Hooray!
Did we count correctly?
Yes, we did.
(No one was sure
when they raised their hands.)
- We did it right.
- Let's be honest.
Raise your hand
if you just guessed.
- I followed my hunch.
- Me too.
- I guessed.
- This is unbelievable.
- Ji Hyo, let's begin.
- Ji Hyo.
Five rats.
- Caught it.
- Missed it.
- It ran.
- Caught it.
- Hooray!
- Three rats!
- Caught it.
- It ran.
- It ran...
- That doesn't work.
- That'd be minus one rat.
- Caught it.
- It ran.
It ran...
(He's out because there's no rat
to run away!)
All right. That was good.
(It's time for them to hit him
with their toy hammers.)
Why can't anyone hit him?
- Hey!
- Cheer up, Jong Kook!
- Why won't you hit him?
- Hit him now!
- Why won't you guys hit him?
- Why did you hit him so lightly?
Why didn't you hit him?
Why did you hit him so lightly?
- I didn't want to mess up his hair.
- What was that?
Did you guys see him hit Jong Kook?
- Why?
- He just tapped him on his head.
Let's move on already.
We should continue.
- This is so funny.
- Gosh, seriously.
Here. Are you satisfied now?
- By the way, we've improved.
- Suk Jin...
Suk Jin...
tried to be as polite
as he could be.
(It was a polite touch.)
He hit Jong Kook like this.
After hitting Jong Kook,
he even asked if it was good enough.
- To make sure he wasn't upset.
- His hair...
I didn't want to mess up his hair.
How many times did you hit me?
Three times.
He spoke in a cute way.
I hit you three times. Why?
- Let's try to keep going. It's fun.
- Let's do this.
Catch rats, catch rats,
squeak, squeak, squeak
- How many rats?
- Six rats!
- Caught it.
- It ran.
- Missed it.
- Caught it.
- Caught it. Hooray!
- Hooray!
Suk Jin is out.
- Caught it.
(He raised his hands too early.)
- Why did you do that?
- Suk Jin.
I'm starting to get confused
when it's almost over.
Hang on. Suk Jin promised to let
Se Chan hit him in the forehead.
Shut it. It's over now.
- It's over now.
- But a promise is a promise.
You made a promise.
- But it's over.
- You should keep your promise...
- because it's your birthday.
- You promised.
- Do you want to hit me?
- Consider it as a birthday noogie.
No, I don't,
but it's a birthday noogie for you.
- What do you mean?
- Or apologize to the viewers...
- for making an empty promise.
- Why did you even make a promise?
- Earlier...
- You said it yourself.
Hey.
(He revealed his forehead
in the end.)
All right.
My forehead is still fine. Here.
- Happy birthday, Suk Jin!
- Go ahead.
My finger will hurt too
since it's winter.
- I know.
- Exactly.
- That's true.
- Right.
It hurts both ways.
Why did I make this promise?
I realized it was a mistake
right away. Take it easy.
Hit me just hard enough
to make the sound.
They can increase the volume later.
- And I'll overreact.
- Okay.
- You really are a professional.
- Of course.
You know what can be done
in the editing process.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- Somehow it makes me feel...
So Min, dance for him
as his daughter-in-law.
- Do we have some toilet paper?
- I will...
- When you hear me hit him,
- Then start dancing.
- start dancing.
- "Here we go!"
- Can you...
- Yes?
- Can you play gugak music for me?
- Of course.
Can you play some music too?
- On someone's phone?
- What?
So Min, that's great.
- She prepared herself properly.
- Yes.
(Flapping)
(His daughter-in-law's
filial dance...)
That's great. So Min, way to go.
- She's such a good daughter-in-law.
- Play it as soon as I hit him.
- Your daughter-in-law...
- She's a great dancer.
- She's...
- All right.
So Min, wait over here
until I hit him.
She's amazing.
Suk Jin seems happy.
- He looks happy.
- He's finally smiling.
- He's blushing.
- You see...
- His daughter-in-law is...
- You're doing well.
such a great dancer.
- She drew my attention.
- Yes.
Please make the pain go away.
- Through a laugh.
- Make me laugh.
She's like a laughter therapist.
This is so funny.
Your daughter-in-law learned
to dance properly.
(Here I go.)
- Here I go.
- All right.
(One blow, locked and loaded)
(Bam!)
(As soon as the finger flick signal
was sent,)
(So Min started performing.)
Here we go!
Happy birthday, Suk Jin.
(Happy Birthday, Grandpa Big Nose!)
All right. Here we go.
(His sons are giving him
a palanquin ride on their arms.)
- I wish you a healthy, long life!
- Great!
I wish you health!
- I wish you health!
- I wish you a healthy, long life!
He must be really happy.
- Stay healthy. That's all I want.
- He must be happy.
He must be really happy...
- seeing that he's smiling.
- He's smiling happily.
- Happy birthday!
- Thank you.
- So Min!
- Cheers.
This is amazing.
- Happy birthday.
(Thank you, my boys.)
All I want is
for you to stay healthy.
(The eldest son practiced
juggling toy hammers for this day.)
That's incredible.
He's juggling toy hammers.
Toy hammers?
That's great.
(The second son performs
fire blowing.)
(Their father got drunk
on their cute performances.)
Why would he climb up
on my back suddenly?
- Gosh.
- Happy birthday!
(The father, who just got smacked,
and his children are all happy now.)
This is so good.
I'm happy as long as you're
enjoying this.
Jong Kook, you should demonstrate
some ssireum skills.
- I'll do that.
- His forehead is so red.
- Suk Jin, are you okay?
- It hurts so much.
(The finger flick helped
boost his energy.)
- Oh, gosh. Look at him.
- Suk Jin.
- Look at his forehead.
- Are you all right?
- You got one year older.
- It hurts.
Suk Jin, it looks like
there's a road on your forehead.
- You got one year older.
- I see a road on your forehead.
- It's okay.
- His forehead is so red.
I think you should buy that land
since there's a new road.
It's quite bumpy.
It's okay.
It made a loud noise.
The results are out.
Only the people in the top three
will go out...
to use the tracking chance...
that I told you about earlier.
- Only three of us?
- Yes.
The first place is...
(Who could be the 1st person
to obtain the chance?)
- Se Chan.
- Really?
- Me?
- Se Chan?
- I didn't make many mistakes.
- He was out only once.
- Only once.
- The second place...
(Who are the other 2 people
to get the chance?)
are Kwang Soo and So Min.
- Oh, yes! Okay.
- Okay!
Okay. The youngest members won.
Let's join forces together.
It's been a while!
We can go anywhere we want, right?
- See you later.
- I'll see you later.
- So Min, make sure to find it.
- We should...
After all the eight of you
finish searching,
we'll give the three of them
the tracking chance.
- We must find it.
- It must be us to find it.
- Even if it's not me.
- You can split up.
- Can we start searching?
- I'll go through every place.
Let's search every place.
I didn't go into that place earlier.
We have to win by any means.
I'll go up there.
(Haha is going
into the House of Props.)
"House of Props".
Since it went off there,
it must be somewhere around here.
(Left: House of Props,
Right: Se Chan's previous location)
House of Props.
Right. I'm sure of it.
(Considering the distance, the House
of Props is likely the right place.)
(Surprised)
(He found a hint.)
(He found it unexpectedly
while looking for gold.)
Let me have a look.
Including Suk Jin,
there are all eight of us here.
What does it mean?
Is this... Wait. Am I supposed to
figure it out from this? Wait.
(What does this photo indicate?)
There must be something here.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo and So Min...)
(The House of Games)
I saw a clue being placed here.
(So Min also found a clue.)
"It's darker under the lamp."
(It's darker under the lamp.)
What could this indicate?
The phrase means
that we miss what's...
- right under our noses.
- Under our noses.
"It's darker under the lamp."
(Which place could be
right under their noses?)
Did you find anything?
- Nothing's here, right?
- Nothing.
Did you find anything downstairs?
Yes, I did.
What did you find?
(He ponders for a while.)
"Even walls have ears."
- What a liar.
- How did you know that?
How did you know?
- As if I couldn't tell.
- But it made sense.
It's an idiom you could think of.
It's exactly at your level.
"It's darker under the lamp."
As if.
(Actually, he just doesn't trust
anything that Kwang Soo says.)
Unbelievable.
(But I was telling the truth.)
You're in for a bad day today.
(While wishing each other the worst,
they head to the House of Books.)
You're done for today.
Our teammates are here.
- Jae Suk...
- Don't let them come in.
- First of all...
- Wait!
You're supposed to find the pieces.
No, we were just
solving this puzzle.
(So Min and Se Chan
are solving a puzzle.)
(During the 1st search)
This is odd.
I see pieces to a puzzle
lying around.
I see more over there too.
Anyone can tell
that they're not random.
It's odd, right?
Wait, I think I'm right.
The pieces are scattered
around the place.
We need to solve this puzzle.
What's this?
It must be someone's face.
I think this needs to be solved.
Help me with this.
There are two of them.
When will we finish this?
We need to combine forces.
- We need to solve this.
- Right.
(While solving the puzzle
with Se Chan...)
You're supposed to find the pieces.
- Well...
- That's not right.
(Se Chan hasn't been
much of a help though.)
This will take too long,
so I give up.
(After seeing them solve a puzzle,)
(they leave the scene
feeling relieved.)
It's not worth it.
There's a puzzle here.
(Jae Suk joins in
on solving the puzzle.)
When up high, check down below.
("Up high" lingers
on Kwang Soo's mind.)
(He heads into a building
to find higher ground.)
Must I go someplace higher?
(Will Kwang Soo be able
to find something on higher ground?)
This is a tricky one.
Wait a second.
I think it's doable.
It won't take long.
(Thanks to Jae Suk,
they have someone's body.)
This goes here.
- Isn't this the place?
- Yes.
No way. This is Jae Suk.
- It's you.
- It's Jimi Yu.
It's you.
- It's you.
- It's Jimi Yu.
It's you.
Why is this of Jimi Yu?
- What's this?
- Why am I in the puzzle?
(This tacky man
has the face of Jimi Yu.)
The outfit seemed like Jimi Yu's.
Why didn't you tell us then?
- Hold on a second.
- Weren't you going to share?
- Of course not.
- You would've easily noticed.
Wait a second. I had to make sure.
I wasn't certain.
Where was this taken?
Do you remember this rope?
Of course I don't.
You didn't say anything
when you knew it was you though.
That's not true.
I just wanted to be sure.
- The mouth makes it obvious.
- Right.
(Why has Jimi Yu
been offered as a clue?)
(There must be
a meaning behind this.)
This must be a clue.
It seems like one.
(Big Nose discovered
another puzzle.)
Wait, these eyes...
Is this us? This could be you.
- That must be it.
- It's a face.
I see someone's eyes.
(This puzzle reveals
another person.)
Did I put this in the right place?
(The eyes seem to belong
to a foreigner.)
"When up high, check down below."
(So Min's House)
(He figures that the gold
is somewhere up high.)
"When up high, check down below."
What's this?
Why is this photo here?
(There's a photo of So Min
and Bo Pil in So Min's house.)
(This photo...)
(is one that Jae Suk ignored
after seeing it.)
(Kwang Soo takes it
with him though.)
Is it Bo Pil?
"I'm watching you."
That could be his words.
(I'm watching you.)
(He's always watching the members.)
"It's darker under the lamp."
(It's darker under the lamp.)
(The main director always
sits in front of them.)
(It's darker under the lamp.)
(I'm watching you.)
It's not odd for So Min
to have her photo at her house,
but why would Bo Pil be in one?
(Haha's House)
(Kwang Soo makes an advance.)
(A pick-pocketing attempt)
(If he's right,
Bo Pil would have the gold.)
- What's with him?
- Unbelievable.
(What's going on?)
- What's with him?
- Unbelievable.
What is he doing?
(But just then...)
(He pulls out a jewelry box!)
Did you find the gold?
Is that the gold?
(So Min goes through
the other director's pockets.)
(Kwang Soo dashed in
and found the jewelry box.)
(Anyone who finds the gold
will instantly win.)
(And the race will be over.)
(He hurries out
and checks the contents.)
What on earth?
(You've been fooled.
Find the real jewelry box.)
Seriously?
(A fake jewelry box?)
(In the letter
sent by the village head)
(Beware of the fake jewelry boxes.)
(Kwang Soo was the only one
not aware of the fake boxes.)
What?
Are you kidding me?
(Kwang Soo runs back in
with his hair flying.)
Let's keep solving the puzzle.
- Why...
- What's going on?
- What's wrong?
- Tell me what this is.
(Kwang Soo was fooled
by the staff's trick.)
- What's wrong?
- Tell me what this is.
I don't know what that is.
What's going on?
Stop frisking me.
(He checks the director's pockets
out of disbelief.)
(That's odd...)
Kwang Soo, is this
what you're looking for?
I think it is.
Kwang Soo, is this
what you're looking for?
I think it is.
(I think it is.)
What is it?
Anyone can tell
that's a ssamjang container.
(Kwang Soo's not as stupid
as one thinks.)
- How did you know that?
- How did you know?
- It's obvious.
- You see,
- he's the famous...
- Ssamjang.
- What's that you have?
- What is it?
I think it's an empty box.
The second search is over!
Let's head out for now.
(The 5 who weren't in
the top 3 leave first.)
I think someone's house
was that way.
I doubt it'd be
anywhere near here.
I'm lost.
Will this tracking device
really go off?
"I'm watching you."
(It's why the second tracking chance
must be used wisely.)
(Which house could the gold be in?)
Who on earth is watching us?
"When it's big, have a close look."
If only I knew
whose device went off earlier.
(Se Chan's more at ease...)
(since his tracker
was the one that rang.)
It can't be down there
since mine went off around here.
Can't you tell me the distance
between me and the gold?
(The gold must be near
where he first stood.)
(He decides to stand
close to where he originally stood.)
Kwang Soo, stand down there.
(Se Chan sets a bait.)
Haha was at the House of Dolls
and I was here.
Ji Hyo was in that house...
and Suk Jin was in that one.
No one stood down here though.
Meanwhile, I'll stand here.
(Nonchalantly,
he steps to the spot he decided on.)
- The House of Games?
- I'll stay here.
(Nonchalantly,
he steps to the spot he decided on.)
That can't be the spot.
(It has to be someplace higher.)
Hold on.
When up high...
When it's big...
"When it's big, have a close look."
"I'm watching you."
Could it be a dashcam?
(When up high and when it's big...
This van is always watching them.)
- Here?
- Yes.
Near the House of Dolls.
(He stands somewhere up high.)
(He starts searching
the House of Dolls.)
Could it be inside a doll?
(The House of Dolls)
There's a clue in every house,
but not in this one.
No way!
(He finds a clue
in the passenger seat.)
What's this?
(It's a photo of something
taken up close.)
I found a clue.
(It must be a photo
of where the gold is.)
Will it ring automatically?
(Meanwhile, So Min...)
Right, then...
(She arrives at
the House of Cooking.)
I'll sit here.
(She sits in the center
of the House of Cooking.)
It all looks delicious.
(She only came in here
because she's hungry.)
Please let my device ring.
(So Min, Se Chan, Kwang Soo)
(The three have taken their places.)
(Where the alarm first rang)
(The device closest
to the gold will ring.)
(Where the alarm first rang)
(The device rang!)
(So Min's the closest!)
My device is ringing.
I'm the closest.
You are currently...
the closest to the gold.
(So Min's the closest to the gold.)
(She only sat here out of hunger,
but she got lucky.)
Then...
This means
I'm closest to the gold, right?
To the gold...
(Where the alarm first rang)
(Not so far away,
the second device rang.)
(Where the device rang next)
(So where exactly is the gold?)
Gosh, what a feast.
It must be Suk Jin's birthday meal.
Gosh, it's a feast.
Are we allowed to eat this?
- No way.
- Can we eat this?
This is a work of art.
It's Suk Jin's birthday after all.
Thank you for the meal.
The seaweed soup looks delicious.
- Thank you for the meal.
- This is a feast.
So this is where
I get my birthday meal.
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Suk Jin
My gosh.
I was carried by the members
and got hit as a means to celebrate.
Jong Kook and I...
should bow first.
Right, of course.
Unbelievable.
- Please don't.
- Let's do that.
- Are you serious?
- We should.
He means it.
Don't do it!
Get Suk Jin's wallet, guys.
- We need to get the money gift.
- Suk Jin.
(In hopes of receiving a money gift
from him, they all line up.)
- Happy New Year, Suk Jin.
I wish you good health!
Thanks.
I hope everything you wish for
comes true this year.
You didn't have to make a deep bow.
- This is nice. It's heartwarming.
- Sit down.
Give us the money now.
- Please give me the money now.
- I'll treat you to a good meal.
Where is the money?
I'll treat you to a good meal.
Suk Jin, 2,000 dollars
will be enough for me.
Since I'm younger than Jae Suk,
I can do with 1,800 dollars.
My gosh.
- It looks good.
- The seaweed soup looks good.
- It really...
- Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
We're having a feast
thanks to Suk Jin.
It's nice.
They came early in the morning
to make all these dishes.
This is good.
I usually have a simple meal
on my birthdays. This is amazing.
(As many people's effort was put in,
we wish Big Nose good health.)
I think they prepared a game where
we get splashed with something.
It's Kwang Soo's favorite game.
This is the last mission.
This mission is similar to the game
Suk Jin played as a kid.
- Me?
- It's a modified version...
of Rice Barley Game.
It's called In a Split Second.
(Second mission, In a Split Second)
It's a game where we pick
either barley or rice.
Rice, barley.
Two people will play the game
at a time.
You'll be using your face
instead of your fist.
The opponent will wear
the cylinder cardboards...
and use the pot lids
covered in flour to play defense.
The one playing offense...
can pick either barley or rice...
and put their head in between
the opponent's pot lids.
You need to move your head
up and down.
- You succeed if you don't get hit.
- Oh, up and down?
So in the end,
we'll all be covered in flour.
There's no way we can avoid it.
You can yell out barley
as many times as you want,
but you can yell out rice
only five times.
If you yell rice and avoid getting
hit, you'll earn one point.
If you fail, then your point
will be deducted.
So we can hit however we want
when they yell barley?
This game is meant for Kwang Soo.
- It totally is.
- No, it's not.
What's important in this game
is the lineup.
You can play against
one person only.
You play offense and defense
with the same person,
so the lineup is very important.
He's right.
It's important.
The lineup is important.
Then let's decide with this.
- We can play Game of Wits.
- Game of Wits?
How can we decide the lineup...
- through that?
- Let's just give it a go.
- There's a way.
- 1st place and 2nd place will...
- That's it.
- Oh, really?
Let's get ready.
Start.
(Game of Wits starts.)
One!
- 2!
- The 2 of you can go first.
(The first lineup is ready.)
That's not fair!
- But...
- Isn't this clever?
- We'll play against each other?
- This is how it's done?
- We didn't win the game?
He's such a great MC.
- There's no number 3 and 4?
- Number 1 and 2 can go first.
You two can play
against each other.
Se Chan and Kwang Soo,
please step forward.
- How...
- How do we play?
- The one playing defense...
- They're going to play for real.
And the one playing offense...
They're going to listen to Jae Suk
and play.
They're so naive.
- Flour party
- I can only say rice five times?
- I can only say it 5 times, right?
- Yes, you only get 5 chances.
But if you get hit,
we'll deduct a point.
If you manage to not get hit,
then you'll earn a point.
You need to use all five chances
to finish the game.
- Don't hit when I yell barley.
- I'll stay away from them.
- I can only hit him in this zone?
- That's right.
Let's practice first.
- No, move your head up and down.
- You need to go up and down.
- Try it. Is this how he goes?
- Yes, that's it.
Up and down.
- I hit him like this?
- Doesn't he have to move...
- back and forth?
- You should go forward more.
We tried moving back and forth,
but it wasn't fast enough.
So the ones playing defense
need to play fair.
- If he's in the zone, then...
- Down here?
- Like this?
- I think that'd be better.
- Try it.
- Or maybe not.
- Try going as fast as you can.
- I think that'd be better.
You can go back and forth then.
- Barley.
- So this should work better.
It's just a practice round.
(Se Chan attacks Kwang Soo
without prior consent.)
- It's just a practice round.
- He said barley.
- I can hit him when he says barley.
- Yes, he can.
Barley is equivalent to safe.
You can say rice whenever you want.
- That's right.
- It's safe.
Barley is safe.
You've played Rice Barley Game
before. It's exactly the same.
- You need to go fast.
- Ready, go.
Barley. Barley.
- Is this how I'm supposed to play?
- Wait a minute.
- What is this?
- Yes, it's allowed.
- This is...
- Is this how we play?
It is.
- But this is...
- He should move fast and say rice.
- Say rice and move out fast.
- I need to say rice fast?
- But...
- No, that's not it.
I dodged, but he hit me anyway.
Kwang Soo, you can't ruin the game.
We can't play the game now
because of you.
So if you move up and down,
you can dodge fast.
I think moving up and down
would work better.
He needs to go down fast.
- Let's practice.
- Move up and down.
- Try going down.
- Barley.
- It works.
- This works, Kwang Soo.
- That's it.
- This works.
- That's good.
- Then I'll play now.
- Okay.
(They begin the first round
after figuring out the rules.)
Barley!
That was close.
- "Rice".
- Barley!
Is this how we play?
Hey, you're bad at this game.
- I moved really fast.
- You're bad at this game.
He puts his head right in the spot
for me to hit.
It's like Suk Jin is watching
a variety show on TV.
I love this game.
It's hilarious.
This is perfect
for Suk Jin's birthday.
- He's having fun. He seems happy.
- He loves it.
It reminds me of
the Rice Barley Game I used to play.
I'm having so much fun.
- I need to pass my head through.
- Yes, you need to pass through.
Rice!
(He brutally fails the first attack
and loses a point.)
- That's minus one point.
- You got hit.
- That's right.
- I need to avoid getting hit?
- Of course.
I can play offense later, right?
He's in big trouble.
- You need to move really fast.
- By the way,
you look like the Magic Monkey.
He really does!
(Even its protruding mouth
looks like Se Chan's.)
- Doesn't he look like one?
- He looks like Abu in "Aladdin".
- Do I really look like it?
- Yes.
Let's play, Kwang Soo.
- You need to pass through fast.
- Or you can...
- You need to miss the hit.
- I'll make sure to succeed now.
You need to say rice
after deceiving him with barley.
- Barley. Barley.
- That's it.
- Barley.
- You don't have a knack for it.
- That's it.
- That's how you play.
- Barley. Barley.
- Move fast so he can't hit you.
Barley. Barley. Barley. Rice!
(He makes a fuss
and manages to succeed.)
- Okay!
- Wow.
You have only one chance left.
- Okay.
- All right.
You're quite good.
I can hit him
before he says rice, right?
- Kwang Soo is good at games.
- Barley.
- He's good at them.
- Barley. Barley.
Wait. He hit me when I didn't
even go down. Is this allowed?
- I need to defend too.
- Is this allowed?
- Hey, hey!
- I need to defend, don't I?
- He can't hit me...
- when I didn't attack, can he?
- That's right.
It's because
there's a battery in me.
Se Chan didn't do
anything wrong though.
- Right.
- So this is allowed?
- Of course!
- You're not good at this.
You need to keep saying barley
until you get a chance to say rice.
(He's making a fool of Kwang Soo
without even batting an eye.)
- Barley.
- The space is too tight for him.
Barley.
- Barley.
- Okay.
Barley.
(He gets hit anyway
even if he uses a different rhythm.)
I pity him now.
(Slapping)
Why did you hit me?
Kwang Soo, I was only defending!
(The fool covered in flour
finally explodes.)
I was only defending!
Are you sure this is how we play?
- Why wouldn't you yell out rice?
- He should hit me...
- You went down!
- only when I attack!
You should hit me
after I yell out barley.
How can you hit me
when I didn't yell out anything?
What's the point of saying
barley and rice then?
You need to go down
when you yell out rice.
I didn't yell out anything,
so why did you hit me?
You need to go down
when you yell out rice.
You hit me
when I didn't yell out anything,
so when can I yell out rice?
That's when you go down.
You need to do a better job.
Are you Toshio or something?
I'm going to start now.
(Be calm.)
Barley.
- That's how you should play.
- Yes, go slowly and get the rhythm.
There you go.
He's such a fool.
- It's tense.
- Barley!
(He yells out barley
after calmly breathing.)
Gosh, I should've yelled out rice!
I should've yelled out rice!
- I thought too hard.
- Why didn't you yell out rice?
I thought too hard.
Why didn't you yell out rice?
It was a battle against myself.
I gave you a signal this time.
- Yell out rice already.
- It was the right speed for rice.
I should've yelled out rice.
You have only one chance.
- You have only one chance.
- If Se Chan does well...
(Flinching)
Wait. Don't give me signals.
Don't give me signals.
You have only one chance.
Barley. Barley.
- You should've said rice.
- Rice!
All right!
Kwang Soo's final score
is minus one.
- Minus one?
- Yes.
- He did well.
- It's not easy, but he did well.
I should go down at once. You...
(Collecting all the flour
as he's desperate to get revenge)
That's enough already.
Kwang Soo is gathering
all the flour.
- You can't put your arms down.
- Okay.
He looks so scary.
Gosh, if you get hit by those...
- I mean...
- You can only start when I'm ready.
- He's so determined.
- He is.
- Lift your arms a little.
- He's just going to hit Se Chan.
He's clenching his teeth.
- Look at his face.
- I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, but he's gone mad.
- Look at my finger.
- I can see it.
- You're okay, right?
- Yes.
(Will Kwang Soo who's gone mad
be able to get his revenge?)
- This is...
- He can go fast if he wants to.
- Look at him. He's good.
- He's twerking.
- Play until your energy runs out.
Rice!
(He easily scores 1 point.)
(He scores another point
right away!)
- I'm going to go again.
- He's good!
Rice!
- Wait.
- What's wrong?
- Why aren't you doing anything?
- I have two more chances.
(He couldn't even swing once
and lost 3 chances in a row.)
Why aren't you doing anything?
- You should yell out barley too.
- I will.
- I will yell out barley.
- You should say barley a few times.
- Okay. I'll say barley first.
- You can't only yell out rice.
- You want me to say barley first?
- You should say it a few times.
Barley, barley, and then rice?
Got it.
- Twerking.
- "Twerking"?
(The twerking master
gets ready to play.)
You're good, Se Chan.
That's so hot.
It looks like a skit
from "Comedy Big League".
(Shaking)
There's not enough space here.
Sir, there's not enough space here.
- Should I make more space?
- Yes.
Please make some more space.
He's dying to hit Se Chan.
He doesn't care about the game.
He just wants to hit Se Chan.
Rice!
You dodged again? Hold on a second.
(There's only one chance left,
but he's far from hitting Se Chan.)
- That's good!
- Se Chan earned four points.
- I earned four points.
- Kwang Soo hasn't hit him once.
Rice!
It hasn't even started!
(It hasn't even started!)
You brat. It hasn't even started!
- Rice!
- How could you play right away?
- I'm done.
- Good job!
- We'll accept that.
- For real?
All right!
Se Chan won five points.
Well done, Se Chan.
(Se Chan wins with 5 points.)
- That was a neat finish.
- Well done, Kwang Soo.
I can't hit as fast as I want to.
- I can't hit fast.
- It's Ji Hyo versus So Min now.
Hang on. I want to practice first.
That's a good attitude.
- She's fast.
- She is.
It's not that easy to hit.
- Right.
- I'm serious.
Let's begin now.
- It's nerve-racking.
- Yes, it must be.
It's nerve-racking. Barley.
- You need to find the right timing.
- I should've said rice.
Barley.
(They seem to be having a good time
for now.)
You can't go down with So Min.
- She can't help it.
- It can't be helped.
- It's only natural.
- I didn't say anything!
- It can't be helped.
(Ji Hyo just smacked her.)
I'm so sorry, So Min!
(Grabbing)
Don't give up, So Min!
- So Min.
- I didn't mean it. I'm so sorry.
(Ji Hyo expresses how sorry she is
by applying flour on So Min.)
- I'm so sorry.
- Ji Hyo means it.
Ji Hyo is really sorry.
- You'll be covered in it anyway.
- It's okay.
It's hilarious.
Rice!
Good job.
(So Min succeeds in her attack
while Ji Hyo still feels sorry.)
You should keep it up.
I shouldn't meet her eyes.
Barley! Barley!
Barley!
- Ji Hyo.
- Aren't you just beating her up?
- She keeps...
- Ji Hyo keeps beating her up.
- Don't do that!
- She's so harsh.
She hits So Min all she wants
and hugs her to say sorry.
So Min went down
as she yelled out barley.
- Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo followed her and hit her.
It's because I keep losing strength
to keep my arms up.
If she gets hit...
It's because I keep losing strength.
(She attacks So Min mercilessly
before she loses her strength.)
(Nervous)
Rice!
(So Min has earned 2 points so far!)
(Smack)
What was that?
- You just hit her?
- Why did you hit her?
Weren't you going down?
- Song Jeoktoma is back!
- You weren't going down?
I thought she was going down.
- That's so cunning of you.
- Why did you hit her?
She just smacked her.
(She just smacked her.)
She kept mouthing something.
She kept doing that,
so I thought she'd go down.
- Song Jeoktoma, you're impressive.
- I thought she was going down.
- Song Jeoktoma.
- It's my turn now.
- Run, Song Jeoktoma.
- Look at this, Ji Hyo.
- You need to coat them thoroughly.
(Hitting)
(What was that?)
(Delinquent Ji Hyo
kicks Kwang Soo in the head.)
She kicked his head. Wow, she...
She kicks his head now.
Isn't the purpose of this game
to get flour on our faces?
She precisely hit
the crown of his head.
- It didn't hurt though.
- I think...
Kwang Soo's been hit a lot. Ji Hyo
must have a lot of experience too.
- She's tough.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Good.
Why do you always go through
the pockets when you find a jacket?
I was looking for a hint.
- I was looking for a hint.
- He has a habit of stealing.
- I thought there'd be a hint.
- I mean...
I was just checking.
You don't even hide
and go through her pockets.
- No, that's not true.
- He has issues.
- Let's play.
- Barley.
- Wait, so when I say barley...
- You need to go down fast.
Barley.
- She's quite slow.
- Put down your head fast.
So Min is quite slow.
- Rice!
- That's it!
You only need to say it fast.
- Put down your head fast.
- So Min can't catch up.
You only need to say it confidently.
(Will she say it or not?)
Barley!
- Barley!
- Wait a minute.
- She can't hit her like that.
- You...
- Barley!
- Wait a minute.
- So Min hit her like this.
- You can't go down with me.
That's not true.
- She hit her like that.
- That's not true.
- She followed me down.
- No!
- She definitely followed me down.
- How can the game proceed...
if she keeps going down Ji Hyo?
No. That's not true.
Don't hit the back of her head!
- That's not true.
- She hit the back of her head.
- So Min, you...
- You hit me right here.
- No, I didn't.
- That's not true.
- That's not cool, So Min.
How could you... Gosh.
- I won't go down from here.
- From here?
From here?
(The game resumes.)
- That's it. Stay there.
- Stay here.
You need to be in the spot
where her head passes through.
Just go down fast.
(Will she say it or not?)
This is fun.
Rice!
(She succeeds
in the delayed attack.)
Wow, she played with So Min.
- Wow, she used a fake move.
- "Rice!"
I totally fell for it.
That was really well-played.
- We should play like that.
- She's good at this game.
I think she hit my ear too hard.
It's time for me and Haha to play.
(The Precious Sister's game
ended on a good note.)
- It's time for me and Haha to play.
- Okay.
(Round 3, Jae Suk versus Haha)
It's all about speed.
- It's...
- He's at it again.
Hang on. I'm not ready yet.
He's got a good posture.
That's good.
- You need to go down really fast.
- Of course.
(Will he be able to
show what he got this time?)
- You need to go down really fast.
- Of course.
- He passes through so fast.
- That's it.
Here we go.
- Okay.
- Can I start?
- He has a bad back though.
- Right.
- I'll start now.
- His back must hurt then.
Rice! Rice!
Wait a minute.
(Rice! Rice!)
(He's covered in flour
after yelling out rice twice.)
Are you okay?
Jae Suk.
You only yelled out rice twice,
and you're covered in flour already.
You're covered all over with flour
after saying rice twice.
He yelled out rice
only twice, right?
How could he be completely covered
in flour after only saying it twice?
He looks the same as Kwang Soo now.
- What happened?
- I got it now.
- You said it's all about speed.
- Okay, I got it now.
- I should calm down.
- He must've been hit on the nose.
- You should calm down.
- He was hit on the nose.
(He lost two chances with no gain.)
Here we go. Barley.
Haha doesn't hit him
when he says barley.
Barley. You're not hitting me
when I say barley.
I don't think he'll hit you
even if you say rice at this rate.
Barley!
"Rice."
Barley! Barley! Darn you...
(The guy who's not good at games
is rich with flour now.)
- Hey.
- You basically asked for it.
- You went down at the right timing.
- Haha hit you at the right timing.
- You put your head there to be hit.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- It was really rhythmical.
You failed twice already.
Twice?
(He has three chances now.)
Barley! Rice! Rice! Rice!
(Barley, rice, rice, rice)
Didn't he cheat?
- My goodness.
- Didn't he cheat?
That was hilarious.
- You put your head there to be hit!
- What's wrong?
- You're terrible at games.
- You're not fast at all, Jae Suk.
He got the lowest score?
Yes, he got minus five points.
That's the lowest.
Wait, that's Big Nose!
- That's Big Nose!
- He turned into Mr. Big Nose.
His nose is attached
to his glasses.
How did only his nose get hit?
- Only his nose was hit.
- Right, only his nose was hit.
Your nose...
If you play defense well,
- you still have a chance.
- Of course.
Haha has gained weight recently,
so he might not be as fast.
(Haha is not as fast because
he recently gained weight.)
- You're so ugly.
- It's scary, right?
Rice!
(He suddenly yelled out rice.)
(After shaking him up,
Haha succeeds in his attack.)
- That's acceptable.
- Is this allowed?
- Of course it's acceptable.
- Rice!
- There he goes again.
- What was that?
- Focus, Jae Suk!
- Don't be fooled by what he says.
Haha is using an advanced skill.
(The man with a dirty mustache
keeps flinching.)
(Big Nose is tensed up.)
Rice.
- Darn it.
- That was amazing.
- Keep going!
- I'm going to hit him this time.
(He gets his hips working again.)
(Hitting)
Jae Suk.
- No! You can't do that!
- What's wrong with you?
(A fight breaks out
between the men covered in flour.)
What's wrong with these guys?
No, you can't do this! Stop!
My gosh, he's so annoying.
Stop it!
Jae Suk is upset!
Jae Suk is upset.
Haha knows when to be annoying.
- You should hit him at least once.
- I should do that.
You can't let him take five points.
(Haha starts
teasing Jae Suk again.)
- He must be really annoyed.
- That's cute though.
(Haha uses all his skills
to annoy Jae Suk.)
He's so annoying.
(Darn him.)
He's getting into the beat.
(Crazy beat
that drives Jae Suk mad)
- This battle...
- It's exciting!
(DJ Bachelor Ghost)
(Getting into the beat)
Jae Suk
is getting into the beat also!
It's actually exciting.
I want to join them too.
(They're just excited.)
- Rice.
- Darn it.
(Jae Suk allows the counterattack
while getting into the beat.)
(It's Haha's complete victory!)
Here we go.
This is so upsetting.
- Goodness.
- Here we go.
My goodness.
I think we got
enough footage for the show.
You are right.
I can't wait for this big match.
My goodness.
- It isn't easy, right?
- If I am not careful,
I will hit him with my wrists.
You need to win.
The rules.
- He is fast.
- He is good.
He is fast. Suk Jin is fast.
- Didn't I hear a crack?
- He is fast.
He is like
a long-headed grasshopper.
- He is fast.
- All right.
He greets people so well.
He ran out of energy.
His back hurts now.
- He ran out of energy.
- He is dizzy.
- It's like he has cupulolithiasis.
- He ran out of energy.
All right.
Rice.
(He succeeded
to land the first attack!)
So that's how you play.
- He got covered in flour.
- He has a nice tactic.
Why are you covered in flour
when you dodged?
Barley.
(He got flour on his big nose.)
(Giggling)
The daughter-in-law is happy.
- It's so much fun.
- Suk Jin is aging!
(Seeing her father-in-law's struggle
makes So Min laugh.)
Suk Jin is getting white hair.
Mother-in-law will be happy.
Long life, health, and blessing!
(She enjoys
her father-in-law's antics so much.)
He is so charming.
The daughter-in-law is happy.
- That's my father-in-law.
- Three times remain, right?
Okay. That's it.
It won't be easy.
(It seems impossible
to pass through Jong Kook's hands.)
Isn't this too narrow?
Okay, okay.
(He picks up his courage
and passes through the hands.)
- You didn't say.
- You need to say "Rice".
You didn't say.
You need to say "Rice".
- You just passed through.
- I didn't say it.
My goodness.
- It hurts.
- Father-in-law, good luck.
Okay. Look at this. This is speed.
This is speed.
He is bound to get fooled.
(Jong Kook doesn't get fooled.)
- Rice.
- Father-in-law.
Father-in-law.
Let him go now.
(Suk Jin's final score is
minus 1 point.)
Let's switch sides.
Okay.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
Jong Kook will go this time.
- Okay.
Jong Kook's tights will turn white.
My goodness.
(Putting on)
Seeing him makes my heart ache.
Seriously. He is living a cool life.
Suk Jin became so old.
- I don't know what to do.
- Seriously.
His hair turned gray.
My goodness.
How did that happen?
- Let's go.
- We began, right?
- Yes.
- Let's begin.
Rice.
He is fast.
He did it twice.
I bet he won't hit Jong Kook once.
Suk Jin, isn't this too narrow?
Rice.
(Hitting)
(He ends up hitting Jong Kook
after getting fooled many times.)
- Jong Kook!
- Hey!
- It's Suk Jin's birthday.
- It's his birthday.
It's Suk Jin's birthday.
- You hit me in the eye!
- It's Suk Jin's birthday.
- I am so annoyed!
- Jong Kook.
(He hit Jong Kook
for the 1st time in 11 years.)
Jong Kook.
- I am so annoyed!
- It's Suk Jin's birthday.
- You can't do that.
I had to hit him once.
- I had to hit him once.
- For goodness' sake.
I had to hit him once.
To the winners
of the second mission,
Se Chan, So Min, Haha,
and Jong Kook,
we will give the tracking chance.
- Okay.
(The winners of each round
get the tracking chance.)
What could it mean?
I don't understand the hint.
What could be similar to the photo?
I am 100 percent sure...
that the gold is moving.
(The gold is moving?)
Listen. In the beginning,
I heard the sound when I stood here.
(He was the closest to the gold
out of 8 members!)
(The gold was located
somewhere close.)
(Se Chan)
(During the 2nd tracking,)
(he situated himself nearby
to narrow down the location.)
(But he wasn't the closest
to the gold.)
(That's why Se Chan thinks
the gold is moving.)
If my device doesn't go off,
that means the gold is moving.
The gold.
I will stand here.
(Who is the closest to the cold?)
I hope it goes off.
(So Min, Jong Kook, Haha,
and Se Chan)
The device went off.
You aren't the closest to the gold.
It's moving.
(The device went off...)
Mine is going off, right?
(at Jong Kook's location.)
Look at this.
(The gold is somewhere near here.)
I need to look closely.
(Meanwhile, So Min went
to Jae Suk's House.)
What?
Isn't this the background
of Jae Suk's puzzle?
I think it is.
(So Min spent nearly a day
on the puzzle.)
(She resumed working on the puzzle
during the 3rd search.)
Where is this place?
(Is the background...)
(Jae Suk's House?)
There must be something in here.
(So Min begins to search
Jae Suk's House.)
What? Look at this.
(And...)
(Jae Suk quietly
resumes his search.)
- Can I begin now?
- Yes.
(It's the last search.
Who will take the gold?)
This is... Who is he?
Who is he?
He is American, right?
Jong Kook would know.
He is American.
(He seems like an American.)
Who is he?
Can we use the internet?
(Can we use the Internet?)
Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook!
- Yes?
- Did you find something?
- It's an American.
- An American?
- We don't know who he is.
Why is there an American?
You know Americans well.
- Why is there an American?
- It's an American.
Who is he?
(He somehow became
the expert of Americans.)
What?
- Who is he?
Isn't he... No, that's not it.
- Is he a politician?
- I think so.
He has to be a politician.
That tie...
Is he a Republican?
(He doesn't know what that is.)
I mean,
politicians wear ties
of certain colors.
What? Who is he?
The puzzle...
The puzzle points to someone.
(He searches House of Books
for more clues.)
(Staring)
Hold on.
(Hold on.)
What is this?
(One DVD is upside down.)
(It has a number sticker.)
Hold on. What is this?
(There is a number sticker
on the "Les Miserables" DVD.)
What is this?
Number six.
(He finds another DVD
with the number 6.)
Number three, "The Way Home".
(He keeps getting
DVDs with stickers.)
Number four.
(Jae Suk appears.)
- Se Chan.
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
- There are numbers.
- What?
I found these.
I am missing numbers 1 and 2.
What is this?
(He has numbers 3, 4, 5, 6.)
"House underneath is"?
What does this mean?
We aren't supposed to combine
the first letters, right?
"House underneath is".
- "House underneath is"?
- "House underneath is".
("House", "Underneath", "Is",
and underlined "Gold")
Jae Suk.
We are missing numbers 1 and 2.
It's underneath someone's house.
- It's underneath someone's house.
- You are right.
It's underneath someone's house.
Everyone has a house.
The missing letters could be
"Suk Jin" or "Jae Suk".
- It's underneath someone's house.
- That must be the case.
"It's darker under the lamp."
(Kwang Soo is hung up on the hint
about the lamp.)
(He finds a hint in the duvet.)
"A wheeled house"?
(A wheeled house)
"A wheeled house"? The van?
(Does the wheeled house mean
House of Dolls?)
Kwang Soo, where are you going?
Kwang Soo, come here.
- What?
- Where are you going?
Go to the car.
I found a hint that read
"A wheeled house".
- Okay, okay.
- The car.
(Obsessed with the gold,
Kwang Soo arrives in no time.)
Suk Jin, this is
the only wheeled house.
- This is the only one.
- "A wheeled house".
- Is that what the hint says?
- Yes.
- What?
- Suk Jin.
- We are close to winning.
- What is this?
- Who is this?
- Jae Suk,
- who is this?
- Who is this?
Jimmy Carter.
- Who is Jimmy Carter?
- A former US president.
(The 39th president of the US,
Jimmy Carter)
- Why is Jimmy Carter here?
- I don't know.
Jimmy. Is it Ji Suk Jin?
The puzzle I saw earlier showed
Jimi Yu.
What is Jimi Yoo doing here?
(The puzzles showed Jimi Yu...)
(and Jimmy Carter.)
- Jimmy Carter. Jimi Yu.
- Jimmy.
Jimi Yu. Jimmy Carter.
There must be something
between the dolls.
There are more dolls in the trunk.
(The photo does seem to show...)
Here.
(a part of this car.)
Kwang Soo,
you need to look underneath.
(The hint said,
"When up high, check down below.")
(Is the van
the wheeled house from the hint?)
(In that case,
is the complete hint...)
("House of Dolls,
underneath is gold"?)
I don't see anything.
No?
Is there another wheeled house...
- other than House of Dolls?
- "A wheeled house".
Gosh.
Jimmy. "House underneath is".
(Jae Suk and So Min combine
the hints.)
- I know. Jimi.
- Jimi.
Is it underneath my house?
(Is the gold
underneath Jae Suk's House?)
(After a few words,
he runs to his house.)
My room. Jimi Yu.
Jimmy. "House underneath is".
(Is the gold hidden
at Jimi Yu's House?)
What does it mean?
Jae Suk!
What?
What? What is it?
- I am so shocked.
- Why?
Jimi?
- And? "House underneath is"?
- Jimi Yu.
Yes.
Jimi Yu's House.
If you take out Yu...
It's "Jimmy's House,
underneath is gold".
Who is Jimmy?
Jimmy Jib, underneath is gold.
"Jib" is a homonym for "House".
Jimmy Jib, the camera.
(Jimmy Jib)
"Jib" is a homonym for "House".
Jimmy Jib, the camera.
I became so shocked just now.
('House" that is different
from other houses.)
(All the houses aren't the same.)
"When up high, check down below."
(When up high, check down below.)
(It always looks down
from a higher place.)
"I'm always watching you."
(I'm always watching you.)
(It always watches the members.)
(They didn't recognize
the details of the Jimmy Jib.)
What is this?
(The members were filmed
using the Jimmy Jib.)
Bo Pil and So Min?
(It was actually a photo
of the Jimmy Jib.)
It could be among the members.
(Something that watches everything
among the members)
(Its name is Jimmy...)
(and it's a wheeled house.)
Is there another one
that is hidden somewhere?
(The reason why the gold could move)
(The 1st search)
(Then the Jimmy Jib moved
for filming.)
(During the 2nd search,
So Min's device went off.)
(It was right behind Jong Kook!)
(The gold is hidden
at the Jimmy Jib.)
"Jib" is a homonym for "House".
Jimmy Jib, the camera.
(Even as they iterated the hints,
they had no clue.)
I became so shocked just now.
(The gold is at the Jimmy Jib!)
It's the Jimmy Jib!
- There must be something.
- What?
(Everyone learned about the location
around the same time.)
(Jae Suk arrives 1st.)
Under the Jimmy Jib.
Where is it?
(He found the jewelry box.)
(The 1st person to touch the gold
will have it for oneself.)
- Did someone take it?
- Who took it?
Isn't this the end?
(Did someone take the gold?)
- "I will take it."
(One of the members)
Who took it?
Who is it?
Let me see the handwriting.
I think it's Jae Suk.
It isn't me.
Jong Kook was here earlier.
But I didn't find anything.
- I can't believe it.
- Someone took it.
(The gold disappeared.)
Someone found the gold already.
- Really?
- Let's go to the final location.
I am getting goosebumps.
Who is it?
(Someone is fooling the members
after taking the gold.)
For goodness' sake.
It's so scary.
- It isn't me. One of them took it.
- That's right.
Someone is acting.
It's so scary.
Someone has the gold right now.
I wonder who took it.
It's so scary. Someone is acting.
The gold rings were hidden...
at the Jimmy Jib.
That's right.
The mottos in the houses pointed
to the Jimmy Jib.
Had you gathered all the DVDs,
the letters would have made,
"Jimmy Jib, underneath is gold."
But you didn't find the 1st 2 DVDs.
- We found them at the end.
But someone found the gold first.
- Seriously.
- I am impressed.
Who found it?
This member even left a note
because he or she found it early.
- That's incredible.
- It's 1 of the 3.
- Who is it?
- Against our expectations,
- Did this member find it fast?
this member found it fast.
I hope it's a member of our team.
This member found the gold
before anyone else...
and acted throughout the race.
(Found the gold before anyone else
and acted throughout the race)
(The winner's team will decide...)
(the candidates for the penalty.)
(Who is the winner of the day?)
Congratulations, Kim Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
My goodness.
Congratulations, Kim Jong Kook.
(My goodness.)
(The winner of the day is
Kim Jong Kook.)
- How did you find it?
- How did Jong Kook do that?
(The first hint was given
only to Suk Jin.)
(Jong Kook ruled out
the regular houses.)
(As he would with dumbbells,
he lifted up his deductive skills.)
It's "I'm always watching you."
"I'm always watching you."
A camera.
(During the first search,
he pointed to a camera.)
It's always watching us.
"When up high, check down below."
"I'm always watching you."
"When it's big, have a close look."
Isn't it the Jimmy Jib?
Where is the Jimmy Jib today?
Is it here?
"It's darker under the lamp."
I think it's the Jimmy Jib.
I will stand here.
There is no reason
for the Jimmy Jib to be here.
Mine is going off, right?
"It's darker under the lamp."
(Then he began to search
the Jimmy Jib.)
There it is.
My goodness.
(He became flustered too.)
My goodness!
How did this happen?
(He succeeded to acquire
3 gold rings.)
(The bright color of the gold...)
Hold on. But...
(made him grin from ear to ear.)
A piece of paper.
(Then Jong Kook asked
for a piece of paper.)
Hold on. They would recognize
my handwriting.
"I will take it." I won.
(He used his left hand
to fool the members.)
(Thus, he even left a message.)
- Who is he?
(He went to different places
and meddled in people's business.)
You guys are so mean.
You gave them such a difficult hint.
Aren't you going to tell
Kwang Soo and Suk Jin?
Suk Jin and Kwang Soo need
to make an effort.
Suk Jin likes having hopes.
Hope keeps him going,
so I will give it to him.
(He kept quiet
to give Suk Jin hope.)
- I made the right choice, right?
- Suk Jin.
(He gave Suk Jin
the happiness of hope.)
He is so annoying.
- He is so annoying.
The hints were "A wheeled house"
and Jimmy Carter.
I was like, "It's so easy."
My goodness.
(Here is the gold.)
Okay.
My goodness.
(The three men got
friendship rings.)
- They got friendship rings.
- That's too bad.
- The rings are shiny.
- I am jealous.
Why couldn't you tell
from all those hints?
We couldn't tell.
You guys are so slow.
I knew it was the Jimmy Jib.
- I knew it was over there.
- For goodness' sake.
This is frustrating.
- We will reveal the penalty.
- Okay.
The penalty of the day is making
a video for Suk Jin's birthday.
Two members will film a fun video to
Turbo's "Happy Birthday to You"...
so that it's
a minute and 30 seconds long.
- That's so much work.
- After the episode airs,
it will be revealed
on Running Man's social media.
- On Running Man's social media?
- It's so much work.
You have to come up
with an idea too.
- It should go...
- It's so much work.
to someone who finds it annoying.
- I want Haha to do it.
- I think Ji Hyo should do it.
Haha.
- I am okay with it.
- We should see her dance.
It would be funny if Ji Hyo does it.
Ji Hyo would be a good choice.
- But I don't have an idea.
- Do you want to do it or not?
I wouldn't mind it.
Then let's have Ji Hyo do it.
Haha, do you want to do it or not?
I don't want to do it.
Let's have one who wants to do it
and one who doesn't.
That's a good idea.
- Besides,
- The two of you.
it will be convenient since you live
in the same neighborhood.
We made our choice. Haha and Ji Hyo.
Okay.
- Okay.
- I don't know how to do it.
I can't wait to see it.
I don't have any ideas.
Ji Hyo, let's film it here.
(They have no intention
to celebrate Suk Jin's birthday.)
Music, cue.
(They begin filming
in a strange way.)
(What is up
with her facial expression?)
(She walks over...)
(and stares into the distance
in this strange video.)
(The video will be uploaded
to social media and YouTube.)
We did it.
(Evil spirits are rampant
in the Running Dynasty.)
(The people are suffering
because of the evil spirits.)
(Why is Yang Se Chan the king?)
Make them kneel.
(Due to the tyrannical king
and treacherous subjects,)
I feel so victimized.
(the nation is in a bad state.)
(Jang Dong Yoon, Keum Sae Rok)
(Park Sung Hoon, and Kim Dong Jun)
(Then...)
(evil spirits enter the palace.)
- An evil spirit.
- Evil spirits have a mission.
(The evil spirits who want
to take over the country...)
(versus the ones who want
to save the country)
Some are born as evil spirits.
(What will become
of the Running Dynasty?)
(Records of the Running Dynasty,
the Appearance of the Evil Spirits)