- Hello, you're here. - Hello.
(A cafe in Gyeonggi Province in May)
- Hi. - Hello.
- Are you all right? - How are you feeling?
- He sprained his ankle. - I've never...
(Jong Kook sprained his ankle during a soccer mission.)
- Is it swollen? - sprained my ankle...
this way before.
Is it swollen or not?
(Luckily, it doesn't seem serious.)
The swelling isn't that bad.
Let's not play soccer in this show.
Jong Kook just gets carried away.
(He can't hold back his desire to win when he sees a ball.)
In Running Man, I think a day like today is a good chance for me.
Because Jong Kook is injured?
(The weak's vain hope)
- Today is the day. - I just can't help it.
Today...
I don't know why we're being like this. I know it's bad.
(Instinct to be cunning)
- But I just can't help it. - His upper body is just fine.
(He can handle them with his upper body.)
It's not like I'm dying.
In fact, it's not a good chance.
(In the end)
You just can't beat him.
(Either way, he's unbeatable.)
This is crazy.
You've got an invitation card.
(Running Man received a mysterious invitation.)
- What is it? - Would you like to open it?
- Isn't So Min coming today? - So Min is coming.
(By the way, So Min's coming back today.)
She's coming back today.
So Min planned something.
What is she doing now?
(They all suspect who sent the invitation.)
- What is So Min up to? - Suk Jin.
- What's wrong with your face? - What about my face?
(Out of the blue)
Did you get hit or something?
What's going on?
(Suk Jin looks puffy.)
I'm tired from yesterday.
I was sound asleep on my way here.
"What's wrong with your face?" That's hilarious.
(Out of nowhere)
- What happened to you? - I mean...
(Why is your face so puffy?)
The thing is...
Earlier today, Suk Jin...
(Jae Suk didn't say anything until the shoot began.)
kept talking about his face, but Jae Suk didn't care.
And he suddenly started talking about it as the camera is turned on.
(As soon as the camera turns on, Jae Suk starts attacking Suk Jin.)
That's what I do.
- Hey. - Right. He didn't say anything.
(The pro's attitude)
Why would I talk when the camera is off?
You're up anyway.
- That's right. - I know.
You're so healthy.
- I sprang up in my car. - Okay.
(Showing off his health)
(He's glad Suk Jin's healthy.)
It says invitation.
(They read the invitation.)
"Hi, guys. I've got a life-changing chance."
"There's this fantastic land where I can dig up huge diamonds."
(Hi, guys. I've got a life-changing chance.)
"The town even has the Immortal Heart..."
(The town even has the Immortal Heart,)
"which is the world's most precious diamond."
(the world's most precious diamond.)
"Isn't it amazing? Let's go fall for the charm of the diamond together."
- What is this? - It's like So Min's handwriting.
It's like So Min's handwriting.
What? Hang on. What are you talking about?
(What?)
- It's obvious that it's typed out. - It's just typed out.
(It's obvious that it's typed out.)
Just let it go.
His eyes are all puffy. Look at his eyes.
(He's talking without thinking.)
Everything he says is fake.
(You're unbelievable.)
- Seriously. - What's your true face?
- I got goosebumps. - Oh, dear.
(Embarrassed)
The person who invited you guys is waiting in there.
- Really? - Isn't it So Min?
- Isn't it So Min? - You'll find out once you get in.
(Pretending not to hear him)
It must be So Min.
- Bo Pil wouldn't tell us yet. - Stop it.
(Why would you keep saying that?)
We know that already.
It'd be strange if I pretended not to know it.
You don't have to pretend not to know about it.
(You don't have to say it.)
Just don't talk about it.
It's stranger that you said it's So Min's handwriting.
(It was typed out.)
It gave me goosebumps too.
(They head to where the mysterious person is waiting.)
I'm still half asleep.
This feels awkward.
It feels like I'm starting all over again.
It feels like the first day I joined Running Man.
(Who's the mysterious woman waiting for the members?)
What should I do? I'm so nervous.
(So Min is back.)
Why am I feeling nervous? My heart is pounding.
(The members are slowly coming to So Min.)
(And So Min waits for them.)
They're here.
(She tucks her hair behind her ears.)
This is it. So Min, why are you sitting with your back against us?
(Pleased)
- So Min. - Hey, So Min.
Why are you sitting with your back against us?
(As soon as they get here,)
So Min.
(she goes over the top.)
(What are you doing?)
- So Min. - Hey, So Min.
Have you been doing well?
(We missed you, So Min.)
So Min's back.
- It's So Min. - So Min.
(They are happy to meet again.)
Hey, So Min.
- You look much better now. - You look healthier.
(So Min returns safely.)
- You look a lot better now. - You look better.
(So Min looks more cheerful and healthier than ever.)
She really does.
- Hey. - You did something.
Why do you keep drawing your hair back over your ears?
Women become prettier when they are sick.
(I want to look pretty.)
- Is that it? - Sure.
- Hello. Hi, Ji Hyo. - It's nice to see you again.
- Have you been doing well? - Yes.
(Everyone's glad to see So Min again.)
So Min is back.
It's so good to see you again.
There are celebrities here. They all are celebrities.
(So Min's hyped up as soon as she returns.)
- You guys look like celebrities. - So Min.
Your hair has grown a lot.
Your face has got smaller.
- I lost a lot of weight. - Your hair has grown a lot.
- You have hollow cheeks. - All right then.
You should say hello to our viewers first.
(Officially)
- It's been two months. - It's been a long time.
(So Min returns almost after two months.)
It feels really awkward.
(It feels new.)
I didn't know there were so many cameras.
- It's always been like this. - You just took a short break.
- He's right. - What are you talking about?
So Min, you know we won't be welcoming you like this for long.
(Cold)
I don't want you to pay attention to me.
(She still finds their attention awkward.)
- I feel really uncomfortable. - Just say hello then.
Hello, everyone. Well...
- Say hello to them. - Hello.
(Awkward)
- What are you doing? - She feels awkward.
- She's feeling awkward. - Just say it.
If you feel awkward like that...
What's wrong with her?
Those who are watching us...
(Even the viewers find it awkward.)
might want to change the channel.
- They'd feel awkward too. - Right.
Hello, viewers. I'm Jeon So Min.
(She says hello cheerfully.)
I heard So Min has changed...
- the course of her life. - Is that true?
I'm born again.
(You're right.)
Like how?
(She's born again.)
- I think... - It'd be fun to watch it.
- It won't last for long though. - That's not true.
(Certain)
What's the change in your mental attitude?
(What's the change in her mental attitude?)
People don't change easily.
I realized the importance of my acquaintances.
(While I was resting)
Now I can tell who truly loves...
and cares about me.
Is that it?
(Are you sure you've changed?)
What has changed? You just sound terrifying.
(What on earth has changed?)
- You mean people around you? - Even in this group.
In this small group, there are people who care about me,
(She created a death list while resting.)
- and... - She has a list.
- She has her own rankings. - I told you before.
She's got Death Note.
I checked who called or texted me how many times.
(She checked who called or texted her how many times.)
- Hey. - The frequency doesn't show...
how much we care about you.
We just call you on a periodic basis...
(Those who feel guilty give excuses.)
only when we are truly worried about you.
- Sure. - It's different.
I also remember...
(Detailed)
who called me a lot at first and let up later on.
- I won't mention the names though. - She's specific.
(She holds grudges.)
Look at her.
(Staring)
- It's interesting. - I know.
A certain someone called me less and less as time went by.
Are you looking at that person?
(So Min's eyes are fixed on that certain someone.)
By the way,
Se Chan said the other day...
(By the way...)
So Min did all five things women do that give men the wrong idea...
(So Min did all 5 things women do...)
- I saw it. - to him.
(that give men the wrong idea.)
You saw it? What did you think?
So Min did all five things to me.
She did all those things.
She smiles at me,
(So Min did all five things that give men the wrong idea.)
and remembers little things about me.
- That's why I got the wrong idea. - He's right.
(Se Chan argued that's why he ended up getting the wrong idea.)
When did I do those things to you?
(Playing dumb)
- We can find it. - You're mistaken.
(Their opinions conflict.)
- Everything was filmed. - I never did those things.
You did all those things while shooting Running Man.
(The victim thinks it's unfair.)
- So Min, you did those things. - What I did is...
just smile at him.
(So Min insists she only smiled and Se Chan took it wrong.)
But from his point of view,
I must look like this.
I've never given him a big smile once.
(And...)
- This is driving me crazy. - The thing is,
he must look at me through a filter or something.
(Has Se Chan been deluding himself all along?)
(Video assistant referee)
Hey, are you confident?
(Sometimes, she acted like a big sister.)
- What do you call your boyfriend? - Chu.
(Sometimes, she acted like a girlfriend.)
(Little by little, Se Chan got used to this forced romance.)
Se Chan.
She's cute.
(So Min calls Se Chan's name in a nasal voice.)
She's doing an impression of Jeon Do Yeon.
(The video assistant referee proves Se Chan's innocence.)
Did you ask Se Chan,
"Are there any guys like you?"
(5th place, when she says, "Is there any guy like you?")
- You did. - Did you?
You said, "Set me up with a guy like you."
I did, but I didn't say that to you only.
(Flustered)
I said that to all the other guys.
(I've said that to others too.)
- But you did say that to me. - I said that to Jae Suk too.
Have you ever asked me, "Are you up?"
(4th place, when she suddenly texts, "What's up" or "Are you asleep?")
Have you?
- I have. - Right?
Why did you say you never did those things to me?
- You did all those things. - She did.
(So she did all 5 things after all.)
- I say that to my friends too. - Still...
(I was just saying hello.)
- You gave me the wrong idea. - Of course.
(Fortunately, Se Chan didn't take those wrong.)
You guys appreciate each other more now. That's what's important.
(Teasing)
- Of course. - There he goes again.
(He's doing it again.)
- There he goes again. - There he goes again.
(The romance maker finds an opportunity.)
- He's at it again. - You know...
Even when things are going well, Haha can ruin everything.
- He ruins everything. - Definitely.
(Haha is well-known for breaking couples.)
Ji Hyo called you a lot, right?
(By the way...)
Ji Hyo...
(Ji Hyo called a lot when So Min was sick.)
called me and texted me really often.
More often than anyone else.
The funny thing is, after the articles...
(She talked to Ji Hyo on the phone after the news was released.)
about my break were published,
we talked on the phone, and she said,
"So Min, why are you not here yet?"
(She never saw the news.)
"When are you coming?"
I thought, "Hold on."
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo never checks the news.)
I realized that Ji Hyo really doesn't use the internet often.
(So Min's news failed to get to Ji Hyo's cave.)
You should understand her.
I called her six days ago,
and she hasn't called me back yet.
It's been six days,
(He's been waiting for 6 days for her to call back.)
and she hasn't called me back yet.
We even shot together after that, but she hasn't called me back.
Ji Hyo sometimes surprises me.
(Ji Hyo's pattern is still hard to understand after 10 years.)
But when you're sick, she's really nice to you.
- Right. - When I injured my leg,
I had to protect my cast in the shower,
- Gosh. - and she sent me something.
I thought you said she helped you take a shower.
Why would she?
- Why would she? - He did this.
(Everyone thought that she got Kwang Soo a shower,)
- In the shower... - I mean she sent me a cast cover.
(and they're startled.)
I didn't understand what he meant.
I mean a cast cover.
- She sent it to me. - "Turn around."
(Would it look like this?)
She didn't help me take a shower.
If you want Ji Hyo's attention, you should get sick.
(How to get Ji Hyo's attention: Tell people you're sick.)
- If you want her attention... - She's like Nightingale.
Can we talk about the invitation now?
(By the way...)
- Oh, what is that? - Oh, right.
(They forgot about the mysterious invitation.)
Who sent it? We can find diamonds?
The invitation is from So Min, right?
(That's...)
- Yes, that's right. - Are you into fantasy now?
- I mean... - Hey.
(So Min takes something out of her bag.)
- I saw this. - What's that?
This flyer...
(What flyer?)
- What's that? - This is why I called you here.
- Read the flyer. - What's this?
- Gems? - Gems are buried in the ground?
(There is a village where gems are buried in the ground.)
Gujeon Village?
(Find the world's most valuable diamond, the Immortal Heart,)
"There is a village where gems are buried in the ground."
(and your life will be fantastic.)
"Find the world's most valuable diamond, Immortal Heart,"
(Stop your pursuit of small happiness.)
(You can exchange the gems for cash later.)
- "and your life will be fantastic." - Really?
(We invite you to Gujeon Village!)
If you think of a scarecrow in a golden field,
(Lee In Kwon, announcer)
a village will come to your mind.
It's Gujeon Village.
It is the only village in the country where gems are buried.
There will be a local festival this year too.
(Digging the gems is the only local festival of Gujeon Village.)
Also, the world's most valuable and mysterious diamond,
(People flock from everywhere to find the Immortal Heart.)
Immortal Heart, is supposed to be buried in the ground too.
That's why the village is visited by so many people every year.
Why don't you visit the village...
(Lee In Kwon, announcer)
and try your luck?
There are gems buried in this village.
(Tempted)
Gems?
So what is this?
(Curious)
Simply put,
it's a local festival. The gems you dig up...
(They'll take part in the festival,)
- will be exchanged with money. - Really?
(and the gems they dig up will be exchanged for cash.)
- With money? - Do you mean real money?
- Real money? - It's supposed to be a bonanza.
Yes, we're giving out cash today.
(They'll be given actual cash.)
- We can get cash? - Can we have it?
(They respond instantly to cash.)
Yes, you can get cash.
- Really? - Really?
I don't believe it.
(They'll give us cash if we dig up gems?)
- These days... - We can dig up gems?
It's called the Immortal Heart.
(They're all interested as it's about money.)
- I'm getting interested. - Does this make sense?
Let me see.
Since everyone is here,
we prepared a nice brunch.
- Really? - Really?
(What's going on today?)
- Enjoy. - As soon as we start?
- We can already eat? - It looks nice.
- Look at this. - It's salmon.
(A special brunch to celebrate So Min's return)
- It's chicken breasts. - It's my favorite.
Thank you.
Oh, my.
(Thick cheese...)
This looks delicious.
(and fresh salad)
- Thank you. - Unbelievable.
There are pizzas too.
They must be fresh out of the oven. They look delicious.
(A brunch they have never experienced on Running Man)
- Let's eat. - This is nice.
- This is delicious. - This tastes so good.
This feels weird, right?
(They talk about last time during the meal.)
I was taking a shower with Suk Jin and Se Chan after soccer,
(Suk Jin, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan took a shower together yesterday.)
and Suk Jin's showerhead kept turning to the side.
- He could just turn it back. - Right.
(Suk Jin's shower was facing Kwang Soo.)
But he just followed the water...
(What's important is...)
until his bottom almost touched me.
He obviously wanted me to move.
(With his butt)
- He came so close to me... - Seriously.
(He's too lazy to turn it.)
instead of turning his showerhead.
- He could just turn it. - He didn't?
He didn't.
I'm disappointed in him.
(It's obviously a decision that Suk Jin would make.)
His body almost touched me.
At his age, it's hard to change.
(You should understand.)
It is.
Unless he's born again...
(Suk Jin can't refute.)
I don't think he'll be born again as a human.
(This is what I think)
I want to be born as a poisonous mushroom.
Aren't mushrooms fungi?
Why do you want to be born again as a poisonous mushroom?
Then I won't die alone.
(A poisonous mushroom doesn't die alone.)
(Creepy)
- So Min hasn't changed a bit. - I have.
(Shaking his head)
- She hasn't. - I have.
- Didn't you say you'd be different? - It's not like that.
(He can't believe his ears.)
Then you won't die alone?
She's become so mean.
Everyone was quiet for two seconds.
(For an instant...)
(Fortunately, she's the same, everyone.)
- You scared me. - But she has a point.
Ji Hyo, what do you want to be in your next life?
- Me? - Yes.
I want to be a rock.
(Ji Hyo wants to be a rock in her next life.)
- A rock? - I won't ask why.
(We won't even have to ask her why.)
- It suits you. - It suits you.
A rock?
She's a bit like a rock in this life too.
(In this life...)
- That was so funny. - A rock?
(Rock Ji Hyo)
She wants to be a rock? That's hilarious.
- But you didn't laugh. - I laughed a lot.
(What's the matter?)
I can't believe him.
Please be honest just once.
You didn't even laugh. Why do you say it's hilarious?
(His sincerity is nowhere to be found.)
- He confuses me. - I laughed a lot.
Nothing he says is true.
(Let him be.)
He didn't laugh at all.
This is a bit too cheesy.
(He tries to ignore them.)
You've been only eating cheese the whole time. Why do you say that?
You've been only eating cheese.
- In the morning... - Cheese...
(Suk Jin in crisis goes for other dishes.)
I like eating cheesy food in the morning.
Of course.
Of course I laughed. Let me try this.
Didn't you say the food was too cheesy?
(Ridiculous)
- What are you really thinking? - He only eats cheese.
(I can't figure him out.)
You confuse me. Please make me like you.
(What does Suk Jin really think?)
By the way, why are they feeding us so much?
(By the way, why are they feeding us so well?)
- This is all we'll eat all day. - Because we work hard?
So Min, did you plan this episode?
(Doubting)
- What? - Did you plan this episode?
No, I just read the flyer.
- Really? - I thought you invited us.
This is strange, right?
(There's no way they'll only dig up jewels on Running Man.)
- I love this, but... - Because we work hard?
(What's the secret to today's gems?)
We're going to dig up gems?
- It's crowded in here. - Yes.
(They get on a van to dig gems after the meal.)
- Right. - Right?
Did you find something?
(Kwang Soo reads the flyer carefully.)
- We're to find the Immortal Heart. - The Immortal Heart.
(They leave for Gujeon Village, where the Immortal Heart is.)
What could this be?
There must be hints hidden here.
Try reading it vertically.
I've already tried it.
(The 3 fools work together.)
- "Ground, ground, world..." - Try reading it vertically.
"Ground, ground, world..."
Why are these words colored?
- This... - Gems...
- Why is "gems" colored? - Right?
(Snatching)
The Immortal Heart...
- So Min, why did you take it? - Why did you take it?
(So Min, why?)
It's mine.
(Confident)
You said you'd be different.
(Why did you take it away?)
It's not like that.
- We were reading it. - I'm different.
(She's never changed.)
- Why did you... - Why did you become so mean?
You're getting greedy again.
- I'm nice now. - I already...
(A person doesn't change so easily.)
felt it while talking to her.
- I'm nice now. - She hasn't changed a bit.
- Why... - So Min, are you having fun?
(Now)
- Are you happy? - Yes.
(I'm having a blast.)
- I'm excited. - Let us read it.
You can read it.
(She shows the flyer to Haha.)
- Why can't I read it? - I can read it?
- Kwang Soo can't read it. - Why not me?
(What about me, So Min?)
- Why not me? - Move.
You're out.
(Laughing)
(You can't, either.)
Why not me?
- Yesterday... - I'm the only one who can read it.
(She won't let both of us read it.)
- Why are you doing this? - I'll read it later.
- Yesterday... - Why not me?
Yesterday, I realized that So Min...
Guys, did you feel it too?
I'm talking to myself.
No one is listening.
(No one's listening to him.)
No one is listening to Suk Jin.
It's okay.
They're talking.
(Acting cool)
I shouldn't have cut in.
- I think it's your fault too. - It's my fault.
(It's obviously Suk Jin's fault.)
The ones who called me often get to read it first.
(So Min is still bargaining for the flyer.)
- Okay. - I think it's your fault too.
- Thank you. - Why are you doing this?
- This is driving me crazy. - You let Haha read it?
(Gosh.)
- Show us too. - That brat?
So Min, you're going to betray us again, right?
(Is she...)
What are you talking about? Today...
We all...
- It's supposed to be a bonanza. - Really?
(They get closer to Gujeon Village...)
Don't you want to start digging already?
(without knowing anything about today's race.)
We'll find so many gems.
- In movies, - Okay.
people often die one by one in a remote place.
(They die one by one on the way to a remote place.)
- That's right. - There are many movies like that.
I think the first one to die...
will be either Haha or Suk Jin.
(Haha or Suk Jin would have died first.)
That's when the movie starts for real.
I think I'll be the 2nd or 3rd person to die.
(And the next one is...)
Also, couples always go deep into the mountains...
(The couple is usually the second victim.)
- to kiss and die. - That's right.
(They go to a forbidden place to kiss, and they die.)
- They die as soon as they kiss. - And...
I know how Suk Jin will die.
He dies while doing something forbidden.
(Suk Jin would...)
- Right, he'll do that. - You know what I mean?
(A character like Suk Jin would die regardless of the story.)
"I don't care. I'll do it anyway."
- Bang! - Exactly.
- Or while peeing alone. - Right.
Ms. Rock will survive the longest.
(On the contrary...)
Right, because she doesn't say anything.
- She could be a criminal too. - Right.
(Ji Hyo is either the quiet murderer or she survives in the end.)
It's so funny that she wants to be a rock.
Right, it suits her.
(Ji Hyo's new nickname is perfect for her.)
I laughed so hard.
I want to be born again as me.
(Full of self-love)
- One more time? - Yes.
As you?
(That's cool.)
That's incredible.
- You want to be yourself again. - That's so cool.
Kwang Soo, what about you?
A basketball player.
- A spoon worm. - A spoon worm?
(Or...)
- Who wants to be a spoon worm? - You'll definitely be a spoon worm.
(That's absurd.)
- You'll be caught in Busan. - A spoon worm?
You'll then be eaten by me at a sashimi restaurant.
- Right. - Must you put it that way?
(Sweating)
Why not?
(Kwang Soo spoon worm would be tasty.)
Nice and chewy.
- A spoon worm? - A spoon worm.
- I'll enjoy it too. - Spoon worms are good.
(After a 10-minute ride,)
(they arrive at the village.)
What now?
- Over there. - What's that?
- "Kim Sang Yeob"? - There's something here.
(How does Gujeon Village for digging gems look like?)
- I'm getting a headache. - What's this?
They don't waste any time, do they?
Must we start digging the moment we exit the van?
(They arrive at Gujeon Village famous for diamonds.)
- I'm already getting a headache. - What's going on?
- As soon as we got here... - I'm already getting a headache.
(It seems like an ordinary rural village.)
I wonder what's here.
(However, an eerie vibe can be detected.)
(Padlocks can be seen everywhere.)
(The village seems ordinary, but it isn't.)
(What events will take place here?)
Wait, what's this?
- Why are we here today? - Hello.
(Someone welcomes them.)
- Hello. - It's a village.
- Hi. - Digging up gems...
Hello and welcome.
- Hi. - We're at a village.
- Hello. - Welcome to Gujeon Village.
- The village head. - Is he the village head?
(Is he the village head?)
- I'm the chairman of the youth. - Hello.
(No. I'm not the village head.)
- Hello. - It's good to see you.
(Park Cheong Nyeon, chairman of the young village people)
(He shows visitors around who are here to dig up gems.)
- I'm the chairman of the youth. - Hello.
(He's the youngest resident of this village.)
- Chairman of the youth? - Yes.
(You don't look young.)
- Did you hear that? - Are you sure?
Yes, that's right.
You should first sanitize your hands.
(His name is Park Cheong Nyeon.)
Are you here to dig up the diamonds?
I heard that there are diamonds everywhere.
(Excited)
That's right. Every time you dig,
(Countless gems are supposedly buried in the field.)
- you'll find a diamond. - Really?
The most valuable gem...
- is the red diamond. - Red?
- The one called the Immortal Heart. - It's called the Immortal Heart.
So you already know.
Word got out that the diamond could change your life.
(Finding the Immortal Heart will change your life.)
Anyway, our proud gem field is that way.
- There are some people digging. - Right.
(It's a gold mine where countless gems are buried.)
You can get digging too.
Why aren't you also digging with the others?
(Curious)
- I mean... - You must already have a lot.
I may not have the touch because I'm never lucky.
- I see. - So it's not easy.
- They're not easy to dig. - It's not easy at all.
(It's not as easy as you think.)
- You need a bit of luck. - Yes, exactly.
Can we get digging then?
Yes, you can.
Once you dig up the gems, you will take them to the pawnshop.
(Pawnshop)
- There it is. - Right.
(You can exchange gems for cash at the pawnshop.)
- So there... - We can cash them in?
- Yes, straight into cash. - Really?
If you get hungry or thirsty while digging,
(Store)
you can head to the stall to buy snacks.
(You can also shop at the store with cash.)
- Got it. - Now, please take your tools.
- You can then get digging. - Sure.
I can't believe this.
(Will they be able to find the Immortal Heart?)
I don't know what to expect today.
There are a lot of people here.
(Many tourists are already digging for gems.)
- Look at all these people. - Now I'm getting greedy.
(They enthusiastically enter the gem field.)
- Hello. - I'm getting a weird feeling.
Are the gems randomly spread out?
- Hello. - Goodness, hello.
Have you dug up any gems?
(Seriously)
- Did you find the red diamond? - Have you gotten lucky?
- What does it look like? - We haven't seen it either.
(The tourists didn't find any yet.)
Please let us see it if you come across one.
- Exactly. - The red diamond.
(Everyone wants the Immortal Heart.)
- Have you not dug it up? - The Immortal Heart.
- Hello. - Hi.
- I doubt there's anything here. - They haven't gotten lucky.
Are you residents of this village?
(By any chance...)
- No. - Are you outsiders?
- We came after hearing the rumors. - Where are you from?
(They are four non-residents who came after hearing the news.)
- We heard about the diamonds. - So you came to dig them up?
- Yes. - You all have name tags though.
Are you sisters?
- Yes, sisters. - You four are all sisters.
(Kim Il Nyeo, Kim E Nyeo, Kim Sam Nyeo, Kim Sa Nyeo)
(Four sisters, non-residents)
(They all dig to find gems.)
There must be a few things buried here.
It's getting hot though.
(The weather changed abruptly after they start digging.)
But it was chilly all day.
We were told to dig because there's something here.
(They keep digging anyway.)
- There probably is. - How deep should we dig?
Let's see.
Are you sure there are diamonds here?
(They can't find any.)
Are they even here?
I thought we just had to dig?
(He surely said that.)
There's nothing here.
Are you sure they're buried here?
(Are gems really buried here?)
- Right? - Did you find something?
Hold on.
What is it?
(Did Kwang Soo find it?)
It's nothing.
- Why? - What is it?
Did you find something?
(It's just a rock.)
- It's only a rock. - Seriously?
Hey, you found Ji Hyo.
(Stone Ji Hyo)
A rock. That's you, Ji Hyo.
(It's Ji Hyo.)
Look how big it is. I was startled too.
(What's Ji Hyo doing here?)
Ji Hyo!
(She said it to a rock.)
That's huge.
(Throwing)
Can't you guys just leave me alone?
Ji Hyo's everywhere.
(Ji Hyo's buried everywhere.)
This is odd though.
(They can't find anything but rocks.)
Are you sure there are gems here?
It doesn't make sense that gems would be buried here.
(Not even the 4 sisters have been successful.)
- What's this? - My gosh!
- My gosh! - What is it?
- He must've found one. - I found one.
- Really? - He did!
(He finally finds a gem.)
- It was there. - They really must be buried here.
- Let me see. - They're really buried here.
(Everyone else is now motivated.)
- It's true. - Let's get digging.
- This wasn't a hoax. - Look at him.
- You've all gone crazy. - It's red!
(Completely energized)
They're really here. Anyway, I'll head to the pawnshop.
They're really here.
- The rumors were true. - I wonder how much it's worth.
(How much are these worth?)
It was really here.
- Welcome. - Hi.
What do you have for me?
(Jeon Dang Po, a master haggler)
- I found a gem. - Really?
Let me take a look.
(His hopes are up.)
- But it's quite big. - You're not kidding.
Since you're my first customer, I'll give you a good bargain.
(How much is this gem worth?)
- Three dollars. - What?
- But it's a gem. - Three dollars.
(Totally disappointed.)
- I'll take it then. - Good.
- Here you go. - Got it.
(He exchanges it for cash on the spot.)
Thank you.
Bring me another and I'll give you another good bargain.
I mean...
(That's too cheap for a gem.)
Three dollars for a gem?
(He's pleased to have found a gem though.)
- How much was it? - What?
Did you cash it in?
You'll be surprised by what it's worth.
(He tries to trick them.)
- Really? - You'll be shocked.
I'm switching to a pickax.
(He starts to dig harder.)
I see you're all busy digging.
My body will ache all over tomorrow.
(He starts to dig harder.)
I'm going crazy now that I know there are gems here.
(Opportunity makes the thief.)
This is why we were fed this morning.
(It's why they were given breakfast.)
- Found it! - Really?
- Where? - I found one!
- Where was it? - I found a gem.
(I want to find it too.)
Many must be buried over there.
- Nice! - Are they all over there?
- Was it buried deep? - No.
(They couldn't be more jealous.)
You don't have to dig that deep.
Really?
Is that the pawnshop?
I want to check out the stall first.
And then I'll head to the pawnshop.
Hello.
- Welcome. - Do you only take cash?
And the gem must be cashed in at the pawnshop?
(You can only use cash at the store.)
- Are you here to dig up the gems? - Yes.
- You can get anything you want. - I'm just here to look.
(Price List)
- Is that so? - Yes.
(Snacks: 2 dollars Cup noodles: 3 dollars)
- They're on the pricier side. - Really?
(Sausage: 2 dollars Drinks: 1 dollar)
- Anyway, I'll be back. - Sure.
(Kim Ga Ge, stall owner, doesn't intend to sell anything)
Was it buried deep?
(Meanwhile, in the gem field...)
You don't have to dig deep.
- Found one! - What?
- I... - It's blue.
I bet you haven't seen a blue one before.
It's a real gem.
It's also known as an angel's teardrop.
(He came up with his own name.)
- An angel's teardrop? - That's not it.
It's the Immortal Heart.
You have your chance now.
- Hurry over to the pawnshop. - Get going.
- Here. - Let me see.
I bet you haven't seen one like this before.
(Kwang Soo came to the pawnshop with the gem.)
- What is it? - It's a diamond,
also known as an angel's teardrop.
- Isn't this the Tear of Yondu? - It isn't.
(Refer to Episode 488)
- Hold on. - It's blue.
You brought me a precious kind.
- It's quite valuable. - But it's covered in scratches.
(She tries to ruin it.)
- Look at the scratches. - Since it's a precious one,
I'll give you a dollar for it.
(Angel's teardrop is worth one dollar.)
He said a dollar.
It has too many scratches on it.
(The gem has many scratches.)
But that's not my fault.
You should've brought me one without any scratches.
(Kwang Soo's heart is scratched.)
Off you go.
Get digging again.
I was hoping for a lot since it's a gem, but a dollar...
(Kwang Soo can't seem to walk away.)
What can I do with a dollar anyway?
Where's the stall?
(He heads to the stall with a dollar.)
- What? - Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo!
Are you here to dig up gems too?
(Someone seems happy to see Kwang Soo.)
- The Immortal Heart. - Yes?
- Isn't that what you're after? - Yes, the red diamond.
(Kwang Soo talks to a mystery woman for quite some time.)
Thank you.
(Then he heads to someplace.)
The pink container building?
The pink container building...
Why is he running over there?
(Where is he going?)
- Where is he going? - Where... Hey!
(He looks very suspicious.)
Where... Hey!
(He chases Kwang Soo without any reluctance.)
He must have new information.
Is this the place?
(He finds a new field behind the pink container.)
- Must I dig again? - Let's follow them.
Don't bother.
(The 4 sisters also get restless after seeing Kwang Soo.)
- Come on. - Gosh.
Let's get over there.
- But wait... - I'm heading over there.
- Come on. - Come with us too.
(Everyone heads to Kwang Soo except for Kim Sam Nyeo.)
Don't force me.
- Let's go. - I'm going to keep digging here.
What's going on? Why did they head over there?
(What's going on?)
Kwang Soo suddenly ran over there.
(Kwang Soo starts to dig.)
Jae Suk. How did you know to follow me?
(Jae Suk, sensing something suspicious, joins in.)
You don't know yet, do you?
- Know what? - The Immortal Heart is buried here.
- Really? - Yes.
The Immortal Heart is buried here.
A local resident told me.
It's no use digging over there.
What is it?
- Hurry on over. - Get digging.
(Se Chan joins them.)
Whoever finds it must split the money though.
- Of course. - Now everyone's here.
(Flustered)
- We'll dig too. - We're here to dig as well.
(Kim Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, and Sa Nyeo join them too.)
Promise that you'll split the money though.
If only there's anything here.
(Is the Immortal Heart buried in this field?)
Until when must we dig?
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo talked to a woman earlier.
- What? - She told me...
that the Immortal Heart was here.
She was wearing a white hanbok.
- A white hanbok? - Yes.
Her name is Kwang Ja though.
- She had a name? - Really?
I wonder who she is.
(Jong Kook was headed to the pawnshop.)
(He sees the name tag of the mysterious woman.)
Kwang Ja? That name...
Kwang Soo!
(Just as Jong Kook noticed,)
- Are you here to dig up gems too? - Kwang Ja?
That name...
(the woman's name was Kwang Ja.)
Her name is Kwang Ja though.
- She had a name? - Really?
- Is she your sister? - Is she family?
Who's Kwang Ja? Tell us.
(Suspicious)
I don't know who she is. She said she lives here.
I find Kwang Soo strange.
He was with her.
(Kwang Soo looks fishy.)
I swear it's not me today.
I swear it's not me.
Why is her name Kwang Ja then?
I didn't see her name tag. I didn't know she was Kwang Ja.
I find it so strange that you didn't see her name tag.
That's strange.
That's the first thing I saw.
- Okay. - Right?
- Anyway... - I didn't see it.
Kwang Soo made us all come here, right?
Is it possible he lured us here...
(Is this part of Kwang Soo's scheme?)
- so that he can do something else? - That's true.
- Maybe there's nothing here. - No way.
- No way. - What is it?
I'm not certain either, but she told me.
(Repeating)
- She lives here. - She was Kwang Ja.
He's avoiding our eyes.
(Name: Lee Kwang Ja, occupation and characteristic unknown)
There's nothing.
(There's not even a gem.)
- There's nothing here. - There's nothing.
We kept digging, and there's nothing.
- That was false information. - We went deep.
- What is it? - He found it.
(He found the Immortal Heart gem box!)
He got it.
- He knew the location. - I'm sure.
(No way. He really found it?)
- There must be a gem for real. - It's okay.
- What's this? - It's a red diary.
This is the Immortal Diamond.
(He means the Immortal Heart.)
It's a red diamond.
- You found it? - Can I see too?
(Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, and Sa Nyeo gather around the gem box.)
- Hold on. - It's a red diamond.
Please don't get close.
Can I touch it?
Get closer.
- Don't touch it. - I won't.
(Sensitive)
- We'll watch. - We'll watch.
- Hurry. - I saw something shiny.
(He wants to open it,)
Open it with the key.
(but there's no key.)
- There's no key. - There isn't.
If it's a real gem, you get good energy when you touch it.
- If it's a real gem? - Really?
- Oh, no. Wait. - Don't touch it.
I'll only touch it.
- Show us. - Touch it.
- I can't open it. - Find it.
- If you touch it... - They said...
(Just by touching it, you get good energy.)
- you get good energy. - Just by touching it?
- Come here. Let me touch it. - Let me touch it.
- No, wait. - Let me touch it.
Did you find it?
Let me touch it.
You get good energy when you touch it.
(So Min approaches the gem box to get good energy.)
What do you think? Do you feel energized already?
(Everyone touches the gem box.)
- I'm not sure. - Let me touch it.
- Why? - My gosh.
- Do you feel it? - We found it.
- Don't take it. - Hey!
(At that moment!)
- Do you feel it? - We found it.
- Don't take it. - Hey.
(Kim Sa Nyeo steals the box and runs away!)
Sa Nyeo!
What is she doing?
You can't take it.
She's a thief!
- What are you doing? - She's a thief.
This is good, so I want to bring it home for my husband.
(They confront for the gem box.)
- Why did you take it? - You can't!
- I want to let my husband touch it. - Kwang Soo found it.
(The sisters blame Sa Nyeo who stole the gem box.)
You can't take it.
Why?
Fine.
I was just fooling around with you.
- We just wanted to touch it. - She was fooling around with you.
- I'm sure. - There's no key.
(It ends as a joke.)
We have no key.
- Il Nyeo, - Why do they want this?
(The ladies who pulled a bad prank leave.)
- let's so somewhere else. - Let's go take a rest.
- Let's go somewhere else. - We have no key,
(Where's the key to the gem box?)
- so there's no point having this. - I know.
He met Kwang Ja in front of the supermarket.
(Does Kwang Ja know?)
- Let's go there. - Let's go over first.
- Let's find out why. - Ji Hyo, hold onto this.
(Ji Hyo's reliable.)
But I found it.
It doesn't even matter.
(Kwang Soo takes the gem box again.)
Still.
- I found it. - That's true.
- Sure. - There's a supermarket.
(Does Kwang Ja know where the key is?)
We have to meet her to resolve this.
- There she is. - There's a supermarket.
- Kwang Ja is over there. - It's her.
Hello.
- We found it. - You're back.
We found it.
What's that?
- We found it. - Can I have it?
- Can I have it? - Maybe not.
- She's Kwang Ja. - She talks weird.
(Flustered)
She sounds just like you.
(Don't be ridiculous.)
I sound like her? What are you talking about?
- You sound like her. - Do you know about the key?
Do you know where it is?
Well, I don't know much,
but the village head knows everything.
Where's the village head?
Where is he?
The village head is over there!
Over there? There must be a village head.
(As Kwang Ja told them,)
We have to find him.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(they set out to meet the village head.)
- Thanks a lot. - Thanks a lot.
Their names are so similar.
Lee Kwang Ja.
It's a coincidence. She's not related to me.
(What did Kwang Ja and Kwang Soo talk about earlier?)
Hey, she won't do that if she's not related to you.
The village head. Village head!
- He's over here. - It's him!
(They find the village head.)
He's over there.
Mr. Choi!
(Choi Yi Jang)
(Village head, knows most secrets, has early dementia)
Mr. Choi?
(They approach the village head carefully.)
- What's wrong? - Mr. Choi.
- Mr. Choi! - He's in a wheelchair.
- Is it you? - Hello, sir.
Who are you?
- We're visitors. - Are you guys visiting?
Yes, sir.
We're here to find gems, and we dug this up.
(He shows the gem box to the village head.)
Do you know where the key is by any chance?
What is that?
Do you not know what this is?
(Double check)
That?
Isn't that a brand name chocolate?
- It's not chocolate. - It's not.
- It's not chocolate. - You know about the field, right?
(It's not chocolate.)
- It's a gem field. - There's a gem field.
(Do you know?)
Who said that? I don't know anything about it.
Sir, do you know any of us?
(Glancing)
(He looked at either Kwang Soo or Suk Jin.)
He looked at you.
He looked at Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, he looked at you. - He looked at you.
- It was him. - Why are you pointing at me?
- Is he your friend from school? - Elementary school friend?
(Primary school friend?)
Elementary school friend?
- Say, "Nice to meet you, friend." - Do it.
- "Nice to meet you, friend." - "Nice to meet you, friend."
I don't know.
Nice to meet you, friend.
- Goodness! - He's not.
(Goodness)
(They're not friends from school.)
Then sir.
(Back to the point)
Where can we find the key?
My memory is faint.
- I don't know. - I'll give you some gems.
(Haha tries to buy him.)
My gosh. What's wrong with you?
I can't, right?
(I was curious. I'm sorry.)
Every word you say is awful.
Hey, this is not that kind of world.
Stop bothering me! Go away!
(Yelling)
He didn't answer anything.
(When you think about it)
- But this... - I already told you.
(Yi Jang gets mad at their continuous questions.)
I don't know, so I have nothing more to say.
- Okay. - We'll get going.
- We're leaving. - Excuse us.
There's something.
(His instinct at work)
There's nothing!
(Yelling)
Why is he so angry?
You get angry once every minute.
(Calm down.)
- He's strange. - It's bad for your health, sir.
- We'll get going. - We're leaving.
(He's not feeling good.)
- Thank you, sir. - Mr. Choi.
- Good luck. - I wish you good health.
- He's the worst. - Why would you say "Good luck"?
(They leave without obtaining any useful information.)
Why would you say "Good luck"?
I wish you good health, sir.
Should we divide ourselves into teams?
Let's split and look.
(The key)
- I'll go with Kwang Soo. - No, I will.
I'll go with him.
(Kwang Soo who's holding the gem box is popular.)
Wait. Why am I so popular?
- I have nothing! - Let's go.
- Kwang Soo. - Then...
I'll go with one of you.
(They scatter in the town.)
- I'll go with you. - Let's go.
- Leave! - Okay, I'm going by myself.
(The town)
(Se Chan is looking for the key by himself.)
What's the R mark?
I can hear them. What?
(He found something.)
- What is it? - It's nothing.
- Why? - It's nothing.
(He goes somewhere in a hurry.)
Stop being so cheap.
- Stop being so cheap. - What's this?
What's this?
(He finds a mysterious treasure box.)
What's that? He found something.
- Hey! - Don't speak so loudly.
- Don't say it! - I have to carry it around.
(It's locked. They can't open it.)
- I have no key. - I'm curious.
Let me see. I'm only going to look.
- Haha! - Look at this, Haha.
- What's that? - We don't know.
- He found it. - Where did you find it?
- Down there. - Down there.
You two are amazing when you're a team.
Here he goes again.
Love power?
(Is this love power?)
I knew you were going to mention it.
(The make-believe relationship mania is at work again.)
- He found it by himself. - Hey.
Hold her hand. Stop running off.
(The make-believe relationship mania)
There's something over there.
- Where? - Up there.
(Se Chan and So Min are off to find another gem box.)
- By the scarecrow. - Did you see it?
There's something up there.
Don't do it.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are searching for the key together.)
Inside...
What's this?
Did you find something?
(Ji Hyo shares her find with Jong Kook.)
Let me see.
- "I had fun with my friends today." - "With my friends today."
(It's a diary.)
- "He watched us pleasantly." - What?
(I had fun with my friends today. He watched us pleasantly.)
Remember the gems from earlier?
They had colors.
Right? They were all different colors.
Right. There were purple,
(I had fun with my friends today. He watched us pleasantly.)
- pink, and yellow. - Right?
These match the colors of the gems.
(Is there a connection...)
- Right, Ji Hyo? - You're right.
(between the gem color and the color in the diary?)
Right? These are the colors of the gems.
- Gems from earlier. - Red too.
The writing.
Let's get going, Ji Hyo.
There's a scarecrow here too. Is this the children?
(By the way)
- It's not, right? - I don't think so.
There's a scarecrow over there too.
(There are scarecrows all over the village.)
Where?
Is this pink? What's the color of this hat?
There are too many colors.
- On this hat. - There's nothing.
(What's it got to do with the color of scarecrow's hat?)
It looks kind of frightening.
Why are the pants down? Is that Kwang Soo?
He takes his pants off all the time.
Maybe it does have something to do with Kwang Soo.
(They are suspicious of Kwang Soo for several reasons.)
- There's a safe. - Where?
- This is a safe. - There's a safe?
(Meanwhile, Se Chan and So Min...)
- There's a safe. - Where?
- This is a safe. - There's a safe?
(find a safe...)
It's on the right.
(on the 2nd floor of the village head's house.)
Oh, wow.
- My gosh. - So Min.
- So Min. - What?
(The safe is hidden in the village head's house.)
- We need a passcode. - It's locked.
Don't press random numbers. You'll get locked out.
(What's the safe for?)
You'll lock it.
What are you doing?
(The village head)
- Sorry? - We did nothing.
Are you thieves?
- No, we're not. - No.
Why are you in my house?
(The village head gets angry at Se Chan and So Min.)
- I'm sorry. - It's the old man.
Get lost before I kick you out!
Okay. Sorry, sir.
(Is the safe keeping a secret?)
He's mad.
So Min.
Sir.
Why do you think...
I can't sell this?
The pawnshop won't take it.
(So Min asks him about the gem they found earlier.)
What's this?
It's a gem. I dug it up from the field.
It's chocolate.
Se Chan...
(He's talking about chocolate again.)
- Se Chan. - It's chocolate.
- It's chocolate? - Yes, it's chocolate.
- It's chocolate. - Se Chan.
- I'm using the bathroom. - There's something strange.
He keeps looking for chocolate.
Is it a brand name chocolate?
(He mentioned chocolate earlier too.)
- It's not chocolate. - It's chocolate.
- How much do you have? - What?
- How much do you have? - I have one gem.
Should I get chocolate? I'll get chocolate.
- But it's two dollars. - What?
- It's two dollars. - I'm going to exchange it.
- No, you need money. - Do you have money?
(Will they find something if they buy chocolate?)
- Hold on. - Let's go together.
He keeps looking for chocolate.
Is the scarecrow hiding something?
(A vacant lot in front of a supermarket)
This is strange.
(Suk Jin searches around the scarecrow.)
Suk Jin, shall we go into the building?
(There's nothing.)
- Let's go inside the building. - Let's do that.
Even if we find the key...
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Just tell me the truth. What are you up to today?
(He keeps doubting.)
- I'm not doing anything. - Are you sure?
(They go into the house looking for the key.)
Really?
- Why? - What's this?
(Kwang Soo found a box that looks like what Se Chan found.)
This is amazing.
Let me keep this with me.
Suk Jin.
We are on the same boat.
(Don't betray me.)
- Sure. We're a team. - Seriously.
- Okay. - You know what I mean.
- Gosh, this is... - We should never be apart.
(They're both excited.)
- Feeling! Intuition! Cross! - Feeling! Intuition! Cross!
(It's been a long time.)
If you and I work together, we will definitely win this race.
Suk Jin, we should have one of this each.
(They feel encouraged after finding the gem box.)
- Okay. - Seriously.
What is this? There are things here and there in the house.
(There are things hidden all over the house.)
There are a lot of things.
What is this?
I guess it's just a sheet of paper.
(He looks for the key outside of the house.)
I think it's a clue.
How should I open this?
I need a key.
(And Kwang Soo watches him.)
(Shouting)
(Suk Jin suddenly cries out.)
(Ripping)
(And the thing that's left in the spot where Suk Jin was...)
(Victim)
(Meanwhile, Haha is...)
It's not working.
It doesn't work.
(Haha is doing something with the gem boxes.)
(Does he have a key?)
(What's the key that Haha has?)
- But we don't have money. - I have gems.
You can't use the gems.
(Se Chan and So Min go to buy chocolate for the village head.)
Gosh, what is this?
What's this?
They're not here.
(So Min finds on the street...)
- They're gone. - Victims?
- Are they dead? - They're the people we met earlier.
(the name tags of the sisters digging up gems.)
Who tore off the name tags?
Who's doing this?
(Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, Sa Nyeo are gone with their name tags left here.)
Is someone tearing off the name tags?
I guess so.
There are victims.
(Their name tags say victim on the other side.)
Hang on.
Someone's running around tearing off the name tags.
(Is someone tearing the name tags in the village?)
- Take them. - They are the ladies...
- we met earlier, right? - Yes. Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, and Sa Nyeo.
The three of them lost their name tags.
Where's the rest?
Right. Sa Nyeo.
(Kim Il Nyeo, Kim E Nyeo, and Kim Sa Nyeo)
- No, Sam Nyeo is not here. - It's Sam Nyeo.
(Sam Nyeo's name is not here.)
We don't have Sam Nyeo's name tag.
Let's go.
- You two should just go. - Come with us.
(Sam Nyeo was left alone while the other three went to Kwang Soo.)
Let's go, So Min.
(Where did Kim Sam Nyeo go?)
Excuse me.
Did you see Suk Jin?
- Who's Suk Jin? - Oh, right.
(Screaming)
What's going on?
Why? What's wrong?
(Where the scream came from,)
Gosh, what's that?
Haha!
(Kwang Ja is lying on the ground,)
What is this? What's going on?
(and Haha is there.)
- She tried to rip off my name tag. - Haha!
- She tried to rip off my name tag. - Who is that?
(Kwang Soo sees...)
She kept trying to rip off my name tag.
(Kwang Ja lying on the floor without her name tag.)
She tried to tear off my name tag, so I took hers.
She kept following me around.
- Why did you do that to Kwang Ja? - It has nothing to do with you.
What's the deal between Lee Kwang Soo and Lee Kwang Ja?
- I've never seen her before. - Then why do you even care?
It's just strange.
(Haha keep cornering the witness, Kwang Soo.)
- From up there... - Mr. Choi kept watching you.
- I have nothing to do with her. - It's just strange.
I have nothing to do with her.
(Repeating)
- Later, you will... - Why would you care about her?
I don't care about her. You just took her name tag off.
(Kwang Soo quickly leaves.)
- I don't know. - You better watch out.
I don't know anything.
- Kwang Soo, did you find anything? - Jae Suk.
- No? - The thing is...
Haha eliminated Kwang Ja.
What?
Haha just eliminated Kwang Ja. She was lying on the ground.
Why did he eliminate her?
I don't know. She's lying on the ground now.
- Why did he eliminate her? - Did you find anything?
I don't know.
Apparently, Kwang Ja attacked Suk Jin and Haha.
- Really? - Yes.
Where have you been?
Actually, there was...
- Hey. - I was...
- What? - I wasn't going to say this,
but you're being strange now.
I understand it looks suspicious.
But I don't have anything.
(Kwang Soo pleads his innocence,)
And...
- just now... - Why does it have to be Kwang Ja?
(and Jae Suk questions Kwang Soo.)
I don't know that either.
So...
Jae Suk.
- You're going the wrong way. - What are you up to?
I didn't do anything. I'm nothing.
I have nothing to do with this village. I've never been here.
And in the pension next to this building...
Get lost.
(Upset)
Okay. You're so doomed.
(Okay.)
I don't know what it is,
but if there's a penalty, you will definitely get it.
You'll get all wet.
I just said it involuntarily.
(Yoo Jae Suk, suffering from Doubt Kwang Soo Syndrome)
I just can't help it when I see your face.
Do you want me to tell you?
- You know I didn't mean it. - Okay.
I just said it before I knew it.
- Do you want me to tell you? - Tell me.
I stopped it.
(He stopped his right hand with his left hand.)
Before I knew it...
- You do a lot of strange things. - I didn't mean to do it.
(What's wrong with him?)
I just did it involuntarily.
I stopped it.
(Yoo Jae Suk, suffering from Doubt Kwang Soo Syndrome)
Tell me, Kwang Soo.
- Do I have to tell you this? - Just tell me.
In the next building,
Suk Jin and I found a box.
(He tells Jae Suk about the gem box that Suk Jin found.)
- Really? - There's another gem box.
- And does it need a key? - Yes.
It's locked.
And it looks totally different from this.
Actually, I found a photo here.
Look at you.
(What photo is it?)
(A little while ago)
What's this?
(A group photo of the villagers)
It looks like a family photo.
Kwang Ja is looking the other way.
(And what is Kwang Ja staring at?)
I guess there's a secret about this village.
(Kim Ga Gae and Park Cheong Nyeon)
What's this?
Kwang Ja is looking the other way.
You're right.
- They are the villagers. - He's the pawnbroker.
(What do Kwang Ja's eyes mean?)
- This is Park Cheong Nyeon. - Cheong Nyeon.
And she's the supermarket owner.
- And this is... - He's the village head.
Isn't this your house?
Why would it be my house?
Isn't this your village?
What are you talking about?
(He doesn't know what a nucleated village is.)
There must be something.
What's the thing Suk Jin found?
Why is Kwang Ja out?
- She didn't go there. - Kwang Ja is lying down there.
Haha eliminated her.
It's not like that.
- Why did you eliminate her? - Listen to me.
- Why did you do that? - I'll tell you why.
(Explaining the whole story)
She kept coming to me.
She shook a flower at my face...
and tried to tear off my name tag as I turned around.
(He says Kwang Ja tried to rip off his name tag.)
I was going to buy her something.
(Will this be true?)
But she tried to tear it off.
So I took hers off.
- And she's out? - Yes.
(When you ripped it off...)
- She fell down when you did it? - Yes.
Then he came to me.
- Do you know what he said to me? - What did he say?
He sounded as if I harmed his family.
(He claims that Kwang Soo's reaction was more suspicious.)
"Why did you do it?"
It didn't sound anything like that.
"Why did you do that to Kwang Ja?"
- Why would you think that way? - He kept talking to me like that.
(Thinking)
- His family... - No. That's enough, Haha.
I figured it out.
What are you doing?
What's up with you?
Why are you pretending to be so sharp?
I'm the protagonist of this episode.
(Sudden)
- Why? - Why?
I feel like I should unravel the whole mystery here.
(Yoo Jae Suk, suffering from the protagonist disease)
We should eliminate him.
(While they have an exhausting conversation...)
Isn't it strange?
Haha.
- We almost figured it out. - What?
(Triumphant)
Did you see this, guys?
What's that? What's a victim?
The ladies are gone.
(She shows them the name tags of Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, and Sa Nyeo.)
- Did you take them off? - No. I found them on the ground.
- What's this? - Haha, we need something sweet.
You and I should...
- get the village head something. - To whom?
(The village head)
- You got money, didn't you? - To the village head?
- If we get him some chocolate... - He will give us a hint.
(Se Chan guesses that the village head will tell him the secret...)
- What? - We need chocolate.
(if he brings chocolate.)
How much is the chocolate?
It's one dollar.
(He buys chocolate.)
One dollar? Thank you.
- Really? - Excuse me.
How come you're all out of tissue boxes?
Tissue boxes?
It's because of the virus.
(The tissue box is the only thing that's sold out.)
People buy a lot of tissue these days.
But I didn't get extra.
(Sold out)
It's the only thing that's sold out.
- Why is it sold out? - I told you.
It's because of the virus.
(Something's strange.)
My gosh.
What is this?
(Se Chan and So Min find something on their way to the village head.)
- What is this ddakji? - What's that?
(This ddakji is...)
(what Kwang Ja played with.)
It's a letter.
It says something. Let's go.
Read it.
(The letter says...)
"May 1, 2019."
"If what I found out is true,"
(If what I found out is true, those who were tempted by the diamonds...)
"those who were tempted by the diamonds..."
(will soon be eliminated by him.)
"will soon be eliminated by him."
(Is it a journal about the elimination?)
"Figure out a way to eliminate him as soon as possible..."
"and share it with people."
- Does this say anything? - No.
Then...
We will get eliminated if we become greedy.
It says "those who were tempted by the diamonds".
Jae Suk, I found a letter.
(I should tell them quickly.)
Who is it?
- I'm sure someone's here. - There's someone.
- My gosh. - What?
What's that sound?
(Kwang Soo found...)
- Jae Suk. - What?
(Suk Jin's name tag.)
Why?
(Is Suk Jin eliminated?)
What's that?
- What happened to Suk Jin? - Look at this.
- What? Suk Jin. - What's going on?
Suk Jin is a victim.
- Jae Suk. - You mean Suk Jin?
I was right about that.
What I said in the car is right. It's just like a movie.
- We will die one by one? - I said we'd die one by one.
I told you. Suk Jin or Kwang Soo would die.
(His joke is coming true.)
- Jae Suk. - The letter.
- The balloon. - I found this letter.
"May 1, 2019. If what I found out is true..."
(Se Chan shares what he found in the ddakji.)
Look at this.
It means there's someone.
We don't have time.
(In this village,)
What is going on?
(there's someone going after...)
I think there's a secret about this village.
(the members' name tags.)
I'm sure our routes overlap here.
(I should be careful not to get eliminated here.)
(Se Chan is back at the village head's house with chocolate.)
Sir.
I brought chocolate.
(He suddenly grabs the chocolate.)
(The village head takes the chocolate.)
(Is chocolate the key that will open his mouth?)
Do you have anything to say?
(Do you have anything to say?)
(Shaking his head)
Was it just an ad-lib?
(Was that just an ad-lib?)
But chocolate...
Sir. Did you just want something sweet?
(The village head simply wanted something sweet.)
- Is that it? - I don't know anything.
(He's telling the truth.)
- Gosh, my dollar. - I don't know anything.
(I was tricked.)
Mr. Choi.
(So Min also brings chocolate for the village head.)
Se Chan.
(Laughing)
(I hope this chocolate will unlock the secret.)
Chocolate.
(He ran out of ad-libs.)
- So Min. - Yes?
It was an ad-lib.
(The village head is low on sugar and ad-libs.)
(He got me.)
- Hey. - Mr. Choi
You and I got fooled.
- Grandpa. - I give up.
- Did you simply want chocolate? - I don't know anything.
- Is it unrelated to the plot? - I don't know.
My wife likes it.
(He finally squeezes out an ad-lib.)
(Laughing)
- Are you sure there is nothing? - There is nothing.
This is hard.
(Haha ripped off Kwang Ja's name tag in this garden.)
Kwang Ja disappeared.
What is that?
(Kwang Ja disappeared.)
That's Kwang Ja's name tag.
(Only Kwang Ja's name tag remains.)
- Isn't that Kwang Ja's name tag? - Yes, it is.
- Haha... - What?
What is it?
(There is something on the back of the name tag!)
What is this?
(There are lyrics on the back of Kwang Ja's name tag.)
It's a children's song.
"And whisper to the winged angels."
(Haha ripped off Kwang Ja's name tag and saw the hint.)
"The blue sky... The faces of angels and fairies..."
(Why did Haha hide the hint?)
Does Kim Ga Gae's name tag have a clue as well?
(The owner of the stall)
- Could that be the case? - Right?
People in the photo must have hints in their name tags.
Kwang Ja and...
Should we remove Kim Ga Gae's name tag?
Let's go.
I don't know if we can tell other people about this.
(Is there a message behind the villagers' name tags?)
- You are back. - Yes, Ma'am.
- Jae Suk, will you buy something? - Well...
(He carefully approaches Kim Ga Gae.)
Do you want a fish cake bar?
- How much is coffee? - It's a dollar.
- A dollar? - Yes.
It's hot.
(Ripping off)
Why did you rip off her name tag?
(Kwang Soo ripped off Kim Ga Gae's name tag.)
(What's behind the name tag?)
- Kwang Soo ripped off her name tag. - Whose name tag?
The stall owner.
- "Sold out". - "Sold out"?
(The hint behind her name tag is "Sold out".)
What does that mean?
Why does it say "Sold out"?
Why did you rip off her name tag?
- Jong Kook. - What is up with the two of you?
What is going on?
Hold on.
(The only sold-out item is...)
- What's sold out? - Sold out?
- What? - The tissue box is sold out.
(the tissue box.)
Here it is.
Hold on.
(These greedy ones are neck-and-neck.)
We don't have time to do this.
Where are you going?
They are so greedy.
(Is there a hint inside the tissue box?)
There must be something inside.
The sign read that the tissue box is sold out.
What could this be?
(They hide in a corner and look for a hint.)
- Is there anything inside? - There is nothing inside.
This has to mean something.
(No way.)
The sign read that the tissue box is sold out.
How strange!
(He searches thoroughly.)
Tissue box was the only one that was sold out. What?
(A hand?)
What was that?
(Jae Suk suddenly slaps Kwang Soo.)
(Why did you slap me?)
- What was that? - I got back at you. We are even.
(You just slapped me.)
My goodness.
- There is nothing. - Does this mean nothing?
(They can't find any hints.)
Why did the hint say "Sold out"?
For goodness' sake.
Let's visit the village head one more time.
(They have no choice but to move.)
Is there a different approach?
(He sends Jae Suk away.)
(Kwang Soo searches the stall thoroughly.)
(However)
(There is a note deep inside the box tissue.)
(The witness' number is written on the note.)
(His eyes go wide.)
What?
It's the witness' number.
Hold on. I should call this number.
(Kwang Soo doesn't want to share the information.)
(He finds a safe spot.)
(He tries calling the witness' number.)
(He hears the ringtone.)
- Hello? - Hello.
(Someone answered!)
Hello. Are you the witness?
Who are you?
(Mysterious witness)
I told the reporter everything.
Should I tell you what happened again?
Yes, yes. Please tell me what happened again.
My friends and I visited Gujeon Village two years ago.
One friend found a gem box.
We were looking around the village in search of a key...
when we suddenly heard my friend's scream.
When we ran over, someone was attacking my friend.
That person was strong enough to rip off the name tag at once.
(A strong person who can rip off the name tag at once)
I couldn't get a good look since that person was so fast.
When we ran away in surprise, that person didn't follow us...
despite being fast enough to rip off my name tag.
I just remembered something.
(The witness remembered something.)
Okay. Okay.
My friend didn't even let us touch the gem box.
Perhaps it was unlucky.
(Did her friend want the gem box for herself?)
- Energy. - Let me touch it.
(Everyone tried to touch the gem box earlier.)
- Let me touch it. - Touching it brings good energy.
I don't want to think about it. I am hanging up. I am sorry.
(The witness gets scared and hangs up.)
But... Hello?
(Ji Hyo is looking for hints by herself.)
What is this?
(She comes across a camera.)
Is it a hint?
What?
(Inside the camera...)
(are the photos of various parts of Gujeon Village.)
(What do these photos mean?)
What?
(Screaming)
(Ji Hyo disappears with a scream.)
(Victim)
(Two members are eliminated without a sound.)
Where is everyone? Why is no one around?
Kwang Soo, what are you doing?
(He acts like nothing has happened.)
Did you poop?
(Dumbfounded)
Why would I poop?
- Why would I poop on the camera? - But you were like...
(The pose suggested that he was pooping.)
I was just sitting down. I didn't pull down my pants.
I didn't pull down my pants.
(She's finding traces of poop.)
Did you find something?
- I have something. - What is it?
Give me a hint. What I found is really important.
I will show you.
Let's take it out at the same time.
(They agree to take it out at the same time.)
- Will you show me? Is it important? - Yes.
1, 2, 3.
(Here is chocolate.)
- What is that? It's important. - Forget it. Hey.
(What is that?)
- It's important. - What is that?
Go ahead and tell me.
(I'll give you a chance.)
What is that chocolate?
What is that chocolate? Tell me.
- It's really important. - What is it?
(It's the village head's favorite.)
- The village head kept saying it. - What did he say?
"I will eat chocolate."
"I will eat it later."
(Are you kidding me?)
- What are you playing at? - I am serious. Go to him.
(Female Kwang Soo returns.)
I am serious.
You haven't changed at all, have you?
You have no intention to cooperate.
The village head said, "I will eat chocolate."
(The village head really said it.)
- "I will eat it later." - In any case...
(I love chocolate.)
He is eating so much chocolate. He won't leave his spot.
(She tries to sell Se Chan.)
I think we should join forces and solve the problem at hand.
(Kwang Soo shares the hint first.)
- Really? - Let me tell you one more thing.
It's about Kwang Ja.
On her name tag is a children's song.
- A children's song? - Yes.
(A children's song lyrics are written down?)
The lyrics of a children's song.
Which one?
I am sure you know it.
The faces of angels and fairies
(What's the message within the children's song?)
- I know it. - What was the title?
"Hill".
"I go up the hill to look up at the blue sky..."
(The hill)
(and the blue sky?)
(Meanwhile, at the house of the village head)
- You read it, right? - Yes.
Haha, you didn't read the note, did you?
(They are coming up with theories on the note they found.)
I didn't get to read it carefully.
It talked about...
how you will become eliminated...
(Investigation note)
(Those who fall for the diamond will get eliminated.)
if you fall for the diamond.
We came here...
because So Min invited us.
Hey.
(Is So Min who seduced us to the diamonds...)
Is So Min the one who is seducing us...
with the diamond?
It says invitation.
(So Min sent them an invitation to Gujeon Village.)
"Hi, guys. I've got a life-changing chance."
"There's this fantastic land where I can dig up huge diamonds."
There are gems buried in this village.
(So Min lured them with a promise of gems.)
Gems?
When someone makes a comeback, he or she prepares a special...
- Everyone does it for a surprise. - That's right.
(So Min prepared all this for her comeback?)
Yes.
So Min is acting like she isn't behind this.
(And is she playing innocent?)
She is acting like this is a mistake.
- "I don't know anything." - To be honest,
what I said back in the car was directed at So Min.
- Really? - That's right.
Jae Suk, don't lie.
(Don't be ridiculous.)
- Don't pretend to be sharp. - Why...
(It's too late.)
(Be quiet.)
Why did you interfere when Se Chan almost fell for it?
(Thanks to Haha, Jae Suk stops playing the detective.)
Keep your mouth shut!
He knows you too well.
- Se Chan was like, "Oh?" - I was like, "Oh?"
- For goodness' sake. - Hold on!
Hold on!
Does the password have six digits?
(Pathetic)
Sitting there won't help you find the password.
When is So Min's birthday?
(Six digits?)
- They wouldn't have used it again. - Gosh.
(It's been used already.)
You are a bit...
(Clucking)
You have no basic skills in deducting.
He hasn't been in a lot of those shows, so he doesn't know.
(Haha knows nothing about deduction.)
They wouldn't use the same information again.
(He ignores them and enters the number.)
Come on down.
Why are you guys so expectant?
(Why are you guys so expectant?)
(Their eyes were about to pop out.)
(Just in case)
I thought it might open.
Why are you guys so expectant to see it open?
I think So Min is behind this.
(They leave while suspecting So Min.)
- There is something about So Min. - I know.
I don't know what this hint means.
(Kwang Soo and So Min are still making a deduction on the song.)
- Why... - What does "Sold out" mean?
Why does the tissue box... What?
The tissue box is sold out.
There is an open one.
(It's a lie.)
Jae Suk and I looked inside, but there was nothing.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Yes.
(She suddenly attacks Kwang Soo.)
What?
(I have the witness's number inside.)
What? What are you hiding?
- What's inside? - What?
- What's inside? - There is nothing inside.
- It's my bag. - Then why can't I see inside?
(So Min figures there's something.)
Why can't I look inside?
Do you want to get your name tag ripped off?
Rip it off. Rip it off.
(So Min goes after Kwang Soo's name tag.)
Rip it off. That has happened many times.
Why can't I look inside? You said there's nothing.
What's that note? I have seen it.
Isn't it a reporter's note?
- A reporter's note? - That's right.
Isn't it the one from earlier?
(Flustered)
- No. - Let me see it.
Come on. Don't be like that.
What is it?
(Kwang Soo hides the hint on the witness.)
Why are you hiding it?
(She continues to go after Kwang Soo.)
- I don't have anything. - Hey!
Why did you put it in there?
- I don't have anything! - Why did you put it near your butt?
I don't have anything!
Why won't you show me the note?
I don't have anything! What note?
(Give me the hint.)
What is wrong with you?
(She's enthusiastic as she returns after a long time.)
- What is wrong with you? - Why won't you let me see it?
I don't have it.
(What are you doing?)
I don't have it!
Then why did you touch your butt? Why did you put your hand in there?
It's a habit.
(It's a habit.)
- You put your hand in there. - Hey!
(She searches his back pocket.)
What are you doing?
What is up with them? What's going on?
(Kwang Soo tries to trip her.)
Stop it. Stop it.
(So Min grabs Kwang Soo by his hair.)
(Evil So Min revives.)
- Give it to me. - I don't have anything.
- Hurry up. - Let go.
- Show me. - Let go.
- Let go. - Let go. Let go first.
- Let go. - Let go on the count of three.
(He tries to negotiate.)
- What do you have? - Let go on the count of three.
1, 2, 3.
(The negotiation falls through!)
(So Min became so healthy.)
Show me. Why won't you show me?
Let go.
What are you doing? I can't believe you guys.
(What's wrong with them?)
Let go. I can't show you unless you let go.
- I can't show you. - I let go.
- I let go. - Let go.
- I let go. - Slowly.
Okay.
Get your hands off me.
(She pulls his hair.)
- I don't have anything. - Why won't you show me?
(Crazy So Min hasn't changed at all.)
Why are you doing this to me?
He put a note in his underwear.
- Jong Kook. - So Min, you said you changed.
This is ridiculous.
She put her hand in there!
(Conspiring)
Where?
He put a note in his underwear.
Then you should give up, not put your hand in there.
(Conspiring)
- Don't be like that. - You should give up.
(While they're fighting,)
Why won't you show me the hint?
- What is it? - She touched his butt.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan who suspect So Min arrive.)
I didn't do that!
- She hasn't changed at all! - That's not true.
- So Min. - He hid a note near his butt.
- So Min. - For goodness' sake.
(Reporting)
Listen, Jae Suk. In the shrubs over there,
he was sitting down. He came outside like this.
(He cleaned his hands.)
I asked him about the note.
Did you poop in the shrubs again?
(Natural fertilizer)
- No! - Did you?
Why would I poop when the camera is on me?
(Excreting in nature)
You need to break out of that habit!
- The toilet is right there. - Jae Suk.
(Sad)
When I asked him what it was,
he put it near his butt.
- He put it in the underwear. - She kept trying to take it.
(So Min keeps suspecting Kwang Soo.)
It isn't a good hiding place since your butt is flat.
It must have fallen out. since his butt is flat.
(Then)
- Look for it. Look for it. - Since his butt is flat.
(Annoyed)
Look for it. Look for it.
Look for it. Look for it. Look for it, okay?
(His flat butt causes a suspicion.)
So Min, So Min. Here is the thing.
(By the way, the culprit must be among them.)
- When you come back from a hiatus, - That's right.
(So Min's enthusiastic today. She must be in charge of something.)
- you receive an important role. - That's right.
Also, you need to keep this in mind.
So Min is the one who invited us here.
(Kwang Soo suspects So Min too.)
- That's right. - I don't know anything.
Isn't So Min acting strange today?
That could be the case.
- Why did you bring us here? - It's like that most of the time.
(Why did you bring us here?)
(Suspecting)
So Min, did you come up with this scheme?
No, Jae Suk.
- I am not that smart. - She sent us the invitation.
(They're here because of So Min.)
I saw the flyer and sent you the invitation.
(Innocent)
(Ripping)
(Se Chan...)
(ripped off So Min's name tag!)
(She is back on the show after a two-month hiatus.)
Hey!
(So Min invited them here.)
Were you determined to rip off her name tag?
- Is she out? - Is she out?
(What's her identity?)
What does it say?
(So Min was a victim.)
Hey, I am back in a long while.
(Angry)
My goodness.
(It wasn't you?)
I am sorry.
- I am back in a long while. - I am sorry.
I fought with you, but I didn't do this to you.
So Min.
(Sorry)
So Min, I didn't do this to you.
Why didn't you leave So Min be?
(Angry)
Let me earn some money!
(I can't believe you.)
- I am sorry. - She is back after a long while.
- Is So Min out? - I am out.
(So Min who looked suspicious is eliminated by Se Chan.)
- That startled me so much. - Hey.
(Victim)
Inside the tissue box,
(There are only five survivors left.)
- I found a note. - You little...
(Inside the tissue box...)
I found a note.
(You didn't tell me?)
- You little... - Why didn't you say so earlier?
How dare you?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
You little punk.
- I won't tell you. - Come on.
(I'm offended.)
- I won't tell you for real. - Please tell us.
(Condescending)
This is a hint you can't get anymore.
- All right. - Please tell us.
(Calm down, Kwang Soo.)
- Share the information with us. - Don't be annoyed.
We were simply reacting.
(Soothing Kwang Soo)
- Just go with the flow. - Tell us.
(Okay)
- Tell us. - Tell us.
- There was a phone number. - What?
And?
A witness' number.
What? Did you call the number?
- Yes. When I called, - Who picked up?
a woman picked up.
(He heard a witness account over the phone.)
My friends and I visited Gujeon Village two years ago.
(The witness visited Gujeon Village...)
One friend found a gem box.
(and her friend found a gem box.)
We were looking around the village...
when we suddenly heard my friend's scream.
(She heard her friend's scream.)
When we ran over, someone was attacking my friend.
(Someone was attacking her friend.)
That person was...
very fast and strong.
(The attacker was very fast and strong.)
That person was very fast and strong.
I think he is setting me up.
- No, no. - He could have made this up.
(If he's strong and fast, could it be Jong Kook?)
No, no. The witness really said that.
Her friend who got eliminated didn't let anyone touch the gem box.
- Her friend who got eliminated? - Yes.
Fast and strong?
(The truth of Gujeon Village is shrouded in mystery.)
Someone who is fast and strong.
Let's scatter and find more hints.
(They decide to look for more hints.)
What on earth is going on?
(Jae Suk searches for more hints.)
(What is this place?)
Gosh, you startled me.
(The only survivor among the four sisters,)
(Kim Sam Nyeo is here.)
You startled me.
Mister, please save me.
- What? - Please save me.
What are you doing here alone?
I was hiding because I became so scared...
upon seeing my sisters get eliminated.
Who eliminated them?
You know,
Jeon Dang Po disappeared.
(Jeon Dang Po who stayed with the four sisters disappeared.)
That's right. Jeon Dang Po was nowhere to be seen.
Now that Jeon Dang Po disappeared,
(Then is it Jeon Dang Po who eliminated the victims?)
I think that person might come to me.
That's why I am hiding.
This village seems to have a secret.
Well, I...
I don't know anything!
(He attacks Kim Sam Nyeo.)
- I don't know anything! - Gosh, hold on.
What are you doing? I don't know...
(He ripped off her name tag!)
I don't know...
(Is there a hint on Kim Sam Nyeo's name tag?)
She's just a victim.
(Detective Yu killed an innocent citizen.)
You killed an innocent citizen.
(Kim Sam Nyeo died too early.)
Excuse me.
But...
(I have more lines.)
Did you pass away?
(Jae Suk has no words.)
I am sorry.
Sam Nyeo's name tag doesn't have a hint.
(He killed off Kim Sam Nyeo.)
For goodness' sake. This is hard.
(He thinks about Kim Sam Nyeo's last words.)
(Jae Suk looks for Jeon Dang Po in the village.)
Where did Jeon Dang Po go?
Today's mission is so hard.
(He finds Jeon Dang Po!)
You are here.
(Jeon Dang Po is alone.)
What brings you here?
- Sir. - Yes?
Kim Sam Nyeo said...
you were acting a bit strange.
- She said you had disappeared. - What?
(Jeon Dang Po was with the sisters, but he suddenly disappeared.)
Jeon Dang Po disappeared.
You aren't related to the village head, are you?
(What's his secret?)
No, I am not.
- No? - No.
What are you doing?
(He attacks Jeon Dang Po this time!)
Gosh, my head hurts.
(Is there a hint on his name tag?)
(There is a hint!)
"It's the darkest under the lamp."
What does this hint mean?
(Pawnshop and lamp...)
"It's the darkest under the lamp"?
Is there something at the pawnshop?
(Is there another hint at the pawnshop?)
(He looks underneath.)
What is this?
(He finds a mysterious cell phone.)
What is this cell phone?
Who is "Big Brother"?
("Big Brother" is the contact that is saved on the phone.)
(Jae Suk tries calling Big Brother.)
(Someone answers the phone.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Mysterious Big Brother)
- Hello. - Where are you?
Who is this?
This is your little brother.
Where are you?
I'm at the pawnshop.
What?
(The voice sounds familiar.)
Where?
Where are you?
Isn't this Haha's voice?
(Big Brother turns out to be Haha.)
Where are you?
(What does Haha have to do with this village?)
(What's going on?)
It's Haha.
Haha must be hiding something.
He asked me where I was. That means there's someone else.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook is searching the rest of the houses.)
What? There's a picture.
(What?)
(There's a picture of two men.)
(The man on the left is Haha.)
Haha?
(Haha's arm is around a mysterious man.)
Haha must be hiding something.
(Haha is hiding a secret.)
Who is the man next to him, by the way?
- Did you find anything? - Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook reunite.)
- Come here. - Why?
I found a picture.
(A picture of Haha was among pictures of the villagers.)
It's Haha.
- Who is the other man? - Who is he?
(The call with Haha and his picture)
- Gosh. - What?
What is it?
I found this cell phone.
(A moment ago)
You found this?
What is it?
- Someone is saved as Big Brother. - "Big Brother"?
- So I called this number. - Okay.
And Haha answered the phone.
(All the clues are pointing to Haha.)
Who...
(He's been keeping a distance from everyone and eliminated Kwang Ja.)
Where are you?
(The culprit)
It's Haha.
Is this guy his little brother?
(Does Haha live in this village?)
- Is he? - I don't know.
We should...
(They set out to find Haha.)
drive him into a corner.
(Meanwhile, at the village head's house...)
Mr. Choi!
I know you're not sick.
(Yelling)
(Haha is arguing with the village head.)
Are you?
Why are you doing this?
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook walk in.)
I have all the evidence.
(The village head and Haha are getting into a fight.)
Stop trying to find out more.
(Staring)
Why are you asking me that?
- Hey. - It's because you...
(Sneak attack)
- What's going on? - The village head...
Hold on. I'm serious.
(Listen to me.)
You probably don't trust me, but...
Please stop him.
- He just yelled at me. - He's trying to harm me.
(The village head is frightened.)
I mean it.
(Haha is overreacting.)
He just yelled at me.
He's always angry.
(The village head gets angry frequently.)
- He's always angry. - Mr. Choi is always angry.
- Did you answer the phone? - What?
(Jae Suk asks Haha about the person saved as Big Brother.)
- Yes, I did. - Show me your phone.
- Why is your number saved here? - Give it to me.
(They call Big Brother again.)
(The number is saved as Little Brother in Haha's phone.)
Sit down first. Are you suspecting me?
Of course.
(Did Haha eliminate all the members?)
- Guys. - We'll sit down.
Stand over there.
I have something unbelievable.
- I'm serious. - Show us.
I'll play it for you.
(When he is about to be caught,)
(Haha takes out a voice recorder.)
- What is it? - I'll play it for you.
(Then Haha takes out a voice recorder.)
- The village head... - Hurry up.
(Haha plays something on the recorder.)
It's you, Dong Sik, right?
You stole my keys, didn't you?
I knew it was you.
Why did you pretend to have Alzheimer's?
Your keys...
What are they?
You're going to die soon anyway.
So give me back my keys.
Where are they?
- So what's the cell phone? - What is it?
(What's the recording about?)
My little brother is called...
- Dong Sik. - And?
He asked me...
to come to this village and settle his grudge.
(Haha's brother Dong Sik asked him to settle his grudge.)
You heard the village head tell him he couldn't leave the village alive.
- That was your brother's voice? - Yes, that was his voice.
(It's my brother's voice.)
(Haha's true identity is revealed.)
Haha, there's a letter for you.
(A few days ago)
Please read it out loud.
(Haha got a letter...)
What's this?
(and a key.)
"Dear Haha."
"Is everything all right?"
"I've been staying in a village for a month now."
"Once I'm done learning about the special diamond here,"
(A reporter is covering Gujeon Village.)
"I'll write an exclusive news story about it."
(Ha Dong Sik)
(Dong Sik, Haha's brother, was writing about Gujeon Village.)
"Tomorrow is D-day."
"I still have to do one last check."
"But I think I'm getting close..."
"to the Immortal Heart, which I've only heard about."
(Reporter Ha got near the Immortal Heart.)
"But this whole thing is pretty dangerous."
"If you stop hearing from me,"
"you'll receive this letter and a key by this time next year."
(Last May,)
Did something happen? Did he die?
(Dong Sik sensed a danger and wrote this letter.)
"Don't trust anyone too fast."
"Please keep this a secret."
"I love you, Brother."
(Giving a key to Haha, Dong Sik asked him to finish the story.)
- What is it? - He found it.
(When Kwang Soo found the Immortal Heart...)
(I should try opening it with my key.)
- He knew the location. - I'm sure.
(While Kwang Soo was distracted,)
(Haha tried to open the gem box but failed.)
It won't open.
(This isn't the key to the Immortal Heart.)
I can't open it.
(He tries opening other boxes too.)
It doesn't fit.
(He hasn't found a lock that opens with the key.)
Are you looking for your little brother?
(Kwang Ja kept following Haha talking about his brother.)
Beware of those who try to get in your way.
(Haha's brother told him to beware of those who get in his way.)
- Did you just try to rip it off? - "If you find those,"
"please get rid of them."
(Haha eliminates Lee Kwang Ja, who has been hovering around him.)
(Was Kwang Ja trying to get in my way or not?)
"I go up the hill to look up at the blue sky..."
(A hint was hidden on the back of Kwang Ja's name tag.)
Grapes, stars, trees...
(Haha examines the bench that Kwang Ja used to play around.)
A hill?
(He finds Kwang Ja's hill.)
This is just like the lyrics.
(Following the lyrics, Haha goes up the hill and looks up at the sky.)
I'm up on the hill now.
(Awesome)
There are angels.
(He finds angel figurines in the tree.)
It's the password for the safe.
(Thanks to the angel figurines, Haha finds the next safe.)
I found the password for the safe. Unbelievable.
(He finds the safe hidden in the village.)
(The safe is open.)
What is this?
(He finds a voice recorder...)
(and the conversations on it.)
I knew it was you.
It was the village head.
(The culprit)
(That's why Haha was questioning the village head.)
Are you saying the village head harmed your brother?
(Haha was an innocent outsider.)
- Yes. - Is that what you found out?
Does that mean that the village head has the key?
(Does the village head have the key to the Immortal Heart?)
No, we have to rip off his name tag first.
I think there's a secret hidden under his name tag.
(The village head's name tag)
- Mr. Choi. - We have no choice.
Don't!
(The village head's name tag is ripped off immediately.)
- What is it? - Right?
(His name tag was hiding the password for the safe.)
- It's the password for the safe. - It's the password for the safe.
(Let's open the safe upstairs.)
- Where's the safe? - It's 940...
- It's upstairs. - Let's go upstairs.
(There's a hint on the village head's name tag like villagers.)
See? I'm innocent. Trust me.
- I mean it. - Is it okay to rip off name tags?
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan are searching another house.)
Who eliminated Suk Jin?
I don't know.
Hold on. Could it be Jong Kook?
- What do you think? - The whole thing?
(Come to think about it, no one suspected Jong Kook today.)
Isn't it possible?
The culprit is supposed to be strong.
(According to the witness, the culprit is strong and fast.)
- Who could that be? - You're right.
It must be Jong Kook.
(Shocked)
- Did you memorize the password? - Start.
(Meanwhile, at the village head's house...)
- Yes. - It's 940302.
(Without knowing what's going on, they open the safe.)
What's this?
It's another box.
(Annoyed)
Are these Russian dolls?
(There's another locked box in the safe.)
- Gosh. - How many are there?
I'll be honest. I have a key.
- Why didn't you tell us earlier? - I mean...
(Would Dong Sik's key open this box?)
It's because you didn't trust me.
- What are you talking about? - I can't believe you.
(The box was hidden deep inside the village head's house.)
Fine, I'll try opening it.
(Maybe Dong Sik's key will open this box.)
I get it. Trust me.
What is this? We just need to find the key.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan and Kwang Soo are coming up with a plan.)
(They find a piece of paper in the trash can.)
What is this?
"A man mysteriously goes missing in Gujeon Village..."
(It's a new article from a few years ago.)
"after finding the most expensive diamond, Immortal Heart."
- Hey. - I'm not supposed to have it?
(Feeling guilty)
I think you're doomed.
Look at this.
(The article says...)
Someone went missing after finding it.
(whoever finds the gem box all go missing.)
- You found it too. - Hold on.
I got goosebumps.
Whoever finds the gem box...
You'll disappear too.
Can you hold this for me?
(Passing)
- Wait! - Gosh, you startled me.
(Just then)
- There's another picture here. - Let me see.
- It's a different picture. - No, it's the same...
(They find another picture by the window.)
- Why is she looking that way? - She's looking the other way.
(Before)
(The new picture, the previous picture)
(The pictures were taken...)
(in the yard next to the house.)
Let's go there.
(Is there an important hint hidden in the yard?)
- Hurry up and open it. - Open it.
(The key fits in the lock.)
(The box in the village head's safe opens.)
- It's open. - Unbelievable.
There's something inside.
Let me see the picture again.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan look around the yard in the picture.)
This is the place, right?
(There's a note...)
- Goodness. - There's something.
(in the box.)
I can't believe you.
- You brat. - You brat.
(This yard is supposed to hold an important clue.)
Gosh, I have no idea.
What is this?
- What does it say? - "To ward off misfortune..."
"and enjoy prosperity,"
"honor the scarecrow as your guardian..."
(The scarecrow grabs Kwang Soo's name tag.)
"and offer him a sacrifice every year."
(Kwang Soo is eliminated immediately.)
"Whoever touches the scarecrow's gem box..."
"will be offered up as a sacrifice."
"The scarecrow will take away everyone's name."
(The secret of Gujeon Village is finally revealed.)
- What's that? - This is why I called you here.
- Read the flyer. - What's this?
(Every May, Gujeon Village attracted outsiders to their festival.)
Gujeon Village.
(Blinded by their greed, the Running Man members attended the festival.)
"There is a village where gems are buried in the ground."
(The villagers were very happy to see the outsiders.)
Hello. Welcome to Gujeon Village.
(Every year, outsiders have been lured to the village.)
- Take it. - Hurry up and dig up more.
(The first one to find...)
- What is it? - He found it.
(the Immortal Heart was Kwang Soo.)
- He found it. - He knew the location.
(That's how the Immortal Heart got uncovered.)
- Hey. - He knew the location.
There must be a gem for real.
(When sacrificial victims touched the Immortal Heart,)
- Let's see. - Let's see.
- Is the hat a clue? - Is it? Let's get going.
(the scarecrow, which they thought was a mannequin,)
(started hunting.)
- Ji Hyo, hold onto this. - But I found it.
(Everybody touched the gem box.)
It doesn't even matter.
(Ji Hyo found the most decisive lead.)
Is this a lead?
(She was looking through the pictures on the camera.)
(The scarecrow eliminated her.)
(The hunter is stronger than anybody,)
That person was strong enough to rip off the name tag at once.
I couldn't get a good look since that person was so fast.
(and he is lightning fast.)
(He eliminated Suk Jin after that.)
(Kim Il Nyeo, E Nyeo, and Sa Nyeo were eliminated as well.)
The person holding this gem box...
(Any outsider who touched the Immortal Heart...)
will disappear.
(gets sacrificed.)
(Last May, Dong Sik investigated and found out about everything.)
(While hiding the Immortal Heart, he got eliminated by the scarecrow.)
(The materials he collected...)
(were locked away by the villagers.)
(Each villager kept a secret.)
- "I had fun with my friends today." - "With my friends today."
(He was the one...)
- "He watched us pleasantly." - What?
(who kept an eye on the village children.)
(He's a silent assassin who was watching the whole village.)
(Scarecrow)
(He eliminated Kwang Soo before he could resist.)
What was that? Hey!
"There's only one way to break the curse of the scarecrow."
"You must burn his straw hat."
"That's the only way to annihilate him completely."
(If you burn his straw hat, the curse gets broken.)
- The incinerator. - Let's go.
Let's burn the straw hat.
(Burn the scarecrow's hat in the incinerator.)
Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk! - What?
- Who? - Jae Suk.
In the picture, it wasn't the scarecrow.
(They finally hear about the identity of the scarecrow.)
- It was a person. - It is.
- The scarecrow... - Wait, let me see the straw hat.
We have to remove this straw hat.
(Once they burn this hat, the scarecrow gets eliminated.)
Let's go catch him.
(Confident)
- There are four of us. - We can do it.
(The scarecrow versus the 4 members.)
- He moves so fast. - Really?
- Over there... - He's coming!
- What? - He's coming.
(The scarecrow approaches.)
What is it?
(The scarecrow's blitz attack.)
What? What is it?
What is it?
Who are you?
(Scarecrow versus Jong Kook)
Hold on.
(He comes up fast and attacks Jong Kook.)
What was that?
(Jong Kook is out.)
What was that? Who are you?
(Why is he so strong?)
- He's so strong! - My gosh.
(The scarecrow of Gujeon Village...)
- What was that? - What was that?
(chases the three members.)
What was that?
What was that? My gosh.
- What was that? - Jae Suk!
Shouldn't we help him?
(He starts hunting the other members before the camera catches up.)
What was that?
I'm so scared.
- What was that? - I'm scared.
(The scarecrow caught up with Se Chan who was running away.)
Hold on.
I'm scared. Wait.
I'm scared.
(Se Chan is out.)
I'm scared!
That was so scary!
(Jae Suk and Haha are the only members left.)
(The scarecrow is powerful and fast.)
Jae Suk, we have to work together.
(He's different.)
Who is this person?
- See? He's out already. - Okay.
(They decide to team up.)
Let's go.
Together. We can do it together.
(The scarecrow disappeared in an instant.)
- Is he out? - Where did he go?
Where did he go?
Don't run away.
He's over there. Jae Suk, he's there.
(Scarecrow versus Jae Suk and Haha)
- Let's do it together. - From above.
From above.
(They fight 2 to 1, but the scarecrow defends himself.)
- He's so fast. - Why is he so fast?
(He's driving them nuts.)
(Haha grabbed the straw hat!)
(He only ripped some straws.)
- Good job. - What was that?
(This is a volatile situation.)
Who is this person?
(Goosebumps)
Come here!
(Will the scarecrow rip their name tags or will they steal his hat?)
Hey, hey.
(He stole the straw hat.)
Burn it.
(Haha narrowly stole the hat.)
Hey, hey.
(He sprints to the incinerator.)
Burn it.
(The scarecrow can't see well because of the mask.)
(If he manages to burn the hat, both members win!)
This is hot.
(He put the straw hat in the fire.)
(The curse has been broken.)
(Gujeon Village doesn't need to make sacrifices anymore.)
(They also obtained the key to the Immortal Heart...)
(that was in the hat.)
Everybody, today's race was the Secret of Gujeon Village.
(It's the final ending.)
(The secret of Gujeon Village is finally revealed.)
This village was protected by the Almighty of the scarecrow.
(They retained the village by making innocent sacrifices.)
- And then? - Outsiders who touch the gem box...
all get sacrificed and get eliminated by the scarecrow.
(They all became sacrifices because they touched the box.)
- I touched it. - The gem box.
People who touched it got eliminated.
(The one person who shocked all the members today)
You were all probably wondering who the scarecrow was.
Who was it?
- Let's invite him here first. - Okay.
(The identity of the scarecrow is finally revealed.)
- Scarecrow, come on out. - He scared me to death.
(He was known to be very strong and fast.)
- He was no joke. - Really?
- He was so fast. - He's so fast.
(The identity of the scarecrow that drove everyone into a panic.)
- He was great in ripping name tags. - He's scary.
Who is it?
You were all probably wondering who the scarecrow was.
(Jong Kook was surprised at his strength and speed. He is...)
He...
owns a channel. It's Kim Gye Ran of Physical Gallery.
(It's Kim Gye Ran of Physical Gallery.)
It's Kim Gye Ran?
- Nice to meet you. - Hello.
- Wow, friends. - I watch his videos a lot.
(His usual greeting)
- I'm the bald man. - The bald man.
(He's extremely athletic as former Underwater Demolition Team.)
(He has a top physique and is stronger than most people.)
(Kim Gye Ran)
I'm the bald man.
(I know him!)
- The bald man. - Hello.
Jong Kook.
(The workout masters meet.)
- I wanted to meet you the most. - The bald man!
(They love each other.)
- I wanted to meet him the most. - Really?
I really like him.
Jong Kook was never this happy with any other guest.
(The best guest for Jong Kook.)
- He's so excited. - He's so happy.
(They greet each other over and over.)
- I love him. - Okay!
I really like him.
I trust his workout channel the most.
(Jong Kook trusts his YouTube videos the most.)
- I know. - Kim Gye Ran?
I watch your videos too.
Haha managed to burn his straw hat.
(The final result is revealed.)
- You stole it from me. - Narrowly.
(It was close.)
The scarecrow got eliminated, and here's the gem box.
(Winner Haha gets the real gem box.)
What's that?
Don't you die if you touch that?
(What's inside?)
No, I broke the curse.
(The prize gets revealed.)
What is it?
- Goodness. - It's the Immortal Heart.
(Not impressed)
It's the Immortal Heart.
This is useless to bring it home.
- Does he have to take that? - Your kids will like it.
You'll get eight dollars from it.
That's the gem of this village, the Immortal Heart.
(Serious)
That's the Immortal Heart?
(Overreacting)
- This is insane. I'm envious. - That's amazing.
(You can't list a prize for the Immortal Heart.)
This is amazing.
I'm envious!
(I'm jealous.)
We usually give the prize to the guest.
(Kind)
It's fine.
- Haha, you can't do that. - Gye Ran.
(Haha tries to give away the Immortal Heart.)
- That's unnecessary. - Take it home.
Since you're on Running Man.
(He tries to run away.)
Can I just take a picture with you?
- Just a picture. - We'll take a picture.
(We thank Kim Gye Ran for taking part.)
- Great work. - Thank you.
Great work.
- That was unexpected. - This is amazing.
(TWICE is back as a whole group.)
- All nine of them are here. - What a surprise.
(Return of popular group TWICE)
- It's TWICE! - It's TWICE!
(It's TWICE.)
She's cute!
(Check out their unexpected charms!)
- Great job! - There you go.
(They rip name tags without hesitation...)
- Rip it, Tzuyu. - You have to rip it.
(and can do slapstick comedy.)
Jeongyeon, we're on the same team.
(She is a bigger traitor than Kwang Soo.)
- We're on the same team. - She's super rash.
(Is she the new traitor?)
Do you want to be the captain?
(They're tempted by the captain role.)
- How could you do that? - I'm sorry, Captain.
Make Jeongyeon the captain,
(Once you become the captain,)
and let's eliminate Kwang Soo first.
(you can eliminate anybody.)
- He betrayed you. - What a traitor.
(Form alliances and betray them to throw off your teammates.)
- Kwang Soo! - You wanted to be the captain.
- You lied again? - You'll ruin everything.
(Build solid trust...)
- Have you gone mad? - Can you be my guarantor?
(and find your guarantor!)
- I'll follow you to the underworld. - What's this? Don't trust friends.
(A war ensues to obtain the captain's privilege!)
You have to become the captain.
(Captains of Running Man)