(To the refreshing blue ocean of Jeju Island)
This is my first time here since shooting Running Man.
(The members flew here early in the morning.)
This is nice.
Ji Hyo, why did you get here yesterday, by the way?
(They arrived the day before...)
- I just... - Did you get here yesterday?
(and woke up in a hotel in Jeju this morning.)
This looks fake. Hello.
(They head to the beach excitedly.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Isn't this computer graphics? - This is amazing.
Jeju Island!
It's so nice to be outside.
Welcome.
(Hyper)
The ocean looks beautiful.
It's been a long time since we did this last time.
(They're excited...)
- It's beautiful. - This is so nice.
(as they haven't felt the wind of Jeju for a while.)
I couldn't go anywhere this year.
I took an airplane after a long time.
This feels different.
It felt strange to fly in a plane.
(Even the long-distance traveler finds the flight awkward.)
- I know. - Because it's been so long.
Look at the stylists. They're taking pictures of the scenery.
(Both casts and production crew are excited after a while.)
- There's Jong Kook's stylist. - They're on a vacation.
They will upload the pictures on their social media.
I was excited last night.
You've got some blusher on your face to look lively.
(So Min's cheeks are redder than usual.)
- Because I'm in Jeju Island. - Really?
She woke up at four to go to a beauty salon this morning.
- Really? - Yes.
I wanted to look pretty. I want to look nice.
(Since I'm in Jeju Island, I wanted to look pretty.)
We've come to Jeju Island after a really long time.
(Jeju Special)
And we have four actresses who are perfect for the scenery...
(4 actresses that match the view of Jeju Island)
- of Jeju Island. - My gosh.
- Really? - Here come the actresses.
Welcome.
- Then... - They've come a long way.
I decided to come here because I heard you'd come.
That's not important. It's just good to be on TV.
(Down to earth)
There they are.
(Two supermodels...)
- That's Choi Yeo Jin. - I haven't seen Yeo Jin for long.
(came all the way to Jeju Island.)
Yeo Jin.
Hello.
- E Hyun. - Hello.
(So E Hyun, Choi Yeo Jin)
There's E Hyun.
(Nice to meet you.)
And who else?
Can we go there? I'm nervous.
(Excited)
- It's Ju Bin. - There's Ju Bin.
(The 2 popular actresses are not used to a variety show yet.)
And Ji Eun is here too.
Nice to meet you.
(Lee Ju Bin, Han Ji Eun)
She's from "Be Melodramatic".
(Han Ji Eun played a single working mom...)
- It's gross. - I said no. Why is it gross?
(in "Be Melodramatic".)
- You'll be more anxious. - I think so.
I love salad. Beondegi is really good.
(She's a rising star who shows her distinctive acting in many dramas.)
You think everyone is twisted but you.
(She played an actress with a unique personality in "Be Melodramatic".)
Our actress is sulky. Let's go.
(Lee Ju Bin showed her impressive acting in "Mister Sunshine".)
(Actresses of Jeju Island Special)
They've come a long way.
- I'm glad you're here. - They've come a long way.
(You came a long way.)
Let's talk to them one by one then.
(It's time to introduce the guests.)
We have So E Hyun here. Your real name is Jo Woo Jung.
- Right. - I didn't know.
- It's a pretty name. - I like your name.
Why are you using a stage name?
My agency consulted a fortune-teller and said it would be successful.
- A fortune-teller? - So E Hyun?
(She got her name from shamanism.)
- You're honest. - Right.
I had nothing to do with it.
I like the name, Woo Jung.
I know. It's like Jo Friendship.
Jo Friendship?
(Laughing)
(Jo Friendship is quite too literal.)
What? Jo Friendship?
- Is it her English name? - Yes.
That sounds great.
(Friendship Jo from Jeonju, Jeolla Province)
And we have Choi Yeo Jin here.
(Next is E Hyun's supermodel friend, )
(Choi Yeo Jin who will present real friendship with Jo Friendship.)
It's been a long time.
- It's been years. - You've met Ji Hyo before.
(Do Yeo Jin and Ji Hyo know each other?)
In "Lovely Horribly".
- Right. - We met in "Emergency Couple".
(They starred in "Emergency Couple".)
I see. "Emergency Couple".
What was Ji Hyo like when you worked with her?
She's a sleepyhead.
(Without hesitation)
- She was the same. - It's the same.
(Ji Hyo is consistent.)
She's consistent all the time.
It was surprising that she could act so well right away.
- That's surprising, right? - Yes.
We're also surprised by that.
(For 10 years)
She's good here as well.
(She reacts fast even while sleeping.)
She just plays games as soon as she wakes up.
- And she doesn't get puffy. - She claps her hands getting up.
I'm serious.
- She's like a machine. - That's amazing.
(She can turn on and off her sleep switch.)
All right. Next, we have Han Ji Eun here.
(Rising actress Han Ji Eun)
- Hello. - When I saw her coming,
I wondered where I knew her from.
- It's "Be Melodramatic". - She was in "Be Melodramatic".
("Be Melodramatic" is Jong Kook's favorite.)
- Right. It's "Be Melodramatic". - I love the drama.
She went to the same college as So Min.
(She went to university with So Min.)
- Really? - Yes.
- We went to the same school. - Tell us about So Min.
Ji Eun, what was So Min like back in school?
(This is our chance.)
So Min?
I don't know much about her.
- She was... - They weren't so close.
(The hyenas go for it.)
I worked really hard in school. That's strange.
(They don't seem close.)
So Min, do you remember anything about Ji Eun?
(Laughing)
- Of course, I do. - Okay.
(But I don't remember it clearly.)
But I don't remember it clearly.
Did you two fight or something?
(It's more awkward when they're not close enough.)
- But I don't remember it clearly. - Did you two fight or something?
- It's so strange. - You two had a fight, right?
(This is getting interesting.)
- So Min, did you fight with her? - You should make up.
(Jo Friendship)
So Min won't start talking before she hears anything.
Anyway, it wasn't...
Something wasn't so clean.
You mean your relationship?
- Me? - I mean, it was clean...
(Flustered)
- Ji Eun is upset now. "Me?" - I mean our feelings...
(Excited)
- No. - They might fight.
There wasn't a man involved, but her friend was involved with a man.
(Giving excuses)
- Me? - I mean...
(Suddenly talking honorifics)
- She said, "Me?" - No.
- "Me?" - So Min.
(They love this situation.)
You two weren't so close, right?
- It's not like that. - What's going on?
(Flustered)
I'm not saying Ji Eun was involved with a man.
(Correcting)
- Ji Eun is upset. - Hang on. Let me correct this.
(She keeps correcting their relationship.)
It's not that there was a man between Ji Eun and me.
- I see. - I meant Ji Eun's friend.
(There was no issue between them, )
(but they became awkward due to a boyfriend problem.)
- I see. - We have plenty of time today.
You should think about it.
Ji Eun said she had something to say. Please tell us.
Well...
She's glaring at So Min now.
This is my first time in a variety show, so I'm not sure...
- how much I should talk. - Tell us about the whole thing.
(Instigating)
- Just be honest. - Tell us everything about So Min.
(What does So Min mean to Ji Eun?)
- It's okay. - You remember something about her.
I remember that she was in the group dating dream team.
The group dating dream team.
- She went on a lot of dates. - That's right.
(They're getting their memories back.)
- And Ji Eun was there. - Right.
- I remembered something. - What?
- I can't say that. - No. What is it? Tell me first.
What is it? Tell me first.
(Flustered)
What?
(Laughing)
- What? She can say anything. - I remember what she was like.
(So Min starts to recall the past, and Ji Eun is nervous about it.)
- Tell us what it is. - I remember it now.
- You're making me nervous. - Tell us.
I once said that I went on a lot of group dates back in school.
I tried hard to lighten up the mood, but the boys asked someone else out.
- Do you remember I said that? - You did.
It was Han Ji Eun.
(Their pasts were finally revealed.)
It was Han Ji Eun, everyone.
I lightened up the mood...
(So Min in charge of lifting spirits)
- and thought things would go well. - You had a good chance.
(Ji Eun in charge of meeting them after)
I just remembered that I was close to her.
- You know that So Min... - She lightened up the mood.
(Jae Suk also admits So Min's speaking skills.)
- is good with words, right? - Indeed.
- I led them while playing games. - We've been there too.
(Slowly remembering)
In short, you were in the same position as Jae Suk's.
- Yes, that's right. - The female version of Jae Suk.
(She was in charge of bringing them together.)
- She was in my position. - She was the ice breaker.
You weren't asked out by anyone because you led everyone.
(Advising)
The atmosphere was so good that day, Suk Jin.
- Jae Suk was always like you. - Suk Jin, don't...
Don't act like you know much about a group blind date.
- We did it when I was younger too. - I know.
(Come on.)
Next up is Lee Ju Bin.
(Last guest, Lee Ju Bin)
- Hello. - Welcome.
- I'm so excited to see her here. - Hello.
I'd like to tell you something right now.
(Reading interesting news)
- She said she wanted to be here, - What's the reason?
and the person she wanted to team up with was...
Se Chan.
Why?
(Thrilled)
- Exactly. - Ask her. We're in Jeju Island.
- Why? - Oh, my.
- No one has picked me before. - Let's ask her.
(His comment made her laugh.)
- Why? - Let's hear it.
- Let's hear the reason. - You have a chance.
(Extremely excited)
- Let's let her explain. - Why did you pick him?
Let's forget why you wanted to be on this show.
(Why did she pick Se Chan?)
Why did you pick Se Chan?
I've been a big fan since he appeared...
- on "People Looking for a Laugh". - "Woong's Father"?
- Yes, I liked "Woong's Father", - My goodness.
(Fluent)
"The Invisible Man", and "The Best".
(Helping Doll Chan)
Se Chan is even more charming in person.
- He has such a kind heart. - But I'm sure...
- I'm counting on you. - But I'm sure...
- She's counting on me. - Really?
(She's counting on me.)
Will you go back to Seoul today?
- Yes, I'll leave today. - Oh, I see.
- What a shame. - I'm sorry.
(That's too bad.)
(Oh, I'm staying for one more day.)
- You see... - She drew the line.
- People like her... - Yes.
usually leave hastily as soon as the shoot ends.
(Many got him excited and rushed home after.)
- They just run away. - We don't even get to say goodbye.
She said she'll leave later today,
but you might see her on the plane tomorrow.
(My schedule has been changed.)
That would be the worst.
- Se Chan's heart is wide open. - Yes, my heart is open.
(Se Chan opens his heart easily.)
I'm sorry to say this from the beginning,
but I don't think you have a chance with her.
- Jae Suk, come on. - Listen.
- We all must... - Don't be so negative.
(Jae Suk is a realist who doesn't accept a single hope.)
- We must face the reality. - I understand.
- I agree. - Yes.
- Gosh, seriously. - He's right about that.
Let's welcome our four guests.
(Welcome to Jeju Island.)
Today,
- you'll be divided into four teams. - I see.
(There will be 4 teams of 3 in today's race.)
Our guests will be the team leaders, and choose their team members.
(The four guests are team captains, )
(and they'll pick their teammates.)
We asked the guests to choose...
(We asked them the 4 best members they want on their teams.)
the best four members to be on their teams,
- Okay. - and ranked you by popularity.
(The members are ranked by popularity.)
A popularity ranking again?
But you won't reveal who picked who, right?
(Feeling sorry)
- It makes us disappointed somehow. - Yes.
- Exactly. - We get our hopes up.
Don't take it to heart.
(Cool)
- Also, some of you... - Yes.
get the wrong idea. It doesn't mean they like you.
- They just want you on their teams. - Just as a team member.
(The preference for victory)
- Just as a team member. That's all. - Exactly.
- But it means a lot to us. - That's true.
(Serious)
- The person in fourth place. - Is that the last place?
Let's find out who's in fourth place.
(4th place, Se Chan)
The fourth place is not bad.
It's Se Chan.
- Is it a good thing? - Of course.
- He must've been her best choice. - I guess only Ju Bin picked him.
(Was he Ju Bin's number 1 pick as she mentioned?)
Only Ju Bin? I don't think so.
- You can say that Se Chan is... - It's not bad.
(4th place, Se Chan, Ju Bin's 1st choice)
- high on the ranking. - It's good.
(Proud of ranking high)
- I'm high on the ranking. - It's not bad at all.
Let's find out who's in third place.
- Oh, my. It's Suk Jin. - Suk Jin? Hang on.
(What?)
- Really? - It's strange.
(Admitting it himself)
- You manipulated the result, right? - What's going on?
It's because they would feel comfortable around him.
I can't believe this. Are you serious?
(3rd place, Suk Jin, Yeo Jin's 2nd and Ji Eun's 3rd choice)
They know who is the most popular member among us.
Let's move on to the person in second place.
- What? - It's Jong Kook.
My gosh. I didn't expect that.
(2nd place, Jong Kook, E Hyun's 1st, Ju Bin's 2nd, Yeo Jin's 4th choice)
- Jong Kook is in second place? - I'm surprised.
- Then who's in first place? - It must be Jae Suk.
That person won by an overwhelming majority.
I'm sure it's Jae Suk.
(Obvious)
- By an overwhelming majority? - What?
(Who won overwhelming support from the guests and came in first?)
- By an overwhelming majority? - It's Kwang Soo.
(1st place, Kwang Soo)
(Kwang Soo seems more surprised than the others.)
- What? - It wasn't Jae Suk?
Then what about us?
Jae Suk is not in the top four?
(The number 3 boasts.)
- Then what about us? - Hey, Jae Suk.
(They'll be ranked at the bottom.)
- What could be our rankings? - Oh, no.
- Kwang Soo is in first place? - This is ridiculous.
- This is ridiculous. - Did you mix up the order?
(1st place, Kwang Soo, Yeo Jin and Ji Eun's 1st, )
(E Hyun's 2nd, and Ju Bin's 4th choice)
- Did you mix up the order? - What's going on?
- Did you mix up the order? - I think that's the case.
(Doubting)
- We didn't mix up the order. - Isn't he in last place?
(They were telling each other not to put too much meaning earlier.)
- But we... - I'm already upset from the start.
Kwang Soo is in first place.
Let us vote for our best choices too!
(They're both offended.)
Check the rest rankings.
- All right. - Let's leave, Ji Hyo.
I knew this would happen when I heard female guests would come.
(Sullen)
Let's go, Ji Hyo. Let's go.
(Whatever.)
- Why did you throw sand? - Hey, get the car ready.
- So Min. - Why did you throw sand?
You two might be in 5th and 6th places.
(He doesn't mean it.)
- Seriously. - Wait and see.
Do you think I went to the beauty salon to be humiliated like this?
(I even went to the beauty salon at 4am to look pretty.)
- At 4am? - Actually,
I understand why you're upset.
One of our guests is your friend.
- Your friend didn't pick you. - No, she didn't.
(No friendship)
- We went to the same school. - The person in fifth place.
(5th place, Jae Suk)
- I'm in fifth place. - Gosh.
I'm starting to feel upset.
(Ji Eun's 2nd and E Hyun's 4th choice)
- Haha sounds like my dad. - This is so annoying.
(Disappointed)
- Haha hasn't been called yet. - He hasn't been called yet.
Let's find out who's in sixth place.
- Haha must be... - I'm so relieved.
(6th place, Haha)
- I almost threw sand. - Haha is in sixth place.
(E Hyun's 3rd and Ji Eun's 4th choice)
However, you know...
- I almost threw sand. - If you'll keep going like this,
(Disappointed)
- You see, - invite male guests for us too.
- Why invite only female guests? - although we have female guests,
(Sad)
I didn't expect Ji Hyo and So Min...
(Today's guests are straightforward.)
- to be in the bottom two. - It's not fair.
This is how yin and yang works.
- They must be disappointed. - I'm disappointed.
- Yeo Jin, I'm disappointed. - They must be disappointed.
(We're pretty close.)
- So Min, you must be in last place. - 1 of them won by 1 vote.
- Although your friend is here. - I'm sure I'm in last place.
(She's predicting she's in the last place.)
I must be in last place.
(7th place)
Ji Hyo is in seventh place.
(Ji Hyo)
(Ju Bin's 3rd choice)
Ji Hyo is in seventh place.
My, your friend is so harsh.
(She's sad, even though she predicted it.)
You have a good friend, So Min.
(Laughing)
You have such a good friend.
Your friend is very honest.
(Sorry)
- You hate her that much? - I mean...
- Her friend... - "You hate her that much?"
(Framing them)
- You hate So Min that much? - Her friend...
- I'm sorry. - She absolutely...
(Their friendship starts to crack.)
I bet you hate her.
- She absolutely... - I think I should remove my makeup.
(Bitter)
I'm going to remove my makeup.
- I'm sorry. - I can't believe this.
(We're looking forward to the end of their friendship today.)
- She hates you. Right. - This is so disappointing.
(Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, Suk Jin, Se Chan, )
(Jae Suk, Haha, Ji Hyo, and So Min in the order)
I'll tell you how the guests will choose their team members.
(How to choose teammates)
- You see the water bottle, right? - Yes.
We'll put flags with numbers from 1 to 4 on them...
(They will put 4 flags in the sand in the order.)
around the water bottle in the order of rankings.
The guests will dance to the music at the starting line,
(The guests will dance lightly and go...)
and when Jae Suk blows the whistle, run and pick one of the flags.
(to pick the flag they want.)
- Pick one flag. - Oh, I see.
People in the top four, please put your flags in the sand.
(The top half of the ranking will go first.)
- Okay. Let's go. - Okay.
- We can pick who we want, right? - The top four.
Yes, you can pick who you want to be on your team.
(Kwang Soo, 1st, Jong Kook, 2nd, Suk Jin, 3rd, Se Chan, 4th)
You know, I am sure...
that Yeo Jin will run like crazy.
(A sportswoman)
- No, I won't. - Really?
(Preparing thoroughly while saying no)
Wait. Let me just put this down.
Are you all ready?
(The first competition to get the top four members)
- We'll play music for them. - Okay.
(They must pick the member they want!)
Yeo Jin must be a fast runner.
Run when the whistle is blown while dancing to the music.
(They'll warm up by dancing and go when the whistle blows.)
- They'll pass by so quickly, right? - E Hyun is also good at running.
(The top four are excited.)
(Her long arms and legs reacted to the exciting melody instantly.)
She's dancing on the beach. All right. Come on.
(Setting the mood)
- She must've prepared for this. - Yeo Jin.
(Her bold dance moves don't hold back.)
Yeo Jin, you're so cool.
(Taken aback)
- She hates it. - We want to see your dance.
(Laughing)
(It suits her taste.)
- Awesome. She's so cool. - Oh, my.
- Yeo Jin is still good at dancing. - That's awesome.
(Her stage presence is on another level.)
(While only Yeo Jin was doing her powerful warm-up, )
(the whistle was blown!)
(Running at full speed)
- Run! - Oh, my gosh.
(She started running while tying her hair.)
Run!
- Hey, hey. - Oh, no.
(She's running as fast as she can among the tall and lean girls.)
Run!
- Hey, hey. - Oh, no.
(Screaming)
(She fell down and went out of the frame.)
- Are you okay? - Hey, Ju Bin.
(What was that?)
Oh, dear.
- Are you okay? - Hey, Ju Bin.
(Laughing)
(Please leave me alone.)
- Ju Bin. - Are you...
(Meanwhile, E Hyun picked Jong Kook.)
(Yeo Jin picked Kwang Soo.)
- Are you okay? - Hey, Ju Bin.
(Ji Eun picked Suk Jin.)
(Ju Bin successfully picked her most preferred choice, Se Chan.)
- Wait. - Ju Bin.
- Did you see that? - Oh, yes.
(Please pretend you didn't see anything.)
I've never seen anyone who fell like she did.
- She used the falling technique. - I've never seen that before.
It's as if she died on the street.
Ju Bin, are you...
(It turns out she's a natural slapstick comedian.)
- Are you okay? - I've never seen anyone who fell...
She's not athletic at all.
- Why did that happen? - I don't know. She fell like this.
(She's not athletic at all.)
- Did you pick the one you wanted? - No.
Did you all pick the person you wanted?
- Ji Eun, what about you? - No.
(She picked Suk Jin.)
(As Ji Eun answered firmly, )
- Did you pick the one you wanted? - She's too honest.
(Suk Jin is disappointed.)
Did you pick the one you wanted?
- Fortunately, I did. - Did you?
- Okay. - You picked the one you wanted?
(She sounded happy to pick me.)
(Excited)
- Yes, I did. - Se Chan...
- Se Chan... - You picked the one you wanted?
(Yeo Jin picked Kwang Soo whom she wanted.)
- Yes, I did. - E Hyun, what about you?
(E Hyun picked Jong Kook whom she wanted.)
- I picked the one I wanted. - Okay.
All right. It's my turn.
(He can't hide his excitement as he was chosen by Ju Bin.)
I have never seen anyone...
(Glancing)
- She fell really hard. - I've been doing this for 10 years,
- I've never seen anyone like her. - Exactly.
I've never seen that kind of reaction before.
(Exclaiming in every way possible)
It must be a memorable moment for her.
I have made my decision. I'll join Ju Bin's team.
(What did you say?)
Ju Bin, please pick me.
- Why? - You're dead meat.
(There should be no romance without Love Frog.)
Go away!
- Pick me, Ju Bin. - She's going to come between them.
- Don't do that. - Oh, to come between them?
(Pick me, Ju Bin.)
All right. Are you ready?
(Now, it's time for the race for the last four.)
- Dance. - Oh, yes!
(As the dance time began again, )
- Dance. - Look at Yeo Jin.
(the predator of the dance world started dancing.)
Dance together.
(E Hyun feels uncomfortable.)
(Even Yeo Jin's friend feels uncomfortable to dance with her.)
- They should dance individually... - We can't do it that way.
because the others are intimidated by Yeo Jin.
(The other guests)
- I won't dance this time. - That's okay. You can dance.
(The newbie dancers weren't even able to move their shoulders.)
- Let's start with E Hyun. - Each of you will dance alone.
(We'll see them dance one by one starting with E Hyun.)
- Play some music. - Woo Jung as in friendship.
Here goes Woo Jung.
(Jo Friendship's dance hazing)
- Here we go! - That's great.
I haven't danced in a long time.
(She started dancing the old-fashioned dance move.)
- Really? - What's that move?
That's an old-fashioned dance move.
(Followed by the dance from the old times, )
Next up is Yeo Jin.
- She's an instructor. - Yes, she is.
(the predator of the dance world appears.)
She's a great dancer.
- She's like Poseidon. - She's amazing.
(Dancing hard)
(The dancing Poseidon takes over the Jeju seas.)
- Poseidon? - She's just like Poseidon.
- She's scary. - Next up is Ji Eun.
(It's Ji Eun's turn, So Min's blind date friend.)
That's an old-fashioned way of dancing.
(What?)
(This dance move can make your blind date a success.)
What's that?
(The whistle was blown right that moment.)
(She started running while dancing.)
Here we go.
Ju Bin is running fast.
(While everyone sprints, )
(Ju Bin is leading the race unexpectedly.)
(She redeemed herself and picked up a flag.)
(She picked up the flag of the eighth place?)
(So Min is on Ju Bin's team.)
Yes, she picked me as I asked.
- Finally. - I'm surprised that Ju Bin...
(Ju Bin complied with So Min's request.)
- She picked So Min. - picked So Min.
Why did you pick the worst member to team up with?
(Very disappointed)
She asked me to pick her.
(This Jeju episode is a dud again.)
Se Chan. Se Chan.
(Yeo Jin picked Jae Suk. E Hyun picked Haha.)
She asked me to pick her.
(Ji Eun picked Ji Hyo. Ju Bin picked So Min.)
Se Chan. Se Chan.
- Why did you pick So Min? - Yang Se Chan!
- Yang Se Chan! - I'm so tired.
(Jeon So Min, Romance Police, Can't let Se Chan be Happy)
- We're in trouble. - I can't swear at her.
It's over here.
(The Romance Police is already...)
I only trust you.
(interfering with others using her cuteness.)
- Okay, good. - I only trust you.
I only trust you.
- I'm Ju Bin's avatar today. - Okay. Let's see it.
(The love triangle team is formed.)
(Team Selection)
We're in trouble if Yeo Jin is...
- the team leader. - This is it?
(Team E Hyun, Team Ji Eun, Team Ju Bin, Team Yeo Jin)
- We're in trouble. - My team is just perfect.
Are you all satisfied with your team?
(After the team selection is done with one very unhappy person...)
- Yes. - Yes.
Today is episode one of...
(The Jeju Island Special: Wind, Women, Rocks, and Bombs)
the Jeju Island Special: Wind, Woman, Rock, and Bomb.
What is that again?
Everyone will choose one card each in secret.
(Everyone will choose one card each in secret.)
The team that collects one card each of the three things...
(The team that collects each card of the three things...)
that represent Jeju Island, wind, women, and rocks will win.
(that represent Jeju Island will win.)
- We must collect one card each. - Is that so?
The team that has the bomb card will receive a penalty.
(The team with a bomb will get the penalty.)
- We need to remove it. - After a moment,
you will choose one card each.
(Woman, Woman, Wind, Wind, Rock, Rock, Bomb)
There are two cards each of the wind, a woman, and a rock.
5 cards are blank, and 1 card is the bomb.
(There's only one bomb card.)
- One card? - Yes.
Ultimately, a team will win if they collect...
one card each of the wind, a woman, and a rock.
(The team that collects wind, woman, and rock card will win.)
If there aren't any teams who accomplish that,
the team that collects the most cards regardless what card will win.
We will give you the chance to exchange cards through missions.
(The winning team of a mission will get to trade cards.)
- We'll start drawing cards. - Okay.
- We can start with this team. - Let's go.
(It's time for each team to pick a card.)
We have a better chance.
Gosh, Se Chan!
- He's leading. - Okay, choose one each.
Se Chan is all the rage these days.
(Win if they pick one of wind, women, or rock.)
Try choosing one each.
(Penalty for picking the bomb card.)
Everyone, come this way.
Didn't Se Chan choose the same card?
(Se Chan, Wind)
Keep a straight face.
(So Min, Woman)
Okay, wait a minute.
Pretend that it's the bomb.
(Team Ju Bin already collected wind and woman cards.)
Okay? You should pretend that it's the bomb.
I know.
We don't have the bomb, right?
(Ju Bin, Wind)
- I'll start first. - Se Chan.
(The other teams also continue to choose cards.)
Are there five of these?
(Ji Hyo and Ji Eun, Unrevealed, Suk Jin, Rock)
- You're okay, right? - Yes.
(Jae Suk and Yeo Jin, Unrevealed, Kwang Soo, Woman)
(Jong Kook and E Hyun, Unrevealed, Haha, Rock)
We'll move to the first mission location now.
3 people will move at once, and the spots are divided into 2.
- Really? - The first keyword is "meat".
(First Mission Keywords: 1. Meat, 2. Seafood)
The second keyword is "seafood".
- We should go to "seafood". - It's Jeju Island.
(Team Yeo Jin picks "seafood".)
Jeju Island is famous for its seafood. Meat is also famous, but...
- We'll choose "meat". - It's obviously famous for meat.
(She doesn't hesitate to choose "meat".)
- It's meat. - It's meat.
(E Hyun and meat restaurant CEOs pick "meat".)
- It's meat. - It's meat unconditionally.
- It's Korean pork. - If so,
we'll move to the first mission location.
(Team E Hyun and Team Ji Eun pick "meat".)
(Team Yeo Jin and Team Ju Bin pick "seafood".)
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Nice! - Let's go.
(Wind, Women, Rocks, and Bombs race takes off!)
I'll put it in my bag for you.
Honestly, it's likely that our team won't lose.
(The car on its way to the "seafood" mission)
- Of course not. - Of course not.
- I'll tilt my seat back a little. - Yes, there's a lot of space.
Just tilt it a little!
- You said you would tilt a little! - Gosh, this is...
You told me to tilt it back!
(He gets angry even though it was his fault.)
I just split my legs straight now.
Why is the tallest person sitting in the back?
Why are you making me uncomfortable by sitting in the back?
(It's his fault for giving up his seat to older members.)
Everything will be over if we eat perch today.
- Isn't perch expensive? - They're expensive.
- Okay. - They're the most expensive fish.
- I don't think that's true. - I don't think that's true.
I just said one word.
Did the two of you take sides to bully Kwang Soo again?
Kwang Soo isn't a fool.
Gosh.
I'm telling you one more time. Kwang Soo isn't a fool.
- There's no need. It's obvious. - That's right.
Doesn't his face look like a type of fish?
Yes, he looks like a type of fish.
- You also look like fish. - Isn't that right?
You kind of look like a rockfish.
(Se Chan)
A rockfish?
- We look like fish. - We look like fish.
- Jae Suk looks like an anchovy. - Anchovy.
(Anchovy Yu)
That's perfect. He looks like an anchovy.
How could you say I look like an anchovy?
- Kwang Soo is... - Yeo Jin kind of looks like...
- a halibut. - A halibut is...
- That's not it. - Do you want to...
- I'm just asking you. - You're making a lot of mistakes.
(Glaring)
You kind of look like one.
- Say something that looks pretty. - Se Chan.
You could say mermaids.
(Teasing)
- That's right. - How could you call her a halibut?
Mermaids?
- Poseidon. - I said, "Poseidon".
- Poseidon is cool at least. - Yes, Poseidon.
- Poseidon is human. - There are so many cool things...
(Rockfish is cornered after making a mistake.)
- in the sea. - That's right.
Please don't try to grab me by the collar, Yeo Jin.
So Min kind of looks like a kissing gourami.
(So Min kind of looks like a kissing gourami.)
- A kissing gourami. - A kissing gourami without a mate.
(But she's a kissing gourami without a mate.)
She's lonely.
- No, I'm a doctor fish. - Yes.
- A doctor fish? - I will gnaw everything off.
(Doctor fish will gnaw everything but has no impact.)
- She will gnaw everything off. - A doctor fish suits you.
What suits Ju Bin? Ju Bin is...
What do I look like?
- Nemo. - Nemo?
- Why am I the only cute one? - Nemo?
- Is she Nemo? - Really?
- That's fortunate. - I thought she looked like a carp.
- A carp? - A carp?
Nemo suits her well.
- Yes. - If so...
Say things like that out loud.
- No, it's okay. - What did you say?
Se Chan just said this shyly.
(Se Chan shyly expresses his assessment.)
"Nemo? That suits her well."
- I told him to say that out loud. - Don't say that out loud.
(She suddenly turns around.)
Don't say that out loud.
Hey, Yeo Jin.
- Why are you so angry? - No...
(Poseidon has a lot of anger.)
- Why are you angry? - You're treating us differently.
(Se Chan)
- That's not it. - Yeo Jin, please scold him.
I'm already hot as it is after coming to Jeju Island.
(Poseidon is scolding them due to the warm weather.)
- Stop that. - Yeo Jin.
- So Min was just teasing me. - Today's team atmosphere is...
Your responses for us are like a hot and cold tub.
It's nice that Yeo Jin is fighting about everything for us.
I'm not afraid of Jong Kook today.
Okay, I will protect you.
We might beat Jong Kook with Yeo Jin.
I think she will beat him.
(After driving along the coast, they arrive at the mission site.)
They must be giving us seafood right next to the sea.
This must be it. "Jeju's seafood rice".
(What is the mission behind the keyword "seafood"?)
Is there something called "seafood rice"?
- It sounds good. - Let's go.
Let's go.
- Cold raw fish soup. - Gosh.
(Team Ju Bin and Team Yeo Jin enter the restaurant.)
- It's really windy. - Hello.
- We should sit by teams. - Hello.
(They sit by teams.)
General Yeo Jin, sit there.
- You should sit at the end. - Sit in the middle.
(Se Chan)
- Will Ju Bin sit there? - Yes.
(So Min pushes Se Chan to sit at the center.)
Sit there.
Am I the only man today?
(His cheeks are rising high since he's treated as the center.)
- Yes. - Okay.
I'll tell you the menu that will be the prize of the first mission.
(It's time to reveal the menu behind the first mission.)
- What is it? - First,
there will be all kinds of fresh raw fish.
(We will start with all kinds of fresh raw fish.)
- We must eat raw fish. - Assorted raw fish.
(You can smell the sea from the assorted raw fish dish.)
Sea urchin roe.
(And there is also savory sea urchin roe.)
- It's my favorite. - I really like sea urchin roe.
- I really like it. - Grilled abalones.
(Tender grilled abalones...)
Grilled tile fish.
(and grilled tilefish that will wind up in your mouth quickly)
- Sea urchin rice. - Sea urchin rice?
(They'll get to taste the fresh Jeju in just one meal.)
Cold raw fish soup, abalone sea urchin seaweed soup,
and top shell kalguksu.
Top shell kalguksu is good.
There is top shell kalguksu.
(Top shell kalguksu is made with various kinds of conches.)
Do they have all of those menus here?
- It's my favorite. - Top shell kalguksu?
(Top shell kalguksu)
I don't know about the others,
(He gets excited after hearing the menu.)
but I'm going to eat top shell kalguksu.
Are you going to give us everything?
- It's the winning team's advantage. - Will we eat everything?
(The winning team gets to taste them all.)
- The winning... - Only the winning team can eat?
- Yes. - Gosh.
(Only the basic food will be provided for the losing team.)
- This is too harsh. - We're going to be in trouble.
- Let's win. - I want to eat sea urchin roe.
(I must really win.)
The losing team will receive some, but there won't be as many as this.
- The first mission is... - Yes?
(Wind, Women, Rocks, and Bombs: The First Mission)
important to keep your cool.
It's Is Jenga the Reason Why My Hands are Shaking?
(Is Jenga the Reason Why My Hands are Shaking?)
Representatives of each team will play Jenga 1 on 1.
(Representatives of each team will play a 1-on-1 Jenga.)
You will attach a low-frequency therapeutic apparatus...
(They'll attach a low-frequency therapeutic apparatus...)
on your wrist and hand.
(on their wrist and hand.)
You will pile Jenga blocks in turn,
and the team that makes it fall down first will lose.
(The team that gets two wins first will win.)
The team that gets two wins first will win.
We won't be able to do it because our hands are shaking.
(Their hands will shake with the apparatus on.)
My hands are already shaking without the apparatus.
- That's right. - Yes.
- I don't like that. I'm afraid. - What am I going to do?
(Worried)
Okay. The winning team can check the cards of their opposing team.
(Another advantage of the winning team)
- What? - We can check the cards.
(The winning team can check the cards of their opposing team.)
Next, they can exchange up to two cards if they want.
(Next, they can exchange up to two cards if they want.)
- Okay. - We can also exchange cards.
- Up to two cards? - Yes.
- Yes, up to 2 cards. - 2 cards.
Who will be the first representative of each team?
(Jenga Round 1, Kwang Soo versus Ju Bin)
- Okay. - Let's stand up.
We can't sit down.
(Ju Bin and Kwang Soo wear the apparatus on their wrists.)
- Ju Bin, you must win. - Okay.
Ju Bin, do you usually like to drink alcohol?
(Nodding)
- Yes. - Do you like to?
We're in trouble. She's going to shake her hands a lot then.
What am I going to do?
(She's shaking a lot.)
Oh, my.
(Their hands start to shake as soon as they wear the apparatus.)
Look at this!
- What is going on? - Wait a minute.
This is too harsh.
(His pupils are expanded.)
But this makes you healthy.
- Isn't it right? - Doesn't it hurt?
(It's a low-frequency therapeutic apparatus for muscle pain.)
- It's therapy. - It doesn't hurt.
(But the hands may shake.)
I think this is kind of strange.
It feels refreshing in the end.
You should pile Jenga blocks like that.
(They must pile Jenga pieces using that hand.)
- I'm in trouble. - Who starts first?
(They'll do rock-paper-scissors to decide offense and defense.)
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
You can do it!
(Shaking)
- What is that? - Rock-paper-scissors.
You can do it!
(He won but his poor hand keeps shaking.)
What is that?
- No... - That's good.
- Ju Bin, you should start first. - Should I?
(Ju Bin will pull out a Jenga piece first.)
You can do it.
- Wait a minute. - We have to win.
(Nervous)
- It won't last long. - Wait a minute.
It's over the minute you make it all down.
(She needs to aim well despite her shaking.)
Are you going to take the middle one out, Ju Bin?
- No. - Take the one in the end out.
- You touched the one in the end. - What?
(Choosing the right piece is already difficult.)
- Can't you pick another block? - It's over if you touch a block.
Take it out.
(They're nervous too.)
I think it will be safe.
But...
- But this is... - No...
(She picks a piece in the bottom.)
- There's a time limit. - It's over.
- There's a time limit. - Nice.
Pile it up strangely.
(She succeeds at taking a piece out safely.)
Hey...
- Hey... - Be careful.
(She places it horizontally.)
- Is it possible to do this? - Of course, it's possible.
- It's possible. - Is it possible?
(Protective of Ju Bin)
- It's possible in Jenga. - Is it possible?
- Is it possible? - Yes.
(The game gets difficult after Ju Bin's Jenga piece.)
Okay.
Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo's turn)
Kwang Soo, your hand won't shake if you concentrate.
(Nagging)
Kwang Soo, concentrate.
(The next-door neighbor is nagging in a loud voice.)
You can do it!
Just take it out, Kwang Soo!
(Shaking)
- Kwang Soo, just take it out. - Oh, my.
- Just take it out. - Pile it on top.
My hands keep shaking.
You know what will happen if you drop it, right?
You're really frustrating.
(He succeeded at taking a block out after many twists and turns.)
- Kwang Soo. - Oh, my.
Will you pile it like that?
- Will you pile it like that? - No.
(Kwang Soo wants to make a bold move without thinking.)
- Kwang Soo... - Are you going to quit?
Kwang Soo, look into my eyes clearly.
(Emergency eye contact time)
- She grabbed him by his collar. - I will pile it properly this time.
Kwang Soo, why can't you do that?
(He just needs to pile it.)
I will pile it properly.
Wait a minute, what is your left hand doing?
- Gosh. - Okay.
I will pile it quickly.
Wait a minute, what is your left hand doing?
(The apparatus is on his right hand. He's playing with his left hand.)
Kwang Soo!
Wait a minute, what is your left hand doing?
(He got caught by doing tricks with his hands.)
- Okay. - Using your left hand is cheating.
(Kwang Soo's acting even surprises his team.)
- I'm sorry. - His left hand is even shaking!
(Shocked)
- Hey... - He's tricking our eyes.
Don't try to fool our eyes.
(The Jenga shark is even acting out low-frequency now.)
- You're cheating! - Sorry.
He's even shaking his left hand!
(I can't believe him!)
I fell for it.
You shouldn't trick our eyes.
(He does it this time without tricking their eyes.)
Go.
(He succeeds at piling it without tricking their eyes.)
- Good. - Right now...
- Okay. - Take number 38 out.
(It's Ju Bin's turn again.)
- You should take that out. - We don't have any time left.
(Despite Jae Suk's nagging, )
- Ju Bin. - Ju Bin, your hands are shaking.
- That's it! - Yes!
(Ju Bin successfully pulls out a piece.)
Ju Bin, piling it on top is important.
- We don't have any time left. - Just pile it.
(Picking a fight)
You can do it.
(He tries to interfere by talking about the time limit.)
Let's just end it the next round.
Let's just end it here.
(Let's end it here.)
- There's no need to shake. Just go. - Okay.
- That's it. Good job. - Ju Bin, you can't do that.
Do it gently.
- You can do it. - You can't do that.
(Out of words)
If number 38 falls down, it will be over.
(They continue to play dirty even when the guest is playing.)
- It really will be over. - That's right.
- Ju Bin, that will be the end. - Concentrate.
- You can do it. - Ju Bin.
The problem won't be solved just because you concentrate.
(Teasing)
- He just won't stop. - Concentrate.
It's not all about concentration.
(He comes up with many dirty tricks.)
- Don't pay attention to him. - That's...
- He's so annoying. - Oh, my.
- Good job. - Stay still.
(Ju Bin succeeds despite their tricks.)
- That's it. - Okay.
- It's over now. - It's over.
- Please end it. - Kwang Soo.
(The burden is now on the Jenga-shark.)
- I want to stop. - Kwang Soo.
- It's over now. - Kwang Soo.
But this is dangerous because this block is...
(He carefully chooses a piece.)
- supporting everything up. - You should start from the bottom.
That's right.
Kwang Soo also knows that. He's not a fool.
Wait a minute, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, I told you to do it with your right hand.
- Is he doing that again? - Don't do that!
(His bad hand tricks relapsed soon.)
Kwang Soo also knows that.
- He's not a fool. - Wait a minute, Kwang Soo.
(So Min didn't even notice it.)
Kwang Soo, I told you to do it with your right hand.
Is he doing that again?
- I almost fell for that. - You should stop it.
(Cheating never ends because someone always falls for it.)
- Jae Suk. - Kwang Soo, your acting is so good.
- Thank you. - We keep falling for that.
- I had no idea. - He shook his hand.
I didn't know.
(The award winner presents...)
He shook his left hand so well.
(a low-quality fake hand acting.)
- It just seemed right. - He acts really well.
Kwang Soo, you can do this if you stay focused.
- You can do it. - Okay.
(He successfully removes it after concentration.)
Good. You should stop pulling pranks now.
Kwang Soo has got the hang of it.
(He needs to put it on top of the Jenga.)
It's not easy.
Kwang Soo, if you put it on there, you'll win.
(Approaching)
(She stays close to him to distract him.)
So Min.
So Min. Stay still unless you want Yeo Jin to slap you in the face.
Yeo Jin can slap you.
Look at her. She raised her hand.
(Yeo Jin plays along.)
Hey!
Don't hold it. If you touch the block at the bottom,
(Will Kwang Soo be able to put the block on it?)
- you will lose. - It's done.
- you will lose. - It's done. Kwang Soo did it.
- Kwang Soo did it. - Oh no.
Oh no.
(Kwang Soo failed.)
- Oh no. - Fail.
Okay.
(Team Ju Bin wins the 1st round easily with Ju Bin's performance.)
- It's 1 to 0. - Yes.
- Ju Bin, good job. - Thank you.
- We have to win this time. - Let's move on.
If you win the next round, you will be the winner.
(If Team Yeo Jin loses the next round, they lose.)
- That's great. - All right, Yeo Jin.
- Yes. - You have to win.
(Yeo Jin versus Se Chan)
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Poseidon.
Get into the sea after winning this game, okay?
- You can't lose. - Good luck.
- She's so charismatic. - Okay. I'll go first.
(Yeo Jin will go first.)
- Hang on, Yeo Jin. - Why?
(Time out)
Why?
What?
(Slapping)
- He turned it off, right? - It's turned off.
(Se Chan's device)
- It's turned off. - Hey.
(He turned off the device secretly.)
It's not turned on.
(He caught me.)
- You punk. Come here. - You know what?
(There are petty criminals everywhere.)
- I can't believe this. - They were shaking differently.
Don't make it too strong.
As a penalty, make it one level higher.
(Cheater Se Chan turns the low-frequency back on.)
- Increase it. - Gosh, it's too strong. Lower it.
A little more.
This is off.
Jae Suk, it's too strong. It's just too strong.
- It's too much. - Okay.
(The twinge hits his body.)
- It's too powerful. - I'm sorry. Okay.
- Okay. - Will you be nice then?
I'll be nice. I swear.
- You should be nice. - I'll be loyal.
(He swears to stay loyal.)
- Be nice. Behave yourself. - I will. Okay.
(You punk.)
- It's done. - I guess it's strong.
Will you date So Min or not?
(Enjoying)
- Will you date her or not? - I'll just do as you say.
- I'll do as I'm told. - Will you date So Min?
I'll do whatever you say.
(Tingling)
- Say sorry to So Min. - I'm sorry.
It's all my fault. I'm so sorry.
(The low frequency is very effective on a guilty date.)
Behave yourself, okay?
- I want to keep this. - It's level four.
I want this.
(They want to have an instrument of power like this.)
It was strong.
Yeo Jin isn't shaking her hand a lot. She seems fine.
(Yeo Jin starts Round 2 stably.)
I know how to do this.
This is fun.
- Good. - What do I do?
You can't pick it up like that.
(A delinquent hand)
- Yeo Jin. - You should pick it up like this.
(Come on. Seriously.)
Don't do that.
- Yeo Jin. - You can just pick it like this.
(Her two fingers greet the Jenga.)
- But this is too... - Do whatever you want.
You can do whatever you want.
(She cups her hand and tries it again.)
(Petty)
(Her fingers look petty when they're put together.)
This is quite unique.
It looks like a duck.
(She overcomes the shake in her four fingers.)
This is really strong.
- She overcame it. - I did it.
(She successfully puts the first block up.)
- She did it. - Se Chan, show us what you can do.
- I will. - Okay.
- Let's eat. - Se Chan.
This will end soon.
Once he fails, it's over.
(The round is expected to end soon as his hand shakes a lot.)
- Once he fails, it's over. - Okay.
What? It will be over.
- So Min. - Be careful.
(Please.)
Do it right.
- It might collapse. - Gosh, this is...
(Touching the low-frequency device)
Se Chan, you're really bad at this.
Touch it lightly.
(Groaning)
- That's for Yeo Jin. - I'm sorry, Yeo Jin.
- I'm really sorry. - Hey!
(He attacked his own team.)
(Flustered)
- That's for Yeo Jin. - I'm sorry.
(He pulled a petty trick on the wrong person.)
- I'm really sorry. - I can't believe this.
Hey, you did it to Yeo Jin.
- Hey! - I really didn't know.
(Poseidon's angry.)
(She felt a twinge at an unexpected moment.)
- It hurt so much. - I really didn't know.
Just hurry.
I will overpower the high-frequency waves.
- I should overpower it. - It's low frequency.
Is it low frequency?
- High frequency? - Why did you point that out?
(Disappointed)
- I didn't know. - Hey, Se Chan.
(Se Chan reveals that he has no common knowledge.)
If it were high frequency, you would've died.
Ju Bin is surprised.
Se Chan.
It's over.
(He tries to overcome low frequency.)
It's almost over.
Oh no.
(Se Chan failed.)
Fail.
(As Se Chan fails, it's a tie.)
It's done. It's over.
- I can't do this. - I can beat So Min.
- Okay. - We can still win.
(The result relies on the last round.)
Watch me. I'll win with my mental and physical strength.
Show us.
(He shows off before starting.)
This is stronger than you think.
Don't worry, Yeo Jin.
(Jae Suk versus So Min)
This is the final round.
So Min, let's eat.
- This is hard. - Good luck.
(They must win this round to try the Jeju Island seafood.)
It's okay. You can do this.
Jae Suk, you can eat top shell kalguksu.
Right. There's also sea urchin roe and grilled abalone.
(You can trust me.)
- You can do this. - That's my favorite.
(Last game over seafood delicacy)
Above all things,
- I'll eat top shell kalguksu. - Jae Suk, let's just do this.
(Jae Suk of mental strength versus So Min of tenacity)
- Watch me. - Are you holding out?
- Sure. - It's not turned off yet.
(He was bluffing while the device was off.)
This hurts a lot. It really hurts.
(It tingles a bit.)
- Is this right? - It hurts when it's strong.
It will hurt if I do this.
(Screaming)
But this is fine. This is okay.
(Se Chan enjoys the power of low frequency.)
- This is okay. - This is fine, right?
- It hurts when it's stronger. - It will be about this.
Stretch out your hand. Okay.
It will be like this.
(Slapping)
- Gosh. - I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
It just happened before I knew it.
(He blames the low frequency and enjoys slapping.)
- I accept that. - You know what it is.
It doesn't feel like your hand because of the low frequency.
(He admits it.)
- It hurts. - Just do it, So Min.
(So Min starts the last round.)
Why does it hurt so much? It's really painful.
That's right. So Min, well done.
- Slow down. - It hurts so much.
(She removes it smoothly...)
- Good. - She's really good.
(and leaves it on top.)
Nice. This is good enough for the final round.
(They speed up as it's the last round.)
It hurts so much. He's holding out.
(It's the low frequency boaster's turn.)
- Put it on. - It's hard to put it on.
This is all about mental strength. It's no big deal to me.
(Showing off)
It's hard now. Look. He can't put it on there.
He overcame the low frequency, but he's shaking out of fear.
- That's the only explanation. - He's shaking his hand.
(He has stage fright even in Jeju Island.)
- Because of the cameras. - See?
- I'm sure we're going to eat. - We have to eat.
(It's So Min's turn again.)
That's right. Good.
Good. So Min, well done.
(She puts it vertically again.)
Once you get through this...
- You'll overcome it. - Watch me.
I'll overcome it.
- I'll do it right away. - He can't overcome it.
It's shaking.
We don't know it yet.
Okay. It's done.
So Min, what's hard is to put the block on it.
It feels horrible.
(He should put the block on the Jenga tower.)
I think it's hard.
(Please.)
Jae Suk doesn't shake his hand a lot. He overcame it.
He's shaking. Bounce.
(If Jae Suk fails, Team Ju Bin wins right away.)
- He's focused. - Gosh.
(Exclaiming)
(It's breathtaking.)
Gosh, he has good concentration.
It's almost time.
Let's move on to Part Two.
- Already? - Is it too early?
No? Isn't it time yet?
(Is it too early?)
- What? - It's too early.
(Running Man Part 2 will start a while later.)
Drop it.
(After taking a break, )
(he manages to put the block on the tower.)
It's done.
(Her turn keeps coming back.)
- So Min. This is it. - It's over.
It's taking a long time because it's the final round.
(So Min)
- You can do this. - Just do it.
(Sea urchin roe is waiting.)
- I want sea urchin roe. - Make it short.
- She better fail. - Keep the balance.
It's falling down.
- Keep the balance. - It's falling down.
(She puts it vertically again.)
Stay still. We did it.
(They are getting extremely excited with the unstable Jenja tower.)
Look at you. You must be nervous.
(Smiling)
(Extremely nervous)
Kwang Soo is shaking his hands. Good.
(The unstable slant of the tower makes him sigh.)
Hey. It shouldn't be so easy anyway.
(He goes for it.)
Let's do this.
I'm so distressed. It's really painful.
Hang on. Wait, Jae Suk.
Hang on a second.
- What is this? - What?
What?
(A toothbrush case?)
Why did you put it in here?
- My hand was shaking. - This is...
(A while ago)
Hey. It shouldn't be...
so easy anyway.
Let's do this.
(He took the wire off the device...)
(and connected it to his toothbrush case.)
(Then he shook his hand himself.)
Hang on. Wait, Jae Suk.
I can do it this way.
(The low-frequency swindlers got caught in the end.)
This isn't the device.
(Come on.)
This is a toothbrush case.
Why did you do that?
(Blaming)
Jae Suk, when I unplugged it, you started shaking your hand.
That's teamwork. It's good teamwork.
He says it's teamwork.
(They practiced teamwork to cheat for 10 years.)
They are unbelievable.
Jae Suk is so good at this.
(Jae Suk concentrates and tries to pick a Jenga again.)
Good.
It will be over once he puts it on the tower.
This is the hard part.
Wait. Are you sure the device is working?
(Doubting)
- It is. - He's overcoming it.
Okay. It's working.
(Straining)
He overcame it.
(Groaning)
- What was that? - He shows off his strength.
He's showing it off against the low frequency.
(He fights against the low frequency.)
It will be over once he places it. You should pray, Se Chan.
(Nervous)
It's over.
You can't use your body like that.
(So Min made the Jenga tower unstable.)
Leave him be. You know how it will turn out.
- He might push it. - It will collapse anyway.
- It will crumble away. - Hang on.
I should do it as slow as I can.
- Gosh. - Yes!
(Jae Suk failed.)
(They cheat in all kinds of ways but lose poorly.)
Fail.
We will enjoy the food.
(So Min wins the final round.)
(Team Ju Bin gets to eat the Jeju Island seafood.)
We will enjoy the food.
- Team Ju Bin wins. - Okay.
(Team Ju Bin wins.)
- Bring in the food. - You're the best.
Well done. So Min, you were amazing.
(While their emotions are extremely opposite, )
She's been playing board games a lot.
What?
- This is beautiful. - My goodness.
(Team Ji Eun is on their way to the Meat mission.)
I have a question. Should I carry this around?
(This is her first variety show.)
- Yes. - But don't show it to others.
- Okay. - Be careful around Kwang Soo.
(Blacklist)
- Kwang Soo? Why? - And be careful around So Min.
So Min is dangerous.
Tell us about So Min. I bet she's talking about you now.
(Slandering)
I'm sure she talked behind your back, Ji Eun.
(They come between Ji Eun and So Min to make her talk about school life.)
- Really? - Did you have...
(The variety show rookie takes the bait.)
- any problems with her back then? - Me?
You two were friends, but you weren't so excited to see her.
(They exaggerate in the calmest voice ever.)
I know.
I think there's a secret between you two.
(They pretend to know everything for sure.)
I'm sure there's something. She holds a grudge.
(Thinking)
Earlier today, she said I was dirty, right?
- No. She didn't say that. - What did she say?
No. She didn't say that.
(Her memory is distorted.)
What did she say?
(Flustered)
(Correcting her memory)
- It wasn't clean. - Our relationship wasn't clean?
She said it wasn't clean, but it's become dirty.
(Distorted)
"Ji Eun is dirty." This is what she remembers.
(The victim of slandering)
It's not easy to say such a thing about your friend.
(She joins the slandering.)
- It's not easy. - Gosh, this is hard.
(Ji Eun puts her guard down as they work together to fool her.)
I'm serious.
Actually, when there was a group date,
our seniors decided who should go on the date.
(As a result, she tells the old blind date story.)
They were like, "You, you, and you will go on the date."
(They induce her with big reactions.)
- Really? - And So Min and I got picked a lot.
(So Min and Ji Eun went on blind dates a lot.)
- Your seniors decided it. - They picked the best ones.
(Adding an exaggerated reaction)
If I did something on the date, I'm sorry about that.
(If I did something on the date, I'm sorry about that.)
I didn't mean to be like that.
What can I do...
- when that's what they said? - Right.
(She does a 180.)
What can I do...
- when that's what they said? - Right.
(It's her fault for being too popular.)
Right? It's not like...
(She finally starts talking as everyone corners her.)
I told them to choose me.
- No, right? - But So Min could think that...
(He plays her against So Min once again.)
you flirted in a way.
To be honest, this is how I remember it.
(She's hilarious.)
My relationship with So Min boils down...
(Smooth)
to her having a victim mentality.
To her having a victim mentality.
(Victim mentality?)
(The bait caught the biggest fish yet.)
Gosh, that's harsh.
That's what I believe.
(Naive)
Also, there's something...
quite complicated between So Min and me...
regarding a good friend of mine.
(She took the bait.)
Is that friend a man or a woman?
- A man, no, a woman. - It's a woman.
(Through numerous blind dates, )
- So a woman... - A man got in between them.
(So Min and Ji Eun share a lot of memories.)
That's right.
And I was kind of stuck in between.
- You couldn't take one's side. - Right.
(Taking her side)
When splitting into groups...
- Was that too mean? - Who?
(Regretting it instantly)
- Was I too mean? - Of course not.
(Don't worry.)
- So Min thinks she's a victim. - It could happen.
(No, that's not what I meant.)
Yes, exactly.
(The members have dirt on her now.)
Guys, seriously?
Gosh, this is hilarious.
- This isn't how it should be. - An old friend of mine...
(Worrying)
- Is this the place? Looks tasty. - I bet it's delicious.
(The members arrive at the destination in the meantime.)
(They enter with full hearts.)
This is what you'd expect at Jeju Island.
(The commission agency of Jeju 200 years ago as it was)
Check out the names of the buildings.
(Where local food of Jeju is served!)
(A place where you can experience the old Jeju)
We're here at the Commission Agency Site of Kim Man Deok.
- The first mission... - Yes?
(The first mission will be held here.)
Teamwork will be key...
in this game of I Can't Hear Your Voice.
I Can't Hear Your Voice?
(What kind of mission is that?)
You'll be given 100 seconds each.
(2 members of each team will wear the headsets. And in 100 seconds, )
Two chosen members will put on headphones.
One will describe the word while one answers.
(they have to guess the word the other one is describing.)
A total of four rounds will be played.
(The team with the most right answers win after 4 rounds.)
The team with the most correct answers will win.
Please note that you can't directly name the word.
(They cannot say the word directly, and they can't skip a word.)
- The winning team... - Yes?
(The winning team's benefits)
will be able to see a card of their choice...
(A chance to see a card of their choice...)
and receive a chance to swap their cards twice.
(and a chance to swap their cards twice)
- Twice? - Twice.
Three servings of a meal will be served...
(They will also be given 3 servings of a meal.)
while the losing team...
(The losing team only gets 1 serving.)
- only gets one. - A single serving?
- That's mean of you. - No way.
(Understood)
The name of our team...
- is 1, 2, 3. - Why?
- He has 1 child, she has 2, - I have 2.
(1 daughter in LA, 2 daughters, and 3 children)
- while I have 3. - 3.
- 1, 2, 3. - 3.
(He just accepts it.)
We'll call ourselves Victim Mentality.
(Ji Eun can't get out of it now.)
That's our team name.
No way.
(So Min, that's not what I meant.)
- Victim Mentality. - Mentality!
How hilarious.
(She realizes how scary variety shows are.)
Let's do this!
I'll try and guess the word.
(Round 1, Team E Hyun, Jong Kook and E Hyun)
Ji Hyo, you should stand over here.
- Okay. - That's a good one.
(She'll tell him the length of the word by using her fingers.)
You can't point out the number of syllables.
(They can't use their fingers.)
How about this then?
Can you please start the music?
(Nod your head instead.)
(Okay.)
(The music is on.)
I bet it's loud.
- It's really loud. - Here we go.
(I can't hear a thing.)
Ready, get set, go.
(Macaron)
The most expensive item...
at coffee shops.
- Expensive? - You're insane?
(Error)
- A dessert... - A sort of cake.
The most expensive dessert!
(Giving her advice)
The most expensive cake.
(As he doesn't understand the word, "expensive", )
- A snack. - What?
(she switches to using "snack".)
A...
A snack.
- A snack! - An expensive one.
(He got it!)
- An expensive one? - Yes.
(An expensive snack...)
Squid-peanut Balls!
No, it's round.
(Squid-peanut Balls are most expensive to Jong Kook.)
- What... - How is that expensive?
(Shocked)
It's a round-shaped snack.
Homerun Balls?
(Another expensive snack for him)
An expensive snack.
- Homerun Balls? - A snack?
- He must really not eat snacks. - An expensive one?
Is it round? Onion Rings?
- Pass. - I'll pass.
(She skips it since Jong Kook doesn't know well about snacks.)
Pass.
- I like how frugal he is. - Snacks that women like?
(He's quite frugal.)
- Pass! - This is a tricky one.
(GPS)
When driving...
When joining the military?
The military?
- This is fun. - A car!
A car.
The Let's Play app?
(The GPS system led him to a lodging establishment.)
- The Let's Play app? - Are we advertising it?
(All of a sudden...)
- That's what she said. - What?
The Let's Play app.
(I'm certain that's what I heard.)
(It's natural to misunderstand.)
When you're driving a car...
You're driving.
- A towel? - Yes, that.
- When driving... - Right, a towel.
(He only gets the vowels right.)
It shows you the way.
(Frustrated)
On our cellphones.
(She tries to describe a cellphone now.)
- Cellphones. - Cellphones!
The T Map app.
- The T Map app? - The T Map app!
(Welcome to the world of indirect advertisements.)
The T Map app.
- What was that? - A map. A map!
(Describing GPS has gone way off the rails.)
- A see-saw? - Yes, a map.
A map you need when driving.
(See-saw? When driving?)
Driving, see-saw...
- A map you need when driving. - Yes, while driving.
- Tell him the number of syllables. - That's not allowed.
(Pass)
You'll pass.
(The next word is...)
- This... - Hey!
You'll probably get this one.
(Naengmyeon)
Pyongyang or Hamhung?
Bibim.
- Park Myung Soo. - After eating!
Park Myung Soo.
(She's trying to describe the song "Naengmyeon" by Park Myung Soo.)
Park Myung Soo!
After eating.
(Understanding Park Myung Soo as "after eating")
Jessica.
(Pondering)
What you eat in the summer.
- What you eat. - Yes.
- Noodles. - Patbingsu?
(Summer food)
Noodles.
(Summer food went through to him.)
- What? - In the summer.
- The summer. - That's right.
- What you eat. - What you eat!
(They're almost there.)
- Naengmyeon. - Naengmyeon!
(She said it loud and clear.)
(She was so frustrated that she said it out loud.)
You can't just say it!
Your time is up.
- This... - Hold on.
Is it over?
- I mean... - I was completely clueless.
- Just the words... - Not without any gestures.
(Team E Hyun has gotten none of the words.)
- Especially without any gestures. - I see.
It's impossible to know.
(He says they're too hard to guess, but...)
- Naengmyeon. - Hold on though.
Jong Kook, have you never had any snacks before?
How can an expensive snack...
(He would never know a snack as he only takes protein.)
- be Squid-peanut Balls? - But...
Squid-peanut Balls and Homerun Balls.
I couldn't make any of it out.
(Team E Hyun gets 0 answers in Round 1.)
I'll describe the word.
Ready, get set,
(Round 2, Team Ji Eun, Ji Eun and Suk Jin)
go!
Go!
(Ceiling price)
Shares. Stocks!
Army doctor.
Stocks.
(Frustrated)
- That's right. - Shares.
- Soldier. - Nice!
(So that's what it looks like.)
The stock price...
is going up.
- Going up! - Don't.
(Moving)
- You can't do that. - The frustration gets to you.
(No moving)
- A soldier goes up. - Yes, the stock price goes up.
(What?)
Say that in another way.
(A soldier goes up?)
A soldier goes up.
- An airplane. - An airplane...
- An airplane? - She's very one-dimensional.
(He grasps it.)
The opposite of floor price.
- A soldier. - Shares!
- From what I can tell... - The price goes up!
- Say it again. - She doesn't know much.
(Ji Eun is...)
The stock price goes up.
(She doesn't know much.)
What do you call that?
I doubt she knows what this is.
(Convinced)
- Hey! - Just move on to the next one.
- Pass. - This is probably new to her.
Pass.
- Pass. - This is an easy one.
Hang glider...
It's over. We're moving on.
(I skipped it.)
- The next one. - We're moving on.
- Look at her expression. - What?
- What? - We're moving on.
(Why can't you move on?)
- We're... Yes, we'll pass. - Pass!
(She asks to pass it when it's already been done.)
- It's already been done. - Pass...
It's been done.
Gosh, this is frustrating.
(Frustrated)
At the sea...
(Listen well, Ji Eun.)
- Pass. - In the sea...
Can't we pass?
We already did!
- In the sea... - Can't we pass?
(It's impossible to communicate with her.)
We already did!
(She's the only one that hasn't moved on.)
We already moved on.
(She finally understood.)
- Got it. - We're on to the next one!
Okay.
They go into the sea...
(Haenyeo)
Abalones...
(Since it's haenyeo...)
What? Jjamppong?
Abalones.
- Abalones. - Abalones.
(She understood abalones.)
- Abalones! - Oh, I know.
Haenyeo!
(I got it!)
(She answers haenyeo correctly.)
That's right.
(Tattoo)
(Tattoo?)
The people of Hongdae area.
(The people of Hongdae area are attacked.)
(Spouting out)
- Rooftop? - The people of Hongdae area.
(The people of Hongdae area meant tattoos for him.)
- What? - The people of Hongdae area.
Why not just say the Korean word "munshin"?
(Short and clear)
Alone?
A dragon on one's back.
(The tattoos back in the old days)
- A dragon? - Yes, dragon.
(A dragon on the back is the only tattoo Suk Jin knows.)
A dragon that's drawn on the body.
- A dragon? - A dragon that's drawn on the body.
(Buffering)
- A dragon. - Swearing?
- Yes, a dragon. - She thinks it's swearing.
- Your time's up. - Swearing?
- Gosh. - What a relief.
- I'm so glad. - Just you wait.
(Team Ji Eun gets 1 answer.)
We'll end it for sure in this round.
(Haha and Jong Kook are up next.)
Why else would I have chosen these two?
(She relies on the best combination.)
- Okay, good. - They're the best.
- All right. - Hold on.
(Current score, Team Ji Eun: 1, Team E Hyun: 0)
Are you ready?
- And go. - They'll dominate for sure.
(Pork cutlet)
- Our restaurant! - Yes?
You and I.
- Yes, you and I. - What do we sell?
(A smooth start)
What do we sell?
(Investor Kim listens well when it's about business.)
- Pork cutlet. - Yes!
(They easily get one right.)
(I can't believe they got it so easily.)
I didn't expect them to get it right.
Pororo.
(Penguin)
I didn't expect them to get it right.
Pororo. The animal.
(Pororo?)
What am I?
Two syllables.
Haha? Haroro.
(Two syllables)
- Haroro. - Haroro.
(He tells the word length by nodding as planned.)
The animal? Penguin!
(Penguin is correct.)
(They take the lead with 2 correct answers.)
This one seems tricky.
(Ilchwiweoljang)
(He's weak when it comes to four-syllable idioms.)
- I... - You?
(4 syllables)
I've improved.
A four-syllable idiom.
I've suddenly...
(Ilchwiweoljang to Haha: I've improved.)
He has suddenly improved.
(He can't hear it, but it's funny.)
I've, you know...
I'm the bomb now.
(He's trying to explain what ilchwiweoljang means.)
I'm the bomb now. I didn't expect this either,
- but I'm the bomb now. - A superpower?
Four syllables.
(How could anyone guess this?)
- A four-syllable word? - Your time's up.
He almost understood "ilchwiweoljang" though.
(Sad)
Why don't you two give it a shot?
Was "ilchwiweoljang" a word I needed to guess?
(Hearing it for the first time)
(Team E Hyun gets 2 right in Round 3.)
Ilchwiweoljang? Seriously?
You have to do well in order to eat lunch.
(Team Ji Eun: 1, Team E Hyun: 2)
It won't be easy though.
(Round 4, Team Ji Eun, Ji Hyo and Ji Eun)
Ready,
get set, go.
(Nucksal)
- Goodness. - Oh, dear.
A rapper!
- He's a rapper. - A rapper.
He has thick skin.
(Nucksal means to have thick skin?)
- A rapper? - He has thick skin.
(Reinterpretation of Nucksal)
- What on earth? - Thick legs?
- His skin. - His foot.
(Huge eyes)
- Horse? - What's with her expression?
(He's fascinated)
- Look at her expression. - Horse?
Moon.
(Pondering)
- Horse? - What's with her expression?
- Look at her expression. - Horse?
(Two syllables)
- Horse? - Look at her expression.
(She takes a note out of Haha's book.)
What on earth is she doing?
A rapper who talks well?
- Two syllables! - She's copying Haha's strategy.
(Copying Haha's strategy results in...)
- Two syllables? - Yes.
(being able to tell Ji Hyo that it's a two-syllable word.)
This is what I like.
(This is what she likes?)
- This is what she likes. - She must like Nucksal.
(They finally understand what she's saying.)
- The rapper! - Rapper.
It's a name.
- Name. - "It's a name."
(What's with the way she talks?)
- A name. A rapper's name. - Name?
- "It's a name." - A rapper's name.
(Ji Eun's explanations became more desperate.)
A rapper is what?
- No, it's a rapper and... - A rapper and...
She's so desperate.
(Unsettled)
- This is crazy. - She's so funny.
- She's... - Sit down when you talk.
- This is good. - Good?
(It's good.)
(Frustrated)
Just pass.
(We don't have time.)
- Move on. - The next one.
(Pass!)
- My goodness. - My goodness.
(Repayment of kindness even after one's death.)
- My goodness. - Gosh, no.
(It's a four-syllable idiom.)
- Moving on to the next. - She doesn't know what it means.
(She quickly moves on to the next question.)
(She quickly gives up questions that are too difficult.)
You know this one, right?
Don't know this one either?
(Omegi rice cake)
You know this one, right?
- Jeju Island. - Jeju Island.
(Confident)
Famous rice cake!
Just talk slowly.
- She doesn't know what it is. - Jeju Island's...
(Ji Hyo doesn't know.)
- She doesn't know. - Jeju Island? Say it again.
1, 2...
(How many syllables? Four syllables.)
(He's about to give up.)
- Rice cake! - We won't be able to have dinner.
Say goodbye to the food.
Jeju Island's rice cake.
Jeju Island's rice cake? Omegi rice cake!
(Correct answer)
Omegi rice cake!
(Now it's a tie!)
- Come on. You're doing great. - I'm sure she knows this one.
(Just one more question and they'll win!)
Just get one more correct answer.
- Come on. You're doing great. - I'm sure she knows this one.
(Olle Trail)
Just get one more correct answer.
- 1, 2, 3. - Olle Trail. Her face is red.
It's on Jeju Island.
- It's on Jeju Island. - This one is easy.
It's a trail!
It's a rail on Jeju Island?
(Input error)
KT!
- Gosh, KT? - KT.
- Why? Did you hear it? - KT.
- She won't get it. - KT!
- She won't understand. - Don't do that. Don't do that.
(A continuous 5G-like shock)
(The first two syllables)
- A famous trail in Jeju. - On Jeju Island.
It's famous in Jeju. It's KT!
- KT is famous in Jeju? - In Jeju Island!
(Why is that famous?)
Three syllables!
A taxi is what?
- Jeju Island! - Taxi fare?
(They try their best by screaming at each other.)
You should move on to the next.
(But the communication fails.)
- Pass. - All right.
(Acting cute)
(Using her whole body to express what it is.)
What do you call this?
- This is weird. - It's weird that she got that.
(It can't be more perfect.)
- You don't know this? - What is this called?
Acting cute.
(The whole explanation is one-dimensional.)
What do you call this?
- It's about how you act. - Action?
(The action right now)
- Action. - Action?
(She continues to act charming as much as she can.)
Acting cute.
(That is correct. Act charming)
(Finally got the correct answer)
- Acting cute. - Gosh, she got it.
(Turned the table but 3 to 2)
Okay, time's up.
(The game automatically ends as the winner is clear.)
- You are... - One day?
- Right now. - Right now.
(But they're not done.)
You're wearing it.
(They can't hear each other.)
- You should stop. - You're wearing it.
- She's good. - It took longer than I expected.
(You're done.)
- Good, good, good. - Excuse me?
He said we won. We won.
(Now she finds out they won.)
- Hey. - My goodness.
- She turned it around at the end. - Ji Eun.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo and Ji Eun, the team turned the table.)
When this episode is released,
- other variety shows will want you. - Great.
- Too bad you lost. - Gosh.
(Team E Hyun was close.)
Here is the result of the first mission.
(Team Ji Eun can check one card from the other team.)
Ji Eun's team can choose a member to check a card.
You should decide which one's card you want to check.
Do we swap cards with the one they pick?
It's up to them.
(The winning team can decide whether to trade cards or not.)
- They'll take it if they like it. - They can choose not to take it?
- They won't if they don't like it. - Oh, I get it.
- Then we will... - What card are you holding?
(An unexpected question)
- Your card. - If you want to know,
(It doesn't work on him.)
you have to pick mine.
She's unusual.
(Ji Eun)
Did you really think he would tell you that?
E Hyun, are you holding a useful card?
(Then he asks blatantly too.)
- Your card. - Mine is a bomb.
- It's a bomb? - Yes.
She doesn't mean that it's literally a bomb, right?
(Does she have the bomb card?)
Shall we check E Hyun's card?
We'll check So E Hyun's card!
(They decide to check E Hyun's card.)
- We'll check So E Hyun's card. - So E Hyun.
- Show us. - So E Hyun, show them your card.
(It's time to reveal E Hyun's card.)
They can check your card just like that?
(Does she really have the bomb card?)
I guess they can.
Mine really is a bomb.
(What kind of card would So E Hyun have?)
(It's blank!)
I will make an exchange.
Yes, let's do that.
I'll make an exchange with Haha.
(After checking E Hyun's blank card, they trade with Haha's.)
Song Ji Hyo wants to make an exchange with Haha.
(Ji Hyo trades her card with Haha.)
(Ji Hyo got Haha's rock card.)
(Ji Hyo, Rock)
(What is on the card that Haha received from Ji Hyo?)
(E Hyun, Blank Card Jong Kook, Unrevealed)
(Haha, Unrevealed)
Now your meal will be served.
(It's time to enjoy the meal.)
The winners get three servings.
(The winning team will have three servings.)
The losers will only get one serving.
(The losing team will only have one serving.)
Please serve the food.
(It's a feast of appetizing meat!)
Okay, this is why we're in Jeju.
- This looks really good. - It's amazing.
(I'm so jealous.)
- I'm so hungry. - It looks delicious.
(That's why the keyword was "meat".)
- My goodness. - This is why it's called "Meat"?
The yukgaejang is unbelievably delicious.
(Sweet bracken yukgaejang, dombe meat...)
Yes, it's good.
(and noodle soup with pork)
This is dombe meat.
(As they enjoy bountiful meat...)
This one is dombe meat?
Before we serve you your meal, you should exchange cards.
(Seafood Team also trade cards.)
- Exchange cards. - Should we pick one?
- Let's... - Hey, it's obvious that...
(Team Ju Bin needs a rock card.)
Kwang Soo or Jae Suk has a bomb.
So we should make sure who that is.
Then should we pick Jae Suk's card?
(They suspect either Jae Suk or Kwang Soo has the bomb card.)
Jae Suk's? Okay.
We made a decision.
(They first check the most likely candidate, Jae Suk.)
- We'll check Jae Suk's card. - Okay.
- Show us your card. - Show them your card.
(Which card did Jae Suk pick?)
This goes very well with Jeju Island.
- Oh, gosh. - It's empty.
- Nothing's in it. - No.
(Jae Suk has a blank card.)
It's blank.
- It's blank. - Nothing's in it.
Kwang Soo, what's yours? A rock?
A woman.
(Serious)
Did you just call Kwang Soo a rock?
Hey!
(He outbursts first then realizes it later.)
- No, I didn't mean it like that. - What's wrong with that?
- You deliberately said that. - What's wrong with saying "rock"?
He asked if I have a rock, so what's wrong?
Let me get this straight.
- I'm okay. Don't make a big deal. - Hey, you.
Don't you dare call Kwang Soo a rock again.
- You just stay quiet. - I don't care what he calls me.
- You watch your mouth. - What wrong with that?
I straightened it out.
(Calm down.)
It was also funny when he said he has a woman.
(Another touching story of Jae Suk siding with his close friend.)
Since he has long hair.
A woman.
He's lying.
(It's time to decide whether they'll trade cards or not.)
- Shall we? - Tell us how your picks.
Well, we should try it.
- This is the first game. - All right.
- We will make an exchange. - Yes, we will.
(Team Ju Bin decides to trade as they need the rock card.)
Who will exchange with whom?
I will exchange with Kwang soo.
(They'll trade Se Chan's card with Kwang Soo's card.)
- Making one exchange? - Yes.
- Please change your cards. - Open it.
Gosh, it's wind.
(It's not that bad.)
- Wait, it's a woman. - It's a woman.
We told you honestly.
(It doesn't look too bad for Team Ju Bin.)
- Wait a minute. - We knew you were being honest.
- This is good for both. - Yes.
- Well, for us... - Right? For her too.
(Team Yeo Jin didn't lose much too.)
Yes, you're right.
(It's time to enjoy the seafood.)
- It was a good exchange. - I'm happy for both.
Now we will serve you your meal.
- It's hard to have a meal. - Thank you for the meal.
(From the assorted fish freshly caught nearby...)
- This is the meal? - Gosh, it's abalone.
It's amazing.
(A complete set of seafood)
Look at the abalone. It looks really delicious.
(Mouth widened)
It looks really good.
- The smell. - Smells good.
How is it?
- Is it good? - Yes, it is.
(They are speechless as they're too busy enjoying the food.)
The rice and sea urchin bowl is nicely scorched at the bottom.
- Amazing. - Can they have some too?
I don't think so.
Jae Suk.
- This is so good. - It's rice with sea urchin roe.
(An opportunity to enjoy the rice with sea urchin roe!)
It's really good.
Who can imitate an abalone?
(Imitate an abalone?)
What do we do about her?
- This is humiliating. - How could she do this?
(That's very insulting.)
- This is ridiculous. - Why aren't you giving us food?
- It's urchin and abalone. - Come on. Imitate an abalone.
Cue!
- Here he goes. - Imitate an abalone. Cue!
(Here's a wild abalone.)
Here he goes.
There's an abalone.
(Polite)
Taste this. It's so good. It's scorched nicely.
(It's been long since he swallowed his pride.)
I won't let you humiliate me, Jeon So Min.
The rice with sea urchin roe is so good.
(The first mission is over.)
You think so?
It's time to choose the keywords for the second mission.
(It's time to pick the keyword for the second mission.)
The first word is "steal".
(Mission 2 Keywords: 1. Steal, 2. Take off)
The second word is "take off".
(Where will each team go?)
What is this?
(Team Yeo Jin arrived at the mission site first.)
- What is it? - What's this?
(Which keyword did they choose?)
Why is this "take off"?
Are we doing taekwondo?
(A "take-off" mission)
They're taekwondo uniforms.
There are socks. Maybe we're taking each other's socks off.
(An airplane zooms through over their heads.)
(It's noisy because there's an airport nearby.)
There are airplanes flying by because there's an airport nearby.
An airplane flies by every four minutes.
Really?
(An airplane flies by every four minutes.)
My goodness. Jong Kook shouldn't be here.
(The other team just arrives.)
- Who is it? - Please let it be Suk Jin.
(They're all waiting for Suk Jin to arrive.)
- Okay! - That's it!
It's Jong Kook.
Can't you hear Haha? Haha's here too.
(Frustrated)
Come on! You're all dead!
(It's Jong Kook, Haha, and E Hyun.)
- So E Hyun. - E Hyun's here.
- Jong Kook, gosh. - I'm scared of her.
It's Jong Kook.
(Even Poseidon becomes weak in front of Jong Kook.)
Gosh, it's Yeo Jin.
Yes, there she is.
(Hello!)
Gosh, I'm scared of her.
(A change in attitude)
Hello.
Gosh, this sucks.
We're so dead.
(Team Poseidon's passion is nowhere to be found.)
- I'm so scared. - Hey, you're here.
Gosh, what's with the uniform?
(What's with the uniform?)
All of you chose the word "take off".
(The mission for the teams that chose "take-off".)
Here's the second mission.
You have to take off your opponent's clothes...
in order to gain points.
- Take off clothes? - What?
You have to take off your opponent's clothes to win points.
(So you literally should take off the opponent's clothes?)
- Take off clothes? - What?
- Are you serious? - This is so one-dimensional.
- Seriously? - It's so one-dimensional.
(Wind, Women, Rocks, and Bombs: Second Mission)
The second mission is called Stake Your Life on a Single Match.
(Stake Your Life on a Single Match)
One member from each team will fight one-on-one.
(A member from each team will fight one-on-one.)
We're adopting the rules of judo.
If you take off your opponent's pair of socks, you get a Yuko.
(It's effective when you take off the opponent's socks.)
If you take the top uniform or the bottom, you get a half-point.
(It's a half point if you take off the opponent's top or bottom.)
(It's one full point if you rip off the opponent's name tag.)
If you get the name tag under the uniform, you get a point.
(Two counts of effective will equal a half point.)
Two Yukos equals a half-point.
So if you get their socks and a top, you get a full point.
(Two half points will equal one full point.)
Which male member will go for the first round?
It depends on who you're fighting against.
I'm sure anyone can win you.
(If we lose against Jong Kook, we must win against Haha.)
So it doesn't matter who fights, Kwang soo or me.
(You think you can win me for sure?)
You're the one who should choose carefully.
I pick you.
(He calls Jae Suk without titles as he's treated as the weakest.)
- He wants you. - Just this once.
"I pick you."
(A match between the two weak members is set.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes.
(Confident)
- I'll fight Haha, you fight him. - All right.
- Haha chose me, so I'll fight him. - Okay, okay.
(A small boy hunter)
Let's go.
Shortie said he wants to go against me.
My back hurts today.
Your back hurts?
- Yes, a little. - Where?
Which part?
- Hey. - Just let me see.
My goodness.
(It's a question with no good intentions.)
- This part? - Go away.
This part?
(Punching)
(He precisely aims for Jong Kook's pain points.)
How dare you!
- What's wrong with him? - He says his back hurts.
(He knows Jong Kook's weak points.)
Then should we focus on punching him in the back?
I knew he wouldn't worry about me but this is unbelievable.
I can't believe this.
Kwang Soo, what is that?
- I tied a knot. - Gosh, that's really...
(Kwang Soo's knot style)
- unattractive. - What?
(Very messy)
Then how should I do it?
(Shameless)
- Is it called "untie your knot"? - He said it's unattractive.
Then should I tie this?
We're on the same team, but you really are pathetic.
(Even the same team members think he went too far.)
Aren't you tired of it?
- It's really fun. - It's really fun?
(He says it's fun.)
I thought you would be really tired of yourself.
(He never gets tired of it.)
- Seriously. - It's therapeutic.
Thank goodness.
(He finds playing dirty therapeutic.)
Is it therapeutic for you?
(Running Man is therapeutic.)
I am glad that it's therapeutic.
You know the rules, right? Let's begin.
(The first round)
Get ready.
Let's go! We need to win no matter what.
(Jae Suk needs to win this round no matter what.)
Let's go!
(Let's begin!)
Shortie said he wants to go against me.
(It's a match between the weakest members.)
I pick you.
(They look weak from the start.)
(Who will be the weaker one?)
Is Haha drunk?
Seriously.
(Useless tension between the weakest members)
You didn't even budge.
(Whirring)
(An airplane passes over the arena.)
- You little... - You...
(What?)
(They swear at each other while the audio gets drowned out.)
I can't hear you over the sound of the airplane!
(What are they saying?)
(They continue to have a private conversation.)
(They are fighters who use their mouths, not bodies.)
(The airplane passes by...)
(and Haha aims for Jae Suk's sock.)
You got it!
(His back is wide open as he reaches for Jae Suk's sock.)
Okay. You got it!
No! Guard your name tag!
Guard your name tag, Haha!
(Jae Suk will get one full point if he rips off the name tag.)
- No! Guard your name tag! - Guard your name tag, Haha!
(Ripping off)
One full point!
(Jae Suk wins with one full point!)
- No! Guard your name tag! - Guard your name tag, Haha!
(The weakest members' match ends so fast that it's embarrassing.)
One full point!
He won with one full point!
(Dazed)
Does the game end if the name tag gets removed?
(Incredulous)
(Their teammate is weaker than they expected.)
- Isn't it about the socks? - He didn't know.
- I didn't know. - He didn't know.
This is about taking off clothes.
- One full point! - Good!
(Jae Suk wins a fight for the first time in his life.)
- The man with one full point! - Okay!
I had a really cool plan.
- Haha looked so stupid. - Hold on.
- This match shouldn't count. - He tried to lift me up.
(Whatever his strategy was, )
This match shouldn't count. I had a really cool plan.
(it helped him lose in the shortest time.)
- Okay. - Haha loses with one full point.
- Hey! - Okay!
(He's yelling in a uniform that is bigger than him.)
- I was going to... - All right!
I even swore when the airplane flew by.
(Satisfied)
It took me more time to change into these clothes.
- He didn't understand the rules. - Seriously.
(Jong Kook stands up to redeem himself.)
- Kwang Soo! - All right.
I will do my best.
(The dirty player Kwang Soo stands against him.)
- Just do some damage to him. - I might beat him.
For goodness' sake.
I am in a bad condition. For goodness' sake.
Jong Kook has a bad back today.
(He pretends to be worried.)
(An intense and dirty game is expected.)
Don't overexert yourself.
This is bad.
Kwang Soo, just do some damage to him.
Do your absolute best...
(Jumping)
so that he is humiliated even if you don't win.
(He may not win, but he will insult Jong Kook.)
- Okay? - Okay, okay.
Just fold him in half.
(I don't want to play against him.)
(Hitting)
Kwang Soo, that's your specialty.
(He will aim for Jong Kook's back.)
Jong Kook's back is hurting! And you're aiming for his back?
(He will hit only where it hurts!)
There you go!
(He will hit Jong Kook's back with his heels.)
- He is the worst. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - He is flippant.
Kwang Soo, know this.
(Aiming at the spine)
Kwang Soo.
Remember that the airplane passes by every four minutes.
(Angry)
Why did I pick him?
- What? - Why did I pick him?
(He's very reliable when he's in the same team.)
Isn't it great that he is on our team?
- He is insane. - Had he been on another team...
(He is the number 1 person to avoid when he's in a different team.)
I really don't want to do this.
(Picking up)
Hold on. You can't use that.
(He picks up a rock from the corner of the park.)
- It's a rock for therapy. - You can't use that.
(It's a rock for therapy.)
You can't use that.
(He acts like he doesn't know anything.)
Hey! You jerk!
(He stopped playing fair 10 years ago.)
He is absolutely ridiculous.
(I can't believe him.)
He has a license.
A license?
(The viewers go, "He is always like that.")
- The viewers... - They forgive Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
Remember that the airplane passes by every four minutes.
Okay, okay.
Get ready. Set...
(Round 2 begins!)
He is ridiculous.
- Five minutes, right? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo's eyes and limbs go crazy upon the start.)
There is a tie, right?
- Just take off his socks. - Okay.
(Jumping)
Think of it as skinning him.
(Jong Kook, think of it as skinning him.)
Skin!
(He's acting up as best as he can.)
Kwang Soo, that's good.
- Kwang Soo, save up your energy. - Jong Kook,
he is getting tired.
(He exhausts his energy by being flippant.)
- Hey! - He is breathing with his mouth.
(Panting)
- He is exhausted. - Let's go!
(Playing dirty requires a lot of energy.)
Kwang Soo, why are you taking off your clothes?
- Kwang Soo, fasten your belt! - Okay!
Why are you taking off your clothes?
- Hey! - It came undone.
(His belt gets untied unexpectedly.)
What is going on?
(It's time to stop playing dirty!)
Kwang Soo!
(Jong Kook begins to strike back.)
Jong Kook, he is intimidated. Look at his face.
(Kwang Soo is intimidated.)
He is totally intimidated.
He is aiming for a tie game.
(He aims for a tie game with a scared look on his face.)
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo. Hang in there.
Here it comes.
(At that moment)
Kwang Soo!
(Collapsing)
(Jong Kook uses brute strength to throw him down.)
Kwang Soo!
- My goodness. - Oh, no.
- He is putting on a show. - This is...
(Kwang Soo gets folded up...)
(in that position.)
- You jerk. - Wait. Stop!
(Kwang Soo gets folded up.)
You jerk.
(Whirring)
It's an airplane! It's an airplane!
(An airplane flies by while Kwang Soo gets folded up.)
(He swore so loudly that they could hear it clearly.)
(He is saying everything he wants to say.)
You little punk. Come here.
(He successfully insults Jong Kook.)
- My goodness. - That's so funny.
Good job.
(Satisfied)
That's so funny.
- Come on. - Okay.
(He attacks the lumbar spine.)
He is kicking.
I don't want to play against this jerk!
(There is nothing to be gained by playing a game with Kwang Soo.)
"I don't want to play against this jerk."
He is a lunatic!
(He plays dirty and kicks repeatedly.)
- Oh, no! - Kwang Soo, hang in there.
- That's good. - He keeps hitting Jong Kook's back.
(Jong Kook finally manages to remove Kwang Soo's name tag!)
He wins with one full point!
(Jong Kook wins with one full point!)
- Gosh. - Good job.
(Jong Kook won, )
Why is it the winner who always gets hurt?
(but it feels like Kwang Soo won the match.)
Kwang Soo, LFW. LFW.
- LFW? - Yes, LFW.
Why is it the winner who always gets hurt?
(Upset)
What does LFW mean?
"Lost but fought well."
(I don't want to play against Kwang Soo.)
- LFW. - I did my best.
Say something to Kwang Soo!
No one else would put up with his behavior.
(Punching)
(It's not over until it is.)
- That crazy... - He is full of energy.
- That crazy jerk. - LFW.
(He still has energy left.)
He hit me for real.
Hey, LFW.
(Can someone make Kwang Soo play fair?)
- He hit me for real. - Okay.
- Seriously. - LFW.
That phrase suits him very well.
(It's a tie.)
- Did you play Jenga? - We destroyed Jae Suk.
(Along Sanji Stream that flows through the city, )
Did Jae Suk get shaky hands?
We played it with this.
I see.
We will win this round easily.
(Team Ju Bin and Team Ji Eun gathered in Buksugu Square.)
- Thank you for the food. - They are no match for us.
Thank you for letting us play against Suk Jin,
(They used up their energy while criticizing each other.)
- the weakest member. - But there is Ji Hyo.
- So Min, I... - You guys don't look so strong.
The second mission is...
(The Jeju Island Special: Wind, Women, Rocks, and Bombs)
Tubes on a Tangerine Tree.
(Tubes on a Tangerine Tree)
Pick a member who will protect the tubes...
(Pick a member who will protect the tubes...)
as the tangerine tree.
(as the tangerine tree.)
(The 2 other members need to steal the tubes...)
The two other members need to steal the tubes...
and put as many of them as they can on the tangerine tree.
(and put as many of them as they can on the tangerine tree.)
You can steal tubes from the other team's tree.
The team with more tubes on the tangerine tree wins.
(In short, the team with more tubes on the tangerine tree wins.)
The winning team will get a chance to check one member's card...
(The winning team will get a chance to exchange the cards.)
and exchange the cards.
Who won earlier?
- We won. - We won.
Ji Eun, did you get to eat? Did you win?
(Dazing)
- It was no joke. - You are still...
thinking about it, right?
What? Did something happen between her and So Min?
- Nothing happened! - We heard a lot about So Min.
(It's very awkward to see each other again.)
- We heard good things. - I didn't do anything.
Then why aren't you looking at So Min once?
(Instigating)
- I am looking at her. - She is looking at me. Come on.
(Awkward eye contact)
I heard there is bad blood between them.
(Suk Jin makes them feel more awkward.)
- There is nothing. - Check it when the episode airs.
There must be a story.
So Min, let go of your grudges. We are on Jeju Island.
- She has grudges. - This is my first variety show,
so I did as they asked.
Don't do that, Ji Eun.
I did it to give you more screen time.
(Comradeship)
Thank you.
I don't know what's happening, but thank you.
Please pick a member who will be the persimmon tree.
(They start the mission.)
Get ready.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo become tangerine trees.)
Set...
You can go slow.
(The game begins.)
You can take your time in the beginning.
- Ji Eun working so hard. - Put the tubes on her.
Go ahead.
- I will throw the tubes. - That's good.
That's good. That's good.
(Ji Hyo gets tubes fast.)
We got as many as we can.
We got as many as we can. Wait.
Knock out their tubes!
(The awkward alumni meet in front of a tangerine tree.)
We just need to keep those tubes.
(She gets past Ji Eun.)
(So Min does her Tiger Moth kicks.)
We just need to keep those tubes.
Hey!
Don't kick!
What?
My goodness. My goodness.
(She bumps in after kicking.)
That was no joke.
All right. Stop.
(Ji Hyo falls twice.)
- All right. Stop. - Hey.
(Ji Hyo runs somewhere.)
Hey.
(What?)
(Why is she attacking Ju Bin?)
Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo! - Hey.
(Ji Hyo the delinquent attacks the wrong person.)
(Ji Hyo the delinquent locks her head and throws her down.)
- For goodness' sake. - Hold on.
(It's a bolt out of the blue while moving tubes.)
Ten seconds remain.
(While Ji Hyo lost it, )
She is heavy!
She is grabbing me by the neck.
(Se Chan got dunked on.)
(Se Chan currently has 0 tubes because of Ji Eun.)
- Hurry up. - Hurry up.
(Ji Hyo is also struggling because of Ju Bin.)
Hurry up.
- Hey! - I will hold on to her.
(The tangerine tree plays defense.)
(Ju Bin is in Ji Hyo's clutches!)
- Oh, no. - Get your feet up.
(Se Chan's blocked by Ji Eun.)
- 5, 4, - Get your feet up.
(Who's the winner?)
- three, - Hurry up and stick them in.
- two, - Ji Hyo.
- one. - Let's go down together.
Let's go down together. Come here.
Come here.
(The game ends.)
- Okay. Ji Hyo has five tubes... - What is this?
(Team Ju Bin: 2, Team Ji Eun: 5)
- and Se Chan has two tubes. - How many does he have?
(Team Ji Eun wins.)
I am exhausted.
She cheated too much!
- Seriously. - Excuse me.
Ju Bin...
cheated much more.
I... I...
(Angry)
- She is so strong. - You know,
Ji Eun is so strong.
(They expected Ji Eun to be sloppy, )
(but she had hidden brute strength.)
She is really strong.
She must be angry at someone.
- Guys. - It's So Min, right?
(He comes between So Min and Ji Eun every time he has a chance.)
- You should make up here. - You want to attack her, right?
(You run into your worst enemy at the worst time.)
- She attacked me. - Okay.
- You must be angry. - She attacked me already.
"I haven't met my enemy in a while!"
"I will show her!"
(He adds a skit to his made-up story.)
- I understand, Ji Eun. - She is so strong.
(Team Ji Eun can check 1 person's card.)
Ji Eun's team can pick a member and check his or her card.
(Ji Hyo, Suk Jin, Ji Eun, Ju Bin, Se Chan, So Min)
We will check Ju Bin's card.
- Ju Bin. - We will give you another chance.
- No, thank you. - Okay.
(They decide to check Ju Bin's card.)
All right.
(What's Ju Bin's card?)
(They check that it's the wind card!)
- For goodness' sake. - They must have the same card.
(The members of Team Ji Eun school their faces.)
We figured it out.
(They fall for the poker face.)
You must have the same card.
It's the wind card.
Then we will exchange two cards.
(It's time to exchange the cards.)
Se Chan.
Will you exchange cards?
- We will switch Ju Bin's card... - And Ji Eun's card, right?
(Ju Bin and Ji Eun exchange cards.)
Exchange cards.
Then...
(Ji Hyo, Suk Jin, Ji Eun, Ju Bin, Se Chan, So Min)
Let's check it later.
(Ji Eun originally had...)
(a blank card!)
We don't know what will happen.
- The rock card. - The discussion is taking forever.
(Team Ji Eun gave away a blank card and received a wind card.)
- We have 2. - We have 2,
- so we need to give one to them. - It's a technique.
I will switch my card.
(Now, Team Ji Eun needs a woman card.)
Let's take our chances.
That means...
- I will switch mine with Se Chan's. - Okay.
(Suk Jin and Se Chan exchange cards.)
(Se Chan has...)
(the woman card.)
For a second...
- I was about to take that. - Okay.
(They check the cards they exchanged.)
Let's check the cards. Come here.
We did it.
(Team Ji Eun collected all three cards.)
Gosh, what is this?
Are you satisfied?
(Trying to keep a poker face)
I guess this is a bit better.
Let's move to the location of the last mission.
(Team Ji Eun completed their deck.)
(The supermodels are having the final match.)
The strap is too...
Come here.
(Poseidon's tornado!)
That's too...
(The game is too one-sided for the final game.)
This match is too one-sided.
- Help me! - It won't take long.
(Grinning)
Yeo Jin is smiling.
Yeo Jin!
- Yeo Jin! - I will take this.
(Poseidon goes for the sock.)
Yeo Jin! Yeo Jin!
What is going on?
(Pulling)
- She ripped it. - What?
- She ripped it. - Did she rip it?
- Don't rip it. - What is going on?
Yeo Jin! Yeo Jin!
- What? - She ripped it.
(She ripped the sock with brute strength.)
- Did she rip it? - Don't rip it.
What is going on?
(Shocking)
- Hey. Hey. - What is going on?
- What is going on? - She ripped it.
(E Hyun's sock passed away on Jeju Island.)
She ripped it.
(After ripping a sock, )
Yeo Jin.
(Yeo Jin takes the name tag for one full point!)
I got it!
You won with one full point!
- Okay. E Hyun, you worked hard. - I am exhausted.
(Ms. Jo Woo Jung lost her sock and has a meltdown.)
Team Yeo Jin won.
(Team Yeo Jin wins.)
- You fought well. - You fought well.
- Okay. Whose card shall we check? - Well...
(It's time for Team Yeo Jin to check the losing team's card.)
Shall we check Jong Kook's?
- Sure. - We will check Jong Kook's.
(They check Jong Kook's card.)
He looked a bit...
(Jong Kook's card is...)
What is it?
(blank.)
It's blank.
- His card is blank. - My card is blank.
I will exchange mine with Haha's.
(Jae Suk and Haha, and Yeo Jin and E Hyun trade cards.)
- And... - Mine with E Hyun's.
(Jae Suk and E Hyun have blank cards.)
- Haha. - Okay.
Check the cards.
(Jae Suk received Haha's card.)
(What was Haha's card?)
(A blank card!)
- Here you go. - Here you go.
(Yeo Jin and E Hyun switch cards as well.)
All right.
(Yeo Jin got E Hyun's blank card.)
(Blank, blank, wind)
It can't be helped.
- Here you go. - Here you go.
(What did E Hyun get from Yeo Jin?)
(Blank, blank, blank)
(She got the bomb.)
What is it?
(E Hyun got the bomb from Yeo Jin.)
I see.
(Yeo Jin picked the bomb card in the opening.)
Okay, okay, okay. I see.
- This isn't half bad. - I get it now.
(What will happen to Team E Hyun that got the bomb card?)
I get it now.
Please gather around in the center.
(Now, it's the last mission.)
You know,
- So Min. - Yes?
I heard the news.
Did it travel that far?
Ji Eun said something about you.
(So Min and Ji Eun's relationship is an issue.)
Ji Eun just thinks...
that she didn't do anything wrong.
She just thinks that you have the victim mentality.
Look at her facial expression.
(She was instigated by the guys and made a mistake.)
- We asked. - We asked.
She said it wasn't so clean.
(She said it wasn't so clean.)
Something wasn't so clean.
Ji Eun is clean.
She is clean. Her friend is the problem.
- Her friend? - Her friend is the problem.
(She brings up the real name.)
The puzzle pieces are coming together.
(The behind story of Team Blind Date is revealed.)
- Later on, - That's the problem.
you should sort things out with Ji Eun.
An airplane passes by every four minutes.
You can swear as much as you want.
(They can finish talking about it in the airplane engine sound.)
- Sort things out then. - Okay.
That's how it is.
When your acquaintances visit the show,
- it's the most exhausting. - That's right.
- You know what it's like. - You get older.
(Meltdown)
- I am getting older. - They know you too much.
(An airplane approaches and drowns out the audio.)
So Min, now is your chance to speak.
(It's now.)
(She finally gets freedom.)
(She gives the behind story.)
Don't speak ill of my friend!
(Ji Eun counterattacks!)
"Don't speak ill of my friend!"
(This is interesting.)
(A childish fight between real friends)
"Don't speak ill of my friend!"
Hey!
(She brings up a real name.)
- Are you living well? - The airplane is gone!
- The airplane is gone! - She is my friend!
(Fighting back)
The audio is working. The airplane is gone.
(It's over.)
Their fight is interesting.
(Their battle is interesting.)
That was hilarious.
I hope another airplane will fly by.
(It's fun.)
Why don't we go to an airport for the next location?
I can't help but wait for the airplanes.
Please.
(They were able to check their friendship thanks to the plane.)
That was so funny.
- It's time for the final mission. - It's the final one.
(The last mission to exchange the card for the last time)
One team has the bomb...
(Team E Hyun is likely to receive a penalty.)
and other teams are collecting the cards.
(Team Ji Eun already completed the cards.)
The last mission that will give you a chance to switch the cards is...
I Got Fooled in an Attempt to Find What's Real.
(I Got Fooled in an Attempt to Find What's Real.)
The game names are long today.
It's the random game in three stages.
(It's a random game in three stages.)
Every time you get past a stage, you will win a point.
(Stage 1, 1 point, stage 2, 1 point, stage 3, 1 point)
One member from each team will begin at the starting line.
(1 member from each team will participate.)
Stage one involves boxes.
(1 person who chooses the box with a water bucket is eliminated.)
Out of the four boxes, one has a water bucket.
One person will be eliminated.
The next stage involves the vaulting boxes.
(1 person who chooses a vaulting box made of polystyrene is eliminated.)
Two are real vaulting boxes and one is made of polystyrene.
That leaves behind two people.
One will get a water-filled ball and the other will get a real ball.
(1 person who kicks the real ball gets 1 point.)
If you kick the real ball, you get a point.
If you score a goal, you get two additional points.
(If you score a goal, you get 2 additional points.)
You need to kick gently.
(Each choice will affect the final result.)
- Yes. - If it's the fake ball...
- It won't go far. - It won't go far.
The team that places 1st can exchange 2 cards.
(The team that places 1st can exchange 2 cards.)
The team that places 2nd can exchange 1 card,
(The team that places 2nd can exchange 1 card.)
but they won't be able to exchange with the winning team.
- One member's card. - We need to avoid last place.
(We need to avoid the last place.)
(Team E Hyun has to place 2nd and give the bomb card away.)
This is hard. This is hard.
Who will participate in the first round?
(Tournament table)
I will go.
Okay. I will survive until the end.
(Team Yeo Jin, Team Ju Bin, Team Ji Eun, Team E Hyun)
Jae Suk, just avoid the ones you want to choose.
I want to choose this one,
(He wants to avoid number 2.)
- so I will avoid it. - Avoid it.
Choose well.
Ji Hyo, it doesn't matter.
I choose...
number one.
Is that your choice?
- Yes. - No!
I chose number 1 although I wanted to choose number 2.
- Okay. - You know what I mean.
(The man of terrible choice is playing smart.)
We need to do this.
- I choose number three. - Let's go!
- I choose two. - I will advance.
(Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Haha, Se Chan)
- Okay. - Let's advance.
- Go, go. - Jump!
- Show us your jump! - I will jump high.
(Groundless confidence)
- Let's go. - One,
(Will Jae Suk avoid being unlucky this time?)
two,
(In one of the boxes is a water bucket.)
three.
(Who will get eliminated first?)
- Three. - Let's go!
Okay!
(Ji Hyo is out.)
- Three. - Let's go!
Okay!
(She gets a foot bath.)
- Three. - Let's go!
Okay!
(Oh, no!)
Great!
(Our team survived!)
(Ji Hyo got eliminated in Stage 1.)
That serves you right!
I told you.
(His shoulders are high.)
Kwang Soo, I told you that I wanted to choose number two.
(Boasting)
That's a good strategy.
(The deity of terrible choice can figure out which one is terrible.)
- I really wanted to choose it. - You wanted to choose number two.
Let's go. Let's go!
Jae Suk, just go for it.
(Level 2: Vaulting)
- Okay. I'll go with number one. - Oh, wow.
I'm on a roll.
You seem so confident.
(A bad hunch)
A man must be in the center. I'll go with number two.
Okay.
Then I'll go with number three.
- I'll show you how high I can jump. - Okay.
(Shall I show you a Sargent jump?)
- Okay. I'll show you. - That's good.
All right.
- Let's go. Let's go. - Just go for it.
- Let's go at once. - Let's go.
(Number 1 Jae Suk, Number 2 Se Chan, Number 3 Haha)
- Okay. - 1, 2,
(1 of the 3 vaulting boxes is made of polystyrene.)
- three. - Jump.
Three.
(Could Jae Suk be able to avoid the bad one again?)
- Jump. - What could be the result?
(Jae Suk failed.)
Jump.
(He picked the bad one again.)
Nice!
(I was a fool to get my hopes up.)
(Getting this far is a miracle for Jae Suk.)
Jae Suk.
I told you not to follow your hunch.
- You can do whatever you want. - You should've avoided it.
I really wanted to pick that one.
(The tragedy of having too much confidence.)
- Exactly. You should've avoided it. - I told you not to do that.
Nice.
(Se Chan and Haha go for the random water-filled ball.)
Nice. Good job.
Oh, gosh. I have no idea how to tell the difference.
(Seriously)
Pull this off.
(The two balls look the same from the outside.)
How do we tell the difference?
- This time... - Haha, did you pick that one?
(Number 1 Se Chan, Number 2 Haha)
- Yes, I'll go with this one. - Okay. Go ahead.
- Good luck. - Go ahead.
All right. Ready.
(Only one of them is the real ball.)
Get set. Go.
(Who will kick the water-filled soccer ball?)
(Haha picked the water-filled ball.)
(That means Se Chan picked the real ball.)
(If he scores a goal, he gets extra two points.)
Okay.
(Se Chan scored a goal.)
- Okay. - The ball went into the goal.
(He made a clean shot.)
- Okay. Okay. - All right.
(Se Chan is the best.)
- Good job. - So Min, I think I did well.
- You did well. - Was it a real ball?
(Se Chan from Team Ju Bin earns a total of 5 points.)
- It was a real ball. - That's awesome.
(What a shame.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
(Round 2: Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Suk Jin, and Ju Bin)
- Let's go. - You're our last hope.
Let's go.
- Ju Bin, you can do this. Let's go. - Ju Bin.
- I don't know what to choose. - Let's go.
(I'm nervous.)
- Let's go! - I don't know!
Which one should I choose?
(He lets his team members decide.)
- This is the last round. - This one was...
- The box at the end. - At the end?
(Suk Jin)
It was number two in the previous round.
(That's where Ji Hyo failed.)
I'm sure it's not the same box.
(He picks number 2.)
- Okay! - I'll go with...
I pick the box that was the bad one.
(Jong Kook picked the same box.)
- Okay! - I'll go with...
(But I already picked that box.)
I pick the box that was the bad one.
You picked the box that was the bad one earlier?
Sure. Go ahead.
(Acting cool)
I can pick something else.
- We have as many as four boxes. - Just do as you always do.
Okay. This one?
- Okay. - Let's go!
(Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Ju Bin, and Kwang Soo)
- Go, go, go. - Okay.
1, 2, 3.
(Even a single point can change the ranking.)
(Who will be eliminated in the first round?)
Three.
(Big Nose fell into water.)
(Team Ji Eun failed in the 1st round 2nd time in a row.)
You failed.
- This is ridiculous. - I told you...
I told you to choose that box.
(I told you.)
- No way. - I told you to pick that one.
(Even after completing the set, the team is at risk of being last.)
I was worried.
- It's hard to tell the difference. - This is...
(The other 3 members go for Level 2.)
- But... - I'll go with this one.
- I'll go with that. - Okay.
(Ju Bin chooses number 2.)
Good.
Ju Bin, do you want to switch places with Kwang Soo?
(Number 1 Kwang Soo, Number 2 Ju Bin, Number 3 Jong Kook)
No, don't do that.
Give him a chance. Ask him if he wants to do that.
(Ask Kwang Soo)
Just in case.
How about we play rock-paper-scissors?
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
- Okay. - Switch with him. Good.
- Do you think that's the bad one? - This is a great chance for us.
(Ju Bin and Kwang Soo change places.)
- Go, go, go. - I don't think it is.
- I think this is the bad one. - Kwang Soo, go.
- I think this is it. - No.
(I have a bad hunch.)
- Go, Kwang Soo. - I think this is it.
(Wherever Kwang Soo passes by seems to be unlucky.)
1, 2...
- I think it's made of polystyrene. - You should sit on it.
(Kwang Soo never gets lucky.)
Three.
(Ju Bin switched places with him. What could be their fate?)
(Ju Bin fell.)
Three.
(The terrifying curse of the unlucky man)
(Nice!)
- I knew it. - She should've stayed there.
(She lost after changing places.)
- I knew it. - I'm sorry, Ju Bin.
- I'm sorry, Ju Bin. - Se Chan.
- You're a spy, aren't you? - No, I'm not.
- You're a spy, aren't you? - You did well.
- Thank you, Ju Bin. - Ju Bin.
(Thanks to her, Kwang Soo moves on to the next step.)
She shouldn't have switched places with him.
I knew it. I had a feeling that it was the bad one.
I didn't know. You did a good job.
- Kwang Soo will fail in this round. - Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook are at the final Level 3.)
This is the most difficult round.
(It's very hard to tell the difference from the outside.)
It's confusing.
I think this one is it.
This is the most difficult round.
(Looking closely)
(Looking at it won't make any difference.)
This is the most difficult round.
(Jong Kook chooses carefully as if he chooses a protein shake.)
I'll go with this one.
(Number 2)
- Go, Kwang Soo. - Just kick it into the goal.
(Kwang Soo chooses number 1.)
1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo didn't expect he would make it this far.)
Three.
(Will his luck last until the end?)
(No way. He picked the water-filled ball.)
(Now, what's important is whether Jong Kook will score a goal or not.)
(If he scores a goal too, his team will win the race.)
(Will he scare a goal?)
- They both missed. - You unlucky man.
(He missed a goal!)
I got scared before I kicked it.
(Coward)
I thought it was the water-filled ball.
Both of them failed.
(It's a critical mistake of a field general.)
How could you miss that?
I thought it was the water-filled ball.
- How could you miss that? - I thought it was the fake ball.
(Dumbfounded)
(He keeps repeating.)
I got scared and pulled my foot back.
(The mission ends with Jong Kook's mistake.)
Each team won one point every time they pass each round.
(It's time to reveal the final score.)
The winning team is...
(Which team will win the chance to exchange two cards?)
Team Ju Bin.
The winning team is Team Ju Bin.
(We shall celebrate.)
- Oh, yes! - Let's go around in a circle.
(That's a shame. If only I had scored a goal.)
(Gosh. They're annoying.)
(They're trying hard not to show their emotions.)
This is your last chance to exchange your cards.
(It's time to trade cards for the first-place team, Team Ju Bin.)
The winning team, please tell us which cards you want to exchange.
- We will... - We'll exchange...
(They only need the rock card.)
- exchange only 1 card. - only 1 card.
(They'll only switch 1 card.)
Whose card will you exchange?
(Ju Bin, Blank Card)
Mine.
- We'll exchange hers for Ji Eun's. - For Ji Eun's.
(Ji Eun, Wind)
- Mine? - Yes.
(They picked the rock card that Ji Eun has.)
Whose for whose?
(They gave Ji Eun the wind card at the second mission.)
- For Ji Eun's. - Let's exchange the cards.
(And they received the blank card from Ji Eun.)
Listen to me carefully, okay?
(So they knew that Ji Eun had the wind card.)
We have to get Ji Eun's card no matter what.
(They focused on Ji Eun's wind card strategically.)
Mine.
(They choose Ji Eun as planned.)
- We'll exchange hers for Ji Eun's. - For Ji Eun's.
Mine?
(Ji Eun, Wind, Ji Hyo and Se Chan, Rock, Suk Jin and So Min, Woman)
Give us your card, Ji Eun.
- Give it to us. - It's okay.
That's not it.
Give us your card, Ji Eun.
(Team Ju Bin completes rock, woman, and wind cards.)
- Give it to us. - It's okay.
- Here you go. - Okay.
(They try to maintain the poker face until the end.)
I can hear you.
(Se Chan, Ju Bin, and So Min have rock, wind, and woman.)
Everything went well for us.
- This is hard to believe. - Exactly.
(Their strategy worked.)
- It's unbelievable. - Later...
The team in second place, tell us the card you want to exchange.
(Team E Hyun must remove the bomb card.)
We'll exchange mine...
(Will E Hyun's bomb card...)
(go to Team Yeo Jin? Or to Team Ji Eun?)
We'll exchange mine...
for Ji Hyo's card.
We'll exchange mine for Ji Hyo's.
(They'll exchange E Hyun's bomb card for Ji Hyo's rock card.)
Okay.
Can they exchange another card?
(She accepts the bomb card without knowing anything.)
They can exchange only one card, right?
(We're done for.)
(Maintaining his poker face is pointless.)
- Why did they all take our cards? - Why did you do that?
Our team...
- Did we do something wrong? - You know...
All right. The card exchange is over.
(The card trade is over.)
Reveal your cards starting with Team Ju Bin.
(Team Ju Bin reveals their cards.)
- You go first. - Let's do it.
(Whispering)
- We go first? - Yes.
- Must we do this? - Yes.
- Se Chan nagged us to do this. - Just this once.
Let's give it a try.
The hilarious Rock.
The best in the universe, Woman.
The fist beauty, Wind.
- We succeeded. - We succeeded.
(They look cheerful like the cast of "TV Kindergarten".)
(But the adults are very cold when it comes to reactions.)
We did a perfect job.
It's awesome.
(This is so annoying.)
What?
We did a perfect job. It's awesome.
(The three of them worked hard but only helped another team win.)
What?
We got lucky only in the beginning.
- Awesome. - See?
(He compliments himself.)
Those comments were so neat.
Look how they're whispering to each other.
They all look upset.
They're just jealous.
(He is very unhappy.)
They're jealous.
The next team, please reveal your cards.
- I have the bomb card. - Okay.
- They'll get the penalty. - We lost our cards.
(Team Ji Eun will get the penalty.)
They took our cards.
(I'm so sorry.)
They were the first team we met.
The winning team of the first part...
(It's time to announce the result.)
of The Jeju Island Special is Team Ju Bin.
(Team Ju Bin won.)
- The winning team will receive... - We won!
(The special prize for the winning team)
top quality Jeju Island's black pork gift sets.
Oh, my. That's amazing.
(Genuinely envious)
I bet the meat has gone bad.
(He's acting jealous.)
Thank you.
(They have their hands full.)
- Thank you. - Oh, my.
It's heavy.
I've never won before.
(Feeling proud)
Now, I'll reveal today's penalty.
(It's time to reveal the penalty.)
Okay. What is it?
- The penalty is... - Yes.
You will be slapped on the forehead with a wet hand.
(Getting slapped on the forehead with the wet hand.)
- That's easy. - It's not a harsh one.
(Suk Jin willingly gives up his forehead.)
It's time for Suk Jin...
- I'm sorry. - Oh, no.
(Jae Suk is getting ready.)
I need to temper my hand...
- by repeating wetting and drying. - Tempering your hand?
- Like this. - Jae Suk.
- Dry it in Jeju Island's breeze. - Of course.
(He gets ready with Jeju's natural wind.)
Of course, I use the breeze.
You must know what you've done wrong.
(Welcome, wet hand slap.)
(It's as refreshing as Jeju Island's scenery.)
Let's hear how they feel about being on the show.
It was nice to get some fresh air since it's been a while.
(Thanks to Choi Yeo Jin, Lee Ju Bin, So E Hyun, and Han Ji Eun...)
- Exactly. - That's right.
(for joining us today in Jeju Island!)
- Thank you. - Thank you for your help.
- Good job, everyone. - Good job.
Hey, number three. You a human cultural asset.
(The Jeju Island Special Part Two: Welcome To Running Group Tour)
It's because I'm a human cultural asset.
(Jae Suk is a human cultural asset, and Suk Jin is his student.)
I'm a human cultural asset, you punk.
- Honey. - You're so pretty.
(Se Chan and So Min are a newlywed couple.)
He's an assistant manager, and I'm a newbie.
(Haha is an assistant manager, and Jong Kook is a new employee.)
We came on our company outing.
I'm the runner-up.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are math contest winners.)
You're the winner of a math contest.
- Here we go, here we go - Here we go, here we go.
(Running Tour begins with many tourists.)
The first thing you'll do...
- I'll go shopping. - I'll enjoy my shopping spree.
(The highlight of a group tour, shopping)
- You bought so many things. - I'm here to spend money.
- It's beautiful. - This must be the spot.
(Having the best photo in life taken)
This is the best photo in your life.
(The feast that you can enjoy only in Jeju Island)
- That looks delicious. - Jeju Island has great food.
Can I really enjoy shopping like this?
The person who must pay 662 dollars is...
(Some of them enjoy themselves...)
(while the others pay the bills for them.)
I can just avoid getting caught.
(If you get caught, you have to pay!)
- We'll be in big trouble. - Okay. You're doing well.
(You will be the one who pays for everything the others enjoy.)
"This never has a peaceful day."
(This never has a peaceful day.)
What could be...
My family never has a peaceful day.
(My family never has a peaceful day.)
Get it together, will you?
(What could this strange loser-pays-all group tour be?)
It's over when you get caught.
(The Jeju Island Special Part Two: Loser-Pays-All Group Tour)