- Hello.
So Min dressed up today.
I'm wearing dress shoes
in a long while.
- Hello.
I'm wearing dress shoes
in a long while.
Actually, Jong Kook is
on a new show. I saw it.
- "Fly Shootdori".
- Things have gotten friendly now.
- You're promoting other shows.
- Right.
- We're a real family.
- I started filming "Fly Shootdori."
- Yes.
Se Chan is on the show with you.
- Se Chan.
- Jong Kook,
- didn't you help him get cast?
- Yes, he practically hired me.
I found out that
we're filming in Taebaek.
We have to film for two days
when I go down there.
I thought
I would be really bored there,
so I decided to take
one of my sidekicks.
Jong Kook, is that
why you picked me?
That's why you brought me there.
It will be so boring if I go
there alone. Don't you agree?
Right.
- I feel comfortable around him.
- In a nutshell, he's your doll.
- Right.
- Yes.
He keeps me in his pocket.
When he tells me to come out,
I come out.
He's a doll you keep next to you
when going to sleep.
I knew it.
Doll Chan, you're something else.
- Doll Chan.
It's a combination of
"doll" and "Se Chan."
- Seriously.
- My gosh.
That's crazy.
So Min was bored either
at the end or in the beginning...
of the year,
so she called Se Chan.
Se Chan told her that
he was on his way to Taebaek.
- She said she was very lonely...
- Really?
- at the beginning of the year.
- I'm sorry.
I took away the doll
you're attached to.
Gosh, the doll she's attached to?
(The conflict of the custody
around the doll)
- I'm a doll?
- Hey, let's share him.
Let's share him.
- He's a doll I cannot touch.
- Is that so?
- I see.
- When it snowed earlier,
So Min was standing by the window
and was watching the snow...
by herself. I thought to myself,
"My gosh, So Min."
But the automatic door opened,
and she got squashed.
(But the automatic door opened,
and she got squashed.)
- She's a true TV entertainer.
- I'm serious.
- She's a real TV entertainer.
- I missed that.
- I should have seen that.
- So Min, what were you doing?
- I was so embarrassed.
- Her life is entertaining.
Before you start your race,
only one guest will join you today.
- We only invited one.
- Really?
- There's only one guest.
Please come on in.
- Gosh, it's the only guest today.
- Who is it?
- The only guest of the day.
- The stairs?
- It's been a while.
- The guest is coming. Who is it?
She's wearing a pink jacket
and boots.
It's been a while
since I saw those long boots.
People usually wear them
when they go horseback riding.
I think she's been on variety shows.
- She's...
- She's very... Is that Jin Young?
- Who is it?
- It's not Jin Young.
- Han Na?
- Is she...
- Hello.
- It's Ha Na.
(The actress won over the viewers
with her countless charms.)
- My goodness.
- Please stand in the middle.
- How are you? It's been a while.
- Park Ha Na.
We were told we'd have
only one guest, and Ha Na came.
Ha Na... I think you were
on our show quite recently.
- It's been a year.
- Really?
- It's already been a year?
- I saw a rerun of the episode.
- Right.
- Yes.
Well, today... My goodness.
This is the first one on the list.
It's underlined in blue.
The writer added three stars
on this.
- You'll show us your EDM dance.
- All of a sudden?
- Jae Suk, are you serious?
- Before saying hi to the viewers?
- My gosh.
- That's all right.
- That's so 2020.
- You can do it.
These days, we don't build up
to reach the climax.
We cut to the chase right away.
- Let's go.
- Ha Na, can you show us the dance?
- Of course.
- Great.
It's embarrassing to dance
by myself.
- I brought friends.
- Where?
- What?
- What friends?
Did you bring dancers?
- Yes.
- She brought dancers.
She came determined.
- Buddies!
- What?
My gosh. Goodness.
(Surprised)
What's that?
(Ha Na's friends shock everyone.)
- They are real parrots.
- What's going on?
(Ha Na's friends, 2 parrots)
Really?
Are they shy?
My friends!
- So Min's nickname is Parrot.
- They are my friends too.
By the way, they are beautiful.
- Ha Na, how old are they?
- Yes?
So this one is Nana.
I think it's five years old.
I adopted Nana.
- You adopted Nana.
- Gguggu is...
- eight months old.
- It sat on your finger.
- They are beautiful.
- That's fascinating.
It went to Ha Na.
Will it come if I put my finger
here? It came to me too.
Hello.
- How interesting.
- That one...
- easily makes friends.
- Don't come. You won't come? Don't.
I think Nana is going to dig out
Suk Jin's earwax.
- He's about to cry.
- My gosh.
- Nana is friendly.
- What's going on?
It's eating your shirt.
- No, he doesn't have a lot of hair.
- Do they bite?
- Suk Jin.
- No.
- It's so loud.
- He doesn't have a lot of hair.
- Suk Jin.
- No.
(Every strand of hair
is so precious to him.)
It's eating lice
from Suk Jin's hair.
It was eating lice.
He should put it on his shoulder.
Jong Kook, try it on Se Chan.
Let's see he'll come to you.
(Is Se Chan a bird?)
Can it talk?
That depends on the species.
They can't talk.
- But they can dance.
- What?
- You'll dance with them?
- Yes.
- Nana can dance.
- Really?
- She can dance.
Let's watch Ha Na's EDM dance
with Nana.
- Let's start with that.
- I need Gguggu.
- It doesn't look like it'll dance.
- Gguggu needs to help us.
That's intriguing. It's so calm.
I've only seen this
on "How Is That Possible?"
I've never seen this in person.
- A dancing parrot.
- Right.
You can do it, right?
Please help me.
- Help me out.
- Let's watch Nana's dance.
- Nana.
(Their eyes are on the parrot.)
What is it?
Look at the wings. They are moving.
What?
- It's dancing.
- The wings are moving.
(Dancing)
- Seriously?
- My gosh.
(What on earth is this?)
- Look at the body roll.
- It's dancing to the rhythm.
It's really dancing.
(It even danced on beat!)
It's coming down.
It's on the stage now.
- Okay.
- It's on the stage.
Nana needs a partner to dance.
(Copying the parrot)
Nana needs a partner.
(Suk Jin is having a blast
with Nana's trick.)
In my opinion,
Nana danced really well.
Right.
(Nana dances better at home.)
It was better than I expected.
- Nana. Gguggu. Thank you.
- Thank you.
That was so much fun.
When they played the EDM track,
I was really surprised to see...
So Min doing
the outdated dance move.
With the EDM music?
(The female warrior
of techno music is summoned.)
That's for techno music.
She did a move for techno music
when they played the EDM music.
All right. Let's wrap up here.
Wait, Ha Na. Did you prepare
another dance performance?
- She prepared a lot.
- I prepared a lot.
Earlier, her pets danced.
Will you dance this time?
Yes, I prepared to dance
to Jong Kook's song.
- My song?
- Which song?
My songs are oldies of old songs.
It's "Black Cat."
- That's an old song.
- I'll show you a snippet.
- All right. Ha Na.
- "Black Cat Nero".
- Dance to "Black Cat Nero."
- I'll show you a snippet.
I feel shy now.
(As soon as the intro begins,
she bounces like a cat.)
Is this how you dance to the song?
- That's correct.
- Is this how it goes?
- Just like that.
- She's got swagger.
- Yes.
- Is this it?
She should come to your concert.
- She's a cat.
- That move.
She should come to your concert.
(Let's go back to the 90s!)
- In 1, 2.
- Go.
(She transforms into a powerful cat
from a gentle cat.)
What? What was that all of a sudden?
(Fluttering away her pink jacket)
- She's amazing.
- Is that the right move?
That's right.
That's one of the moves.
That's the dance for the bridge.
(She finishes
with a cute kitty act.)
- Ha Na.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry to ask you this,
but what was the last move?
- I didn't memorize that part.
- I see.
- Is that why?
- I felt shy.
But she works hard.
- Yes.
- She works hard.
The dance moves were really funny.
(It's funny?)
Funny? Did you say it's funny?
- Why are you leading the show?
- Jong Kook's life...
- is in that song.
- No, it's not that.
But it's funny?
Jong Kook, why don't you
demonstrate for us?
- Why are you leading the show?
- Why would I do that?
- Shall we do it together?
To be honest, you didn't even
memorize the routine properly.
I would've done it
if you memorized it properly.
To tell you the truth,
I couldn't make big reactions.
- Well, she worked hard.
- I want to see the original dance.
- She didn't have much time.
- Right.
- We should see the original dance.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Dance for us.
- Do you want me in the back?
- It's been so long.
- Should I join too?
- You should do it too.
- By the way,
- You guys, stand in the back.
when he was active as Turbo,
he didn't dance zealously.
Right. By the way, both of them...
- rapped at my concerts.
- Really?
- So he can...
- I'm the first Kim Jung Nam.
- He's the second Kim Jung Nam.
- Right.
I can even do Mikey's part.
(He can do Mikey's part.)
- Haha is Jong Kook's first doll.
- Right.
- He's the 2nd doll.
- I'm the 2nd one.
- Kwang Soo is a temporary one.
- It goes like this.
- Do we just repeat this?
- He threw Kwang Soo out.
All right. Play the music.
- My gosh.
- Great.
(Dancing in sync)
- They look cute.
- Don't you dare...
- go in front of Jong Kook.
- You should join them.
Ha Na. Why did you go
in front of him?
(At a glance,
it looks like Turbo has united.)
- Stand behind Jong Kook.
- You're doing great.
- Make Jong Kook stand out.
All right.
(It's as if Turbo is back.)
(I can't believe
I'm seeing this in person.)
- That's so cool.
- Right. That was the move.
This move.
Gosh, they are so in sync.
This is the part.
(This is the part for Jung Nams.)
- Go.
- It's war.
(As soon as he says, "go,"
they dance intensely.)
Great job. Nice.
- Great.
- You're too young for it
(Greatly satisfied)
- Cut it. That's enough.
- Nice.
- That's it.
- Great job.
Great job!
- You know what?
- I knew it.
- You are my dolls.
- Jong Kook.
- My dolls.
- Dolls.
I felt so bad for them.
- Why? I do it because I want to.
- Two of them did the same part.
Goodness.
(A tear-jerking scene
of sharing the same part)
After the intro,
Jong Kook was resting in the back.
I rest up here and get ready.
- I catch my breath.
- Right.
Thanks to Ha Na,
- Jong Kook performed.
- Right.
- I suddenly danced to an old song.
- Right. All of a sudden.
If this is all you can do,
don't say that you prepared
a dance performance.
(Don't say that you prepared
a dance performance.)
- It didn't deserve three stars.
- You know this wasn't...
There were three stars next to it.
- It didn't deserve three stars.
- Right.
I'm not sure if you know this,
but we wrapped up the mess
you created.
- We wrapped it up.
- We cleaned it up.
- We did all the finishing touches.
- Okay.
- You guys are brutal.
- It was somewhat lacking.
I'll explain the rules now.
Today's race is called
Empty House: Oh, My Thieves.
You are nine thieves who are eyeing
the valuables in a mansion.
(They are 9 thieves
after valuables.)
We are thieves?
There will be three per team.
The mansion owner will go out
from 3 p.m. to 5 p.m.
There's the mansion owner.
You must steal valuables
when the mansion is empty.
The team with the most money
will win and receive a prize.
And the losing
team will face a penalty.
However, in the mansion,
there is the Tear of Yondu necklace.
It costs 30 million dollars...
which is more expensive
than all the valuables combined.
- Tear of Yondu?
Tear of Yondu?
- Tear of Yondu. That's her.
- There's another one here.
I can cry as much as you want me to.
Obtaining the gem will guarantee
a victory for your team.
Please look for it thoroughly.
The team of three thieves
consists of...
a firearms expert, hacker,
and appraiser.
A firearms expert
who will be the captain...
will get a water gun that allows
them to eliminate a member.
And an appraiser will get a tool
that distinguishes valuables...
between expensive and cheap ones.
And for hackers,
it's advantageous
to select the smartest member.
I'm probably a hacker.
Some of you can't be.
Before you start,
you'll select your teams first.
We appointed the captain
of each team.
Captain Yoo Jae Suk.
Captain Kim Jong Kook.
And Captain Haha.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
- but shouldn't it be Suk Jin?
- What about Suk Jin?
One of them should be Suk Jin.
(He was defeated mysteriously.)
- Aren't you being too cruel?
- By the way...
- He was waiting for his name.
- Listen.
As soon as
he talked about captains...
I was trying hard
to keep a straight face.
His face turned dark.
- You should let him be a captain.
- My gosh, seriously.
Gosh, this is so weird.
Team Member Ji, join me.
Join me.
(Since you're smart, be a hacker.)
The three of you will play
rock-paper-scissors.
The winner will get to choose
their members first.
Really?
Will we play rock-paper-scissors?
- Play it and pick one member.
- Let's do it.
- I'm a hacker.
- We should step back.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Suk gets to choose first.)
- Okay!
- What are you talking about?
Come on, Kwang Soo.
Suk Jin is the smartest one.
- Hold on. Do I choose a hacker?
- Yes.
- Pick a smart member.
- Class president in sixth grade.
I was the class president
in the 7th grade...
and vice president in the 8th grade.
- Go back to your spot.
- Hey.
(Listing her achievements
to be a hacker doesn't work.)
Can't you tell just
by looking at me?
Right. I can see that you're old.
(He's not a hacker. He's just old.)
- It wasn't "aged." He said "old."
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin, it's your face.
- You look very tired.
My gosh, you punk.
I'm good at the acrostic poems.
- You're good at acrostic poems?
- Yes.
- You must be smart for that.
- Give it a try.
- Hold on.
You keep starting things,
but you can't finish them.
- Do we have to finish this too?
- No.
- Stop making us clean up your mess.
- Where are you going?
- Hold on.
Don't make a mess here.
I shouldn't have asked her to do it.
Why did you say that?
- Why did you do that?
- Goodness.
- She likes to show off.
- My goodness.
- Will she do it with her parrots?
- For acrostic poems?
- She should...
- Will the parrots recite the poems?
(The more enthusiastic she gets,
the more anxious they are.)
Her poem must be really good.
- She's coming.
- Here she comes.
- She's coming?
- Where did she go?
Where did she go to prepare
for her acrostic poem?
- What did you do?
- What was that?
- Where did you go?
- Did you go to the bathroom?
I prepared acrostic poems
for all eight of you.
- Eight poems?
- I know I can't...
We don't have that much time.
- I only brought the best one.
- That's great.
- Whose name will you use?
- So Min's.
- So Min's name.
- My name is hard to do a poem with.
- You should do one with her name.
- First line.
I came here by myself.
- Second line.
- So Min, please help me a lot.
Third line.
When it comes to embarrassing acts,
we should do them together!
(Raising her hands high)
(In fact, everyone did join
her embarrassing moment.)
We can't even make this work.
- Don't you get this?
- No, we get it.
- My gosh.
- So Min.
- She went to the restroom.
- She wet her armpits.
- She looked in the mirror.
- She did this with the water.
- She put water on her armpits
- Come on.
- Right now...
My gosh.
So Min's armpits.
- She brought the incident back.
- The water park.
- She reminded us.
- It's not that.
Am I that famous?
Hey, that meme went viral.
- By the way,
- This...
- I...
- So Min and her armpits.
I went there to splash water on me,
But I was already sweating.
- There's no need for water?
- You were already sweating?
You didn't have to tell us that.
All right. Ha Na.
- I'll choose Ha Na.
- Okay.
- Ha Na.
- She's amazing.
How could I not choose her?
I chose her for her enthusiasm.
- Are we going in order?
- Yes.
I'll choose So Min
who will publish a book soon.
Ji Hyo!
- I'll choose my doll.
- Kwang Soo.
(Selection of Teams)
We'll distribute the tool
to each team.
- The pen is for the appraiser.
- The pen?
- This doesn't suit me.
- Is that your role?
- Yes, that's my role.
- My gosh.
- That's yours, Jong Kook.
- Use the light on the pen.
You'll see what's written.
(Scribbling something)
- Shine it.
- Write it with the pen first.
(Laughing)
- She's driving me crazy.
- What is it?
What?
Why?
"Se Chan."
- She drew a heart and signed it.
- "From So Min."
(Only the appraiser
can read the love letter.)
- So Min got a good team today.
- Exactly.
- Why do you keep...
- My gosh.
- following me around lately?
- Right.
(The mission tools are provided.)
- What is that?
- What is it?
- There are three cars.
- That's going to be really cold.
- What is this?
- It'll be really cold.
- Which one?
- I want to ride that one.
(A luxurious sedan
with the best ride quality)
No, I don't want that one.
It'll be cold.
It's a convertible.
Gosh, it'll be freezing.
- In this weather?
- It will be so cold.
But riding a convertible now...
- It's too cold.
- doesn't sound good.
- Isn't that a penalty?
- A convertible...
I don't like it even when it's sunny
because of the micro-dust.
I like convertibles.
You don't know the address
of the mansion you need to rob.
You need to complete missions...
to obtain the address and passcode
of the mansion,
locations of surveillance cameras,
and the patrol schedule.
Arriving at the mansion quickly
will be advantageous.
The mansion will open
from 3 p.m. to 5 p.m.
(It will stay open
only for 2 hours.)
You have three options
for transportation to get there.
Team Ocean's will drive...
- the luxurious sedan.
- Team Ocean's.
Team Home Alone will drive
the van.
Team Home Alone.
Team Les Miserables will put on
a wig and ride the convertible.
- These are the teams.
- Let's avoid that one.
Don't we look like the thieves
in "Home Alone"?
- It's "Home Alone."
- Right?
It totally suits you.
The hat helps too.
- Let's go for that one.
- It's on fire.
(The hat and his facial expression
look exactly the same.)
- Macaulay Culkin.
- You're wearing the same hat.
- You have to scream like this.
- This?
He has the same hat.
Only 1 of the 3 silver trays
has cherries from Chile.
The team that picks the tray
with the cherries from Chile wins.
The winning team will assign
the cars to all of the teams.
The winning team will decide.
Hey, riding that car is a penalty.
- I want to ride the sedan.
- I want this one.
I don't care which car I get
as long as it's not the last one.
Discuss among yourselves
to pick a tray.
Ha Na, you should choose.
When I observed Ha Na,
I could tell she gets unlucky too.
Let me feel the energy of cherries.
(She makes a fuss
when she can't get the job done.)
- She's enthusiastic.
- Indeed.
She's enthusiastic.
I need enough airtime for myself.
- What is it? Did you decide?
- I have a good feeling about that.
- Do it. Get whatever you want.
- Open it.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(The cherries will be
on only one of the trays.)
(What is on the tray Ha Na chose?)
(Full of cherries)
That was amazing.
- How did you know that?
- That was amazing.
You called it.
(Ease your disappointment
with sweet cherries.)
Try it.
- Okay.
- Cherries are good in snowy winter.
(Sweet and sour cherries
eaten in a warm room during winter)
- These are good.
- Yes.
These are great.
(And...)
- I like cherries.
- Me too.
(Suk Jin is eating cherries
in a unique way.)
(Eating it in one go)
I heard your teeth crack.
Are you okay?
(Get your dental implants
with cherries.)
- I heard a crack.
- I think it hit your tooth.
- No.
- What's wrong?
You know what?
Everything is going my way
this year.
He uses up his luck
on useless things.
He uses it on the bottle flip.
You're right. You have a boint.
I have a "boint"?
(You have a boint.)
- "Boint"?
He needs to "cherry" up, you know.
(He needs to "cherry" up, you know.)
He needs to "cherry" up.
(Suk Jin,
please cherry up this year.)
- Can we start?
- This is fun.
- Which team will get that car?
- You must decide.
- You can choose however you want.
- Let us play rock-paper-scissors.
To make it entertaining,
they should...
- They're Team Les Miserables.
- He can drive.
So they are Team Les Miserables.
- Even if we make them drive it...
- Jae Suk, they can be newlyweds.
- Right.
- Jong Kook won't say a thing.
Jong Kook can drive the car.
And they can sit in the back.
- Right.
- That will be so fun.
- Take that off.
- I can't.
- Take it off.
- I can't give it up.
- The wig looks great on you.
- You look beautiful.
- Take it off.
- I can't give it up.
- Jae Suk won't even listen.
- We can change his mind.
- Kwang Ja will take it.
- It's settled.
- Which team gets the convertible?
We'll take the Maserati.
I'd rather see Kwang Soo
with the wig than Jong Kook.
- We'll have a comfortable ride.
- We'll take...
I'll give you the address
of each spot.
- Se Chan.
- Hello.
- Honey, let's go.
- Okay.
- What's Jong Kook's role? Our son?
- Yes.
- My son.
- Son?
My son.
- I have a great son.
- You raised a nice son.
- He's reliable.
- I gave birth to a great son.
How did I give birth
to a handsome son with you?
You have a great son.
This is the mission card.
There are three places.
Even if we go to one of these,
we need to know the passcode.
Then we should go here first.
We need to know
the passcode first.
Don't you think everyone will go...
- to this spot?
- I'm not sure.
It's snowing a lot today.
This is pricking my head.
- Darn it.
- It's so prickly.
It's pricking my head.
It keeps going into my mouth.
This is so irritating. It is!
Let's turn on the heater.
(Is this the heater?)
- Where's the heater?
- You opened the trunk.
You opened the trunk.
How do I close it?
Please close the trunk.
Let me punch in the address.
- I'm on the wrong team.
- Hey, we just have to win.
- Yongmun...
- Yangpyeong-gu.
Everyone's staring at us.
- I saw Yongmun just now.
- Really?
(They're inserting the address.)
You can't even use
the navigation properly.
Then you try it. This isn't easy.
- Hold on.
- Let's go there.
- It's snowing a lot.
- Let's just go there.
(They set out in a convertible,
wearing wigs while it's snowing.)
Let's go.
(They do look cool.)
(I got a new car)
Everyone's staring at us.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- This is so embarrassing.
My hair's a mess.
- This wig is...
- Haha.
It's so freezing!
(It just happened to snow today.)
This car is fast.
- Haha.
The faster you drive,
the messier Kwang Soo's hair gets!
It's so fast, though.
- Haha!
- I can't hear you.
Okay, I'll slow down.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
(Laughing)
My goodness.
Let's eliminate
Jae Suk's team first.
- Of course.
- Do you have the water gun?
Okay!
See? He can't hear me.
He's making no sense.
He can't hear a thing.
Let's not talk.
I'm freezing.
(Team Jong Kook is heading
to get the passcode and address.)
Anyway, we should go
to the mansion and...
Aren't we supposed to steal
as much as possible?
You're right.
This mission is perfect
for Kwang Soo.
It suits Se Chan too.
- Am I a petty thief?
- Yes.
I'm awful at stealing.
I get caught...
- because I can't lie.
- You stole my heart, didn't you?
I never did.
- Are you sure you didn't offer it?
- She offered it?
- I think you offered it.
- Is it out on the market?
No.
- We're here.
- Are we?
- Are you sure? Let's go inside.
- Yes.
Are we the only ones here?
I think so.
This would be a great place
to come and relax.
Wouldn't it be great
to spend a night here?
- It'd be wonderful.
- It'd be great.
- Let's come here again.
- Se Chan.
Where?
- Us three should come here.
- And spend the night?
Sure, as long as
he doesn't leave midway.
- You better not leave.
- Hey.
- You better not.
- Why would you say that?
Just in case.
I don't want him to disappear.
I'm done. This is hurting my pride.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I'm done.
- I was only joking.
- Get out.
- I think this is it.
- It's so pretty.
(This is the mission spot
for the address and passcode.)
I think we'll be playing a game.
If you win this mission,
you'll get the mansion's address...
- and its passcode.
- Okay.
The mission is called
Strawberry, St-raw-berry.
- "Strawberry, St-raw-berry"?
This is a popular game these days.
Really?
(1 beat, you say strawberry.
2 beats, you say st-raw-berry.)
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(1 beat, you say strawberry.
2 beats, you say st-raw-berry.)
- Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(If they reach the 8th beat,
they succeed.)
- What is this?
- What?
- St-raw-berry counts as two beats.
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- This is a famous game?
- This is the third beat.
- Strawberry
- Darn it.
- We came first.
(Team Jae Suk arrives.)
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- This is really hard.
- How do you do the eighth beat?
- Do you know this game?
- St-raw-berry
- Do you know this?
No, this is my first time.
- Watch us.
- Let's begin.
Ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
- Straw-berry
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- It's st-raw-berry.
- St-raw-berry.
Straw-berry
(Straw-berry)
Do you have to be that strict?
- Get out.
- Get out!
- Give us one more chance.
- St-raw-berry
- Goodness.
- Hold on.
You should give us
at least three tries.
- Do we get 3 tries?
- Give us 3 tries.
- Gosh.
- We just sat down.
- Gosh, this is frustrating.
- We'll start once again.
- We say straw-berry in my area.
- Wake up.
All right.
- Ready, set, go.
- Let's go.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry and st-raw-berry
Hold on.
(Strawberry and st-raw-berry)
(He gets it wrong.)
Hold on.
- Get out.
- Hold on.
Please leave, Se Chan's girlfriend.
- Explain the rules.
- Please leave.
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- Say it again. And then she says...
- Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
Let's practice.
- I like strawberries
(1 beat: strawberry
2 beats: st-raw-berry)
- Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
Strawberry and st-raw-berry
- The beat was wrong.
- What was that?
(He misses a clap.)
- The beat was wrong.
- What was that?
- What was I supposed to do?
- Show us.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Right.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- No. It's strawberry, st-raw-berry.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Say it while you clap.)
Look. Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Let's start.
- Strawberry
- You go first.
- No, you should go first.
- Let's change. I'll go first.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Hey!
(He gets it wrong again.)
- Goodness.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Get out.
- Give us one more chance.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- That's it.
- Let's start.
- Let's change seats.
You two should change seats.
- All right. Ready, set, go.
- Is this right?
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(He finally gets it right.)
- Is it my turn?
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Suk Jin is infuriated.)
- Aren't we going this way?
- Get out.
(Team Jae Suk fails.)
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Let's change seats.
So Min will go first.
Okay. We can do it.
- Jong Kook will come next.
- All right.
- We can do this.
- Get ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry... What is it?
(He's supposed to say
strawberry, st-raw-berry.)
- What is it?
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Get out.
- It's not st-raw-berry?
- No.
- Is he stupid or what?
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- All right.
- I'm sorry,
- but So Min.
- So Min.
Are you the class president
or something?
Why are you so hyper?
(She looked very excited.)
(She stood up.)
(She seemed like
a friendly class president.)
Guys, I'm the brain of our group.
I'm the hacker.
She's so confident.
- St-raw-berry, strawberry
- Jae Suk will sit in the middle.
- Ha Na will be the last one.
- Hold on.
This isn't good.
- Ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(He's supposed to say
st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry.)
- St-raw-berry
- Get out.
- Give us 1 more chance.
- We'll give you 2 more.
St-raw-berry
You have two tries.
Right?
- Ready, set, go.
- What's the seventh beat?
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
- St-raw-berry
- Come on.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Okay!
What's the seating arrangement
this time?
- Why do we have to change seats?
- Jong Kook will start first.
- What's wrong with you?
- Hey.
He keeps changing our seats,
and it's confusing me.
Is this right?
Get ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, straw-berry
- St-raw-berry
- You can't say straw-berry.
- Can't you just let him be?
That's how they say it in my area!
Can't you just turn a blind eye?
They're the same.
Get out.
- Straw-berry, straw-berry
- Get out.
- Isn't this right?
If it wasn't for Se Chan...
I'm so distracted
by the pronunciation.
It's so confusing.
- I like strawberries
(This team has yet
to understand the game.)
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Straw-berry
(Straw-berry)
(He mimics Se Chan.)
That's not right.
- It's st-raw-berry.
- Isn't that what he said?
Is that what I said?
Why can't you do it properly?
- I like strawberries
- You're done!
(Let's hurry up and start.)
You're done!
- You're done. Don't be sly.
- Get out.
- It's our turn.
- Wait.
- Come on, Suk Jin.
- Hold on.
- Did I really say that?
- It's st-raw-berry.
- That's what I said.
- St-raw-berry
Get ready, set, go.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,
strawberry
(He finally gets it right.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,
st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(It's the final 8th beat now.)
(He just needs to say
st-raw-berry 4 times.)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,
st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
We did it!
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,
st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(Team Jong Kook succeeds.)
I think he mispronounced it.
- No, he didn't.
- I think he did.
- I think he mispronounced it.
- No, I didn't.
- We're good.
- We're pretty good.
- Good work.
- Great job.
- I think he mispronounced it.
- Se Chan did it.
- I did it.
- I thought it'd never end.
Since you've succeeded,
we'll give you the address...
and the hint for the passcode.
- Okay.
You must read this outside.
- All right.
- You must go outside first.
- Let's pack.
- All right.
- St-raw-berry
I have a feeling
they won't end soon.
- You're wrong.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
During the last part,
shout, "Lee Man Ki!"
Be quiet.
- Please do that.
- Shut it and leave.
Here we go.
I'm curious about the hint.
Let's see.
(They read the hint.)
The passcode is...
- It's 200202.
- 200202.
- 200 and 202.
- 200202. I get it.
We should retrieve all the hints
and then head to the house, right?
Right.
Haha, to the right.
- The right?
- Yes, make a right.
- Are you looking at the map?
- Make a right.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
(Kwang Soo checks the map
on Ji Hyo's phone.)
Gosh, it's freezing!
- What's this?
- Let me see.
I lowered the map and...
(He's lost for words.)
- What is it?
- The names of the months...
- are in English.
- How is that important?
(The names of the months
are in English.)
(The screen is filled
with basic English words.)
We need to check the map.
- Have you been studying?
- Of course not.
- Are you studying English?
- You've been studying.
This is for real.
There's no doubt about it.
(This is for real.)
- I just put them on the screen.
- You're trying hard.
Good job.
November and December...
I'm always confused
by those two as well.
It's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
- Exactly. You're just studying.
- Haha, make a right over there.
- It's never too late to study.
- Of course.
- Is this the place?
- I'm inspired, Ji Hyo.
Stop talking about it!
- Over here?
- On our way...
Hold on. Make a left.
What's the fourth month of the year?
Se Chan, do you want some water?
- Sounds good.
- Water?
(Sweet and loving)
Here you go.
- Are you done?
- Thanks.
- You have the lid.
- Right.
It's nice to have
So Min take care of me.
Just so you know,
it's better to have...
a talkative wife or a girlfriend.
- They respond well.
- You'll get bored.
I like women who respond well
and laugh a lot.
- Someone who responds well?
- Yes.
No way! Really?
(She gives him the top 3 responses.)
(Yes, that's what
I'm talking about.)
(Exploding with exclamations)
Gosh, look at you
steering the wheel.
That's so cool.
I've never seen anyone
who does it with two hands.
(He must be a beginner!)
Gosh, look at his gums.
Look.
- His gums?
- No way.
It'll be fun to go
on a trip with So Min.
- Being talkative is better.
- Of course.
It's the best.
I love it too.
Don't you prefer someone
like Park Na Rae?
Na Rae isn't exactly my type.
What about Do Yeon?
Yes, Do Yeon's amazing.
Do Yeon's great.
Is it me or Do Yeon?
(The punch comes out of nowhere.)
(He's suddenly forced
to choose his type.)
(Is it the talkative So Min
or the funny Do Yeon?)
Unbelievable. Of course, it's you.
(Of course, it's you.)
Must I even say it?
(Jeon So Min is my type.)
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
This will air on TV, you know.
She says it'll air on TV.
- But...
- It'll be written in an article.
- I'm sure of it.
- No way.
I wish we'd get there soon.
Oh, we're here.
- Are we? That was are.
- Right.
(Team Jong Kook arrives at
the surveillance camera mission.)
(If they complete the mission,
they will be given a hint...)
(regarding the locations
of the surveillance cameras.)
- What's that?
- I'm nervous for some reason.
I see the ropes. Are we supposed
to tie up or drag someone?
Let me inform you of the rules.
This is to find out the locations
of the surveillance cameras.
Endure the Weight of the Paper.
- The weight of the paper?
- Its weight?
One person will have a piece
of paper laid on his or her head.
You will then compete
in a four-legged race.
Your goal is to place the paper
in the basket...
within 60 seconds.
(Those who complete the mission
will be given hints...)
(regarding the locations
of the surveillance cameras.)
What if we made his hair pointy...
- and stick the paper there.
- Should I?
No, you're adorable enough.
- I'll flatten it then.
- He's cute.
Let's make it flat
and put the paper on it.
From what I can tell,
they're the couple in love.
(From what I can tell,
they're the couple in love.)
(They're the true couple
on this team.)
No matter how I think about it...
It's called bromance!
(Glaring)
They seem inseparable.
- So Min, please don't sulk.
- He's right.
- Come on.
- This way.
Let's get on with the game.
(The three in a love triangle
will give the game a shot.)
Wait, this is too easy.
- Big strides.
- Don't turn your head.
- Gosh.
- Why did you turn your head?
- I get it now.
- Good.
- Do something funny.
- We can do it.
- It wasn't even funny.
- Exactly.
It wasn't funny.
We should do better.
Are you failing on purpose
just to keep holding my hand?
(Is that why he's been failing?)
- Wait...
- It sounds like it.
- Is his palm sweaty?
- You see...
It is sweaty, and he's holding
my hand really tight.
I'm startled.
- I didn't lock fingers though.
- Stick your tummy out.
(Stick your tummy out.)
Jong Kook, must you do that?
(The two men start
acting like a couple again.)
(Frowning)
Something's definitely
going on between them.
(They lead a dangerous relationship
with him having a fake girlfriend.)
- So Min.
- Okay, we're ready.
(After numerous attempts,
they change the courier.)
- All right. Let's go.
- It's the magnet lady.
(The magnet lady returns.)
Gosh.
- Let's go.
- All right.
We can do this. It won't fly off.
- Let's go.
- This won't fall off me.
We can even walk at a fast pace
to make sure it won't fall off me.
- Sure.
- It won't come off.
It won't come off.
- She's the magnet lady!
- It won't come off.
Here comes the magnet lady.
Okay, we're almost there.
Magnet lady, do your thing.
- Gently...
- Stick your head in there.
- We did it!
- Nice!
- Magnet lady.
- You succeeded in the mission.
- Hold on.
- Okay, we did it. It was fun.
- It's fine.
- Here you go. It's a hint.
- What's this?
- You may read it here.
(No one's around,
so you may read it here.)
In sub-basement level 1,
there are two near the stairs...
(Locations of Surveillance Cameras)
This doesn't seem easy.
We should go down...
That's a lot of cameras.
- There are three.
- Right.
Inside Room 1...
We need to turn
all three of them off first.
Where exactly are they?
- Right.
- There are a lot.
(They have 5 seconds
to turn each of them off.)
Before 3 p.m.?
- We're running out of time.
- Oh, dear.
Unbelievable.
(What game will they play here?)
What are these for?
- Here are the rules.
- Sure.
What are we supposed to do?
The patrol schedule is
what you'll obtain if you succeed.
The game is called Clap Your Hands.
You will choose two members
to compete.
The two will put on...
tights with a glove attached to it
on their head...
and move toward each other
while making the tights swirl.
You have 100 seconds
to make the gloves...
clap each other three times.
(What hint will be provided
if they succeed?)
(They will be given
the patrol schedule...)
(which contains the time
and location for the patrol guards.)
(It will help them stay clear
of the patrol guards!)
Let's get going.
All right, here we go.
All right.
(Park Ha Na and Ji Suk Jin,)
(most likely)
Suk Jin, you should go down.
Go down. Get closer.
Wait, this is too low.
(Oh, no!)
(The tights give her a nose lift.)
You were wearing it too low.
It wasn't spinning well.
It was on your forehead.
(Laughing)
Ha Na.
(She gets a facelift too.)
Try to do better.
(Lifting)
You have to do better.
You don't have time for that.
(Dumbfounded)
Seriously.
What are you doing?
(Let's take a photo together.)
We don't have time for this.
(The most hilarious shot
of the first half of 2020)
I can't see anything.
Ha Na, move.
Suk Jin and I will play.
(As soon as they begin,)
(they manage to clap.)
- There you go.
- You clapped.
(The 2nd clap)
- Okay.
- Two.
(The 3rd clap)
- We're done.
- You clapped again.
(They accomplish the mission
so fast.)
Since you've completed the mission,
- I'll give you the patrol schedule.
- Thank you.
What's this?
(The patrol time and location
are revealed.)
(Patrol Schedule)
(Meeting Room 1 and 2,
Hacker's Room 2,)
(and Dining Room at 3:30 p.m.)
(Hacker's Room 1 and Reception Room
on the 1st floor,)
(Hacker's Room 3 and Meeting Room 3
on the 2nd floor at 4:30 p.m.)
(1st Floor, 2nd Floor)
(In order not to be eliminated,)
(they shouldn't be seen
by the patrol guards.)
We've been doing well so far.
- Let's succeed at once.
- Okay.
I'll go first.
You say, "st-raw-berry."
I say, "st-raw-berry, strawberry,"
right?
- Okay.
- Let's start.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, strawberry
(She ignores the beat.)
(Loss for words)
You can continue until you succeed.
- The first one is "strawberry."
- Do you get it?
- The third one is...
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- You're pronouncing it wrong.
- St-raw-berry
It seems like...
Ji Hyo doesn't know the beat.
Do you?
She's smart, but she has
no sense of rhythm.
That's why.
- Please understand her.
- Strawberry
- No.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Can we just give up?
- Hold on.
- We know the rules now.
It's not that she doesn't know.
Should we give it a try?
Let's try.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Say "strawberry"
when you clap your hands.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- St-raw-berry
- Okay.
- Repeat after me.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Pronounce it properly.
Start saying, "st-raw-berry,"
when you point to the right.
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- There you go.
- Okay.
- Pronounce it right.
Let's give it a try.
If we fail, we can try again.
Ready, start.
- I like strawberries
- Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
(She misses the beat again.)
St-raw-berry
(Is this wrong?)
- I said it.
- You pronounced it wrong.
- St-raw-berry
- And the rhythm...
How should I explain it?
- It's hard to explain.
- Strawberry
St-raw-berry
- I get it now.
- Okay.
Switch seats first.
We'll start with the person
on the far right.
Ji Hyo and Haha,
please switch seats.
- You say...
- You'll go first.
Strawberry.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Okay.
- Let's start.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Haha.
(Even Haha misses the beat.)
- What did I do?
- Hold on.
- I think it's the stool's fault.
- What's wrong?
It's the stool's fault.
- Did I do it wrong?
- You were doing so well.
Hold on.
- The first one was correct, right?
- I'll sit here.
Okay, let's try. This is strange.
- Is it "Strawberry, st-raw-berry"?
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Ready, start.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
(He was late.)
(Shocked)
What's wrong with me?
(Embarrassed)
Do we have to do this?
- Do we have to get it?
- Isn't this correct?
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Okay, I get it perfectly now.
We can't fall behind
because of this stupid game.
(From the captain to the hacker,
everything is a mess.)
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Ready, start.
- I like strawberries
- Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
(They finally got
the second one right.)
(What about Kwang Soo?)
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(It's completely off the beat.)
(Seriously...)
It's difficult to start right away.
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Hacker Song has been struggling
for 20 minutes.)
And then right away...
I say, "St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,"
when I pat my lap.
If I don't understand,
please explain.
How many times do I have to explain?
- You failed too.
- Strawberry
It's "Strawberry, st-raw-berry."
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry. Okay.
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- Ready, start.
- Let's slow down a bit.
- I like strawberries
Strawberry
St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(It's Ji Hyo's turn again.)
(She needs to say,
"St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry.")
St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry
(Correct)
St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry,
strawberry
(Haha even gets
the fifth one right.)
St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry
Strawberry, strawberry
Hey!
St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry,
strawberry, strawberry
(You're the problem here!)
- St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Say "st-raw-berry" three times.
- She's right.
- St-raw-berry, St-raw-berry
(The three of them
work it out together.)
No.
Okay.
Kwang Soo, switch seats with me.
Kwang Soo will do
the first one then.
We just have to repeat it
over and over again.
Ready, start.
Don't you feel embarrassed?
Don't you?
- Very much.
- Should we go out and come back in?
- Let's pretend we just got here.
- Should we...
pretend we just got here?
I'm so embarrassed.
We'll do it again.
Please edit out the first part.
We look so stupid.
- You can go out and come back in.
- Okay.
What's wrong with us?
We were doing so well.
Why is this so hard?
This is so embarrassing.
We're so bad.
We got here first.
- Is no one else here?
(They hurry in.)
- We got here first.
- I smell coffee.
It smells so nice.
- I'll sit here.
I don't know what game
we'll be playing.
(They all sit down where they want.)
- Let's get started right away.
- Okay.
We haven't even heard
about the rules yet.
- Let's just go with our gut.
- Let's go with our feelings.
- We're entertainers.
- Okay.
We've been doing so well today.
- We have 10 years of experience.
- Let's give it a try.
- I don't even know what game it is.
- Do you know the intro?
- Pardon?
Is it, "I like strawberries"?
- Not "st-raw-berries"?
- I have a feeling.
- Should we try it?
- It has a nice ring to it.
- Okay.
- It sounds so nice.
Let's try. 1, 2, start.
- I like strawberries
- Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(Ji Hyo misses the beat again.)
(Let's go out again.)
Let's pretend you arrive late.
I'll stay here.
You arrive late.
(1 minute later)
- What's this place?
- It looks cozy here.
Is no one else here?
It's nice and warm in here.
I see a xylophone.
- It must be something simple.
- This mission is...
I like strawberries
(They waste no time.)
- Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(They even get
the fourth one right.)
(Following Haha,
Ji Hyo gets it right too.)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,
st-raw berry, strawberry
It's, "strawberry, st-raw-berry."
We were almost there.
- What's this place?
- Oh, my.
- We're...
- We're the first ones here.
(Let's slow down.)
Strawberry
You should have said
"st-raw-berry" twice.
- Was it my turn?
- You're on my right.
Was it? I'm sorry.
How could she forget that?
- It's scary.
- I'm...
- It must be a simple game.
- I think so.
- Let's slow down a bit.
- Let's slow down.
We're getting too carried away.
If we play it slowly,
can you speed it up afterward?
(This is it.)
(Slow)
- Strawberry
- St-raw-berry
(The beginning is no problem.)
(Once they slow down,
they manage it pretty well.)
(Ji Hyo gets the sixth one right.)
(After Haha, it's time for Kwang Soo
to finish the game.)
(Will Kwang Soo manage to say
"st-raw-berry" 4 times?)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- Yes!
- We're done!
(They finally succeed.)
This was our first try.
We succeeded at once.
We're on fire today.
- We're geniuses.
- We didn't even know the rules,
- and we succeeded at once.
- We're so smart.
- We only just got here.
- Is this how you play it?
- Gosh, this is crazy.
- I'm so thrilled.
(The three brains win
the address and passcode.)
It's 3 p.m. The mansion is empty.
Anyway, we have to get there first
to steal expensive stuff.
- I know.
- Hey.
Let's hurry up.
We have to get there first
to steal good stuff.
The team that steals
good stuff first wins.
(It's just past 3 p.m.
Who will enter the mansion first?)
(Team Jae Suk arrives first.)
All right. Let's go.
Thank you.
We need to get there first
to get the good stuff.
(It seems like we've arrived first.)
Hey.
- 252...
(The doors open.)
There you go.
(This is the secret mansion
that will be broken into today.)
(The thieves can steal things
from the mansion...)
(between 3 p.m. and 5 p.m.)
(They should steal valuables...)
(and move them to their tents.)
(The team
with the highest total value wins.)
(Name: Tear of Yondu,
Price: 30 million dollars)
(Bulletproof vest,
one-time protection from water guns)
(There is only one bulletproof vest,
and it's hidden.)
(If they get caught on surveillance
cameras for more than 5 seconds,)
(the patrol guards will arrive.)
(Once they get caught
by the patrol guards, they're out.)
Please fill your water gun
with the water provided.
Your water gun can eliminate
only one person.
Each item has a tag on it,
which will tell you its price.
Suk Jin, come here!
- Okay.
- We need an appraisal.
Guys, get out.
Can we go in?
Someone already broke in.
Let's go in.
Shouldn't we do something
about the surveillance cameras?
What's this?
I turned it off.
(A surveillance camera
gets turned off.)
(They begin to turn off
the surveillance cameras.)
(You are out if you are
on the camera for over 5 seconds.)
(Thus, it's easier if you turn off
the surveillance cameras.)
Okay. I turned it off.
Isn't this a surveillance camera?
- It is.
- Look for them carefully.
(Jae Suk's team finds
a surveillance camera by chance.)
- Turn it off.
- Don't get caught on camera.
Let's turn it off.
(He succeeds to turn it off
before 5 seconds pass.)
What? You turned it on just now.
I turned it off.
The light is at "Off."
Isn't this how you turn it off?
(He turns on
the surveillance camera.)
You turned it on.
For goodness' sake.
Oh, it should be at "Off."
- The light is at "Off."
- You don't know the basics.
There are
so many surveillance cameras.
- That's a surveillance camera.
- That's right.
(What?)
(He turns it back on.)
(He is proud because he thinks
he turned it off.)
Why is the light at "On"?
- Did I turn it off?
- The light should be at "Off."
I see.
I can't believe you.
What is wrong with you?
(Meanwhile, Se Chan)
How much is this? 3,000 dollars?
3,000 dollars.
(Let me steal it.)
(So Min was walking around
aimlessly.)
This could be expensive.
It could be a good bicycle.
All right.
(She rides the bicycle to the tent.)
Be careful.
(Jong Kook's team has stolen
5,000 dollars' worth of items.)
What is this?
(At that moment)
(A box with an R mark?)
(What's inside the box
Kwang Soo stumbled upon?)
It's a bulletproof vest.
(A bulletproof vest?)
(This is incredible!)
This is incredible.
(Kwang Soo can nullify
1 water gun attack.)
Where is Haha?
Haha? Your teammate.
- He is downstairs.
- Downstairs?
Why are you wearing a vest?
- Oh, it's a bulletproof vest.
- That's right.
Where did you get it?
What a coward! You were so scared
of being eliminated...
that you put it on right away.
- Go and sit in prison.
- Sure.
(Jae Suk finds something
on the 2nd floor.)
What? Why is there
a framed photo of me?
(A framed photo of Jae Suk is
in the living room.)
It's a framed photo of you.
I guess it has a price.
Let's check the price.
I don't have anything like this
at my own house.
Let's see how much Yoo Jae Suk is.
It's 10,000 dollars.
(Jae Suk's photo is
10,000 dollars.)
(That's pretty expensive.)
That's incredible.
I will move it to the tent.
(Here comes a 10,000-dollar item.)
I stole a 50,000-dollar item.
Let's check out the next room.
Let's see what's inside.
- How expensive is that?
- Why is there Yu San Seul's CD?
- How much is it?
- 200 dollars.
200 dollars. That's good.
Haha.
- That's my album!
- Haha.
(Haha's legendary debut album
no one has purchased, "The Gang")
- It's 15 dollars.
- For goodness' sake.
- 15 dollars.
- This album is really rare, okay?
This is...
Tear of Yondu?
Where is Tear of Yondu?
- What?
- So Min.
This is the hacker's room.
- What's the hacker's room?
- What?
This is the hacker's room.
(If 2 or more people stay
for over 5 minutes,)
(the alarm will sound
and the patrol will show up.)
(There are 3 hacker's rooms
in the mansion.)
(They might look like
an ordinary study,)
(but they contain...)
(a hint on Tear of Yondu.)
If 2 or more people stay
for over 5 minutes...
- I found it.
- So Min.
- No way.
- What is this room?
There are
no surveillance cameras, right?
(Do you want to know the location
of Tear of Yondu?)
- Haha, lock the door.
- Let's lock the door.
I am a hacker.
- This is a hacker's room.
- I am a hacker.
- If two or more people...
- What is this?
Se Chan, we need to do this.
We need to solve this
(There are a locked laptop
and a piece of paper with a code.)
It's a passcode.
(Will the passcode lead them
to Tear of Yondu?)
We will be fine
if we leave within five minutes.
Let's set a timer.
Alarm watch. Stopwatch.
"Alarm watch"?
Stopwatch. Five minutes.
(The clock is reset
if they leave the room.)
This is "I am."
(He uses
his limited English skills.)
I, M. A, I, M.
(His knowledge runs out.)
I don't get it.
What does "WXY" mean?
A, B, C, D, E, F, G,
H, I, J, K, L, M...
(She thinks for a while.)
(She begins to interrogate
the cameraman.)
What? What did you say?
You saw something, right?
Please tell me what you saw.
(Se Chan joins her.)
Can I come in?
If you come in, the patrol will come
after five minutes.
- I am going in.
- A, B, C, D...
I don't think you should fixate
on the passcode.
Leave before five minutes are up.
What time is it now? Come on.
Check the time.
Five minutes. I set the timer.
What is going on?
- What did you do?
- We didn't do it.
We didn't set the alarm off,
did we?
There are vowels and consonants.
What is going on?
Two or more people have stayed
in a hacker's room...
for over five minutes.
- What?
- The patrol is on its way.
(The patrol is dispatched
because of Ji Hyo and Haha.)
Do we need to hide?
(Is the patrol coming?)
(The patrol enters the mansion.)
I need to hide.
(The cowardly petty offenders
scatter to different places.)
(The siren made them scatter.)
(The patrol makes the rounds
on the 1st floor.)
(They pass by the room
in which Jae Suk is hiding.)
(Nervous)
(A few minutes pass.)
(The patrol leaves
without apprehending anyone.)
(I can go out now, right?)
Hey, So Min.
Jong Kook, I can't solve it.
These books must be here
for a reason.
Maybe the first letters
of the books make out this code.
- A...
- No.
(A deep sigh)
- That's right.
- You know,
I shouldn't have become a hacker.
This is so hard.
The other team's hacker is Ji Hyo,
so we can take our time.
I am not good at deciphering codes.
I, M, A.
- You know,
- What do you see?
these alphabets are in order.
U, V, W, X, Y.
- So...
- Turn them into numbers.
A is one.
(Hush!)
- For goodness' sake.
- What?
(You need to be more careful.)
- It's right.
- Do you want everyone to know?
- For goodness' sake.
- But I figured it out.
- What do you mean?
- A is one.
- Listen to me.
- What number is I?
A, B, C, D, E, F, G,
- H, I. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
- That's not how you solve it.
Here.
Three letters...
would go into these question marks.
- That's right.
- Now,
the ends are A and Y.
I wrote out the alphabet
from A to Z.
These letters are symmetrical.
That's what I am talking about!
- These letters are symmetrical.
- Look.
W, X.
(If you divide all the letters
in half...)
- All of them are symmetrical.
All of them are symmetrical.
We need to find three letters
that are symmetrical.
We did it.
What should I do with this?
Symmetrical letters.
- B.
- B doesn't work.
- C.
- C doesn't work.
- H.
- Look.
- O.
- O works.
- Keep your voice down.
- T.
T works. T.
Hot. H, O, T.
(The answer is "Hot.")
- Hot.
Let's go outside.
(Jae Suk's team
deciphers the code.)
Leave it behind.
Jong Kook, I think I figured it out.
I need to find symmetrical letters.
- H.
- H, O, T.
- Three letters.
- Hot.
Let's try it.
H, O, T.
That's impossible.
("HOT" isn't the password
for the laptop.)
"H, O, T" doesn't work?
(How did this happen?)
But this is the hint.
Hey, Ha Na.
We got "H, O, T,"
but it isn't the password.
That means...
we need to find an object
that says "HOT."
You know what I mean, right?
(Is there an object that says "HOT"
in a hacker's room?)
This is an escape room.
Think of it as an escape room.
(Jae Suk spots something!)
"H, O, T".
(The object that says "HOT" is...)
(a water purifier!)
(He finds "HOT.")
(They study the water purifier.)
Should we take off the sticker?
I'll close the door.
(He secures the room.)
(When they take off
the "HOT" sticker,)
(they find something written.)
(Sand went into my ear,
so I went to the hospital.)
"Ear, sand, meat, and mouth."
What do they mean?
- They are in blue.
- Let's see.
- What could it be?
- "Sand went into my ear,"
- Ear.
- "so I went to the hospital."
(Why are four words
written in blue?)
Haha's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
Police special forces have been
dispatched.
Haha's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
Police special forces have been
dispatched to arrest him.
- Haha?
- Hurry and come out.
Running away won't be any use.
If his position is revealed,
doesn't it mean that he's caught
on a surveillance camera?
Is that what it means?
Is it because he was caught
on surveillance for a long time?
- Don't you think so?
- With the water gun?
He got caught
on the surveillance camera.
He's such a fool.
Why did he get caught?
(Haha is arrested.)
(Haha is out.)
Shouldn't he leave
the water gun with us?
- He should hand it to us.
- Right?
- That's true.
- Kwang Soo.
Can you solve it? I have no idea.
I can't stay here
longer than five minutes.
What's the hint?
(Unlike Ji Hyo
who didn't get "HOT"...)
"Sand went into my ear."
(Jae Suk and Ha Na are working
on step 2.)
Ear, sand, meat, and mouth.
(At that time)
(They hear the cuckoo sound.)
(They obtain the patrol schedule
after clearing the mission.)
(The cuckoo sound indicates
the start of the patrol.)
(Patrol schedule)
(Patrol location at 3:30 p.m.,
Meeting Room 1 and 2...)
(First patrol starts at 3:30 p.m.)
Gosh, they're coming in.
(Suk Jin runs away
to where there is no patrol.)
(Without knowing, Jong Kook hides
based on others' behavior.)
(They must hide
before the security finds them.)
Where should I hide?
(They move in order.)
Hide here.
(Each member hides.)
(Security starts to patrol
assigned locations.)
(He gets nervous
by the sound of footsteps.)
(They shouldn't patrol this room.)
(The security search
assigned locations in order.)
(They move to the next room.)
Se Chan.
Did you see security
during the patrol time?
(Of course not. I was also hiding.)
No.
(He sighs.)
Why?
Is someone on a mission...
after making us hide?
(Is someone doing something
in secret?)
Really?
It might be true
because I didn't see any security.
Do you see any security guards?
You don't, do you?
Someone is secretly on a mission
right now.
(The room where Suk Jin
and Se Chan are hiding)
They're here.
- Security?
- Policemen.
- Policemen?
- Yes.
- You're lying.
- They're here.
Go outside and look.
They're here indeed.
They are policemen.
(He can't check
in case he gets caught.)
I don't want to get eliminated.
(First patrol is over.)
Let's go.
(After checking
that the patrol is over,)
(everyone goes back
to their own hacker's room.)
When the security is on patrol,
all of us hide.
When we hide,
what if the spy does something?
Suk Jin said the same thing.
If you think about it... Really?
It's strange that we hide.
Hiding is too easy.
Suk Jin, doesn't something
feel strange?
- What?
- Jong Kook said exactly...
what you said before.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's why I asked
whether you saw the security.
I did.
- I saw them.
- Isn't someone on the move?
When we hide, everyone hides,
and no one does anything.
What if there's a spy
who goes around...
with the security?
- All we have to do is hide.
- Right.
Isn't it too easy?
I was hiding,
and the security saw me...
All right, be quiet.
What?
(All right, be quiet.)
(No one asked for your story.)
- Listen.
- But this is...
- It's not that important.
- If I don't talk about it...
- Was it important?
- It was very important.
It's very strange.
We should figure it out to solve it.
- So Min, let's go in.
- So Min.
We have to solve it.
- Don't go in.
- What? You go in first.
Come in when I set the timer.
I'm jealous of you.
Ji Hyo is the hacker on my team.
(He's jealous.)
- That's why I said that it's okay.
- It started.
We can take our time.
It's Ji Hyo on that team.
She's writing ABCD on repeat.
She's driving me crazy.
I thought that she was calling
the spirits.
X, Y.
(Please let me know the password.)
Why doesn't it work?
(She can't figure it out.)
- Here's what I think.
- There's something.
The owner of the mansion
or someone is up to something.
Isn't it strange that
there's a photo of Jae Suk?
It's strange that Jae Suk's
photo is in this house.
- Think about it.
- Also, the price is...
- It's 10,000 dollars.
- so expensive.
I wasn't going to say this,
but Haha's "The Gang" CD was
1.5 dollars, so I put it back down.
How can it only cost 1.5 dollars?
- I think it's Jae Suk's house.
- It's strange.
- Isn't it his house?
- Isn't this Jae Suk's house?
- Yes.
- This house?
He also interrupted you
a moment ago.
Hey, I think it's right.
That's why his photo is pricey.
- That's what I'm saying.
- Get out and go back inside.
- Right? It's strange.
- Yes.
I think this is Jae Suk's house.
(Se Chan is looking
for something to steal.)
What's this?
(He finds something.)
(He finds a safe by chance.)
(However...)
(Why is the siren ringing
all of a sudden?)
What's going on?
Yang Se Chan has been caught
on surveillance cameras.
Se Chan is out.
(Yang Se Chan is caught
on surveillance cameras.)
This is where
the surveillance camera was.
Why is that on?
(Surveillance camera is on.)
(Who turned it on?)
(Jae Suk definitely turned it off
a while ago.)
(Someone turned the surveillance
camera back on.)
Yang Se Chan has been caught
on surveillance cameras.
Se Chan is out.
That fool.
(Gosh, what a fool.)
Why did he get caught?
Where did it happen?
Did he go to the restroom?
- Se Chan is out.
- He got caught on camera.
I don't know. I don't think so.
(The more confusing it gets)
Who are you today?
- Me?
- Yes.
- What about me?
- What...
- You're very suspicious.
- Why me?
(However, there is no evidence.)
We have to be careful
of the surveillance cameras.
(Sand went in my ear...)
(Jae Suk is concentrating
on figuring out the password.)
(How are they related?)
(Staring)
(What is that number lock?)
(Sand went in my ear,
so I went to the hospital.)
Ha Na.
(Come here, Ha Na.)
(Did Jae Suk notice something?)
Ear, meat, mouth.
- What's this?
- Chinese characters.
(He finds numbers
with Chinese characters.)
(Ear, sand, meat, and mouth)
Chinese characters.
(2, 4, 6, 9)
(Team Captain Jae Suk figures out
the password.)
- This is it.
- I'll try.
Is it 2 and 4?
Four.
(She tries 2,4,6,9.)
(The lock unlocks.)
- Is it number four?
- Yes.
- You're a genius.
- No.
It's four.
(What is inside the cabinet
that was locked?)
- What is it?
- What?
They're balloons.
(Are they balloons on plates?)
(There's a key next to a balloon.)
Do we have to inflate the balloons?
(He's curious.)
(They inflate the balloons first.)
Wait, ear is number two.
- Meat is six.
- What about sand?
Sand is number four.
It's 2, 4, 6, 9.
Is it 2, 4, 6, 9?
What's this?
(There are only balloons
in the cabinet.)
What is it?
What's the point of opening it?
There's a key. Goodness.
(Why am I going through this?)
(Where did Jong Kook go?)
I'm not smart.
(She introspects herself quickly.)
(Class leader in the sixth grade)
(Class president
in the seventh grade)
(Class vice president
in the eighth grade)
(She probably wasn't voted
for being smart.)
What's this key for?
I'll keep it for now.
(What is the key for?)
(One)
(Man)
(Show)
(At that moment)
Ji Suk Jin's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
Police special forces have been
dispatched to arrest him.
Someone else is out.
(Did Suk Jin get eliminated?)
(Jong Kook left So Min behind.)
I'm out.
- What?
- I'm out.
- Are you out?
- Yes.
(How did Suk Jin get eliminated?)
(He checks his name tag.)
Come this way.
- You got hit.
- Is it the water gun?
You got hit.
(Suk Jin's name tag got shot
by a water gun.)
So Min, Suk Jin got eliminated.
He got hit by a water gun.
(We're in trouble.)
(What? Water gun?)
The water was pink.
(When they received a tool
this morning)
(The color of the water was
definitely blue.)
(Why is it pink?)
- Was it pink?
- Yes.
- Whose is it?
- Did you get it?
Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
Do you have a water gun?
Yes, I got a gun.
- What?
- I got it...
after Haha got eliminated.
Let me see your water gun.
I have something to check.
- Shoot it.
- You won't steal it?
No, just shoot it.
(It's blue.)
Suk Jin got eliminated.
He got hit by a water gun
and the color was pink.
(They need to find the member
with the pink water.)
Ours shoot blue.
The announcements are different.
When Suk Jin got eliminated,
the announcement was,
"Ji Suk Jin's location
is revealed."
"Running away
will be of no use."
When Se Chan got eliminated,
the announcement was,
"Yang Se Chan is caught
on surveillance cameras."
"Se Chan is out."
That means Haha got hit
by a water gun.
(The announcement is telling.)
Ji Suk Jin's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
(When Se Chan got eliminated)
Yang Se Chan is caught
on surveillance cameras.
Se Chan is out.
Haha's location is revealed.
Running away will be of no use.
(Haha got eliminated
by the pink water!)
Now...
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk and Ha Na
are still working on the balloons.)
(What do these balloons mean?)
(There are 3 balloons
on each plate.)
(Only the last plate has
2 balloons and a key.)
I think...
(They rack their brains.)
it's about mixing the colors.
(Could that be it?)
(Will mixing the colors help them
solve the hint?)
- Right?
- You are right.
If we mix the colors...
(Then the key has to do
with the color pink.)
Pink.
(Ha Na did an incredible job
as a hacker.)
Ha Na, you are right.
Pink.
Look at the diary, it's pink.
(They find a pink diary!)
(The pink diary is locked.)
This is incredible.
(They open the lock with the key.)
What is it?
"You are almost there.
This is the last problem."
What is this?
"Cross you out from 'Partner'
and reverse the rest."
(Cross you out from 'Partner'
and reverse the rest?)
Shall we retrace our steps?
What does this mean?
(Clueless)
What is this?
(So Min is trying to figure out
the use of the key.)
This key is for a small diary.
(She had such a diary
when she was little.)
(From the key, she guesses
that she needs a diary.)
(She finds the diary.)
Jong Kook,
- I found it.
- Hey.
Come here.
- I got this.
- What?
"You are almost there.
This is the last problem."
- "Cross you out from 'Partner'..."
- Jong Kook, I am exhausted.
Do you have an energy drink?
(I want to solve the problem
and relieve my exhaustion.)
I haven't studied this hard
back in school.
I am serious.
"Cross you out from 'Partner'
and reverse the rest."
What are these?
What are these balloons?
The balloons are about
mixing different colors.
You were supposed to find
the pink diary that way.
(The production crew reveals
the answer.)
But you found it without needing to.
I bypassed that step.
(She resorted to tricks.)
I am like a genius.
I got the answer without thinking.
Jong Kook.
This is really fascinating.
Solving the patterns of the colors
gives us pink.
Really?
Yes.
Mixing the colors...
Jong Kook.
Let me do it again.
Give me another chance.
Oh, Jong Kook!
(Acting surprised)
If we blow these balloons,
we get pink.
Really?
- Really?
- So...
(Let's blow the balloons.)
Then we get the pink diary!
No way!
(It's unbelievable!)
That's it.
- That's how we get the pink diary.
- That's incredible.
I found it.
(Ji Hyo still goes over the letters
like a Ouija board.)
- Did you solve the passcode?
- Kwang Soo.
- I can't do this.
- Jae Suk is suspicious.
(Kwang Soo suspects Jae Suk.)
What do you mean?
I think Jae Suk has
another mission.
(She has no idea
what's going on outside.)
(She has been inside the room
for an hour.)
This is driving me crazy.
This sticks out
from the other books on the shelf.
Forget about "HOT."
What is this?
(She found the pink diary.)
There should be a key.
Why is that diary here?
(Kwang Soo is just as clueless.)
I can't open it.
(The two fools struggle.)
(Kwang Soo gives up.)
What?
- What is it?
- Where is that thing?
- The pen?
- Yes.
(She wants to use
the appraiser's pen on the diary.)
That could be it.
(Eureka.)
(That's not it.)
I will look for more items.
Did you find expensive items?
Yes, I did. No one else but me
is doing it.
This makes no sense.
- We don't have partners today.
- I...
- Why does it say "Partner"?
"You are almost there.
This is the last problem."
"Cross you out from 'Partner'
and reverse the rest."
What does "Partner" mean?
- We don't have partners today.
- Teammate.
"Cross you out..."
Maybe it's about taking out.
Take out what?
This makes no sense.
It's "Part."
"You" is read as "Ner" in Korean.
(Cross "Ner" out from "Partner.")
(Part?)
(Part)
- Part.
- That's it.
If we cross "Ner" out,
we are left with "Part."
"Cross you out from 'Partner'..."
Write "Part" in English.
"And reverse the rest."
Reverse it.
(Reverse the rest?)
- Cross "Ner" out.
- That's right.
Let's write "Part" in English.
Give it to me.
Give me the spelling.
- It's T, R, A, P.
- P.
(They reverse the letters.)
(Trap)
Trap.
T, R, A, P. Trap.
- We got "Trap."
- T.
(They quickly type in "Trap.")
(They are in!)
- Trap.
- We are in.
(So Min and Jong Kook
gain access to the computer.)
Jong Kook, step outside
for a second.
- I am anxious.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook goes outside
to keep the patrol from coming.)
- Close the door.
- Trap. We got it.
- The location of Tear of Yondu.
- Hold on.
How is Ji Hyo supposed
to solve this?
(Hold on.)
It's in the basement.
- I have been there.
- I will take a photo of the plan.
- Do you know where this place is?
- What?
I went to the basement earlier.
(Tear of Yondu is at the end
of the center staircase.)
(The safe is located in B1.)
- The password is "Trap."
- It's "Trap."
Okay. I will go there.
(He moves to B1 to find the safe.)
(He is close to finding
Tear of Yondu.)
(He goes down the staircase
without hesitation.)
(He remembers to turn off
the surveillance camera.)
(After turning off
the surveillance camera,)
(he safely reaches the safe!)
(If he opens the safe
and gets Tear of Yondu,)
(Jong Kook's team will win!)
(When he enters the password,
"Trap,")
(the safe opens!)
(He checks what's inside.)
(It's not Tear of Yondu,
but a mysterious file.)
(He takes the file
and moves hurriedly!)
Jong Kook! Jong Kook!
Jong Kook!
- What is it? What's wrong?
- Jong Kook!
Who is it? What's wrong?
(So Min got attacked by someone.)
- So Min's location is revealed.
- Who is it? What's wrong?
Police special forces have been
dispatched to arrest her.
Jong Kook.
(To make matters worse,
they hear the cuckoo sound.)
(Jong Kook leaves hurriedly.)
I will go and hide.
My goodness.
(But Jong Kook doesn't know
which area the patrol will be.)
All right. Come in quickly.
(He hides in a nearby room.)
(Jae Suk's team knows
the patrol location...)
(and hides accordingly.)
The patrol.
(Ji Hyo doesn't know
the patrol location,)
(so she hides as well as possible.)
(She hides every inch of her body
in case the patrol enters the room.)
I need to hide.
(The patrol enters the mansion.)
(Once he takes cover,)
(Jong Kook checks the file.)
For goodness' sake.
This is yet another twist.
(What does the file reveal?)
There is a spy.
(A spy?)
(A mysterious report
inside the file)
(Lure the 8 thieves
to 1 police officer's house.)
Today, we will play
Empty House: Oh, My Thieves.
You are the police officer
who is hiding among the thieves.
But the empty mansion
the thieves will rob...
belongs to you, the police officer.
The police officer
will carry out a sting operation...
called Tear of Yondu Project
to catch the thieves.
The object of the thieves' desire,
Tear of Yondu,
will be in your possession,
the police officer.
You win by shooting the water gun
on the thieves' name tags...
and arresting all of them
in the final race.
You lose by getting eliminated
by the thieves first.
The thief who eliminates you
will take Tear of Yondu,
and their team will win the race.
(There is a police officer
among us.)
(Knocking)
(Who is it?)
It's the police!
(The police?)
I didn't get hit by a water gun.
(The police rush into the room
Jong Kook is hiding.)
What? What is going on?
Do I just get caught?
(Jong Kook's team didn't get a hint
on the patrol schedule.)
(Thus, they didn't know
where the police will be.)
(Patrol schedule)
(Patrol location at 4:30 p.m.,
Hacker's Room 1, Reception Room...)
(He hid in a room that was included
in the patrol schedule.)
(Jong Kook uses brute force
to avoid arrest.)
What happens now?
Do I just get caught?
(But he is trapped.)
(Jong Kook couldn't avoid
the patrol.)
- You are under arrest.
- How can this be?
(The patrol finds him.
Kim Jong Kook is out.)
Thief Kim Jong Kook was
eliminated by the patrol.
(Team Jae Suk heads to the safe
after realizing its location.)
- It opened.
- It did.
(The safe is empty.)
- Is there a hint?
- No.
Aren't you looking for a hint?
I know, but we didn't find it.
We can't find it anywhere.
We need the hint to solve it.
Ji Hyo.
The other team figured it out.
- Really? I found it.
- What?
There's a piece of paper.
I found it.
Look at it.
(She shares what she found
with Kwang Soo.)
"Sand went into my ear,
so I went to the hospital."
"More people had mouth pain
from eating meat."
(Who is she?)
What could this mean?
(Jae Suk is looking for hints.)
(In the room where
Jong Kook was eliminated,)
(he finds a project folder.)
What's this?
(He checks the contents
of the folder.)
"Lure the eight thieves...
to one police officer's house."
Ha Na.
(He tries to share the information
with Ha Na.)
Thief Park Ha Na's location is
revealed.
Police special forces will be
dispatched to arrest her.
(How did I get caught?)
Where was the camera?
(The police find out
Ha Na's location.)
(Is Ha Na out?)
Why Ha Na?
(There's pink on her name tag.)
(Arrested by the police,
Ha Na is out.)
Be careful, Ji Hyo.
- Why?
- Not many people are left.
It looks like six members remain.
There are 2, 2, and 2.
To solve this...
- I had such...
- What did you say?
- I had a hard time solving it.
- Before that.
- How many people remain?
- Six people, isn't it?
You were in there for too long.
Follow me back in.
- Did something happen?
- Stay inside.
- Why?
- Everyone got eliminated.
That was such a long time ago.
Look, Suk Jin,
Se Chan, and Haha are out.
- So Min and Jong Kook are out too.
- What?
- Really?
- Yes.
Only these remain?
I didn't know, Kwang Soo.
- I stayed here too long.
- You stayed in this room too long.
You're like the one from "Old Boy."
- I know.
- The world changed.
(As if hiding
from a surprise attack)
Let's see.
(Ji Hyo hid in a cabinet.)
(While hiding,)
(many of her colleagues left.)
It's not six anymore.
My goodness.
(Jae Suk enters the room
where Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo are.)
Kwang Soo.
(The situation has changed.)
Gosh, hey.
(Kwang Soo passes the water gun
to Ji Hyo.)
(Calm down and listen to me.)
A police officer is inside.
- What?
- Inside?
- What do you mean?
- It's a police officer's house.
- It's a trap.
Look at this.
(He shares information
about the police.)
Is this it?
There's no point in searching.
The police officer already
has the necklace.
Do we have to eliminate
the police officer?
I think so.
(Only three people remain.)
(One of them is a police officer.)
It's 10 minutes before 5 p.m.
After 5 p.m., you will be locked
inside this mansion.
Let's go.
(They have to find the officer
before the mansion gets locked.)
Ji Hyo.
- It's Jae Suk.
- How do you know?
He stayed with Ha Na all along.
Isn't it you?
No, how could I be?
- Isn't it you?
- I'm not.
Why do you keep accusing Jae Suk?
It's one of us three.
I know that it's not you.
And Ha Na got eliminated
when she was with him.
We have 10 minutes left.
- Watch where Jae Suk is going.
- Okay.
- I'm here.
- What?
(Speak of the devil...)
Gosh, you startled me.
- You dirty...
- I was telling her to be careful.
I was telling her to be careful
since she's on my team.
What happened
while I was in the room?
In my opinion,
it's not you, Ji Hyo.
It's not me.
I just came out
after solving the passcode.
(Ji Hyo claims to be innocent.)
(Ji Hyo took a long time
to figure out the hint.)
(What if she left the room
during that time?)
(Kwang Soo is
another police candidate.)
That's the surveillance camera.
(Thieves turned off
the surveillance camera.)
(But Kwang Soo turned it back on.)
(Did he do it to catch thieves?)
(The last police candidate is
Jae Suk.)
Why is my photo here?
(There was a big photo of Jae Suk
from the start.)
(She's suspicious.)
(Was his photo here because
he's the owner of the house?)
Is it you?
My goodness.
Ji Hyo, considering many things,
he's the police officer.
Gosh.
Wait.
- Your fate depends on me.
- Explain your photo.
What?
If this isn't your house,
why is there a large photo of you?
What do you think?
That was placed by the police
officer who lured us here.
As I said, this entire...
Why are you stammering?
(She's very suspicious.)
Ji Hyo, you have to decide quickly.
- We have no time.
- Ji Hyo.
It's over once you're eliminated.
He's wearing a bulletproof jacket.
Do you understand what I mean?
(He's the only one
wearing a bulletproof jacket.)
He won't die.
(He can protect himself
from elimination.)
The one who remains will be
eliminated.
- Okay?
- I can't eliminate you.
One of us has to take off
his bulletproof jacket.
Conditions should be even.
- That's true. That's my decision.
- Yes.
Let's make it fair.
Will you shoot me?
- You have the bulletproof vest on.
- We need to take it off first.
- Right.
- Take off the bulletproof vest.
- Isn't that fair?
- Let's start with that.
Okay.
(He takes off the bulletproof vest
to get rid of the suspicion.)
(Shooting)
Kwang Soo, take off
the bulletproof vest.
Jae Suk's gun can't be used
anymore.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Kwang Soo can't be...
(Only Ji Hyo's water gun remains.)
It'll be difficult
if he's not the police officer.
(Ji Hyo discovers something.)
What is Kwang Soo doing? Wait.
(Inside Kwang Soo's
cameraman's bag,)
(there's pink-colored water.)
Suk Jin got eliminated.
He got hit by a water gun.
The water was pink.
(It's the water gun
that shot Suk Jin.)
(If Kwang Soo has pink water...)
What is Kwang Soo doing? Wait.
(Kwang Soo is the police officer.)
He has a water gun.
- Jae Suk, I'll shoot.
- Go away.
(Officer Kwang Soo takes action.)
Today race is called
Empty House: Oh, My Thieves.
You're the police officer hiding
among the thieves.
I'll show you that justice prevails.
(Surveillance cameras
that were turned off...)
(were turned back on by Kwang Soo.)
(Se Chan walked around
without noticing the camera.)
(Caught on surveillance camera,
Se Chan is out.)
(Se Chan is out.)
(Kwang Soo can win
only after eliminating all thieves.)
(He eliminates Haha
with his water gun.)
What?
(Without his identity known,
he eliminates Suk Jin.)
What are you?
Am I out?
Jong Kook, Jong Kook!
(So Min gets eliminated
wandering alone.)
(Kwang Soo is the police officer.)
- How...
- I'm sorry.
(Even he eliminates Ha Na.)
(Under the name of justice,
he eliminated many thieves.)
- Jae Suk, I'll shoot.
- Go away.
- Go.
- I'll shoot him.
Please.
- Wait.
- I'll do it.
(The one who shoots wins.)
Catch him.
Shoot Jae Suk!
- Why you...
- You think I'd fall for that?
(Shooting)
(He blocks the shot with his face.)
I'm the justice.
- Get lost, both of you!
- That's nonsense.
(At that moment)
(Kwang Soo aims
for Jae Suk's name tag.)
(Unfortunately, he misses.)
(She counterattacks right away.)
- Shoot him.
- I got it.
I shot him.
(The thief's water gun can
eliminate only one person.)
(Did she hit him?)
It's over.
(There's a clear blue spot.)
- You got hit.
- Did I get hit?
(Did I get hit?)
(He got hit.)
- Ji Hyo.
- He got hit.
Jae Suk.
- Did I get hit?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry for suspecting you.
- It's okay.
- You did it, Ji Hyo.
- Gosh.
How could he fool me completely?
(I had to win for justice.)
Goodness.
- I'll announce the result.
- Okay.
The final winner is Team Thieves.
Officer Kwang Soo lost.
- Did you lose?
- Did you?
- That's right.
- He lost his initial intention.
Did Kwang Soo lose?
The final winner
of today's race is...
Ji Hyo who won Tear of Yondu.
Is it Ji Hyo?
- What's this?
I came an hour early for this.
This is Tear of Yondu.
I should have worked harder.
(He's very disappointed.)
She was so funny.
When she came out after solving
the passcode, everyone was dead.
When I came out, everyone was dead.
(Ji Hyo also wins a nice present.)
Kwang Soo the police officer is
the only one who lost.
He'll be penalized
with the water cannon.
- What?
- It's the last thing that we hoped.
How about this?
Don't hit his entire body.
Just hit his head.
- His head?
- That's better.
- The head is the best.
- Okay.
- I'll take that.
- You can do that instead.
Or get it in your face.
- Let's go out for the penalty.
- Thank you.
Okay.
Kwang Soo will get his penalty.
It will only hit my head, right?
- Only your head.
- Thank you.
- Stay back and stick out your head.
- Okay.
One,
two,
three.
Happy New Year!
Stand back.
(Splashing)
(We prepared a lot, thinking
8 thieves would get this.)
- Hey.
- What was that?
Kwang Soo.
- There was so much water.
- What was that?
(You said it'd only splash my head!)
What is this?
- Okay.
Good job.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
(Thank you for joining
the show today, Ha Na.)
(There's a fancy party
to celebrate an occasion?)
(They reveal the presents
they prepared with all their heart.)
(Their memories of 10 years
are revealed with the presents too.)
(The party isn't over yet!)
(Even Jong Kook joins
the parade of the cute acts.)
That's so cute.
(A feast with rare dishes)
(Special effects you see
only in blockbusters)
(The one who enjoys the party
is the winner.)
(And...)
(they introduce their friends
who attended the party.)
(Sometimes, you can't
anticipate our behaviors.)
(Sometimes,
we express intense feelings.)
(What's the secret weapon...)
(that will move the friend's heart?)
(A Special Party: Hungry Race)