(Last week)
(Hyosung, Yoyomi, Kyung-hwan,
and Tae Oh joined last week.)
(Ggannes Film Festival:
The Uninvited One)
(2 directors and 1 national actor
are among them.)
(Team Actors will win
if they identify 2 directors...)
(with the national actor
and eliminate them.)
(If the directors find out
who the national actor is...)
(and eliminate the national actor,
Team Directors win.)
(They checked their identities
on their mini name tags.)
(Who are the 2 directors
among the group?)
(Team Jong Kook obtained
a hint about the director.)
(1 director is a man
and 1 director is a woman.)
(1 of the directors is a man,
and the other, a woman.)
This is the second mission
to earn hints about the directors.
It's called Speed Movie Review King.
One person comes forward
and looks at the given movie title.
You must stick your face out and
describe in 1 sentence in 3 seconds.
You win a point
if you get the answer right.
However, you cannot directly mention
the movie title,
the cast or quotes from the movie.
(They didn't earn the hint
as they failed the 1st round.)
You failed your 1st round.
Pick someone for your 2nd round.
We should switch.
- Shall we start? Start?
- Let's switch.
I have to show you how it's done.
I have no choice.
(The directors might fail on purpose
to sabotage the game.)
(Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, So Min,
Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, and Se Chan)
You can discuss it before answering.
- Goodness, this one.
- Gosh.
Guys, you guys are so frustrating.
(What was that?)
I bet all of my money
that he won't get it right.
By the way,
he's the king of improvised lines.
- Jong Kook. You know...
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
You should go first.
The king of improvised lines.
(Is it time for me
to take the lead?)
- The king of improvised lines.
- Gosh.
- The king is going to play now.
- I'm already looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to that.
Jae Suk, you look
very nervous right now.
Not at all.
- You look very nervous right now.
- Not at all.
- Don't be so nervous.
- Look at me.
Why are your lips so purple?
- Don't be so nervous.
- Hey.
- Just watch me.
- Okay.
Do you know
what I'm doing behind this?
- What?
I have my hands in my pocket.
(He's laid-back as he's the king.)
This shows that I'm totally at ease.
- He's confident.
- You're no joke.
- You're totally relaxed.
- I'm flexing it.
- He's "flexing".
- You're so cool.
Here's your question.
- You have three seconds. Ready,
- Let's go.
set, go.
Hey, it's...
"Hey".
(The explanation of the movie
by the king of improvised lines)
- Hold on. Al...
- Goodness. This is so easy.
(They didn't get it wrong, but why
did he get the water balloon?)
(He's punished
for his weak explanation.)
- Not yet. You have to answer first.
- We didn't answer yet.
Hey, throw it at him.
- "Al"? Hold on.
- Do it.
"Al"?
Could it be "Jurassic Park"?
- "Running Man".
- No, no.
- "Jurassic Park".
- We're talking about movies.
- There's a movie with that name.
- Oh, the movie?
There's no way they gave us that.
There's no way.
I doubt that they gave us that
as our question.
- "Jurassic Park" is the only one...
- That's it.
- I can think of.
- Fine.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- What's your answer?
- "Jurassic Park".
(The king of improvised lines' hint
was "Al".)
(Will the answer be
"Jurassic Park"?)
- In 1, 2, 3. "Jurassic Park".
- In 2, 3. "Jurassic Park".
- What's the answer?
- What was the hint about?
(Incorrect)
"Aladdin".
I see. It was the first syllable
of the title.
- I gave you the first syllable.
- But you cannot do that.
- You can't say the title.
- That's cheating.
- What did you say?
- You can't say part of the title.
It's okay for you
to be bad at games,
but you cheat and play dirty.
- Why put your hands in your pocket?
- Why isn't that allowed?
- They did that earlier.
- We can't say anything about it?
- Okay, I got it.
- You can't.
- We'll start.
- Watch me. I'll "shaw" you.
- He'll "shaw" us.
- "Shaw"?
Watch me. I'll "shaw" you.
(You'll "shaw" us?)
Se Chan sounds really nervous.
- He's really nervous now.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
- I'll shaw you
I'll shaw you. Watch.
(He's a fool.)
- I can "dew" a good job.
- That's cute.
The way he said it was cute, right?
- I'll show you.
- Start.
(The second question begins.)
He goes up somewhere
and meets a grandma.
(He goes up somewhere
and meets a grandma.)
"The Way Home".
- "The Way Home".
- Hold on.
- He goes up and meets a grandma?
- "The Way Home".
Does he go up the mountain?
He goes up and meets a grandma?
"The Way Home".
- Wait. Be quiet.
- Does that count as going up?
Be quiet!
(Wait. Be quiet. Be quiet!)
(He gets mad
in the middle of the quiz.)
Don't be so rash!
- Hey.
- Why are you so...
- I was just talking.
- What's wrong with you?
He sounds very mad.
Who meets the grandma?
- The grandma?
- It has to be "The Way Home".
- "The Way Home".
- That's the only possible answer.
- It's "The Way Home".
- Okay. It's "The Way Home".
- What's your answer?
- "The Way Home"!
- That's correct!
- Yes!
("The Way Home"
is the right answer.)
- I did a good job, right?
- "The Way Home".
- Did I do a good job?
- Well done.
- I did well, right?
- I did well.
- You did very well.
Hey, it's your girlfriend's turn.
My girlfriend?
(Peekaboo)
My goodness.
You're unbelievable.
You're something else.
Here you go. Start.
- Gosh.
- That's hard.
Gosh, the doll is really scary.
(Gosh, the doll is really scary.)
- Okay.
- "Child's Play".
(Answering right away)
- Wait.
- Hold on.
- It's "Child's Play".
- No, she can't mention that.
- I told you not to be so rash!
- Jong Kook.
Goodness.
- Why are you wasting our chance?
- Jae Suk...
Let's discuss this first.
It's not because he's the director.
- He's just easily distracted.
- Listen.
I bet that for 12 years,
in his student record,
- it said he was easily distracted.
- How did you know that?
I'm the same way with you.
We could have discussed it.
She can't probably mention the doll.
- It has to be that. "Annabelle"
- "Annabelle".
What's your answer?
(She mentioned a scary doll.
What's the right answer?)
- Okay.
That was well-played, Jong Kook.
(They answered
2 questions out of 3.)
They are good at this.
Jong Kook, you can go next.
- Jong Kook, show us.
- Jong Kook.
- Let's see how good you are.
- "Let's see how good you are."
I'm not saying
that I'm good at this.
I just want you
to answer this carefully.
We'll calm down.
- We'll give it a go.
- Ready, set, go.
(Fourth question,
"Bohemian Rhapsody")
He sings songs on stage.
- Hold on.
- He sings songs on stage?
- It could be "Bohemian Rhapsody".
- "Born to Sing"?
There's "Highway Star" too.
- No.
- There's "Born to Sing" too.
It's "200 Pounds Beauty".
- There are too many.
- Then, he should've said "she".
Right.
- "Bohemian Rhapsody".
- Gosh, "Bohemian Rhapsody".
- There's one for The Beatles too.
- Wait. You can't...
- You can't make a face for it.
- "Bohemian Rhapsody".
- No?
(Making a face
while blinking furiously)
- "Bohemian Rhapsody".
- What? Hold on.
- Wait.
- What's wrong with that?
- I didn't do anything.
- He just blinked.
"200 Pounds Beauty".
Wait. No.
"Bohemian Rhapsody".
Jae Suk.
What? I didn't do anything.
- "Bohemian Rhapsody".
"200 Pounds Beauty".
Bo.
200.
- "Born to Sing"?
- That's it.
- Come here.
- All right. Jae Suk.
(He doesn't need to speak.)
- Hey, Jae Suk. In 1, 2, 3.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- "Bohemian Rhapsody".
(Fine, we'll let you take it.
That's correct.)
Okay!
Wait, he opened his eyes wide.
- Okay. Great.
- Okay.
(When everyone is having fun now,)
(the Airtime Destroyer
is worried about his airtime.)
(Mom)
Ready,
set, go.
- He uses magic.
- Start.
He uses magic. He uses magic.
- What?
- "Harry Potter".
- He uses magic.
Gosh, this is hard.
- Goodness, this is difficult.
- When it comes to magic,
- I only think of "Harry Potter".
- No.
Don't do anything.
What are you doing?
What else do we have
other than "Harry Potter"?
- No, you can't do that.
- It's not "The Lord of the Rings".
- What other movies are about magic?
- What is it?
Jae Suk keeps asking what it is.
What other movies do we have
for magic?
- The one with Gang Dong Won.
- "Haunters".
The one with Gang Dong Won in it.
He wears that costume and flies.
- "Jeon Woo-chi"?
- "Jeon Woo-chi".
(Could that be the answer, Se Chan?)
"Jeon Woo-chi" must be the answer.
(Smiling)
(When he hears "Jeon Woo-chi",
he can't stop smiling.)
(They communicate
with the trophy of the truth.)
- That's not a bad answer.
- "Jeon Woo-chi".
- That's cheating.
- Shall we go with that?
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Jong Kook.
- "Jeon Woo-chi".
(That's correct!)
- How did they get that right?
- That's amazing.
How did you get that right?
- Next.
- Go, Mr. Fish.
Okay.
- Make sure to fully discuss it.
- Okay.
All right. Here we go.
- Ready,
- Look at his face.
- set,
- You must explain right away.
go!
Why is this day on this day?
- Hold on.
- "Why is this day on this day?"
- But his explanation was great.
- I'm sure they'll get it right.
I guess it was a good explanation.
- It has to do with a date.
- It wasn't bad.
"Why is this day on this day?"
- It has to be a date.
- "1987".
- "1987"?
- "1987"? Wait. No.
We must say it as a group.
(He tries to cheat.)
What?
You keep moving your fingers.
Not yet.
- Goodness.
- "Why is this day on this day?"
I guess this day
must not make sense for this day.
I got it! I figured it out!
It's "Christmas in August".
- Yes, that must be it.
- Yes!
(It's "Christmas in August".)
- That must be it.
- I got it. "Christmas in August".
- "Christmas in August".
(Is the right answer
"Christmas in August"?)
- "Christmas in August".
(That's correct!)
Yes!
- His fingers...
- Why did you throw the balloon?
- Why did you throw it at him?
- We could've done that too.
Wait, this isn't a team match.
It's for everyone.
I thought we were competing
against each other. I got confused.
- He's acting really strange.
- I really got confused.
- My gosh.
- I did give you a hint.
- Why did you do that?
- But he threw the balloon at me.
You gave us a hint?
- I was doing this with my fingers.
- Really?
All of a sudden, Haha threw
the water balloon at me.
- What are you doing?
- We can do that too?
I really thought
this was a competition.
It's not a competition.
We must all get the hint.
- It's for the whole group.
- What's wrong with him?
- You didn't give us the hint.
- Hey.
Of course,
we're competing against you...
because you're a director.
- What are you talking about?
- And we...
(Jong Kook starts to activate
his radar for spies again.)
The spy instinct hits you
before you know it.
- This is crazy. Okay, fine.
- When you get into it, it happens.
Let us play one more time.
- We should play again.
- Hear us out.
- We didn't have time to discuss it.
- I was doing this the whole time.
- So our clip wasn't funny at all.
- We can be funny too.
You have one more round.
You must complete the next round
to complete the mission.
Listen. The winning team
doesn't get the hint.
- This isn't a match between us.
- We're on the same team.
- I know that.
- Listen.
- Because we have this guy here...
- Excuse me. "This guy"?
(Haha is super sensitive.
Kyung-hwan sounds like a thug.)
(They aren't happy
as there won't be a lot of airtime.)
They are not interested in the hint.
- It's because of the airtime.
- We're just worried...
- that our clip won't air on TV.
- Let's do this.
We want to be entertaining too.
- You guys were fun in your own way.
- Right.
When were we funny?
(Let's get something straight.)
- There's the third round.
- Let's play again.
- You must pick six people again.
- What?
- You should form a team again.
- We'll play again.
- We'll play.
- Okay.
- Listen.
- This is unfair.
We're on the same team.
Ready, set, go.
("Ant-Man")
Gosh, I didn't know a hero
as small as me existed.
- Hero?
- A small hero?
- "Ant-Man".
- He's small.
- Hold on.
Is that the only small hero?
- It's a small hero.
- I know who it is. It's him.
- Let's see if there are more.
- Right.
- They're making it harder for them.
- They are.
- They're making it harder.
What other heroes are small?
Isn't it just him?
(They can't think
of anything funnier.)
- Lego.
- "Stuart Little".
You already got the answer.
Why are you hesitating?
You already got it.
Come on.
- Come on.
- You're trying so hard.
Aren't you going to say,
"Ant-Man" anyway?
We need to think
of something funnier...
so that we'll get more screen time.
Hold on.
(They're trying to get
more screen time.)
(Smiling)
- It's obviously "Ant-Man".
- That's enough.
Be more creative!
(He pressures them
to be more creative.)
"Ant-Man".
- "The Incredible Hulk".
- "Superman".
- It's "Ant-Man" for sure.
- What's your answer?
- "Ant-Man".
- 1, 2, 3.
(They're not in harmony.)
(Nothing is working out for him.)
They're not in harmony at all.
- 1, 2, 3. "Ant-Man".
- "Ant-Man".
- My team's so boring.
- Right.
(That is the correct answer.)
(My team's so boring.)
- No, Chul Min edits well.
- You guys are boring.
Don't be ridiculous.
They can make it interesting.
It gets boring when Kyung-hwan...
- is in the picture.
- Right.
(He's boring.)
- It's so weird.
- What do you mean?
- Why are you like that?
- What are you talking about?
I'm making everyone laugh.
Is this magic?
- Kyung-hwan.
- My goodness.
How can I make it funnier
when we already have the answer?
- But...
- I know.
(Take this water balloon
for more screen time.)
(Kwang Soo hits him
with a water balloon.)
It didn't burst.
- It could've been funny.
- Why didn't it burst?
Please!
(His screen time is reduced.)
Darn it!
(It fails again.)
- Like this! Like this!
- Okay!
Let me.
(No matter how much I try,)
(this balloon is quite sturdy.)
- Hold on.
- What is this thing?
Why isn't this working?
He can't even make us laugh.
Here he comes.
Show us.
- This is your last chance.
- I'll make you laugh.
Are you ready for it?
- Let's go.
- Ready, set, go.
("Frozen")
It's a cold world.
(They get it immediately.)
- A cold world?
- Is it the kingdom?
- I think so.
Here we go again.
The answer is weird.
No, just try it.
A cold world? Ice world?
"Tears of the Antarctic".
It could be "Frozen II".
There's also that other movie...
starring Song Kang Ho.
That train movie.
- "Snowpiercer".
"Snowpiercer"?
(He's embarrassed.)
(He has nothing left to say.)
- Merry...
- Just say the answer.
He gave up.
Just say it.
- Just say it. You got it.
- Hey.
- You got the answer.
- I wanted to help.
- This is the end.
- What's your answer?
- "Frozen".
Yes!
- Goodness.
- How long will this last?
It's not that he's boring.
It's just impossible for him
to be fun.
(He's funny, uninteresting,
and has no screen time.)
- It's impossible.
- You're right.
Come on.
That one was easy.
- I bet your game...
- Kyung-hwan is...
will be shown in a small box
on the right-hand corner.
It'll be shown briefly.
- They'll charge the audience.
- They do that when it's boring.
("Tidal Wave", "Highway Star")
(Their game is shown in the box.
Although it wasn't fun,)
(they got everything right
and receive a hint.)
Since you got everything right,
I'll give you a hint.
- Here comes the hint.
- Are we finally getting one?
(What kind of hint will it be?)
The directors...
(The directors...)
(During the 1st mission,
they received a hint.)
(Yoyomi and Tae Oh were suspected.)
(Will the hint be about them?)
The directors...
debuted more than three years ago.
Yoyomi isn't included.
(Yoyomi is not on the list.)
- It's not Yoyomi.
- No way.
We were all suspecting her.
- One of the directors is among...
- She was suspicious back there.
So Min, Ji Hyo, and Hyosung.
It's not me.
- It's not me either.
- It's So Min or...
We were young.
(One of the directors is among
So Min, Ji Hyo, and Hyosung.)
All right. You need to protect
the national actor...
and eliminate the directors.
The final mission is called
I Am an Actor.
I hate this position.
Hints regarding the directors
and the national actor...
are hidden throughout this building.
You must obtain them.
During the two trials...
that take place every 30 minutes,
you must eliminate the directors.
If you do, the national actor
and the actors win.
If the national actor
is eliminated...
or if you fail to eliminate
the directors during the two trials,
the directors win.
The losing team will be penalized.
Before the trial,
only the directors
and the national actor...
can remove the name tags.
The other actors can only
eliminate them through the trials.
However, if the directors
and the national actor...
eliminate three actors,
they will lose,
and the game will come to an end.
So the actors can't remove
the directors' name tags?
No, they can only do that
through the trials.
Only through the trials.
But we can help
the national actor, right?
We can grab the directors
or twist their arms.
- Or make them faint.
- Correct.
We can do that.
- You can't rip their name tags.
- Got it.
Once you've moved
to your locations,
- we'll start the race.
- Let's go!
Ever since the beginning,
Haha seemed a bit awkward.
I'm suspicious.
I think Tae Oh has a distinct role.
He's either a director
or the national actor.
I don't need to explain
about Tae Oh's actions.
He's making it very obvious.
I think Hyosung
is the female director.
I glanced at her during our break,
and she had a suspicious gaze.
I think it's Tae Oh and So Min.
(Kwang Soo suspects these two.)
I have no idea
who the national actor is.
I hope Kyung-hwan
is one of the directors.
That way,
he'll get some screen time.
(This is a wish of his.)
This is my last chance
to get my screen time.
If this doesn't work,
and you guys invite me again,
I won't come back.
(He's more focused
on gaining more screen time.)
- This is my last chance.
- The race will begin now.
(The announcement
for the start of the race is given.)
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
You may begin.
Where should I go?
What are you doing?
I'm searching.
I'm looking for hints.
You're an actor, right?
(He asks
a straightforward question.)
Yes.
(Yes, so what?)
I don't need to worry
about you then.
(He's daunted.)
Why? What about you?
I'm an actor too.
- In which genre?
- What?
Variety shows.
I act in variety shows.
If you're a national actor,
let me know so I'll protect you.
Of course.
Wait, there's a hint.
(Kyung-hwan finds a hint.)
There's a hint. Okay.
- Let's read it together.
- No, we shouldn't.
That's how we do it.
We always share the hints.
(Brushing off stubbornly)
- What was that?
- Fine.
- What? This is fine.
- Okay, okay.
Let's see.
"Director A
is a Running Man member."
(Director A
is a Running Man member.)
It's not me, see?
It's a Running Man member.
But we don't know
who Director B is.
- I see.
- Director A could be a female.
Why do you think Director A
is a male?
I have a lot of guy friends
who have blood type A.
Anyway...
Are you in bad condition?
(Yes)
Where do I keep this?
Someone's here. Hide it.
(He hides it.)
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is also suspected
of being a director.)
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
You just saw her a while ago.
I bet it'll come down...
- to either So Min or me.
- Why do you say that?
- That was random.
- Those two are similar.
Yoyomi was excluded,
so it's Hyosung, me,
- or So Min.
- So Min.
I'm certain it's not me,
so I suspect them.
If it's one of them, I pick So Min.
And back at the bus...
(Ji Hyo suspects So Min.)
So Min seemed suspicious.
If So Min was the director,
wouldn't it be too easy?
(Why is she suddenly accusing her?)
(Jae Suk gets into the elevator.)
Which floor are you going to?
Hey. Hey!
(It's so fun to tease Kwang Soo.)
What's wrong with him?
Why is he acting this way?
That was hilarious.
(This is worse than getting
your text messages ignored.)
My time with Kwang Woo
is always fun.
(Now that he's had his fun,)
(he looks around for the hints.)
What?
(He finds a box with an R sticker.)
What is this?
(What could it be?)
(It's a tablet.)
It's a tablet.
Is this the hint?
I am Kim Yoon Sang
of "That I Want to Know".
(What is "That I Want to Know"?)
In order to find out the truth...
about these two directors,
we've talked...
with their close associates.
I know Director A.
How do I put it?
I think I could say this.
"Running Man's fan-meet",
"tears".
"tears"?
One of the directors is related
to tears.
Who is Director A?
I got this. I know who it is.
(Jae Suk knows who it is.)
Goodness.
Did you get a hint?
I can't read it.
They have dignity?
(She misreads "director"
as "dignity".)
How could you misread this?
- Is it dignity?
- Who cried during the fan-meet?
Who was it?
(Who cried during the fan-meet?)
I'm dying to know.
- I want to search it up online.
- It's Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo was the one who cried.)
(During the fan-meet,
Ji Hyo shed tears.)
(Does this mean
she's one of the directors?)
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
(He immediately goes to her.)
I found a hint.
Was it about me?
It read "Running Man's fan-meet",
"tears".
It's really not me.
- This is too obvious.
- I'm serious.
I'm just frustrated that's all.
It's seriously not me.
- Let go of me.
- It isn't me.
Don't be clingy.
- Yoo Jae Suk!
- Go away.
You'll pay
if you leave me like this.
- Don't follow me.
- It isn't me.
- Don't come any closer.
- It isn't me!
Be quiet.
Unbelievable.
I knew I'd be suspected this way.
(Who's the national actor?)
Is everyone
thinking of the same person?
(They only know about
the directors right now,)
(but So Min spots something.)
(Who is the hint about?)
(The national actor's age
doesn't include the number 9.)
(In 2019, Kyung-hwan and Ji Hyo
were both 39.)
(Neither Kyung-hwan nor Ji Hyo
is the national actor.)
"Doesn't include..."
- Did you find something?
- A hint.
(It's Ji Hyo who many
suspect as a director.)
What did it say?
Wait, hold on.
You're just leaving?
I can't show you this.
- It's fine.
- I'd only show you...
- if I'm a director.
- I've been suspecting you,
- so you're not showing me...
- Look.
It's about the national actor,
so what if you're a director?
I'm just an actor,
so I should help the national actor.
One of the directors is female.
(Does she want to know so that she
can eliminate the national actor?)
(Meanwhile, Haha
is still searching for hints.)
(He spots something.)
(He finds a box with the R logo.)
What's this?
(It's a tablet
that contains a video.)
Hold on.
I am Kim Yoon Sang
of "That I Want to Know".
The two directors
desperately want to know...
the identity of the national actor.
I met with a close acquaintance
of this person.
Maybe it's a quality
of a national actor.
This person is generous
and is a skillful actor.
I almost forgot.
This person goes by a stage name.
(The national actor
goes by a stage name?)
I don't mind this person's
actual name though.
This person goes by a stage name.
So who is this national actor?
(Someone with a stage name...)
(who isn't of an age
that includes a 9.)
This is huge.
(National actor candidates:
Kang Tae Oh, Haha, Yoyomi)
This was the biggest hint ever.
This seems weird. Wait, what's that?
Haha, did you find a hint?
Not at all. What was that?
- Did you find a hint?
- Yes.
Regarding whom?
I have more on the national actor.
- The national actor?
- What about you?
I have two regarding
the national actor...
and one about the directors.
- Tell me about the directors.
- What are you though?
- Are you just an actor?
- Yes.
- What about you?
- I've...
seen you lie on TV too much
that I can't trust you.
Whatever. Forget about it.
(Subtly)
Forget about it.
(Tae Oh tried
to rip of Haha's name tag.)
What?
Why are you making me look bad?
I felt your hand just now.
Anyway, share whatever you find.
You're being very suspicious though.
(He's acting super suspicious.)
(Haha follows Tae Oh.)
Are you sure?
(Out of the blue)
- Sorry?
- I'll tell you what I know.
It's hard to guess who though.
- Write this down.
- Sure.
(While Tae Oh is preoccupied)
(Ripping)
(While his guard was down)
(A blitz attack)
(Haha eliminates Tae Oh
who could be a director.)
I'm sorry, Tae Oh.
I know that you're
the national actor.
(I know that you're
the national actor.)
(You think I'm the national actor?)
(This morning, they all checked
the roles they were playing.)
(Haha...)
(is a director!)
(Haha was chosen
for the role of a director.)
You're the national actor, right?
(Haha guessed it was Tae Oh
because he uses a stage name.)
You're just an actor?
(The twist)
- Unbelievable.
- You're not the national actor?
(Tae Oh acted suspiciously all day,)
(but he wasn't a director
nor the national actor.)
(He was just an actor.)
(Actor)
But you use a stage name
just like me and Yoyomi.
I was too naive.
Sorry, Tae Oh. I'll explain later.
No way.
Does it always end in vain?
What's up?
(Haha comes across Jae Suk.)
(Haha laughs awkwardly.)
You won't believe it.
I learned about the national actor.
- You found a hint?
- The biggest one ever.
(He must've found it over here.)
- What now?
- Gosh.
Kang Tae Oh has been eliminated.
(Jae Suk spots Tae Oh
who was just eliminated.)
Kang Tae Oh has been eliminated.
You've been eliminated?
Actor Kang Tae Oh
has been eliminated.
Wait.
Please get him.
(Only those with a special role
can eliminate others.)
Actor Kang Tae Oh
has been eliminated.
- What?
- Tae Oh was eliminated?
- Tae Oh?
- It's Haha.
- It's obvious now.
(They suspect those
who aren't here with them.)
That narrows it down.
I suspect Haha.
Did you eliminate Tae Oh?
(Haha was caught red-handed.)
I'm the national actor.
- What?
- I know something huge.
Why was Tae Oh eliminated
when he was only with you?
I thought that he was a director.
I'm telling the truth.
I know something huge.
- I'm not lying.
- 30 minutes have passed.
- Please gather at the court.
- We'll see at the trial.
I'm sure of it.
You should head to the court.
- The court.
- He was faking it.
We should continue this later on.
- Let's head to court first.
- Jae Suk, trust me.
You really should.
If I could,
I would show you the video.
(What will happen
at the first trial?)
I know it's confusing, but trust me.
So you're the national actor?
Gosh, keep it down!
- Gosh.
- You shouldn't say anything.
I don't believe you though.
Jae Suk!
(The others arrive at court.)
Who eliminated Tae Oh?
- Who eliminated him?
- Who was it?
Tae Oh...
Actor Kang Tae Oh was eliminated.
Now, we will commence
the first trial.
Please discuss among yourselves
and put one person on trial.
I witnessed it.
What happened?
Haha and Tae Oh were together,
but Tae Oh was eliminated.
(The witness testifies.)
(Haha pretends to be unfazed.)
- What?
- Then it's obvious.
(All he does is nod.)
(Haha seems unfazed.)
That's the expression he holds
when situations get awkward.
(Jong Kook pretends
to be perceptive.)
It's why I'm not saying anything.
I'll only speak if I'm on trial.
- I...
- That's right.
I'm worried because
he could be the national actor.
He could've thought that
Tae Oh was a director.
I think we should protect him.
It's definitely a risk.
I have a feeling that
Haha's the national actor.
He never puts on
a serious expression like that.
There's a hint
that we all know though.
It read "Running Man's fan-meet",
"tears".
The hint that Jae Suk found.
I'm confused because
that points to Ji Hyo.
I saw that too,
but the hints point
to Ji Hyo too directly...
which is why we should
let her be for now.
- So it's not her?
- It might not be.
- It's to throw us off?
- How about this?
Why don't we start by
narrowing down the female director?
It has to be one of you.
Yes, there are only
three possibilities.
I spotted a lady
who let something slip by mistake.
- What?
- In what way?
It was Jeon So Min.
(I let something slip?)
I told her about "tears"
being a hint that indicates...
who the director is,
but she claimed that tears
have never been...
a hint to anything over three years.
They never have been.
It hasn't happened before.
Have you ever seen a hint like that?
Then as she passed me,
she said to herself that she has
never cried on the show.
(Is Kyung-hwan telling the truth?)
(Like he said,
he shared the hint with So Min.)
(She didn't realize
she was saying it.)
(I never cried at the fan-meet.)
(Kyung-hwan was right!)
(Suspicious)
(Did So Min make a huge mistake?)
"I didn't cry, so how come
I'm one of the directors?"
I've never cried on the show before.
To be honest, I find it weird
not to put Ji Hyo on trial...
after learning
what the hints indicated.
- You're right.
- The staff of Running Man...
would've written that
to indicate So Min.
- As a twist?
- Yes, it's So Min.
- I think it was to throw us off.
- Right?
Don't you agree?
What about this then?
Let's put two
of the ladies on trial.
(He didn't fully
comprehend the rules.)
- What?
- Only one can be on trial.
- Kwang Soo?
- Hold on.
Seriously?
Hold on then.
Why don't we just put
three people on trial?
- Unbelievable.
- I'm sorry.
I think it's right
to put So Min on trial first.
Me? That's out of the blue.
I find So Min suspicious.
Also, she hasn't said anything
up until now.
There's nothing to say.
Then make a rebuttal
and convince us otherwise.
Well...
We need to fish out
one of the directors.
I think it's best
to find the female director first.
- Right.
- Then let's take a vote...
and put whoever receives
the most votes on trial.
He's right.
The person with the most votes
will be put on trial.
- Okay.
- Then I'll write my own name.
- What?
- Why?
Go ahead and see who I am.
- She's taking a risk.
- Exactly.
She's taking a huge risk
to clear her name.
Go ahead and vote then.
What? I should place my vote?
Yes, place your vote.
- If I do, will you trust me?
- So Min, you're pushing it.
- What if it is you?
- I'm...
Jae Suk wrote down your name and
is walking over to place his vote.
- Guys.
- Can you place mine for me?
Vote for me then.
Just know, that it isn't me.
(She checks Jong Kook's ballot.)
- It really isn't me.
- Place my vote for me.
- But it isn't me.
- Place my vote, please.
- So Min, here.
- I hear you.
- I'm sorry.
- "Jeon So..."
But all the hints point to Ji Hyo.
- Wait.
- Place my vote.
I swear that it isn't me.
If So Min isn't the director,
we should have the national actor...
eliminate Ji Hyo and Yoyomi.
- Exactly. Jong Kook's right.
- Right?
Sure, got it.
Here's the result.
So Min received
9 votes out of 11...
(The voting result)
(So Min will be put on trial.)
- Please stand on the platform.
- So Min, please head out.
(Sighing)
We have no other choice.
It's a process of elimination.
I don't get why no one wrote down...
Hyosung's name.
I doubt it's her.
- There are no hints on me.
- We have no hints about her.
But if So Min turns out
not to be a director...
If she turns out
Then it's either Ji Hyo
or Hyosung.
(Could Ji Hyo or Hyosung
be a director?)
I'll rip it off now.
(So Min's identity
will be revealed.)
Let's do it.
(Because of Kyung-hwan's testimony,
their fates have changed.)
(What is So Min's identity?)
- What is it?
- She is a director!
I told you!
(I got caught.)
(The director was not Ji Hyo,
but So Min.)
I told you, right?
(Shocked)
So Min!
Gosh, I can't trust you anymore.
Seriously.
(There is only one director
to catch now.)
Guys, listen.
So Min, an actor who has been
playing a director,
is out now.
So Min, who is an actor, is out.
(Is So Min an actor?)
So Min, who is a fake director,
- is out.
- A fake director?
What do you mean?
(What is going on?)
(Underneath her name tag,)
(it said, "Actor whose role
is a director.")
(So Min is not a female director.)
So Min, who is an actor, is out.
She is an actor?
- What?
- Oh, that's right.
It says, "actor".
Her role is a director.
- She is an actor?
- What are you talking about?
What's going on?
She is an actor
whose role is a director.
- What?
- Then why...
- She plays a director...
in the movie.
- What's with her face?
- Why did you do that?
- Are you a director or an actor?
- Aren't I a director?
I don't know.
- So Min...
- She thinks she is a director.
What is going on?
The staff tricked us.
- There must be a twist.
- Something doesn't feel right.
- Why is it so hard?
- What is this?
All right.
The court is adjourned.
Let's go back to the race.
They may not know
what their roles are.
Let's start the race again.
She thinks she is a director.
(Will they find the real directors
and the national actor?)
I can't believe the staff.
I mean...
I'm so angry.
I'm really angry.
(She feels victimized.)
Are you out?
- Are you out?
- I got fooled.
(She still feels victimized.)
I got fooled too.
I worked so hard,
but it was only a test.
While saying that,
- your eyes look so sad.
- Really?
You're smiling,
but you look very sad.
Why is that?
I'm glad that you know.
I'm not just saying this.
I didn't want to make you
feel uncomfortable,
but I've always liked you a lot.
(You've liked me a lot?)
You're so charming on Running Man.
I mean it.
(So Min's heart flutters.)
Maybe it's a good thing
that I got eliminated early.
- Why?
- I can be here with you alone.
(He feels a little uncomfortable.)
Can you lock the door?
I don't want anyone to come in.
- You were so funny at that time.
- When?
When your armpits got sweaty.
(When your armpits got sweaty)
That was...
That was hilarious.
Did you see Yondu too?
I saw everything.
(He really is a huge fan.)
There's the fish-shaped bun version,
but did you see
the fan-meet version too?
Like I said, I saw everything.
(Hopeless)
I see.
It was so funny.
I'm not teasing you though.
Can you marry a woman
who looks like Yondu?
(If I can marry her?)
(You said you like me a lot.)
Stop staring at me like that.
It's a bit uncomfortable.
I'm not.
(Tae Oh doesn't want her
to get any wrong ideas.)
Let's start the race again.
(The race starts again.)
This is crazy.
So Min is not a director.
Then what am I?
(So Min is an actor
whose role is a director.)
I'm...
I'm an actor
whose role is a director,
just like her.
The tablet PC said...
the national actor
goes by a stage name.
The candidates
are Haha, Song Ji Hyo,
Kang Tae Oh, and Yoyomi.
It's not Ji Hyo, Tae Oh, or me.
There was no reason
to eliminate Tae Oh.
(The only person left is...)
That leaves only Yoyomi.
(Is Yoyomi the national actor
as the hint suggests?)
They will suspect me now.
(Ji Hyo will be suspected
of being a director now.)
They will definitely suspect me.
(Is Ji Hyo a director?)
Let's hope the new hint...
will help us.
I have to find a hint.
(Everyone is looking for a hint.)
(Yoyomi, a national actor candidate,
finds something.)
(It's a hint.)
(Director A is not
in his or her 40s.)
(According to the hints
found so far,)
(Director A is
a Running Man member...)
(who is not in his or her 40s.)
(The candidates are...)
(Se Chan, Suk Jin,
Kwang Soo, and Ji Hyo.)
(Among them, who is a director?)
Does Kwang Soo have a role?
I don't think so.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Did you meet the staff earlier?
- No.
If I was a director,
- I would have hindered the game.
- Right.
Did you do anything wrong today?
- I made no mistakes today.
- No mistakes?
Okay. Am I a director then?
(Okay. Am I a director then?)
(What's with this guy?)
Bye.
(Their useless conversation
is over.)
I'll go downstairs.
(Just then)
(Kwang Soo looks around.)
(Making sure no one is around,
Kwang Soo follows Suk Jin.)
(He stares...)
(at Suk Jin's back.)
(Suk Jin looks back.)
He is acting strange.
He is suspicious. Okay, I got it.
- You're being super suspicious.
- What?
You were watching me
from up there. Okay.
It was Kwang Soo.
It's Kwang Soo!
(He shouts it.)
Gosh, Kwang Soo was staring
at my name tag from up there.
(Kwang Soo, whose identity
is unknown, follows Seok JIn.)
Kwang Soo might think
I'm a director.
(If Kwang Soo thinks Suk Jin
is a director and targets him...)
That means...
Could Kwang Soo
be the national actor?
Suk Jin.
Kwang Soo,
are you the national actor?
You're the national actor,
aren't you?
(Nodding)
(Is Kwang Soo really
the national actor?)
Right?
(Kwang Soo
was the national actor.)
I'm just an actor.
I'm nothing special.
Do a good job.
- You should eliminate someone.
- I know.
- You have to.
- Right.
- I will.
- You have to.
Who... You have three chances...
(Just then)
You have three chances...
(Suk Jin's name tag
is ripped off.)
(Kwang Soo eliminates
a director candidate.)
What did you do?
Are you a director?
Are you the national actor?
(What is Suk Jin's identity?)
(Suk Jin is...)
(just an actor.)
Gosh.
(Kwang Soo got
Suk Jin's identity wrong...)
(and eliminated Suk Jin.)
(Then what is Kwang Soo's identity?)
Actor Ji Suk Jin is out.
Who?
(The Director A candidates are
Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and Ji Hyo.)
Suk Jin was an actor?
Suk Jin? Why was he eliminated?
Who eliminated him?
This is crazy.
(Kwang Soo could be either
a director or the national actor.)
(He looks for another hint.)
(Checking)
What?
(He finds a mysterious document.)
(Is there anyone around?)
What is this?
I almost missed it.
- It says, "R".
- What is it?
(Jong Kook finds a document too.)
- It's a scenario.
- "A Hint to You."
(It's titled, "A Hint to You".)
- Is it a scenario?
- It's a scenario.
(The document turns out
to be a scenario.)
Let's check it out.
"Each member, dressed as his
or her role, walks the red carpet."
(The producer
explains today's race.)
(The scenario describes
what they are shooting.)
(Haha and So Min,
the fake directors,)
(look happy
after checking their identities.)
It's Haha.
(Haha plays a director.)
(Haha is a fake director too.)
Look at this. It's Haha.
Haha thought he was a director.
I knew it.
That's why he was acting strange.
My hunch was right.
- He thought he was a director.
- Yes.
Right. Wait.
It was fake?
The video hint was fake.
(The members find
a fake video hint.)
(Running Man's fan-meet, tears)
(That means Ji Hyo.)
(The members believe the fake hint
and suspect regular actors.)
(Because of the fake hint,)
(Ji Hyo was suspected
of being a director.)
(If the hint was fake,
Ji Hyo might not be a director.)
(Haha found the second video hint.)
(This person goes by a stage name.)
(Believing the fake hint,)
(Haha eliminated Tae Oh.)
(If the hint was fake,)
(Yoyomi might not be
the national actor.)
But the hints from the staff
are true, right?
They're true, right?
(Only the written hints are true.)
"The producer informs
the real directors of hidden rules."
"The two real directors..."
"have to eliminate
Haha and So Min..."
"before eliminating
the national actor."
(After the two fake directors
are eliminated,)
(the real directors can
eliminate the national actor.)
(Oh, I see.)
We have to go protect Haha.
Haha is so stupid.
He makes it so obvious.
He loves his role.
Seriously, it's so confusing.
(Haha runs into someone.)
- What is it?
- So Min...
So Min thought she was a director.
What are you?
I am nothing.
You are just the owner
of a barbecue restaurant.
Don't try to fool me.
(Haha, Celebrity and owner
of a barbecue restaurant)
Avoid the others like me.
- You are Yang Se Hyeong's brother.
- That's right.
(Meanwhile,
Hyosung is searching for hints.)
Hold on.
(She finds the real hint.)
(Startled)
(The national actor
is a man in his 30s.)
(If we combine all the hints
on the national actor...)
(The national actor
doesn't have 9 in his age.)
is a man in his 30s...)
(who doesn't have 9 in his age.)
(Then the national actor
candidates are...)
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo.)
(They are also director candidates.)
Let's split. Go away.
I have nowhere to go.
I am nothing.
Do you want me to rip off
your name tag?
(Take this!)
(He ripped off Haha's name tag!)
(Se Chan eliminated Haha
in an instant.)
(Is Se Chan a director?)
This is a big hint.
(Is Kwang Soo a director?)
It will be over once I find him.
(If one is a director,
the other is the national actor.)
What was that?
(Is Se Chan a real director
who eliminated a fake director...)
(or the national actor
who thought Haha was a director?)
(Who is a director
and who is the national actor?)
Haha, an actor who
plays a director is out.
(Haha, an actor who
plays a director is out.)
(No way!)
(She gets goosebumps.)
I got goosebumps.
Who ripped off his name tag?
Did the national actor
think he was a director?
Did a director think...
Come this way.
Did a director think
Haha was the national actor?
(Is it the work of a director
or the national actor?)
This is bad.
(Both fake directors are out!)
(Once the national actor
gets eliminated,)
(Team Directors will win.)
That startled me.
(The two director and national actor
candidates meet.)
(One is the national actor
and the other is a director.)
- Did you find anything?
- No.
Where are you going?
I am going to look for hints.
(Staring)
What?
- Hold on.
- What?
Hold on. It seems like...
- you are trailing me.
- No.
You...
(He follows Se Chan.)
- What?
- You...
(Se Chan, you...)
You have two cameras on you.
(There are two cameras on him.)
- Kwang Soo, I moved up the ranks.
- Hold on.
A lot of people got eliminated.
This is the 1st time in 3 years
for you to have 2 cameras...
on you.
Listen.
A lot of people got eliminated.
They had a cameraman
who had nothing to shoot.
Is it for the online video channel
you run with Se Hyeong?
No, of course not.
No. We don't use
a professional camera.
We use a cellphone.
You used this camera for the video
of you eating pho, right?
No, I didn't.
It's a misunderstanding.
I should write this down.
- What are you writing down?
- "Se Chan has..."
"two cameras on him."
It's not like that.
It's a misunderstanding.
I have an extra camera on me
because many people got eliminated.
Hyosung, Haha is out.
What happened?
(Flustered)
This is so hard.
Now,
I need to find more hints.
(It seems like
she is doing a poor job of acting.)
- That was strange.
- What?
What?
- Hyosung, that was so strange.
- Was it sloppy?
Without moving your feet, you said,
"I need to find more hints."
Hyosung, that was so strange.
I am just beginning
to figure things out.
I need to hurry up.
You aren't the national actor,
are you?
No, I am not.
Why do you keep looking
for the national actor?
(She seems even more suspicious.)
I need to find the national actor
and protect him.
(The national actor
is an important figure.)
(Hyosung is suspicious.)
Something doesn't seem right.
(Could Hyosung be a director?)
(At that moment,)
Hey.
(someone shows up.)
(Jae Suk is happy
to see this person.)
Hey.
(Both of them greet
this mysterious person.)
- Hold on.
- What is going on?
- What...
What is going on?
(Hyosung joins him.)
(A 2-on-1 fight suddenly occurs.)
(Ripping)
Good job.
You jerks!
(Who could be
the mysterious shadow?)
You jerks! You jerks!
(Hyosung worked with this person
to eliminate Jae Suk.)
(What could be her identity?)
You are the directors who
hold a grudge against the actors...
for repeatedly turning down
your childish scripts.
Directors.
Eliminate the national actor
before the race ends...
or keep your identities hidden
until the end in order to win.
The two of you must wait...
until the fake directors
get eliminated...
in order to eliminate
the national actor.
If you eliminate
three actors by mistake,
you will lose and the race will end.
(Hyosung, a director, was looking
for the national actor.)
The national actor.
(I need to find the national actor.)
- Actor Jae Suk is out.
- What?
The race will end in 10 minutes.
We have 10 minutes.
We need to find something...
for the second trial.
(The members aren't certain about
the 2 directors and national actor.)
(The two directors must eliminate
the national actor...)
We don't have much time.
(and the national actor
must eliminate the 2 directors.)
Jong Kook. Jong Kook.
- What?
- Here.
Let's talk for five minutes.
- What?
- You can't rip off his name tag.
- I am not scared.
- Jong Kook, are you scared?
- Then you don't have to come.
- What? I am not scared.
- Then come.
- Sure.
Fine.
You may not believe me,
but I am...
- the national actor.
- Okay.
I thought you would make a move.
It's the right time for it.
Listen.
- People who are cornered do it.
- I will give you...
a reason to trust me.
Hyosung told you earlier...
that Director B is a woman, right?
(Is Director B a woman?)
(Jong Kook heard from Hyosung
that Director B is a woman.)
(The crucial hint
Se Chan claimed to have found)
(Se Chan's claim)
(He says Hyosung is Director B
since she is a female guest.)
Here is the deal.
If I rip off Hyosung's name tag...
and she turns out to be Director B,
please believe me.
I won't play any tricks.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Let's cast the die.
- Come on.
- What a coincidence!
- Jong Kook.
(Hyosung appears
as soon as they finished talking.)
Who is it? Oh, here she comes.
(Isn't the timing too uncanny?)
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Can you help me?
Can you hold her for me?
- The two of them could turn on me.
- It's not like that, Jong Kook.
- When I grab Hyosung,
- Please.
you could suddenly rip off
my name tag.
I can see that happening.
Who is a director?
Come here.
What are you?
I am an actor.
(She feigns innocence.)
(Jong Kook watches.)
- This is driving me crazy.
- We need to survive from them.
- What are you?
- I am an actor.
- You are a director.
You are a director.
- Are we repeating the same words?
- Yes.
- I am an actor.
- Hyosung.
(Se Chan attacks Hyosung.)
(Jong Kook still doesn't move.)
(Se Chan tries to prove
that he is the national actor.)
What is going on?
(Ripping)
Are you the national actor?
(Are you the national actor?)
(It's time to check
Hyosung's identity.)
Let's see it.
- Let's see it.
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, trust me this once.
(Hyosung is...)
(one of the directors.)
(Does that mean
Se Chan is the national actor?)
You trust me now, right?
Her tone...
Hold on. Is he acting?
For goodness' sake.
(Hold on. Is he acting?)
(He can only laugh.)
"Are you the national actor?"
Maybe the two of you planned this.
- Hold on.
- Jong Kook, I am going insane.
She came out of nowhere.
After her name tag got ripped off,
she said,
"Are you the national actor?"
Hold on.
Jong Kook,
don't let Hyosung fool you.
All right.
(Se Chan eliminated Hyosung
before Jong Kook's eyes.)
All right. You should go over there.
Even when I show you proof,
you think I am acting.
(The members are still unsure
about everyone's identity.)
The second trial will begin.
This is getting interesting.
(Both of them are the candidates...)
I have no idea.
(for a director
and the national actor.)
- Yes?
- Kwang Soo.
Yes?
Did you find anything out?
I found out many things.
Just now, I watched...
a very nicely-planned sketch.
(It wasn't a sketch.)
(You are a director.)
(What he showed is believed
to be part of a sketch.)
Sit down.
The second trial will begin now.
Hyosung, who was a real director,
is out.
Ji Hyo.
This is making me talkative.
Listen to me.
I am the one
who eliminated Hyosung.
How did you know?
I found a hint.
"Director B is a guest."
- Did someone see the hint with you?
- Only I saw it.
(Only I saw it.)
That's not how you scam people.
(He suddenly criticizes
Se Chan's scamming skills.)
(The senior member of Running Man
criticizes Se Chan.)
I get that you are desperate,
but that's not how you scam people.
Jong Kook, tell everyone.
Since you didn't believe my words...
I will recount what I saw.
Listen to me.
Se Chan claimed
that he was the national actor...
and asked whether I would trust him
if he eliminated Hyosung...
before my eyes.
I said that he was scheming,
but Se Chan begged me to trust him.
Then out of the blue,
Hyosung walked towards us.
This is driving me crazy.
- What timing!
- This is driving me crazy.
Then the two of them
started talking.
They didn't know the script
very well.
So they didn't make much sense.
You thought that was scripted?
All of a sudden...
I questioned her one last time.
- I tested her.
- Then all of a sudden,
he ripped Hyosung's name tag,
but as soon as he ripped it,
she was like,
"What? Are you the national actor?"
Hey!
(That was bad acting.)
(Hyosung's awkward acting
convinced Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook, if you do this,
you'll hurt many actors.
No, listen to this. Goodness.
I watched...
a very awkward play.
Not even.
What if Hyosung wasn't acting?
She could just be awkward in life.
"Are you the national actor?"...
was because she knew
who the director was.
I have a question.
You knew...
Director A is a Running Man member.
- I know.
- Why didn't you say anything?
Then why didn't you rip Se Chan's
name tag? From the beginning?
You told me
that was the first hint you saw.
Did he say that last?
Because we deduced that...
(Because we deduced that...)
Anyway, when I heard...
(Kwang Soo can't answer properly.)
- when I heard...
- "Anyway?"
(Something's strange.)
it's somebody in their 30s,
I know it's not me so that's when
I started looking for Se Chan.
I don't get it.
Four of you,
please make your decision.
Okay.
Please say it in three.
- Gosh.
- One,
(4 actors will choose a director
by majority vote.)
two,
(Who do the actors think
a director is?)
- three.
- Yang Se Chan.
(Se Chan is their suspect.)
Yang Se Chan. I don't know.
It's strange
how he went and came back.
I know. He kept on leaving.
Jong Kook, rip my name tag.
I want to see your face.
Me? All right.
- Yes.
- I'll do it.
I opened up about everything.
- I...
- Okay.
Look at my face
then look at Kwang Soo's face.
- I'm going to look at you.
- Okay.
Fine. Okay.
- One,
- Let's see.
(If Se Chan is a director,
Team Actors win.)
two,
(What is Se Chan's identity?)
three.
(If Se Chan is a director,
Team Actors win.)
(If he's a national actor,
Team Directors win.)
(What is Se Chan's identity?)
(National actor)
(Se Chan was a national actor!)
Hello.
(Before the start of the show)
What kind of informer role
do you need from me?
- What am I today?
- You are...
a national actor every Korean loves.
(You are a national actor
every Korean loves.)
Are you lying already?
Okay.
(I witnessed it!)
(Haha and Tae Oh were together,)
(but Tae Oh was eliminated.)
(Se Chan heard
Jae Suk's statement.)
(Haha is a director.)
(Se Chan was certain Haha was
a director and eliminated him.)
(He was the national actor
who was looking for the directors.)
(At that moment!)
(Yes!)
(Is he the remaining director?)
National Actor Yang Se Chan
has been eliminated.
- Really?
- Yes!
(The remaining director
was Kwang Soo!)
(I think it's Suk Jin.)
(The fake director)
(He eliminated Suk Jin,
but he was an actor.)
You idiot.
(An actor who plays a director,
Haha, is out.)
How did that happen?
(Actor Haha was out, so he could
eliminate the national actor now.)
(He eliminated Jae Suk who was
closing in on him.)
The winning team of Ggannes
Film Festival: The Uninvited One...
is Team Directors.
(Winners of Ggannes Film Festival:
The Uninvited One: Team Directors)
I was a director all day today.
Team Actors lost the race.
Since there are only
two water cannons,
National Actor Se Chan
has to take one.
You can choose another person
to join you.
It was my mistake, so I'll go.
Let's go together.
(He feels pressured.)
- Hold on.
- He feels bad.
For Jong Kook, the timing was...
- It was my fault.
- perfect.
The person who will stand under
the water cannon with me...
(He chooses the person who'll
receive the penalty with him.)
is Kyung-hwan.
(It's Kyung-hwan.)
Are you crazy? What was that for?
What?
What was that for?
Kyung-hwan,
you need the camera on you.
So you were nothing today,
but you acted that way?
I know! You deserve
the water cannon.
This is nuts.
Why is Kyung-hwan standing there?
(He's getting ready
for the water cannon.)
Kyung-hwan.
You showed your presence
in unique ways today.
We never had a guest like him.
Unfortunately, I joined late,
so I wasn't too funny.
As a penalty,
- That's not true.
- I get the water bucket.
- That's why he's here.
- Then...
Let's go!
(Pouring)
That's cold.
(That was a good one.)
(We would like to thank Kyung-hwan,
Hyosung, Tae Oh, and Yoyomi.)
- That was cold water.
- It's cold.
(That was a refreshing penalty
in the frigid winter.)
(Day in Yeouido when cold weather
warning was in effect)
It finally feels like winter.
We'll start separately today.
- Are we starting?
- Yes.
All eight members will
start separately.
This is the mission.
(All 8 members started
at different locations.)
"Form a team
and come to the opening location."
"4 guests today..."
There are 4 guests?
"Four guests today are captains."
"They'll recruit two people
from Running Man."
"Once you form a team of three,
you will obtain the address."
"The first 2 teams will
receive benefits." Oh, my.
(Form a team of 3 to obtain
the address. 2 teams get benefits.)
So we don't know
who the captains are?
Who's the other member besides me?
Do you not tell us that either?
Who are the guests? Goodness.
Am I the only one who's cold?
It's so cold. This is no joke.
It's freezing.
(Born to be actor, Ahn Jae Hong)
(The lovable actress, Kang Sora,
Rising-star actress, Jeon Yeo Been)
(Kim Sung Oh, an actor
with a distinctive character)
(Casts of "Secret Zoo"...)
(are on Running Man!)
(Ahn Jae Hong captured
the movie scene with his warmth.)
(Kang Sora always shows
new charms.)
(Kim Sung Oh's face and acting are
always memorable.)
(Jeon Yeo Been has a bright future
with her characteristic acting.)
Welcome to Running Man.
We invited you separately
before the opening segment...
because of a special mission
since this is your first time.
Sung Oh, Jae Hong,
Sora, and Yeo Been,
you are captains of each team.
(We're captains?)
You need to pick two people
from the Running Man cast,
pick them up,
and get to the opening location.
Pick them up?
Please pick two members each.
- Let's go.
- Is it a lottery?
- Do we pick 2 each?
- Yes, 2 each.
Pick two.
I'm getting nervous for some reason.
(They carefully check
who their teammates are.)
Why?
I picked somebody reliable.
(Sung Oh's first pick is Jong Kook!)
(The four teams)
Let's start the race now.
(They pick their teams
and start the mission.)
Please give me Ji Hyo's number.
- What?
- Please give me Ji Hyo's number.
- Who do you need to find?
- Ji Hyo.
- Do you have her number?
- She's here.
But I don't know where she is.
- Her car's white.
- Really?
All these cars are white.
Go to the parking lot.
Really? Okay.
Se Chan.
Let me call So Min.
(He shot a commercial with her.)
What? It's Jae Hong.
Jae Hong is calling me. Jae Hong.
(Why is she so happy it's Jae Hong?)
Date for a day.
(Jae Hong is...)
(her ideal type.)
(Her ideal type is
finally on Running Man!)
(She is excited
to receive a call from him.)
- Hello.
Are you visiting the show today?
(She uses her cute tone.)
Hello, So Min.
(Hello, So Min.)
What is going on?
Are you coming? Are you a guest?
Yes.
My goodness.
Are you on my team?
Yes. Where are you? We need to meet.
I am at the Han River parking lot.
Who else is on our team?
Yang Se Chan.
(He tries to get
Se Chan's phone number.)
Are you near Yeouido Park?
It's not far from here.
- I will give you his number.
- Okay.
I will text you.
(He adapted to Running Man
as soon as he arrived.)
Hello.
Who is this?
Hello, Se Chan.
I am Ahn Jae Hong.
Stop lying. Who are you?
I am not lying.
- Is it really you?
- Yes, it is.
My goodness, hello.
Hello. Have you been well?
You and I are on the same team.
You are cold, right?
You don't sound like
you are in a hurry.
It's as if you aren't
a fellow team member.
(Distrust is prevalent
on this show.)
- You should be in a hurry.
- I am remaining calm...
in order to be dependable.
I will put my trust in you
and wait here.
Okay. Don't tell So Min.
We are on the same team, Se Chan.
- You have to trust me.
- I trust you.
(Sora got Kwang Soo's number
from a friend.)
Hello.
- My name is Kang Sora.
- What?
I became a captain.
- Where are you?
- You are Kang Sora.
I need to go to you.
I am at Exit Five
of Yeouido Park Station.
Exit Five of Yeouido Park Station?
Whether you are the captain or not,
I will get on the van.
Okay.
- If this is a lie,
- Okay.
I will be brokenhearted.
It's real.
I need to pick up
you and Jae Suk...
and go to the opening.
I will send you his number.
- Okay.
This is fun.
I didn't get any sleep yesterday,
but it's fun being here.
(Sung Oh, the variety show newbie,
is excited.)
(To get his team members'
phone numbers,)
(he calls his acquaintance, Ji Hyo.)
The number you have dialed
is unavailable.
Is she not picking up on purpose?
(No way.)
I feel like
people are scheming already.
Then...
(He becomes nervous.)
(He has no choice
but to call Jae Hong.)
Jae Hong.
Did you meet your team members?
I am almost done now.
You told Jae Suk
that he is on your team.
(What?)
- Me?
- Yes.
That's what he said.
(He throws another lie.)
I can't do this.
Everyone lies.
I don't know.
I haven't found anyone yet.
I don't think
I will be able to star on the show.
The shoot will end
before I find anyone.
Please give me So Min's number.
I need to meet my team members.
I just got on the van.
So Min.
(Hanging up)
This is unbelievable.
Is this how it usually goes?
(It's a culture shock.)
He just hung up!
(Rummaging)
Entertainment...
YES IM...
(He searches the web and calls
the team members' agencies.)
- It's a weekday, right?
- Yes, it is.
Why is no one picking up?
I called So Min's agency,
but no one is picking up. It's 10am.
(He is the 1st guest to call
the members' agencies.)
(While Sung Oh searches
for their phone numbers,)
(Jong Kook waits for the captain.)
It's so strange
that no one is calling me.
(Why is no one calling me?)
Who on earth is the captain?
For goodness' sake.
I am beginning to get angry.
Everyone got a call except for me.
Unbelievable.
(Will Sung Oh's team be able
to meet?)
(Jae Suk calls someone.)
She picked up right away.
Hello.
The flowers sway
(So Min sings
Jae Hong's theme song in a drama.)
So Min.
You aren't in a drama with Jae Hong.
Jae Suk, there is
an unwanted member between us.
- Who is it?
- Se Chan.
(Her former love interest became
someone she wants to eliminate.)
This is interesting.
Sorry, Jae Suk. I have to go.
Where are you going?
For goodness' sake.
(She left to find love.)
So Min is so annoying.
So Min, where are you?
I am...
in front of the convenience store.
Are you here?
- I am nearly there.
- Okay.
I will go to greet you.
Are you nearly here?
Oh, that must be your van.
Jae Hong!
Oh, that must be your van. Jae Hong!
I am here. Hurry up.
Jae Hong.
I will go to you. Wait.
I will go to you.
Jae Hong, I will go to you.
Have you been well?
It's good to see you.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
How did this happen?
Seriously.
Thank goodness you knew my number.
- If the guest...
- Seriously.
- didn't know my number...
- It's cold, right?
Let's go.
Do you want to go in first?
Have you been well?
Yes. My goodness.
The flowers sway
And I smell your shampoo
- My goodness.
- It's good to see you here.
Seriously.
All the guests had a lottery...
- and I got you and Se Chan.
- He is useless.
We need to go right away...
- to get a priority.
- Let's go.
That fool...
is going to Kwang Soo.
He doesn't know he is on our team.
- Really?
- Yes.
Let me call him.
Who is Kwang Soo's captain?
Hello.
- Kwang Soo.
- Hey.
You and I are on the same team.
(Hanging up)
(The line is dead.)
He has no trust in you.
She keeps getting worse.
It might as well be a condition.
Hello.
Sora, I will send you
Se Chan's number.
Please tell Se Chan
that he is on our team.
Okay.
Did you understand my words?
Yes.
- Okay.
- Should I pick up Se Chan as well?
We will lie to Se Chan
about being on our team...
so that his team will arrive late.
Jae Suk and I are
in your team, right?
That's right.
Okay.
(Did she really understand?)
I will be on my phone all day long.
Hold on.
What is this?
Hello.
Gosh, everyone is playing tricks.
All the captains are tricksters.
Who is this?
My name is Kang Sora.
I don't know
if I should believe you.
I got your phone number only now.
The line was busy too.
I am sorry, but it sounds like
you are acting.
You are trying to trick me.
Are you really a captain?
Yes.
- Okay. Then I will be on my way.
- Okay.
- Call me.
Please wait a bit longer.
- Okay.
The captains are dirty.
For goodness' sake.
Yeouido Park?
I will run to Yeouido Park.
The statue...
Yeo Been!
Where is she?
Yeo Been, I am here.
(The first meeting
between a captain and a team member)
(Suddenly, Haha enters.)
My goodness.
(An uninvited guest appears.)
Thank goodness.
- Thank goodness.
No.
- Let's go.
- You're not on my team.
Why not?
(Aren't you my captain?)
- You're not on my team.
- Why not?
- Let's go.
- Let's hurry up.
Haha, I am sorry.
Sir, please get out.
If you get out...
(He tries to steal the van.)
I will drive.
(He is the politest car thief.)
Stay in the van.
- No.
- I will drive you there.
- Sir.
- No, no.
- No.
- Sir.
- No, no.
- No.
- All right. Let's go.
I will drive you there.
- What are you doing?
- I will drive you there.
- Go away!
- Yeo Been, it's nice to meet you.
You keep threatening me,
- but I can do the same.
- Okay.
If you keep threatening me,
- I will drive to Sokcho.
- We didn't...
- We understand.
- Okay?
- We didn't say anything.
- Do you want to eat mulhoe...
- at Sokcho?
- No, no.
You don't need to drive to Sokcho.
You know that I am a man of action.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is waiting
for Se Chan.)
Hey.
Where are you?
Kwang Soo,
you know the opening location
of "2 Days 1 Night", right?
Do you think it would be a good idea
for us to go there?
Don't you know the opening location
of "2 Days 1 Night"?
I know, but...
How do you know it?
- What?
- Do you watch "2 Days 1 Night"?
It's not like that.
- A long time ago...
- I don't know where it is.
My head is filled
with the locations of Running Man.
I have an incoming call
from the captain.
- Hurry up and come here.
- Okay.
(When will Sora get here?)
Hello.
Where are you?
I am trying
to pick up Jae Suk first.
But the Han River Park is
so big that...
What do you see?
I am at Yeouido Park,
not the Han River Park.
- Yeouido Park?
- Yes.
I specifically asked you
if you understood what I had said.
- That's right.
- You keep saying that.
But I never mentioned
the Han River Park.
(I told you that
I'm at Yeouido Park so many times.)
- I will meet up with Se Chan.
- Okay.
What? Is that Ji Hyo?
(Yeo Been and Ji Hyo run
toward his direction.)
(They ignore Kwang Soo.)
- Yeo Been!
- Kwang Soo, hello.
Hey, you...
How could you go
without stopping to say hello?
What is going on?
(They run past Kwang Soo
and get on his van.)
- Let's go.
- Hurry up and get in.
Hurry up and get in.
(Captain Yeo Been and Ji Hyo
get into Kwang Soo's van.)
So this is how it works.
(Kwang Soo's van door closes.)
- Lock the door.
- Close the door. Hurry up.
- What's going on?
- Close the door.
- What's wrong?
What?
Why did they get in my van?
Please take us to exit nine.
Kwang Soo.
(Se Chan came for Kwang Soo.)
- Hey.
- I'll pick up Jae Suk first.
Lower your voice.
I'm talking to Se Chan.
I just...
(Se Chan is confused
because Jae Hong called him.)
- Ahn Jae Hong.
- He called me too.
Hang up.
Se Chan, he's trying to trick you.
- Is it Sora?
- Hang up. Yes.
- But this...
- You got your van stolen.
If you don't meet your captain
and fall behind,
you have to walk
to the opening location.
- Why doesn't he have a van?
- Just now,
Ji Hyo and Yeo Been took his van.
They have our van?
Shouldn't I report this
to the police?
That's not fair.
- Hold on.
- Who is it?
Hello. Se Chan.
(Sora met up with Jae Suk.
She's calling Kwang Soo now.)
- Hello?
- Where are you now?
I'm leaving now.
You said we're on the same team
as Se Chan.
- What?
- Is it the three of us?
No, I picked up Jae Suk.
(She's clueless.)
(But Se Chan...)
Are we on Jae Suk's team?
Who's on our side?
I told you multiple times.
(He's flustered.)
Hello?
(You have to trick Se Chan.)
I just... This is driving me nuts.
Excuse me, Sora.
I'm Se Chan.
I thought we were on the same team.
Forget it.
What did you do?
Forget it. We're going to go first.
Put Kwang Soo on the phone.
Sora.
How many times did I ask you
if you understood me?
(What?)
(While Se Chan wasn't paying
attention, he stole the phone.)
Give it back.
I have to get going. Don't go.
I stole Se Chan's phone.
I'm running away.
Give me my phone back!
I can't go without it.
I'm sorry, Se Chan!
(He's a nice thief.)
I'm sorry!
We can't even be aired. We're going
back and forth in front of KBS.
We won't be aired.
(Se Chan lost his phone
and his team.)
Goodness, Kwang Soo.
Where is Se Chan?
We have to pick him up, right?
- We just have to pick him up.
- Then we're done.
Gosh, you brought luck.
- I know.
- Things are going smoothly.
(Sorry, So Min.)
(Jae Hong is calling Se Chan.)
Where are you? Hurry up.
- We're in front of the banner.
- Hangang Park.
- I'm at Hangang Park.
- Hurry up. Run.
Hangang Park.
- Run.
- Where is he?
- Hangang Park.
- Everybody met up.
We have to hurry.
I'm at Hangang Park.
Why aren't you talking?
Hangang Park.
Why are you at Hangang Park?
(Se Chan was walking.)
I think that's our van.
- Come here.
- Why aren't you talking?
(She was talking
to the fake Se Chan.)
Why are you at Hangang Park?
(The real Se Chan is here.)
I'll just get on.
Se Chan!
Who is it?
Jae Suk!
(Devil's advocate)
Hurry!
What's going on?
Where are you going?
Kwang Soo stole...
my phone, so I fell behind.
- Where?
- Hurry. This way.
- Am I on your team?
- Yes.
- Really?
- We were looking for you.
- Really? Are you sure?
- Hurry.
Hurry up.
You're not supposed to be there.
We're by the main building of KBS.
Come to
the National Assembly Building.
This is Kwang Soo, right?
You're Kwang Soo, right?
Where's Se Chan? Hurry up.
We were looking for you.
You don't have a phone.
- Kwang Soo took mine.
- What a huge relief.
- Where are we going?
- Come this way. Get on.
- Who is it?
- Why don't you have a phone?
- Were you serious?
- Yes.
Get in the back.
Goodness.
We looked for a long time.
- Sora, you were serious. Hi.
- Hurry up.
- What was that?
- Kwang Soo...
stole my phone.
What's wrong with him?
- Are we really on the same team?
- Yes.
Really?
You didn't have a phone,
so we looked for a long time.
Jae Suk, I...
Now,
we have a team, so let's go.
Are we good then?
- Yes, it's you, me, and Sora.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo.
He didn't trust Sora,
so he said he's on her team.
He snatched my phone
and went to meet up with her.
Where are you?
I'm...
at Yeouido Park by exit six.
It's not there.
We're by the main building of KBS.
We're by the main building.
Come this way.
Hurry up.
How did you get your phone stolen?
He was talking to you.
I had it, but he snatched it.
- Hold on, Jae Suk.
- What?
Sora,
we have our team. Look.
We have to go to
our destination then.
We have to take your phone.
We have to communicate through this.
Why do we need to?
There are three of us.
- That's true, but...
- We have to meet again.
Hold on, Jae Suk.
I'm not on this team, right?
(Se Chan is smarter than
they think.)
(She blocks his way.)
Move. Move!
You bad people! Move.
Sora, gosh.
You too. Kwang Soo.
Move.
Stay in our van.
(He loses time but escapes.)
(Grabbing)
Get out.
(They almost tricked him.)
- My time!
- Se Chan.
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
My gosh.
(We should have held
onto him longer.)
We should have gone.
Where are you?
- I'm...
- Who is it?
Se Chan.
- Hey!
- I'm...
(They see Suk Jin passing by.)
Se Chan.
I'll get him.
Suk Jin!
(Crying)
- Who is it?
- Hurry up.
Where are you?
I was waiting for you. Hurry up.
- Is it you?
- Yes.
No, I'm on Jae Hong's team.
You're not on his team.
- Really?
- We kept on looking for you.
Sora?
Yes, get on.
- Jae Hong said...
- Get in the back. Let's go.
Jae Hong said...
- You're not on his team.
- I have to meet him.
You're not on Jae Hong's team.
It's Sora, me, and you.
What are you talking about?
- Really?
- Yes.
Why didn't you call me then?
This is so chaotic.
I don't think I'm on this team.
You are.
- I don't think I'm on this team.
- Let's get going.
- I'm not on this team.
- Let's go.
Put your seat belt on.
Why are you not happy to see him?
He's on our team.
(I can't do this.)
- Excuse me.
- Sora.
- I'm not.
- He's on our team.
He's on our team.
Why aren't you happy to see him?
- I'm not on your team.
- I was startled.
We're on the same team.
Why aren't you happy to see him?
Move.
I can tell from her face!
Move!
- It's obvious.
- Goodness.
Sora can't lie.
Move. I'm not on this team.
Hey.
Sora.
Why are you doing this?
Why is everybody...
(Se Chan is still by KBS.)
Why is everybody trying to get me?
Here. Se Chan! Run!
It's here!
Se Chan!
Yang Se Chan!
I'm at Yeouido Park by exit six.
Run.
Where are you?
- He got his phone stolen?
- Yes.
He got it stolen.
- Why did you get your phone stolen?
- We waited for you. Let's go.
- Let's get going.
- Jae Suk held me.
- I got everything stolen.
- Hurry up.
- Hurry. We're ready.
- There was bloodshed.
- Hurry up.
Get in.
Hurry.
We have to get going. We might lose.
(If this was the team, they would
get told the destination.)
Where do we need to go?
Should we pick up Haha too?
Let's go somewhere else.
I want to say hi to him.
We're not a team then.
- What? I'm not on this team?
- Are we not?
Jae Hong, if I'm not on this team,
I'd be very disappointed.
Jae Hong, I have a reason now.
I can beat somebody up now.
I have a reason to beat somebody up.
I'm going to beat somebody up.
- You have to trust me.
- Who?
- You?
- Me.
Really? Is Haha on our team?
(Meanwhile, Sung Oh is...)
We'll be done
by the time I find them.
Should we go eat?
(He couldn't reach anybody,
so he had almost given up.)
There he is.
- We're coming.
- Jae Hong.
- Yes? Where are you?
- Brace yourself.
- I will.
- Can you stop here?
(He finally got a chance to talk
after an hour.)
- Goodness.
- Where?
Hello.
Hold on. What's going on?
- Hello.
- Hold on.
- I have to find people.
- What happened?
I couldn't find you.
Who's on your team?
Your team.
You two.
- Are you sure?
- Don't do that.
- Are you serious?
- This is driving me nuts.
I don't think I can do this.
(He's exhausted.)
I woke up at 5 a.m.
Everybody's lying.
- Is this real TV?
- No, so...
- You have to be somewhat truthful.
- But then...
Nobody trusts me
or answers my calls.
- What's this now?
- Fine.
We sometimes...
don't trust the guests,
but I can't trust you even more.
(He always plays the villain.)
I'm leaving.
- This doesn't make sense.
- That's not why. Listen.
- Wait. He's calling again.
- I thought it was going to be easy.
Look. I looked you up
on the internet.
You can't find my number online.
- I was looking up your agency.
- My agency.
I called your agency,
but why aren't they picking up?
- You called my agency.
- It's 10 a.m. on a weekday.
- Why aren't they working?
- You called my agency?
- Convince me.
- Hold on.
- I have Jae Hong on the phone.
- Listen.
- I figured it out too.
- Talk to him.
- Jae Hong.
- Yes. Where are you?
Hey, let's not do this.
- No one believes me. Seriously.
- Wait. Hey.
Hey, let's not do this.
My head hurts too.
It's too early in the morning.
I admit that I do lie a lot.
But no one will believe me.
Nothing will come of this.
- Let me.
- I don't care if I place last.
- Hello.
- Jae Hong.
- That's Sung Oh.
- Hello, I'm the chief producer.
(Hello, I'm the chief producer.)
- Who?
- It's Se Chan.
You scumbag. That's enough!
(Haha gives Se Chan
New Year's words of blessings.)
Don't curse at me.
I'm frustrated too.
Where are you? Let's meet.
He's trying to buy time.
Right.
Jae Hong is trying to buy time.
- That's that.
- Who are on your team?
You always play this,
so there's no reason to go all out.
But why is everyone lying?
- It's not that.
- What?
Let's get in.
I mean,
you should have called me sooner.
We were wondering
why our captain wasn't calling us.
All right.
The three of you are here,
- but I cannot give you the address.
- Come on. Unbelievable.
- I can't believe him.
- Why are you doing this?
(His anger has dissipated now.)
(As they figure out that he lied,
he becomes an innocent lamb.)
When I spotted you two...
- He's unbelievable.
- Listen.
Both of you...
- This...
- Wait.
- This is...
- I don't get it.
Who's on your team?
- I'll be honest.
- Who is it?
- Sung Oh.
- I'll really be honest.
Turn off the camera.
- We can't turn that off.
You and I are on the same team.
And we need to find So Min.
- Really? Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
Hold on. Wait!
- Hold on a second.
- Stay here.
Okay. You might run away. Wait.
We need to keep a member
that's not on our team.
- What are you doing?
- I get it.
- What is this?
- Don't move.
That's right.
Jae Suk!
(Meanwhile, other teams...)
- Come quickly.
- Hurry.
- Let's go.
- Gosh, Se Chan.
I have Se Chan's phone.
- Nice to meet you.
- Sora.
- It's crazy, right?
- Things are so hectic.
- This is so exhausting. Hello.
- Goodness.
- All three of you are here.
- Okay.
- You can go to this address.
- That's SBS.
- You know where it is, right?
Yes, it's SBS.
See? You were with us. I told you.
- Right.
- See?
- I'm sorry.
- You were with us.
Hold on.
- Yes.
- Where are you?
Tell So Min...
I don't know.
I'm done with today's filming.
(He's totally exhausted.)
- I'm done with today's filming.
- Why all of a sudden?
- He's angry.
- Sung Oh, where are you?
Gosh, there's a limit.
No one told me what to do.
Sung Oh.
- Hello?
- Right away?
You must be very upset.
I'm the writer of the show.
I see. Hello.
(Suddenly acting polite)
Things have gotten slightly mixed
up here. Who's on your team?
- My team?
- Yes.
Jae Hong will know.
Hold on.
Hello?
See? Everyone on the show is weird.
Wait, I see someone.
Hey, Se Chan got off.
Where?
Can't you bring my phone?
I don't even think I'm on his team.
- Isn't that So Min?
- Right.
- I can just bring her here, right?
- Yes.
Hey, So Min! Come over here!
- Come here. Hi.
- Hello.
Jong Kook. Hello.
- You're on my team. Come here.
- I am?
- No.
- The three of us.
- Hello.
- I'm on Jae Hong's team.
We're on the same team.
The three of us.
So Min. The three of us...
Hey, Haha is running away
through the trunk.
- Hey, the trunk won't open.
- Hold on a second.
- Hey, get in.
- I'm on Jae Hong's team.
I'm on Jae Hong's team.
- Hey.
- I'm on Jae Hong's team.
(Haha manages to escape.)
- Where's Jae Hong?
- Let's hurry!
Let's hurry.
- Haha.
- Right here.
- Hurry.
- All right.
(The 3 members of Team Jae Hong
meet after a long chase.)
- Is this our team?
- Yes.
- Your team has been formed.
- Hurry.
- Hurry!
- Yes!
Get in. Everyone is leaving now!
- Jae Hong said I was on his team.
- You idiot.
You idiot.
- Darn it. Hurry. Sung Oh, come.
- What's going on?
Wait, he and I aren't
on the same team?
He totally fooled you.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
- He said I was on his team.
- You should've answered your phone.
- Goodness.
- Listen.
Just because he said so,
you're on his team?
He's not the type to lie.
Ridiculous.
Your agency
won't pick up their phone.
Why did you keep calling
the agencies?
- I don't know your phone numbers.
- If you called them in the morning,
who would give you our numbers?
(Which team will win the race?)
(Humans have one strong instinct.)
(This instinct always rules over
humans wherever and whenever.)
(Their instinct to survive)
(Humans struggle to survive
even in extreme situations.)
(However,)
(there's the Grim Reaper
who is jealous of human life.)
(They cannot find out
its shape, smell, or sound.)
(They will only hear
people's screams.)
(At that moment,
a piece of truth is discovered.)
Hold on. Are you all Grim Reapers?
(There are more Grim Reapers now.)
Be careful!
(The survival mystery thriller
between two worlds in 2020)
(If they can't get away
from the Grim Reapers,)
(a tragedy awaits the humans.)
(If you want to survive as a human,
use every means possible.)
(Is your survival instinct intact?)
(We Won't Harm You)