(One winter day when you want to listen to ballad songs)
(There's Running Apartment in a quiet place.)
(And the residents of Running Apartment)
Hey, good morning.
Hello.
(1st floor: Haha, Ji Hyo)
It's been a while.
(2nd floor: Jong Kook, Jae Suk, So Min)
- Okay. - Hello.
(The residents of Running Apartment are having a neighborhood meeting.)
- My gosh. - You all are here.
- Hello. - Hello.
(They start gathering in the meeting place one by one.)
(He says hello in a hoarse voice.)
Nice to meet you.
Is that how a laughter therapist talks?
(What's their theme?)
- He sounds like... - Hello.
(HaHa: Unit 101, laughter therapist, Se Chan: Unit 310, magician)
(Kwang Soo: Unit 306, bar exam taker)
- He sounds like... - Hello.
(He's full of laughter energy.)
Clapping hands is good for your health.
(They greet each other with a clap.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Next is...)
She's a simultaneous interpreter?
(Chuckling)
(So Min: Unit 208, poet)
(Ji Hyo: Unit 103, simultaneous interpreter)
- Am I a poet? - She's a simultaneous interpreter?
(A simultaneous interpreter doesn't match her real-life personality.)
It's hilarious.
Ladies and gentlemen. Please translate it.
Hello, everyone.
Is that right?
(She can't even interpret a 6th-grader vocabulary.)
Isn't this modernized hanbok?
Are you a laughter therapist?
(Jeon So Min, poet)
- Why is he a laughter therapist? - I have no idea.
You should treat me.
- I have to treat myself first. - Treat me.
- Okay. - He's a bully.
- What? - He's a bully.
He's a bully.
(Backing up)
- Are you sure you're a trainer? - This is real.
(He's in charge of security and conflict in the apartment.)
- He's here to work out. - He's a real trainer.
(Jong Kook: Unit 205, health trainer)
What is Jae Suk?
(Next is...)
- What? - It's Hurricane Blue.
Hurricane Blue.
(He's full of rock spirit in a leather jacket.)
Come here.
Jae Suk seems familiar, but I don't remember where I saw him.
(Jae Suk, Unit 207, indie band rocker)
Who are you guys?
(Immersed)
This is how he talks when he's wearing a wig.
- He speaks like that in a wig. - It looks great on you.
(His speech changes for the skit as he puts on the wig.)
- It's a habit. - He looks good.
- I look good, don't I? - It's not strange at all.
- It just feels natural. - I've seen a guy like him.
I'm a little sensitive because of my music. Don't get on my nerves.
(The musician in the room doesn't feel out of place at all.)
- Really? - You write your songs.
I'm working on my new song, but it's not going well.
Do you want me to make you wail instead?
(He wants to help Jae Suk find his own voice.)
- What? - Instead of singing.
What is this guy up to?
(They yell at each other even before the meeting begins.)
You're working on your new song.
Are you a bully or something?
(Writing)
- What's that? - I'm a poet.
Really?
"Music is magic."
(The poet hands a note over to him.)
- Gosh. She's a poet. - I'm...
- I just... - So she just wrote a poem.
- Really? - She wrote about music.
"Music is magic."
(To the rocker, music is magic.)
And she wrote this for the interpreter.
"Translate my heart."
(To the interpreter, translate my heart.)
- That's good. - She's a crazy poet.
Yali yali yala sheong.
"Yali yali yala sheong"?
- What about a trainer? - Isn't "Yali yali yala sheong"...
- a folk song from Goryeo? - Anything for a trainer?
- For a trainer? - Yes.
(The poet writes a phrase for the trainer right away.)
Like "You're a trainer of love"?
"I hope I could build up muscles in my heart too."
(To the health trainer)
(It seems like he's talking about pec muscles.)
"I can help you grow muscles that withstand breakups."
They're good, but they sound like...
I've heard them before from somewhere.
Abracadabra, that's nice!
They're something that I wrote just now.
(Something that they would regret the next day after posting online)
"Grow me muscles that help me withstand breakups."
(Satisfied with what he said)
My goodness.
- The wig is so uncomfortable. - Wait a minute.
(But surprisingly,)
- Did you write this? No, right? - No.
(they still haven't noticed Suk Jin's absence.)
- There are many sitting mats. - This is so funny.
How many sitting mats are there?
(No one notices it for 10 minutes.)
I guess we have many guests today.
- Se Chan. - Yes.
(Are we having many guests today?)
Se Chan, do you know who'll be here today?
(When no one's interested,)
- Goodness. - Gosh, Suk Jin's here.
(Suk Jin enters.)
- Good morning. - Suk Jin!
- Goodness. - Gosh, Suk Jin's here.
(Embarrassed)
- Are you a taxi driver? - Who are you supposed to be?
(Suk Jin wearing a silk shirt joins the group too late.)
- Taxi driver. - Who's he supposed to be?
Excuse me!
- Who do you think I am? - Genie?
(What's his identity?)
Are you a recreation instructor?
(Today's host, Ji Seok Genie)
Excuse me!
- Genie? - Who do you think I am?
- He's "Genie". - Oh, Genie?
(Ji Hyo is a huge fan of Genie.)
He's Genie.
I see. He's Genie.
Hello, everyone.
(Bowing)
- So you... - Wait.
- You should cover yourself. - What? Why?
- This is in style now. - But...
(Two peaks stand out.)
I can see things through your shirt.
Then cover them with something.
(They're jutted out through the thin silk shirt.)
- I'm fine. - You can see Genie's things too.
- Genie is always like that. - Then cover them with something.
(He even depicted the physical details.)
Yes, he's always topless.
- Why don't you use these to... - Don't do that.
- Cover them with the Post-its. - Don't.
But if you want me to, then I will.
(It looks like he's playing a certain role.)
- As you know, I'm your servant. - Yes.
(He's dealing with 7 people without being able to introduce himself.)
- Put them inside. - All right.
You want me to put them in here?
Genie, I want to watch SBS.
- SBS? - He's not that Genie.
- Not that Genie. - No, he's not.
- Genie! - Turn on "Banana Chacha"!
(Ji Seok Genie isn't that kind of Genie.)
All right. How this?
I can still see them through the Post-it!
Where?
- Post-its won't cover them. - Don't...
Everyone.
(Its presence penetrates the sticky note and the shirt.)
Don't focus on things like this.
- But I can see them. - Don't.
I can clearly see them.
Suk Jin's sweating. He's nervous.
(The opening isn't going as Genie had hoped.)
It's because the shirt is too small for me.
But everyone, just don't look at them.
- How can we not notice them? - I mean,
- they're looking at us! - That's right.
- They're very noticeable. - Don't mind them.
(Sharing a look without intention)
So let's start this.
I'm the manager of this apartment.
(Ji Seok Genie is today's host and the apartment's manager.)
Yes, so if there are any requests,
(I'm here for all of your complaints, dear residents.)
- This is an apartment? - please let me know.
- My goodness. - Look at Suk Jin's face.
- He's overwhelmed by pressure. - I know.
I think he didn't get enough sleep last night.
(He's had a rough night thinking about hosting and being the Genie.)
Yes, he said he didn't sleep well.
- So he's hosting it today. - Yes.
No wonder.
This morning, he screamed when he got out of the car,
"I can do this, I can do this!"
So that was why you did it. Because you had a big mission.
(He tried mind control secretly before an important mission.)
You lie so well that it seems like it's true.
(Ji Seok Genie)
So today, we're gathered here...
(Barely getting through his words)
- because... - How many times are you saying it?
Wait a minute.
You be quiet!
- Ji Hyo finds this fun. - Sure.
- Are you having fun? - Yes, this is fun.
(The interpreter likes Ji Seok Genie.)
- All right. - You're doing great.
Three writers are sitting there...
- biting their nails right now. - All right.
- They're regretting it. - So today,
(3 writers have half fingernails left due to the slow opening.)
you can tell me anything if you have any requests.
(He finally explained his role after 10 minutes of appearance.)
- Is that so? - Yes, I will fix it for you.
So should I call you Ji Seok Genie?
(Scary)
You can call me either Genie or Ji Seok Genie.
Why don't you practice? 1, 2, 3!
(Shall we all call it out?)
- Ji Seok Genie! - That's not it.
(Grumbling)
Why aren't you saying it?
That's too old-fashioned.
What are you going to do about it?
- Gosh. - This is getting boring.
(Genie cures insomnia.)
- Catch the mouse. - Catch the mouse.
(The old-fashioned hosting method reminds them of...)
- Squeak, squeak, squeak. - Squeak, squeak, squeak.
- Catch the mouse. - Catch the mouse.
How many mice?
Three mice.
(Genie was a host of a popular show on KBS 15 years ago.)
I got them.
(He's Ji Seok Genie now, but he was the best MC in the old days.)
- How many mice? - Three mice!
Three mice.
(The rhythm reminds him of his best days,)
- I got them. - I lost them.
It feels good to see you play along so well.
(and he's pleased.)
Yes, he was good in the old days.
That's right. I was a famous MC in the old days.
(Ji Seok Genie sticks to his old hosting method for 15 years.)
So we're all here today...
(The reason the meeting is held...)
because we have to welcome some new residents.
(is to welcome the new residents.)
Let me introduce them to you.
Here are our new residents. Please come out!
(Who are the new tenants of Running Apartment?)
- Here he is. - My goodness.
- Hey. - Jin Wook!
(Lee Jin Wook, Unit 206, detective)
My goodness.
- It's Jin Wook. - Hello, Jin Wook.
(Followed by Jin Wook is...)
Hey, Song Kang!
(Song Kang, Unit 210, a would-be actor)
- Gosh. - You're here again.
- Si Young, long time no see. - Back then...
- Do Hyun. - Hello.
(Lee Do Hyun, Unit 305, Lee Si Young, Unit 309)
- He's alive. - What on earth is going on?
(Four lead actors of "Sweet Home"...)
They're becoming monsters.
(to be released on Netflix on December 18th)
They're only monsters.
(A thriller with fresh material and shocking visuals...)
(about people isolated in an apartment against monsters)
My goodness, Jin Wook.
(It's good to see you, Jin Wook!)
So you moved in here?
- It's good to see you. - Here.
Thank you.
They're giving us rice cake.
- Gosh. - Have some.
(As soon as he sees Si Young,)
(the frivolous boxer starts shadowboxing.)
- Stop it. - Why?
Stop it and have a seat.
(Let me host the show.)
- Gosh, Si Young. - Sit down.
You're supposed to do this when you see Si Young.
(He'll be knocked out if she really fights him.)
- Just stop it. - Why?
You two should stand here since you're wearing the same sweats.
(Do Hyun.)
Gosh, you're a bar exam taker also?
- Why are we dressed up... - What is this?
Why are we dressed up the same?
They're both exam takers, but they look so different.
You can compare the two.
Do Hyun looks great.
(Appearances are relatively evaluated.)
- He really looks like one. - Yes, he looks real.
How am I different from him?
Everyone, these are our new residents.
(The new residents also join the Running Apartment meeting.)
Please give them a big hand.
(Welcome to our apartment!)
He's a bar exam taker.
Now they'll introduce themselves.
Starting from Jin Wook.
(They'll take turns to introduce themselves.)
I live in Unit 206.
I'm a detective, and my name is Lee Jin Wook.
- A detective? - He's a detective.
I haven't seen Jin Wook for a long time.
- Yes, he's right. - That's not it.
(Jin Wook hasn't been on a variety show for a long time.)
He's on our show for the first time.
(It's his first appearance on Running Man!)
Back when I...
It's the first time I've seen him since "Family Outing".
(Jin Wook from 12 years ago)
Yes, he was on "Family Outing" 12 years ago.
- 12 years ago. - It's been so long.
- Yes, it's been a long time. - Hello.
I live in Unit 210.
I'm an actor trainee, and my name is Song Kang.
Gosh, he's handsome.
Yes, Song Kang.
(Peeking)
So Min's looking at him like she's interested.
Actually, we've met before.
(The Love Frog takes another look at the familiar face.)
- Yes, on "Village Survival". - Right, on "Village Survival".
- Lee Si Young. - Hello, guys.
(Now the owner of the building, Si Young, will say hello.)
Hello, guys. I live on the top floor.
Why are you speaking casually?
(The bar exam taker is flustered by her using the non-honorific.)
- She's the landlady. - She is?
I should keep my eyes on him.
(Kwang Soo)
Aren't you a boxing trainer?
No, I'm the landlady.
Come on, you're a boxer.
Gosh, you'll get beaten up.
(Acting up)
Stop provoking her.
- Stop it. - What's wrong with him?
(The frivolous boxer keeps acting up in front of her.)
But I've seen her boxing.
No, she's the landlady.
(The owner of the building also introduced herself.)
- She's the owner of this building. - I see.
- I should suck up to her. - Do Hyun, you're next.
Hello, I live in Unit 305. I'm Lee Do Hyun, and I'm an exam taker.
- His voice is... - I know him very well.
- He has a great voice. - As you all know,
(I'm back!)
Running Man raised Do Hyun.
You're right.
I'm right, aren't I? What do you think, Do Hyun?
(They want to brag about him at any time.)
- Aren't I right, Do Hyun? - Yes, it's true.
We raised Do Hyun ourselves.
(Taking the credit)
- We did. - Yes, we did.
(We understand how they want to take credit for raising him right,)
(but the truth is, Do Hyun raised himself well!)
My girlfriend is Se Chan's girlfriend.
- We love you, ma'am. - I love you, Mom.
We raised Do Hyun.
And we took care of Suk Jin with fake nipples since infancy.
Yes, we changed his diapers too.
Right, we did.
I joined you as an adult.
- What are you talking about? - I was an adult.
(Ji-rasoni grew along with Running Man.)
- Nipple Genie. Nipple Genie. - Nipple Genie. Nipple Genie.
(As they pay much attention,)
(he dances along.)
- He loves it. - He does.
(Smiling after getting more airtime)
- He's excited. - Just call me Genie.
He's Nipple Genie.
Jin Wook, how does it feel to be on our show for the first time?
(Getting confident)
- How do you... - What?
(What?)
- Your way of hosting is old! - Why? What did I do?
(He skips everything while he hosts the show.)
- This isn't the 60s. - So how do you feel?
- I feel good. - Do they normally ask that?
(Composed for now)
- I feel good. - Oh, is that so?
Suk Jin, try to make him talk more.
- Don't listen to others. - Don't.
(He's about to run out of things to say after one question.)
- Just stay focused. - Don't listen to others.
Weren't you two in the same military base?
(Squeezing out questions)
- Yes. - Yes, you're right.
He was my superior when we were in the military.
(Se Chan and Jin Wook were in the army together.)
- You two must be close then. - Sure, we are.
- What kind of superior was he? - Yes, tell us that.
(What kind of superior was Jin Wook?)
Just as you imagine. He was quiet and nice.
- Really? - He was nice to the others.
And he's more humorous than you think.
Yes, I'm sure he is.
He's funny, but Genie isn't good enough to bring that out.
He's a funny guy, but Genie isn't helping.
(He's originally funny.)
He doesn't talk when he's intimidated.
Why is he intimidated?
Jin Wook keeps shaking his head.
(He's only been shaking his head without talking.)
Well, to be honest, Suk Jin is really good.
(He gives an empty compliment as his senior comedian.)
Gosh, this is funny.
Suk Jin is so funny today.
(Ji-rasoni makes them laugh with an unprecedented hosting method.)
Why don't we all have a seat now?
- All right. - Are we sitting down?
I'll explain the rules to you. Please pay attention.
(Ji Seok Genie explains the rules.)
Through today's mission,
you'll increase or reduce the number of members who will get a penalty.
(Increase or reduce the number of members who will get a penalty.)
The race is called The Apartment You Live In.
(The Apartment You Live In)
Through the mission, more members could get a penalty...
(The number of members to get the penalty will increase or decrease.)
or fewer members could get a penalty.
If you fail, one more person will get a penalty,
(If they fail in the following mission,)
which means every member could end up getting penalty.
(1 more person gets the penalty.)
Every time the mission ends,
each of you will go back to your room and use the laptop...
(After the mission, they'll be in their rooms respectively.)
to vote for the member you want to give penalty to.
("This is a chatroom for penalty voting.")
("Send us the name of the member you want to give the penalty to.")
Gosh, they make us do that all the time.
(They can vote for 1 penalty member through the chatroom.)
I'm going to write Genie first.
- Can I get a penalty too? - It's okay to write nothing, right?
- I can't get a penalty. - Why can't Genie get a penalty?
(Ji Seok Genie is exempted from the penalty today.)
I can't get a penalty.
Instead of not getting penalty,
(He'll concentrate on solving their complaints.)
I have to take care of all of your requests.
So I'll be very busy today.
But if everyone votes for no one,
(If no one casts a vote for a penalty member,)
then one less person will get a penalty.
(the number of penalty members decreases by 1.)
If you don't vote, one less person will get a penalty.
- One less from all members? - Then I won't vote.
(Then...)
Yes, from all members.
I won't vote.
(If none of them casts a vote, one fewer member gets the penalty.)
But if even one of you votes,
(If any of them casts a vote, the number stays.)
the same number of members will get a penalty.
And the members with most votes will get a penalty.
(Stuttering)
Can't you read the script prior to the shoot?
- I'm reading it for the first time. - Yes, you're reading it now.
(The rule doesn't really get across.)
But they gave me this a minute ago.
- My goodness. - So many times do you vote?
(The residents quickly lose focus.)
Only two times.
- You only get to vote twice. - Excuse me.
- Anyone can tell... - Genie, no one's listening to you.
- Hey! - They're busy eating the rice cake.
I'm explaining the rules.
But the new residents and the landlady brought us the rice cake.
- So we should eat it. - All right.
Well, since you have ears, just listen.
- What? - How can you say it like that?
You only use your mouth to eat so listen while you eat.
(He has a talent for speaking the truth harshly.)
- Gosh. - Just listen.
And when there's a request you want to file,
(Residents with complaints...)
- use the notes on the table. - All right.
(will write it on the note and submit it to Ji Seok Genie.)
Write your request on it...
and put it in my mission bag.
Then I will take care of all of your requests.
- Really? - All of them?
- All of them. - Okay.
- You'll take care of all of them? - I'll do my best...
(Scribbling)
- to take care of them. - Here is one.
(The rocker files a complaint first.)
- What did you write? - What is it?
(What is it about?)
Maybe he wrote, "Please go home."
"Genie, get lost."
Why would you want me to get lost?
I can't take care of this kind of request.
- Really? - I can't get lost because...
(Genie has a quick temper.)
Can't you go back into your magic lamp?
(They request him to return to the lamp.)
- Get lost. - Go back into the lamp.
- In this apartment, - Please get lost.
(Staying faithful to his concept)
I'm being paid.
- My gosh. - So I can't get lost.
Even the guests can give me a note...
(The opportunity is open even to the guests.)
- Really? - if there's anything they want.
Then I will be sure to take care of all of your requests.
Because I'm Ji Seok Genie.
Suk Jin, will you go wash my car then?
I can't do that.
(That's too difficult.)
- He says no to everything. - But...
(He says he can do anything, but he can't do most of it.)
He's not doing anything.
It requires a lot of work, but it wouldn't get me enough screentime.
Ask me something else.
What kind of Genie cares about his screentime?
(Genie has no spirit of volunteering.)
- You know what I mean. - Actually, that sounds good.
It takes about an hour, but it will be on screen only for two minutes.
(Ji Seok Genie puts efficiency first in handling complaints.)
Suk Jin, washing his car sounds hilarious.
- Right? You should try. - Write it down here.
- Put it in here. - Put it in?
(The complaints are flooding in.)
I didn't know there would be so many requests.
(Some malicious complainers exploit it as an opportunity.)
I can't take care of all of them.
Who put this in?
What should I make him do?
(He checks all notes one by one.)
"Cover this."
Who wrote this?
"Get a crew cut."
(Get a crew cut. From Lee Kwang Soo the bar exam taker)
- Can't you do that? - Who wrote this?
That's my request. Can't you do that?
Why do you want me to get a hair cut all of a sudden?
(It's a note asking for a stricter hairstyle rule.)
Why can't you do that?
I have my own style.
I can't do things like this.
(He unilaterally decides to discard the complaint.)
- He can't do anything. - It's not like that. Guys.
- He's giving you one. - It's from Kang.
(Song Kang submits a complaint.)
Read it for us.
This is from Song Kang.
"Please take good care of the guests."
(Please take care of the guests. From Song Kang)
On our show,
- no one takes care of others. - Kang said that.
(Cold-hearted Genie)
- He really meant it. - We all are on our own.
(Genie forces the guests to survive on their own.)
He's serious about that.
I'm getting too many requests all at the same time.
(Many complaints are being discarded.)
- He says no to everything. - I'll keep reading.
- Oh, this one! Who wrote this? - What is it?
- This is something I can do. - What is it?
"Please get me some coffee." Who wrote this?
(Please get me some coffee. From Writer Jeon)
- Okay. Wait a second. - Okay.
I like a request like this.
(He only accepts requests that are easy to do.)
- He wants to drink coffee. - I'm from Unit 208.
- He wants coffee for himself. - I really like it.
Why? Is it his mission?
Why does he like it? This is strange, isn't it?
- Really? - You should order coffee.
I can make coffee... Hang on.
(He hastily moves around upon receiving the coffee request.)
- Iced coffee. - I can get you coffee.
Genie, make it one shot.
- What? - Make it weak with one shot.
- Hang on. Did you see that? - Make it weak.
Suk Jin said he liked it, but he was just like this.
(He just spun round and round at the same spot.)
- He was like this. - What are the writers doing?
They should get me some coffee.
I gave you enough time to get me coffee.
I kept running around in here.
(He had no intention of going out to get coffee.)
You should get me coffee...
so I can continue my skit.
We just don't click.
(Suk Jin's skit is only completed by Running Man writers.)
He was like this.
(He just kept turning round and round at the same spot.)
We just don't click.
All right. This is what I can do.
(They quickly give Suk Jin a cup of coffee.)
- You're not doing it yourself. - He's the worst.
Here you are.
- This is... - He's the worst.
(Thanks to the writers,)
(Suk Jin successfully fulfills the request.)
- Genie. - We all want coffee.
You should give coffee to all of us.
- You will have some free time now. - What?
(1st Free Time)
Do we have free time?
For 10 minutes,
you can either vote for a person to get a penalty...
(For the next 10 minutes, they can either rest...)
or get some rest in your room.
(or vote someone to get a penalty.)
Like Suk Jin said, if none of you vote,
(If none of them casts a vote,)
the number of people to get a penalty will be reduced.
We shouldn't vote at first.
(the number of people to get a penalty will be reduced.)
(The current number of people who'll get a penalty: 1)
- We shouldn't vote. - Then it will be reduced by one.
- Why would we vote? - Otherwise, it'll keep increasing.
(If no one votes this round, everyone can be exempted.)
If someone votes,
the person who gets the vote will be more likely to get a penalty.
(But someone who was voted...)
(will more likely to get a penalty...)
If someone votes, the person with most votes will get a penalty.
(as that person has received the most number of votes.)
- Please go back to your places. - Okay. Let's go home.
(They all move into their rooms to enjoy their free time.)
Make sure not to vote.
Okay.
It would be stupid to vote.
(All residents return after promising not to vote.)
It would be really stupid to vote now.
I wonder what's in our rooms.
- There's Genie's room. - This is Genie's room.
(There's a room at the entrance of the apartment.)
This is Genie's room.
I'm wearing thin clothes, but my room is outdoors.
(Genie's room)
- Okay. Let's go. - Is this my room?
My place is Unit 310.
(This is where he receives requests.)
- Mine is Unit 208. - They bring requests here.
(He's being nice to the residents.)
I'll receive requests here.
Gosh, I've got a lot of requests.
(He reveals his true self.)
Let me check them.
(He checks the requests he's received.)
"Pick up my second son, Soul, at his kindergarten..."
(Pick up my second son, Soul at his kindergarten...)
"and get me cheonggukjang for lunch."
(and get me cheonggukjang for lunch. From Haha)
My gosh.
"Order jjamppong and fried dumplings for me."
(Order jjamppong and fried dumplings for me. From Ji Hyo.)
(He's trying to fulfill the request.)
Hello?
Is this a Chinese restaurant?
I'd like to have jjamppong and fried dumplings.
(Meanwhile, all residents enter their rooms.)
What is this?
What is this laptop for?
(There's a notebook for the voting.)
What's this?
(There's also a chatroom.)
Gosh. What is this box for?
(What is this box for?)
(There are 3 boxes next to the laptop.)
(All 3 boxes are locked up.)
I guess something's in here.
(What's the secret of these boxes?)
This is strange. Why are there books?
(The books are as suspicious as the boxes.)
Let me see. What is this book for?
(All the residents have books in their rooms.)
I can have a chat with others.
(They can chat online before the voting.)
Is this how I cast a vote?
(Through chatting?)
"Kim Jong Kook." Why would she call me like this?
(Song Ji Hyo)
"Why would you call me like that?"
(He's giving her an etiquette lesson online.)
"You punk."
(Why would you call me like that, you punk?)
(Fine.)
(This is pretty cool.)
(I think this is the room escape game.)
(Jong Kook, try to type faster.)
He wants me to type faster.
(He types fast with his webbed fingers.)
- Can I create a group chat room? - Sure.
(He creates a group chat room without Kwang Soo.)
(They have a friendly conversation without Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo isn't in here.
(While the residents are busy building a friendship...)
(Ji Seok Genie is busy responding to online requests.)
Cookies and iced coffee.
My gosh. Where's the cafeteria?
(Se Chan asks for coffee and snacks.)
Excuse me.
- Come in. - Okay.
- Hello. - Hi.
(Very friendly)
I got you the cookies.
(The magician is happier to see the snacks than Genie.)
- You brought them here? - Sure.
Please tell me if you need anything.
(Satisfied with the room service)
- And send me a lot of requests. - Okay. Thank you.
(The bar exam taker across the hall is very angry.)
It's been a while since I sent my request.
What is it? I haven't checked it yet.
(The tone already suggests his rudeness.)
Please tell me what it is.
I asked for jjamppong with rice and a lot of pickled radish.
Gosh, I'm in trouble. Okay.
- Jjamppong with rice? - And a lot of pickled rice.
(The bar exam taker submits an extra request.)
- Got it. - Okay.
Is it possible?
My goodness.
They could order jjamppong themselves.
Don't they have phones at their places?
(He tries to relieve his stress in his own room.)
(While Genie is busy taking care of the requests...)
Hello?
I got a message.
"This is the chat room to take a ballot for the penalty."
(This is the chat room to take a ballot for the penalty.)
(A message appeared on the residents' laptops.)
"If you want to cast a ballot,"
(It's a secret message to cast their votes.)
"send me the name of the person whom you want to give a penalty."
(This is the chat room to take a ballot for the penalty.)
(If you want to cast a ballot,)
(send me the name of the person to whom you want to give a penalty.)
If we don't cast a vote, none of us will get a penalty.
(If no one votes, nobody will get a penalty.)
(If at least one of them votes, one person will get a penalty.)
(Si Young doesn't want to vote.)
So I shouldn't probably vote.
I've never seen...
(Do Hyun only learned about betrayal in Running Man.)
the members keep their promises before.
But this time,
(He will trust other residents and abstain this time.)
I'll trust them.
(Meanwhile, the other bar exam taker, Kwang Soo...)
(asks if the vote will remain anonymous.)
(He votes for Lee Si Young immediately.)
(Because of Kwang Soo, the number of people to get a penalty is still 1.)
I'll vote for Lee Jin Wook.
He's a great guy.
(Song Kang votes for Jin Wook.)
I sent the message.
(Si Young has 1 vote, Jin Wook has 1 vote.)
(The magician doesn't hesitate and votes for Si Young.)
(At the moment...)
(The password of Box 1 is "1218".)
(Those who cast a vote gets the password of Box 1.)
It's 1218. Hang on.
Do they give me the password?
(Kwang Soo also gets the password of Box 1.)
What?
(The password of Box 1 is "1218".)
Hang on.
(He tries to open the box with the password from the administrator.)
(It's open.)
What is this?
(What's in the mysterious box?)
(1 R coin)
Can I take this off? What is this?
R coin?
(Those who cast a vote got 1 R coin each.)
What is this?
This is an R coin.
I got the password because I cast my ballot.
The password is like a benefit.
(The sweet benefit of the ballot is an R coin.)
(Yoo Jae Suk.)
(Can I cast a ballot again?)
(He wants to cast a ballot for everyone to get more coins.)
When you meet other members,
don't talk about the coin.
(However, this round of voting is now over.)
I knew it. They wouldn't let us cast a ballot for nothing.
(Kwang Soo found out that he can get a coin by casting a ballot.)
There's something.
(Only the three of them know the secret.)
(The residents gather together after the short break.)
I won't send him any more requests.
I won't ask Genie for anything anymore.
Why not?
He's a big senior, but he got me this coffee.
He said, "Here's your coffee."
I can't do this anymore.
(Se Chan is heartbroken by Suk Jin's hard work.)
Hey, since when did you care about things like that?
You should do it more for him.
You think? Okay.
He'll become healthy this way.
Okay. I'll do it for his health.
Sure. He should move a lot.
(Genie is getting healthier by moving his body around.)
- Give us the coffee. - All right.
- Oh, no. - This is what I heard...
from the hallway.
(They could hear Suk Jin's moaning in the hallway.)
(He delivers his final coffee even as he sweats.)
Genie was sweating a lot.
(His joints are hurting.)
I'm like your servant.
I'm not Genie. I'm a servant.
- Hurry. - This is crazy.
(The group mission that will decide the number of people...)
The first test is called Nerve-wracking Quiz.
(who will get the penalty!)
(Nerve-wracking Quiz)
- What? - Have you heard of it before?
The 11 residents will be...
divided into 3 teams of 4, 4, and 3 people...
- to solve quizzes of each category. - What? "Catagory"?
- "Catagory"? - Did you say "catagory"?
If you find fault...
(The hunters spotted their prey.)
- You're like this every time. - People make mistakes.
I hope time will fly by quickly today.
(Sympathetic)
The host should speak clearly.
- It could be "catagory". - It's category.
- You know what I mean. - It's category.
(He stubbornly responds.)
You know what?
It seems that Suk Jin has to deal with five of us...
- while talking for one minute. - Please...
Please go easy on me.
(Ji-rasoni always fights alone against 5 people.)
- He's the Sirasoni of MCs. - That's right.
- He's incredible. - The Sirasoni of MCs.
- Ji-rasoni, you're amazing. - Ji-rasoni.
(He's memorizing the script without listening to them.)
You'll be divided into 3 teams of 4, 4, and 3 people.
The category for Team One is "Singers".
"Singers"?
The category for Team Two is "Entertainment".
"Entertainment".
The category for Team Three is "Common Knowledge".
Jae Suk, you'll choose "Common Knowledge", right?
(Jae Suk will be in charge of Common Knowledge to win.)
You should choose "Common Knowledge".
Then Jae Suk and I...
- Yes... Why you? - "Common Knowledge"?
Don't choose that. Are you insane?
- Exactly. Don't do that. - Maybe that's best for him.
(Everyone's against Kwang Soo playing for Common Knowledge.)
- He doesn't know anything. - Hold on.
Don't you think it's too mean to to call me insane...
- because I chose that? - Don't be ridiculous.
(You can't do it.)
He can't be in that team.
- Do Hyun, which team will you join? - I choose "Common Knowledge".
(Bar exam taker Do Hyun applies for Common Knowledge.)
"Common Knowledge"? Really?
- Really? - I choose it too.
- Si Young, are you serious? - You choose "Common Knowledge"?
- Really? That's unexpected. - Si Young, choose "Entertainment".
- Sorry? - Choose "Entertainment".
(Just choose Entertainment.)
No. I choose "Common Knowledge".
(No, I choose Common Knowledge.)
- That doesn't suit you. - Don't be upset.
- What's with her? - Don't be upset.
- Why would you be upset? - I don't understand...
(The residents decided the teams under the agreement.)
- I think Kwang Soo is targeting me. - I said nothing wrong.
Please sit with your team members.
(The teams)
- 4, 4, and 3 people. - Where's Team Entertainment?
(Team Singers, Team Entertainment, Team Common Knowledge)
Team Singers, please sit on this side. Thank you.
(Singers, Entertainment, Common Knowledge)
If even a single team succeeds within seven attempts,
(If even a single team succeeds within 7 attempts,)
the number of people to get the penalty will remain.
(the number of the people to get the penalty will remain as 1.)
I see.
(At least one team should answer continuously.)
You have to succeed consecutively.
Team Singers, you will see a photo of an idol singer,
(See a photo of an idol singer and name the group in 3 seconds.)
and guess the group name in three seconds.
- That's easy. - It's easy to succeed.
- Indeed. - It's easy.
(It doesn't sound hard.)
Team Entertainment, I'll tell you the name of an actor or actress.
(Name the films the mentioned actor starred in without overlapping.)
Each of you has to say a movie that he or she acted in.
I can do that. I'm confident.
(Feeling confident)
Movie titles?
- Lastly, Team Common Knowledge, - Yes?
(It's an open book quiz.)
you will take an open book quiz.
- An open book quiz? - You'll receive a newspaper...
(Newspapers will be given from which the questions are made.)
- from which the questions are made. - I see.
Say the correct answer written on the newspaper in three seconds.
(Listen to the question and answer in 3 seconds.)
- It's so difficult. - A newspaper?
- Each member will receive it. - Read it as much as you want.
(It's important to read the newspaper in order to answer.)
Oh, my. Look at this.
It's too difficult.
(It's the most difficult among 3 teams.)
- This is too difficult. - They can find the answer in it.
Wait. This is an economy newspaper for middle and high school students.
- It's too difficult. - This is an economy newspaper.
(The questions cover...)
(the financial paper that is rare in Running Man.)
- It's so difficult. - From the newspaper,
we made easy questions.
We'll begin the first round.
(Team Common Knowledge begins first.)
- Okay. - Okay, Jae Suk?
You can browse the newspaper to find the answer freely.
(From Jae Suk, Jin Wook to Si Young)
- Do I go first? - I'm sure Jae Suk will succeed.
(If those three pass, it's a success.)
I'm sure he will.
This isn't a tabloid.
Janet Yellen, the former Federal Reserve chairwoman, has been...
nominated as the Treasury Secretary...
for Joe Biden's cabinet that will be formed in January, 2021.
Then...
who is Biden's running mate and the vice-president-elect?
Kamala Harris.
(He said the correct answer without hesitating.)
I knew it!
Kamala Harris.
(Impressed)
(Jae Suk, the undisputed king of common knowledge of Running Man)
I knew it!
(The smartest member of Running Man made everyone proud.)
We all can trust Jae Suk!
- My, he's so cool. - We all can trust Jae Suk!
(Everyone is amazed by the smart rocker.)
- He didn't even look at it. - He's so cool.
(It's an open book quiz.)
Jae Suk, you looked so sexy.
(Jae Suk is enjoying their compliments.)
He's a close friend of mine.
His pronunciation was also very good.
(He wants to show off that they're close.)
Jae Suk, that was so sexy.
(Jealous)
Next up is Jin Wook.
(Next up is Jin Wook.)
Jin Wook, you have to succeed.
Jin Wook reads newspaper every day.
(He knows Jin Wook well.)
- Does he? - You must not tell him the answer.
- Okay. - How did he know the answer?
Due to the COVID-19 pandemic, the global debt increased...
by 15 trillion dollars through September this year.
There are concerns...
that many developing countries will declare this.
What is this?
5, 4,
- Three... - A default.
Okay!
(Correct)
(Smiling)
A default.
(Amazed)
(Jin Wook got the correct answer following Jae Suk!)
- That was awesome. - My goodness.
(Even his brain is sexy too.)
- "Fault"? - It's "default".
Right? It's "fault", right? I knew that word.
- No, it's "default". - You should know that much.
(What?)
- Haha, that's common knowledge. - All right. Good.
- "Fault"? - Yes, "fault".
(They lack common knowledge.)
If Si Young gets the correct answer,
- this team will succeed. - Then we'll succeed at once.
(If Si Young succeeds, the mission is cleared on the first attempt.)
We'll definitely succeed.
- Si Young, you can do it! - Si Young, keep reading it.
- It's not easy to make it this far. - Go, Si Young!
Be quiet.
She tells me to be quiet whenever I say something.
You did talk too much.
- I was cheering for her. - Be quiet, Kwang Soo.
(Interrupting Kwang Soo)
(Gosh, there he goes again.)
- This is also in the newspaper. - Okay.
(If Si Young succeeds, the mission is accomplished.)
"Multi-personas" means to express a person's various identities...
by transforming into a different person.
Then what are the three characters of Comedian Yoo Jae Suk...
who's shown his multiple identities that were reported in the newspaper?
What are the three characters of Comedian Yoo Jae Suk...
that were reported in the newspaper?
(You know the answer, right?)
What... Three characters in the newspaper?
But it's not in here.
(Incorrect)
- Locust. - Yoo San Seul.
(Jae Suk's alter egos are even in the economy newspaper.)
It's in the newspaper.
- Yoo San Seul and Jimi Yu. Right? - Really?
Yoo San Seul, U-Doragon, and Jimi Yu. It's in the newspaper.
(Yoo Jae Suk has many alter egos.)
But this is... This is common knowledge.
(To Se Chan, everything about Jae Suk is common knowledge.)
But this is...
- She should've known... - What a shame.
They were so close, but Si Young ruined it.
(Glaring)
(There's a tension between the bar exam taker and the landlady.)
I mean, it's hard to make it this far.
Team Entertainment will go next.
(Team Entertainment gets the chance next.)
The four of you have to say the movie titles...
(They must say the films the actor starred in without hesitation.)
that this actor appeared in consecutively.
- If anyone fails, the team fails. - Okay.
(Focusing)
The actor is...
Lee Kwang Soo.
(Which films did Kwang Soo star in?)
"Collective Invention".
Darn.
(Incorrect)
What was that?
"Collective Invention".
- Darn. - What was that?
(Murmuring)
(Is it that difficult?)
I was going to say "Collective Invention".
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks".
(He remembered one.)
"Once Upon a Time in a Battlefield".
- I'm relieved. - "Atka Mackerel Seven".
"Atka Mackerel Seven". You should've known all these.
What's "Atka Mackerel Seven"?
- Didn't you play in that movie? - Hey, it's "Sturgeon".
- Oh, right. "Sturgeon". - What about "Once Upon a Time"...
- Yes? - "in a Battlefield"?
(Confident)
- It's "Battlefield Heroes". - Oh, right.
I can't believe none of you knows any of my movies.
(Actor Lee Kwang Soo's filmography)
("Battlefield Heroes", "Love On-Air", "The Scent")
- He played in "The Treacherous". - Did you play in "The Treacherous"?
- I didn't play in that movie. - You didn't?
I didn't play in "The Treacherous".
I thought you did because you're so treacherous.
("The Treacherous" starred by Lee Kwang Soo)
I didn't play in that movie.
- Kwang Soo, "An Eagle Family"? - I didn't...
(Confident)
- Come again? - "An Eagle Family".
- It's "A Dynamite Family". - Oh, right.
Enough, you punk!
- He can't say any title correctly. - That's enough.
(They blow up the second chance after hurting Actor Lee Kwang Soo.)
- Just shut it. - This is the hardest category.
- "A Dynamite Family". I knew it. - Gosh. What do we do?
- It was quite difficult. - You don't know any of my movies.
- It was quite difficult. - Jin Wook...
swallowed saliva many times.
As if he was thinking, "I can't do this with these idiots."
(Jin Wook was frustrated by their childish conversation.)
"These idiots..."
- Kang, switch seats with me. - Movie titles are confusing.
(This isn't working.)
- Okay. I'll go there. - What a shame.
(He runs to Team Singers after the difficult question.)
I think I'll do better in this category.
- Let our team try. - It's Team Singers' turn.
(It's Team Singers' turn after revision.)
- All right. - See the photo and say the answer.
(See the photo and name the group.)
And then, the next person will do the same.
Why am I so nervous when this is just a game?
(Photos of their prime will be given.)
Here we go. Ready.
Get set. Go. Two.
- Turbo. - That one was easy.
(Mikey of Turbo)
- Go! - 2, 1.
- TWICE. - Wow. He did a great job.
(Jeongyeon of TWICE is correct.)
You're almost there.
(Half of them succeeded easily.)
2, 1.
- Who is he? - ZE:A.
- ZE:A. - Who is that punk?
(The man who doesn't know is angry.)
"I can't stop crying somehow". The singer of "Aftereffect".
- Who are you? - He's Kim Dong Jun of ZE:A.
(Staring)
He's so cute.
- He's a member of ZE:A. - So Min.
It's not the time for you to compliment Dong Jun's face.
(She doesn't care about the quiz. Love Frog just can't stop smiling.)
Jong Kook, move to Team Entertainment.
I'll move to Team Entertainment.
(They release the man who only shouts.)
So Min, join our team.
Ji Hyo, join our team and solve common knowledge questions.
- No, Ji Hyo, stay here. - Okay.
(MC Yoo cares about Ji Hyo's airtime.)
- Ji Hyo, it's an open book quiz. - Stay here.
- No, Jae Suk. I won't go. - Come with me. Give it a try.
(She's driven by her nice colleagues.)
- Give it a try. - Give it a try.
- Just give it a try. - Gosh.
She ended up joining Team Common Knowledge.
(Laughing)
I hope she gets a question from the article she's reading.
You can just read the answer.
(Ji Hyo advances to Common Knowledge quiz.)
- You can just read it. - I'll find it for you.
- Hey, submit a request. - Gosh, seriously.
(Ji Seok Genie)
- Ask me to find it for you. - She ended up in that team.
Suk Jin is simply trying to get more screen time.
So don't mind him.
- The same goes for you, Jae Suk. - Pardon?
(Calculating the angle)
I think you're trying to get more air time too.
I'll help you find the answer when your turn comes.
(You can tell that he's desperate for airtime.)
How about we continue while they're reading it?
- Which team should go next? - Team Singers.
(Only four chances are left. It's Singers this time.)
- Team Singers? - Yes.
Please give me a chance to say something.
- Ready. - We can do this.
- Go. - Three.
- H.O.T. - That's easy.
(Lee Jae Won of H.O.T is correct.)
That was so easy.
- 3, 2... - Solid.
- It's Snail, you punk! - Gosh, it's Snail.
(Lee Juck in his prime)
- It's Snail, you punk! - Gosh.
- It's Snail. - Snail!
- The answer is Panic. - Oh, right. It's Panic.
(Snail will sing "Panic".)
I'm panicking right now.
He and I formed a duo called Sagging Snail, you know.
- He's called Snail. - I was...
- My gosh. - We were Sagging Snail.
He yelled at me when he didn't know the answer either.
Chul Min, Si Young wants to try again.
Si Young wants to try again.
Ji Hyo, you can do this. Give Ji Hyo double points.
Okay.
- Give Ji Hyo double points. - Okay.
(The embarrassing demand and the director's quick consent...)
Hey, bring it on. Let's do this.
That's the spirit.
- Ji Hyo will pull it off. - She'll pull it off.
(wake up sleeping Ji Hyo.)
- Bring it on. I can do this. - Go, Ji Hyo!
- I've never seen her like that. - Ji Hyo, prove yourself.
(Ji Hyo versus Common Knowledge)
- Will Ji Hyo go first? - Yes.
- Go, Ji Hyo! - She's good at an open book quiz.
Let's overcome this.
(He tries to get airtime.)
Here's your question.
(Ji Hyo's challenge for common knowledge quiz!)
In "Parallel Lives" written by the Greek historian...
Plutarch, the name of Alexander's horse is...
Bucephalus.
- Then what's the name... - She doesn't seem to know.
of the horse Lu Bu and Guan Yoo ride that can run 420km in a day?
(Given up already)
Then what's the name of the horse Lu Bu and Guan Yoo ride...
that can run 420km in a day?
(Let's go!)
You know the answer, right?
Then what's the name of the horse Lu Bu and Guan Yoo ride...
that can run 420km in a day?
- Red Hare! - That's correct!
(Throwing the newspaper)
Red Hare!
That's correct!
(Ji Hyo got the correct answer.)
- Red Hare! - That's correct!
(Unbelievable)
(All the residents are cheering.)
Song Ji Hyo! Song Ji Hyo!
(Her success makes their jaws drop...)
(Her success makes their jaws drop,)
(and they give her a standing ovation.)
(Touched)
That's amazing. She got the right answer.
Song Ji Hyo!
(The opsimath of Running Man's graduation ceremony)
- I did it! I got it right. - Good job.
(Doctor Song's graduation thesis on Red Hare)
- Ji Hyo, you did a great job. - She actually pulled it off.
(Feeling pressured by Ji Hyo's performance)
- Next up is Jin Wook. - She sure is an interpreter.
- She knew the answer. - She's so smart.
That was sexy.
(Ji Hyo becomes brain sexy through Red Hare.)
- She's so cool. - Intelligent and sexy.
(Shy)
She's happy.
I haven't seen her smile like that in a while.
- I'm proud of her. - Ji Hyo seems so happy.
(Everyone's proud of onscreen text, "Ji Hyo's correct".)
Ji Hyo, I'll ask you about difficult questions later.
I'll tell you the answers.
(Common knowledge flex)
She's so cool.
She'll probably watch this episode real time this week.
(Her family and friends will gather to watch the show together.)
Queen Red Hare.
Let's move on to Jin Wook.
(All the pressure is on the next person.)
- Let's go. - Jin Wook, here's your question.
(I must succeed not to let Ji Hyo's success go to waste.)
Jin Wook, please succeed.
This literally means to glare at someone showing the white.
This refers to look down on...
Prejudiced view.
That's correct!
What was that? What did he say?
(He got it even before finish reading the question.)
Jin Wook, great job!
He didn't even need to look through the newspaper.
(Prejudiced view)
- That was good. - He's amazing.
(He got it even before hearing the whole question.)
My goodness. He's so smart.
You knew that expression, right?
- It's written here. - Oh, my.
(Scoffing)
I knew it would be in the quiz.
(The only person who can't smile despite her team members' success)
- Si Young, you're up next. - Sure.
She needs to get it right this time.
This is our last chance.
(She's the last one to go.)
- We'll be better off giving up. - Help me, guys.
Si Young said herself that she had a lot...
- of common knowledge. - Yes, she did.
- She insisted. - If you get it wrong again,
you should switch places with Suk Jin.
(She might become the genie.)
Oh, dear. Anyway, I'm ready.
- Get it wrong, and we'll switch. - Sure.
(Ji Seok Genie watches for an opportunity.)
- Si Young, here's your question. - Right.
(The mission will be a success if Si Young gets it right.)
Let's see.
- We all need insurance policies. - Right.
Which coffee house in London...
gave birth to the modern insurance industry?
What did you just say? A coffee house?
(Laughing)
A coffee house. Hold on.
A coffee house in London.
(All she did was repeat the question.)
You should've named any coffee house you know!
(Discouraged)
Starbucks!
(Lloyd's Coffee House)
- Starbucks is everywhere, right? - Come on!
Starbucks! Unbelievable.
You should've at least said Star Coffee House.
Si Young...
You should've said it at least for a laugh.
Tell me about it!
(He's more than a match for her at variety shows.)
- Si Young! - It wasn't even funny.
You should've at least said Mindeule Youngto.
(Frustrated)
- There are many shops to name. - MY!
(The most Korea-related stuff is the most global stuff.)
- Star Coffee Shop. - A punch is what you need.
You'll get beaten up instead.
You deserve a punch.
(She's knocked out after the common sense punch.)
Not again.
Look at Ji Hyo studying.
How cool!
(Clearing her throat)
I haven't seen her like this before.
(Ji Hyo is reading a newspaper. Who would've thought?)
- I should get her a subscription. - How about this?
Let's give Si Young another chance.
Team Singer should go first.
She must be feeling bad.
Genie, is the color of the mat rubbing off on you?
Unbelievable.
(He's become all blue due to the mat.)
It's like he's dressed for a green screen in movies.
- Can you see me? - What?
(It's a perfect outfit to edit out.)
No, we can't tell you apart.
Are you sure it's not rubbing off on you?
- Director. - We'll start with Si Young.
(Genie chooses "common knowledge" again.)
Si Young, Jin Wook,
- and then Ji Hyo. - Let's do this.
(Si Young gets a chance to redeem herself.)
What's the distance between Dokdo and Ulleungdo,
the two most well-known islands in Korea?
It's written in there. I saw it.
- Where... - It's on this page.
What?
Count it down for her.
(Time's up.)
(Dokdo, which is 88km apart from Ulleungdo...)
Seriously, Si Young?
Count it down for her.
(She fails to answer 3 times in a row.)
- Seriously? - Si Young!
(Shouting)
- What on earth? - Unbelievable.
Southwest of Ulleungdo
80km by sea
- A lonely island - A lonely island
- The hometown to birds - The hometown to birds
- Despite others claiming - Despite others claiming
(She doesn't know where to put her body.)
- It's theirs - It's theirs
- Dokdo is our land - Dokdo is our land
- Our land! - Our land!
The answer is in the song.
(200 Chinese miles along the sea route)
What's wrong with her?
(He's especially sensitive about Dokdo.)
Even traitor Lee Wan Yong would know.
- Lee Wan Yong? - Hold on.
Lee Wan Yong?
(Unbelievable!)
Hold on a second.
(No wonder the sly face looked familiar.)
(The insult leads to an altercation.)
Hold on a second.
My surname is Yang!
(Ending the traitor with a kick)
You're Lee Wan Yong.
Are you Lee Wan Yong today?
(The laughter therapist shows no mercy to traitors.)
Traitor, get back here.
I'm done with the mustache.
Lee Wan Yong, you traitor!
(He gets rid of the remnants of the pro-Japanese traitor.)
- Lee Wan Yong... - He makes me sick.
(He rips off the remnants...)
Anyway, I've been reborn.
(and is newly born as the protector of Dokdo.)
All right!
Lee Wan Yong...
(The laughter therapist is completely satisfied.)
"He makes me sick."
- Let's get back to the quiz. - Let's do this.
(It's their last opportunity.)
- Red Hare! - Red Hare!
(They put their faith in Ji Hyo and Team Common Knowledge.)
Ji Hyo should go first.
(Calling out Ji Hyo's name in the midst of crisis)
The Red Hare of Mapo-gu.
- Ji Hyo, let's do this. - You've got this!
(Ji Hyo is ready to gallop.)
- Here we go. - Go, go!
Novels are treasure chests filled with vocabulary.
What is the spelling for the English word "squeeze"?
S, Q, U, E, E, Z, E.
(She even gets the spelling right!)
- Song Ji Hyo! - Song Ji Hyo!
S, Q, U, E, E, Z, E.
(The interpreter squeezes out the spelling...)
(with perfect pronunciation.)
(Oh, my gosh!)
- Song Ji Hyo! - Song Ji Hyo!
(First "Red Hare," and now "squeeze"!)
(They chant her name with the same thought in mind.)
- Red Hare! - Red Hare!
(I'm in trouble.)
- Red Hare! - Unbelievable, Ji Hyo!
(They celebrate.)
(Proud)
(They ride off like Ji Hyo...)
(who only rides toward the correct answer.)
- She did it! - Nice one.
She did it!
(They have to toss her into the air on this monumental day.)
- No, wait. - She did it.
- Hey! - I'm amazed.
(Go, Ji Hyo!)
You're amazing.
You're amazing, Ji Hyo.
- You did it. - Unbelievable.
(Finally, after 10 years,)
(Ji Hyo wins the battle against common knowledge.)
- Nicely done. - She actually spelled the word.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo, they're close to success.)
- No way. - I got the chills.
She didn't even hesitate.
History, English...
What doesn't she know?
She's a genius.
(The simultaneous interpreter has mastered history and English.)
The lady with a sexy brain.
She must be taking classes or something.
(People suspect her getting private lessons.)
Si Young must really be feeling the pressure now.
(Her face is gloomy on this happy day.)
- That was so cool. - Jin Wook should go first.
- I'll read one more. - Jin Wook's up.
(Next is Jin Wook, the verified sexy brain.)
- All right. - The man with a sexy brain.
(A bit nervous)
Let's go.
What's the English word for only seeing...
people in a neutral way regardless of their gender?
- Gender neutral. - All right!
(That is correct!)
Gender neutral.
All right!
(Once again, he answered without looking at the newspaper.)
Nice!
(Si Young collapses on the table again.)
Come on up.
(Sorrow and joy)
Okay!
All right.
(Joy is shared by tossing him in the air.)
Okay!
(I'm in so much trouble.)
The man with a sexy brain.
Okay, gender neutral.
(She can't hear a thing.)
- That was incredible. - Okay.
You both couldn't be sexier.
(Pressuring)
It's like I'm watching art.
That's 2 down, 1 to go!
(Pressuring)
Si Young, you've got this.
It's the final question of the day.
(It's the last question to maintain the number of penalty members.)
Guys, get ready to rise on your feet.
Si Young must feel burdened.
Here we go.
(It's her time to throw that uppercut.)
- Oh, no... - Si Young, focus.
Focus. I got it.
She's been reading this for over an hour now.
Adam Smith!
Sorry?
(Taken aback)
He didn't even ask the question.
(She gives herself the question after excessive reviews.)
- I was just getting fired up. - Here we go.
Si Young, focus.
(The fate of all residents depends on this final chance.)
Focus. I got it.
In "Snow-falling Map" by poet Yoon Dong Ju,
who is "Soon Yi"...
that he desperately searches for?
- 5, 4... - Soon Yi, Yoon Dong Ju.
(She repeats the question.)
"Snow-falling Map"!
(Time's up.)
Give her 10 minutes, will you?
- Just 10 minutes. - I'll give her 5 seconds.
(She's given 5 more seconds after a desperate request.)
- What was it again? - 4, 3...
Jin Wook, what's the answer?
The snow. The snow!
(Incorrect)
- Darn it. - Wait, it's the letter.
- The letter. - Let's get going.
(This mission is over.)
- The letter. - Have a good day.
- Let's get going. - Have a good day.
(He's holding back harsh words.)
The letter.
(Clinging)
Letter.
- The answer is "our people". - The letter.
Seriously?
(Her wrong answer wasn't even close.)
(Throwing down his bag)
Don't you know what a metaphor is?
(She even kills the joy of the laughter therapist.)
- It was a metaphor. - So much for laughter.
Why insist on being on Team Common Knowledge?
All you had to do is read it.
"Our people". How hard is that?
Why not sit around and guess names of celebrities instead?
(Acting up)
(The landlady lost her place for this one mission.)
Names of singers.
- She's clueless. - Sit down, everyone.
Okay, I'll see you all in the chat room.
(It seems like the residents have come to an agreement.)
Come on.
(Now 2 people will have to receive the penalty.)
- Unbelievable. - What else can we do?
We should open another chat room immediately.
I smell jjamppong!
- You're right. - I smell jjamppong too.
(Is it jjamppong?)
Jjamppong?
I bet you're hungry.
(Genie returns with spicy jjamppong they've ordered.)
- It's here! - Your meal is here.
I see it receives applause.
Take whichever you want.
- We'll serve ourselves. - Sure.
(Putting down)
You should serve this for us.
(If you're Genie...)
Got it. Can you wait though? There's quite a lot.
Unbelievable.
Suk Jin has never done anything for others his whole life.
(Laughing)
- You ordered a lot though. - Jong Kook...
(Developing his altruism)
Of course. This is tangsuyuk.
- Tangsuyuk's a good choice. - Here you go.
(He suits all the tastes...)
- Si Young. - Yes?
(of the complaining resident and the picky resident.)
Here are fried dumplings.
- They had it on the menu. - Here you go.
No way.
(Genie is sincere to every one of them.)
Here you go. It's what you wanted, right?
- Can I get some wet wipes? - Wet wipes?
(A request)
Coming right up.
(Obedient)
He must be the part-time server.
We're missing the sauce.
(He even brings the tangsuyuk sauce himself.)
He doesn't like it when people tell him to sit down.
(Pouring)
- We wanted to dip. - We wanted it as a dip.
Are you kidding me?
Did he pour the sauce over?
(Sighing)
- That's insane. - We wanted it as a dip.
How inconsiderate!
This is plain crazy.
We explicitly told you that the sauce would be a dip.
(Genie upsets the ones who wanted to dip...)
(by pouring the sauce without asking.)
Who pours the sauce over tangsuyuk?
No wonder that they say "Beating is the answer."
I mean it.
(Beating is the answer?)
Kwang Soo, hold on.
Beating is the answer?
- "Beating cures all." - Isn't it "cure"?
You do know that knowledge is power, right?
(Do you know this?)
Kwang Soo's just as clueless.
(Even Se Chan's vocabulary is wider than the bar exam taker's.)
"Beating is the answer."
(Embarrassed)
- Beating... - Beating is the answer.
Here's some Coke.
(Meanwhile, Genie delivers soda to the residents.)
Here.
(Pouring in the rice bowl)
Why are you pouring it here?
This is rice.
(He pours soda in the rice.)
Coke and rice? Are you insane?
- There aren't any cups. - But the rice...
(Genie's sudden behavior makes them speechless.)
- Just drink it. - You poured it over rice.
- Just drink it. - Hold on.
(Genie was too hungry and tired, he made soda rice.)
I'm busy too, you know. I need to eat as well.
What's wrong with you?
Who pours Coke over rice?
How many are angry with him right now?
(Ji-rasoni resolves a complaint in his own way.)
Suk Jin, my gosh.
(Anyway, I dealt with all their requests.)
(They vote for the second time after lunch.)
(Kwang Soo gets busy right away.)
(Lee Si Young)
I'm already casting my vote.
What's this though? "Books are the legacy..."
"left to mankind by great geniuses."
(Jae Suk is interested in the phrase written on the wallpaper.)
Why is this quote here?
The books must be a clue.
We opened a chat room and left Si Young out.
I mean... I couldn't be more disappointed.
(The counterforce is formed because of her poor quiz skills.)
(Se Chan, goodness.)
Look at Se Chan.
How many chat rooms are there?
(Si Young was terrible in the last round,)
Si Young's been left out.
(so I thought we should leave her out.)
(Se Chan tries something.)
(He hold a video conference.)
- My gosh. This is... - No way.
What's this?
This is incredible.
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo is moved by the new technology.)
(While Se Chan pats himself on the back,)
(Kwang Soo gets busy.)
(Lee Si Young)
(He tells on Se Chan to Si Young.)
(Shocked)
(Song Kang, So Min, Haha agree about casting a vote your way.)
No way.
Se Chan made a chat room and left Si Young out,
(But he voted for Si Young as soon as he came here.)
so I told her that.
This way, she won't cast a vote my way.
(He protects himself with the double betrayal.)
(Kwang Soo, Se Chan did the same earlier,)
(but left you out instead.)
- Hold on. - No way.
(Are you serious?)
Can you believe this?
(Se Chan was caught making group chatrooms.)
I can't believe this.
Which room is Se Chan in?
(You made a chat room and left me out?)
Just a second, guys.
(Trembling)
Si Young's here in my room!
Just a second, guys. Si Young's here in my room!
(She's here in person to rattle his cage.)
(Streaming live)
I bet you'll get a punch in the side.
Si Young came into my room during the live chat.
(The scary, forced union)
Hold on.
(Kwang Soo is going somewhere.)
Hey.
- Is it true? - What is?
Did you really open a chat room?
- What do you mean? What chat room? - "Si Young..."
- Did you leave me out? - What?
- Did you leave me out? - No, I didn't. Trust me.
(How dare you create a room without me?)
- Did you really do that? - How could you...
(She really grabs him by the collar.)
Wait. Hang on a second.
- She's actually hurting me. - Did you really leave me out?
Hey, she's actually hurting me. Wait.
(They get to see a UFC match online.)
I think he's getting beaten up.
She went to his room.
Leave now.
(Si Young suddenly takes the box.)
Can she take those boxes?
- Shut it... - You can't take the boxes.
She's like a game destroyer.
- You can't ignore the rules. - How dare you?
Do you all want to get beaten up by her?
(Don't you know her?)
Will you come to your senses after that?
She always does everything as she pleases.
Kwang Soo, hurry up and cast your vote. Let's vote.
(She doesn't care.)
- My gosh. - Guys.
(The two return to their rooms.)
- Jin Wook. - Yes?
The people in this chat room are...
Ji Hyo, So Min, Haha, you, and me.
So I think we should all vote for Si Young or Kwang Soo.
(He shares his plan.)
- I should vote now. - I'm still here.
(He's really flustered.)
What?
- Hey, Se Chan. - I'm sorry.
(Did you hear that?)
I said, I'm still here.
(His camera is turned off.)
Hey.
(Se Chan notified his betrayal right in front of Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
(While the others are doing underhanded things to each other...)
I think I should vote for Se Chan.
(Jae Suk cast his 1st vote for Se Chan.)
- The way it seems... Yes? - Hey.
(Do Hyun also quietly cast his 1st vote for Si Young.)
(These 7 people voted for the 1st time.)
(He got the password for Box 1 after casting his 1st vote.)
Oh, I have to cast my vote to get the password.
(He realizes the secret.)
(He finally found out the secret and opened the box.)
This is so unexpected.
(The 7 people who voted finally got to open Box 1.)
There's an R coin.
(While Jae Suk obtained an R coin in the box...)
Should I vote?
(Jin Wook is still undecided.)
I won't vote.
(I won't vote.)
(He decided to trust the others as he did at the 1st voting time.)
(The 3 people who won R coins earlier voted again right away.)
How could you be so clumsy?
(I'm sure I'll get another piece of information.)
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
(The password for Box 2 is 0128.)
All right.
(He's opening Box 2 as soon as he gets the password.)
"If you want another benefit, vote again."
(There's a mysterious message with 1 R coin.)
"But if you vote, there will be another person to get the penalty."
(He can get another benefit if he votes again!)
(He voted for Se Chan right away.)
(He's like a train of greed with broken breaks.)
(The password for Box 3 is 9516.)
Has everyone left this chat room?
(He got the password for Box 3.)
(He's opening the box hastily hoping for a better benefit.)
"Among residents, you can find one monster."
(There's a message with an R coin in this box as well.)
(There's a monster among the residents?)
"To survive, you have to eliminate the monster,"
"or escape before the monster eliminates you."
(Among residents, you can find one monster.)
(It'd be advantageous if you kept this from the others.)
(List of Residents)
(Among the 11 residents,)
(there's 1 monster.)
Who could be the monster?
(Se Chan opened Box 3 at the same time!)
(Song Kang also opened Box 3.)
He's voting again.
(Only the 3 of them know about the monster.)
I have to escape? From where?
(Escape before the monster that tries to eliminate the humans.)
(Which of the 11 residents could be the monster?)
(The other people don't know about the monster.)
(Everyone receives a message with the rule.)
"The residents must escape this place in one hour."
"Among the residents who fail to escape,"
"the number of people that we just announced will receive the penalty."
"The ones with the most votes..."
"among those who failed to escape will receive the penalty."
"Below is how you can escape here."
(There's only one way to escape.)
"Collect seven R coins,"
"and put them into the coin box in front of your room."
(Collect 7 coins in the coin box in front of your room.)
"And you will obtain the Certification of Victory."
(The person will obtain the Certification of Victory.)
"Go to Ji Seok Genie with the certificate,"
(Certification of Victory)
(Ji Seok Genie will take you to the room of winners.)
"and he will take you to the room of winners."
(In the room of winners, there are comfortable chairs...)
(and all sorts of snacks for the winners.)
(Find the hidden tickets to enter the room of coins.)
"If you find tickets that are hidden in random places,"
"you can enter the room of coins..."
(Coins will be distributed according to the mission result.)
"where you can get more coins."
I see. The room of coins?
(The 3 people want to escape before the monster eliminates them.)
Okay.
(And the other 8 people think they just have to collect 7 coins.)
(Either way, they all need to get 7 coins...)
(and go to the room of winners.)
(And the monster among them will try to eliminate them.)
(Where is the ticket?)
Who could be the monster?
Right now, my goal is...
(Kwang Soo, who knows about the monster, is nervous too.)
to get seven coins and escape from here.
(Get 7 coins and escape before the monster finds you!)
(They need to find the ticket to get more coins.)
(He finds something.)
- Kwang Soo, let's go together. - Okay.
Darn it.
(That wasn't it.)
Tell everyone not to throw garbage like this.
I thought you found a ticket. Gosh.
(An unexpected cleanup during his search of tickets.)
(Put your garbage in the bins.)
Gosh. This is driving me crazy.
(It's hard to find the ticket.)
(At that moment!)
(Si Young came right behind him quietly like she's shadowboxing.)
Where is it? My goodness! You scared me.
- Why would you do that? - Kwang Soo.
(You scared me!)
- What? - Show me what's in your bag.
Why?
- Do you have any coins? - Yes, I do. But why...
(Why?)
Give me just one.
This is ridiculous. What's wrong with you?
(The hungry boxer brazenly extorts his coins.)
- I have only one coin. - Or do you have a ticket?
This is no joke. It's like a battlefield.
(The laughter therapist is also searching for tickets.)
Wait.
She's trying to rob me of my coin.
(He's telling on her.)
Why would you do that? What has gotten into you?
(A quick body check)
- She's so scary. - Did you find any tickets?
Isn't there a ticket there?
(They try their best to avoid Si Young.)
(Rushing)
- Why? What's wrong with you? - My gosh.
- Don't be like that. - Come on.
(The fighter is blinded with the desire for coins.)
- You're scaring me to death. - Right. I'm so scared.
(Jin Wook, the only person with zero coins...)
(is searching for the ticket.)
(It's not here.)
(He can't find the ticket either. He has a long way to go.)
How would I know where a ticket is?
(Si Young tries really hard to find tickets.)
Oh, my. Oh, yes. I found one already.
(She finally finds the ticket!)
"You want more coins!"
(Mission Ticket)
"Come to the room of coins with this ticket!"
Where is the room of coins?
(She can enter the room of coins with this ticket!)
- Did you have any? - No, I have none.
(She rushes to the room of coins.)
(Crowded)
- What do you mean? - Pardon?
- What don't you have? - Nothing.
(She just has to go downstairs.)
(The laughter therapist noticed her suspicious behavior.)
- Si Young. - You must have found something.
- What is this? - She must've found something.
(Everyone's gaze is focused on Si Young.)
What's in that bag... Gosh. You startled me.
(She suddenly swings her bag around.)
- What are you doing? - Stop it. Why...
You startled me.
(Running away in fear)
Is there something in the bag?
(What's wrong with her?)
Is it that big?
(She walks to the room of coins after securing her path.)
Where is she going?
- So soon? - Can she do that?
(She hands in her ticket.)
What's that?
- Is she going in there? - Why? Why did she go in there?
(The room of coins is opened.)
- How could she go in there? - Si Young already went in there.
(The residents become rattled after she enters the room.)
That can't be.
To get a chance to try the mission for getting more coins,
you have to cast a vote for a person to receive the penalty.
- Would you like to vote? - Yes.
(She doesn't hesitate.)
I vote for Yang Se Chan.
You've won a chance to try the mission by voting.
It's a can-rolling mission.
(Roll a can, and she'll get coins...)
Roll a can, and you'll get coins...
(according to the number that's written where the can stops.)
according to the number that's written where the can stops.
I'll begin now.
(Immediately)
I'll start.
(She can earn up to 2 coins.)
Why did you stop there?
(She gets 0 coins.)
(Devastated)
I failed, right?
(She earns 0 coins as she failed her mission.)
You obtained no coin.
- Where is it? - You mean, the room of coins?
- I can go around too, right? - Yes.
(Ji Seok Genie is not so busy anymore.)
What... Hey, what should we do to go into the room of coins?
(I forgot.)
I read the instruction earlier, but I'm confused.
(Jae Suk puts in a complaint to Genie.)
The room of coins...
We have to find something to get there.
(How can I earn coins as fast as possible?)
The thing is...
I'm trying to figure it out, but the writer won't tell me.
- I'll see what I can do. - Thanks.
(Genie is not very helpful.)
- I'm here to help you all. - Exactly.
I got another request for a hint on the mission.
Give me just one tip.
Ji Seok Genie is...
(The image of Genie...)
Entrance tickets are hidden in random places.
They have to find a ticket to enter the room of coins and get more...
Oh, I see. I'm going to take care of this request.
(Genie is excited to do his job.)
- Jae Suk. - Yes?
- I found out something. - What is it?
(Excited)
- Come this way. - Your uniform looks too thin.
(Genie's working environment is rough, which includes his uniform.)
- I'm very cold. - Of course.
- I should wear a jacket. - What is the hint?
- If you find an entrance ticket... - I already know that.
(Cutting off)
- Come on. My role in this game... - Of course, I know that.
Listen to me. My gosh.
(It was basic information that everyone but Genie knew.)
You should...
(Now the jobless fairy is out of tasks again.)
give me some information so I can grant the request.
Gosh, seriously.
(Kwang Soo is now in a rush as he knows about the monster.)
- Of course. - Really?
(Haha actively searches for the tickets too.)
Si Young, did you...
(I found it!)
- Hey! - What's going on?
(A physical battle breaks out.)
Hey, give me that.
- I'm the one who found this. - Hey.
I'll use that ticket. Give it to me.
(The fighter becomes more violent due to the coin she just lost.)
I'm the one who found this.
(She even uses her ground skills.)
Hey, stop it.
- Let go of it. - I found this ticket.
(She lost her mind.)
(The laughter therapist lost his smiles.)
Si Young!
(Crashing with her head)
(She uses her entire body to easily subdue 2 men.)
I didn't do it.
Leave me out. Leave me out.
- Si Young is so cool. - She's so scary.
(She finally steals the ticket.)
- She's too scary. - No.
You can't take that!
(You better let it go.)
No!
- You can't... You can't... - She's so cool.
(She even sacrifices her shoes to run away.)
- Si Young, wait. Si Young. - What's wrong with her?
(The barefoot fighter walks away with her prize.)
Why does she have to do that?
(Shocked)
There must be something related to the books.
(Jae Suk is still suspicious about the book.)
Maybe I should collect all the books.
We should collect the books and figure it out together.
How could you have the books all to yourself?
(Jong Kook suspects the books too.)
Exactly. What does it mean?
Try to find some words to combine or something.
(There must be something about the books.)
Were these books in your room?
The title of one of the books I had had "resident" in it.
And it was underlined in yellow.
- "Resident"? - Yes.
(After talking with Jong Kook, Jae Suk searches for other books.)
What could this mean?
(He takes a look at the books placed in the room.)
(Some letters are underlined!)
There it is.
(Find other books with underlined letters!)
Gosh. Someone took all the books from this room.
Come here and lift this mattress.
(So Min has the books that Jae Suk is looking for!)
Check this out.
This is number 205. Let's start with this one.
(She also focuses on the underlines.)
"One..."
"Monster".
- "You can find one monster." - "Monster".
(Among the residents, you can find one monster.)
A monster? There is a monster?
(There is 1 monster among the residents.)
Did you see the sentence the syllables make?
We should combine them.
- Did you see it? - What was it?
(Do Hyun shares the current situation.)
- It was something about a monster. - Se Chan and So Min figured it out.
- "You can find one monster." - A monster.
There is a monster among the residents!
That's right.
(Now the hints fall into place.)
"Among residents, you can find one monster."
There is a monster among the residents.
(Everyone finds out about the monster.)
(The residents become more nervous upon finding out about the monster.)
(Se Chan is writing something down.)
(What is Se Chan doing?)
(Se Chan leaves as soon as Do Hyun comes.)
- What did you write? - Nothing.
I saw you write something.
(I saw it.)
No, I erased it.
(He goes to the place where Se Chan was writing something.)
("Protein" is written at Jong Kook's room.)
Why did you write "Protein"?
It's Jong Kook's nickname.
"Protein" is the name of the monster in our drama.
- What? - Excuse me?
What?
Why did you write it?
(It's suspicious.)
- It's Jong Kook's nickname! - Why did you write it?
(Flustered)
Hold on. Stop cornering me.
I am not cornering you. Protein is the monster in our drama.
(For real)
- Seriously. - Really?
Yes. Se Chan wrote "Protein" on the whiteboard.
(What does "Protein" mean?)
- What? - It must be his mission...
to write the monster's name at each room.
Gosh, I don't know what he is talking about.
(Do Hyun's interrogation makes him nervous.)
Protein is the monster in the drama?
(Se Chan leaves them for now.)
Then Jong Kook must be the monster!
Is Se Chan the monster?
(He shares his deduction with others.)
Doesn't it add up? Think about it.
Se Chan is writing things on the whiteboard.
- What is he writing? - Seriously.
- Earlier, - The name of the monster.
- he wrote "Protein". - Really?
Where?
There is a high chance you will be the protein monster.
- Me? - Yes.
(What's he talking about?)
Is there such a thing as the protein monster?
It's a monster that appears in our drama.
Really? What does it do?
(Protein monster)
- It's just the protein monster. - Really?
- Hey, watch what you say. - It's just the protein monster.
(Jong Kook is still here.)
- Really? - Hey, watch what you say.
(Jong Kook, the human protein, feels uncomfortable.)
Is there such a monster?
- Yes, there is. - Really?
If it's a lie, Jong Kook will go after you.
It's in the trailer too.
- Really? - Yes.
- Is it in the trailer? - Yes. But...
(Protein monster in life, protein monster in drama)
Are you the protein monster?
(The protein monster looks real.)
Am I the protein monster?
That could be the case, right?
(The creator of "Protein" appears.)
- There he comes. - Hey.
(Right on time)
- Come here for a second. - Come here.
It's not like that.
Why did you write "Protein"?
I wrote it to tease you.
He says it's the same as the plot of the webtoon.
I collected all the coins.
(Did someone receive the Certification of Victory?)
Congratulations.
A resident received the Certification of Victory.
(Did someone collect 7 coins already?)
What?
A resident received the Certification of Victory.
(Hold on.)
Isn't that your voice?
(This voice)
I recorded it in advance.
(Yes, it's me.)
- That startled me. - Seriously.
That really startled me.
(But Genie is here.)
- I recorded it in advance. - Gosh.
Congratulations. A resident received the Certification of Victory.
(Before the shoot today)
(Suk Jin automated all the time-consuming tasks.)
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Okay.
- That startled me. - Seriously.
(It scared me.)
I was so surprised to see Suk Jin when the announcement came on.
(Suk Jin's here.)
I thought you were a genie for real!
What was that? That startled me.
(Ji Seok Genie deals with what bugs him quickly.)
I recorded it in advance.
I recorded a few comments because I was busy.
Do we have a winner?
It seems that way.
(I guess so.)
- Suk Jin. - Yes?
There is a winner.
(Se Chan suddenly calls Ji Seok Genie.)
- Is it Se Chan? - Who escaped?
- What is it? - Come here for a second.
(What's going on?)
- Something isn't right. - Come here for a second.
(He heads somewhere with Ji Seok Genie.)
What is it?
Something isn't right.
Should I go in here? Do you have a request?
(Genie's room)
(He takes something out of the pocket.)
(The Certification of Victory)
(Se Chan opened 3 boxes by voting 3 times.)
(He started out rich with 3 coins from the boxes.)
- Go further. Stop. - There you go. 1? 2!
(In the 1st room of coins, he acquired 2 more coins!)
(Then he acquired 2 more coins in another room of coins.)
Okay!
Through the mission, you acquired two coins.
(Thus, he collected 7 coins...)
(and became the first member to get the Certification of Victory.)
(He becomes the first person to enter the room of winners.)
This is the room.
Congratulations.
Please take a seat...
(Luxury room service...)
- and eat tasty snacks. - Thank you.
(greets the first winner.)
- You can wait here. - Okay.
Congratulations on entering the room of winners.
Let's have a toast!
That's impressive. You became the first winner today.
What's your role?
(By the way)
I just show people around and stuff.
- It drives me insane. - Why didn't I get such a role?
(He thought he was the host, but he's only an assistant.)
You are working so hard today, Suk Jin.
It drives me insane.
(He feels bad for Suk Jin.)
They are making me do everything I hate today.
- Seriously. - I hate running errands.
How did it happen?
I think they gave me this role to torment me.
(The production crew pricks)
(While Ji Seok Genie complains about his situation)
Is Se Chan done?
He is done.
When did he collect so many coins?
(They hear that Se Chan received the Certification of Victory.)
When did he do that?
How did he complete it so fast?
We need to get seven coins no matter what.
(The residents become anxious now that there is a winner.)
Is this how it's going to be? There are no tickets.
(Si Young showed strong tenacity for a ticket.)
(She finally found one.)
I am anxious. Director, hurry up.
(She received another opportunity.)
- Please vote for someone. - Okay.
(She votes for Se Chan...)
I am sorry. Se Chan.
(to participate in the mission.)
It didn't hit the floor.
(She succeeded to catch the bottle after it bounced over the ball.)
Thank you. Hold on.
(She got a coin.)
- Director, did I add one earlier? - Yes.
(She deposits the coins she got.)
Did I add one earlier?
I added two!
Look, there are two coins.
(There are 2 coins in her coin bank.)
3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
(She throws in all the coins she carried.)
(Si Young collected 7 coins.)
Please take this to Ji Seok Genie.
(Si Young also receives the Certification of Victory.)
- Please take me to the room. - Yes?
Let me see the certification.
Nice!
(She meets up with Ji Seok Genie.)
- Thank you. - Okay. Please enter.
(She enters the room of winners second.)
It's the room of winners.
My goodness.
(So Min was looking for the coins.)
What was that sound?
Why did I hear a bell?
It wasn't me.
(Even a little sound gets on his nerves in case it's a monster.)
It must have been the whistle.
See? The sound didn't come from me.
(It wasn't from me.)
What?
(Jae Suk stares at So Min without a word.)
I didn't know...
you would come of your own volition.
Please don't be like that. Please don't be like that.
(What is it?)
It can't be helped.
Don't be like that.
I am the monster.
(Is Jae Suk the monster?)
(Jae Suk says he is the monster.)
No way.
- No way. Are you serious? - Yes.
(He tries to rip off So Min's name tag.)
Are you serious? Why?
I am dressed in black.
How could you be the monster just because you look like one?
(Was he picked as the monster because of his looks?)
That's so annoying.
Jae Suk.
How could you say that I look like a monster?
(She discourages the monster.)
Then there is no twist whatsoever.
I will let you off this once.
That's your pride talking.
(He finishes the skit by acting cool.)
That's your pride talking. Jae Suk, are you the monster?
- Of course not. - Right?
(Who could be the monster that is hiding among the residents?)
(Jin Wook found a ticket for the first time.)
All right. I will enter.
(He enters the room of coins.)
Hello. What is this?
You must vote for a member who will receive the penalty...
to participate in the mission.
Will you vote for a member?
Can I win coins if I vote for a member?
(He must vote in order to participate in the mission.)
I won't vote for a member.
(It's the first time a member refused to vote.)
(Jin Wook didn't vote either in the 1st or the 2nd vote.)
(He decided not to vote even in the room of coins.)
(Sitting)
Please pick one.
(After refusing tor vote, he is suddenly asked to pick one.)
(There was a hidden rule of today's race.)
Hints on the monster will be released as well.
(You can receive a hint on the monster's identity...)
Those who refuse to vote...
(if you refuse to vote in the room of coins.)
in the room of coins will receive a hint on the monster.
(Other residents have voted without hesitation.)
I won't vote for a member.
(But Jin Wook refused to vote.)
(Jin Wook's belief brought an unexpected chance!)
(Jin Wook picks one without knowing what it is.)
"Investigation Log Number One, witness accounts on the monster".
(Investigation Log Number 1, witness accounts on the monster)
(According to the Investigation Log, the monster is a man.)
(There are 7 men besides Se Chan who has already won.)
Congratulations. A resident received the Certification of Victory.
It's the room of winners.
(More residents receive the Certification of Victory.)
- I am here. - Here.
It's this room.
(After Song Kang who collected 7 coins,)
This is incredible.
(residents enter one after another.)
Here comes another resident.
(Jin Wook figured out a way to receive the hints.)
(He focuses on searching for the tickets.)
(He finds a ticket.)
(He enters the room of coins with ease this time.)
I won't vote.
(He receives another hint by refusing to vote.)
A hint.
(What could be the second hint?)
(Ga Eun: The monster was born in April.)
(Five men are remaining.)
(Do Hyun and Jong Kook were born in April!)
(Could one of them be the monster?)
What are you doing here?
(Kwang Soo runs into Do Hyun.)
I am looking for tickets.
- Did you find a lot? - No.
- I didn't find a single ticket. - This is driving me crazy.
I looked everywhere.
(Do Hyun stops in his track with a serious expression.)
What is up with that facial expression?
What?
Are you the monster?
You are the monster, right?
I am not the monster.
Didn't you receive something? You must have a mission.
(It's not me.)
No.
I don't understand how Se Chan escaped...
when he was writing things on the whiteboard.
I guess Se Chan wasn't the monster.
Then you must be the monster.
- Why? - "Collective Invention".
You...
I am...
(I can't believe you.)
I am the fish-man in that movie, not a monster.
- The fish-man. - The fish-man.
(Jin Wook searches everywhere for another ticket.)
(While looking at the desk,)
(he moves in a hurry.)
(This laptop...)
(stayed with the members since morning.)
(Does the laptop contain information?)
(He sees something.)
(The laptop is locked with a password.)
(Hint for the password)
(What does the hint mean?)
The hint.
(Jin Wook studies the notebook for a while.)
(Then he goes through the rooms.)
- Jin Wook. - Yes?
(At that moment)
You know something, right?
(Jae Suk approaches Jin Wook.)
No, I don't have a clue.
(He grabs the books from his room.)
Putting the books together...
You are looking for books.
- The number... - You need a number, right?
That's right.
(Jae Suk noticed that Jin Wook wants the number.)
- You aren't the monster, are you? - No.
I can't be the monster.
I know the number.
(Does Jae Suk know the number?)
Avoiding the penalty isn't the end of it.
(A moment ago)
It's here.
(While looking for the hints,)
(Jae Suk put the books together.)
All the books are here.
(If you put the books in the order of the room number,)
2028.
(you get four numbers at the bottom.)
What does 2028 mean?
(Jae Suk didn't know the purpose of the number.)
What is the number for?
- Shall we work together? - That's right.
(Jin Wook who knows the laptop meets Jae Suk who knows the number.)
Okay.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- You aren't the monster, are you? - Of course not.
(They trust each other and head to the laptop.)
(They enter in 2028.)
(The laptop becomes unlocked.)
"Only those who received the Certification of Victory..."
(Only those who received the Certification of Victory...)
"by collecting seven coins become the monster's targets."
(by collecting 7 coins become the monster's targets.)
Collecting seven coins makes you a target.
I am voting for Si Young.
(The secret behind today's race)
(They could make fewer people receive the penalty.)
- Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(To receive coins,)
(some residents voted for the others to receive the penalty.)
- Will you vote? - That goes without saying.
I will vote for Se Chan.
I don't have it!
(For the tickets,)
- What is wrong with you? - I am sorry, but I found it!
(they even had scuffles.)
Congratulations.
A resident received the Certification of Victory.
(As a reward, they won the Certification of Victory.)
(But the Certification of Victory actually is...)
(the Certification of Greed.)
Someone's here.
What?
(Se Chan was the first to receive Certification of Greed.)
(He got eliminated by the monster that feeds on greed.)
(The other residents who entered the room of winners...)
(became the monster's targets as well.)
You are out.
What?
(The greedy residents met a tragic end.)
I see.
(They finally realized the meaning of today's race.)
The message is that you die...
if you live selfishly.
(The second piece of information in the memo)
"The monster's name tag..."
"contains the password of the exit for humans' survival."
"Rip off the monster's name tag to acquire the password."
(Rip off the monster's name tag to acquire the password.)
(Humans win if they get the password and escape through the exit.)
We need to eliminate the monster.
(They must eliminate the monster.)
Who could the monster be?
(Humans win if they avoid the coins and rip off the monster's name tag.)
(Hiding behind the secret identity, the monster takes out the winners.)
(The hints suggest...)
(that Jong Kook and Do Hyun are the monster candidates.)
Where did you receive so much information?
(Jin Wook)
I didn't vote for a member.
(He didn't vote for a member in the room of coins.)
That way, I received a hint.
This game teaches you various lessons.
My goodness.
You shouldn't desert the others...
(Jin Wook got lucky for not voting for a member to receive a penalty.)
no matter what.
Will you vote?
(He learned how to receive the Investigation Log.)
No, I won't vote.
(Speaking out loud)
Please pick one.
(This is it.)
Gosh, I should have done this from the start.
(He looks back on the days he was busy voting.)
"Witness accounts on the monster".
(Jae Suk receives the Investigation Log as well.)
(A Reum: The monster is among the guests.)
I won't vote.
(Upon receiving the tip-off, Ji Hyo refused to vote as well.)
This is why you shouldn't be greedy.
(What does her hint say?)
This is driving me crazy.
"The monster isn't wearing glasses."
(Yeon Ju: The monster isn't wearing glasses.)
(Hyo Im: The monster is a man.)
(The only member who fits the witness accounts is...)
That means the monster is Do Hyun.
(Lee Do Hyun.)
(All the hints point to Do Hyun.)
- Hey! - Yes?
- He wasn't born in April, right? - That's right.
(Kwang Soo wasn't born in April.)
I wasn't born in April.
Do Hyun, were you born in April?
(Sounding out)
Yes.
- Jong Kook was born in April. - I was born in April.
(Jong Kook was born in April,)
(but the monster is a guest.)
(What are you doing?)
(Ripping off)
(Do Hyun is out.)
You are the monster, right?
(Four hints pointed to Do Hyun. What's his identity?)
What was that?
- You are the monster. - I am not the monster!
What?
- I am not the monster! - What?
(Isn't Do Hyun the monster?)
I mean... I mean...
(All the hints pointed to Do Hyun.)
Aren't you the monster?
(But Do Hyun was a human.)
(Sad)
I mean...
All right.
(At that moment)
We will give a coin to Jin Wook.
- What? - What?
- Why? - Why does he get a coin?
(Jin Wook who ripped off Do Hyun's name tag gets a coin.)
Why?
- You ripped off the wrong name tag. - What is going on?
(Jin Wook gets a coin for ripping off the wrong name tag.)
- What? - Why does he get a coin?
- I don't know. - The race will continue.
I don't know.
What is going on?
(Jin Wook knows that coins will get him closer to elimination.)
So Do Hyun isn't the monster?
I don't know.
- What? - Why does he get a coin?
(Other people think coins are just nice.)
- I don't know. - The race will continue.
- I don't know. - Are you the monster?
(They gave you a coin.)
I am not.
The hint said the monster is among the guests.
(The monster is amongst the guests.)
I am not the monster.
So Do Hyun isn't the monster?
(Who is the real monster?)
(The eliminated members)
(Se Chan, Si Young, Song Kang, Haha, Do Hyun)
I should gather more hints.
I think...
My goodness.
I found it.
(She finds a ticket for the room of coins.)
Let's hurry up and go.
(She picks the Investigation Log.)
(What will it say?)
"Investigation Log Number One, witness accounts on the monster".
Hold on.
(I get it now!)
Guys! Guys! Guys!
(She calls them in a rush.)
Guys! Hold on.
Did you find a hint?
(What does So Min's Investigation Log say?)
Listen.
Seo Rim, Yeon Kyung...
"A Reum is lying."
- "A Reum is lying." - A Reum?
(Investigation Result: Among them, A Reum is lying.)
(It's a lie.)
It's a lie.
(A Reum's witness account is a lie,)
The monster isn't among the guests.
(so the monster isn't among the guests.)
- A Reum? - Earlier...
(They finally realize the meaning of the Investigation Result.)
What was A Reum's witness account?
Where is it?
Then the monster is among us.
Then I am the only one who fits the description.
(Then I am the only one who fits the description.)
You are the only one.
(Jong Kook is the only male Running Man member who was born in April.)
- Jong Kook. - While that's the case...
You are the only one who fits the description.
- Let's rip off his name tag. - I am the monster?
(Jong Kook denies it vehemently.)
Hey.
(What's his identity?)
(Panting)
No! That's not enough!
More. More.
More.
(Someone is working out in the early morning.)
I love it.
(While pumping up his muscles, Jong Kook receives a call.)
Who is it this time?
Hello.
You couldn't suppress your desire for muscle growth.
You will turn into a monster from this moment.
What are you talking about? My muscles are being well-fed now.
Gosh.
No, it's not enough.
(He starts lifting weights after hanging up the mysterious call.)
(But...)
(He turns into a muscle growth monster with high skit engagement.)
(A protein monster was really born like that.)
You will win if you induce the residents to give in to desire,
and put out eight humans.
(Induce 8 humans to give in to desire, and put them out.)
They shouldn't be hidden too well.
(He relocates the tickets so he can arouse the desire of humans.)
Okay.
That's it.
(And he must enter the room of coins sometimes to avoid suspicion.)
I'm a monster, so I can't do it anyway.
(Grinning)
Okay, I got it.
It's hard.
(Sneaky)
(To humans who went to the room of winners after collecting 7 coins,)
- What is happening? - What is happening?
- Did you succeed? Okay. - Did you?
(he approaches them as if he's one of the winners.)
- Gosh, Jong Kook. - Okay!
Jong Kook, gosh.
(Ripping)
Jong Kook, gosh. What happened?
You punk. You came back so quickly.
(A sudden change in attitude)
(What happened?)
Wait a minute, this is unfair.
(Jong Kook came to kill the winners in his spare time.)
- I'm really okay. - How could you do this to me?
(But he was caught red-handed during the investigation.)
- So follow me. - No.
I...
(3 people couldn't be his target since they didn't collect 7 coins.)
- I... - Grab him quickly.
So Min, grab him quickly.
(They all attack together against Jong Kook.)
Do you think it will be okay to do this to me?
Do you think it will be okay?
(They ripped his name tag.)
- Do you think it will be okay? - We had to rip it off.
(Monster Jong Kook is out.)
- What is it? - Is he a monster?
- Let's take a look. - Gosh.
(It was a close game, but he lost.)
- Yes. - You... This is...
(The sign of monsters and the password)
You... This is...
- You punk! - Gosh.
(What? Wait a minute.)
- He really is the monster. - Jong Kook.
- How could you look in my eyes... - Wait a minute.
79?
(Only the two digits of the password are revealed.)
Why is it "79"?
- The race isn't over yet. - Jong Kook was born in 1977.
(Monster Jong Kook is out,)
(but the race isn't over yet.)
- He was born in 1976. - That's right, 1976.
(They only have two digits for the emergency exit password.)
It's different from the book hint earlier.
There's one more monster.
(There is more than one monster?)
(According to the book hint, there's one monster among the residents.)
(For some reason, there seems to be one more monster.)
Isn't it either Kwang Soo or Jin Wook then?
(Goosebumps)
No, it's really not me.
- How could we trust you? - He also ripped the name tag off.
It's Kwang Soo then.
- Naturally... - Let's go to Kwang Soo.
- Let's go to Kwang Soo. Hurry up. - Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo is outside. - Hurry up.
(If there's one more, Kwang Soo is the likely candidate.)
(They get separated to go to each building to find Kwang Soo.)
(At that moment!)
This is unbelievable.
(So Min found the mission ticket.)
(She received another investigation log like that.)
"Monster eyewitness account".
(Min Hee: The monster wasn't in their 50s.)
It's Kang!
Wait a minute, investigation log 1 and 2 are different.
(There are also numbers for the investigation logs?)
Are they the same or different?
(If you look closely, investigation logs have numbers written on them.)
(But the members couldn't figure out the difference of the numbers.)
(Even after acquiring "Investigation Log 2",)
No way.
"The monster isn't wearing glasses."
(they mistook the hint thinking it was pointing to the same monster.)
(Investigation Log 2, Monster Eyewitness Account)
(Yeon Ju: The monster wasn't wearing glasses.)
(The number of investigation logs implied there are two monsters.)
Yoo Jae Suk.
(But at that moment...)
- Since you collected seven coins, - I didn't.
(The Certification of Victory was issued...)
the Certification of Victory has been issued to you.
(to the two without enough coins.)
I didn't collect seven coins.
(At that hour, Kwang Soo is in front of the coin bank.)
(He puts in several coins and stands up with determination.)
(Yoo Jae Suk's room?)
Do I really have to go there after receiving the coins?
(Kwang Soo already collected 7 coins.)
- I... - Just come.
(While Genie left the room,)
(the protein monster appeared after hearing the news.)
- I heard that you... - Oh, my!
(Lee Kwang Soo is out.)
- I already told you. - Isn't that right?
- What? - Did we get something?
(The humans who were dejected...)
(from being eliminated received a chat.)
(Running Man Administrator 1, Will you remain as a human?)
(Or will you resurrect as a monster underling?)
If I go out as a monster and the monster wins,
(Human or a monster underling?)
I won't receive the penalty, right?
Can I be the one to choose?
(1. They can resurrect as monster underlings as Team Monster.)
(2. But, they can't rip name tags off directly.)
(3. They will automatically receive the penalty when they're out.)
I...
will become the son of the monster.
But I suddenly became so embarrassed of myself.
(Haha and Si Young decide to remain as humans.)
I was suddenly reminded of the things I did.
I'll just become a monster.
(Song Kang and Se Chan took long to announce their resurrection.)
(Kwang Soo was putting coins in secretly as a monster underling.)
Kwang Soo.
(But Jae Suk and Jin Wook appeared.)
(As soon as he got caught,)
(he started a grand release of the coins.)
(Lee Jin Wook is on the way.)
- Kwang Soo. - Where did you put them?
(Ripping)
(Monster underling Kwang Soo is out permanently after doing his job.)
Come here.
This is it.
(They both think that Kwang Soo is the monster.)
- He's a monster. - "Underling 3"?
Lee Kwang Soo is completely out.
The race isn't over yet.
(Why is he the monster underling?)
- What is this? - Monster Underling 3?
(He's the last in ranking among the monster underlings.)
Am I number three in rank?
Kwang Soo, are you number three among the monster's underlings?
(You're also not a monster?)
(In the meantime, Ji Hyo received another investigation log.)
"All of the eyewitnesses are lying."
(Investigation Log 2, Monster Eyewitness Account)
(Investigation result: All of the eyewitnesses are lying.)
(Yeon Ju and Min Hee are lying.)
(The monster is wearing glasses. The monster is in their 50s.)
(The real monster is leading two underlings.)
(Ji Seok Genie)
Please go up.
No, don't crash. Don't crash!
(Suk Jin couldn't take his eyes off of the stock market.)
No!
(His mood swings maximize according to the KOSPI index.)
Please go up.
Who is it? I'm really busy!
(Someone called him during the middle of the day.)
Hello?
You couldn't suppress your desire to become rich.
You will turn into a monster from this moment.
What is this? Don't make prank phone calls!
(He was only watching the chart crashing while ignoring the call.)
It has to go up.
(He turned into a monster that went crazy because of stocks.)
(He's the number one actor when it comes to this kind of acting.)
I will also turn all of you into monsters.
(He even improvised lines that were not on the script.)
(A stock monster was born.)
("There's 1 monster among the residents." confused the members.)
(Among the residents, there was Kim Jong Kook.)
So let's start this.
I'm the manager of this apartment.
(Aside from the residents, there was Ji Suk Jin.)
Yes, so if there are any requests...
(The secret of submitting complaints which he shouted so much is...)
And there's another mission...
- for Suk Jin. - Okay.
Write down the requests all day,
(Ji Seok Genie even fulfilled the malicious requests.)
and pass them on to the administrator Ji Seok Genie.
Ji Seok Genie has to take care of all of those requests.
- Me? - Yes.
(As the humans pour in more selfish requests,)
Taking care of those desires...
will seem like a joke to others,
but we will give you two a coin for each request.
(he'll get 1 coin for each request.)
You can give all of the coins to someone who doesn't have seven.
(They can save coins to human coin banks by force...)
(with the coins they earned from the complaints.)
This... Who wrote this?
"Please get me some coffee". Who wrote this? Yes!
(Ji Seok Genie's complaint time started like that.)
Genie.
(Plus 1 coin)
(Ji Seok Genie saved coins from inducing the desire of humans.)
- You wanted this, didn't you? - Who did?
(Plus 1 coin)
You got a total of 12 coins.
(In total, he processed 12 requests.)
(He earns 12 coins.)
Okay.
Si Young made me mad today.
(Ji Seok Genie's first target is Lee Si Young.)
(He puts the coins in himself.)
Si Young's room...
(Lee Si Young mistook all of them...)
I don't have any at all, right?
I added 2! Look, there are 2 coins.
(as her coins blinded by desire.)
- Gosh. - Why?
(She was out with their cooperative play like that.)
(He was teased all day,)
Okay.
(but Monster Number 2 was preparing for revenge.)
Kwang Soo, I helped you.
(Ji Seok Genie)
(He appeared imposingly with his underlings.)
Am I number three in rank?
- Kang, why did you come out? - Me?
(Song Kang, Underling 2, He can't directly attack.)
- I'm his tour guide. - I requested a tour.
(He gathered his underlings with the ridiculous excuse of sightseeing.)
Yes, please come this way.
(He's a monster, but he was mistaken as a zombie.)
Wait a minute.
(Jae Suk and Jin Wook still don't know that Suk Jin's a monster yet.)
- Jin Wook, are you a monster? - No, he's not.
Kang, why did you come out?
Wait a minute. Why did you come out?
(Ji Seok Genie's preemptive attack)
- Wait a minute. - Rip his name tag off.
Kang, rip his name tag off.
- Is it Kang? - Rip it off.
Kang, grab him.
(The two didn't see the hint "Everything is a lie.",)
(so they think that guest Song Kang is a monster.)
Grab him.
- Let me go. - Rip it off.
(The Monster is trying to maintain his poker face.)
- Song Kang! - Grab him.
(Monster underling number 2 Song Kang is out.)
- I ripped it off. - He's a monster.
- I ripped it off. - He's out.
(Ripping)
(Jae Suk, the 7th human, is out in the meantime.)
Who is it?
Grab him.
(Underlings!)
Is Suk Jin a monster? What is happening?
(Goosebumps)
Who is it? I'm out.
(Team Monster will win if they eliminate Lee Jin Wook.)
Jin Wook!
You need to rip Suk Jin's name tag off.
(Detective Lee Jin Wook versus Monster Ji Suk Jin)
- No! - Oh, my.
(Lee Jin Wook just grabbed Suk Jin's name tag at that moment.)
(The person who rips it off first will win today. Who is the winner?)
Wait a minute.
(Ripping)
(Human Lee Jin Wook is out.)
Good job.
(It was Suk Jin.)
(Team Monster won after eliminating 8 humans.)
Good job.
(The race ended.)
Okay, I will tell you the results.
(It's time to announce the result.)
The monster among residents who eats the desire of humans...
- was Kim Jong Kook. - Gosh.
The monster aside from the residents was Ji Suk Jin.
- Yes. - It was Genie.
- Genie betrayed us. - Gosh.
Why do you have so many underlings?
(Monsters)
As such, Team Monster won.
(Genie was able to rip off Jin Wook's name tag.)
- Gosh. - Really?
- Honestly, I... - You made this happen?
- Suk Jin... - I could have won.
(That was close.)
- He did such a good job. - Really?
He left while leading underlings, but he was really not trustworthy.
I blamed you.
(Not-so-trustworthy Genie led the team to victory.)
Among all of the humans, five of them will receive the penalty.
(The 5 humans will receive a penalty.)
That's a lot.
Kwang Soo and Kang, who used to be humans,
had their name tags ripped off. They're penalty candidates.
(The 2 humans that were resurrected but eliminated will be included.)
Me?
That was the condition of resurrecting.
(The total of 7 will participate in the penalty-deciding game.)
That's right.
And 5 among the humans... We ended with 5 humans earlier, right?
(Based on penalty votes for 5 Team Human members,)
In that order, a total of seven are penalty candidates.
(there are 7 candidates for the penalty.)
Penalty candidates.
Please draw a card now.
(They will select 3 people to receive the penalty with a draw.)
He survived.
(Haha's safe.)
- I survived. - Haha survived.
- I also survived. Next. - What is happening?
(Jae Suk the unlucky man is also safe.)
- Are you okay? - Do Hyun...
(Do Hyun the lucky man is safe.)
Did you die?
(What about Si Young?)
- Penalty. - Penalty.
(They picked penalty.)
- Penalty. - Gosh.
(Si Young and Jin Wook picked penalty.)
Wait a minute. Who will receive the penalty between the two?
(Between Kwang Soo and Song Kang, who will receive the penalty?)
1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3. - Penalty.
(Kwang Soo picked penalty.)
- Gosh, Kang. - Song Kang...
He's really unlucky.
(Kwang Soo, Si Young, and Jin Wook will receive the penalty.)
That's amazing.
For today's penalty, you will get your cheek slapped with water...
to cleanse your human desires.
(It's a water slap penalty.)
- It's simple. - It's simple.
I understand why people want to come again because they're upset.
- That's right. - Come again.
- Come again. - I kept thinking about that.
(He promises to appear again to redeem himself.)
- Come again. - You will be reminded of this...
when you go back home.
(He takes a refreshing shower.)
1, 2, 3.
(Si Young and Kwang Soo will splash at each other.)
(Splash)
Be careful.
(Only Si Young got wet.)
I didn't do it on purpose. I'm sorry.
(Kwang Soo's cunning, sudden attack wraps up the penalty.)
- I was too fast. - That was cheap.
I would like to thank the four leads of "Sweet Home".
(Thanks to Song Kang, Lee Jin Wook, Lee Si Young and Lee Do Hyun...)
- Good job. - "Sweet Home"!
"Sweet Home"!
(of "Sweet Home" for participating as humans.)
2021 Running League Rookie Draft.
(2021 Running League Rookie Draft)
(This is the 2021 Running League Rookie Draft.)
Yoo Jae Suk, Yang Se Chan.
(The two club owners made an appearance,)
- NT... - I will skip that player.
(and distinctive rookie players followed them.)
- I will never draft that player. - That player is kicked out.
- You can be sure to skip them. - You can be sure to skip them.
(Only players who you can trust to skip have participated.)
He's a monster rookie the world is paying attention to.
(Real world-class players finally came.)
Ryu Hyun Jin.
(Korean Monster, Monster pitcher, Ryu Hyun Jin)
He's the crown prince of the mount who dominates with his sliders.
(The crown prince of masterpiece sliders!)
Kim Kwang Hyun.
(Korean Big Leaguer, Ace KK, Kim Kwang Hyun)
Kwang Hyun, can you show us a slider?
(He will finally show his masterpiece slider at Running Man.)
(He threw it to the ground.)
- What is he doing? - We're better than him.
We're better than him.
Okay.
(Because of their inadequate performance,)
Ryu Hyun Jin is 10 dollars, and Kim Kwang Hyun is 5 dollars.
(their annual salary is decreasing mercilessly.)
Are you going to cut my salary?
- Let's break off the deal. - Mr. Ryu!
(Did they even end up breaking off the deal with the club owner?)
- I will quit. - Hyun Jin's deal broke off.
The competition is fierce.
(Running League's big match will continue right away after that.)
Is it possible to hit the ball with that?
(But are they playing baseball with a frying pan and flippers?)
- Gosh. - No!
Do you know how much you cost me?
(The Running League ended up with a bench-clearing brawl.)
Are you a thug?
(World-class Ryu Hyun Jin versus Kim Kwang Hyun's...)
- That was cheap. - Kwang Hyun!
(variety show baseball match, what will be the ending?)
The vibe here is no joke.
(Ryu Hyun Jin and Kim Kwang Hyun, Fiery Stove League)