- Hello.
- Suk Jin finally...
- That's right.
- started his YouTube channel.
- I did.
- YouTube.
- "Ji Suk Jin World".
"Ji Suk Jin World"
How did you know that?
Thank you so much.
You asked us
to mention it in the show.
- Don't say that. Stay quiet.
- "Ji Suk Jin World"
I was originally going to start
a talk show,
- but...
- Actually,
Suk Jin wants
to make it a talk show,
- but I'm worried about it.
- I see.
You're not a good talker.
(Straightforward)
(He's known as a poor talker.)
He just rambles on.
My nickname is Jee Talk.
I can't believe this.
Hey!
- You're Jee Talk.
- This is crazy.
You always talk about yourself.
He's funny when he's a guest.
- I know.
- That's not true.
I shot the first video,
and it was really fun.
- Was it fun?
- Because I talk about myself.
Suk Jin, I watch your video
when I can't fall asleep at night.
(It helps eliminate insomnia.)
- I just sleep listening to it.
- It puts me to sleep.
You should sleep with the video on.
- That's right.
- It works.
- It's really funny.
- A lot of people recently...
started their own channels. Suk Jin
started "Ji Suk Jin World."
Jung Jun Ha started
"Ox Head Rice Soup."
I heard you came up with that name.
- Right. I did.
- For Jun Ha?
- I joked that it was the best name.
- It's a really strange name.
- What?
- "Ox Head Rice Soup".
It became the talk of the town
because it's strange.
- Really?
- Sure.
- It's somewhat addictive.
- I know.
Yours sounds a little lame.
It just sounds like a pun.
- It's a pun.
- Right.
Don't you think so?
- Hang on.
- He sounds upset.
Are you hurt?
Why do you sound like that?
- Why are you so huffy?
- Anyway,
I promise that I won't get
any help from you guys.
- Suk Jin.
- I'm serious.
- Can I give you some advice?
- What?
They say singers live
lives that are like their songs.
- That's true.
- And so do the TV shows.
So "Ji Suk Jin World" might
end up as your own world.
- That's right.
- Oh no.
- Seriously.
- What should we do?
Suk Jin, you seem
very disappointed.
- I'm not disappointed. I'm furious.
- What?
(Jee Talk explodes with anger.)
- Suk Jin.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
What a mean thing to say.
- I'm sorry.
- Suk Jin.
I'm so sorry.
- That's just mean.
- I apologize.
I was about to curse at you.
But I held it back
so you wouldn't cry.
Actually, I find So Min's book
more interesting than your channel.
I see. Is it fun?
- It's fun, isn't it?
- I just can't stop reading it.
The reason I can't
stop reading it is...
because I don't understand
what it means.
So I have to keep reading it.
I just don't get it.
You just have no literary sense.
I have no idea what this means.
Read it for us.
"It was weaker than I thought."
"It was softer than steamed eggs."
"The earthen pot
hasn't gone cold yet."
- What?
- "It wasn't thick."
This is okay.
"The spoon touched
my heart immediately."
- What does that mean?
- The title is "Again."
It's "Again." It means my heart...
- My mind is...
- Is this a publication party?
Ms. Jeon.
- We're doing this right.
- Ms. Jeon.
- She does sound like a writer.
- Is this a publication party?
"Again" is about
before you fall in love again.
When your love ended,
you thought you'd be very stiff.
But you were still weak
and even softer than steamed eggs.
So it's still easy for you
to have someone in your heart.
- Then...
- All right then.
Then you should publish
a commentary on this book too.
Like the key.
We would need a commentary.
- Like a director's cut.
- Exactly.
What is this?
There's a bookmark.
- It's a bookmark.
- You can use this.
- What's this?
- It's a bookmark.
A bookmark.
You should keep this in your wallet.
Me?
- You can keep it in your wallet.
- Okay.
Se Chan said it's fun.
Don't ask that.
Before we start the race,
we will have two guests today.
- Are we having guests today?
- Please come on in.
Who are they?
(Who are today's guests?)
- Hello.
- Is she Han Na?
- Han Na.
- Is it Han Na?
- It's Han Na.
Han Na is here.
Han Na, you should be here
with us during the opening.
- Han Na is always...
- You don't need to wait.
- I know.
- You should start with us.
- Han Na.
- Happy New Year.
You're wearing a formal suit.
- A formal suit?
- Long time no see.
- Han Na.
- Yes?
You have a new stylist now.
- You look pretty.
- I like your clothes.
I'm wearing something for the fall.
- It's pretty.
- Do you like it?
- I can't believe this.
- Thank you for coming the long way.
You should welcome me.
His clothes are hilarious.
Kyung-hwan has changed
his style a lot.
- He looks different.
- I know.
Gosh, Kyung-hwan.
- What happened?
- What happened to you?
- I'll bite all you guys.
I guess...
about two of us will be...
let go this spring.
(He feels threatened
by their frequent appearance.)
There will be a reorganization
taking place this spring.
It's good
that Suk Jin brought it up.
- Sure.
- I'm very grateful.
(Good self-assessment)
What are you talking about?
Then the average age of the members
will be lowered.
That's right. Anyway...
Thank you.
we should think about...
- Han Na's frequent appearances.
- I see.
And Kyung-hwan is here too.
- All right.
- Why do you think...
I started my YouTube channel?
- Is it his big picture?
- Sure.
- He's so cool.
- I know.
- He has a big picture.
- He's so mature.
He's really mature.
- I guess...
- He's the oldest one here.
there wasn't a plan,
but they might think about it.
(A commission on Suk Jin's
retirement has been established.)
- Exactly.
- Aren't I right?
- It wasn't a plan.
- The directors will start to move.
"Is he that cool? Then we should
go forward with the plan."
They started
to write down something.
"Suk Jin said okay."
It's an early retirement.
Today...
- Please pay attention to guests.
- Kyung-hwan is here.
- These days...
- Kyung-hwan, relax.
You're throwing out
your chest too much.
- Why is he throwing out his chest?
- Just relax.
Why are you so nervous?
- I have to do something.
- But...
- I should at least show my chest.
- About Kyung-hwan.
I'm very happy to see
Kyung-hwan on our show.
But he's never been
much of a performer.
Han Na is always good.
- She shows a lot of funny things.
- She's funny.
But Kyung-hwan is...
- I know that.
- Kyung-hwan is different.
I guess the directors
are quite tenacious.
- But I think...
- They don't give up.
- They wait until it works.
- Until he shows something.
Actually, a few days ago,
I met a kid on the street.
The kid called me
"the guy from Running Man."
- He watched you on TV.
- I appeared a lot.
But there are a lot
of bad comments about me.
Kyung-hwan, what do you mean?
"I'm Kyung-hwan's fan,"
"but I don't want to see him
on Running Man."
(I like Kyung-hwan, but I don't
want to see him in Running Man.)
It's positive and negative
at the same time.
"Did you watch Running Man?
Kyung-hwan is unbelievable."
- You're unbelievable.
- "He was not funny in the show."
People say stuff like that.
That's quite unique though.
You're here a lot
as a guest who's not funny.
When I was here last time,
I got my part cut
during the opening.
And I got water splashed
over me at the end of the show.
- It just doesn't seem right.
- It doesn't seem right.
You're saying
it's somewhat unbalanced.
It's just unbalanced.
That doesn't seem right.
So I want to keep things
balanced today.
Please pay a lot
of attention to me today.
- I'll try my best.
- All right.
I bet Chul Min likes you.
He keeps calling you.
I got a wedding invitation
from him as soon as I got here.
I get 200 dollars
for doing the show.
But I have to give him
a monetary gift of 100 dollars.
I'm here to make 100 dollars today.
- Hey.
- It's only 200 dollars.
You should think about
the next show Chul Min will work on.
You should worry about yourself.
Things aren't going well now.
- You should be prepared.
- You're being funny today.
- You're good.
- You're on a roll today.
- It's the reorganization season.
- Kyung-hwan is funny...
- when he doesn't try hard.
- He's funny.
- You're good.
- You're funny.
- You've been here a lot.
- That's right.
So you don't have to try so hard.
If you keep farting,
you might end up pooping.
- I don't like that.
- I'll poop.
- Don't say that.
- You can't poop here.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
The crew members are tenacious.
They didn't want to give up.
He's the guest we don't give up on.
And there's good news...
about Han Na.
- She's hosting a radio show now.
- Right.
She recently posted a video...
with ZICO.
Se Chan told me about it.
"Did you watch it?"
"Han Na danced with ZICO."
"I watched the video by chance."
"She's a terrible dancer."
(Se Chan said
she's a terrible dancer.)
(What was her dance like?)
(Squeaking)
(No groove)
(No composure)
- What?
- That's because Han Na...
danced right after Hwasa
and other good dancers.
- That's right. I watched it too.
- She was right after them.
I did it well. It's really hard.
Han Na.
- But you were a dance major.
- Right.
But it's different
from the dance moves of today.
I also thought she didn't
have the vibe.
She should have this feeling.
Han Na, why don't you show it to us?
- All right then.
- Please play...
- "Any Song" by ZICO.
- I can't dance alone.
- Suk Jin, dance with me.
- You tried it as well.
- Suk Jin did a good job.
- You two should dance together.
- It wasn't my official video.
- Just try it.
Suk Jin was like dancing
at his 60th birthday party.
- He was like this.
- Hey!
- Why would you say that?
- You will see.
- Let's give it a try.
- Dance with me.
Please play ZICO's song.
This is really hard.
- Han Na changes her face.
- Touch your nose, Suk Jin.
It's a performance.
I can't believe I'm watching this.
This is amazing.
- They're doing it.
- It's started.
(Before they start, please watch
ZICO and Hwasa's dance first.)
This is...
(Squeaking)
- What's that?
- That's not how you do it.
(That's not how you do it.)
Look at him.
Why is he being like this?
(He's acting cute
all of a sudden.)
It's not right. He almost hit her.
Look at Suk Jin.
It's a mess.
This is terrible.
It's so funny.
Isn't this right?
(Running)
It's just a random dance from him.
(She suddenly turns the wheel.)
It's so strange.
Something's not right.
Like I always say,
Han Na and Suk Jin are
a good duo.
- That's true.
- I agree.
All right then. Kyung-hwan,
dance in your own style.
- Me?
- He doesn't dance well.
"I'm dancing." Something like this.
- Can you do that?
- But...
I need someone to dance with me.
We have Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is recommended.)
Ji Hyo just asked me whispering,
"What song this is?"
(She just asked me
what song this is.)
The song topped
all the music charts.
But she never heard it before.
Gosh, she's so...
She lives in a cave.
- Ji Hyo is so...
- She's like Robinson Crusoe.
That sounds just like Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
You should do this
when the song starts.
Let's do this. Music, please.
The song suits your outfit.
You can just dance as you like.
Kyung-hwan and Ji Hyo.
(The song starts.)
- Ji Hyo seems to know something.
- There they go.
(Swaggering)
Kyung-hwan got it wrong,
but Ji Hyo is copying him.
(Ji Hyo copies what's wrong.)
- She's just copying him.
- This is nice.
(This is just a random dance.)
These are different dance moves.
- Ji Hyo doesn't know anything.
- Isn't this right?
She's never seen it before.
Ji Hyo doesn't know anything.
She has no idea.
She's never heard it before.
(Kyung-hwan is going too far
with his dance.)
What's that?
Don't come near me.
That was good. Well done.
(They are so funny.)
Kyung-hwan, you're so funny.
- It was amazing.
- She's got the vibes of the 40s.
That was very good.
This is Ji Hyo's new character.
Ji Hyo has found her new character.
- This is who she is.
- Right.
She doesn't know
what's going on in the world.
She's like a frozen woman
who's back after a long time.
We're going to start the race now.
We were going to shoot this show
in Europe in February,
so we already finished
making an on-the-spot survey.
But we decided not to go...
- because of the current situation.
- I see.
So we will have an Indoor Special
in this building for the time being.
- Good.
- It's hard...
to shoot a show with a lot of people
in the open air now.
So before the race,
I'll hand out some phones first.
Phones?
- They have numbers on them.
- They have numbers.
- What's that?
- We should pick a good number.
I want you to take turns
and pick a phone.
Can I just pick one?
- I want number 3.
- I'll pick number 4.
- Number 3.
- I'll go with number 2.
You're not supposed to see
what's on the phone yet.
They all have different things.
Now you can check
the phone you chose.
Okay.
This is important.
What should we do?
What? Time?
(Yang Se Chan)
- What is...
- What is this?
It shows a time.
You're not supposed
to talk about it.
(So Min's stopwatch, 30 minutes)
(Jae Suk's stopwatch,
2 hours and 10 minutes)
(Kyung-hwan's stopwatch,
3 hours and 10 minutes)
(Se Chan's stopwatch, 50 minutes)
Please push the start button
all at the same time now.
- It's running down.
- I pressed it.
How much time do you have?
It's running down.
I guess some of you
don't have much time.
Please hurry.
You're given a random time
on your phone.
- Time is ticking.
- The second you run out of time,
- you'll be eliminated.
- What?
You will get eliminate
when the time runs out.
(Eliminated?)
- It's too soon.
- Then...
I don't have much time left.
But each of you has
your special circles.
While you stay in the circle,
the countdown is paused.
- I see.
- It sounds fun already.
- I should stay in the circle.
- Let me tell you where they are.
They are in the studio
on the second floor.
And your time is ticking even now.
You should hurry
and find your circles now.
- It's on the second floor.
- We have to hurry.
- Let's go to the 2nd floor.
- The 2nd floor?
We have to go to the second floor.
The second floor?
We have to hurry.
(Kwang Soo is going up the stairs.)
I can't believe this.
It's coming down
from the fifth floor.
This is faster.
Over there.
Circle? What circle?
Where is it? I don't have time.
(Where on earth is the circle?)
Is it here?
(He finally finds the studio.)
This is it.
Is it here?
(As he put his foot on the circle,)
(it turns green.)
Okay.
I don't have much time left.
Is this the circle?
Jong Kook, you have to hurry.
It stops once you get on here.
Step on it and pause the stopwatch.
This is it.
Move over.
(The other members
rush to the studio too.)
- What?
- Hey.
You can pick any circle you want.
- What do I do?
- Gosh.
It's done. I lost too much time.
- Me too.
- I'm doomed.
- It's so close.
If I get eliminated, can I go home?
- Can we?
- I guess we can go home.
Let me tell you something.
This is an individual game,
Indoor Special Part 1,
Running Countdown.
- Cool.
- Okay.
- This is an individual game.
- I like it.
You should stick to the timetable
that you're given today.
The last one to survive...
after the Name Tag Elimination race
will be the winner...
- and get a prize.
- There's the Name Tag Elimination.
The members who are eliminated
during the mission...
will be the judges here.
You will be the judges
in the yellow costumes here.
- I see.
- It will be humiliating.
You will help the crew members
with the shooting.
- We can't go home.
- We're not going home.
- It will be fun to be a judge.
- No.
- It sounds like fun.
- It must be hard.
Judges will just watch the game.
- I might be on TV longer that way.
- That might be true.
(He'd become a judge
to be on TV for a longer time.)
- Just keep trying hard.
- Okay.
- I'm just saying that.
- Don't give up too soon.
While you sit
in the circle like that,
the countdown is paused.
- Okay.
- Once you leave the circle,
the time will run down again.
That's amazing.
The time will keep running even when
you eat or go to the restroom...
- once you leave the circle.
- Really?
Do I have to stay in the circle
the whole day then?
I should've gone
to the restroom sooner.
You can move around.
It will just take some of your time.
- I'm in trouble.
- Some of us...
might have very little time left.
Right.
How much would it be?
He doesn't have
much time left for real.
This is too harsh.
Let's not do this to him.
Can I give my time to Suk Jin?
- This is sad.
- Please.
Hang on.
Is Ji Suk Jin World
where he ends up?
Suk Jin.
Thank you.
You should get out of the circle
and complete your mission...
while the time runs down.
The team
who completes the mission...
will get a chance
to win more time...
by investing their time
to spin the roulette.
Can we do that?
- We play games to get more time.
- We need to do that.
Or you will get a chance
to find out how much time...
a person you pick has left.
It's an individual game.
You can win twice as much time
as your investment.
"Twice as much"?
You can steal time from others
as much as you invested.
- Gosh.
- That's good.
You can also give time to others
as much as you invested.
There's also a dud.
You can steal from who's
in first place plus 20 minutes.
These are the five sections.
After you change
into your team uniform,
we will start the race.
Do we get timed
when we get changed?
Yes, it will be counted.
- Come on.
- Seriously?
You're being strict.
Then I'll get changed here.
- Let's stay here.
- I'll get changed here.
Your team uniforms are set
in the waiting room.
I should hurry.
Jae Suk is going.
Can you bring mine?
- Jae Suk.
- No.
- Bring mine.
- Bring mine too.
- We'll lose time if we go.
- I don't have much time.
- I really don't have much time.
- Me neither.
I think I'm okay.
- He must have a lot of time.
- I know.
I'll tell my stylist to come.
I'll call someone too.
- I'll ask someone to bring it.
- Could you ask for mine too?
Can you bring my clothes?
I don't even have my phone.
I didn't bring it.
- Goodness.
- Ji Hyo, do you have...
access to the Internet
on your phone?
- On this phone?
- Yes.
- Yes, I do.
- You're completely disconnected.
That's not true.
(In the waiting room)
Are you here for the clothes?
You can't.
- Why not?
- You can't.
Do you think I don't have a stylist?
- No.
- You can't do this.
I said no.
You can't take these for them.
How dare you?
Kyung-hwan, take it away.
You can't do this.
She's here.
- Push them hard towards me.
- Han Na.
Why isn't mine here yet?
Play fair and wait until we leave.
(What?)
(Jae Suk and Kyung-hwan take
Kwang Soo and Se Chan's clothes.)
Jae Suk, I don't have time.
These are Kwang Soo's.
Where are mine?
Where are my clothes?
Give them to me now. Goodness.
(Kyung-hwan steals
Se Chan's clothes.)
No, give them to me.
I really don't have much time. Look.
All right, go. Let's go.
(Jae Suk stole
Kwang Soo's clothes.)
(He plans to go far away.)
Wait, I'm using up my time.
(Kwang Soo is the only one
without his clothes.)
Where are my clothes? What?
- Give them to me.
- He stopped me...
from bringing them to you.
- Who?
- Jae Suk.
- What? Who?
- Jae Suk did.
- Jae Suk?
- It was Jae Suk.
Goodness.
(He gets playful again.)
What's wrong with Jae Suk?
That's the reason why Jae Suk is
on Running Man.
- He's such a trickster.
- Just to tease you.
I suppose Kwang Soo doesn't have
much time.
My clothes.
(He goes to find his clothes.)
Okay.
(Why is he coming back?)
Is he going to carry it?
What? It's Jae Suk's.
He's going to hide it.
It's dirty from the start.
What's wrong with Jae Suk?
(He goes to the 2nd floor after
hiding the clothes on the 1st.)
Where is he?
(Why is he in the elevator?)
(Were you looking for me?)
Let's die together.
Come on.
We don't have time.
Go and find them.
- Where are they?
- Go.
(He gets on the elevator.)
Kwang Soo has...
his clothes downstairs,
but he took the wrong elevator.
He should be going down,
but he went up instead.
Kwang Soo did?
It's getting worse.
Wait.
It's going up.
- Yes.
- They're going to the sixth floor.
Kwang Soo.
- He's so funny.
- Okay.
Why is he sitting here?
- You moved your seat.
- He moved his own seat.
Come back to your original spot.
Why did you do such a thing?
- That wasn't necessary.
- Wait.
You focus on the wrong things.
He loves Running Man, doesn't he?
Right.
I almost lost my mind
for the last two weeks.
I think he loves it.
Let's have a shoot every week.
He's a big fan.
He's one of those
who love Running Man.
It's inside out.
Hey!
(He gets playful again.)
It started.
Their fight is endless.
How will they survive
without Running Man?
They're on the show just to do that.
(Their precious reason why
they're on the show)
Do you see the look on his face?
(He's doing the same thing.)
Hey.
He might get an electric shock.
- It'd be funny if he passes out.
- I know.
- Why did he do that?
I don't understand why he did that.
He's funny too. Why can't he
wait for Jae Suk to come back?
Darn it.
Why did he do that?
Why did he flip them?
It was to gain one more second.
- He ended up losing more time.
- Right.
He does a good job
of acting his part.
(After getting a break)
(Jae Suk gets playful again
for the third time.)
Seriously?
My goodness.
- It's deja vu.
What is he doing?
He's doing it again.
- What's wrong with him?
- Why does he do that?
I don't understand why he put it
on top of the other.
Why did he do that?
Do the two of you have
a separate script?
- What's wrong today?
- We don't.
(It's the same story as last time.)
- He must have a lot of time.
- Right.
- He has free time.
- He does.
- He has additional time.
- That's why.
- Kwang Soo doesn't have much time.
- I don't think he does.
Isn't he already a judge?
- You can be a judge, Kwang Soo.
- You're wearing it backward.
(His top is on backward.)
It must say on the script.
"Kwang Soo wears his top backward."
(Do they get a separate script?)
"He makes a silly face
while panting."
(Everyone gets changed.)
(Current Time Status)
- Let's start the first mission.
- All right.
- We're off to a good start.
- We're finally starting.
You will play in 2 teams of 5.
Your first mission is
Finding Hidden Objects.
- Finding Hidden Objects?
- Hidden Objects.
Did they hide them in advance?
The leader of each team will look at
a picture with five hidden objects.
Find each object...
from the Running Man office
on the 16th floor...
and bring it back to succeed.
Bring five objects in a relay.
The first team to finish wins...
- Is it a relay?
- and gets to spin the roulette.
It's a relay.
- Today...
- The 16th floor is far from here.
- I know.
- Sixteenth floor?
It's quite far.
(Is that so?)
Discuss and divide into two teams.
Do we discuss it?
The two guests can pick
their team members.
That's right. Kyung-hwan.
I pick Se Chan.
(His first pick is Se Chan.)
He knows the building structure,
and he's sharp.
- I pick Jong Kook.
- Okay.
You made a good choice.
Kyung-hwan, pick Jae Suk.
He has a lot of time.
- Does he?
- He was relaxed before...
- because he has free time.
- That's why he went around.
Okay, I'll join you.
So Min.
(He selects whomever he wants.)
I got it.
She doesn't have much time.
It was so that you can be together.
(She gets time with Se Chan.)
- He's setting it up.
- He is.
- You're thinking like the staff.
- Okay.
I should set them up.
(Team Han Na and Team Kyung-hwan)
Please sit with your team.
Come to where the team leader is.
- Go, Suk Jin.
- Did you change the seats?
We have to sit with our teams.
- We should split in half.
- Come here, Suk Jin.
Go slowly, Suk Jin.
(Time passes when they stand up.)
Hey.
(Jae Suk grabs Suk Jin's jacket.)
(Go slowly, Suk Jin.)
(The time ticks away helplessly.)
(Suk Jin kicks back but misses.)
- Suk Jin.
- Darn it.
Go.
- Go.
- Why you...
- Gosh.
- He lost 10 seconds.
That brat.
What did you say?
Do you mean a brat?
"That brat".
Please pick the first player.
When it starts,
come up and uncover it.
Find an object, say it out loud,
and go upstairs.
To the 16th floor?
You have to decide the order
in advance.
- Really?
- Yes.
- To avoid confusion, go this way.
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
- Otherwise, it's confusing.
- Go, Han Na.
- Let's start with Han Na.
Let's do that same.
- Go this way.
- Start with Se Chan.
- Okay.
- Since I have time, shall I start?
- How much time does Jae Suk have?
I know. He must have a lot of time.
Shall I go?
To distinguish the teams,
one of you will wear this.
Han Na.
She's so fast.
- Han Na.
- You dropped one.
Why are you telling us to wear them?
Make the other team wear them.
Aren't these for us?
- She's nice.
- She is.
Han Na is nice.
Is it only for one team?
Yes.
This will be taken into account
during the reorganization.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
Will Suk Jin run for anything
to win points?
Did you hear what Suk Jin said?
"Han Na, why did you take them?"
This will be counted.
- It's considered during evaluation.
- Of course.
The producers' behavior
is suspicious.
Everyone is taking notes, Suk Jin.
Let's get started.
- Okay.
Get ready, set...
- Go.
- Do I go too?
- Isn't Jae Suk starting?
- We start from that side.
Goodness.
- I thought you were starting.
- What's this?
- Let us see it.
(Finding hidden objects
for Team Han Na)
Why is it this way?
(Se Chan also checks his picture.)
(Finding hidden objects
for Team Kyung-hwan)
Se Chan, sit down and look.
Let us look too.
Can you sit?
Should we find this?
(I don't have a clue.)
You only have to spot one.
(The viewers can join in too.)
(Looking closely...)
I see one. Can I spot it out?
A mouse!
(I see one. Can I spot it out?
A mouse!)
(Is there a mouse in this drawing?)
(A mouse)
Hold on.
Go!
A mouse!
- Hurry up and get one.
- Spot one for starters.
(Se Chan runs to the office
to find a mouse.)
Han Na, at least spot something.
A mouse...
(Every second counts.)
A mouse.
Let's go.
(Se Chan's familiar with
the building layout.)
I don't have much time to spare.
Han Na, at least spot something.
Spot an object in there.
- A flower!
- Find the hidden object.
A flower!
A flower being there isn't odd.
No, this.
This. I see this. The pointer.
Okay, go.
- The pointer.
- Okay, go.
- Okay.
- Find one.
- Where are you going?
- Where are you off to?
(Where is she going?)
(Han Na urgently runs off.)
(Am I going in the wrong direction?)
You should go that way.
I don't know
the layout of the building.
- What's wrong with you?
- What about that pointer?
What about that pointer?
You have to find one
on the 16th floor.
- Sorry about that.
- You made her waste time.
Goodness.
(Han Na heads toward the elevator.)
Someone pressed the down button.
It's on the 16th floor, right?
It's my first time in this building.
I'm on the 2nd floor,
so I can't run upstairs.
Right? Right.
(She gets on the elevator
she waited for.)
(What?)
Wait.
(She's lost for words.)
(There's no button
to the 16th floor.)
I have to go to the 16th floor,
so why isn't there a button?
(Her first trip to SBS isn't easy.)
What now?
(The elevator Han Na took
doesn't go up to the 16th floor.)
Sir, does the clock stop
during lunchtime?
Or will the time keep running?
Yes, it'll keep running.
Then we can just eat here.
You always...
address him as "sir"
with these types of challenges.
He might answer me more kindly.
It has become a habit.
Sirs, you're all doing great today.
(The Alchemist of Titles)
- Right?
- She won't know this.
Han Na would never know.
So it's here.
Can I take any one of these?
(Se Chan sees...)
(a mouse.)
Can't I just take this?
Is that it? Okay, that's simple.
Can it be this easy?
I must've found an easy one.
(He manages to save a lot of time.)
Where could Han Na be?
Wait, she hasn't come by.
Okay.
(Meanwhile, Han Na...)
Over there... Should I go there?
(She runs and runs
throughout the unfamiliar layout.)
Why won't this respond?
(The elevator won't respond to her.)
Hello?
What is this?
(The elevators at SBS
aren't easy for first-timers.)
What's going on? It didn't stop.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
No...
That elevator
must not stop on this floor.
It must travel straight
to the 16th floor from the 1st.
Gosh, it's going down again.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan returns.)
Okay, I'm good.
- He's here.
- Here's the mouse.
- It's a relay.
- Already?
It's a relay, so who's next?
All right, hurry up.
Spot it as fast as you can.
So we're spotting for others?
We're spotting objects
in the same drawing?
So Min, listen to me
while you look for the object.
Make a left right away
and take the stairs down.
(Se Chan explodes with charisma.)
Make a left right away
and take the stairs down.
Head to the main hall
and take the elevator on your right.
Take the elevator
up to the 16th floor.
(They all get butterflies
in their stomachs.)
That was cool.
- The one on the right?
- Yes.
- Which one?
- The right. Keep looking!
- The shortcut to love.
- That was manly.
Take the right elevator up.
Maybe he'll be waiting for her
at the top.
With a rose in his hand...
and flipping over a sketchbook.
I see one. It's a whistle.
(Meanwhile, she spots a whistle.)
(That is correct!)
- Go.
- A whistle?
Yes, a whistle.
Just know that you're
walking into an office.
Oh, dear. What now?
Take a left and go down the stairs.
(She recalls what Se Chan said.)
Yes, this goes up to the 22nd floor.
Sorry, guys.
(She gets on the elevator
that heads to the 16th floor.)
Did I use up about five minutes?
Oh, gosh.
(She's in a rush
due to the lack of time.)
I don't have a lot of time.
Please get on.
Go ahead.
Gosh.
(So Min)
I need to be on the 16th floor
as fast as possible.
If I don't, I'll die.
(She spreads false rumors.)
I don't have much time.
(While the urgent So Min
speaks nonsense...)
We need to win
in order to gain more time.
- Yes, the roulette.
- Right.
We need to win this.
Where on earth is Han Na?
I didn't see her
on my way back here either.
(I didn't see her
on my way back here either.)
Just know that.
- Did she go to the bathroom?
- She doesn't know how to get there.
Doesn't this look like
a commercial for an apartment?
Right.
It's her first time
in this Mok-dong building.
Right, she doesn't know
the layout of this building.
But then Ji Hyo mentioned
that she hosts a radio show.
Her radio show is for KBS,
so Ji Hyo apologized.
She is disconnected from the world.
(Disconnected from the world)
- Ji Hyo...
- Unbelievable.
She tries though. Do you know what
she was doing on her phone earlier?
She was listening to ZICO's song.
(She was listening to ZICO's song.)
- So...
- Still...
- She was listening to his song.
- I see...
- that she's trying.
- She does.
Ji Hyo, choose one or the other.
If you want to generate laughter,
keep staying disconnected
from the world.
(It's best to put up a wall.)
That's right.
I honestly didn't know.
You don't have to.
Not everyone has to anyway.
Which recent songs do you listen to?
Recent songs?
I know what it is.
- What is it?
- "Y" by Freestyle.
("Y" by Freestyle)
(The 2007 song
is a recent release for Ji Hyo.)
Do you know the mini homepage?
- The mini homepage!
- Want some acorns?
The famous BGM on mini homepages?
That's what you listen to, right?
It's as if she was frozen in time.
"Y" by Freestyle.
(Suk Jin joins in on teasing her.)
I don't think you know the song.
Must one know it?
- Well...
- "Must one know it?"
- What's the point in knowing that?
- Then...
why would you tease her
for not knowing it?
Suk Jin, the producers
are making suspicious movements.
I glanced at them and there were
ticks next to his name.
- The number of ticks...
- Suk Jin.
They seem to be up to something.
(We hope that he can do better
on variety shows.)
Suk Jin will soon
open his own hotline.
Mr. Noh will make his move.
(The CEO of Suk Jin's agency
will make his move.)
"Mr. Noh, I need you here."
(Mr. Noh, I need you here.)
"Take a stroll around
the SBS Variety Department for me."
Run!
Run, Han Na.
- Hold on.
- I think it's Han Na.
- Han Na, hurry up!
- Han Na.
Put it there in that blue basket.
- What took you so long?
- Ji Hyo's already standing.
Han Na must sit down first.
(Ji Hyo is confused too.)
- Not you, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo must be fast.
(I was talking to Han Na!)
- Not you, Ji Hyo.
- What are you doing?
- You shouldn't sit.
- Of course, I shouldn't sit.
Why would you sit?
Could Ji Hyo be funnier?
I love how she can play
the cavewoman.
- I'm jealous.
- A snake!
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo
finds one quickly.)
- What? A snake?
- A snake.
There's a snake on the 16th floor?
- Gosh, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo finally has a new identity.
It's been a while since you had one.
Where do I find a snake?
(Ji Hyo)
A whistle.
Whistle, come to me.
Do you know where it is?
(She asks the cameraman.)
(Found it!)
(She's found the whistle.)
I found the whistle.
Will someone else look for this?
Should I hide it?
Whatever. Let's go.
All I need to do is get back safely.
Is this it? Should I take this one?
So Min should be back by now.
- She should be back.
- She's taking a while.
Who would have a whistle?
A whistle would be hard to find
since it's small.
Are you worried about her, Se Chan?
Yes, of course. We need to win.
(Look at you.)
- She should hurry back.
- Stop forcing it.
(Jong Kook quietly
lets out his inner voice.)
You're forcing it.
(They're forcing
the relationship on them.)
They're forced to act.
He's forcing them.
- Force...
- You make my life worthwhile.
Haha does tend to force things.
It's why he makes
people uncomfortable.
He ruins what should be a success.
He makes people uncomfortable.
Things work when he's not involved.
I want to be a part of everything.
Don't people around you...
ask about her?
I have an eight-year-old nephew.
He doesn't normally talk to me.
Anyway, on New Year's Day,
he asked...
who I like on Running Man.
I asked what he meant...
and he mentioned Ji Hyo and So Min.
- What about me?
- What?
(Butting into the innocent question
by an 8-year-old)
(Uncle Muscle is who Uncle Se Chan
is scared of the most.)
- You can't put your name in there.
- Hold on.
That's not what
his nephew was asking.
Why would you be a choice?
Of course, I should be.
He was asking about
the woman he liked.
I see.
I see you want to cross that line.
(Jong Kook is mostly
obsessed with Se Chan.)
- I'm obsessed with you.
- If you were included,
- I would've chosen you.
- Right.
So I asked who he thought
I looked better with.
He said So Min
and it felt odd for some reason.
(It felt odd.)
- What did Se Hyeong say?
- My brother seriously asked me.
- Asked you what?
- On New Year's Day,
we enjoyed gamjatang
and soju together.
After having half a bottle
and a few words later...
(What do you think about So Min?)
"What do you think about So Min?"
I was like, "What?"
"How do you feel about So Min?"
I told him that
there was nothing going on,
but it feels odd
to receive those questions.
Your family is curious
about you two too.
- It makes them curious.
- It does.
(Without knowing
what goes through Se Chan's mind,)
(So Min rushes in,
blowing the whistle.)
- She's here.
So Min, put the whistle in the box.
- Put it in the box.
- And switch.
Okay.
- Kyung-hwan, hurry up.
- Find an object.
While talking,
I completely forgot
about Kyung-hwan.
- Right.
- Join in the conversation.
I can't find anything.
Kyung-hwan isn't good at this.
He's not observant.
I already found a mouse
on the girl's foot,
so there's probably nothing else
on the left side.
- I can't find anything.
- Focus on the right side.
It gets harder and harder.
Look at the forest.
Okay. Wait!
A brush.
Run!
- A brush.
- Run!
- There was a brush?
A brush is an object
that appears often.
(Kyung-hwan has plenty of time.)
I host a radio show here.
I'm very familiar with this place.
Don't worry.
So Min, while you were away,
Se Chan told us what happened
on New Year's Day.
- What did he say?
- His family keeps asking about you.
I'll be honest.
My mom wants your phone number.
(Their nephew, brother, and mom
are brought up.)
(Their families are even more
interested in their relationship.)
Why? I'd love to talk to her though.
Her mom loves Se Chan.
I visited my parents
on New Year's Day,
and Mom told me seriously...
- that I should get married.
- Really?
And she added...
that she wants me to marry
someone in show business.
I told you, right?
She had never said that before,
so I asked her why. And she said,
"Give me Se Chan's phone number."
Unbelievable.
She said,
"I think I should talk to him."
It might happen earlier...
than we expect.
But tell your mother
not to call him.
Hey, instead,
tell Suk Jin to stay out of it.
Instead,
(Suk Jin is being nosy.)
- Her mother should tell him.
- It's none of his business.
"Suk Jin, please stay out of it."
Also, you should never
play with someone's feelings.
- Suk Jin!
- What?
Will you be heartbroken...
if So Min gets married?
Why are you doing this?
(Is Suk Jin having a crisis?)
Why do you keep...
What is that supposed to mean?
- Why are you doing this?
- "So Min!"
"So Min!"
(He might show up at her door.)
(So Min, I have something
to tell you. Open the door.)
Never play with someone's feelings.
At first, I thought So Min
was too good for Se Chan...
That's enough.
(Suk Jin is interrupted.)
- Wait.
- Hey!
He hit himself.
(He threw his jacket...)
(at himself.)
(His jacket crash-lands.)
- What did you do?
- Are you okay?
- I heard a loud noise.
- The light turned off.
Suk Jin, what did you do?
In the pocket...
My phone was in the pocket.
His phone was in the pocket.
(Ji Hyo comes back
with a fake snake.)
- She's here.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hurry up.
- Gosh.
- Hurry.
- Let's switch.
(The snake is handed in,
and Kwang Soo starts playing.)
Kwang Soo, look at the trees.
(Two objects have already
been found in the trees.)
A cap.
A cap is what the pig is wearing.
Are you sure it's not a ladle?
A ruler!
Okay!
(He has to find a ruler
in the Running Man office.)
(As soon as someone leaves...)
I might be thinking too far ahead,
but let's say you two get married.
Then Suk Jin will officiate
your wedding.
We're not getting married.
How could I marry Se Chan?
I hate people like So Min.
(Out of nowhere)
(He suddenly announces
that he hates So Min.)
What's with him?
(Why would you suddenly say
you hate So Min?)
Suk Jin!
Someone must have hurt him.
I hate it when people
play with someone's feelings.
I wanted to have bingsu with him,
but he turned me down.
Don't push her away.
Go along with her.
- Why didn't you do that then?
- Right.
(Ji Hyo used to
push someone away too.)
Then you'd be on
"The Return of Superman" now.
(If only she hadn't
pushed him away.)
(No mention of another show
has had more impact than this.)
Gosh, that was strong.
No, we were different.
Gary and I were different.
Hold on, guys.
Think about which team will win.
We'll find that out soon enough.
We're more interested in those two.
(Kyung-hwan is
searching for a brush.)
Is someone here?
(Kwang Soo is here
to look for a ruler.)
- Hey.
That was fast.
What are you looking for?
Lettuce.
- Lettuce?
- Yes.
- Did you say lettuce?
It has to be here,
but I can't find it anywhere.
Do you mean lettuce?
Yes.
(He finds a ruler in a file holder.)
(I should hurry.)
How did he find it?
This is driving me crazy.
I'm in trouble.
- I found a ruler.
- He's here.
- He came back first.
- He found it.
- That was fast.
- What happened?
That was really fast.
What happened to Kyung-hwan?
Gosh, Kyung-hwan.
Kyung-hwan can find his way.
He hosts a radio show here.
- Hold on.
- The sky!
- The chimney!
- Is there something on the chimney?
- Just...
- A ruler!
A ruler was just brought here.
Please pay attention
to what others do.
- Try looking at it from a distance.
- Why?
- It's easier that way.
- Be quiet!
- Try looking at it from a distance.
- A mirror!
No mirror?
A brick.
A brick... What's this?
Guys, he'll use up all your time.
Give me a second.
I can't find anything.
I've never done it before.
Do we have reading glasses?
(He might need reading glasses.)
Just a second.
I really can't find anything.
What's this? Hold on.
This is hard.
(The clock is ticking away.)
Gosh, this is annoying.
(Annoyed)
Han Na, why did you pick Suk Jin?
- Why did I do that?
- Why did you do that?
- I'm regretting it.
- I apologize in advance.
- He's here.
- What took you so long?
- Kyung-hwan.
- Hand it in.
- Is it hard?
- Start.
- What are you doing? Hurry up.
Look at the house.
A brush.
Oh, an envelope.
(He already found an envelope?)
(The envelope Haha found is...)
(right here.)
(Haha turns the game around.)
What?
Go!
Let's go!
(How could Haha
find an object so fast?)
I need to pee.
(He has to use the bathroom.)
I have to run.
(He's going up to the 16th floor.)
It's here.
I have to go to the bathroom.
(I have to go to the bathroom.)
(He runs to the bathroom.)
(He responds
to nature's call first.)
After Suk Jin, it's your turn.
You guys have
two more objects to find.
But it's impossible.
You won't find anything either.
There are two objects left.
Suk Jin and Jong Kook,
you can switch if you want.
Jong Kook, you should play first.
- Suk Jin, go back to your seat.
- Jong Kook, you should go.
- Really?
- Hurry up and go.
I might not find anything either.
It's impossible.
It'd be funny
if he finds something right away.
Please find something right away.
A ruler was already found.
A stethoscope.
What?
(What did you say?)
Hey!
- Suk Jin!
- Gosh, this is crazy.
- What's with him?
- Suk Jin!
I can't believe him.
- You can't look at it now.
- You can't do that.
- I want to see it.
- You can't.
You can't look at it now.
(The stethoscope
only invisible to Suk Jin is...)
(right here.)
Where's a stethoscope?
(He still can't see it.)
- He can't find a stethoscope.
- Suk Jin.
What's with you?
This is driving me crazy.
I can't believe him.
A stethoscope was right there.
Let's go.
(Haha gets back in the game,
feeling a lot better.)
(I have to run to the office.)
Is this the right place?
Is this the Running Man office?
(This is how the Running Man
office hallway looks.)
(I've been coming here for 10 years,
but it looks unfamiliar today.)
This isn't the place.
(Has it been renovated?)
Is this the office?
Which floor is this?
Is this the ninth floor?
(Is this the ninth floor?)
Why am I on the ninth floor?
How did I end up here?
(I can swear I pushed "16".)
(5 minutes ago)
(Haha did push "16".)
I have to pee.
(But because of
the urgent call of nature...)
I really need to pee.
I have to go to the bathroom.
(When the elevator stopped
at the ninth floor, he got off.)
Gosh, I have to go to the bathroom.
(Having to use the bathroom,
he failed to go to the 16th floor.)
What am I doing on the ninth floor?
(In the end, he decides
to climb the stairs.)
A stethoscope is here?
(Jong Kook is looking
for a stethoscope.)
Was someone just here?
Haha? Wait.
Did he just get something from here?
(Because he went to the bathroom,)
(he's now training his legs.)
- Jong Kook.
- You got here now?
Where's Suk Jin?
You got here now?
I was on the ninth floor.
Is Suk Jin playing last?
What?
(Haha is in pain.)
(Jong Kook finds a stethoscope.)
I have to run.
(Almost at the same time,
Haha also finds...)
Who should I say it to?
Okay.
I'm going back.
(He can't run anymore.)
- Jong Kook!
- Jong Kook came back first.
- Okay!
- Oh, my.
- Gosh.
- Did you see...
- I'm the only one left.
- Haha?
He's here.
My goodness.
- Haha.
- Hurry up!
- Go!
- Hurry!
Is this a stethoscope?
Is it? This?
Forget about the stethoscope.
- You should hurry...
- It doesn't look like one at all.
They're the last players.
Find something else.
- Did someone find a brush?
- Yes.
Next to that...
It's a match
between horn-rimmed glasses.
- What did you say?
- Only one pair is real.
The big nose match.
What is this?
This definitely doesn't look like
a stethoscope at all.
- Forget about the stethoscope!
- Please!
- Please stop!
- Look for something else!
I spotted a stethoscope right away.
- We found a mouse, right?
- Yes, we did.
Look at similar places.
See? He isn't much better than me.
- Focus on finding your item.
- Okay.
This is driving me crazy.
Just say anything, Jae Suk.
A pipe.
- No?
- A pipe.
- Don't copy him.
- What is up with the two of them?
- Is he a parrot?
- Seriously.
A needle.
- An envelope.
- We found it already.
Really? For goodness' sake.
- You should know that.
- He didn't listen to the others.
He is the younger version
of Suk Jin.
They are neck and neck.
- This is...
- How can Jae Suk be so bad at it?
You found every item there is.
Old fossil versus Super old fossil.
A clothespin.
A bag.
Aside from the hat,
they look the same.
Stop talking about us.
- Seriously.
- Who is who?
- They look the same.
- They're facing the same direction.
- They are like decalcomania.
- This is insane.
- They have the same pose too.
- Look at their pose.
Their stance is the same.
I don't see anything.
- Hold on.
- Hurry up and find it!
- Aren't there only four items?
- No, there aren't.
Is there an additional item?
I don't see anything.
A musical note.
Let's go! Let's go!
Old fossil, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Old fossil, let's go.
- Suk Jin can't go.
- What is this?
A nail clipper.
(Sighing)
Suk Jin, the judges look worried.
The judges look worried.
You should get ready to be a judge.
This is driving me crazy.
The production crew drew it wrong.
Does Suk Jin have a lot of time?
He hasn't passed away yet.
- My goodness.
- I have a lot of time.
He hasn't passed away yet.
- My goodness.
- I have a lot of time.
- "He hasn't passed away yet."
- For goodness' sake.
- I mean...
- You might see the Grim Reaper.
Maybe it says "Suk Jin is out"
in the picture.
Maybe the item is a shoe
or a boot.
These pigs aren't wearing shoes.
I am saying it could be hidden
in the picture.
Look at Jong Kook's
facial expression.
We...
If it weren't for the time,
he would have gotten up.
Anger came after frustration.
- Let's see it.
- I am just too curious.
- I would gladly use three seconds.
- I will use my time.
- A stethoscope.
- Apparently, this is a stethoscope.
It's a stethoscope.
What else would it be?
Go back to your seat.
- Did you find it?
- My goodness, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin.
My goodness, Suk Jin.
- He is so frustrating.
- What's the last item?
- What is it?
- My goodness.
- Maybe he is a spy.
- A thumbtack.
(Is a thumbtack hidden
in the picture?)
(In a suspicious-looking hat
is a thumbtack.)
- You used it a lot in school.
- That's right.
A protractor.
A pencil sharpener. A crayon.
Even if he had gotten the picture
the day before...
Seriously.
He would have claimed
that he got the wrong picture.
This is just ridiculous.
(At that moment)
- He is back.
- Oh, dear.
Bye, bye, bye
What's the item?
I am so annoyed. What's the item?
Suk Jin, the last item is
a thumbtack.
- Se Chan found it.
- I see it now.
- I told you to look closely.
This is great.
Thus, Team Heo Kyung-hwan won.
(Team Heo Kyung-hwan won.)
The winning team
must make a choice now.
Please bring in the roulette.
(Roulette)
- There is a dud.
- Get twice the invested time.
If you get your time stolen,
you could become a judge right away.
I don't have much time.
It might be a bad idea
to spin the roulette.
- That's right.
- Just don't land on dud.
- If you...
- I'll invest 20 minutes.
20 minutes.
- 20 minutes?
- Spin the roulette.
If I stand up to go to the roulette,
am I using my time?
- Yes.
- You need to spin it really fast.
Of course.
- I don't have much time.
- Ask someone to spin it for you.
Jae Suk! Oh, I shouldn't ask him
since he is unlucky.
Oh, I shouldn't ask him
- Hey.
- For goodness' sake.
Jong Kook, please spin the roulette.
Sure. I will do it for you.
- Please let me get a good one.
- Okay.
- Here I go.
- You never know what you will get.
All right.
20 minutes!
(In the worst-case scenario,
he will lose 20 minutes.)
(What will happen to Se Chan,
the man with 40 minutes?)
- What did he get?
- A dud?
It's not half bad.
Steal 20 minutes and
the invested time from the top 1.
He will steal time from the top one.
Steal 20 minutes and
the invested time from the top 1.
He will steal time from the top one.
I will steal time!
You get 20 minutes
and the invested time.
That means I get 40 minutes.
- It's really nice.
- Jong Kook, thank you.
- Okay.
- Who is the top one?
You should tell us
who the top one is.
I won't reveal who the top one is.
- I see.
- That's reasonable.
- Did I get 40 minutes?
- You got 40 minutes.
- The top 1 lost 40 minutes.
- That's incredible.
- So Min.
- So Min, you are up next.
- 10 minutes.
- Should I spin the roulette?
- Who should do it? Jae Suk?
- No.
- Jong Kook?
I am sorry, Jae Suk.
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, please spin it.
Jong Kook already used his luck.
Will he get a good one again?
You are my favorite writer,
so I will do it.
Here I go.
(Jong Kook got the best choice
for Se Chan.)
- I hope it's a good one.
- It's spinning.
(How will he do for So Min?)
- Please.
- It's not too bad.
Steal the invested time
from another.
- Okay, okay.
- Jong Kook, you are lucky.
(Steal the invested time
from another.)
- Okay, okay.
- Jong Kook, you are lucky.
- You are lucky.
- Steal the invested time.
- He must have some kind of luck.
- Seriously.
- It's fascinating.
- Jong Kook.
- My goodness.
- He is really good at this.
Do you pick a member?
Do I... Do you pick a member?
- Yes. Whose time will you steal?
- Really?
Pick someone who was in a hurry.
It means they don't have...
- much time.
- Okay.
Pick a target.
In that case,
I will steal 10 minutes
from Ji Suk Jin World.
- Ji Suk Jin World.
- I will remember this.
It's a good choice.
Just you wait.
You know that I hold grudges, right?
Does that mean you have
three minutes left?
Gosh, you showed your true colors.
You will be my target
in the next round.
Okay.
Kyung-hwan.
Kyung-hwan, should I spin it?
- An hour.
- Really?
- You have so much time.
- No, no!
- An hour.
- Really?
- You have so much time.
- No, no!
An hour.
I wasn't done talking.
- I spun the roulette.
- I wasn't done talking.
Is it stealing?
(Steal the invested time
from another?)
It's stealing.
Is it stealing?
(He can steal an hour
from another.)
It's stealing.
Look at Jae Suk.
- This is incredible.
- Look at Jae Suk.
Look at Jae Suk.
- You know...
- He can steal an hour.
- An hour.
- You know,
I was going to subtract 30 minutes
from an hour,
but someone spun the roulette...
- without listening to me.
- He came out on top.
- That was incredible.
- Kyung-hwan, I did this for you.
- That's right.
- I will steal...
Jae Suk's time.
He might not have an hour.
He is unbelievable.
- No, no.
- Jae Suk is finished.
- Is Jae Suk finished?
- I have enough time.
- Not many people would be fine...
after losing an hour.
Is he still in the race?
I need that information...
- to make my decision.
- But he lost an hour.
- He is in the race.
- He is in the race!
- I have enough time.
- How is he still in the race?
That means he began
with over two hours.
I will have Jong Kook spin
the roulette for me.
- Okay.
- How much time will you invest?
15 minutes.
Gosh, that's so trivial.
- 15 minutes.
- He has 40 to 50 minutes.
He is so small-minded.
- That's so trivial.
- He is so small-minded.
- If you invest 15 minutes...
- I will invest...
17 minutes.
That's so trivial.
- That's so trivial.
- He has 50 minutes.
All right.
If I try to do well,
- I might not get a good option.
- Greed ruins everything.
Here I go.
(Jong Kook spins the roulette
for the third time.)
Please.
My business partner.
Avoid the red ones.
(Give the invested time to another)
Okay! Okay!
My goodness.
The train...
has stopped.
Greed ruined his luck.
He will have to give
17 minutes and 30 seconds.
It's a bad option.
You need to give the invested time.
Give it to me.
- Give it to me.
- Haha, give it to me.
Haha,
I will give it back to you later.
- Really?
- I will give you 20 minutes later.
Writer Jeon.
I choose Writer Jeon. Jeon So Min.
- Does he still trust So Min?
- I can't believe he trusts her.
- Didn't he learn his lesson?
- Does he still trust So Min?
So Min and I have...
- a connection.
- I can't believe he trusts her.
I will invest 30 minutes.
- Do you have that much time?
- Jae Suk,
that will leave you
with five minutes.
Will you be okay?
Does he have that much time?
He got an hour taken away.
I can invest more time, okay?
The moment he gets a bad one,
he will wear a yellow outfit.
That's not true.
I am...
quite relaxed.
I am quite relaxed.
I think you will get a red one.
What are you going to do?
(What will he get for himself?)
(Dud)
- Oh, dear.
- You're in trouble.
(His 30 minutes become a dud.)
- Dud.
- You're so unlucky.
- It's so strange.
- Good.
He was too confident.
- It's so strange.
- How embarrassing.
I'm blushing for him.
- What is it then?
- Do you lose time?
- You lose time?
- Jae Suk.
You do lose the time.
I'll deduct 30 minutes.
(12 minutes left
until the 1st judge is ready)
How is this possible?
- He's so rich.
- Where is the judge outfit?
- Does he still have time left?
- I have enough.
He had over 1.5 hours.
- Do you have enough?
- Yes, I do.
- I have enough.
- How much time did you have?
I bet he has 15 minutes left.
- Can he eat?
- He has 15 minutes left.
- Give him a potty.
- What?
(Current Time Status)
You need two people to get the food.
Jae Suk has spare time,
so he should go.
- You should go.
- Oh, gosh.
I can definitely go.
He lost everything.
It'll take a while
if we have to go outside.
It's lunchtime now.
We ordered from the gimbap place
across from SBS.
Two of you have to go and get it.
It'll be nice for
Se Chan and So Min to go.
Right, two of you can go.
- Why?
- Why don't we...
just pick spoons randomly?
- Should we pick spoons?
- Yes.
I have to go with Kyung-hwan.
- See you later.
- I have time to spare.
Go get bulked up.
Bulk up?
Let's see how fit he is.
I'm going downhill.
- Let's go.
- Are you rich?
- What?
You have a lot of time, right?
I have enough.
Maybe I shouldn't have taken
Jae Suk's time away.
He's talking much less now.
He's talking much less.
I agree. He's talking much less.
I usually leave him alone,
but I interfered this time.
It's a bit tight now.
(He's anxious and restless.)
I'm so unlucky.
Jong Kook.
Oh, dear.
I should stand up, but I can't.
- Here's the bibimbap.
- It's all right.
- That looks good.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes.
- Gosh.
Please take what you want.
Are there tables?
We have trays.
Please take them if you need them.
- Where?
- Is it self-serve?
Yes.
Get mine too.
Se Chan, get mine.
You should have used
the 17 minutes on me.
(Se Chan takes his time
using the self-serve.)
I realized.
It's so good to have time.
(She steals Se Chan's cutlery.)
(The petty offender DNA squirms
inside of her.)
It's so good to have time.
(When did you take that?)
What?
So Min.
Where's mine?
Here's yours.
Se Chan.
It's because you took my spoon.
Thanks.
This is not fun.
I need to focus on work.
Goodness.
You took my spoon.
You're not letting me work. Gosh.
- Here.
- You little guy.
Where did you get
the wooden chopsticks?
Do you need some?
Give him some wooden chopsticks.
(He tries desperately
to save some time.)
Kwang Soo, I have some here.
- There are a lot.
- Give me a pair.
Kwang Soo ran here...
and took a pair of chopsticks,
but it was the wrapper.
- I took the wrapper.
- It was the wrapper.
(Please go away, wrappers.)
Throw away garbage
in the garbage bin.
- Why did you leave it there?
- There are so many here.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food. Enjoy.
(They all enjoy lunch together.)
Stir-fried pork is so good.
Gosh,
I have to do well in the next game.
(He really doesn't have much time.)
You only realize
when you don't have much.
I'm more desperate
because I used to be rich.
After you eat,
you have to clean up.
We have to pick people.
Please pick two people
to clean up the trays.
Jae Suk's time might be over
while he cleans.
Goodness.
(He can't deny it.)
Who wants to
brush their teeth with me?
We can resume filming
feeling refreshed.
You weren't planning
to brush your teeth?
Flex.
- Let's go.
- That's out of the ordinary.
I'm sorry, but I can't feel
refreshed for the time being.
(The poor get poorer,
and the rich get richer.)
- My bad.
- Aren't you going to flex?
Brushing teeth is a luxury.
Is it?
Let's play Race of Wits and
pick two people who'll clean up.
I'll let two winners
spin the roulette.
- Really?
Suk Jin is
already eliminated.
- He is because he's not here.
- He's not here.
Set...
- We need one more person.
- Let's get started.
Are you starting without him?
Of course. He should have been
paying attention.
We need one more person then.
- Right.
Start.
- If you stand up first...
- One.
That was fast.
- 2.
(They both did 2!)
- Two of you?
- Why did he copy me?
My gosh. He's driving me nuts.
Two of you lost,
so once Suk Jin comes back,
do rock-paper-scissors?
Three of them can do
rock-paper-scissors.
You have to pick two people
from the rest of them.
Yes, we have to pick
the two winners.
- Do we have to pick 2 winners?
- 2 winners.
Start.
One.
- 2.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
Six.
Jong Kook is out.
- Were you not even trying?
- No.
(How unpleasant.)
I just wanted to enjoy my food.
Fine. You have time to spare.
- You must have a lot of time.
- You have time to spare.
I have enough.
- Five.
- Take it.
What was that for?
- He has a lot of time.
- Do you?
- I have a lot of time.
- That much?
Okay, next.
He's so into this.
Look at Jae Suk.
- Set...
- He's back.
Suk Jin, you have to do
rock-paper-scissors.
- You got eliminated.
- Why?
- Do rock-paper-scissors with them.
- Three of us.
- Se Chan and Haha.
- Haha.
- Cleaning up.
- One person.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(He wins.)
I won.
Rich people are worse.
Everything is working out
for you this year.
That's so true.
Everything will work out for me.
Your schemes don't matter.
He blocked the sharpest spears.
Okay, let's go again.
This is cutthroat.
Kwang Soo, are you desperate too?
No, I'm not.
Start.
- 1.
- 2.
- Three.
- Gosh.
(Kwang Soo and Jae Suk are
desperate for more time.)
- Both of you are out.
- You're out.
You're completely out.
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
Only one person
needs to be eliminated.
Ready, set, go.
- 1.
- 2.
What was that?
- 1.
- 2.
What was that?
So Min is out.
That was useless.
Is it the two of them?
Do we spin the roulette?
As promised, Han Na and Ji Hyo,
you get to spin the roulette.
Why don't I get a chance?
- You left.
- You...
barely survived.
- Really?
- Yes.
(He plays dumb.)
I don't understand
why I don't get to spin it.
I get to spin the roulette.
Why don't I get a chance?
- I don't get it.
- When we suggested the game,
you weren't there,
so you were eliminated.
It's your fault you left
when the camera was on.
We keep moving around when
the cameras are on. That's the idea.
Anyhow...
- That's the idea?
- Hey.
Whose idea is that?
Goodness.
You shouldn't have left
to brush your teeth.
- Okay.
- You first.
How did I get a dud?
Ji Hyo, how much
would you like to invest?
- Let's go high.
- Me?
Go high. Be cool.
Be a big spender.
Don't be like Jae Suk.
I'll invest 10 minutes.
- 10 minutes?
- You must be really poor.
She probably has 25 minutes.
- Do I spin?
- Yes.
(Ji Hyo spins the roulette.)
(Ji Hyo is good with chances.)
(Where will she land on?)
- She got blue right away.
- It's a dud.
- Look.
- She went from lucky to unlucky.
- Dud.
You're getting more fun now.
- Hey.
- She's unlucky now.
It's better
the more unlucky you are.
Han Na.
Han Na, be bold.
I'll invest 50 minutes.
- She's rich.
- 50 minutes.
(Everybody is surprised
she invested 50 minutes!)
- She has time.
- She has plenty.
She pretended like...
- she was poor.
- Can I do that?
She was running around.
- 50 minutes.
- 50 minutes?
- Okay.
- She has at least an hour.
She had time.
- "Give the invested time..."
- Start.
"to another" sounds really good.
"Give the invested time to another."
(She can gain 100 minutes
or lose 50 minutes.)
Han Na.
It's a dud.
It's not.
- Please, Han Na.
- "Get twice..."
"the invested time."
(She clasps her hands together.)
- Please, Han Na.
- "Get twice..."
"the invested time."
"Steal the invested time
from another."
- 50 minutes?
- Steal.
(Her investment was a huge success.)
Really?
Somebody will get the yellow outfit.
- Can I decide now?
- Yes.
Suk Jin.
- Hey!
- Suk Jin.
(Han Na gains 50 minutes,
and Suk Jin loses 50.)
Hey.
What's wrong with her?
- Amazing.
- Why would you do that?
She's creating a story for Suk Jin.
I got disappointed at the thumbtack.
- I knew it.
- Why?
- She's creating a story for him.
- Thumbtack Suk Jin.
- He's still alive.
- Yes, I'm still alive.
(What is the result
of the scramble for time?)
(Current Time Status)
This game is called
Strawberry, St-raw-berry.
- This is the worst.
- You have to be lucky.
Please.
(The awful strawberry game is back.)
What's this?
(Why? What is it?)
(Strawberry for 1 beat)
(St-raw-berry for 2 beats)
(Strawberry, st-raw-berry
for 3 beats)
(St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
for 4 beats)
(St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,
strawberry for 5 beats)
st-raw-berry for 6 beats)
("Strawberry" is for 1 beat,
and "st-raw-berry" is for 2 beats)
(You must say the terms accordingly
from beat 1 to 8.)
Isn't it a difficult game?
(It's a game
everyone struggled with.)
We changed the rules a bit.
You chant "I like strawberry" first.
Let's say Haha goes, "So Min, four."
Then she should go,
"St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry."
The one who is called must do it.
Then the attack continues on.
This is hard.
The member who gets it wrong...
must leave the circle
and stand at the back.
- Really?
- This is bad.
Is this a tournament?
You can only sit back down
when the other team gets it wrong.
If your team gets it wrong,
you keep standing up.
The game will continue on that way.
You could get eliminated
while you are standing up.
(This is bad.
I don't have much time.)
This is bad.
It looks like Jae Suk will wear
the yellow outfit.
Jong Kook and I will divide
the members into two teams.
- The two of us?
- We are in the middle.
He doesn't want to move.
(He doesn't want to lose any time.)
- Let's change the seats.
- Okay.
Se Chan and Haha, go over there.
The team
that gets 12 points 1st wins.
This is so nerve-wracking. Hold on.
- My heart is about to burst.
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- St, st, st, st
(I need to win and get more time.)
The two captains will decide
which team attacks first...
- with rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Team Jae Suk will attack first.)
- Okay!
- This is important.
- We need to win some points.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk is distracted.)
- Show us an attack like an awl.
- Let's go.
- I like strawberry
- Ha Na, seven
- What?
He said "Ha Na."
(As soon as the game started)
(He yelled, "Ha Na, seven.")
(He changed her name
from Han Na to Ha Na.)
- Ha Na.
- He said, "Ha Na, seven."
- Let's start over.
- I heard Ha Na.
Hold on.
Please overlook this mistake...
because Jae Suk is really nervous.
- I am sorry.
- He said Ha Na.
He is really nervous.
Okay. I understand.
Start.
- I like strawberry
Se Chan, eight
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,
st-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- Jae Suk, three
- I like strawberry
(I like strawberry)
Why did you say,
"I like strawberry"?
(He showed his nervousness
by repeating the intro.)
(Jae Suk is so embarrassing.)
I am in trouble.
(Jae Suk is the target of the day.)
Go.
- Go and stand in the back.
- Jae Suk.
- He is so embarrassing.
- Hurry up.
Hurry up and play the game.
So Min, hurry up.
(His clock is ticking.)
I like strawberry
(He copies Jae Suk.)
- I like strawberry
- Suk Jin, seven
- Strawberry
(He said "Strawberry"
in a weird way.)
For goodness' sake. He got me.
Start.
- I like strawberry
Ji Hyo, three
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
What was that?
(She said "Strawberry, st-raw-berry"
after missing two beats.)
(Ji Hyo is the worst at this game.)
- Go.
- She has no sense of rhythm.
(Suk Jin is in and Ji Hyo is out.)
This is so hard.
What's the current score?
- I like strawberry
- Haha, six
- St-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- Jae Suk, seven
- Traw
(Traw...)
What is wrong with him?
(Kwang Soo explodes.)
"Traw"?
(He babbled something
about a strawberry.)
No one got a chance to play.
"Traw"?
I don't think
he understands the rules.
Just hurry up and change...
- into the judge's uniform.
- All right.
I still have time.
We are behind by so many points.
- I like strawberry
- Han Na, three
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- So Min, six
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- St-raw-berry
- They are good.
- Suk Jin, three
- St-raw-berry
(He said "St-raw-berry"
in a strange way.)
- All right.
- It's "St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry."
Play rock-paper-scissors
and the winner sits down.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(He loses.)
- What is he going to do?
- Rock
(He lacks composure,
skills, and luck.)
- Ji Hyo, that little...
- He has the worst luck today.
He has the worst luck today.
Start.
- I like strawberry
- Kyung-hwan, seven
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
St-raw-berry, hey
- For goodness' sake.
- Kyung-hwan, seven
(Strawberry, st-raw-berry)
(St-raw-berry, hey)
(He takes himself out.)
(Kyung-hwan's wrong answer
makes everyone laugh.)
My heart aches.
Kyung-hwan! Come on!
(Jae Suk is tense.)
- That was hilarious.
- We don't have much time.
- Didn't we win?
- Start.
- I like strawberry
- Suk Jin, three
- St-raw-berry
(He enunciates his wrong answer.)
- Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min goes back in!)
Gosh, I need to sit down.
This is driving me crazy.
(Jae Suk continues to lose time
as they play the game.)
- I like strawberry
- Ji Hyo, seven
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
Haha, three
(Babbling)
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Kyung-hwan goes back in
this time.)
Why do you win all the time?
- Why do you win all the time?
- Why do you lose all the time?
- I like strawberry
(The game continues on.)
- Jae Suk, three
- Straw
Strawberry, st-raw-berry
This is driving me crazy.
Hurry up. We don't have time.
- Jae Suk, seven
- Staw, raw-berry
(Staw, raw-berry)
"Raw-berry"?
(He can't believe himself.)
- Jae Suk, six
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
(He calmly succeeds this time!)
Jae Suk, six
(He had it right. But...)
(He attacks himself.)
- "Jae Suk, six."
- That's too much.
- I am sorry.
- This is heartbreaking.
- I made a mistake.
Hurry up. We don't have time.
- Why do you keep saying that?
- Hurry up.
- I like... Hurry up.
- What's the point...
- of hurrying up?
- We don't have time.
We don't have time.
- I like strawberry
- We are going to lose.
- Han Na, three
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Jae Suk, eight
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(He calmly defends himself.)
- Han Na, three
- Strawberry, st-raw-berry
- Come on!
- Kwang Soo, eight
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry,
st-raw-berry
(Jae Suk has about 2 minutes left,)
(but the rally continues on.)
- So Min, seven
- St-raw-berry
(When will this end?)
- Se Chan, eight
- St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
- Hurry up!
- Jae Suk, two
- St-raw-berry
That little...
(He ignored the beat.)
(Feeling pressed for time,
he ended the game.)
(Team Jong Kook wins
with a score of 12 to 7.)
He got angry. "St-raw-berry!"
Just how little time does he have?
That was so funny.
- The game ended.
- Did it end?
- We lost.
- You lost.
- This team will spin the roulette.
- Okay.
- Han Na, do you want to go first?
- Shall I go first?
This is Han Na's second time
spinning it.
I will invest...
an hour.
(She invests 60 minutes.)
Han Na, you might get
"Give the invested time to another."
- What?
- Then please give it to me.
- There is that option.
- That's right.
Han Na, I am begging you.
Han Na.
I will spin it.
You should give it to someone
on your team.
(What will be the result
of Han Na's big investment?)
- Han Na could finish someone off.
- You never know.
Han Na, please help the poor.
Steal the invested time
from another.
Steal the invested time.
(She gets
"Steal the invested time.")
She will finish someone off.
Han Na, you are so cool.
I didn't know I would get that.
That's incredible.
Kyung-hwan has...
a lot of time, right?
(Startled)
- Kyung-hwan has a lot of time.
- You have a lot of time too.
Hey.
Finish someone off.
I will pick someone
who has a lot of time.
- I pick Suk Jin.
- Hey!
You have a lot of time.
(I pick Suk Jin.)
- I...
- Suk Jin.
- I mean...
- You stole two hours from me.
She stole an hour and 50 minutes
from Suk Jin.
Flex! Flex!
An hour and 50 minutes?
You said you have
all the time in the world.
- Han Na is amazing.
- He is her target.
I can't believe you!
- This is driving me crazy.
- You have a lot of time.
Hold on. The judges are talking
among themselves.
- They are talking.
- Something is happening.
Suk Jin is...
Let me spin the roulette at least.
- This round isn't over.
- That's not how it works.
- Suk Jin is out.
- Is he out?
Change into the judge's uniform.
I should be able to spin
the roulette.
It's effective immediately.
- You are out.
- Why is everyone so happy?
Hey.
- Hey, you...
- The first judge, Suk Jin.
Suk Jin, put on the judge's uniform
and help us as a staff member.
- Let's move things along.
- He will lose the cameras.
Put on the judge's uniform.
Hey.
My goodness.
I can't believe it.
My stomach hurts
from laughing too hard.
This is hilarious.
This is driving me crazy.
- Okay.
- Look at Kyung-hwan.
Look at Kyung-hwan.
- Kyung-hwan is jealous.
- He is jealous.
- Suk Jin.
- He wants to be a judge.
(I want the spotlight
and screen time.)
- Rules are rules.
- You should take off the cap.
It's none of your business.
(Forget it.)
- What's wrong with you?
- I was being considerate.
When you are done changing,
sit by my side.
- Is he out of the picture?
- He's going off-screen?
He'll help me with the shoot.
Why do I need to sit here?
Do I get no screen time now?
You fit in right where you are.
- Be quiet.
- He doesn't look out of place.
That outfit suits you better.
Haha, how much time will you invest?
I will go all in.
- You will go all in.
- How much time is that?
I can't say.
Let's go!
(In the best-case scenario,
he will get about 63 minutes.)
(In the worst-case scenario,
he will become the 2nd judge.)
(What will be the result?)
- Steal the invested time...
- From the top one.
Steal 20 minutes and
the invested time from the top 1.
- Okay!
- That's good.
Who is the top one?
Will you reveal who the top one is?
How much time did you have?
Not much.
(Haha gets 51 minutes and 46 seconds
from Kyung-hwan.)
Everyone is getting a good one.
(He talks to himself.)
(He glances
at the producer and the writer.)
I'm sitting here as a staff member,
but they're whispering.
I can't hear them.
Wouldn't a banner be better?
This is work.
Go, Jong Kook.
I'll do 30 minutes.
- 30 minutes?
- Yes.
I'll go.
(Jong Kook invests 30 minutes.)
(He can earn 60 minutes at most
or lose 30.)
(What is the result?)
- It's a dud.
- What's the matter?
It's a good one. Wait.
"Steal 20 minutes and
the invested time from the top 1."
For real?
You can steal 50 minutes from top 1.
(Han Na is currently top 1.)
- Okay.
- If I were you...
I...
(How much time will Se Chan invest?)
50 minutes.
Somebody will join me.
It's all-in.
(He tries the roulette.)
One will join me.
- Come. Is it a dud?
- Dud.
What is it?
- Twice.
- Yes.
- 50 then? Do I get 100?
- 100 minutes.
(He becomes a time millionaire.)
That changes everything.
That should have been me.
You would have gotten a dud.
Judges, please move the roulette.
- Come here.
- Hurry up.
Hurry. Move it.
We have him.
We have another judge.
- We only need 1 more person.
- We only need 1.
He won't try, so be careful.
He won't try.
- It's heavy.
- You have to lift it.
He's the oldest.
Suk Jin.
He's only doing it
because the camera's on.
(The camera's on.)
- I know.
- Why is the old guy doing this?
He had fun for 2.5 hours,
so he's working hard.
Oh, gosh.
(Play then work, YOLO Suk Jin)
First place could have changed.
Maybe I'll win...
by default.
The last race is called
Time Expedition.
(Countdown Race Final Mission:
Time Expedition)
It's going to be
Name Tag Elimination.
If you rip off the name tag of
someone who has less time than you,
you get to steal half of their time.
(If they have less time than you,
you steal half of their time.)
If they have less time than you?
If you rip off the name tag of
someone who has less time than you,
you get to steal half of their time.
If you accidentally rip off the name
tag of someone who has more time,
then only you lose
half of your time.
Hold on.
This is an unbelievable twist.
Even if I rip Jae Suk's name tag,
I only get 3 to 4 minutes.
(It's even less than that, punk.)
Wait up.
- Everybody will come at me.
- Wait up.
The piranhas will rip him apart.
If you hold hands
with another member,
your times get combined.
(If you hold hands,
your times get combined.)
If you hold hands?
Let's say Jae Suk has 10 minutes,
and Jong Kook has 70.
If they hold hands,
their times become 80 minutes.
If they rip off So Min's name tag
who has 20 minutes left,
they can steal half
of her 20 minutes.
Each person will earn five minutes.
If they rip off the name tag
of somebody who has 90 minutes left,
Jae Suk and Jong Kook will lose...
half of their respective
remaining times.
Once you let go
of each other's hands,
you become weak again.
I have to be fast.
Let's say I have 11 minutes,
and Jae Suk has 10.
I try to rip off his name tag,
but we accidentally hold hands.
- Then you lose.
- Even if it's for a moment?
- Correct.
- Okay.
People will betray each other.
It'll be a mess. You'll hold hands
and let go. This sounds fun.
This sounds fun.
- Suk Jin.
- Why is the judge talking?
- Don't pay attention.
- What's wrong with him?
- Sir.
- Don't pay attention.
You were so loud.
How can we not pay attention?
Don't pay attention.
I really want to play.
- What am I supposed to do?
- You lost all your time.
You don't get eliminated
when somebody takes your name tag.
You only get eliminated
when your time runs out.
The race is over when
there's one last person standing.
Your name tags are hidden
inside this building.
If you collect two name tags
of the same person,
their remaining time gets revealed.
If you collect
two of your own name tags,
you earn an additional 10 minutes.
- That's good.
- Inside the building is...
also the special Room of Time.
Room of Time opens without notice
at random locations,
and only one person can use it.
It disappears after use.
In order to use Room of Time,
you must pay...
a third of your remaining time
as the admission fee.
It's probably worth it though.
Please move to
your starting locations.
Your time won't run for now.
Judge, please join us...
(Is it time for
Judge Jee to step up?)
and help us hide the name tags.
(Help us hide the name tags.)
- Tell us what happens later on.
- How cute.
We're really curious
about that world. Let us know.
- Let's get moving.
- Goodness.
Han Na,
I'm going to remember this.
(Judge Jee is hiding the name tags.)
I'll put Jae Suk's name tag here.
(Jae Suk laughed at him the most
for becoming a judge.)
Jae Suk.
(Take his name tag.)
Han Na. This is a bonus.
Here. Whoever sees it first
gets to take it.
I'm done.
Good luck, guys.
(He hides the name tags
very poorly.)
There are targets beneath me.
I don't have to worry about
Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo or Jae Suk.
The rest are tricky.
I'm planning to...
be loyal to Se Chan.
I think Haha took...
Han Na's time
because she was on top.
Jong Kook probably stole
Kyung-hwan's time.
There's a possibility
I might win by default.
I'm either top 1 or 2.
I'm sure
Kyung-hwan has more time than me.
People on a similar level as me...
are Han Na and Se Chan.
Jong Kook probably has around
1 hour to 1 hour and 10 minutes.
People know I have some time,
so it won't be easy. Jae Suk first.
Jae Suk...
I don't know
if Jae Suk actually has no time.
He was really nervous
during the strawberry game.
(He can't be that nervous for real.)
If he was serious, I would be
really disappointed in him.
If that amateur side of him
was for real.
(The amateur is still nervous.)
Do you have a strategy?
I have no strategy.
I have to hold hands with somebody
before I die.
I have to hold hands with Kwang Soo.
- Start the race.
- I'm in trouble.
I have no time to waste.
(Jae Suk doesn't have much time.
Will there be a twist?)
(Next week)
(Room of Time is the key.)
(They fight with honor
in the time war.)
(The one who found Room of Time,
and the one who's about to avenge)
(What will be the outcome
of this relentless time war?)
(On one peaceful afternoon)
(Shin Hae Sun
and Bae Jong Ok are here.)
(Did they bring a catastrophe
with them?)
(Why do they have
suspicious items in their cars?)
(Jong Ok and Hae Sun incite
betrayal and conspiracy.)
(And...)
(100...)
(lies)
(There are numerous choices
for them.)
(Regretful choices
and accumulating secrets!)
(They run into traps
to test their luck.)
(What is the cruel secret
that gets revealed at the end?)
You betray.
(Decide! Bag)