(A wedding venue in Suwon)
To the eighth floor? I see.
The eighth floor?
(Suk Jin shows up in a neat outfit.)
It's the top floor.
(I look cool today.)
(He arrives at the opening venue showing off.)
The captain...
- What am I? - Suk Jin.
(What's going on?)
(He's dumbfounded to see Suk Jin in uniform.)
- What am I? - Hang on.
What are you? Are you a spy?
No. The other guys already saw me.
(No, I don't know either.)
Am I a pilot?
- A pilot? - I look like a pilot.
(It looks familiar.)
He looks like a guy in a costume who works at an amusement park.
(From the parade of Big Nose Land)
My gosh.
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook arrive.)
- Hello. - What?
- What's that? - What?
(Jae Suk's wearing the same outfit as Suk Jin.)
- I came with him. - He's dressed the same.
- What's going on? - What's with your pants?
I thought he was an elevator attendant or something.
(A customer has arrived.)
I was surprised.
Are we pilots or what?
- I guess so. - And what are you?
(Out of the blue)
(What?)
What about me?
These are just my clothes.
You should get a hair cut.
(By the way)
He's right. You should look neat.
What's with your hair?
(They found their target.)
What's that? Is it because of your new movie?
(Long hair)
- Yes. - Are you the only actor there?
Are you the only actor there?
Why are you showing it off?
- I'm not showing it off. - You don't have to show it.
You seem so condescending.
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook tease Kwang Soo together.)
It's not like that. My hair...
- It's not like he's the only actor. - I know.
Why aren't the other members coming?
(Feeling tired)
And why do you keep your hair long every time you shoot a movie?
(It's not over yet.)
That's because the director told me to.
(That's because the director told me to.)
Do you let your hair grow long like that because of the director?
(He keeps attacking.)
Why are you two hitting it off today?
(It's annoying.)
(They have great chemistry when they tease Kwang Soo.)
- This is crazy. - That's not true.
I'm really stressed out today.
- Why? - We just like each other.
(Kwang Soo's biggest stress is Jae Suk and Jong Kook together.)
Today, we are having Trade King Race.
- Trade King? - Trade King?
It's called Trade King.
LA Lover Jong Kook will be the captain of American traders.
(LA Lover Jong Kook...)
(will be the captain of American traders.)
And Asian Prince Kwang Soo will be the captain of Asian traders.
(Asian Prince Kwang Soo...)
(will be the captain of Asian traders.)
- I see. - He and I are captains?
Am I a captain?
And Jae Suk and Suk Jin will be...
(How about Jae Suk and Suk Jin in uniform?)
customs agents and two MCs.
(They will be customs agents and 2 MCs.)
Customs agents?
What is a customs agent?
(Customs agents take care of customs issues.)
A person who takes care of customs issues.
When I make a purchase abroad...
(Showing off his knowledge)
Stay quiet.
I'm trying to explain.
I should tell viewers what a customs agent is.
(1 additional meme)
Bo Pil is talking.
- I'm a fan of these clips. - You only listen to...
movie directors.
- That's not true. - Won't you listen to Bo Pil?
He's right. You should listen to Bo Pil.
- Listen to Bo Pil. - My gosh.
- I'm disappointed. - What are you talking about?
(Don't be ridiculous.)
- You disappointed him. - Do you want me to disappoint you?
Jae Suk and Suk Jin will handle the overall race...
(What's Jae Suk and Suk Jin's duty as a customs agent?)
(They will handle the race...)
and broker trade deals to collect taxes.
(and collect taxes from traders.)
You're good at collecting money, right?
- I'm an expert in this. - I'm not good at it though.
(The former card shark group chairman is...)
(an expert in collecting money.)
I'm good at collecting money.
- So Suk Jin is... - It's Petty Gang again.
my subordinate, right?
- Your underling. - No. You're my subordinate.
(Angry)
You're a member of Petty Gang.
You're my subordinate.
- You're obviously his subordinate. - Right.
(Brutal fact)
Now the members will split up into two teams.
(The Petty Gang boss has no actual power.)
(The rest of members...)
They will see the captains' names on each door.
(will choose a captain's room of their choice.)
They will see the names and pick a team.
But you two will be in each other's room.
So those who pick Jong Kook...
(The captains will be in each other's room.)
will be joining Team Kwang Soo.
Okay, okay.
- It sounds fun. - Okay.
(It will be a chance to check their friendship and loyalty.)
So the members who get into your room didn't pick you.
- Exactly. - Exactly.
I see.
I will be a little disappointed.
They will try hard to hide their feelings.
They didn't pick you, but they will be your team.
(However, the teams will be formed according to the room they choose.)
- Right. - Okay.
If I get a lot of members, I'll be disappointed.
(Kwang Soo and Jae Suk entered Jong Kook's room.)
If no one comes in, Jong Kook will be disappointed.
I know.
Jong Kook will be upset until tomorrow.
- This isn't a good time. - Right.
(There will be another shoot tomorrow. They'll suffer big time.)
We are having another shoot tomorrow.
Haha should definitely come.
(Haha should definitely come.)
- Right. - Haha has to be there.
(He loved Haha for a long time.)
Right. Haha must pick me.
The last episode was quite touching.
"If you had to choose one, Jong Kook will be your business partner,"
(Last week's episode)
- "but it won't go well." - This is hard.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(If you had to choose one. Jong Kook or his business?)
(He chose Jong Kook.)
Isn't it B?
- Why? - I'm being serious.
(Jong Kook was deeply moved by Haha's choice.)
It was touching.
Today, I'll be able to see if he was serious.
(His choice)
I know. Today...
If Haha comes in here...
(If Haha comes in here...)
(He doesn't even want to imagine Haha's betrayal.)
It means he made fun of you.
We're in the pyebaek room. Do you have some jujubes?
I'll throw them at him.
(Jong Kook is determined to teach him a lesson.)
(Se Chan shows up humming without knowing anything.)
(Jong Kook's favorite member No. 2)
Hello.
For today's race, it's important to pick a good captain.
(Between Captain Jong Kook and Captain Kwang Soo,)
So we will let the members pick their captain themselves.
(who will Se Chan choose?)
If Se Chan comes in here... Gosh, what should I do?
You know what I'm like when I trust someone.
(Jong Kook embraced Se Chan with love.)
Right. He just gives his everything.
- I give my everything. - Once he trusts someone.
Right. I'm not calculating at all.
(Se Chan wouldn't betray me.)
Haha and Se Chan might not come here.
(He's expecting to see them.)
Right.
Come on.
(Se Chan shows up.)
- Come on. - It's been a long time
(He feels betrayed.)
- I knew he'd come. - My gosh.
- I knew he'd come. - Kwang Soo, wait.
(Flustered)
- I'm sorry. - Just keep singing.
(Whatever)
Gosh, this is...
(His heart is hurt by Se Chan's serenade for Jong Kook.)
- Did you not even hesitate? - No.
Listen to me. The reason I came in here...
Did you not hesitate?
(No hesitation)
It's not that I didn't hesitate.
(He chose Jong Kook with his instinct.)
If I don't pick Jong Kook...
- The thing is... - What?
It's been a long time
I can't believe this. I was going to slap you in the face.
I want to be in his favor. So he's in the other room.
(Jong Kook's loyal subordinate Se Chan made a choice.)
Right.
(It's So Min's turn.)
Let me choose a room.
(What's So Min's choice?)
Don't you think So Min will come?
- I'm sure So Min will come. - I'm 100 percent sure.
(She will definitely choose Kwang Soo.)
- I'm 100 percent sure too. - Me too.
What if So Min picks the other team? You'll be moved, right?
- Sure. I'll be moved. - I know.
Actually, we had some talk in the parking lot earlier.
(Things we just talked about now)
Right. I saw you two having a talk.
(I'll look forward to it, So Min.)
It might affect her choice.
I know. She's... What?
(Peeking)
See?
(So Min shows up, letting Jong Kook down.)
(Flustered)
(See?)
This isn't the room. What's going on?
(I know. What's going on, So Min?)
So Min.
- Yes? - Come on in.
(Her eyes are wide open.)
(I knew it.)
- How could you... - I told you so.
- This is just as expected. - Come here!
(She even tries to escape.)
You never go beyond my expectations.
(She'd rather escape from Jong Kook.)
I was 100 percent sure that you'd pick this room.
- Just come here. - Let me explain.
- Go ahead. - Have a seat.
(Giving an excuse)
I was told we wouldn't be using our physical strength today.
- So I picked the sly one. - Just come and have a seat.
(She makes things up to survive.)
- You're not sly at all. - Just sit.
(Be quiet.)
This is just as we expected.
(He was right.)
Do you think I like Kwang Soo? I bad-mouth Kwang Soo a lot.
Why are you sitting on your knees?
(Her hands and knees have become polite before she knew it.)
I don't know.
So Se Chan went to the other room.
(So Se Chan went to the other room.)
- Gosh, Se Chan. - Gosh.
I can't help but like him.
He got your back.
Se Chan has a face that I can't hate.
(So much love)
- I know. - His face is...
(What about me?)
What are you doing?
(She's trying to survive.)
I just can't hate his face.
- She's... - Gosh.
(Acting cute)
You're such a troublemaker.
(Not a chance)
Just go sit there.
(She's doomed.)
I'm in trouble. What do I do? Our team is at a disadvantage.
(Next up is Ji Hyo.)
I already have my answer.
I'm sure about this.
Ji Hyo will go there, and So Min will come here.
(I believe you, Ji Hyo.)
(Ji Hyo shows up.)
Ji Hyo is here.
Kwang Soo, what are you doing here?
Ji Hyo, why did you come?
(Disappointed)
I didn't know you would come.
(Ji Hyo broke everyone's expectation.)
I thought Ji Hyo would pick the other team.
Isn't this Jong Kook's room?
(Isn't this Jong Kook's room?)
Right. This is Jong Kook's room.
Then what is he doing here?
(She doesn't know what's going on.)
- They switched rooms. - You can't say that to me.
You're supposed to feel sorry for me.
(Shameless)
I'm just flustered now.
- It's Haha. - Honestly...
(There's only Haha left.)
- If Haha... - If Haha comes in here...
He is going to have a hard time.
(Sighing)
Was Haha supposed to come in after you?
If Haha comes in, I'll ask for my money back right away.
(He'll return his investment money.)
My goodness.
(Haha comes in.)
Jong Kook. I knew it.
(Haha is about to return the investment money.)
(I knew it.)
(Haha, how could you do this to me?)
Jong Kook. I knew it.
(The anticipated picture is complete.)
I knew it.
I really knew it. I swear.
- I came here because I knew it. - Stop it.
Jong Kook, I really knew you would be here.
(You're dead too.)
- Stop lying. - Listen. I really knew it.
- This is shocking. - I knew it.
(The shocking betrayal of his trusted member)
- I knew it. - I didn't think he'd come in.
- I knew it. - He acted like Jong Kook's brother.
(Repeating)
- Hey. - I really knew he'd be here.
- They were so close. My goodness. - I knew it.
(You've humiliated me.)
Jong Kook, see how relaxed I am.
(She's also scared.)
Why are you sitting on your knees?
I don't know. I'm comfortable in this pose.
Exactly. She's been sitting like that.
(He threw his cap on the floor.)
(He's punishing himself to reflect on himself.)
You lied to Jong Kook.
After all these years... Gosh.
(Peeking)
- Come on. That's not why I'm here. - How could you do this to me?
You see, I knew they switched the rooms before I made my choice.
(To calm Jong Kook down,)
- I meant what I said. - You're lying.
(she massages him.)
- Haha, I'm so disappointed... - I'm in shock.
(While Jong Kook is getting calm...)
- You look pale. - It itches. Darned mosquito.
(What? "Darned mosquito"?)
Gosh, I didn't refer to you. I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- It wasn't like that. - "Darned mosquito"?
(Her remark brought out the painful memory of Jong Kook.)
- It was itchy. That's why. - Come here.
- Are you making fun of him? - No. I have a mosquito bite.
(Shaking his head)
You know how much Jong Kook hates that nickname.
You want a really big mosquito bite?
(Scared)
That was unbelievable.
(The horrifying team selection ends.)
Let's go for now. Let's get out.
Can we leave now?
Jong Kook.
- It has been a long time - How could this happen?
(He's finally singing the song to the one he wanted to sing to.)
Se Chan, you won a lot of brownie points.
(He sings Jong Kook's song showing all of his gums.)
- It feels natural - It feels natural
- Just by the look on your face - Just by the look on your face
(And this one man replies to Se Chan's song.)
- Ji Hyo. - I can tell how you feel
(The reconciliation centered around Jong Kook)
- Like a close friend - Like a close friend
(And these 2 members can no longer smile.)
- I knew Haha would betray him. - Hello.
So, he smiles happily at me only when I have a picture taken...
- at his restaurant. - Exactly.
- He said he'll withdraw investment. - He used me.
(He's about to go bankrupt.)
He meant it.
(Holding a grudge)
Only when we discuss about his restaurant business.
I can't trust Haha.
(He's going to lose an investor because of his misjudgment.)
Haha.
I'm not feeling well.
(The team selection ends as they see each other's thoughts.)
- Just as I told you earlier, - Yes.
today's theme is Trade King Race.
- Jong Kook's team is Team America. - Team America?
(Jong Kook won't respond.)
I mean, this is...
(Scared)
- Jong Kook, come on. - This is a variety show.
- Show some reaction. - Stop being upset.
Are you on the robot mode?
He's just standing there.
(His frozen heart won't thaw that easily.)
I'll cheer up a little when our guests arrive.
(It will be a long day.)
- Look at his face. - The other team is Team Asia.
Team Asia!
Jae Suk and Suk Jin are Team Customs...
(And another team, the customs agents)
- and today's MCs. - Okay.
Team Customs will be given 100 dollars of fund.
Wait. Give it to me.
Why? Hey, why?
Suk Jin, I heard Jae Suk is your superior.
- Of course, he is. - And...
(He demoted from the boss of Petty Gang to a subordinate.)
each of Team America and Team Asia will be given...
- 200 dollars. - We receive money too.
(Team America and Team Asia both get 200 dollars each.)
Is it for the captain?
- 200 dollars? - It's for the team.
Also, as you might know if you watched the show,
So Min and Haha made necklaces.
(So Min and Haha made necklaces due to the penalty last week.)
Yes, we did.
- Oh, right. - I remember that.
I'll give it to Ji Hyo.
(So Min will give it to Ji Hyo, and Haha to Suk Jin.)
- I'll give it to Suk Jin. - Okay.
Haha, you should make it pretty.
I'm making this for Suk Jin. That's pointless.
(Just do whatever.)
All right. I'm done.
(Quick)
- That was quick. Haha... - I'm off. Bye.
Haha.
(Handmade mask necklaces made by So Min and Haha)
- Oh, right. - Yes, it was their penalty.
So Min and Haha, give them what you made for them.
(Here you go, Jong Kook.)
(She switches from Ji Hyo to Jong Kook.)
For whom did they make those?
- We chose the same person. - They already made their choices?
(I was going to give it to Jong Kook too.)
They already made their choices.
(She's giving it to Ji Hyo as she planned.)
Oh, she picked Ji Hyo.
- I chose him... - Your role model.
(Inner conflict)
hoping he'll live young.
(He gave it to Suk Jin hoping he'll feel younger.)
- Suk Jin. - Me?
Thank you.
Since you received a gift,
it looks as if today is your last day at work.
(Ji Suk Jin's Retirement Ceremony)
- We should give him some flowers. - It's like his retirement ceremony.
- His retirement ceremony? - Yes, his retirement ceremony.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you.
(So far...)
- Try it on. - Now?
(Feeling lazy)
- You should... - Try it on.
(The younger members want to see him wear it.)
- try it on. - You should try it on.
I can try it on later.
- I know you won't. - I don't think I should...
(We know.)
He'll probably give it to his stylist and say,
(It's obvious.)
"Hey, you can have this."
(So obvious.)
- Pull it. - Like this.
(He ends up wearing it.)
- It's pretty. - It's nice.
- He looks great. - Thank you for your hard work.
(Congratulations on your retirement.)
- Thank you for this. - You did a great job.
- Indeed. - You did...
- Thank you, Haha. - It's nice.
He's lying.
He didn't mean that.
(He thanked Haha halfheartedly.)
He must be thinking, "When can I take this off?"
(The retired agent isn't good at hiding his feelings.)
- He thinks it's a hassle. - He's waiting for the right moment.
Thank you, So Min. This is so pretty.
- Today, we have guests. - I see.
(The guests who will join both teams are waiting.)
We'll meet them downstairs.
(Let's go and welcome them.)
- All right. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Let's go, everybody.
- He's taking it off right away. - He's taking it off.
- Suk Jin. - Suk Jin.
Put it on at least until you get to the elevator.
(Come on.)
(Disappointed)
- Haha looks so disappointed. - You're the worst.
I'll cherish it.
"Let's go, everybody." What was that?
Ha Na.
(His stylist)
(After Big Nose thanked Haha,)
(they all move to meet the guests.)
For our today's theme, Trade King Race,
two guests will join...
each of Team America and Team Asia.
(2 guests will be joining each team.)
- Yes. - Okay.
Let's meet the guests who will join Team America first.
(Who are the guests that will join Team America?)
Team America.
- Please come in. - What's up?
(The 2 guests with American swag)
(Joon Park, Wassup Man from god)
What's up, brother?
(Joon, what's up?)
Look. Ailee is here.
(Ailee, the Beyonce of Korea)
(It's nice to meet you.)
(They're greeting excitedly as if they're in America.)
What's up?
- They really are Team America. - No wonder.
- They really are Team America. - We got both coasts covered.
We got both East Coast and West Coast covered.
(The perfect guests to join Team America.)
- By the way, Joon. - Yes?
Isn't it a little bit chilly to wear a sleeveless shirt?
(It's fall.)
To be honest, if I had known it would be this cold...
You know what I mean, right?
(This is Joon's signature phrase.)
- I haven't heard that in a while. - "You know what I mean, right?"
- I'm freezing. - Even I'm wearing long sleeves.
(Team America is already getting noisy.)
- Gosh. Look at you. - Even I'm wearing long sleeves.
Now, let's meet the guests who will join Team Asia.
(Revealing the guests of Team Asia)
I bet they're related to Asia.
(Screaming)
(Kangnam, the romanticist who dotes on Lee Sang Hwa)
Oh, Kangnam is here.
(Come on in.)
- Welcome. - Hey.
Yiren of EVERGLOW is here too.
(Yiren of EVERGLOW)
- Hello. - He's overacting.
He's forcing himself to act more energetic.
- Come over here. - He was too intense.
(Joon...)
(His excitement is unbeatable.)
- He's overacting. - Come over here.
(Calm down.)
- You don't have to do that. - You're on this team.
- You're on that team. - Oh, over there?
- Where should I stand? - Your name tag is there.
(Kangnam seems confused from the start.)
- Where should I stand? - Kangnam...
When Kangnam just made his debut,
- he was so charismatic. - My gosh.
- You gained some weight. - Right?
(His jawlines and face contour...)
- Yes. - Why did you gain so much weight?
(are hardly there as he gained weight on his cheeks.)
- Since I got married, - Really?
- I've been eating a lot. - You look great.
We have another guest. A member of EVERGLOW,
(Another guest of Team Asia)
- Yiren! - Yiren!
(Yiren, the Chinese member of EVERGLOW)
- She came on the show before. - Yes, I did.
She came on the show before.
(I remember.)
That's right. I appeared for a short while.
(She was an impactful extra in Episode 477.)
Whenever she's on a TV show, she draws attention.
- Really? - Because she's pretty.
(Yiren's pretty face draws attention whenever she's on a TV show.)
Ailee, did you release a new song?
(And...)
- Yes, I released a new song. - Really?
(Ailee's new song will be released on October 6th.)
- What's the title of the song? - Let's hear it.
It's "While We Were in Love".
- Let's hear her sing. - Let's do that.
("While We Were in Love" by Ailee)
(Why didn't you tell me While we were in love?)
(I can't imagine How hard it must have been)
(Her beautiful heart-wrenching voice makes everyone sentimental.)
(While we were in love)
(I did everything as I wanted)
(The sad melody reminded him of his past love.)
(Her voice is always easy on the ears.)
She can sing like that so early in the morning?
- That was awesome. - It's so early in the morning.
But why does So Min look like she's about to cry?
What's with your face? Gosh.
(Her eyes get moist.)
- What's wrong with you? - That's enough.
(The Love Frog empathized with the song too much.)
- So Min. - She ruined the mood.
- These days, So Min... - Yes?
starts crying when she just hears a love story.
- She's been single for two years. - Thank you.
(She gets very sentimental in the fall.)
I think it's time for you to publish another book.
"I Called Him Drunk".
("I Called Him Drunk", Jeon So Min's 2nd book of essays)
I heard...
that EVERGLOW also released a new song.
(EVERGLOW also made a comeback with the new song.)
- Yes, that's right. - Please show us a bit.
- Please show us a bit. - Okay.
- The title track is "LA DI DA". - I guess she'll dance.
(Expectant)
("LA DI DA" by EVERGLOW)
(Awesome groove)
(Smiling excitedly)
(Her powerful dance moves make her look charismatic.)
That was Yiren.
(Everyone is applauding her beautiful dance.)
- She looked so different. - That's a great song.
Indeed.
(Today's race begins with four of these guests.)
Today, we're having Trade King Race.
Three teams will compete, and the last place team...
will receive a scary penalty.
(The last place team will face a scary penalty.)
Penalties these days are not very intense,
- but they're annoying. - It was...
(The penalties nowadays...)
- boring, and it took a long time. - It's annoying, right?
(Today's penalty will also be tiresome.)
- I know. - Yes.
Each member of the winning team...
(The winning team gets 20 dollars after every mission.)
- will receive 20 dollars. - 20 dollars?
After you complete a mission,
you will have time to declare at customs.
(After every mission, they can get additional money...)
You can gain additional mission fund while doing that.
(during the customs declaration process.)
When we declare at customs?
Then we'll move to another place to begin the mission.
(Let's head for the first mission.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(They're gathering at the place where they'll complete the mission.)
(There are seats reserved for the MCs.)
You two really are a duo?
Where should I sit?
- I'm looking forward to this. - We're not a duo.
Please be gentle on us.
You know how powerful we are, right?
(Brightening)
- Please be gentle on us. - We make the decision.
(She bows in front of them as they seem powerful.)
Jae Suk, please be gentle on us.
Your smile looks so pretentious.
(They're not a fan of her unusual politeness.)
- Why don't you bring some snacks? - I hope...
(Acting arrogant)
That's not how you ask a favor.
(He openly asks for bribes.)
Do we have some chocolates?
So I can feed them.
(She had already given up on playing fair.)
(She tries to feed them to win.)
I think I need to give the MCs some food.
- First of all, we're going to... - Yes?
(Let's see.)
Jong Kook, listen. There will be punctuality score.
"Punctuality score"?
(The members are a bit late as they're getting changed.)
- Some of you are not here yet. - Those punks are not here yet.
Only the guests are here from this team.
- Exactly. - It's a disaster.
(The attendance rate is really low.)
Running Man is a popular show though.
- What is taking them so long? - Kwang Soo and I don't get along.
(He finds Kwang Soo's team coming in late.)
Hey!
- Don't... - Come quickly.
Don't yell.
(No shouting.)
Let me yell at them since I have power over them.
(His voice gets louder as he has power.)
Listen. You must be punctual.
Jong Kook, one of your members is missing.
(We were late because we were changing clothes.)
(Team Asia arrived in the midst of shouting.)
Guys. About the punctuality score...
(In terms of scores, Team Kwang Soo won.)
You were winning, but they turned the tables.
- I know. - They won.
But you yelled at us a lot.
- What? - You yelled at us too much.
- Hey. - Almost all of our members...
(No comment.)
- are here. - This is crazy.
Do you know what power I have?
(In this mission)
- What is it? - Do you have power?
(The winners will be decided by customs agents' consensus.)
Jae Suk and I get to decide.
We will decide the winner.
(He grasps the situation quickly.)
So you will have to listen to Jae Suk.
- What? - You can't decide it yourself.
Jae Suk and I have our own opinions.
So can you make a decision by yourself or not?
(Pressuring)
We will go 50-50.
So can you make a decision by yourself or not?
This is a democratic society. I can't decide anything alone.
We won't listen to you then.
What did you say?
(For the 3rd time)
We just need to get on Jae Suk's side.
Jae Suk.
Se Chan just ignored me.
I'm the director here.
(He draws a line.)
If you're a director, what is he?
- What's his title? - He's an intern.
- He's a section chief. - A section chief?
Are you talking about marinated crab?
Marinated crab? That sounds about right.
- Chief Ji. - It sounds good.
(Yoo Jae Suk, Director, Ji Suk Jin, Section Chief)
- I'm the director. - Director?
Director Yoo and Chief Ji.
- Chief Ji. - It sounds like a carrier.
(Is he the person who carries objects around?)
Chief Ji.
By the way, Team Jong Kook isn't still here.
(Haha still didn't come.)
Haha is getting makeup now.
(Haha is getting his makeup done.)
- Why would he get makeup? - Why?
- He even wears cologne. - Everyone.
He started talking.
(Director Yoo proceeds.)
- It's started. - We have 9 people out of 10.
(The mission starts with 90 percent attendance.)
- It's 90 percent attendance. - Sure.
I agree.
(It's consensus for now.)
He's very wise.
- You're so cool. - Director Yu, you're very wise.
Hey, why are you treating him differently?
(Feeling hurt)
- And... - That's because...
- Chief Ji. - you have no power.
You should be respectful towards them.
- Right. - I agree.
(Director Yoo is the best.)
- The thing is... - Now I have my power.
(Chief Ji wants to boast his power.)
It's not like that. This is a public office.
(Director Yoo wants to abide by the rules.)
- A public office? - We're here for the civil service.
- He's different. - Sure.
- In the old days... - You'll see.
(Whatever)
I also have my vote. You guys should remember that.
So your team has a director and a parrot.
He's not a parrot. He's a section chief.
(He often screeches, but he's not a bird.)
- Chief Ji. - Director Yoo and an old geezer.
Look at him.
- That punk. - Look.
(Haha comes late after his makeup.)
You can walk past.
Excuse me.
- We just... - How did it go?
(We need to impress the 2 hosts.)
lost our points.
Let me tell you about today's race.
(Trade King Race)
(The first mission of the day)
We are going to tell you about three controversial stories...
(The 2 hosts will introduce to 3 popular stories online.)
being discussed online.
That's good. I like it.
We will hear your opinions on the issues...
(After listening to all stories,)
(they'll pick either Okay or Not Okay as a team)
and decide if it's okay or not.
- We will make a decision. - Let me see.
Excuse me, but...
(I want to see it.)
Will you stay still?
Just sit still.
I'm sorry, but you haven't been an MC since "Six Heroines".
- Director Yu. - I'm sorry,
(Chief Ji is extremely curious as a host in a while.)
but you haven't been an MC since "Six Heroines".
- "Six Heroines"? - Just stay quiet.
Keep your mouth shut.
You haven't done this since "Six Heroines".
(He couldn't hold back and spits out harsh words.)
You need to watch your language for the civil service.
I just want to see it.
So the captains will pick one of these two.
(He resumes to explain the rules again.)
Each team will pick "Okay" and "Not Okay"...
(The two captains will pick either Okay or Not Okay.)
(The team must persuade the 2 hosts.)
and convince us accordingly.
- I see. - I've done this before.
If we pick "Not Okay",
we should go against the idea.
It's not about our real opinion.
(How they think on the matter is not important.)
- Exactly. - It's about what we pick.
(The key is to persuade the 2 hosts on what they pick.)
I will tell you a story...
that's under great controversy...
on the Internet.
Who told you to drink water?
(Crime: Drank water while Director Yoo was speaking)
- I knew you'd get scolded. - This is important.
- You're our captain. - I'm telling you...
(I'm sorry.)
- about something important. - You need to win his favor.
- How dare you... - I'm sorry.
(He fully exploits his power.)
How dare you drink water?
I'm really sorry.
(Team Asia leader is humiliated after drinking water.)
I just saw water here.
We have strong power here.
- I'm sorry, but... - We have strong power.
Ailee was about to drink water.
- Go ahead and drink it, Ailee. - Go ahead.
I will tell you a story...
Who told you to drink water?
(Surprised)
I was thirsty. That was close.
(Ailee decided to suppress thirst...)
- Go ahead and drink it, Ailee. - Go ahead.
Ailee, you can drink.
(as the hosts yell.)
What are you doing?
- Let her drink water. - She was thirsty.
She's our guest.
- She says she was thirsty. - It's okay. Go ahead and drink.
(Ailee, the guest)
You are okay.
(Host Ji is friendly even if he can't enunciate well.)
Ailee, I like your song, "I'll Go to You Like the First Snow".
Stop it.
About the cue cards Suk Jin is holding...
This one? It's fake.
This is real.
- It's real. - It's nothing.
(Is he pretending with the fake cue cards?)
- This is real. - No, it's fake.
I'll read a story.
This is like "Men Who Top the Charts".
It has some words,
but it's different from mine.
It's just for a show.
(The cue cards have no important parts.)
It doesn't have the important part.
Suk Jin, switch seats with him.
- So there's fierce controversy... - It's not fierce.
(It's time to reveal the first controversial story.)
over these stories online.
Here's the first story.
- This is good. - I'm excited.
We can make a coherent argument.
(What do each member think about the story?)
- We have So Min too. - Sure.
- We're good at this. - This...
has been under controversy...
(It's been under controversy since the invention of mobile phones.)
for a long time since we got cell phones.
- It applies to all of us? - It's about...
sharing the phone password.
(Sharing the phone password: Okay or Not Okay?)
Who do we share it with?
My girlfriend or parents?
(He pretends as if he knows.)
- Your girlfriend. - My girlfriend?
- Not my parents? - No.
- Let me read... - I'll...
read a story.
Stay quiet.
I've been waiting to read this.
(Chief Ji has been waiting a long time for his part.)
Suk Jin. Just sit here.
(I'd just recommend a seat in this corner.)
- Stay quiet! - Suk Jin, come have a seat.
I feel bad for Suk Jin.
(The word impossible is not in Chief Ji's dictionary.)
My gosh.
Let me read a story for you.
(He finally earned his right to read the story.)
- We will talk about this story. - All right then.
- Chief Ji will read you a story. - Right.
(He proceeds with Director Yu's approval.)
Please listen.
"We're a couple in our early 20s, and we've been dating for 6 months."
- In their early 20s. - Think carefully about it.
"We were watching a movie together at home a few days ago."
"Then my girlfriend asked me to unlock my phone."
All of a sudden?
"I thought she wanted to see some photos, so I unlocked it."
"Then she asked me about my messaging app password."
She asked about his messaging app password.
She crossed the line.
"My girlfriend said..."
- Just stay still. - Hurry.
This isn't important. Just hurry and get it over with.
"My girlfriend said there should be no secret between lovers."
(The story continues despite Director Yu's push.)
(Yawning)
"She asked me to share my phone password..."
(He continues to read as if he doesn't care.)
"and messaging app password."
"I think even couples..." Think carefully about this.
"She asked me to share my phone password..."
"and messaging app password."
(He even reads all the unnecessary...)
"I think even couples..."
(part of the story.)
(They all fall asleep together.)
- "We should have some secrets." - Director Yu, please read it again.
Gosh, I'm startled.
(Surprised by the loud noise)
- What happened? - "After a long squabble..."
- Hey. - Hello?
- Hi. - Wake up.
- Hello? Hi. - Wake up.
(They can't continue.)
- How are you? - Wake up, everyone.
(Smacking)
Wake up.
(Chief Ji wakes everyone up with the sign.)
- What? - Why? What's wrong, Kwang Soo?
I just had a paralyzing nightmare.
(Goosebumps)
(The story is like a nightmare.)
Everyone. This is exciting, isn't it?
(The person fought with the lover over the phone password.)
"We squabbled for a while, but we failed to reach an agreement."
"So we decided to talk about it again later."
"Is it okay to share the passwords of phones..."
(Sharing phone passwords between the lovers)
"and messaging apps with my girlfriend?"
(Okay or Not Okay?)
All right. Before we start talking about it,
I wonder what you think.
I think we should never...
share passwords in any case.
(Chief Ji is against sharing.)
- Why not? - Why do you think so?
It's uncomfortable. I share my passwords with my wife.
- I see. - So whenever I get a message,
my heart beats fast.
- Why? - I don't know.
(His heart beats fast even when he did nothing wrong.)
- I didn't do anything wrong. - Then why?
- Why? - I don't know.
My wife might get the wrong idea.
(He didn't do anything wrong, but his wife might misunderstand.)
- What? - She might take it the wrong way.
Now I get it. One day, Suk Jin...
(So Min's report)
kept leaving the chat room we were in together.
So I wondered why he was being like that.
(Why would he delete messages with So Min?)
Why did you leave the chat room with So Min?
The problem is,
you act cute with your messages.
(Criticizing)
When did I do that?
(Startled)
- That's not true. - Suk Jin.
You send too many emojis.
- What's wrong about using emojis? - That's not true.
(Chief Ji is still unfamiliar with the realm of emojis.)
Guys. I want you to give your opinions now.
(It's time to listen to everyone else's opinion.)
Is it okay to share your passwords with your lover?
- Gosh, this is... - Se Chan, go ahead.
(Se Chan has a lot to say.)
I once broke up with my girlfriend because of this issue.
- I knew it. - We broke up.
(Se Chan shares a story of his own.)
So the thing is,
(Personally, it's not okay to share passwords.)
you can exchange some jokes...
(Chats include jokes that he shared with friends.)
with your friends on messaging apps.
Sometimes I send some jokes to make my friends laugh.
I also send some pictures.
But my girlfriend took it the wrong way.
- She thought I was being strange. - I understand.
(Se Chan was wrongly accused once.)
Are you talking about the flight attendant?
- Hey! - Okay. I get it.
(What did you say?)
- Why would you say that? - Okay.
(A sudden stop during Se Chan's story.)
- He's mad for real. - All right.
- I'm giving you a warning. - I'm sorry.
(Warning for Lee Kwang Soo)
- I'm really sorry. - Can I talk about her as well?
- I apologize. - I'll talk about her too.
Hey.
Don't mention flight attendants. It also applies to Jae Suk.
Are you crazy?
- Don't say that. - Keep quiet.
(An unexpected attack on the host)
- His wife is watching. - We all have a past.
- Really? - Why would he talk about my past?
(What did you just say?)
Really?
Do you want me to talk about you?
- Do you want to start it? - All right.
(A dangerous risk of unexpected revelation)
- Look at you. - I get it.
- I have a lot to talk about. - Okay, okay.
(You'd better watch out.)
(The revelation of their past happens one after another.)
What about you, Kangnam?
(What does Kangnam think?)
My wife and I share passwords.
We know each other's passwords,
(They know each other's password but don't look.)
but we don't check each other's phone.
- You don't? - No.
- But you know her passwords? - I do, but I don't check her phone.
This is different.
Do you really think your wife didn't check your phone?
(The mobile phone)
- Yes. - I'm sure she did.
Yes.
(He ends the conversation right away.)
I think Kangnam doesn't even want to talk to you.
He's the section chief.
- He's ignoring you. - He still holds a high position.
(He has a title.)
- He is the section chief. - He has his own title.
- I still have a 50-percent share. - He has a vote.
(He will have a vote in determining the winner.)
You can't ignore him.
- Does he hold a high position? - He has a vote.
(I've never heard of him before.)
We should respect each other's opinion.
- You shouldn't ignore others. - I agree.
(One is not allowed to ignore or mock others.)
And you can't make fun of others.
- Make sure not to do those things. - Okay.
- I have my power. - "Yes."
I think it's better not to share passwords.
(So Min is against sharing passwords.)
I've never shared my password with my ex-boyfriend.
- But he figured it out himself. - How?
- How did he figure it out? - He looked over my shoulder.
That's dangerous.
(Shocked)
Then he looked at my phone and got me wrong.
(So Min was also wrongly accused once.)
"Why are you being so kind to other guys?"
But her messages can be misleading.
- She's too kind. - All right.
I'd like you to talk less.
What you said is like 80 percent!
You're the one who talked a lot.
(The 20 Percent Guy still has a lot to say.)
Is he a bully or something?
- He sounds like a bully. - He rarely talked.
- You did most of the talking. - Talk less.
(The talking thug is eager to host.)
It feels like I'm listening to a radio show.
If you don't want to get hit, just stay quiet.
(He recommends to stay put.)
- All right. Continue. - Let's say I told my boyfriend...
(So Min resumes her story.)
my password, and he checked my phone once.
It should end there, but he keeps thinking about it.
(It doesn't end with just one look.)
"Oh, right. I should check..."
"the friends she blocked on the messaging app."
- He even checks those? - He does.
- I didn't know that. - And...
(It's her way of love.)
- That sounds scary. - They even check things like that?
That's why I don't want to know the password in the first place.
- I don't even start. - It's better not to see it.
- It's distressing. - Captain Jong Kook, you're up.
Here's what I think. It's...
Hang on. Don't get worked up even before you start talking.
He's right.
Your shoulders are too broad.
The thing is...
(He speaks in a calm manner by suppressing his muscles.)
If my girlfriend...
- She must have male friends, right? - Of course.
(It's not okay to share the password.)
(My girlfriend has male friends.)
I wouldn't want to see her texts to them with my own eyes.
(I don't want to see her keeping in touch with them.)
- You wouldn't? - I would just trust my girlfriend.
- Exactly. - Right.
(The person who experienced a breakup agrees.)
It seems that most of you, Suk Jin, and I...
- believe... - Many are against it.
(After sharing opinions,)
that it's right for a couple to not share...
(most people said it's not okay to share the password.)
- each other's password. - That's better.
- If you know the password... - That's the prevailing opinion.
You'd want to look through the phone if you know the password.
But 1 of the 2 teams here will defend the opposite opinion.
(However,)
- The captain of each team... - I'm worried.
(the team's opinion depends on the captain's draw.)
- will pick the side. - You will pick the side.
- And according to the result, - This is so important.
you may have to argue...
what is against your point of view in front of us.
(What's the result of their draw?)
You have to convince us.
- Kwang Soo, pick the good one. - You should pick the good one.
(Not Okay seems easier to convince the MCs.)
- I should pick Not Okay, right? - Don't pick Okay.
You should pick the good one.
(Which one will the unlucky Kwang Soo pick?)
- Right. Please pick Not Okay. - You should pick Not Okay.
- I should pick Not Okay, right? - Don't pick Okay.
(Team Asia)
- You should pick Not Okay. - It's Not Okay.
(Team Asia picked Not Okay.)
- Okay! - Now...
- It's Not Okay. - Okay!
- I made it. - Good.
(Team Asia is happy as if they won already.)
- We'll be okay. - Let's win the first round.
- We'll be okay. It'll be easy. - You never know.
(Team America automatically supports sharing of the password.)
- We can do this. - You just have to...
- convince us. - We can do this.
- Your team is Not Okay. - Yes.
(The team that convinces 2 MCs wins Round 1.)
- This team is Okay. - Yes.
You can just convince us.
Just as we said earlier, if a couple shares the password,
(Se Chan speaks up upon the start.)
it leads to a misunderstanding and they end up breaking up.
- Don't cause a misunderstanding. - You shouldn't do anything...
- that can cause a misunderstanding. - What if you didn't?
Even if they did nothing suspicious, it can lead to a fight,
(It's not okay to share the password.)
- and they grow apart eventually. - Even if nothing happened...
(Minor misunderstandings pile up and cause a major fight.)
For example, I came back from the restroom.
- Can you lower your voice, please? - Exactly.
- I was... - You're too loud.
I was the quietest among all of us.
You're too loud.
- I was the quietest. - You're sitting close to me.
(Still, be quiet.)
- You don't have to be that loud. - Should I whisper to you?
- Calm down. - Gosh, seriously.
- Calm down. - We're all wearing a microphone.
He's right. We need to stay calm.
Are we shooting an ASMR video?
(My goodness.)
- We need to stay cool. - Speak quietly.
- What I'm saying is... - In my opinion, in a case of...
- What I'm saying is... - In my opinion...
In a case of...
(Turning their heads around)
- In a case of emergency... - Poor Kwang Soo.
(He lost his chance to speak just like that.)
- Even Ailee cut him off too. - She jumped in.
- She's really something. - Let's hear her out.
- She's not an easy fight. - I want to hear her out.
- In a case of emergency... - I want to hear her out too.
(Extraordinary Ailee's opinion on "Okay")
Let's say I'm meeting my boyfriend,
(It's okay to share the password.)
and we got into an accident.
And my boyfriend is unconscious.
(What if they got into an accident on a date?)
- I have to call his parents, - Of course.
but I don't have their numbers.
I need to know the password to unlock his phone...
(There could be emergency situations where she has to know the password.)
- and call his parents. - Exactly.
- That can't be an excuse. - That's...
- an extreme case. - Wouldn't you call his parents?
- You should call the rescue center. - Exactly.
Listen to me. People have their own ways...
(Ji Hyo's objection)
of interpreting when they read text messages.
(It's not okay to share the password.)
(You read the texts the way you want and think.)
- That's right. - Therefore,
- even some meaningless texts... - Exactly.
(The text doesn't mean anything, but it could cause a misunderstanding.)
- can cause a misunderstanding. - It can cause a misunderstanding.
- Such misunderstandings... - You don't have to read them.
(Just know the password.)
(What if you do?)
But what if you read some texts unintentionally?
- Let's say your girlfriend... - Yes?
or your boyfriend wants you two to share each other's password.
- If my girlfriend wants that? No. - Yes.
Then would you break up with her even though you love her?
- He wouldn't break up with her. - I would convince her...
and ask why she wants to look through my phone.
Just tell me your password, Se Chan.
(Putting on a skit)
Once you unlock my phone, we're over.
- All right. Just tell me. - If you trust her...
If you look through my phone, we're over.
Sure. I'll let you go. Just tell me your password.
("We're over if you go through it"...)
- You said you'll let me go. - Yes.
I said I won't look through your phone.
(versus "Just tell me your password")
If you look through my phone, we're over.
(It's as if they are the only people that exist in this place.)
Sure. I'll let you go. Just tell me your password.
- You said you'll let me go. - Yes.
(They won't stop arguing as if they're a real couple.)
I said I won't look through your phone.
- You said you'll let me go. - Yes.
(Se Chan is running out of patience.)
I said I won't look through your phone.
- Just tell me your password. - Then why do you need it?
- You said you won't see it. - Look at him. He's getting upset.
- You said you won't see it. - He's getting upset.
- Look at him. He's getting upset. - You said you won't see it.
(He's getting extremely upset.)
- He's getting upset. - I won't.
(Se Chan. If you fight, you lose.)
Se Chan. Gosh.
- Sit down. - You said you won't see it.
- You just said you won't see it. - Calm him down.
- I mean, you said you won't see it. - Calm down.
(Se Chan took off his shoes as he got angry.)
- Listen. - You said you won't see it.
- I mean, you said you won't see it. - Calm down.
(I won't look through your phone, but give me your password.)
- Calm down. Stop him. - You said you won't see it.
- Then why do you need it? - I mean...
(The man who experienced a breakup is stimulated by perfect reasoning.)
- I know. - He said he won't see it.
I just want to know your password. That's all.
(Sighing)
- Gosh. What else should I do? - I just want to know the password.
- Sit down and drink some water. - He won't look through your phone.
(Calm down, Se Chan.)
- He won't look through it. - Gosh, I can't believe this.
I know. Just drink some water.
I won't, I promise. I want to set my password the same as yours.
(With a cup of cold water, the dangerous skit ends.)
- In fact, this debate... - Yes.
(In fact, this debate...)
should be based on the premise...
that the couple will look through each other's phone.
- It's only reasonable. - No.
- There's no way you don't see it. - That's not true.
- That's not possible. - Why would you even ask for it?
I'm confident that I won't look through the phone.
Based on the premise that they look through each other's phone...
- I wouldn't look through the phone. - That's not possible.
- How would that be possible? - I wouldn't look through it.
(The debate is back on while trying to clarify the assumption.)
You would become curious if you know the password.
(You would become curious if you know the password.)
- That can start a fight. - I can hold myself back.
(Arguing loudly)
- Listen to me. - No way.
- Everyone, listen to me! - You see...
(Frustrated)
(They suddenly standup.)
- I mean... - Calm down.
(Screaming)
- See? Look at us. - I wouldn't do that.
Talking about it alone made us fight.
- Exactly. - You should never share it.
(See this?)
There's nothing to fight over if you don't know the password.
- If you share it... - You can share the password...
(It's okay to share the password.)
without looking through the phone.
What we're saying is that it's okay to share my password...
(We won't look. We'll only share the password.)
(Jong Kook delivers his final remarks.)
with the person I love...
(It's okay to share the password.)
(It's okay to share the password as a sign of love.)
- as a token of love. - That's right.
It's okay.
- All right. Time is up. - Oh, no.
(Time to convince them is up.)
The team that Chief Ji and I have chosen as the winner...
(2 MCs will choose a team that convinced them better.)
of the first topic...
- You made the decision alone? - about sharing passwords...
to a cell phone and a messaging app...
They didn't even have a discussion.
(They skip the conversation for efficiency.)
- We should discuss first. - Oh, right.
Didn't you two have a discussion?
(Whispering)
I thought they agreed...
- Okay? - Yes, I agree with you,
but this is very unpleasant.
(Chief Ji wants to sulk for some reason.)
I mean, I agree with you, but...
- That's all that matters. - I agree, but...
- I knew that. - I admit...
(I knew it.)
- I agree with him. - We have the same opinion.
(After sharing opinions, they finally make a decision.)
- They have a better chance to win. - The first topic...
(Which team convinced 2 MCs?)
about sharing passwords. 1, 2, 3.
(The MCs picked...)
- Not Okay. - Oh, yes.
(Not Okay.)
- Nice. - Good job.
(Team Asia won the 1st round.)
- Not Okay. - Oh, yes.
(It's sad, but they accept it.)
- I admit they were right. - Good job.
This is great.
- You see... - It was a difficult topic.
(Opinions on "Not Okay" were dominant from the start.)
- It was so difficult. - That's true.
We won.
Kwang Soo's team won the first round.
(Team Asia won the heated debate.)
- I'm glad he picked Not Okay. - This is fun.
(There's still a story left.)
- Next topic. - This is also a sensitive issue.
- Good job. - This is fun.
(Next question)
Actually,
when we first read this topic, we thought the same thing again.
(Chatty)
We're leaning toward one side.
"Giving your jacket to your girlfriend's friend..."
(Cutting off)
(He's not even angry anymore.)
- "on a cold day." - Just get to the point.
That's difficult.
(Giving your jacket to your girlfriend's friend on a cold day)
Okay or Not Okay?
(Okay versus Not Okay)
Not Okay!
- It's not okay. - What was the topic?
- It can never be okay. - "Not long ago, I was..."
"drinking beer with my girlfriend and her friend in the terrace."
"It became quite chilly in the evening,"
"and my girlfriend's friend said she was cold."
"I was wearing a jacket,"
"and I wasn't cold, so I gave my jacket to her."
- He made a mistake. - "While taking my girlfriend home,"
"we started arguing."
(My girlfriend got really mad.)
"My girlfriend got mad at me saying she didn't understand..."
"why I gave my jacket to her friend."
"I did it only because her friend was cold."
"Is it not okay to give my jacket to my girlfriend's friend?"
- Do you think it's not okay? - That's excessive kindness.
- He was being too kind. - Many men don't know this.
(Thinking)
- Let's hear So Min's story. - So Min looks angry already.
(So Min is already angry.)
- She's upset. - She looks very angry.
First of all, I have a similar experience.
If we just consider the situation in this story,
(Relationship expert Doctor Jeon)
it depends on what kind of girl the girlfriend's friend is...
(It depends on who the girlfriend's friend is.)
and her taste in men.
If her friend is popular among guys,
- she would be angry. However... - I see.
(That makes sense.)
- However... - That makes sense.
(Doctor Jeon's smart analysis)
- I see what she means. - She has a point.
- You see... - It's very important.
(The level of anger depends on the friend's popularity.)
- Actually, - That's a good point.
I have a pretty friend. One day, the three of us went to a karaoke.
(So Min, pretty bestie and boyfriend went to karaoke together.)
- I see what she means. - But...
my boyfriend sang the songs my friend wanted to hear.
(Her boyfriend kept singing her bestie's requests.)
- Of course, you'd get angry. - He shouldn't have done that.
(No wonder you were angry.)
We had a big fight while he was walking me home.
I see why you got angry.
But my friend is really pretty and popular.
- That's what any men would do. - She can attract a man...
just by talking to him.
It's so hard to figure out what women want.
When you give a girl flowers, sometimes she's happy,
but sometimes she gets mad at you.
- What must I do to make her happy? - Exactly.
(Suddenly agitated)
That's exactly my point.
(Chief Ji sympathizes with him.)
- You know what I mean, right? - Whatever I do, she gets mad.
I hope there will be a book on this topic.
(Chief Ji asks for a scolding.)
Since we're talking about it, can anyone share a story...
(What was their worst relationship?)
about the worst person you've ever dated?
- Yiren, what about you? - No.
- Hold on. - No.
(She answered right away.)
- Hold on. He wasn't even finished. - That was quick.
- She's an idol singer, you know. - Yiren...
(She says no as soon as she hears the word relationship.)
She seemed like she was ready to say no.
- All idol singers react like that. - Okay.
(Joon Park knows how idols feel.)
- I accept your answer. - Okay.
(They respect the idol's privacy.)
Everyone, imagine a situation where their roles are reversed.
(If you switch the man and woman in the story...)
Let's say your friend joins you when you're with your girlfriend.
Your friend says he's cold.
(What if my girlfriend gives her jacket to my bestie?)
And your girlfriend takes off her jacket...
- The girl gives her jacket? - and gives it to your friend.
- The girl gives her jacket to him? - Yes.
- The girl... - Imagine that situation.
- If you consider... - If you imagine that situation...
(Se Chan imagined the situation.)
Just as So Min explained,
I wouldn't mind if it's Kwang Soo, but I'd be mad if it's Jong Kook.
(The safe friend)
- Gosh. Why? - I was looking at you two.
(The date doc's theory applies perfectly.)
- I thought I'd be okay with you, - Exactly.
but if it's Jong Kook, it would bother me.
That makes you upset.
- That thought crossed my mind. - Exactly.
(Kwang Soo is the safest friend in the whole wide world.)
For example,
you let Se Chan or Suk Jin tag along on a date.
(If my girlfriend takes her jacket off for Se Chan or Suk Jin...)
And when he says he's cold, your girlfriend gives him her jacket.
You would think, "My girlfriend is so kind."
- Exactly. You'd feel that way too. - I see.
(The ugly friend makes you realize how kind your girlfriend is.)
- The same goes for you. - Jae Suk.
- The same goes for you. - It's the same for him.
- Yes. - That would make you...
love your girlfriend even more.
(My girlfriend is a philanthropist.)
In a situation like that...
- If it's Suk Jin, - "I'll be with her forever."
I wouldn't mind even if she wipes his mouth.
That wouldn't bother me at all.
(It's literally a good deed.)
- Whatever she does, - But...
I would only think she's kind.
- Honestly, - I agree.
(He'll never be jealous.)
- I would love her even more. - That makes sense.
But I think I'd react differently.
Let's say I'm with my girlfriend and her friend.
(If my girlfriend's friend is cold...)
If her friend says she's cold,
I would ask my girlfriend if she's okay first.
- That's so sweet. - You should start dating!
- I'm just saying... - All he does is imagine...
- dating a girl. - Wouldn't anyone do that?
- He knows everything about dating. - Of course.
(Another date doc aside from Doctor Jeon)
- He's like a dating expert. - Yes.
(Kim Jong Kook, workout doctor and date doctor)
You need to choose the side. Ailee, pick one.
(It's time for teams to pick their opinions.)
- I'm nervous. - It doesn't matter.
- But the girl... - It doesn't matter.
- Okay. - She picked Okay.
(Team America picked Okay.)
(Team Asia picked Not Okay.)
- The other team is Not Okay. - It's okay.
- We got Not Okay. - It's okay.
- It's not okay. - It's okay.
I'm sure So Min will still say it's not okay.
(So Min has a different opinion from her team.)
He can give his girlfriend his phone password after that.
- That's right. It's okay. - His phone password?
- It's okay. - This is crazy.
It's okay.
(She went back on her conviction to win.)
- It's okay. - Why do you think so?
(She can't say why it's okay.)
- Is it okay? - It's okay.
- Please explain. - I'll explain to you.
When a man acts like that,
(It's okay.)
he does it only to make his girlfriend stand out.
(You do it...)
(to make your girlfriend stand out.)
- He's right. - To make her look good.
- That's a good point. - It shows that he has good manners.
However, some girls...
would think that he does it because he likes her like So Min did.
But there are many women who hate it.
(Kwang Soo speaks as the representative of Not Okay.)
- Yes, there are many. - Kwang Soo.
- You're polite and considerate. - Right.
- So that's what you do. - It's an act of kindness.
- I bet people misunderstood you. - Right.
- That's why you're against it. - Of course.
- If that's the case... - With Kwang Soo...
But this is what you do...
(He starts to get persuaded as he uses himself as an example.)
out of the kindness of your heart.
But this is her best friend.
If...
(Darn. Truth be told, I'm okay with it.)
Darn. Truth be told, I'm okay with it.
- What? - It's okay.
You need to be more persuasive.
- I'm leaning toward them. - You're not winning me over.
You're fine with it too, right?
Ji Hyo's okay with it too.
- Let us make a decision then. - We'll make our decision.
(The 3 hosts will decide.)
Offering your jacket to your girlfriend's best friend.
(Offering your jacket to your girlfriend's best friend.)
Is it okay or not?
- It's not. - We've come to a verdict.
(Their choice is...)
- It's okay. - It's okay.
(Okay.)
You weren't able to persuade us.
(Team America wins.)
You weren't convincing enough.
You weren't able to persuade us.
(I'm actually okay with it.)
- Well... - We couldn't understand it either.
- You're okay with it? - You're only being polite.
The girlfriend should be proud.
- 1, 2, 3. It's okay. - It's okay.
(After the conclusion of the following debate)
Of course, it is.
Team America who won with a score of 2 to 1...
will receive 20 dollars.
(Team America wins!)
So that's how it goes.
(Team America gets 20 dollars.)
Don't we get anything?
What about us?
(Team Customs)
You'll be rewarded too.
This is your first customs declaration process.
(The first customs declaration process)
Each team will take turns entering that room.
(Each team will go into the room...)
While in there, you will choose one box.
(and choose 1 of 10 boxes.)
There are 10 boxes in total, and 2 boxes each contain...
(2 boxes of 20, 40, 60, 80, and 100 dollars each)
20, 40, 60, 80, 100 dollars respectively.
Once you check the amount, you'll bring it out...
(The members will check the box of their team...)
and pay up half of that money...
(and pay half the amount as taxes.)
- as tax. - To us, right?
You are allowed to write down...
(But they may lie to pay less.)
a smaller amount than you should pay.
Let's say you chose a box with 100 dollars.
(For instance, if they acquire the box of 100 dollars...)
You can lie...
(Lie: "I earned 40 dollars, so I'll pay 20 dollars.)
and only hand over 10 or 20 dollars.
(Should we check it or not?)
If you're caught in a lie,
(We'll check it.)
the customs agents will take everything.
(If they get checked after lying,)
- What if you're not caught? - Then...
the agents will pay your tax for you,
(Team Customs will take all the money.)
- and you'll take the full amount. - If we don't catch them?
If they choose to check...
(If they get checked after telling the truth,)
- even though I'm not lying... - That's right.
(Team Customs will pay all the taxes for them.)
- Right. - The agents...
- will receive a penalty? - They'll pay the tax instead.
Got it.
(Team Customs must be cautious.)
The team that lost will go first.
(Team Asia will choose a box first.)
These guys...
- This isn't easy, you know. - They could...
(Psychological warfare...)
try to trick us.
- Okay. - They'll think that we'll lie.
(between paying 50 percent as taxes and dodging the taxes)
- If we take the chance... - It won't help us win.
(They're confused even before they pick a box.)
- This is driving me crazy. - But we need to take a chance.
What's best...
is for us to pick 100 dollars...
and pay up 10 dollars...
- without them suspecting us. - Right.
Why won't they though?
(Kwang Soo is their leader.)
They would.
Kangnam, pick one.
(They'll think after they pick.)
- Should I just choose? - A smaller amount is better.
- Maybe 50 dollars. - Just choose.
Anything? Then I'll...
- This one? - Number four.
(He chooses box number 4.)
Four...
The choice is 20, 40, 60, 80, 100 dollars.
Please...
(Among 20, 40, 60, 80, and 100 dollars,)
It's not too bad.
(how much money did they get?)
(It's not too bad?)
They'll doubt us for sure especially since Kwang Soo's the captain.
(What will be Team Asia's strategy?)
It's all about how much money was in the box they chose.
- Here they come. - We're ready.
(Confident)
Ji Hyo, what's the amount?
(Feeling them out)
- Well... - Look at their expressions.
(No comment)
We picked our box.
- Hand it over. - Pay your tax.
The box we chose had 40 dollars.
- 40 dollars? - Yes.
- So you'll pay 20 dollars? - Yes.
(You earned 40 dollars.)
- There was a heated discussion. - That's right.
(Kwang Soo says they'll pay 20 dollars of taxes.)
- Hold on. - He's not the kind of person...
to pay up 20 dollars when all he has is 40 dollars.
What?
He'd only give up 20 dollars if he had chosen 60.
That's right.
(Keeping a straight face)
The rules say he must cough up half.
- But he wouldn't. - Right.
Yiren's too innocent...
(Born in 2000)
to bluff in any way.
- How much was in the box? - 30 dollars.
- 30 dollars? - 30 dollars?
- Yet you're paying 20 dollars? - No, 40 dollars!
(Suspicious)
- Hold on. - No, 40 dollars!
(Flustered)
(Scoffing)
- We chose 40 dollars. - Hold on.
(The suspicion grows after her answer.)
- No, 40 dollars. - Wait a second.
- 30 dollars? - You chose 30 dollars,
but you're paying up 20 dollars?
I meant 40 dollars.
She got confused because of the Chinese word.
He'd never pay up half.
(Kwang Soo being the team leader tells them that they're evading it.)
- Right? - Of course not.
Also, Kangnam's shaking. Look at his fingers.
- Let me be honest with you. - Sure.
You're absolutely right.
(Jae Suk, you're absolutely right.)
- 60 dollars was in our box. - Right?
But?
(What is he trying to say?)
We chose 60 dollars...
- But you're only paying 20? - Yes.
- So you're lying to us. - Yes.
(Did Kwang Soo confess to tax evasion?)
- Hold on... - Shouldn't you pay up half?
He's playing mind games.
He's trying to get us to confirm what was in the box.
(Is he trying to get them to open the box?)
(If Kwang Soo is wrongfully suspected, he won't have to pay.)
I think we should check.
Can you give me your hand?
This is Jong Kook's trick.
Your palm is wet.
(He can't hide how sweaty his palm is.)
My gosh.
(Sweaty)
Don't do that.
Don't you do that.
(Jong Kook's lie detector test is quite accurate.)
- Don't. - His palm is sweaty.
It can't be wetter.
(What will Team Customs do?)
But his expression...
- Exactly. - This is intriguing.
- Maybe we shouldn't check. - It's getting interesting.
- We won't get much anyway. - Exactly.
So we won't check.
(We won't check it.)
(They've been cleared.)
- We won't get much anyway. - That's the right choice.
(Team Asia's expressions seem subtle.)
There's not much to take anyway.
(Did Kwang Soo's plan work?)
20 dollars is more than enough.
Okay, we won't check.
I have a feeling that So Min will choose well.
(It's time for Team America to choose a box.)
- Really? - Right, of course.
- She's not the luckiest type but... - Really?
(What will the unlucky So Min pick?)
- Still. Just go ahead. - Really? Let's get it.
- Not that one. - This is the number I like.
(She chooses box number 5.)
- Really? - I like this number.
(How much money will be inside?)
- What? - Go ahead.
It's all about how much they pay up.
- We... - Yes?
We chose 80 dollars.
Let's get it!
(Jong Kook claims that his team chose 80 dollars.)
(Without hesitation)
So we'll cough up 40 dollars.
- That much... - Hold on.
(Flustered by the larger amount than expected)
Why would we bother to check?
I mean...
If they're lying, it means they chose 100 dollars.
The highest amount they can get is 100 dollars.
Instead of 50, they paid up 40, so that's a 10 dollar difference.
They're only pocketing 10 more dollars.
You'll go this far for just 10 dollars?
- So 40 dollars. - 40 dollars?
They must be telling the truth.
(The agents decide they couldn't have lied to earn that much.)
- Right. - That's what I think.
We'll clear their team too.
(Both teams are cleared.)
- Then... - Did they fool us?
Both captains will reveal how much was in the box.
(Revealing the actual amount they acquired)
In our case...
(Team Asia already admitted to tax evasion.)
(So how much was actually in the box?)
Jae Suk was right on point.
- Right. - He saw right through us.
(What?)
- How so? - We chose 60 dollars,
(Team Asia earned 60 dollars.)
and I insisted that we only pay up...
(Kwang Soo insisted...)
20 dollars.
(that they pay 20 dollars less.)
I knew it.
(Team Asia saved 10 dollars of taxes thanks to Kwang Soo.)
- Right off the bat... - Right from the start...
- Jae Suk said... - He said I was going to lie.
Still, I asked my team to believe in me this once.
(Yiren can smile again.)
When Yiren said "30 dollars",
it was the amount you originally had to pay up.
- That's right. - I should've realized.
(They were almost caught.)
- Goodness. - You're good at deducting though.
- I called it. - What he said at first...
(Talking big after it all ends)
- I told you his palms were sweaty. - My palms...
No one should be allowed to check palms anymore!
- Anyway, good job. - Nice.
(They successfully evade taxes thanks to Kwang Soo's acting.)
- It went as planned. - We won 20 dollars though.
How much did you choose? Was it 100 dollars?
(Did Team America lie too?)
Was it 100 dollars?
We...
- You told the truth, right? - It was 80 dollars.
Of course.
(They made the right choice not to check.)
That's right.
We played it safe.
(They already had the prize.)
- We had enough. - Team Asia...
(After the first customs declaration process)
will receive four dollars...
(Team Asia: 240 dollars)
which brings its total to 240 dollars.
(Team Customs: 160 dollars)
Team Customs won 60 dollars which brings its total...
- to 160 dollars. - 160 dollars.
(Team America: 260 dollars, currently in the lead)
Team America has 260 dollars.
- Let's move on to the next mission. - Sure!
(They pay their taxes and head to the second mission.)
It wasn't enough for us to take a chance.
Are we supposed to untie these?
(What are all these tangled ropes for?)
- I'm intrigued. - This is the second mission.
Why don't you explain the rules?
Sorry?
Chief Ji will take command for once.
(Chief Ji gets an opportunity.)
- But I'm clueless. - Finally.
(Confessing)
- Chief Ji? - Chief Ji?
(Chief Ji doesn't know the rules.)
Chief Ji doesn't know the rules.
- He doesn't know the rules. - Let me see.
(He barely starts explaining while holding his cue cards.)
Two from each team will compete.
- Two? - Yes.
(He doubts it at first.)
After fastening your hands tight,
(Chief Ji's explanation makes the game more difficult.)
you'll be looking for the rope with the R sticker.
The rope you choose...
That's the sound of him giving up.
No one told me the rules.
- Got it. - This is new to him.
(Chief Ji's explanation ends after causing confusion.)
Can you explain the rules instead?
Do you see these?
(The director steps in after all.)
You will put these on your wrists.
(2 members of each team will play.)
- On both wrists? - Yes.
(They choose one of the ropes and untangle it...)
There will be a space between them.
You will then choose one rope...
(to get to the finish line. The first team to get there wins.)
and keep pulling until you reach the end.
- Gosh. - Because they're all tangled.
(The director is good, indeed.)
No way.
He sure is different, isn't he?
(They can feel the gap between the section chief and the director.)
- It's easy to understand. - It sure is.
That's because Suk Jin is too much of an oldie.
Suk Jin's still in the process of learning.
(His training never ends.)
Shouldn't it be over by now?
(Chief Ji has been an intern for 10 years.)
- It's taking too long. - He's still an intern.
He dreams of being a show host one day.
You can learn something from this moment.
(Ji Suk Jin, a student with a late education)
This is why you must always listen.
I wasn't able to because of my trip to the restroom.
(After his excuses,)
I see.
(the second mission begins!)
Will two from each team please step forward?
Ailee, who do people say you resemble?
- Actress Kim Min Sun. - Right.
And Madam Hwang.
(While talking about Ailee's look-alikes...)
Yes, I know who that is.
(Gently)
Thank you in advance.
(Secretly)
Was that a dollar?
(Lobbyist Jeon's bribes approach the two hosts.)
Thank you in advance.
What...
(Money is given discreetly.)
Our team would appreciate the win.
- How much did she give you? - A dollar.
(He sees what's going on.)
(It's to get on your good side.)
(Of course.)
- Seriously. - Got it.
- It's our money, right? - Right.
(Mr. Ji makes sure he's a part of the cut.)
The other team...
- We were given a dollar. - They gave us a dollar.
I don't know. It just came our way.
(Calm)
- Kwang Soo... - Kwang Soo,
(Team Asia hears about Team America's bribe.)
is it okay with the other team giving us some money?
What don't you come over here?
(The corrupted agent, Chief Ji, asks for a bribe explicitly.)
- What? Who gave you what? - Come over here.
We're just telling you what happened.
- A dollar... - We were given a dollar.
- What... - The other team gave them a dollar.
(So Min...)
- What? - It was to bribe them...
- Why bother though? - The customs agents...
(His true intention)
We'll reconsider if you give us two dollars.
- If you think about it... - The yellow one seems better.
(Cheap Kwang Soo flatly refuses it.)
- There's no use. - Okay, let's play the game then.
Fine, go ahead.
(Embarrassed)
(Would the lobbying have made a difference?)
The yellow one seems better since it stands out.
- All right. - The ladies will go first.
(The finish line)
Good luck!
(The first match, women's event)
- Get ready. - You've got this.
- You can do this! - So Min took off her shoes.
(He's already being unfair.)
But I'll still probably be the worst.
- They could get stomped on. - Ready, get set...
(The lobbyist is barefooted to show her eagerness.)
(Start!)
Good job.
- Ailee is fast. - You have to go into the knot.
- You don't have to be in a rush. - You can move slowly here.
You have to untangle it.
- Do it slowly. - Go inside. Go in between it.
(They all enter the intertwined section.)
Go slowly.
- It's so tangled. - So Min, that's not right.
- That's right. - You have to go inside.
- Go in. That's right. - Hey!
You have to go inside the knot.
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo goes into the knot.)
This is so heavy.
(She only goes after the yellow rope.)
Ji Hyo, show us your skills.
She's calm. Ji Hyo's calm.
- Look at Ailee. - You have to push.
Ji Hyo isn't even making a sound.
Ailee, you need to go inside.
(She struggling in silence amid younger girls.)
- You have to go inside. - Look at So Min.
- You have to go inside. - Where is So Min going?
(Where's So Min headed?)
- Where are you going, So Min? - Hey, So Min!
- I can't go in for mine. - Look at So Min.
(Going in)
You have to go inside.
- Where are you going, So Min? - Hey, So Min!
(So Min's head)
So Min.
Why are you putting her on your shoulders?
(So Min stopped Ji Hyo's silent advance.)
I have to go in.
Move. I have to go in.
What is this?
Hey, So Min...
(They're shocked at the tiger moth bulldozer who only moves forward.)
What is she doing?
What's wrong with her?
- What's wrong with her? - Hey.
- So Min. - I have to go in.
I have to go in this way.
We have to go in together.
Please!
Ailee is strong.
(Working hard)
- Ailee... - Look at Ailee.
(Ailee shows off her strength.)
- Ailee is strong. - She's really strong.
Ji Hyo is also...
- Hold on! - Ji Hyo is also...
(Pushing)
(Falling)
Good job, Ailee!
- Look at Ailee. - You have to push.
You guys are so mean!
(Ailee unties the knot with unusual power.)
- Ailee is good. - Keep going, Ailee!
- The blue one. - Where?
(Ailee moves forward with her Korean-American power.)
Ailee is done!
I'm okay.
I don't care. I just need to get in.
- What are you saying, So Min? - Are you doing okay?
(She's still trying to go in.)
I thought she was done!
Why are you just going in?
- What is she doing? - What are you doing?
(She entangles herself.)
- What is she doing? - You can't go in like that.
- I have to go in. - What is she doing?
Why do you keep locking yourself in?
Ji Hyo, tie So Min up.
- I have to go in. - What?
So Min acts like she's good, but she's really bad at it.
She acts like she's good,
- but she's really bad. - Hold on!
- Ailee is good. - What's the point if she's good?
(She's really bad at it.)
- So Min needs to come out to win. - Ailee.
Ji Hyo, this is a game that we can't lose.
She's pretty much at the starting point still.
(Thanks to struggling tiger month,)
(Team Asia is at an advantage.)
- Where... - We can't lose even if we want to.
You can go slowly.
(Yiren is close to untying the knot.)
You just need to go in and come out.
Ailee is almost out.
(Keep going, Ailee!)
- She's finally out. - Look at Ailee.
(Ailee squeezes out the last of her energy.)
You need to move faster!
(Yiren is almost out too.)
- She's finally out. - Look at Ailee.
You need to move faster!
(Rolling)
Hey.
Ailee.
You have to keep going.
Look at Ailee.
Why did you roll all of a sudden?
Take your leg out.
(She rolled forward out of nowhere while trying to avoid Ailee.)
Gosh, I'm so tired.
This is...
Just take it out like this.
Take this part out.
(Come out.)
- Hold on. - She's on your team, So Min.
Ailee is on your team.
Go in now.
- No! - You're there!
(Despite the tiger moth's attack on her own team,)
- No! - Yes!
(Ailee escapes first.)
- Ailee's out. - She's done.
Ailee's done.
Ailee's in first place.
Ailee is amazing.
- You guys just need to come out. - I'm so tired!
- This is incredible! - She's out.
(Yiren from Team Asia arrives next.)
- Hey! - Come on!
Even though Ailee got out, we can't lose.
What's going on?
Yiren can't go in.
(It's now between Ji Hyo and So Min.)
So Min, what are you doing?
Hey, So Min!
It's So Min versus Ji Hyo.
- What is she doing? - So Min!
Don't let her go.
(Who will win?)
You got it. Just go forward.
- So Min. You got it. - Stop!
You just need to go under the gray. Then you're done.
(He gets excited.)
You're done.
(She does her best to crawl out.)
Then you're done. You're done.
Don't worry about her.
(He's not a hooligan.)
- Hey! - Come on!
You're so cool!
(Ji Hyo has one last knot.)
(So Min arrives.)
This was exhausting.
(Team America wins as the 2 finishes first.)
You were almost to the end.
You are able to escape it.
You guys were great.
(The customs agents are happy for them.)
Let's give them a round of applause.
What kind of game is this?
This is a great cardio exercise.
(In Round 2, Team Asia just enjoyed the cardio and lost.)
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
(Team America takes the final win!)
Kwang Soo, that wasn't right.
It wasn't going to work. It all tangled here.
(Covered in sweat)
We lost.
This was funny.
(Team America wins 20 dollars.)
Team America has won this round too.
- Team America. - We lost everything.
- Captain America. - Team Asia keeps losing.
- I know. - What's going on?
(The 2nd customs declaration process is coming.)
This fight was... Gosh.
(Team Asia will start off...)
(the 2nd customs declaration process because they lost...)
I think they're going to check ours this time.
- I agree. They'll check ours. - Right?
They will.
Did 60 and 80 dollars get taken out? Or...
(Team America is getting ready...)
One of each was taken out,
(after losing to Team Asia during the 1st round.)
- but there's one of each left. - One of each is left?
Chief Ji, we have to be organized.
We have to go with our gut, not be organized.
- We have to be organized. - It's not our first day on the job.
We have to go with how we feel, our gut.
They're here.
(Will they be able to catch them?)
- How much did you make? - How much did you make?
We picked 80 dollars.
- 80 dollars? - Yes.
Then they're telling the truth.
(They pay 40 dollars as tax arguing they picked 80 dollars.)
- They must be telling the truth. - They could be.
We really got 80 dollars.
(Startled)
We got 80, so we need to give them 40.
- Right. - It's better not to check..
(They already paid 40 dollars.)
- Yiren. - Yes?
(A sudden attack)
How much did you get?
80 dollars.
(Stiff)
- She practiced this time. - Her smile...
Her smile is awkward.
- I always smile like this. - Her smile was always awkward.
She can't smile widely.
Yiren got some training in there.
- That's right. - Mental training.
Why are you all standing with your hands together?
(Team Asia is very quiet compared to the 1st round.)
"Mental training".
Did you commit a crime?
- You're right. - Hey.
Hold on. Let's calculate.
- You're calculating something? - Hold on.
(Do you need to calculate?)
- You're calculating? - What's going on?
Please take a step to the side.
We analyze charts here.
(Serious)
You haven't gotten anything right until now.
He majored in Statistics.
(Director Yoo studied Statistics as his major.)
- Look. We have to consider this. - Okay.
That is...
- Explain it to me. - They gave us 40 and 20 dollars.
(Putting his arms around)
I'm the director. You should take your hand off me.
My gosh. Just do it, you punk. You're a junior...
- from my neighborhood. - This is a bit...
Before you became my director, you were my junior.
(Chief Ji is all about personal relationships.)
You guys are at work. You're working right now.
(You ought to draw a line between professional and personal lives.)
You can't do this at work.
I can rest my arm if it feels heavy.
(He doesn't understand.)
- Even still. - Continue.
You shouldn't do this.
(He isn't too smart but he's kind-hearted.)
Take a look.
When it's 50-50,
they wouldn't give us 40 dollars...
(Analyzing probabilities)
if they got 40 or 20 dollars.
- Right. - Do you understand?
We have to be realistic and think that they got 80 or 100 dollars.
(They paid 40 dollars in tax.)
- Right. - Right.
We have to be realistic and think that they got 80 or 100 dollars.
- Isn't that obvious? - That's obvious.
Why are you saying the obvious?
(It's so shocking as the calculations were too obvious.)
Why bother analyzing the charts then?
- Why bother? That's obvious. - My gosh.
- Those are the rules. - That's... It could be 100.
I'm telling you the probability because of this.
(Stubborn)
He's saying the same thing again.
- Why are you repeating yourself? - Why are you doing that?
(That's enough.)
You said the same thing four times.
At least change your tone of voice.
Did you major in Statistics?
No.
If you didn't, why are you speaking?
- Did you major in Statistics? - If not, why are you speaking?
(You'll be immediately punished for the obstruction of justice.)
He didn't either.
Okay.
Ji Hyo is smiling so comfortably.
I'll ask you once again. How much did you bring?
- 80 dollars. - Stop lying!
Stop lying!
- What are you doing? - How dare you...
(Feeling wrongly accused)
- How dare you lie to me? - How can...
What's wrong with this customs agent?
How dare you lie to me?
- Should we open it? - Should we open it or not?
(Losing his temper)
Should we open it? Are you smiling?
- Are you smiling? - Are you smiling?
(The customs agents have an inferiority complex.)
- Are you smiling? - Do we look funny to you?
(They are losing temper as they exploit their power.)
- Are you smiling? - Should we open it or not?
Don't be like this and just ask Jong Kook.
Jong Kook will tell you what to do.
(It's probably better to just ask questions.)
Come here.
- Let's just go with our gut. - Okay.
(Let's go with our gut.)
- Let's do this. - Even if they lied...
- Let's mark it, - Right.
- If it falls. - and if it falls this way...
(You'll rely on your gut?)
- Let's do it. - If it falls, you can pass.
If you were going to do this, why did you talk about statistics?
We did this often back in the day.
- Back in the day. - It was "Go clubbing or go home."
(It's a very traditional decision method with years of history.)
We did this to decide whether or not to go clubbing.
This is it.
(If the marked side comes up, they'll check.)
If this side comes up we'll check,
and if this side comes up, they can pass.
(If not, they'll pass.)
Ready, start.
(The last method chosen by the two customs agents)
(Will they inspect Team Asia, or will they let them go?)
- We have to let them pass. - It's best 2 out of 3.
- In the end... - What was the point of this then?
Just decide.
(They really want to inspect.)
- We should do it again. - What are you doing?
- Hey. - We did this back then too.
- They've already decided. - One more time.
- They've already decided. - They've already decided.
(The result of the second round is also pass.)
They're both curious.
I'm so curious.
- One more time. - One more time.
- You said 2 out of three. - It's until it's what they want.
(They'll repeat until they get the result they want.)
We did this when we wanted to go clubbing.
Hold on.
(It continues to tell them to pass.)
- The same answer keeps coming out. - This is weird.
Just open it then!
Open it!
If you're going to open it anyway, why are you doing this?
(Are they going to inspect the boxes against the result?)
- Okay. - Did you...
see their faces?
You should've studied their faces.
When you said you would open it,
(When they proposed for inspection,)
Ji Hyo smiled.
(Ji Hyo smiled?)
- Really? - Yes, she did.
- Then let's not open it. - Let's not open it.
- We're not opening it. - I can't...
stand to see them smile.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo's smile, Team Asia passes through Customs.)
- They're not opening it, right? - They decided against it.
They decided not to open it, and the other team can go now.
(Team America moves to pick the box.)
(Did Team Asia win with a psychological strategy?)
- Goodness. - There was a low probability.
- You're right. - There was a low probability.
(It's too late now.)
- We have to consider probability. - Right.
It wasn't likely.
What are they doing?
(We're so excited!)
(No way.)
Did you do all of that to get 10 dollars?
(Is this a ceremony for successfully evading taxes?)
Okay.
(Did they fail to catch the tax evasion by Team Asia?)
Did you do all of that to get 10 dollars?
- We kept a good poker face. - You're right.
They're coming out.
(It's Team America's turn for the customs declaration process.)
You have to check their faces.
Their aura is...
(Nervous)
Did you choose well?
We picked 80 dollars,
so we will give you 40.
(Did they pick 80 dollars too?)
This is the most confusing number.
The most confusing number...
(It's an infinite loop of 80 dollars.)
is 40 dollars. 80 dollars and 40 dollars.
- This is... - This declaration...
- Hold on. - This is for real.
(Pleased)
- 80 dollars is... - No.
- No, it's... - You each chose this?
Didn't you choose 80 dollars before and give us 40?
(During the 1st customs inspection)
- No. - One of us is lying.
They chose the last remaining 80 dollars?
(Excited)
In the previous round.
- We're telling you the truth. - We are.
Was there another 80 dollars left?
(20 dollars, 40 dollars, 60 dollars, 80 dollars, 100 dollars)
There were 2 boxes each for 20, 40, 60, 80, 100 dollars.
(There are 2 boxes for each amount.)
- There are 2 of each. - There are 2 of each.
- There were 10. - If they're telling the truth,
(If Team America told the truth,)
that means we had 100 dollars.
(Team Asia's 80 dollars was a lie.)
- Or... - What?
Or maybe they're trying to trick us because they have...
(They won prizes twice in a row.)
- plenty of money. - No.
He's so funny.
(Getting suspicious)
If they got a small amount of money, would they...
Is there a problem if we paid a lot...
- when we chose a small amount? - Out of the 10...
- What if we win like that? - What?
(Flustered)
- What if we pay a lot of taxes... - It's the same thing.
(He think's in reverse.)
even though we chose a small amount?
We only know about our duties as customs agents.
Right. That's why I'm asking.
- It's not that. - Stay quiet.
(We don't accept additional questions.)
- Don't say anything. - What's wrong with that?
- What will happen? - Would we pay 40...
- when we chose 40? - What if we chose a small amount...
- I'm the one in charge, so... - Okay.
(This is the end of Chief Ji's duties.)
You said we paid a lot despite choosing a small amount.
Look. We chose 40 dollars,
(He's stating the obvious.)
but we paid 40 dollars. How would that benefit us?
We have to catch someone.
We haven't caught anyone in 30 years.
They are too timid.
(Laughing)
Let's go. Let's decide by this method.
(When they don't have a clue,)
(they go with the traditional way.)
- Let's go. - There they go again.
- There they go again. - What was the point of analysis?
(Why did they even analyze?)
- We will decide by this method. - They are too unprofessional.
Bring it here.
(The statisticians are desperate to check.)
I want to check the boxes.
- If we check... - It's the result we wanted.
(The slip finally allows them to check the boxes.)
- We will open the boxes. - Okay.
(Team America will check.)
Both captains will open the boxes.
(Team Asia, pass. Team America, check.)
- Kwang Soo, go first. - Okay.
Say it out loud in a cool way.
We paid up 40 dollars. The amount we had gotten was...
(Team Asia got 80 dollars and paid 40 dollars.)
(The customs agents didn't check...)
(40 dollar tax on 80 dollars.)
We paid up 40 dollars.
The amount we had gotten was...
- 100 dollars. - Come on!
(Their strategy succeeded.)
(Team Asia got a box containing 100 dollars.)
For goodness' sake.
(Team Asia was supposed to pay 50 dollars for tax.)
I said we should check.
Let's spin.
(They won 10 dollars by paying 40 dollars in tax!)
(Team Customs couldn't stop tax evasion again.)
- Yes! - Yes!
- Okay. - We did it.
(Calm down.)
- There is one more box to check. - Okay.
Jong Kook, open the box.
As for us,
- we got 80 dollars twice in a row. - Really?
Stop it!
(Team America gets their box checked...)
- We got 80 dollars twice in a row. - Really?
Stop it!
(for saying they picked 80 dollars.)
Did you really get 80 dollars?
- Stop it. - We actually didn't get 80 dollars.
- What? - Did they get 100 dollars?
(They finally succeed to catch the tax evaders.)
- So what's the result? - We are leading.
- Are we leading? - We did it after 30 years.
(The first catch in their 30 years in customs)
- We finally caught them. - We caught them.
(They caught Team America evading tax.)
(They have to pay Team Customs 100 dollars in full.)
- We did it to be funny. - That's right.
(Pretending to be okay)
- We knew this would happen. - We did it to be funny.
We did it to be funny.
- We caught the tax evaders. - They suddenly moved up.
(The statistician finally succeeded with their traditional way.)
Now, the teams are neck-and-neck.
They did a good job.
- Team Customs has 310 dollars. - Really?
(Team Customs has 310 dollars.)
Kwang Soo's Team Asia has 300 dollars.
(Team Asia has 300 dollars.)
Team America has 270 dollars.
(Team America has 270 dollars.)
- My goodness. - It's okay.
- We are at number one. - It's not too bad.
(Team America will likely receive the punishment.)
- We are at number 1. - It's a difference of 10 dollars.
(What will be the result of the final race?)
We can do it.
(2nd customs time)
Let's move for the final mission.
(Team Asia, Team Customs, Team America)
- Yes. - Okay!
(The final race will take place in a mall in Suwon.)
This place is incredible.
- Is it an amusement park? - This is incredible.
(The last mission will take place...)
When else would we visit a place like this?
(in the place full of interesting rides.)
This is what Running Man is about.
What... What is that?
(He spots something.)
- What? What is that? - What is that?
- What is that? - What is that?
It's Kwang Soo.
(The strange-looking thing is Kwang Soo.)
Hey.
I was so startled.
- There are so many strange things. - Right?
- How fascinating! - What is that?
(Enjoying)
Is that his back hair?
- Hold on. - What is that?
(Wait. Is that back of his hair?)
- Is that his back hair? - What is that?
Wasn't he wearing a wig?
(It's real hair.)
- It's his real hair. - Really?
- It's his real hair. - I don't know what to do with them.
(What should I do with them?)
- They are so annoying. - There are so many strange things.
(Hesitating)
If we go on, he will hit us. We need to stop.
(They'll work on their final mission in this interesting place.)
- Everyone. - Yes?
It's time for the final race.
The final race is called the Fiery Trade War.
(The Fiery Trade War)
All three teams including Team Customs...
will participate in this Name Tag Elimination.
Each team will wait at their respective headquarters.
(Each team will wait at their respective headquarters.)
Two people from each team will enter the race...
(2 people from each team will...)
and participate in Name Tag Elimination.
(participate in Name Tag Elimination first.)
Thus, it will be 2-on-2-on-2.
When one member gets eliminated, another one will enter the race.
(When one member gets eliminated, another one will enter the race.)
(The rankings will be determined by the order of total elimination.)
Since Team Customs doesn't have enough members,
(The members of Team Customs can be resurrected once.)
Jae Suk and Suk Jin will have two lives each.
Throughout the set,
(There are also chance cards.)
you will find slips that are the size of your palm.
(Trade blockade cards are hidden in various places.)
They are the trade blockade cards.
(Trade blockade card)
You can cover one-fourth of a certain member's name tag...
(Every time you find a trade blockade card,)
(you can cover one-fourth of a certain member's name tag.)
if you find one.
That's important.
That means up to three fourth of the adhesive can be covered.
(Up to 3 of the adhesive can be covered per person.)
(The more it's covered, the easier it is to rip the name tag off.)
That would be helpful.
In accordance with the rankings,
(50 dollars for 1st place, 30 dollars for 2nd place)
the teams will get 50, 30, or 10 dollars respectively.
(10 dollars for 3rd place)
We will also give you 10 dollars for every name tag you remove.
(10 dollars will be given for every name tag removed.)
- The name tags you remove. - So it's an individual game.
- No, no. It's a team game. - I see.
Don't be like that.
(What's wrong with the captain?)
He wants to betray us.
(Captain Lee worries about how to survive alone.)
- Seriously. - No, no. I am sorry.
- He wants to be on his own. - No, no.
(Captain Lee has never had teamwork in his life.)
- I am sorry. It's not like that. - He always has that wish.
(Habitual betrayal obsession)
Please move to your headquarters.
(They move to their headquarters.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
Let's discuss things once we get there.
- We are at a disadvantage. - Strangely, I think we will win.
We are at a disadvantage.
(We are at a disadvantage.)
Life is all about overcoming the disadvantages.
(Gibberish)
We can't win against five people.
Why can't we do that?
(Ji Suk Jin, So Min's rival)
There will only be two people from each team.
(Chief Ji's groundless confidence makes Director Yu's face gloomy.)
- That's right. - But other members are in the race.
(Other members are in the race.)
We are in the race too.
For goodness' sake.
(We're barely in.)
Why would you be so timid when we are in the race too?
I will rip off the female members' name tags.
(Shameless)
(He makes up his mind to attack the younger women.)
Three teams are entering, right?
(Meanwhile, Team America is having a strategy meeting.)
It would be best...
(The weak member should participate first...)
to keep the other teams wondering...
(and form an alliance with the other team.)
if they should form an alliance.
(If Jong Kook participates first, the other two teams will team up.)
If I enter the race first, the other two teams will team up.
(Therefore, Jong Kook will participate in the end.)
- That's right. - Let's not focus on...
- placing first. - Okay.
- Let's just avoid placing last. - That's good.
(Unless they place last in this race,)
The penalty involves staying behind for an additional shoot.
(Team Asia doesn't have to worry about the punishment.)
- It's the worst. - Really?
(Their strategy is to place 2nd as they're weak.)
"Let's place second."
- All right. - Okay.
- Let's place 2nd. - Let's place 2nd.
Okay.
(The order of participation for each team)
The race starts.
(Team Customs, Team Asia, Team America)
(Team Customs begins to move.)
There must be a card here.
(They look for the trade blockade cards.)
(They find a trade blockade card on the wall.)
It's on the wall.
Suk Jin, go get it.
(Chief Ji attempts to get the card.)
- How do I do this? - Give it a try.
(Floundering)
My goodness.
- My goodness. - I can't believe him.
(Chief Ji keeps floundering when they're in a rush.)
Hey.
- What is up with this? - Are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
(Jumping)
Why... Why can't you do it?
- It's working. - Give it a try.
Give it a try.
(He makes a fuss as if someone is hindering him.)
(Chief Ji continues to fight against himself.)
My goodness.
What was that?
Move. Hold tight. I will do it.
(Jae Suk decides to try it himself.)
- Hey. - Move out of the way.
(Chief Ji is panting.)
- Do you think you can do it? - Of course.
(Confident)
- Hey. - You shouldn't jump there!
Do you think you can do it?
(He disrupts the rhythm.)
Of course.
- Hey. - You shouldn't jump there!
- I jumped because you did. - Wait over there.
(Chief Ji makes Jae Suk nag for various reasons.)
Can you do it?
(After shooing away Suk Jin, he resumes jumping.)
(He catches it.)
(They finally get the first trade blockade card.)
Jong Kook. Kim Jong Kook.
(They block Jong Kook with it obviously.)
You can cover one-fourth of a certain member's name tag...
(One-fourth of Jong Kook's name tag gets covered.)
I wish someone would do that to me.
(She's jealous of containment.)
I wish someone would think that I am formidable.
It's okay. I will make sure people don't touch my name tag.
(Team Customs continues to search for trade blockade cards.)
- It should be here somewhere. - It must be on the wall.
Do you see it?
It's over there.
(They find another trade blockade card.)
Go up there. I will be on the lookout.
For goodness' sake.
(Chief Ji avoids all hassle with his experience.)
Go up there.
The lookout duty is important.
It's quite hard to go up the climbing wall.
I can't do it. Ji Jin Hee is good at it.
Why are you talking about Ji Jin Hee so suddenly?
(He brags about the Jis.)
Ji Jin Hee is an expert.
(Jae Suk begins to climb up.)
I will support you.
Let go.
(There are two team members,)
(but Jae Suk seems to be doing all the hard work.)
You got it. You are good.
(Suk Jin cheers him on soullessly.)
- That's good. - Okay.
(He got the trade blockade card.)
All right. Let's use it on Kwang Soo.
(They cover a portion of Kwang Soo's name tag.)
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, someone used a trade blockade card on you.
- Me? - Okay, okay.
Why did they use it on me instead of Jong Kook?
(Meanwhile, the next participants should get ready.)
You should go in there and rip off their name tags.
You should do it.
I have never gotten my name tag ripped off.
I don't know the taste of it.
- The taste. - I don't know it.
(Kangnam doesn't know the fun of ripping off the name tag.)
- Thus, you should do it. - It's a bit sweet.
It's tasty.
Listen.
(While the three are talking,)
Kwang Soo.
Okay, okay.
Two more trade blockade cards have been used on you.
- Two? - It's over.
(two more trade blockade cards are added.)
It's over. You should go in there last.
(Three parts of his name tag get covered.)
It's over.
- It will come off so easily. - This is just wrong.
Do you know what's fascinating?
For the first time, I can see the name tag on my back.
(This is what my name tag looks like.)
I can see the name tag on my back.
It's the 1st time in 10 years.
- Hold on. - Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk keeps getting attacked by the trade blockade cards.)
- Who used another card on me? - Again?
What is going on?
Three cards have been used on Jae Suk.
(Ji Hyo and Yiren block 3 parts of Jae Suk's name tag.)
Finish him off.
Eliminate Jae Suk first.
What should I do? Why is everyone attacking me?
(As 3 parts are blocked, the name tag is barely hanging.)
It will come off if I flick it.
Suk Jin, come here. We should look for more cards.
(Jae Suk received a concentrated attack.)
(They hurriedly try to find more trade blockade cards.)
This is bad.
- Where is Suk Jin? - He is here.
(Haha and Ailee approach.)
Word on the street is that your name tag is about to come off.
(Team America's target is Jae Suk with the flimsy name tag.)
(Seizing each other up)
- Let's go. - Go on your way.
(At that moment)
- We will go on our way too. - Go ahead.
I will rip off...
the female members' name tags.
(Chief Ji gets to work.)
I will rip off the female members' name tags.
(Team Customs makes a sudden attack.)
Hold on.
Go, go! That's right!
(Excited)
Haha! Haha got caught!
- Who caught them? - Both of them got caught.
(Two teams' tight match)
- Suk Jin and Jae Suk. - He is out. Oh, he isn't out yet.
(The flow in the beginning matters in Name Tag Elimination.)
This is good.
Go downstairs.
Ji Hyo and Yiren, go downstairs.
(While two teams are fighting,)
Go downstairs. Ji Hyo and Yiren, go downstairs.
(Ji Hyo and Yiren try to attack them from behind.)
Suk Jin, Ji Hyo is coming!
Ji Hyo.
(It suddenly becomes a 3-way match.)
Hold on.
- Rip it off! - Rip it off!
(At that moment,)
(Ji Hyo reaches for Jae Suk's flimsy name tag.)
(He barely survived.)
Be careful.
Be careful!
- Rip it off! - No!
(At that moment,)
Be careful!
- Rip it off! - No!
(Haha spots a chance.)
(Ji Hyo is out.)
(Haha ripped off her name tag while she was attacking Jae Suk.)
Ji Hyo is out.
(My goodness.)
Let's go. Kangnam, get ready.
(It's the next participant's turn.)
- Another member will enter. - Kangnam, go.
(Ji Hyo is out. Kangnam is in.)
- Kangnam, hang in there. - Get Jae Suk.
(Kangnam enters the battlefield with a heavy burden.)
Be careful because Haha could backstab you.
Where is Yiren?
- That's good. - Our team is doing well.
(Haha and Ailee did a nice job.)
Haha got one.
Haha.
Hold on.
(Everyone is confused by the change of members.)
(Suk Jin attacks Ailee for the 2nd time.)
What? Jae Suk!
(It's time for Suk Jin to do his job!)
- What? - Jae Suk!
All right, all right. Stop.
(Is she grabbing him by his collar?)
- All right, all right. Stop. - Haha.
(Ailee takes on Suk Jin with one hand.)
Jae Suk!
- All right, all right. Stop. - Haha.
(While Suk Jin is restricting Ailee,)
Come on. Okay.
(Team Customs takes on Haha.)
- Hold on. - Rip off his name tag!
(Then Kangnam shows up.)
- Rip off his name tag! - Hey, hey.
- Get Jae Suk. - Rip off his name tag.
(Yiren and Ailee join.)
- Get Jae Suk. - We got Haha.
(There is a balance.)
Get Jae Suk.
(Yiren attacks from behind.)
(Ripping)
(What? Did Yiren get Suk Jin?)
- What was that? - Okay!
(While Chief Ji flounders,)
(Yiren's quick and well-aimed attack was successful.)
Okay!
(Yiren beats a member with 10 years of experience.)
Yiren, rip it off! Nice!
- Rip it off! - Good job, Yiren.
(Thanks to Yiren's performance,)
Good job, Yiren.
(Team Asia gets 10 dollars and Suk Jin loses 1 life.)
(She got Suk Jin's easy name tag.)
Yiren.
Suk Jin, you need to enter the headquarters for a second.
I can't believe him.
I just...
(He tried to take on Ailee and failed.)
Why did you do something so useless?
- Let's get Jae Suk. - I am sorry.
(Haha suggests to eliminate Jae Suk.)
Let's get Jae Suk. I am serious.
(They suddenly build Overthrow Team Customs alliance.)
- Let's get Jae Suk. - I promise.
- I am serious. I promise. - Okay, okay.
(As long as we place 2nd, it's a deal.)
I promise.
(However,)
Okay!
(he pretended to shake her hand and attacked her!)
Haha, you are a piece of trash!
(Haha eliminates Yiren with extreme speed.)
Seriously.
(I knew Haha would do that.)
That little...
I can't believe him!
(The bitter taste of betrayal)
Haha! I can't believe you!
- You bully! - This is...
(Feeling betrayed)
This is how it is.
(The ecosystem of Running Man is brutal.)
This is just ridiculous.
He ripped off Yiren's name tag. Yiren is out.
(He's watching Name Tag Elimination from the VIP seat.)
- All right. - Okay.
- That's good. - Hold on.
(It's fun for the audience.)
What are they doing?
(The audience is more excited than the players.)
- They need to take out Kangnam. - Right this instant,
- they need to take out Kangnam. - That's right.
(Jae Suk got eliminated once. Ji Hyo and Yiren are out.)
I am disappointed.
(Everyone in Team America survives.)
"I am disappointed."
They need to get him no matter what.
Let's go. Let's rip off Kangnam's name tag.
- Kangnam. He is alone. - Let's get him while he is alone.
(They choose Kangnam who is alone as their target.)
I need to run away.
(He runs away.)
(They begin to chase after him.)
(Kangnam runs as far as he can.)
It's a dead-end.
Kangnam, don't overexert yourself.
(Kangnam is cornered.)
It's a dead-end.
Kangnam, don't overexert yourself.
(What should I do now?)
- You can push me and run away. - What?
- Gosh. - I have a suggestion.
(Haha makes a suggestion to Kangnam who is in a dead end.)
Let's rip off Jae Suk's name tag.
Let's team up...
(He suggests an alliance between Team America and Team Asia.)
- and rip off Jae Suk's name tag. - Do you mean it?
- Do you mean it? - Yes.
(It's real this time.)
- Copy. Okay. - Do you mean it?
(Will this alliance last long?)
- It's done. - He's over there.
- Do you promise? - We put a stamp.
- It's real. - So it's real.
(At that moment)
What? What?
So it's real. What? What?
(Se Chan attempts to make a surprise attack.)
(The alliance breaks down in 5 seconds.)
Come here! We need to be together.
Rip off Ailee's name tag.
Come on up.
(Two teams met in a dead end.)
Come on up. Hurry.
(Confronting)
Go, go, go. There you go. Haha!
(He is super excited.)
(Se Chan's cornered. Kangnam tries to take his chance.)
Hold on. I got her.
I got him!
(Ailee uses her super saiyan mode.)
Ailee is too strong!
(Haha and Kangnam has a 1-on-1 match.)
Haha!
(They grab each other's name tag at the same time.)
(Who will rip off the name tag first?)
(Haha ripped it off first!)
I ripped it off!
(After Ji Hyo and Yiren, Kangnam is out!)
I ripped it off first!
Haha, my name tag is about to come off!
(Ailee is subduing Se Chan.)
- Hold on. - Haha.
(I am sorry that I couldn't save you.)
(Trapping)
(A seatbelt to elimination)
It's too dangerous. It's too dangerous. Hold on.
(We'll make your elimination easy.)
(Let's just go. It will be hard to place 2nd.)
His name tag is barely hanging on.
(Due to trade blockade card)
Leave, you punk.
(Se Chan is out.)
Good work.
(Haha and Ailee are invincible.)
Ailee is doing all the work today.
(They're having a mental breakdown like their ragged name tags.)
She is so strong.
(Ailee)
(Kangnam and Se Chan are out.)
- Kwang Soo, I am sorry. - Did he get eliminated?
(Oh, my goodness.)
- Did he get eliminated already? - He did.
Kwang Soo, you are the only one left.
(Kwang Soo is only one left.)
- They should have waited. - But...
(His name tag is about to come off.)
Am I the only one left?
(He can't believe it.)
(They walk proudly.)
Ailee, look at the camera.
(He found the camera.)
(Full of confidence)
Haha took out Se Chan as well.
- What is up with Haha today? - Today,
(That's awesome.)
we might just win.
(The invincible duo's ceremony)
Ailee!
- Team America! - Yes!
(Team America is leading by a big margin.)
- Se Chan and Kangnam are out. - Are both of them out?
(Team Customs heard Team Asia's elimination.)
- In this situation, - What should we do?
we need to take out the weak team. You know what I mean, right?
- That way, we will place second. - That's right.
We have no choice.
(Let's place 2nd to avoid the penalty.)
- You know what I mean, right? - Yes.
We don't need to team up with the weak team.
When I am with Ailee, I have no fear.
(Feeling confident)
She isn't the type to get scared.
Ailee is too scary.
(Suk Jin is scared.)
(Kwang Soo heads over to the teams.)
Where are they? Where are they?
- Hold on. - How is it going to be?
(Three teams confront each other.)
Shall we get rid of him?
(Team Customs's target is...)
Firstly...
You will attack us, right?
- We will attack Kwang Soo. - Me?
(Their strategy is to place 2nd.)
I want to have another member enter the race.
(Running away)
- Kwang Soo. - Hurry up.
- Let's hurry up and take him out. - All right. Let's go.
(They chase Kwang Soo.)
(They attack Suk Jin instead.)
Hey, hey!
- Let's hurry up and take him out. - All right.
- Let's go. - Hey, hey!
(The invincible duo goes after Suk Jin.)
- Hey! - Jae Suk!
(He quickly comes back.)
My goodness.
(If he gets eliminated again, he will be out for good.)
- Hey! - Jae Suk! My goodness.
My goodness.
(Ripping off)
(Ailee ripped off Suk Jin's name tag.)
- For goodness' sake. - Suk Jin is out.
Why did you run off like that?
(Criticizing)
(They have earned 50 dollars so far.)
For goodness' sake.
He doesn't help me in any way.
(Blaming each other)
- For goodness' sake. - He doesn't help me in any way.
(Chief Ji is forced to retire without any performance.)
Didn't you know that they would backstab us?
- Ailee is so funny. - Why did you run off?
(How can she rip that off?)
- You should have taken cover. - I am exhausted.
(Fighting)
I am exhausted.
(The combination of betrayer Haha and strong Ailee)
This is not fun, you guys.
(The viewer at the VIP seat becomes excited.)
- What is it? - What is it?
- They got Suk Jin! - What?
(Showing American reaction)
Our team is the best.
(Awesome)
Haha is really good.
(Haha is good.)
He is good at betraying.
(Haha is good at betraying.)
Kwang Soo, let's place second.
(Kwang Soo runs away diligently.)
I am exhausted. I am exhausted.
(He's going somewhere secretly.)
This is not fun, you guys.
(Careful)
(Kwang Soo aims to make a surprise attack.)
- I am exhausted. - This is not fun, you guys.
(The members don't know what's going on.)
(Will Kwang Soo's surprise attack be successful?)
(Attacking)
(He tries to figure out what's going on.)
For goodness' sake.
(It was the next door.)
(Reality hits him hard.)
I almost messed it up.
My heart is beating so fast.
I just lost my fighting spirit.
(He carefully opens the door and goes outside.)
(They are already gone.)
How many name tags did we remove?
(How many name tags did we remove?)
Ailee, take me out.
It will give us 10 dollars.
(They will also get 10 dollars...)
There are too many members who haven't gone yet.
(for ripping off their own team's name tag.)
(Team America hasn't replaced a single member.)
Take me out.
(Team America gets 10 dollars.)
- Okay. - 10 dollars.
Let's switch.
(With this strategy, they wouldn't give 10 dollars to other teams.)
Take them on with Ailee.
(Joon goes in and Haha goes out.)
Is Haha out? Is Haha out?
(Kwang Soo witnessed it.)
I should have ripped off someone's name tag earlier.
(Haha goes back to the headquarters and Ailee is left alone.)
Joon is waiting. Joon.
(Kwang Soo appears before Ailee.)
(Upon seeing that Ailee was alone,)
(he charges toward her.)
- Hey! Hey! - You need to go now.
(Excited)
- You need to go now. - Do I need to go now?
(The next player Joon sets off.)
Where is the exit? Which way do I go?
(Kwang Soo takes on Ailee.)
(Laughing)
(Kwang Soo attacks with desperation,)
(but Ailee just laughs.)
(Struggling)
(I give up.)
(He runs away without looking back.)
- He is running away. - He is running away.
Ailee is laughing at him.
(I feel bad for Kwang Soo.)
(He realizes that he is no match and runs away at full speed.)
(Relaxed)
Ailee is alone now.
Her arms didn't come off.
(How could she be so strong?)
(He renews his resolution...)
(and tries for the 2nd time.)
Joon, you need to hurry up. Kwang Soo is coming again.
(Joon just got into the elevator.)
(It's a golden opportunity for Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo does his best to remove the name tag.)
The elevator is too slow.
(There's no time.)
(Ailee is losing strength.)
(At that moment,)
(Jae Suk surprises him...)
(and rips off the name tag.)
(While he was focused on Ailee's name tag,)
(Jae Suk attacks like a bolt of lightning.)
Kwang Soo's name tag came off!
(Jae Suk quickly removed his name tag.)
(But the fight has just begun!)
Hey!
(Joon finally arrives and joins in.)
(Jae Suk lays on the ground and holds them off.)
Joon. Pull him up.
(Team Asia is last with Kwang Soo's elimination.)
- Is Kwang Soo's name tag removed? - Yes, it is.
(It seems too hard to hold off a 2-on-1 attack.)
Rip it off.
(He removes her name tag when she lets her guard down.)
- Your name tag has been removed. - Is Ailee out?
(It comes from 10 years of Running Man experience.)
It's okay. It is.
Ailee is out.
(Ailee did a great job, and she's finally out.)
(Until the next member comes out, they can hold out 1 on 1.)
Okay.
(Jae Suk has 3 trade blockade cards on his back.)
(He secured 2nd place,)
(but he must rip off the name tag and get the money to win.)
They're coming!
(The next player)
I'm alone, so...
(He is outnumbered.)
They're coming! Behind you!
(Team America's next player is...)
- It's Jong Kook! - What?
Hey. Get him!
(The game-ender is here.)
Why did you tell him?
(Jae Suk's name tag is hanging by a thread...)
Why did you...
(as he awaits his chance.)
Hold on. Okay.
I got him.
(Jong Kook catches him?)
I got him. Joon.
(When Jong Kook has him and Joon is about to rip his name tag off...)
- Let go. - Rip it off.
(He avoided him.)
Rip it off.
(Jae Suk looks for the opportunity.)
You have to rip it off.
Grab it and rip it off.
(His name tag gets ripped off.)
- Grab it and rip it off. - This is...
(Jae Suk fails to overcome the challenge and gets eliminated.)
Look at this. Who put it on like this?
This is...
One more. Jae Suk has another name tag.
(It'll get ripped off.)
Okay.
(Jae Suk put on his second name tag.)
(He holds onto a bit of hope as he rubs his name tag on the wall.)
I need Suk Jin to be here.
He's over there.
Just come over here.
(Stop wasting time.)
It's not going to be better if you think about it.
(Let's just end this quickly.)
Just come here.
(I have to die after I make at least 10 dollars.)
- I'll tell you one thing. - What is it?
Give up hope.
(Destruction of hope)
I'm sorry, but...
- Wanting a dramatic ending is fine. - But...
Give up hope.
- Be careful. - What do you mean?
(The final moment is approaching.)
My gosh. I got you.
I got you.
(They've played this game hundreds of times before,)
(but he looks quite pathetic today.)
Just come towards the back.
(However)
(Jae Suk isn't the type to end things easily.)
(The risk-taker, Jae Suk, grabs onto Joon's name tag.)
(Whose name tag will be ripped off first?)
Just come towards the back.
That's right. We got it.
(Jae Suk's name tag got ripped off first.)
- We got it. - Just come towards the back.
(There wasn't an unexpected twist.)
That's right. We got it.
Jae Suk, you're out.
(He never gives up.)
I ripped it off first.
We won by a hair.
(Team America won the race.)
Jae Suk.
(You lost, but you fought well.)
(We won!)
He ripped off Joon's name tag too.
What is this? What about me?
(She feels bad that she could've done better.)
What about me?
You're the princess.
What is this?
- Princess. - I'm feeling good today too.
I would've been able to just rip everyone's name tags.
(That's a shame.)
That's too bad.
I was so determined I even changed my pants.
(The race is over.)
First off, Yiren left first...
(Yiren left first due to the showcase.)
- for her comeback showcase. - Right.
After we gave you 10 dollars for every name tag you ripped off...
(Each name tag is worth 10 dollars.)
and 50, 30, and 10 dollars for 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place,
(The amount was calculated based on the result of the race.)
Team Customs, who was in 1st place earlier,
(Team Customs was in 1st place earlier.)
has a total of 360 dollars.
(The final amount is 360 dollars.)
- You have 360 dollars. - We have 360 dollars?
- Yes, you do. - Okay.
And Team Asia, who was in 2nd place,
(Team Asia was ranked 2nd before the race.)
has a total of 320 dollars.
(The final amount is 320 dollars.)
- So we... - We still...
- It's a 40 dollar difference. - Right, 40 dollars.
(What's the final amount for Team America?)
Right. And Team America, who was in last place...
- We got this. - We won.
They have a total of 400 dollars.
(The final amount is 400 dollars.)
(Team America wins.)
Nobody was eliminated.
(That was close.)
That's too bad.
- So we... - Two people will get the penalty.
(Two members from Team Asia will receive the penalty.)
The penalty is...
(Today's penalty)
Do you see the rail above us?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Yes. - It's a zip coaster.
(A zip coaster is located very high.)
You have to hang there and fly down.
(Today's punishment is a zip coaster,)
(which runs at a high speed at a scary height.)
- I can't. I'm afraid of heights. - There's no bottom. You hang there.
(It looks very scary.)
- It has no bottom? - It doesn't. You just hang there.
(Just thinking about it makes them cringe.)
- I tried it, and it's scary. - What about a rope?
We'll draw lots for this one.
(She proposes first.)
Please choose one.
(Ony 2 out of 4 will receive the penalty.)
It's two of us.
Choose whichever one you want.
(The losers must stay and experience the ride.)
- I'm nervous. - I...
Is this for real?
Please show us what you chose at the same time.
(Who will get the penalty?)
- One. - Do you want to trade?
Two.
Three.
- Good luck. - Okay.
(As a result,)
Good luck.
(Se Chan and Kangnam receive penalty.)
It's all the way there?
Kids these days are intense.
(It's very scary to be up here.)
It's really high.
(Se Chan gets the penalty first.)
Go up.
What is this?
(Completely nervous)
(People look very small as he arrives at the starting point.)
It's so high up.
This isn't right.
If you fall while you go down,
won't you break your butt?
(We filmed with safety equipment...)
Just sit back.
(and the instruction from safety personnel.)
(Taking a deep breath)
(It's at a height in which people feel the most fear.)
Hold on. When will you push me? Hold on.
Departing in 3, 2, 1.
(Start!)
Hold on!
(He exposes his ugliness.)
(It's faster than he expected.)
Hold on!
(Shaking)
It's shaking so much!
(Kangnam proceeds with the penalty.)
It's so fast!
(Kangnam who was laughing has disappeared.)
(He faces the ruthless punishment.)
This is so fast.
(Thank you Joon Park, Kangnam, Ailee, and Yiren for joining us.)
Suk Jin!
(Everyone in the Yoo family has gathered in one place.)
Father!
It's been a long time.
(The eldest, Jae Suk's family)
Nothing has changed.
(Kwang Soo, youngest son, Jae Suk, eldest uncle)
Father.
Father, why do you always treat me like this?
(The youngest, Jong Kook's family)
I'm taking your side.
(Ji Hyo, eldest daughter-in-law, Suk Jin, eldest son)
Did I teach you like that?
- This is my wife. - Hello.
(The youngest, Jong Kook's family)
Right, my daughter-in-law.
(So Min, youngest daughter-in-law, Se Chan, youngest son)
Our lucky charm.
- Uncle is here. - He's here.
(The Yoo family...)
Things are running smoothly at home, isn't it?
(has gathered together for the holidays.)
Why are you discouraging my kid?
- Please accept my bow, Father. - I'm not your father.
(At the shocking and rebellious setting,)
- You punk! - You're my younger brother!
(the family has fallen apart.)
Our family is a mess.
- "To my beloved children." - These are all mine.
(At that moment, they receive a message from their late grandpa.)
(Protect my eggs,)
"Try to protect as many of your 10 eggs as possible."
(but steal another's to make jeon.)
"Set the table for the ancestral rites with three different jeons."
We're family. We're one.
(A war for the inheritance...)
(between the two families regarding Grandpa's memorial meal will start.)
Our family will end up fighting like this.
(The war of nerves between the two families get fiercer.)
It's mine.
Over here!
- Where are you going? - Grab him!
(Which family will complete the meal and get Grandpa's inheritance?)
We're a family.
We're the Yoo family.
(Chuseok Family Race, The Yoo Family's Inheritance War)