(It's a summer day with a scorching heatwave.)
(Oil Tank Culture Park)
Hello.
(It's the 2020 welcoming ceremony of Superpower School.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Anticipating)
Good morning.
- Wang Soo. - What?
I heard Wang Soo was Kwang Soo's childhood nickname.
(Wang Soo was Kwang Soo's childhood nickname.)
I just told you about it in private. Why would you say that?
Were you called Wang Soo?
(Wang Soo is flustered by disclosure of personal information.)
- My family called me like that. - Why?
Today's about superpowers.
(Glad)
Welcome to the entrance ceremony of Running Man Superpower School.
(Welcoming ceremony of Superpower School)
All right.
Today, you are the seniors of Superpower School.
(They're seniors of Superpower School.)
I want you to be good mentors for the freshmen who are joining soon.
(They will become mentors for the freshmen.)
- So this is the entrance ceremony. - We are mentors indeed.
I'm not sure what our superpowers are yet.
(Each member received a superpower before the shoot.)
(A few hours ago, Room of Superpowers)
(Kwang Soo walks into the Room of Superpowers, full of expectation.)
This is just too cool.
Just open it.
(What is my superpower?)
What is my superpower?
"You are an invisible man."
"Doing mosquito dance..."
(Mosquito dance?)
"You are an invisible man."
(He takes a deep breath.)
"Doing mosquito dance,"
"sing, 'You didn't see me, you didn't see me'."
"Sing, 'You didn't see me, you didn't see me'."
(Do you really want me to do this?)
"And put on the invisibility cloak."
(Invisible Man)
"Then you will stay invisible until you take off the cloak."
A giant mosquito bit my foot
I scratched my foot without thinking
(I'm supposed to do this in the Superpower Special?)
It was itchy, but I put up with it
I give up.
(He decides to give up after much consideration.)
(He drinks the potion that gives him a superpower.)
(Once he chants the spell, he gets his superpower.)
Do I have to sing now?
Yes, please.
This is humiliating.
I feel like I'm standing here naked.
It's been over 10 years.
(He shudders thinking about his specialty from 10 years ago.)
(He pulls himself together and tries to focus.)
This is crazy.
- I will give you the cloak. - What?
- This is the cloak? - It's an invisibility cloak.
(This is the invisibility cloak?)
(I'm Invisible Man. Please pretend you didn't see me.)
(The cloak has an earnest request of Invisible Man on it.)
(What's this?)
I thought it'd be something cool.
(It may not look so cool,)
You didn't see me, you didn't see me
(but he can block all superpowers when he becomes Invisible Man.)
(Kwang Soo is invisible right now.)
(Invisible Man)
(Invisible Man, one can become invisible with the cape...)
(and block all superpowers.)
(- That was great! - Winner of Baeksang Arts Award!)
(He traded his embarrassment for the superpower of invisibility.)
You're so cool!
You deserve your award.
(Now it's Ji Hyo's turn.)
"Your superpower lets you summon a bodyguard."
"Raise your arms overhead..."
(Bursting into laughter)
(She's embarrassed even before she could summon a bodyguard.)
Hold on.
(Do you really want me to do this?)
This is... Hold on.
This...
(This is why they're afraid of episodes with superpowers...)
(more than any other special episodes.)
This is driving me crazy.
I'm supposed to do this in front of many people?
- Yes. - For three minutes?
(She drinks a potion while feeling embarrassed.)
And I
(Bodyguard Summoner, one can summon a bodyguard...)
(by singing, "And I," with both arms up in the air.)
Ta-da.
And I
(Bodyguard Summoner)
(Summons 1 bodyguard)
Ta-da.
This is embarrassing.
I'll leave.
(Bodyguard Summoner exits after only embarrassing herself.)
See you later.
(And then comes...)
(Haha, the perfect man for something like this.)
(He becomes one with the character.)
(He looks natural as if they're his clothes.)
(The perfect member for this type of setting.)
"You are Captain Gravity."
"To attack a member out of your sight,"
(Captain Gravity, one can target a member as an enemy...)
"drop two apples..."
"and shout, 'Gravity!'"
"It'll put 5kg sandbags..."
"around the wrists and ankles of the member,"
"which will hinder his or her movement for three minutes."
Gravity, gravity...
This word is hard to remember.
Gravity.
What does it mean?
- It's a pulling force. - What?
Exactly.
(His English skills can't keep up with his level of engagement.)
Darn it.
I see. That's what it means.
To gravity.
(Cheers to gravity.)
(Screaming)
(I can feel the gravity filling up in my body!)
Gravity!
(Captain Gravity)
(It gives a member of your choice 20kg of sandbags.)
"You are the Sorcerer of Five Senses."
(Sorcerer of Five Senses)
"Hold up your hands to your mouth..."
"and shout, 'Jong Kook has donkey ears!'"
"It will let you eavesdrop for three minutes..."
"and find out a member's superpower."
I always get a useless superpower.
(Sorcerer of Five Senses)
Why did you give me this?
(One can figure out other members' superpowers.)
It's completely useless.
"You are Ttuk-nos."
"Snap your fingers..."
(Ttuk-nos)
(3 people among the survivors will pause for 1 minute.)
Completely turn me over
Like that?
All right. Let's welcome our freshmen.
(Followed by the competent seniors,)
(the freshmen will be introduced.)
I heard their voices, and it seems like...
Suk Jin is one of them.
I'm not sure if he's okay with being a freshman.
(Is Suk Jin a freshman?)
Congratulations.
(Congratulations on getting into the school!)
(An excited freshman)
Hey, we're not doing that.
(Acting silly with superpowers)
- We're your seniors. - We're not doing that.
(One of them looks like a senior.)
I'll never get used to this.
(Formal members join the welcoming ceremony...)
(to celebrate the 10th year.)
(Lee Sang Yeob and Kang Han Na)
Hello.
Hello, Seniors.
(Polite)
- Welcome. - Hello.
(The seniors with superpowers welcome the freshmen.)
- It's been a long time. - They're so cute.
- They're really cute. - Hello.
(Cute freshmen)
- Welcome to the school. - Thank you.
Han Na, come over here.
What am I?
(But...)
Sang Yeob, come over here.
(Why is Suk Jin among the freshmen?)
- What am I? - Love your classmates!
- Love your classmates! - Come here.
- I asked, what am I? - One, two.
(Identity crisis)
You're an old man with a passion for studying.
- Why am I a freshman? - You're a returning student.
These five are freshmen at Superpower School.
(5 freshmen have gathered at Superpower School.)
According to Suk Jin's superpower evaluation results,
(In the last superpower evaluation,)
he failed to move on to the next grade and is held back.
(he failed to move up and he had to reapply for admission.)
(We even gave him the phoenix ability,)
(and he was eliminated three times in a row.)
- Gosh. Get off me. Hold on. - Eliminate him.
(Even with such a good superpower,)
- Hold him. - Fine, I get it.
- Just a second. - Suk Jin is out.
(he's the first one to get eliminated from the game.)
Suk Jin, you're out.
(Grade F in superpower abilities)
Gosh.
- You should have moved faster. - What are you talking about?
(Flunked)
He is held back?
(Suk Jin is the only one to become a freshman again.)
That's why you're a freshman.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(Suk Jin, a repeater)
He's held back.
As the freshman representative,
(Suk Jin will represent the freshmen and take an oath.)
- Suk Jin will recite a pledge. - It feels real.
Seniors, please sit down.
It feels more like a principal's speech.
(The superpower students are seated for the oath.)
It feels...
Here.
- Love your classmates! - Get the chairs.
- Love your school! - Here.
- Hello. - Hi, Sang Yeob.
(Setting an example)
Here's one more.
- Take a seat. - Let's sit down.
(Welcome, my juniors.)
All right.
The freshman pledge.
(Aren't you going to say it?)
- We don't have to do it. - We don't have to do it.
(We're not supposed to do it.)
- It's what we have to do. - Please look at us.
- We'll repeat after you. - It's what we have to do.
(The repeater isn't doing so good with the oath.)
All right. You guys don't know how to use magic, do you?
(Condescending)
You guys don't know how to use magic, do you?
- What? - Superpowers...
(Magic?)
- Is it superpowers? - It's superpowers.
He doesn't know anything.
(He came to the welcoming ceremony without even knowing the school.)
Let Sang Yeob do it instead.
He can't do anything right.
He knows even less than I do.
(Isn't this his second welcoming ceremony?)
- So it's superpowers. - Just read out what's written.
- He's blushing. - Just do what you're told to do.
(Embarrassed)
Just recite the pledge.
(He flunked for a reason.)
- What's wrong with him? - Why did he say, "magic"?
The freshman pledge.
- The freshman pledge. - The freshman pledge.
"As the new students entering Superpower School in 2020,"
"we will learn from our seniors' ambitions..."
"and work hard to develop our own superpowers,"
"so that we can use our superpowers..."
"in an autonomous way."
All right.
"Freshman representative Ji Suk Jin."
(One repeater who's having the second welcoming ceremony...)
Lee Sang Yeob.
Yang Se Chan.
(and 4 ambitious freshmen finish their entrance oath.)
Kang Han Na.
Jeon So Min.
That's our freshman pledge.
(It's great to meet you.)
- We'll work hard. - We'll work hard.
- All right. - This is touching.
(The seniors look so cool.)
Salute.
I used to be like them too.
- I used my superpower well. - Good job.
(The freshmen were also given superpowers.)
Hello.
(Se Chan enters first.)
(Very excited)
I should drink my potion first.
(Potion)
I've been waiting for this moment.
(Se Chan is excited to play his first superpower race.)
"You are the Poison Needle Sorcerer."
"Shoot a member's name tag,"
"and he or she will be paralyzed after 15 seconds."
(Poison Needle Sorcerer, shout, "My name is Se Chan.")
("And I'm a gunman," then shoots a poisoned needle to a name tag...)
(to paralyze the target for 15 seconds.)
(We're not putting in CG yet.)
(The freshman is overzealous and misses the timing.)
(This is when we add CG effects.)
(Enjoying the graphic to the full)
My name is Se Chan.
I'm a shooter.
(Poison Needle Sorcerer)
(Shoot a poisoned needle to a name tag to paralyze the target...)
(for 15 seconds. The target can only roll to move for 30 seconds.)
(So Min's turn)
"You are the Wizard of Push and Pull."
(Laughing)
Is this really a superpower?
"Shout, 'Go, go, push!'" "at a member,"
(Witch of Push and Pull)
"and he or she will be pushed away."
"Shout, 'Come, come, pull!'"
"and he or she will be pulled toward you."
"As soon as you breathe, the member can move freely."
(Her superpower ends when she's out of breath.)
"So try to hold your breath as long as you can."
(Zealous)
Go, go, push!
Like that? Or...
(After some fancy preparation moves,)
Come, come, come!
(she chants the wrong spell.)
Oh, is it "pull"?
(The freshman is not familiar with using superpowers.)
- It's "push" and "pull". - Right. "Push" and "pull".
Okay. This is nice.
Will this give me a superpower?
(She drinks a potion to become Wizard of Push and Pull.)
Go, go,
push!
(We're pulling back.)
(The powerful ability affects the cameraman too.)
(Pleased)
Okay, I like it.
Can I try it one more time?
(Very excited)
Come, come,
(Witch of Push and Pull)
pull!
(One can push or pull an opponent.)
"You are..."
(The repeater appears.)
"the Past Life Summoner."
"When you're eliminated,"
(Past Life Summoner)
"lift the bundle..."
This is it.
I still...
have a death.
(He even got the spell wrong.)
(Past Life Summoner)
(One is reborn when eliminated.)
Mirror, mirror,
(Celebrity Copier)
who do I look like?
(One transforms into a celebrity for 3 minutes by doing an impression.)
"Is it wrong to fall in love?"
Drop the beat.
(Charming Dancer)
(Say, "Drop the beat,")
(dance to the music for 30 seconds...)
(to blind the members who witness the dance for 1 minute.)
- You've all been given superpowers. - Yes.
(The freshmen were also given superpowers.)
Running Man's 10th anniversary special is only 3 weeks away.
(10th Anniversary Special is in 2 weeks.)
That day,
(On the day of the anniversary,)
we will go live...
- at the end of the race. - On a Sunday?
(the ending of the race will be aired live in 2 weeks.)
What?
(A live show to celebrate the 10th year!)
A live broadcast?
For the next two weeks,
to decide who will be penalized live on our 10th anniversary special,
(For the next 2 weeks, they'll be playing 2 races that the viewers...)
we will have two races chosen by our viewers as their favorites.
(wanted to see again for the penalty on the day of the live episode.)
Our viewers' number one favorite turns out to be...
War of Superpowers.
(The first race: Superpower Race)
- This was a fun one. - I enjoyed it too.
The Keeper of Time!
(The superpower race series pioneered the show's popularity.)
- Come on! - The Keeper of Space.
- Over here. - Let's go.
(These are children's specials that make everyone cringe.)
(But its low-quality CGs make you watch it more than once!)
(The Superpower Special is back after many requests!)
(The 10th Anniversary Specials, Superpower Race)
(Live broadcast on July 12)
Therefore, we welcome you to the Superpower School Race.
(Race You Wanted to See Again: Superpower School)
The last man standing will become the final winner.
(The last person standing will be the final winner.)
The one chosen by the winner will receive the penalty...
(The person picked by the winner...)
(will be given the penalty during the live broadcast.)
during the live show.
The one chosen by the winner will receive the penalty...
(I really need to win.)
- during the live show. - No way.
The guests will receive a prize if they win...
(Also, there are prizes and penalties tailored for guests.)
or a penalty if they lose.
The details will be revealed at the end of the race.
Before we begin the actual race,
you'll compete in a preliminary mission.
You will split into 5 teams of 2...
(There will be 5 teams of mentor-mentee pairs.)
that consist of a mentor and mentee.
Points will be handed out depending on how you do.
(Points will be given based on the result of the mission.)
The points you receive...
(For every 2 points, members can add 1 use of superpower.)
will affect the number of times...
(They can increase the counts to use their superpowers.)
you'll be allowed to use your superpowers.
So doing well in this mission will be crucial.
- Got it. - The mentors must do well.
- How about this? - It's all down to the mentors.
We've already chosen your teams for you.
(Mentor-Mentee Announcement)
- What? - Really?
Team One.
Yoo Jae Suk...
and Kang Han Na.
(Group 1: Yoo Jae Suk - Kang Han Na)
- Han Na. - I hope we get along.
- Be good to him. - Strong Han Na, Weak Han Na.
Han Na, come this way.
She seems like an excellent student.
Han Na's finally moving out from under my shadow.
I should use this chance to learn from the best.
(The Mentor-Mentee Selection Result)
- She was always... - Team Two.
(Superpower School, Jae Suk and Han Na,)
We have a good chance of winning.
I'm partnered with a true mentor.
(Jong Kook and So Min Kwang Soo and Suk Jin,)
(Haha and Sang Yeob, Ji Hyo and Se Chan)
We're playing the limbo game.
- I'm not good at that. - We're not on the flexible side.
(It's a preliminary mission to increase the number of counts.)
My mentor, come this way.
Your mentor?
(Se Chan greets Mentor Kwang Soo.)
Who's the mentor?
- Kwang Soo is. - We...
He's not directly above us though.
(He isn't your direct mentor.)
- But... - I remember my freshman years.
(Arrogant)
He's the senior because he joined before us.
(Even though he looks like that...)
Does that look like an ordinary pole to you?
(He pretends to be sharp.)
- Kwang-tor. - Kwang-tor?
(Kwang Soo plus Mentor)
(He's the perfect type of a mentor to tease.)
- Kwang-tor. - Are you saying...
that this is no ordinary limbo game?
Please let us know. If you tell us in advance...
Consider the bigger picture here.
(Frustrated)
- As in what? - See the paint over there?
(There are five colors of paint on the other side of the room.)
See the paint over there?
Will we be playing the game with paint on our faces?
(No way.)
- I see you don't know. - Are you sure?
- Are you sure? - We'll be holding the paint.
But someone could slip and get hurt.
That's the fun of it.
(Getting injured is fun?)
He's a clueless mentor.
- Ji Hyo. - That's the fun of it.
(Mentor Ji Hyo walks in.)
- Ji Hyo. - I bet she's clueless.
- Ji Hyo. - She won't know a thing.
- What? Of course, I know. - She doesn't know anything.
(What are you talking about?)
- She's clueless. - Then...
Ji Hyo, do you know the rule of this game?
- The rule? It's a limbo game. - She doesn't know.
(Why would you ask what the rule is?)
See? She doesn't know a thing.
- It's a limbo game. - That's right.
(What's with the limbo set that confused everyone?)
You will compete in a mission...
to earn more chances to use your superpower.
(A mission for more chances to use the superpower)
The game is called Walking with a Third Eye.
(Walking with a Third Eye)
The runner will put on gloves and a blindfold.
(A blindfolded runner wearing gloves will spin 5 times.)
After spinning five times on the spot,
he or she will try...
(The runner must try to reach as far as possible...)
and plant handprints beyond the limbo pole.
(usings hands behind the limbo.)
(Each team will start with 5 points.)
Each team will start with five points.
You will earn an extra point for every 2m,
(They will earn 1 point for every 2 meters...)
but a point will be deducted...
(but lose 1 point if they fail to pass the starting point.)
if you fail to move past the starting line.
You will earn two points for a handprint on the floor.
(2 points for landing a hand within the marked ground...)
Two points will be deducted though if you place them elsewhere.
(but minus 2 points for landing it in the wrong area.)
The points you receive will determine...
(The mentor and mentee will then divide the earned points.)
the number of times you can use your superpower.
- Right. - Can we help our teammates?
(The bystanders can't give hints by making noises.)
No, you must not talk.
You're not allowed to guide your teammate.
What's there to worry about when we have superpowers?
You idiots.
But what's with the third eye?
(The game begins with Haha, fully absorbed in his character.)
- Not both hands? - No, just the one.
(They are putting paints on their hands.)
And you have to spin on the spot.
- In university... - Gosh.
- So Min, you're up. - You've got this.
(Jong Kook and So Min will start.)
- You're ready. - Put on your blindfold.
You can do this. Do I put this on her?
Do you guys major in sports?
- Is this comfortable? - He must major in sports.
(They look like they won't need any superpowers.)
- Are you good? - Yes.
- Okay. - Ready!
(The goal is to land a handprint as far as possible.)
- So Min, your hair looks nice. - Get set.
- It's better to speed up. - That's right.
- One. - Faster.
- Faster! - Two.
- Three. - Faster.
- Pick up the pace. - Faster, So Min.
- Five. - Off you go.
(So Min completes 5 spins.)
Go ahead.
- Get going already! - The game ends with a handprint.
(So Min takes cautious steps.)
Watch out for the camera.
(Staggering)
(Be quiet!)
Beware of the camera.
(Is it this way?)
12, 13.
(Why is she headed this way?)
Who's there?
(Swipe!)
(Jae Suk let her hand touch his face.)
(Everyone is impressed with the location of her handprint.)
This is the spot.
She touched Jae Suk's face right here.
(She traveled far, but her hand didn't touch the floor.)
- Over here. - You smacked a mentor.
(I don't care about the scores.)
Place your handprint here.
- Go on. - How dare you smack a mentor.
(I'm sorry.)
So where her handprint landed...
(Jong Kook and So Min earn 6 points.)
That was hilarious.
She came a long way though.
What's fascinating is that I touched something sharp.
Something sharp?
- It was his protruding teeth. - It was really sharp.
(She could recognize Jae Suk's protruding teeth.)
- His protruding teeth. - What do you mean it was sharp?
You look like Young Gu or Ppak Gu.
- Ppak Gu. - Ppak Gu?
Yes, Ppak Gu.
(He looks like Ppak Gu with a touch of paint.)
- This isn't at all pleasant. - I know.
Haha, please let go of him.
(Next up are Haha and Sang Yeob.)
- Let's go! - You can't say anything.
(Shaking)
I'm dizzy.
It does make you dizzy.
(After spinning just once?)
Two.
- Two. - Gosh, I'm dizzy.
- Five. - My head's spinning.
(He can barely step forward.)
- I'm too dizzy. - Off he goes.
There he goes.
(What?)
- He's off. - Gosh, I'm dizzy.
(Where is he headed?)
(He's completely off course.)
My world's spinning.
(He thinks he's going in the right direction.)
- What now? - He's going that way.
I thought he'd come this way.
I'm too dizzy.
- What's this? - You made contact!
(He touches the lights.)
- You made contact! - That's it.
(His turn ends under the flashy light.)
(Haha and Sang Yeob earn 4 points.)
- The light. - Over there.
What on earth?
(We are doomed.)
- I thought I was walking forward. - I mean...
(That's strange.)
The Keeper of Time!
(Their turn ends after Sang Yeob goes off course.)
The mentees look like they need guidance.
- I can't believe I headed that way. - You did well.
(It's Jae Suk and Han Na's turn.)
And go.
Guys, please step back.
- Gosh. - That's fast. Go for it.
(She is very fast.)
Three.
- Four. - Goodness.
You can't clap.
(After five quick spins, she heads off.)
(Searching for the route)
(How well she does will decide...)
(the number of times Jae Suk can use his superpower.)
(What?)
She has a good balance.
(Is she already playing the limbo game?)
(You're not quite there yet.)
She's already playing the limbo game.
(An error has occurred.)
No way.
She's doing a great job.
(That's not the right place!)
Right there.
(She can feel with her foot where the mat ends.)
Just a little to the side.
To the side.
(She doesn't hesitate to land her hands.)
- Han Na, no! - How did I do?
(Did I do a good job?)
- Is she done? - Tell me how I did.
- Why did you stop there? - Where am I?
(Frustrated)
That was awesome.
(Jae Suk and Han Na score 9 points in total.)
- Why... - I knew she'd fail.
Flimsy as always.
You failed.
The mentees can't seem to do this right.
(Kwang Soo and Suk Jin earn 4 points.)
Unbelievable.
I should show them how it's done.
(Looking forward to his results)
I bet he'll do a good job.
Why are you all bad at this game?
(Frustrated)
(Se Chan will represent his juniors...)
Get ready.
(and show them how it's done.)
Three.
(Se Chan is skillful when it comes to games.)
(It's why everyone watches him silently.)
Three.
Unbelievable.
(Will he able to proudly represent the mentees?)
I should show them how it's done.
(What?)
(He bows down to his seniors.)
(It serves you right for being overly confident.)
Oh, no. He fell there.
I was too dizzy.
My world is spinning.
(Are you kidding me?)
I was too dizzy.
I'm not kidding.
(He was able to make them laugh though.)
Good.
- It's all good. - I was too dizzy.
It was like that comedy skit, "Master".
"Get out of here!"
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan earn 4 points.)
- What on earth was that? - You looked cool though.
Se Chan, seriously?
(The teams that were tied played again.)
Jae Suk and Han Na...
(The Mission Result, Jae Suk and Han Na, 9 points,)
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan, 7 points, Jong Kook and So Min, 6 points,)
- earned nine points. - Okay!
(Haha and Sang Yeob, 4 points Kwang Soo and Suk Jin, 4 points)
With the points you earned,
(Now it's time to distribute the acquired points.)
you can buy how many times you can use your superpower.
The rule of distribution is simple.
(The mentor randomly divides points into three cards.)
Distribute the numbers on three cards.
(The mentee will choose two cards.)
What your mentee picks will be the mentee's points.
(Points written on the first card will be distributed to the mentee.)
The next card chosen will be discarded.
(Points written on the second card will be discarded.)
- The last one is the mentor's. - Got it.
(Points written on the last card will be distributed to the mentor.)
Per two points,
(Mentor, a total of 4 points, Mentee, a total of 6 points)
you will get an extra chance to use your superpower.
(Mentor, 2 counts of superpower, Mentee, 3 counts of superpower)
- So Han Na... - Yes?
(Jae Suk and Han Na with 9 points go first.)
You know I never play dirty.
(The superpower counts will depend on the mentor's distribution.)
Let's share it fairly.
I'll write 5 and 4.
- 5 and 4. - 5, 4, and 0?
(Jae Suk can write 5 and 4 points on 2 of the cards.)
- I mean... - Betrayal isn't all that bad.
We have enough points to go around,
- so there's no need to play dirty. - Right.
- He plays dirty too. - 5, 4, and 0.
(He distributed points in 3 cards.)
That's right.
5, 4, 0. Which one has 0?
Zero?
Card number one.
(1. 0 point, 2. 5 points, 3. 4 points)
Then 5 and 4 respectively.
Card number 1 has 0 written on it?
(Did Jae Suk really do what he said he would do?)
You seem nervous though.
- Card number 1 has 0? - You shouldn't choose it.
- Then... - Yes?
(Full of doubts)
- Please don't. - Let him have that instead.
(Han Na wants to choose number 1.)
She hasn't seen it yet.
She hasn't looked.
(According to Jae Suk, number 1 is 0 points.)
I wrote zero on that.
But...
Really?
(But Han Na chooses number 1.)
You're really taking that?
- Don't you trust me? - Take a look.
(How many points will Han Na get for not trusting Jae Suk?)
(9 points!)
(I am doomed.)
(He put 9 points in card number 1.)
Seriously?
(Jae Suk earns 0 points.)
- It's her superpower! - That leaves him with nothing.
Han Na, you're unbelievable.
- That was insane. - Did she understand the rule?
(Jae Suk: 1 count Han Na: 1 count plus 4 counts)
Jae Suk, I've got to hand it to you too.
He has zero points then.
Of course, I trust Jong Kook.
(It's Jong Kook and So Min who earned 6 points.)
- How can you not? - I trust you completely.
Just do as I say.
I'll write 0 on card number 2.
On card number 3, I'll write down 4.
(Jong Kook distributes the points honestly.)
- He'll write down four. - What? Wait. Hold on a second.
4 on card number 3?
(Is he telling the truth?)
I saw him write a zero.
I'll write two on the last one.
(Jong Kook wrote down what he said.)
- See? It's just like I said. - You can't show her.
- Wait and see what So Min does. - "Wait and see."
(Everyone is looking forward to see how So Min will react.)
(She is still doubtful.)
- Is this four? - Yes.
- Are you sure? - Of course.
You promised, remember?
(So Min earns 4 points from Jong Kook's honesty.)
- Please choose the next one. - You guys are all nice.
This is how we normally are.
(Stuttering)
- Of course. - We're one big team here.
Look at her eyes.
(Uneasy)
Come on. Choose the right one for me.
- Did you write two on this? - Yes.
(He said number 1 was 2 points,)
- 0? - 0. Yes.
You can throw one away.
You really are...
(but she throws number 1 away.)
(His anger explodes.)
- That's right. - He's really angry.
(She sacrifices herself to block Jong Kook's superpower.)
Run away, So Min.
That's how So Min is.
This is what you meant.
(This is how the poison mushroom pays back.)
She's like a poison mushroom.
- I told you. - The strongest member came out.
(So Min gets 2 additional chances to use her superpower.)
I should've done this.
(It's Kwang Soo and Suk Jin's turn with 4 points.)
My head hurts already.
All of them are zero, but...
(Looking forward to seeing them already)
All of them are?
- He's going to do 4, 0, 0 for sure. - Can I see it?
(Certain)
Yes. Take 2 and leave 2.
I'll show it to you.
(Kwang Soo wants to divide equally.)
- Seriously. - You're going to write 2 and 2?
You're going to let him see you write it down?
(You're going to let him see you write it down?)
You're going to let me see you write it. Show me.
You're going to let him see you write it down?
(He will write it down in front of him.)
You're going to let me see you write it. Show me.
- It's true. - He's writing 2, 0, 2.
(Did he keep his promise?)
Seriously.
(Why is he hiding the cards?)
- And then he's mixing it. - He's mixing it up.
- It's like he's doing magic. - He's mixing it up.
It's like he's doing magic.
(It looks like he's mixing them up.)
Are you mixing them up?
(He switches the cards.)
- Hey, you fool. - Hey.
- There are numbers in the back. - Hey.
- There are numbers in the back? - There are...
(He pretends to mix them up.)
You fool. Stop mixing them.
I showed it to you.
(He looks somewhat suspicious.)
Then...
I really showed it to you. What's wrong?
(He hid the cards behind the mic.)
Really? He's telling the truth.
(After failing to find the cards, Suk Jin believes Kwang Soo.)
- I'm telling the truth. - I thought he had other cards...
hidden in his pocket.
- No way. - Then it's 2, 0, 2.
(It already says 4, 0, 0.)
- Yes. - It's 2, 0, 2.
I saw him write 2, 0, 2.
(He keeps saying 2, 0, 2.)
- That's what he wrote. - I showed it to you.
I saw it too.
I'll take 2 then.
- I'll take 2. - Okay.
(What?)
(Why does it say 4 points here?)
Okay!
- You are... - Seriously.
(His strategy failed big time.)
- You're too much. - He overthought it.
(Suk Jin gets 2 additional chances to use his superpower.)
He overthought it.
My goodness.
- That's right. - That brat.
(The results of the other teams' distributions)
- Four! - That brat.
(Han Na has 5 chances.)
- Goodness. - That brat.
(So Min, Suk Jin, Haha, Se Chan have 3 chances.)
(Jae Suk, Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Sang Yeob, Ji Hyo have 1 chance.)
The results are interesting...
because all the seniors have zero points except for Haha.
You guys have really good juniors.
(The seniors are being considerate of juniors.)
- They are really... - That's right.
Let's continue to overcome them!
(A pupil excels his master.)
- This is the worst. - Let's go, juniors!
The seniors need to work harder.
As a result, Han Na has received four more...
(Han Na can use her superpower 5 times.)
and has a total of five chances.
The remaining members have 3 chances or 1 chance.
(It's time to compete using their superpowers.)
- I only have 1 chance. - We'll move on...
- to the location for the race. - Yes!
(Let's go to the location for the final race.)
Goodness, Kang Han Na.
- Good job. - Goodness.
Good job, Han Na.
(After dividing the number of chances for superpowers)
- Who, me? - It's nice and cool here.
- You did a good job. - Oh, for getting 9 to 0?
You did well.
Jae Suk had a weird look on his face.
(Many chances to use superpowers)
- I see. - It was a good game.
We need to choose a representative among the second years.
(It's time to pick a class representative.)
- The rules are... - What are they?
When you get off the bus, the juniors will...
write down the name of their favorite senior...
(Juniors will vote for their favorite senior.)
and give us the ballot.
- The juniors will do that? - Yes.
The juniors will do that.
Is there some type of benefit to the senior?
- The senior chosen... - A benefit.
(The representative will be given another chance.)
as the representative will be given another chance.
- Okay. - Yes.
(Seniors are interested.)
We should hear the reasons why we need to choose them.
- If we look at it like this... - Really?
(They try to win juniors' favor.)
- That's right. - Kwang Soo, I choose you.
As you all know, I gave Han Na...
(Shameless)
nine points.
- That's right. Wait. - You tried to fake it.
(What?)
- You were trying to fool me. - I'm talking about the results.
(She knows what he's after.)
Guys. Hey, everyone.
- Who should be the representative? - It's the representative.
- Let's vote for one person. - I agree.
The way that I see it,
(Junior who flunked has a loud voice.)
I think that the votes should go to...
(Interrupting)
Excuse me. Are you the leader of the juniors?
(He calls himself the leader of the juniors.)
- Yes, I am. - Did they choose you?
- Yes, they did. - I'm sorry,
but the principal should stay out of it.
Stop speaking nonsense.
- The students are talking. - The way that I see it...
(Whatever the seniors say, he says what he has to say.)
- Everyone. - Yes?
Choose someone who's a bit slow.
(He doesn't like it.)
- Someone who's slow? - Someone slow?
- Someone who's easy to manipulate. - Hey.
- They should have good character. - Suk Jin.
- Yes? Did you call me? - Honestly,
you debuted after me as a comedian, right?
(Jae Suk brings up the actual rank.)
- That's right. - Right.
- Keep that in mind. - Who's the junior?
- Pardon? - Who's the junior?
Why are you speaking casually to your senior?
(What?)
- Suk Jin. - Who's the junior?
Suk Jin, don't write my name down.
(The junior is hurt.)
- Oh, my. - Excuse me.
Let's do it together. Hang out with us.
- Hey! - Let's play together.
- Hey! - I choose Ji Hyo.
Don't you know that the juniors have come together?
- I'm leading them. - We haven't done so yet.
Who are you leading? We aren't being led yet.
(Us?)
- We aren't being led yet. - Who said we are?
Juniors, raise your hand if you will join me!
(Loud)
(Silence)
- He's making me feel uncomfortable. - What surprises me...
is that he's a junior like us.
(Juniors turned their back on Suk Jin.)
- It's uncomfortable, right? - But...
- It surprises me. - It's for our benefit.
(Juniors. Listen to me.)
If you know my superpower,
(Appealing)
- First off, - will you support me?
- we must choose someone weak. - Tell us.
(Kwang Soo says his superpower is helpful.)
- I can help you. - How?
- I can give you more power. - Power?
- Stop lying. - It's a lie.
- Has there ever been... - I'm telling the truth.
(But it can only protect him.)
something like that on Running Man?
- He's going to be a burden. - No, that's not true.
(Even though he's an invisible man, his intention is unclear.)
- He's talking nonsense. - I'm telling the truth.
- Show us a motion about your power. - A motion.
(Show us a motion for your superpower.)
- A motion about your power. - I'll show you something.
- A motion related to it. - Here.
- Your superpower. - This is... Goodness.
(Snapping his finger)
- What is that? - Is it Thanos?
(That's an attack.)
- It must be Thanos. - It's an offensive power.
(If it's an attack, there's no reason to vote for him.)
- This is... - It's an offensive power.
- He must kill at least half of us. - Can he get rid of us?
- Show us a motion. - This is mine.
(Kwang Soo)
I say something and do this to the other person.
- Forget it. - And do this to the other person.
(I will help you.)
Forget it. Forget about it.
(It is obvious that he's lying.)
- This is yours? - Lee Kwang Soo, out!
- Take him out. - Can you tell he's a liar now?
(He's lying to become the class representative.)
- I don't believe him. - Did you see that?
- Forget him. - How can you not believe me?
- Let's ignore that one. - Yes, of course.
(Thudding)
- Goodness! - Oh, my!
(The speed bump surprises everyone.)
- Gosh, that surprised me. - Me too.
Did you see that? Everyone was surprised, but I kept my cool.
- Hold on. - You were the one to stay cool.
We need some tissues. Jae Suk peed his pants.
(The elections for the class representative is filled with lies.)
- Am I wrong? - Gosh, Kwang Soo.
I found out something important.
(Making a fuss)
- He's trying to promote himself. - Among the superpowers,
there are some that will help others and...
(Serious)
- some that will help themselves. - I have a power...
that will help everyone.
Don't you think our conversation is really funny?
(Scoffing)
He has a great superpower.
(They suddenly broke out of their characters.)
I have a power...
- When he's 45. - We're all being so serious.
(Grownups talking about superpowers in the same outfit for 15 minutes)
- We're wearing the same outfits. - Some of us are in our 50s.
- Han Na, I'm telling you... - What superpower?
- What R Coin? - if I help you, you'll win.
- Really? - Of course.
- You have to fill in your votes. - Did you write it down?
(It's time to elect the class representative.)
- Yes. - Are you done?
- Yes. Should we hand it in? - Write it down.
Here. I wrote it down.
- Okay. I will announce the results. - Okay.
(The election result)
The first vote goes to...
- Yoo Jae Suk. - Yes!
(Yoo Jae Suk, 1 vote)
- Who voted for him? - Who chose Jae Suk?
- Thank you. - It must've been Han Na.
- Who voted for him? - The second vote goes to...
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Okay!
(Lee Kwang Soo, 1 vote)
- Who chose him? - I will help whoever chose me.
(I'll help you with my superpower.)
- Who chose Kwang Soo? - I'll do this for them.
- I'll do this for them. - He can't be the representative.
- My goodness. - The third vote goes to...
Haha.
(Haha, 1 vote)
- Someone voted for Haha? - Who did?
The fourth vote goes to...
(Yoo Jae Suk, 2 votes)
Yoo Jae Suk.
The fifth vote goes to Yoo Jae Suk.
(As Jae Suk is elected, he gets another chance.)
- I knew it. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Who voted for him?
- Please help us. - Han Na.
(My gosh.)
I didn't expect more than two votes.
(Look at Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook's true feelings just came out.
Not a single person voted for me.
You're right.
My voice is coming back.
(He is back to his voice after getting 0 votes.)
I'm glad you're so in character right now.
- My goodness. - It's like we really have powers.
My goodness.
We're going someplace far.
Aren't we going to Ilsan?
The venue we had intended to go to got canceled because of COVID-19,
(As the venue got canceled due to COVID-19,)
so we'll have our race at Tanhyeon SBS.
(they'll head to Tanhyeon SBS.)
(Tanhyeon SBS has become the mecca of superpowers through many races.)
(The superpower race will be held here.)
During our 10 years, the fans chose this as something they want to see.
(The episode the fans want to see the most in 10 years of the show.)
It's meaningful.
- Yes. - We finally get to use our powers.
(Excited)
It will be meaningful to win today.
It is the War of Superpowers: The End Game.
(War of Superpowers: The End Game)
- The End Game. - The End Game.
It will be a huge honor to be the winner this week.
(10th anniversary)
- It's an honor. - Seriously.
Use your powers to rip off the other members' name tags.
(They'll use their powers to rip off other members' name tags.)
The winner will be the last man standing.
(The last man standing will be the winner.)
However, you are unaware of the other members' powers,
(However, as they aren't aware of each other's powers,)
so you have to be careful while doing the race.
(they have to be careful while competing in the race.)
I'm sure there will be a power that lets you reflect.
(A sad memory)
You can use your power according to how many chances you got earlier.
(They can use their powers according to the number of chances they got.)
Also, there are tickets for the Room of Reinforcement...
(There are tickets for the Room of Reinforcement hidden in the venue.)
hidden all around the venue.
(A ticket to Room of Reinforcement)
If you find these tickets,
(Choose 1 member and bring him or her with you.)
you can choose one person to go into the room with...
and forcibly summon them.
(The chosen member will be summoned forcibly.)
Then you can use the room in a group of two.
(They can use the room in a group of 2.)
- In groups of two. - Both of them must get stronger.
If you succeed in the hit-or-miss mission in the room,
(If they succeed in the hit-or-miss mission in the room,)
both members can add more chances to use their superpower.
(both members can add more chances to use their superpower.)
Even if you fail, you don't lose the chances you already have.
(Even if they fail, they don't lose the chances they already have.)
- You have to go. - However,
you can't rip off another member's name tag while in this room.
(They can't rip off another member's name tag while in this room.)
- In the Room of Reinforcement? - Yes.
Please go to the location of the race.
(They will now move to the starting spot.)
- Let's go! - I'm getting excited.
(Who will be the winner?)
I should try to win.
- It's been 10 years. - Let's try to win.
Oh, my gosh.
(The Number of Times They Can Use Their Superpower)
(Han Na, 5 chances, Suk Jin, Haha, So Min, Se Chan, 3 chances)
I really want to win this one.
(Jae Suk, 2 chances, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, Sang Yeob, 1 chance)
It's been 10 years since we had a superpower race.
(Captain Gravity)
(It gives a member of your choice 20kg of sandbags.)
If it wasn't for our 10th anniversary,
I wouldn't want to win as much.
(Bodyguard Summoner)
I'm so curious as to what the other members' superpowers are.
(Summons 1 bodyguard)
So Min.
You have a cape on.
Yoo Jae Suk. Yoo Jae Suk.
(So Min is excited to put on a cape.)
Jae Suk. I can really...
bring anyone you'd like in front of you.
(With my superpower)
Can you see this?
(Ttuk-nos, Witch of Push and Pull)
(Make 3 members pause for 1 minute.)
You can figure out what kind of superpower I have, right?
(Pull or push an opponent.)
Is that a ring?
Is he really Thanos? He must really be Thanos.
(That looks strong.)
You kind of...
Oh, are you Gollum?
- What? - Are you Gollum?
(My precious.)
You must be Gollum.
My gosh. That brat.
(She's unbelievable.)
He's Gollum. I should run away.
Back in the day,
(Se Chan is excited about the War of Superpowers.)
if you had one of these, you'd be the most popular kid in town.
My name is Se Chan. I'm a shooter.
(Serious)
Excuse me.
(He sees an employee passing by.)
I'm doing something cool.
(Embarrassed)
You're looking at me like I'm childish,
but I'm focusing on what I have to do today.
- I see. - You look the coolest.
(Rooting)
Thank you.
We'll start the race now.
(5 seconds before the race begins)
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
(10th Anniversary Specials, War of Superpowers: The End Game)
(Who will claim the victory?)
Race start.
(Superpower School Race, War of Superpowers: The End Game)
Don't I look cool?
(The cape)
Don't I look like Sailor Moon?
(Transformation)
(A side effect of superpowers: You get too into the character.)
(In the name of the Moon, I'll punish you!)
Don't I look like Sailor Moon?
I'm going to use my superpower like this.
What are you carrying around with you?
What?
(Past Life Summoner's transformation bundle)
What are you carrying?
I found something.
Hey.
(Another patient suffering from the side effects of superpowers)
- What is that? - It's a strong weapon.
(Stepping backward)
I can get rid of you in one shot.
What is that? You really have some type of gadget.
(What kind of device is that?)
It must be a bomb.
(Random words)
- A bomb? - It's a bomb.
(Is it really a bomb?)
Does he have a bomb on his wrist?
- Do you know what this is? - It's a water gun.
(Now he sees what it is.)
It's a water gun.
A water gun?
(They are being cautious as they don't know about the superpowers.)
Once you're shot,
(What is he doing with a water gun?)
- Gosh, what's that? - you'll be eliminated immediately.
- What's your superpower? - What's that, Suk Jin?
- Is it some kind of device? - Are you a peddler?
- What? - Are you a peddler?
Hey, once I open this,
(Trying to threaten them)
you guys will die.
- I think he's a vendor. - No.
(He's not buying it.)
- You're a vendor, right? - No.
He's a peddler.
(It's not working.)
- I'm not here to sell stuff. - I think...
- he will sell this later. - Are you a peddler?
(Sang Yeob shows up with something in his hand.)
(Celebrity Copier)
- Hey. - Wait. He has a mirror.
(One transforms into a celebrity for 3 minutes by doing an impression.)
He has a mirror.
(Sang Yeob is caught with the mirror for his superpower.)
- I just used it to check my face. - What is it for?
Don't be ridiculous.
Once I open this...
(Trying to threaten them again)
and throw it down, you all will die.
Are you Spider-Man?
(Grabbing)
Do you want me to open this?
I'm going to open this.
Do you want me to do it?
I guess he has packed lunch in there.
(It's not threatening at all.)
- Should I open it? - Go ahead.
(He keeps trying to threaten them with his bundle.)
- I will... - I'm going to open it.
I'll buy two.
(Mr. Peddler...)
- I want 2. - Do you want 2?
(Suk Jin, the business magnate)
- It's not something you can buy. - I'll buy two books.
Once you touch it, you will die.
(A hollow cry)
- I'm sure Suk Jin is a vendor. - He's a vendor.
(Convinced)
- Your superpower is selling. - Why is my weapon so heavy?
(Past Life Summoner becomes a vendor.)
His superpower requires a lot of work.
I think I'm the coolest one here.
(Satisfied)
I should find the ticket to the Room of Reinforcement.
(I should first...)
- Suk Jin. What's that? - Hey.
- Feeling! - Intuition!
- Cross! - Cross!
(Meaningless)
What's that?
(The bundle...)
Honestly, my superpower isn't that cool.
(He also admits it.)
But it looks perfect on you.
(Haha and So Min joins them.)
Wish me good luck.
- It's not so cool. - You know it, right?
- It's not cool, but my power... - There's Jong Kook.
(Startled)
- He's wearing gloves. - Why is he wearing gloves?
(He looks charismatic with the gloves on.)
Are you upset?
What are the gloves for?
(They're all scared by a pair of gloves.)
My superpower is...
beating people to death.
(Brutal)
- It's not a superpower. - Hey.
You can do that even without a superpower.
(It's his basic ability.)
My superpower is beating people to death.
- He has a package. - Drop the beat!
(All of a sudden...)
Drop the beat!
- What was that? - Did you use your superpower?
(Did she use her superpower?)
(She suddenly starts to dance.)
- What is she doing? - It has something to do with dance.
(Feeling nervous)
(Han Na starts dancing after shouting, "Drop the beat!")
- What? Did she use her power? - I guess there's something.
(She uses her superpower of Charming Dancer.)
"You're Charming Dancer."
(Charming Dancer)
"If you shout, 'Drop the beat'..."
"and dance to music for 30 seconds,"
"all the members who watch it..."
"will be blinded."
(One can dance to the music to blind the members who witness the dance.)
"And their vision becomes narrow for one minute."
(Suk Jin who watched her dance...)
(gets to wear swimming goggles for 1 minute for narrow vision.)
(Charming Dancer blinds them all with her dance moves.)
(They all get narrow vision.)
- What? - I can't see.
- I can see just a little. - I can barely see.
(It only lasts for 1 minute.)
What is this?
One minute?
(Right at the moment, Han Na attacks?)
(She rips off Suk Jin's name tag immediately.)
What was that?
- Who was that? - What just happened? Suk Jin.
- What? - The race starter is back.
- Hey! - Already?
- This is... - Who took off my name tag?
(Suk Jin is eliminated.)
Suk Jin, you're out.
I'm out?
Hey, we've just started.
- Is it over? - You're so mean.
(I'm sorry.)
- Hey! Han Na! - Seriously?
(The peddler gets to exit early.)
Is it really over for him?
What was that? It's been less than five minutes.
Suk Jin, put down your bundle and get some rest.
But this is for our 10th year anniversary.
(Poor him.)
My goodness.
Kang Han Na.
Han Na, I'll get back at you for this.
(Charming Dancer feels proud after eliminating him.)
This is nice.
What's your superpower?
(The four superheroes are in front of the cafeteria.)
(Showing his ring)
- You're Thanos. - Right. He's Thanos.
(You can tell that he's Thanos from his ring.)
- He can eliminate us immediately. - You will snap your fingers.
With a snap.
It's a random choice. Once he snaps his fingers, one of us will die.
(They try to figure out each other's superpowers.)
Go ahead and try it. Let's see what happens.
No. I can't use it now.
(Trying to look tough)
My superpower is just too strong.
- You might get hurt. - Before I rip off your name tag.
(Say it!)
(Imminent threat)
Come here, guys. Are you ready?
(So Min, Haha, and Se Chan unite.)
- Are you ready? - We're ready.
Shall we begin?
(What?)
(Crying)
You're...
(His poor spell breaks them out of their characters.)
- Hey, you're... - We are three superheroes.
Do you really want to do that to fight against me?
(You should team up with me.)
- We are three superheroes. - Are you ready?
(They try their superpowers again.)
Let's go!
(Bumping)
- It must hurt. - Are you all right?
(It feels painful to even hear the sound.)
- Cut. - Are you okay?
(People with superpowers can feel pain too.)
Okay.
If you're being like this, I'll use my strong superpower.
(Threatening)
- Okay? - Jae Suk.
(Se Chan joins Jae Suk.)
Se Chan.
- You're going to take his side? - Se Chan!
(Traitor!)
Se Chan!
(Unite!)
Let's go, So Min.
(Don't you dare.)
What is she doing?
(Reality strikes.)
- We are very strong. - Okay.
- We can do this. Haha, we can win. - You should give up.
(The superheroes felt how strong they are.)
Se Chan betrayed us. All right.
I'll remember that.
(Ji Hyo, Bodyguard Summoner, appears at that moment.)
- We should form an alliance. - Seriously.
(They suggest Ji Hyo that she joins them.)
I bet you have an amazing superpower.
(At that moment,)
- What? - What is that?
What's going on?
(something appeared out of nowhere.)
- What? - What is that?
- What's going on? - What is it?
(Has Suk Jin become a king?)
(His superpower is...)
- What? - What is that?
"You are Past Life Summoner."
(to be reincarnated as himself from the previous life.)
"If you shout 'I still have a life'..."
"lifting up a bundle,"
"you will be born again in the form of your past life."
(He can be reincarnated even when he's eliminated.)
(He was eliminated by Charming Dancer,)
- Who was that? - What just happened? Suk Jin.
(but there was a reason he was vaguely smiling.)
Who took off my name tag?
I still...
have a life.
I'm born again.
(He's reincarnated as a king of Joseon Dynasty.)
- What's going on? - You brats.
(He gets angry all of a sudden.)
What's all this?
- What is he doing? - What's going on?
(He used to be a tyrant.)
Did you not watch the movie that features Jang Dong Gun?
(Puzzled)
Jae Suk.
Poison Needle Sorcerer used his superpower against you.
You'll be paralyzed in 15 seconds.
(Was Jae Suk hit by a poisoned needle?)
- You'll be paralyzed in 15 seconds. - Really?
- Who used it against me? - 15, 14, 13...
(Who on earth...)
Hurry. Let's follow Jae Suk!
(He escapes for now.)
- Ji Hyo, hurry. Ji Hyo, come here. - I'm coming.
- 11. - Ji Hyo, hurry and run.
(He has to run as far away as possible in 15 seconds.)
5, 4,
(He's about to be paralyzed.)
- 3, 2... - I will use it.
Completely turn me over
(He chants his spell before being paralyzed.)
All right. Pause for a moment.
Jae Suk used his superpower.
(Jae Suk's superpower is...)
What is it?
"You are Ttuk-nos. Snap your fingers..."
(Ttuk-nos, 3 people will pause for 1 minute.)
"and sing, 'Completely turn me over'"...
"to make 3 members freeze for a minute."
Completely turn you over?
(He'll pick 3 people to stop.)
(Please don't pick me.)
Good. It's done.
(The target has been picked.)
(Jae Suk's superpower causes 3 people to stop for 1 minute.)
(Ji Hyo, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo will be paused for 1 minute.)
- What? I can't move? - What?
- How long does he stay paralyzed? - 30 seconds.
There's Ji Hyo.
(Jae Suk is paralyzed for 30 seconds.)
I can't do anything?
(While the three of them are paused,)
(Suk Jin approaches.)
What are you doing? What is it?
- What are you doing now? - Stay still. Attention.
(The King's order)
- What do you want? - What?
- What's going on? - What is he doing?
(He thinks he's an actual king.)
You should shoot a period drama somewhere else.
We're shooting Running Man here. What are you doing?
- Wait. - Just stay still.
(An actor from a historical drama barged in.)
- Why would he say "attention"? - Stay put.
(Poison Needle Sorcerer's superpower)
Isn't it over yet?
- Stay still! - Jae Suk is relieved now.
(His paralysis is cleared.)
Hang on. I should go to Ji Hyo.
(He charges toward Ji Hyo right away.)
And I will
You can't use your superpower when you're frozen.
(She can't use her power when she's paused.)
Gosh, no!
- Come here! - No.
(Ttuk-nos' superpower)
Stop singing.
(She'll be able to move in 15 seconds.)
- Stop it. - No!
- No! - I have to get rid of you.
(Ji Hyo holds out.)
No! You can't do this to me.
- Ji Hyo! - No!
(She can use her power in only 7 seconds.)
I said no!
- Ji Hyo. - And I will
- What's happening, Ji Hyo? - And I will
And I will!
Hey! I called you!
(At that moment...)
- And I will! - What is this now?
Hey! I called you!
(Her bodyguard comes as soon as her spell becomes effective.)
"You are Bodyguard Summoner."
(Bodyguard Summoner, summon a bodyguard for 3 minutes.)
"Summon a bodyguard by raising your arms overhead and singing."
- And I will! - What is this now?
(Her bodyguard, who is her cameraman, is quite weak.)
Is he her bodyguard?
What's going on?
(Grabbing his things)
- What's that song about? - And I will!
- Hey, my superpower is... - What's going on?
(The bodyguard seems unprepared.)
- What was that? - What was that?
(While the bodyguard protects her,)
- What was all that? - She got a bodyguard.
This is...
- Hey! - I mean...
What was the song about?
(Ji Hyo, Bodyguard Summoner, escapes with all her might.)
Why did you not come?
(Resenting her bodyguard)
I almost got eliminated!
(The bodyguard may look weak, but he protected Ji Hyo.)
He protects Ji Hyo.
So our superpowers are like a comedy.
(He looks most ridiculous.)
They are not afraid of me at all.
(Se Chan was watching the whole time.)
(He charges toward Suk Jin.)
- Come here. - Your Majesty.
- What? - Please leave.
Where would I go? I just got back.
(By the way, what is his role?)
What? What is it?
I guess Suk Jin is nothing.
(He figured it out.)
What is Suk Jin doing?
What are you doing?
What is it? Is it a diaper?
Come here.
- Is it your diaper? - Hey.
(Adjusting his outfit)
Why is he running around like that?
Let's get rid of the king.
(Jae Suk and Se Chan decide to let go of the king in a diaper.)
- Let's do that. - Let him put on his name tag.
Come here. I'll get rid of you.
Look at you. How dare you...
(Shouting)
He's got nothing.
(You're not fooling us.)
(He gets caught right away.)
(The king loses his dignity.)
- He's got nothing. - I shot him.
(Poison Needle Sorcerer uses his superpower.)
- Am I paralyzed? - 14.
(Suk Jin will be paralyzed in 15 seconds.)
- You should run away. - 13.
You'll be paralyzed in 14 seconds.
- Me? Okay. - 10, 9...
(His diaper is sliding down.)
This is slipping down.
(He couldn't get far enough.)
You're paralyzed now.
(He'll be paralyzed for 30 seconds.)
- You should lie down. - Lie down.
- What is he, by the way? - You're paralyzed.
(As the poison spreads, Suk Jin lies down.)
How dare you!
(Struggling)
- Forgive me, Your Majesty. - I told you to stop.
Suk Jin is out.
(Ji Suk Jin is out.)
- Forgive me, Your Majesty. - I told you to stop.
(Suk Jin is eliminated shortly after his revival.)
Suk Jin is out.
- What is up with Suk Jin? - Seriously.
(Now they feel sympathetic.)
- Why is he so weak? - I couldn't use my superpower.
(Fragile)
Why didn't you use your superpower?
(Frustrated)
Why didn't you use...
Watch the episode when it airs. You will see why I didn't use it.
Why didn't you use your superpower?
(This is my superpower, Jae Suk.)
You will see why I didn't use it.
Who used the poison needle on me?
I did.
(Being honest)
(You did?)
What is up with him?
(While his attention was on King Suk Jin,)
(he secretly shot the poison needle.)
What?
(He was attacked by someone he thought was on his side.)
I am the Poison Needle Sorcerer.
You are less than human.
Your back was right in front of my face,
(I'm sorry, Jae Suk.)
so I tested my superpower, and it worked so well.
(Feeling betrayed)
I had to figure out what your superpower is.
(He is making excuses.)
Now I know. You know my superpower too.
(I'll forgive you this time.)
- We are even. - Okay.
Do you know that they joined forces?
- Who did? - They joined forces.
(The three feels threatened by Se Chan and Jae Suk's alliance.)
- Jae Suk and Se Chan. - Se Chan betrayed us.
Why don't the three of us join forces?
(Haha, So Min, and Kwang Soo try to form an alliance.)
- I need to be in a team. - What's your superpower?
It's meaningless for me to be by myself.
- Me too. - I need to be in a team.
Even if you get attacked, I can turn the tables.
(They are leaning towards to become allies.)
I can help you rip off someone's name tag.
- You just need to rip it off. - That's right.
- Thus, we should join forces. - Really?
(Tempted)
- Will you join the team? - Let's join forces.
- Yes, I will join the team. - Let's do that.
Hold on.
How did I think to do something with these two?
(I almost forgot.)
The two of you are just as untrustworthy.
(It's the same for me.)
Out of all people, it's you two.
(It's a collaboration of the 3 least credible people.)
I really like this idea.
- I like it too. - I like it too.
You can use it many times, right?
Three times.
(There's no other way.)
- Let's do this. - Let's go.
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go. - Let's go.
(Haha, Kwang Soo, and So Min form an alliance.)
- Keep your promise. - I'm going to use my superpower...
as soon as someone appears.
Let's go. So Min, don't betray us.
(They start off energetically.)
I won't.
If you rip off my name tag... For goodness' sake!
(Surprised)
I didn't do anything.
- It was a cameraman. - It was a cameraman.
- It was a cameraman. - A cameraman.
(I'm sorry.)
I will use my superpower!
(Don't surprise me.)
I will use it!
Come on.
(Reaching out her hand)
(The smallest movement puts them on edge.)
I didn't do anything.
(If you touch me...)
I could use my superpower right away.
Do you want to see me turn my wrist?
Let's keep going.
(Clearing her throat)
(They are nervous as they don't know each other's superpower.)
Come, come, pull!
(So Min uses her superpower.)
"You are the Witch of Push and Pull."
(Witch of Push and Pull)
(Say "Push" to push opponents away from you.)
Go, go, push!
(Say "Pull" to pull opponents toward you.)
Come, come, pull!
(Witch of Push and Pull uses her superpower.)
(Haha, an actor who specializes in superpowers)
What is going on?
(His realistic performance calls for computer graphics.)
(What is going on?)
(Come on and remove his name tag!)
Hey, don't do that!
(While Kwang Soo is in a daze)
(Her superpower ends.)
It's over.
You should have ripped it off!
(Frustrated)
(Feeling deeply betrayed)
- What? - Why didn't you rip it off?
You should've told me the rules! You should've told me how!
(The alliance falls apart in just 5 minutes.)
I can't believe it.
(He signals Kwang Soo.)
So the effect ends when she can't go on.
(Kwang Soo understands the plan.)
What are you guys doing?
(Now everything changes.)
- You ruined our alliance. - What are you guys doing?
What are you guys doing? Stop it!
(They both attack So Min.)
No! This is my first time to have a superpower.
(Crying)
Go, go, push!
Is it a different skill?
(Push)
My goodness.
(The actor who specializes in superpowers puts on a show.)
(Witch of Push and Pull creates a hassle for everyone.)
You ruined our alliance.
(Meanwhile, So Min runs away quickly.)
(She manages to escape.)
Gosh, So Min.
- Kwang Soo, did you see that? - Haha.
(She just betrayed us.)
(Promise)
Let's stay together until the very end.
I will keep my promise today.
(With So Min's betrayal, only the two remains.)
Let's go.
I can't believe So Min. How could she betray me?
(So Min already used 2 counts of her superpower out of 3 counts.)
You have only one chance left.
I need to find the Room of Reinforcement.
(Sang Yeob was wandering around alone.)
Jae Suk.
(He runs into Jae Suk and Se Chan.)
- It's Sang Yeob. - What's his superpower?
He has a mirror.
(Is it his superpower?)
It's just my mirror.
(Sang Yeob seems to be flustered.)
(Jae Suk notices something!)
Lee Tae Oh? What is that?
- What? - Why does it say Lee Tae Oh?
(What's with Lee Tae Oh?)
What do you mean?
Why does it say Lee Tae Oh?
Lee Tae Oh?
Is there another guest?
(It says "Lee Tae Oh" and not "Lee Sang Yeob"?)
You are the Celebrity Copier.
(Celebrity Copier: One transforms into a celebrity for 3 minutes...)
If you do a voice impression of a celebrity,
(by doing an impression.)
you can become that celebrity for three minutes.
(Sang Yeob can gain a new name tag through a voice impression.)
Mirror, mirror,
who do I look like?
It's not a sin to fall in love!
Ji Sun Woo!
(He used his superpower...)
(to become Lee Tae Oh.)
(Even if the name tag gets removed, Lee Sang Yeob will survive.)
(Meanwhile, Han Na was walking around by herself.)
(She discovers Sang Yeob.)
Sang Yeob!
(He is on guard.)
Drop the beat!
(Kang Han Na uses her superpower.)
(She blinds him with a charming dance.)
(Lee Tae Oh is blinded.)
What is this?
Do I walk around like this?
(He now has a very narrow vision.)
That's right.
(This is my chance!)
(She attacks right away.)
(It's hard for him to defend himself due to his narrow vision.)
Lee Tae Oh!
(Ripping)
(Lee Tae Oh is out.)
Lee Tae Oh is out. Lee Tae Oh is out.
(That was close.)
- Lee Tae Oh is out. - Why does it say Lee Tae Oh?
Why does it say Lee Tae Oh?
Lee Tae Oh is out.
- Who? - Lee Tae Oh is out.
Who?
Lee Tae Oh is out.
- Lee Tae Woo? - Lee Tae Oh.
(Who is that?)
- Lee Tae Oh is out. - Who is Lee Tae Oh?
(It's a wrong guess.)
It must be Suk Jin.
(Everyone is confused about Lee Tae Oh.)
Lee Tae Oh from "A World of Married Couple"?
(Lee Tae Oh disappears.)
Lee Sang Yeob is back.
(Lee Sang Yeob returns.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo used up all her superpower.)
This is driving me crazy.
(She is searching for a ticket for the Room of Reinforcement.)
I am the only one without a superpower.
Ji Hyo is over there.
I will go over to her and use my superpower.
You are Captain Gravity.
(Captain Gravity)
(It gives a member of your choice 20kg of sandbags.)
(Ji Hyo is not aware of this.)
(Captain Gravity is out to get her.)
Gravity!
(He is too into his character.)
(Haha uses his superpower!)
(Haha's superpower affects Ji Hyo.)
(Gravity pulls Ji Hyo down.)
(Walking slowly)
Let's go.
(Ji Hyo couldn't run away because of the sandbags.)
(Ripping)
(He ripped off her name tag!)
(Ji Hyo gets eliminated...)
(without a chance to use her strength.)
(Laughing)
(Captain Gravity's superpower was very effective.)
Are these sandbags?
Who used this power on me?
Haha is watching from there. He isn't even surprised.
- I can't even run. - Haha used his superpower on her.
(This is the charm of the War of Superpowers.)
Your superpower is incredible.
(You are awesome.)
(He gives a ceremony.)
What did you do to me?
(Ji Hyo became his first victim.)
(Current Situation)
(Ji Hyo is out.)
(Suk Jin is out, but he can use his superpower 2 more times.)
This is funny indeed.
(It's his time to summon his second past life.)
I still have a life.
(What's Suk Jin's second past life?)
(Ji Suk Jin)
(He comes back as a commoner of the Joseon Dynasty.)
The Korean language is different from the Chinese language,
and the written words and the spoken words don't match.
(He suddenly hears "Hunminjeongeum" verses behind his back.)
(Jong Kook bursts out laughing.)
If I can save the country, I will sacrifice...
(Commoner Ji is patriotic.)
"If I can save the country..."
I will sacrifice myself readily.
(He's too into it.)
(He's born again as a patriot in the month of patriotism.)
Suk Jin.
Suk Jin,
- are you filming something? - What?
I need to keep saying that.
(Pretending to hide his insignificance)
Otherwise, I die.
The Korean language is different from the Chinese language,
and the written words and the spoken words don't match.
(He acts as if he has an amazing superpower.)
- In any case, - Suk Jin.
be careful.
Don't make me recite "Hunminjeongeum".
(Pretending to be strong)
The Korean language is different from the Chinese language...
(Repeating endlessly)
- Do you need to memorize that? - I can't recite what comes next.
I can't make a mistake.
(He finds it funny too.)
(He makes a rule on the spot.)
For goodness' sake.
Suk Jin, you are so funny here.
Why aren't you funny on your YouTube channel?
(Suk Jin's YouTube channel)
(Confessing)
I want to act normal on my channel.
I want to act cool.
(The secret of "Ji Suk Jin World" is finally revealed.)
Don't do that.
- I want to act cool. - It's better when you look foolish.
Where is everyone? Come on out!
You jerks!
- Suk Jin, you are so funny. - You...
(The number 1 fan)
You are so funny.
Once I recite "Hunminjeongeum", you are done for.
- All right. - You jerks!
- Okay. - The Korean language...
is different from the Chinese language...
(That's insane.)
Thank goodness I managed to fool Jong Kook.
Thank goodness.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Wasn't I right about Suk Jin?
Suk Jin is so funny.
(He's almost crying.)
He became a zombie, right?
Today,
(Figured out)
Suk Jin will have a costume show.
He can keep coming back to life.
(Suk Jin's superpower isn't threatening at all.)
The bundle contains costumes.
- That's right. - It seems that way.
We should go and eliminate him.
(They go after Suk Jin whose superpower is revealed.)
We should go and eliminate him. Why didn't you take him out?
(When Jae Suk is inattentive,)
(Poison Needle Sorcerer uses his superpower.)
You need to pause after 15 seconds.
(Jae Suk fell for the same trick.)
Jong Kook, hurry up.
For goodness' sake.
(Time left until the poison needle comes into effect)
Jong Kook, let's eliminate him together.
11, 10...
(However, Jong Kook doesn't budge.)
You should take him out.
9, 8, 7, 6...
(Jae Suk is about to be paralyzed.)
Hey.
(Jong Kook only watches.)
What is going on?
Two...
(Time left until the poison needle comes into effect)
One. You are paralyzed.
(Jae Suk is paralyzed.)
You are paralyzed.
Two...
One. You are paralyzed.
You are paralyzed.
(The poison spreads throughout Jae Suk's body.)
(Time left until the effect is lifted)
(Angry)
You dirty jerk.
I will survive...
(He pledges revenge.)
I will survive and take you out.
(Struggling)
Jong Kook, help me!
- I will survive... - Over here!
(Se Chan asks for help,)
Over here!
Why can't he take out a paralyzed person?
(but he wouldn't budge.)
You...
(Bouncing)
(But Jae Suk perseveres.)
- Hey! - Hey!
He is too strong.
(Only 7 seconds left until the effect is lifted.)
2, 1,
- zero. - Come here.
- Come here. - You are no longer paralyzed.
- Come here. - Jae Suk, I am sorry.
(Change in attitude)
Jae Suk, I betrayed you...
because I was blinded by the idea of winning.
- Jae Suk, I am sorry. - Hey.
(Heartless Se Chan shot a poison needle on Jae Suk to win.)
I was blinded by the idea of winning,
- so I took my chance. - How could you do this to me?
(Feeling betrayed)
How could you use 2 out of 3 poison needles on me?
I am sorry.
How could you use 2 out of 3 poison needles...
(He goes on his knees, but he already lost Jae Suk's trust.)
on me?
(He only followed his instinct.)
I saw a lot of openings.
Jae Suk, I don't have any poison needles now.
(How could you...)
I am done for.
I will stay by your side.
(By the way)
(Why didn't Jong Kook join the attack?)
Gosh, I can't do anything.
(Now, the result of the race depends on the counts of superpowers.)
(She finds a ticket for the Room of Reinforcement!)
(She looks around so that no one would take it.)
(Commoner Ji appears.)
(So Min doesn't notice him.)
(He chases after her with the bouncing bundle.)
(Startled)
Suk Jin, Suk Jin. Let's go to the Room of Reinforcement.
(Let's go to the Room of Reinforcement together.)
The Room of Reinforcement?
- I have a ticket. - It's time to choose.
(Who will she take to the Room of Reinforcement?)
- What? - It's time to choose.
With whom will you go to the Room of Reinforcement?
- Hurry up. Who will it be? - Ji Suk Jin.
Okay. Let's go.
(I'm in.)
(So Min quickly overcame the crisis.)
This is great.
- You found the ticket. - Can we use the ticket...
- right away? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
(So Min and Suk Jin enter the Room of Reinforcement.)
Hello.
You entered the Room of Reinforcement.
Please choose a random mission.
I can't fail.
(Desperate)
- Do we choose one each? - This is bad.
"Random Vinegar Yogurt Drink".
"Pick 1 out of 3 yogurt drinks each."
"You succeed if both members drink a regular yogurt drink."
My goodness.
We can drink a vinegar yogurt drink as if it's a regular one, right?
(If they drink a vinegar yogurt, it counts too.)
- Yes. - Okay.
Please pick one each...
- Okay. - and drink.
(He quickly picks a yogurt.)
Let's do this.
- You must endure it. - Please drink it in one go.
(If they complete the mission, they get a chance to use the superpower.)
- In one go? - Yes.
Please drink it in one go.
- Cheers. For reinforcement! - For reinforcement!
(Will they complete the mission...)
(and obtain more chances to use the superpower?)
(Throwing up)
(He picked the vinegar yogurt drink.)
(He sourly fails to reinforce.)
Suk Jin, you should have endured it.
It was impossible.
Suk Jin.
(Bumping into the wall)
(The sour flavor makes him dizzy.)
It was so hard for me to find the ticket.
Would you give us another chance?
You failed the mission.
Please exit the room and resume with the race.
(As he fails the mission, they leave without any gain.)
What? The race?
(He's back to the race...)
Yes.
(after losing appetite.)
Gosh, why did I pick the one in the middle?
(Someone is there!)
Let's take out that man.
(It's my lucky day.)
Suk Jin is weak.
Why does he keep coming back to life?
What are you doing?
Are you filming a period drama?
If you touch my clothing,
you will go straight to your grave.
Is it a costume show or what?
(That's it?)
No, no.
Don't make me recite "Hunminjeongeum".
(Pretending to be strong)
- What? - Don't make me recite it.
(Suk Jin pretends to be strong in case they attack him.)
Okay?
(They ignore his warning.)
Shall we have Suk Jin change into another costume?
(Let's rip off his name tag.)
(What?)
- Is there another costume? - If we rip off his name tag,
(Is this Beijing Opera or something?)
he will change into another costume.
I am sick and tired of that costume.
- Okay. Come on. - Let's see a different costume.
(Pretending to be strong)
- Okay. - Let's see a different costume.
(Everyone figured out Suk Jin's superpower.)
- But... - What?
The Korean language is different...
- from the Chinese language... - He has nothing.
(He has nothing.)
From the Chinese language...
And the written words...
(Number 1 fan is satisfied.)
Suk Jin.
And the spoken words...
Should I complete the sentence? Should I?
- Should I complete the sentence? - Let's take him out.
(Let's try another costume.)
- Should I? - What was that?
Was he just saying things?
(His act is not effective.)
(Then So Min joins.)
Was he just saying things?
Just rip it off. Rip it off.
(Commoner Ji is in danger.)
- I will help. - Just rip it off. Rip it off.
- Rip it off. - I helped.
(Ripping off)
- I did it. - I helped.
- I helped. - I did it.
(Commoner Ji is out.)
Suk Jin is out.
I helped.
(Drooping)
- Is that all? - Yes.
(His second reincarnation ended while reciting Hunminjeongeum.)
Wasn't he using his superpower?
Is that all?
(The look of a weak person)
Why did you pretend to be scary?
(You have nothing.)
- I helped. - Is that all?
Suk Jin is out.
(Laughing)
Didn't he get eliminated earlier?
I thought I heard the same thing earlier. What's going on?
(The commoner is also out after the king.)
Go and change into another costume. We are sick and tired of this one.
- Does he have another costume? - It's a costume show.
(The audience keeps requesting a rerun.)
Can he keep coming back that way?
- He has costumes in that bundle. - What's his superpower?
He has costumes.
(He prepares for an encore with his disguise tool.)
Is that all?
Is he out?
(Really?)
For goodness' sake.
(What will be his last reincarnation?)
It's about time I wear a different costume.
Where on earth is Jong Kook?
(By the way)
(Jong Kook is wandering by himself.)
I should step away.
Suk Jin is out.
After half of them get eliminated, my time will come.
(Jong Kook makes a mysterious comment.)
(Kwang Soo is looking for a ticket for the Room of Reinforcement.)
(He spots the cameraman.)
(Someone must be there.)
(He approaches carefully.)
(Peek-a-boo)
(His 3rd past life is a beggar from the Goryeo dynasty.)
(Laughing)
(The desperate look makes him cry.)
I am a beggar.
What is up with this getup?
(Feeling bad for him)
- I am a beggar. - How did this happen?
I don't even have a bundle now. This is my last life.
It's over. Are you by yourself?
Yes.
Why didn't you team up with someone?
I didn't team up with anyone because you are the only one left.
Would you team up with yourself? You are a beggar.
(Embarrassed)
Han Na is coming.
(Then Han Na approaches Suk Jin and Kwang Soo.)
Why is she walking towards us?
- She is coming. - It's Se Chan.
(Se Chan approaches them quickly as well.)
Se Chan is coming.
Jae Suk is coming too.
(Jae Suk joins as well.)
Jae Suk.
- Suk Jin. - Yes?
(Everyone with superpowers including a beggar from Goryeo gathers.)
Is Suk Jin still in the race?
Listen, everyone.
Listen.
Jae Suk, make an announcement.
(Significant)
An announcement?
(Jae Suk pretends to be strong thanks to Se Chan.)
No, no. I won't hear it.
What?
What's your superpower?
(Even though he dealt with it before,)
(he still doesn't know what Jae Suk's superpower is.)
What is it?
(How will I appear strong?)
What's your superpower?
(Pretending to be serious)
Will you use your superpower on me?
What's your superpower?
(While they have a war of nerves...)
Will you use your superpower on me?
What's your superpower?
I am sorry. You can pass through.
I am sorry.
- I am sorry. You can pass through. - I am sorry.
(Polite)
- He was waiting. - I am sorry.
We were too absorbed. I am sorry.
I am so embarrassed. I am so embarrassed!
(He was listening all along.)
I am sorry.
That was so... Why didn't you tell me sooner?
(Embarrassed)
He was watching us.
(He listened to them for a while.)
His line was the worst.
- His line was the worst. - Why didn't you tell me sooner?
(His line was the worst.)
- Seriously. - He asked,
(Jae Suk's words were cringeworthy.)
"What's your superpower?"
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
(Embarrassed)
He seemed flustered.
He was like, "Who are these guys?"
Completely...
- He was like, "Who are these guys?" - Completely...
turn me over.
- That's your superpower? - What is that?
(Jae Suk uses his superpower for the second time.)
- That's fascinating. - What is that?
(What's this?)
It must be Jae Suk's superpower.
Who will be the three people?
(He picks 3 members among the survivors.)
Please.
(3 members of his choice will pause for 1 minute.)
Completely turn me over.
(Which three members will be forced to pause?)
Once the three members are announced,
they will need to pause for 1 minute after 5 seconds.
- Do you mean the three members? - Hold on.
- These people freeze? - Yes.
What's wrong?
- Did you pick your name? - Yes.
(Nodding)
I freeze too.
(He has to pause himself.)
Okay!
Yes!
(You need the luck to use your superpower.)
- Come on! - I mean...
Han Na, Kwang Soo, and Jae Suk freeze.
(Ttuk-nos uses his power on...)
I mean...
(Han Na, Kwang Soo, and Jae Suk.)
- Do it. - Han Na, Kwang Soo, and Jae Suk...
- Who? - The three of you freeze.
(The 3 will freeze for 1 minute in 5 seconds.)
- Gosh. - You didn't see me
(After picking his own name, Jae Suk runs as fast as he can.)
You didn't see me, you didn't see me
(Kwang Soo finally uses his superpower.)
"You are an invisible man."
(Invisible Man)
(The cloak makes him invisible and protects him from all superpowers.)
(The cloak protects him from all superpowers.)
(Hurrying)
(After a bit of a hassle,)
Hey, look for him!
(he finally puts on the invisibility cloak.)
- He's over there. - Find him!
(Before they knew it, it became a mess.)
- What's going on? - What happened?
What's going on?
(Two cowards don't even try to attack.)
- What happened? - What's going on?
So Min, Kwang Soo is invisible right now.
(Hang on.)
- You can't see him. - I can't see him?
(Viewers, please pretend you don't see him.)
Read what's written on my cloak!
(So Min bumps into him.)
I can't see him?
You can't see him.
How can you hit me when you can't see me?
- Gosh, that was close. - Is Han Na out?
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk uses his superpower on himself.)
Jae Suk, freeze.
(He freezes himself for 1 minute.)
- Can I rip her name tag off? - Han Na, freeze.
- Can I rip her name tag off? - Yes, you can.
(Betraying)
- What's going on? - Really?
(Han Na is frozen too.)
Me?
(So Min eliminates her.)
- Hey! - Han Na is out.
Hey! Han Na!
(Time left until the release)
How could you do this, Se Chan?
- Hey! - Han Na is out.
(It's a chance to eliminate Jae Suk.)
- Hey, Han Na! - How could you...
- Eliminate Kwang Soo. - How...
(Due to his own superpower, he became a prey.)
How could you do this?
(Time left until the release)
Se Chan, this is not okay.
I used my superpower for you.
I used it for you.
(However,)
Jae Suk, you can move again.
(he succeeds to hold for 1 minute.)
- Come here. - Just a second.
Jae Suk, you can move again.
Hold on.
Come here.
(Agitated)
- Is Han Na out? Come here. - Hold on.
- Come here. - Can you move again?
(Witch of Push and Pull got caught.)
Go, go...
- So Min is out. - So Min is out.
(Witch of Push and Pull is out.)
- She's finally out. - What's with him?
(Han Na and So Min are eliminated.)
He's invisible.
(Now they see Invisible Man.)
What?
(We skipped the computer graphics because it's too much work.)
(Current Situation)
(Eliminated)
(Han Na is sent to prison before using all her superpower.)
That's a shame.
I wish I'd gotten a chance to dance in front of everyone.
(By the way...)
Is Jong Kook hiding somewhere?
(Where is Jong Kook?)
(Jong Kook has been on his own for the majority of time today.)
(It looks like he found something again.)
What...
("Lost Items List"?)
(It's a list of items missing from the property room.)
(He stares at the list for a moment.)
(He folds the corner.)
This...
This is dangerous.
(Then he tears it.)
This...
(And he heads somewhere.)
(There is a mysterious gem.)
(What is this place?)
So Min and Han Na, who have superpowers, are out.
(He's told that So Min and Han Na are out.)
Thank you.
(Along with the news of the two members' elimination,)
(he receives two gems.)
Blue.
Okay.
(What's the secret of Jong Kook,)
(who is collecting gems secretly?)
(Yesterday, Mok-dong SBS)
(Jong Kook meets the staff alone.)
Why only me?
There's only me for real?
(He suddenly feels uncomfortable.)
Only me?
- Jong Kook. - Yes.
Normally, you're the strongest at Name Tag Elimination.
(Jong Kook is the strongest at Name Tag Elimination.)
But once superpowers are involved,
(When superpowers are involved, he got eliminated fast.)
- you always struggle. - Right.
You and Suk Jin are the only ones who have never won...
(Only Suk Jin and Jong Kook have never won in a War of Superpowers.)
- War of Superpowers. - That's right.
Actually, you did even worse than Suk Jin did.
(He tells the harsh truth calmly.)
I was given a useless superpower every time.
(It's unfair.)
It only got in my way.
(One of the superpowers he had is Wi-Fi.)
Gary is outside.
He's outside.
(But the information he got was not very useful.)
I said I didn't need this many times.
(Wi-Fi only got in his way.)
- You're Wi-Fi. - I said it many times.
(His true superpower comes from his muscles.)
(All his superpowers were useless.)
I'm making you feel better.
I'm telling you something important.
(Every time, he just ended up being cute.)
All of them were useless.
So...
we've concluded that you're not good with superpowers...
and deprived you of all superpowers.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
You've never given me any superpowers anyway.
(You've never given me any superpowers anyway.)
- But you'd still want to fight. - Right.
(He can't just suffer because of his incompetency.)
Tomorrow,
you'll be a human weapon hidden among those with superpowers.
(He'll be a human weapon hidden among those with superpowers.)
You'll use your physical strength to rip off others' name tags.
(Eliminate those with superpowers using your physical strength.)
(It's his chance to get back at them and crush their confidence.)
As the freshman representative,
(The human weapon, Jong Kook, sneaks into Superpower School.)
- Suk Jin will recite a pledge. - It feels real.
- Seniors, please sit down. - Okay.
Here. Get the chairs.
(But there were...)
(only 4 chairs for seniors.)
(He gets his own chair.)
Here.
Hi, Sang Yeob. Here's one more.
(As he was not invited, he made all the preparation by himself.)
- The microphone... - I'm making a pledge.
(Jong Kook pretended to be a senior at the school.)
You don't know what that is?
(When the War of Superpowers began,)
This is dangerous.
(he damaged the school's list of lost items.)
(1 invisibility cloak and 1 communication device are missing.)
(His walkie-talkie and cloak were...)
(stolen from the school.)
You'll be a human weapon hidden among those with superpowers.
(The human weapon has been waiting for his moment.)
You'll use your physical strength to rip off others' name tags.
- There's one condition. - What is it?
(There's one condition to eliminate those with superpowers.)
Every time a person with a superpower is eliminated,
(Every time a person with a superpower is eliminated,)
(he'll receive a gem.)
you'll receive a gem.
The gems you receive will be kept in the human weapon's room.
(He must keep those gems in the human weapon's room.)
Okay.
Once you've collected five gems,
(Once he's collected five gems,)
you can start eliminating those with superpowers.
(he can start eliminating those with superpowers.)
Once I've collected five?
(He can get into action...)
(when 5 members are out.)
On card number 3, I'll write down 4.
(He gave away superpower points because he didn't need them.)
- Are you sure? - Of course. You promised, remember?
(He won everyone's trust by pretending to be generous.)
You guys are all nice.
(Even when his prey came near...)
- Your time begins now. - Jong Kook!
Let's eliminate him together!
You should eliminate him.
(He waited for his moment.)
I can't eliminate him anyway.
(I can't eliminate him anyway.)
(When everyone else was given a superpower...)
Gosh, this is...
What's this?
Please read out your fake superpower.
(Please read out your fake superpower.)
(He pretended...)
"You are the Sorcerer of Five Senses."
(that his superpower was Wi-Fi.)
"It will let you eavesdrop for three minutes..."
"and find out a member's superpower."
I don't have to eavesdrop.
There's no point.
I'm only human.
Why can't they eliminate each other faster?
(Two more people need to be eliminated for him to compete.)
Gosh.
(Jae Suk who has no idea...)
Hey.
Let's eliminate Suk Jin first.
(wants to eliminate Suk Jin first.)
Let's eliminate him.
(Se Chan can use his superpower once.)
- We're a team now. - Yes.
Let's go.
(Their target is the Goryeo beggar, Suk Jin.)
You should be more into it.
(But...)
(Jae Suk is shot with a poison needle again.)
(It's almost like he's collecting them.)
You've been shot by the Poison Needle Sorcerer.
In 15 seconds, you'll freeze for 30 seconds.
(Poison Needle Sorcerer?)
(Time left until the poison needle comes into effect)
- 15, 14, 13... - Again?
- You... - Let's run!
(Flustered)
10, 9, 8, 7...
(Seeing him run away is getting old.)
- This is my last chance. - How could you do this?
- I have to eliminate him. - How could you?
- How could you... - Now.
- Se Chan... - This is my last chance.
(He hunts down Ttuk-nos with the help of Invisible Man.)
Lift him. 1, 2, 3.
Lift him. We have to.
1, 2, 3. This is my last chance.
- He's out. - It's over.
(Ripping off)
- This is my last chance. - It's over.
(Jae Suk is out.)
You filthy jerks.
You little...
- Jae Suk is out. - Jae Suk is out.
(He can't believe he got shot by poison needle 3 times.)
Hey, how could you do this?
I shot you three times.
Hey.
(I can't believe I thought we were allies.)
Gosh.
Can you see me?
Yes, I can.
You can't see me.
- You can't see me. - Gosh.
(This is so annoying.)
This is unbelievable.
You shot 3 out of 4 needles at me?
(Poison Needle Sorcerer did it after 3 backstabbings.)
Jae Suk, I had no choice.
Where should I go?
(The news makes someone happy.)
Jae Suk is out.
Wait a minute, I'm starting to have hope.
(Human weapon Jong Kook is cheerful.)
I'm starting to...
(It's time to get ready.)
I'm starting to have hope.
(After Jae Suk's elimination,)
(he receives the fourth gem.)
Okay.
There you go.
(Once he receives another gem,)
(the human weapon can get into action.)
(Just then...)
Sang Yeob is out.
(Sang Yeob is out.)
(Sang Yeob is out?)
You'll be given one more gem and a ring.
(Finally,)
(five members are out.)
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo eliminated Sang Yeob together.)
Kwang Soo!
Sang Yeob is out.
(While those with superpowers are distracted...)
(The human weapon is about to get into action.)
Finally.
(Jong Kook's goal is to win without any superpowers.)
(He is given the fifth gem.)
All right.
(The human weapon is in action.)
Once you've collected five gems,
(He can now hunt down those with superpowers.)
you can start eliminating those with superpowers.
(The school's intruder alarm goes off.)
What's going on?
There's an intruder in the school.
- There's an intruder in the school. - An intruder?
There's another person?
- An intruder? - Kwang Soo.
- What's going on? - Who's the intruder?
(Isn't this a War of Superpowers?)
There's an intruder.
Did someone use a superpower to bring someone in?
(There's an intruder warning when half of them are eliminated.)
- No. - Or did someone just show up?
Someone broke into the school.
There's an intruder in the school.
- What does that mean? - There's another person?
- Is it someone new? - I know. Who could it be?
Should I get ready to go back out there?
What are you talking about?
(Why are you preparing to go out?)
Why are you preparing to go out, Han Na?
Is it time for us to step up?
(Han Na...)
There's no place for us to go.
(She still has her chances.)
Oh, so we're completely done.
(Meanwhile, Haha is...)
(He needs to find the ticket to Room of Reinforcement.)
I'm sorry, sir.
They're looking at me.
(Haha takes a look around.)
(He finds the list of lost items that Jong Kook ripped.)
Someone ripped this, right?
There is an intruder.
(They have no idea as Jong Kook removed all evidence.)
An intruder. There's an intruder.
Who is the intruder?
Hold on. How can I use this? Hold on.
From my head to my toes
(Suk Jin is enjoying his last past life.)
Kwang Soo has an invisibility cloak.
You've been summoned...
- to the Room of Reinforcement. - I have?
- Okay. - Please follow us to the room.
(Someone summoned Suk Jin.)
Where is the Room of Reinforcement?
It's in the main building.
(He can get one more past life if he succeeds in this mission.)
The cafeteria?
How nice.
I should go first.
(He enters the Room of Reinforcement in hopes for better past life.)
(Soon after, the person who invited him to the room enters.)
(The person who invited him was...)
- Okay. - Okay. Thank you.
(Kim Jong Kook.)
Suk Jin.
(The human weapon summoned Suk Jin with the ticket he found.)
Those with superpowers cannot...
(The reason why he called Suk Jin to the Room of Reinforcement is...)
rip name tags here.
(the Room of Reinforcement is a safe zone for them.)
(Warning: This is the Room of Reinforcement.)
(Those with superpowers cannot rip name tags here.)
Those with superpowers cannot...
(However, the human weapon, Jong Kook,)
(can rip off name tags as he doesn't have a superpower.)
rip name tags here.
(That's why Suk Jin, who dreams of a new life...)
- Did you get it? - No, not yet.
- Okay. - Yes!
What was that?
- Did you get it? - No, not yet.
(was eliminated in the Room of Reinforcement.)
- Okay. - Yes!
Okay.
- Why? - He's out.
But this is the Room of Reinforcement.
You can't rip off name tags here.
(Those with superpowers can't rip each other's name tags.)
The intruder of Superpower School, the human weapon,
- has started to move. - What?
(The human weapon?)
The intruder of Superpower School, the human weapon,
(Frozen)
has started to move.
He must be the human weapon.
I'm the human weapon.
I'm a human being who doesn't have a superpower.
You're a human being,
(Jong Kook eliminates Suk Jin.)
who defeats...
- those with superpowers? - Yes.
The intruder of Superpower School, the human weapon,
has started to move.
Who's the human weapon?
I have a feeling they'll know that it's me.
Because nobody knows my superpower.
Jong Kook. I found the list of lost items.
(At that moment, Haha approaches Jong Kook.)
- What is that? - Come down here.
(Haha found the list of lost items?)
- What? - You have to trust me.
I'm the original. Jong Kook.
(At the news that Haha found the list of lost items,)
- Okay. - We're brothers, remember?
(Jong Kook quickly goes down to meet them.)
- Come down. - Okay. Just wait.
I have chills.
My gosh.
This is dangerous.
- Jong Kook. - What's going on?
(Acting)
Your superpower is...
(The human weapon Jong Kook is about to rip their name tags.)
- You have superpowers, right? - Right.
- Take a look. - Okay.
Remember how we all wore cloaks during the opening?
(Haha finds out that a cape went missing.)
- Right. - Take a look.
One of the cloaks is missing. It says one is lost.
What did they say about the human weapon?
(Should I rip his name tag?)
- They said they intruded, right? - Right.
There's a human among us.
(Among us...)
(Haha, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan, who have powers, are left.)
(Jong Kook is in trouble if he gets caught now.)
This punk... Oh, my.
I mean, this person.
I'm sorry. I got overexcited.
(I'm sorry.)
I felt victimized.
This young, little kid...
(Haha is now suspecting someone else.)
stole a cloak and entered the school while pretending he has powers.
(Spot on)
- But look. - Who could it be?
(Jong Kook acts as if he is angry.)
- You have superpowers, right? - Honestly...
- Right. - I have superpowers too.
What was my chant again?
Was it "Tiramisu"?
What was it again? Anyways.
(Captain Tiramisu has bad memories.)
- I have this, my superpower. - Okay.
- And Kwang Soo is invisible. - Right.
(Haha, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo all have worthy superpowers.)
Then who's left?
- Does the last person have a power? - Se Chan?
(Shameless)
- Se Chan has a water gun. - All he has is a water gun.
- That's just a gun. - Okay.
(Jong Kook can't help but smile...)
All he has is that water gun,
(at Haha's wrong guesses.)
but we were fighting among ourselves.
And you were won over by him!
He's fake!
Let's eliminate him.
What is this?
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo...)
This isn't it. What is it?
(He finds something with an R Sticker on it.)
It's a certificate of admission.
(Is it a 2019 Superpower School certificate of admission?)
Haha.
(It looks like the certificate of admission for the 2nd years.)
Ji Hyo.
Jae Suk.
(Certificate of Admission, Name: Kim Jong Kook)
What?
(What?)
Jong Kook's certificate doesn't have a stamp on it.
(There is a stamp marked on four of the certificates.)
(However, Jong Kook's certificate does not have a stamp on it.)
Jong Kook's certificate doesn't have a stamp on it.
I just got chills.
(Jong Kook is the human weapon!)
Jong Kook is the human weapon.
I have to let the others know...
before anyone else gets eliminated.
(Meanwhile, clueless Se Chan approaches Haha and Jong Kook.)
- Hey. - Yes?
Come here.
- Hey, Yang Se Chan. - Come here.
- Yes? - My goodness, Yang Se Chan.
(Jong Kook plans to eliminate Se Chan first before Haha.)
Come here. Stand right here.
- Are you starting again? - I said, stand over there!
(Leisurely)
Why? What's wrong?
You were entrusted with something big after 10 years, weren't you?
(You...)
Who was?
They're going to entrust someone like me...
with a big project like this? That makes no sense.
- Do you know why you're fake? - Why is that?
Jong Kook and I...
have been friends for over 20 years, you punk.
You fake punk.
(You're the fake intruder who came in between us.)
- Big brother! - Okay.
Do you want to go?
(Do you want a taste of my poison needles?)
Se Chan, if you've enjoyed yourself, it's time to sacrifice yourself.
(Jong Kook attacks Se Chan based on Haha's trust.)
But Jong Kook, seriously...
I will sacrifice myself. I will.
- I'll make it quick. - Do it so there will be a CG on it.
(He gives up.)
Please put some graphics on my name tag.
(Is it his will?)
(Due to the work overload of the CG team,)
(we couldn't fulfill Se Chan's dying wish.)
(Poison Needle Sorcerer, out)
- Let me see. - I'm nothing.
(Haha is flustered to find out that Se Chan's name tag is empty.)
Then you should've told us that you weren't more aggressively.
- I told you I wasn't. - What is going on here?
(It's now Haha's turn!)
Are you saying it's the Invisible Man?
(He's making a wrong guess.)
- It must be Kwang Soo. - The human weapon is on the move.
Jong Kook. Hold on.
- Hold on. - Be careful.
(Goosebumps)
Hold on. Is it you?
Are you insane?
(Laughing)
He just said that the human is on the move!
Haha.
(Kwang Soo appears.)
- Do you know who the intruder is? - Who is it?
(Haha!)
Do you know who the intruder is?
(Flustered)
Who is it?
It's Jong Kook.
What are you saying?
- It's Jong Kook. - What are you saying?
You're really...
(Completely flustered)
- I found a hint. - Let me see.
- What hint? - I took a picture of it...
because I knew you wouldn't believe me.
(The human weapon faces a decisive crisis.)
Haha, get ready.
(The battle will look very different...)
(according to Haha's choice.)
(Who will be the final winner?)
I will tell you the results.
(The race is over.)
The 10th anniversary War of Superpowers: The End Game...
(The End Game marked the 10th anniversary of the show.)
was a chance for Jong Kook,
who always got low rankings...
(Jong Kook, who usually didn't do well in superpower races,)
- during superpower races, - Right.
(acted as the human weapon.)
to have no superpowers and participate in the race.
- He was just a human? - But...
- I didn't have anything today, - Really?
(He could only start after 5 superpowers were out.)
and I had to wait until five members were eliminated.
You didn't have anything, but you were terrifying with the gloves on.
(Anyway...)
- I was at a serious disadvantage. - In the end,
Haha and Kwang Soo...
(Jong Kook managed to survive among those with superpowers.)
In the end, Haha and Kwang Soo...
(What were the results of the final match among the last three members?)
ripped off Jong Kook's name tag, and those with superpowers won.
(Haha and Kwang Soo win.)
We won because we didn't betray each other.
ripped off Jong Kook's name tag...
(The human weapon lost.)
(Team Superpowers won...)
Seriously?
(thanks to Haha and Kwang Soo.)
- I feel like... - I'm so touched.
I'm going to cry.
(Earlier, Haha and Kwang Soo were facing off with Jong Kook.)
Kim Jong Kook, Gravity!
(Haha used his last chance of superpower.)
(The 2 scaredy cats joined forces.)
Grab him!
(However, the human weapon is a strong match.)
(The two of them just barely ripped off his name tag.)
- I feel like... - I'm so touched.
(They're overly emotional, and they praise themselves.)
I'm going to cry.
- These weasels... - I'm serious...
I'm serious today.
(I can't believe I lost to those two.)
- What about me? - You used 3 of your 4 powers on me?
So the punishment that Jong Kook must do for losing the race...
during the 10th anniversary live broadcast is...
What is it?
(What is the punishment that must be done during the live broadcast?)
He must put on a costume.
Oh, my.
During a live broadcast?
(He needs to put on a costume during a live broadcast.)
He will be joined by another member who will be chosen next week,
(He will go on the show with the costume...)
and the two of them must put on a costume for the live broadcast.
(with another member selected from next week.)
Two people? So someone else will also do it.
Thank goodness for now.
- I had no idea. - Okay.
Over the course of 10 years,
the eight of you... I'm sorry. He was yawning.
- Why are you yawning now? - What are you doing?
I'm sorry. He was yawning.
(He just yawned for everyone to see.)
- Why are you yawning now? - What are you doing?
(He is too tired from his journeys to his past lives.)
- But... - Why are you yawning?
I know I need to put on a costume as a penalty,
but what about Suk Jin, who had to dress up four times today?
I'm exhausted after living three lifetimes.
(He can't get over the eternal cycle of life.)
The candidates for Jong Kook's costume punishment are...
(List of costumes for Jong Kook)
one of each of your costumes in the past, which you will suggest,
(He'll choose 1 out of costumes that members wore before...)
and four new ones suggested by the crew.
(and the 4 new ones that production crews introduced.)
You must choose 1 of the 12.
- I think they'll be bad. - Suggest one of your past costumes.
- Something that Jong Kook could do. - Okay.
The doll? That's too weak.
(They wore many costumes.)
- A giraffe is too weak. - A mummy's not good enough.
I'll choose the llama.
(They each cautiously pick one.)
- What about the beggar? - I chose the llama.
I choose Kaonashi.
(Which costumes will Jong Kook get to wear?)
I choose Yondu.
(The costumes chosen by the members, the costumes chosen by the staff)
Yondu is a good one.
Okay. Jong Kook, please choose one.
Okay.
Are you going to do the one you choose?
(This is the big data of costumes accumulated over 10 years.)
What is it?
(Among the many costumes, which one will be chosen for Jong Kook?)
Are you going to do the one you choose?
- What is it? - It's Kaonashi.
(This is the best out of all of them.)
This is it. Okay!
This one is not that bad.
- This is not that bad. - This is not that bad.
(That's a shame.)
Kaonashi.
- Okay. - Kaonashi is cute.
(That's a shame.)
I wanted to do something cute.
Are we choosing another person next week?
(One more member will be chosen next week.)
- Yes, that's right. - Okay. Good.
Please say something, Sang Yeob.
(Sang Yeob and Han Na joined to celebrate 10th anniversary.)
It's been a while since I came, and I had a lot of fun.
Please invite me more often.
Okay.
(Come visit us often.)
Okay, Kang Han Na.
I'm sad because I couldn't dance two more times.
- But thanks for letting me dance. - Dance before we end.
(If that's the case...)
- Go for it. - Can I do that?
- If you want to, go ahead. - Do it.
(Should I?)
- It's your last chance. - I hope you trust me
(She shows her final charming dance.)
This was it.
- This is her superpower. - Her moves are loose.
Does it make sense that one would go blind from watching this?
- Her moves are loose. - Of course, you'd go blind.
Her moves are loose.
Congratulations on your 10th anniversary, Running Man.
(Thanks to Lee Sang Yeob and Kang Han Na for joining us today.)
(2020 Reincarnation Special is back.)
Part two of the race that viewers wanted to see.
It's the Reincarnation episode.
(The 2nd episode: Reincarnation)
- Reincarnation? - Reincarnation?
The first Reincarnation Camp.
(ZICO, Lee Do Hyun. SUN MI, Cho Sae Ho)
- ZICO. - All right!
- In 2017. - 2013.
(The members are reincarnated at different time periods.)
It was 10 years ago.
(While they enjoy camping at peace,)
- What? - Is it a siren or what?
- My gosh. - I'm so startled.
(a mystery siren goes off.)
We're locked.
(There's a secret...)
(behind the reincarnation camp?)
Only two people can get out of here.
- I said no. - I saw it. I know who it is.
(Doubt and fear keep growing up with mysterious accidents.)
He's weird.
You better be careful.
- There are 6 of us left. - This is crazy.
(The number of survivors keeps decreasing.)
Only six of us are left.
"By 4pm."
(They've got a limited time.)
- It's 1:53pm now. - We have to find the ticket now.
(They have to find out the secret of reincarnation.)
It's not me.
(The reincarnation special is back.)
What? This is crazy.
(How would it end?)
I think we should find out the secret of reincarnation.
(2020 Reincarnation Camp)