(It's February, the second month of 2021.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - What is this?
(8 luxurious silver stainless trays greet the members.)
- Is it our breakfast? - Hello.
- Hello. - I guess we get to pick something.
I pick number three.
- I'll go with number 8. - I want number 3.
(They shout their favorite numbers.)
- All right. - I'll pick number three.
I want number four.
Why do you like number eight so much?
(What's the secret of 8 silver trays?)
Eight is my favorite number.
I think Haha is doing some mission alone.
He's wearing modernized hanbok.
(The dirty mustache is patriotic.)
Do you want to introduce Korean culture to the world?
Haha. Your fashion is...
quite rambling these days.
When you wear hanbok like that, you should change your hairstyle...
like an aristocrat.
It looks better now.
(The old fossil is summoned.)
- Lord Haha. - His hat...
- Hey. - All right.
"Is anyone there?"
- Good. - Like an aristocrat.
He's a dad and 42 years old now.
And this is what he's doing.
I'm 43.
(The cutest 43-year-old in the world)
- Are you 43? - That's better.
Jae Suk, we have to talk about this. Look.
He dyed his mullet.
- Will you let it slide? - What?
("Actor Lee Kwang Soo Becomes the Talk for Dying His Back Hair")
- He dyed his hair here. - No.
Will you let it slide or what?
- I did it just a little. - Will you let it go?
It turns out his new movie was just an excuse.
He actually thinks this looks cool.
I just became attached to it over time.
(He fell in love with his back hair.)
- I just tried it before I cut it. - This isn't right.
He dyed his hair for real.
(Frowning)
It's so annoying.
You should wear it in a pigtail.
- What? - Wear it in a pigtail.
I'm so disappointed that you said that.
I'm really happy.
You just said you liked my hair in the car.
(Quick change in attitude)
You should wear my pants and a pigtail together.
(The collaboration of modern hanbok and a pigtail ribbon)
Gosh, I hate it.
- We're done. - We're done.
(They warm up their tongues by making fun of Kwang Soo.)
Today,
to celebrate midwinter,
we got you a little something.
- I'm nervous though. - I hope it's a good thing.
- It won't be fun if you all get it. - Only two?
Six of them have different gifts in them.
But two of them are duds.
Really?
I want you to stand behind the table.
(Everyone will choose a number...)
And you all will open your gifts together.
(and open it at once.)
- Okay. - I will...
- I'll pick what's left. - I pick number three.
(Rushing)
- I want number eight. - I'll have what's left.
- I'll just get what's left. - I want number four.
- Number two. - I'll get what's left.
- No. - Then I'll go with number one.
- What do you want? - I'll pick number two.
- I want number 4. - I pick number 7.
(He sits in number 7 as So Min pushes him away.)
Se Chan likes number eight.
Please open your gifts on the count of three.
(Half unwillingly, they all select a number.)
- All right. - One.
(They can predict their luck for today with the gifts.)
Two.
(Who will get the two duds?)
Three.
(Kwang Soo and So Min lost the draw.)
(It's a 100 percent manual squirt gun.)
This is my favorite, hotteok.
I'm so lucky.
All right.
(The water gun doesn't plan to stop.)
- This is amazing. - All right.
(She got into trouble after stealing Se Chan's choice.)
- Look at you. - This is amazing.
(It serves him right.)
I knew you would pick number eight.
I didn't know they would squirt water guns from in there.
(The water gun ran out of water.)
(After checking who it is,)
- Hyeong Gu. - Hey.
(he tries to punish him for squirting a water gun.)
Don't pull his hair.
(He pulls out his head...)
(and slaps him in the face.)
(Hyeong Gu, playing multiple roles, he's in charge of water guns today.)
(He's getting slapped after squirting a water gun.)
Hyeong Gu.
(After punishing, he seals him.)
That's enough.
You're doing all sorts of things.
(Hyeong Gu)
I didn't know number eight would be a dud.
(The two duds of the day)
The gift we prepared for you is six kinds of snacks for winter.
Yes! It's hotteok.
(Hot hotteok, steamed bun, sweet potato,)
- It's still steaming. - Right.
(roasted chestnuts, fish-shaped bun, and tangerine)
It's still warm.
- Look at this. - This is warm too.
(On top of a hot steamed bun,)
(a fish-shaped bun is a bonus.)
Please listen to the rules while enjoying the snacks.
(That looks delicious.)
Today, we will have a New Year Driving Out Bad Luck Race...
with a horrible penalty.
- What is the penalty now? - I'm curious what it is.
Those who just picked duds have been...
(Kwang Soo and So Min picked a dud.)
- selected as Penalty Men. - Okay.
(They'll become the Penalty Men.)
And there will be more Penalty Men after the missions.
(Through missions,)
(more Penalty Men will be added.)
Is it settled already? From the beginning?
(Penalty Man)
It's not decided yet, but you are highly likely to get a penalty.
Can I just get the penalty and go home?
I woke up two hours early to go to a hair salon this morning.
(Pleased)
We will have three guests soon.
- Do we have guests today? - They don't know...
we picked the first Penalty Men during the opening.
(The guests aren't aware that the 1st Penalty Men...)
(are selected in the opening.)
They just think they'll be picking team members as a team leader.
(They believe they pick the penalty men from their teams.)
Do you see the chairs for the king over there?
We will have these chairs for them.
(Among the three guest seats,)
And the one on the right will fall apart.
(the right chair is the dud.)
The guest who picks this chair will start as a Penalty Man.
(The guest who picks the dud chair will become a Penalty Man.)
This is fun.
Can't you tell it's a dud?
(Dud)
You can't tell. It must be fun.
Then we will bring in the guests.
(The guest who will be extremely welcomed is...)
Yes!
(Who are they?)
Hello.
(3 actors walk with short and quick steps.)
- He's Lee Sang Yi. - Sang Yi.
(Lee Sang Yi)
Why? Did you do something wrong again?
(He was the baseball coach in "When the Camellia Blooms".)
Did someone sue you? Pil Gu, don't take your eyes off the ball.
(He caught people's eye playing a comic role.)
Princess Diana wants to sue you?
(And he became a nation's beloved brother-in-law in "Once Again".)
I like you.
That's how much...
(Lee Sang Yi even won the Best Male Rookie Award.)
Da Hee means to me.
- Hello, Eun Jin. - Hello.
(Ahn Eun Jin)
This is an emergency. Please get me an operating room.
(She was a 2nd year resident in "Hospital Playlist".)
The kid is about to die. Please hurry.
Actually, I think...
(With her great acting skills from plays and musicals,)
(Ahn Eun Jin shows her strong presence.)
you've been quite condescending these days.
And we have Yoon Kyung here.
(Bae Yoon Kyung)
(She was the most discussed cast in "Heart Signal Season 1".)
(And now she's establishing her presence as an actress.)
- It breaks my heart. - You don't seem hurt at all.
(She did many dramas like "Record of Youth" and "Hi Bye Mama!".)
They are Bae Yoon Kyung, Ahn Eun Jin, and Lee Sang Yi.
(Ahn Eun Jin, Bae Yoon Kyung, Lee Sang Yi)
- Great. - Hello.
(The 3 rising stars are in a variety show.)
So, Sang Yi.
(The first person to introduce is Lee Sang Yi.)
Jong Kook would be excited to hear this.
- Why? - He's from Anyang.
(Sang Yi's from Anyang.)
- He's from Anyang. - Anyang?
(Befuddled)
- Come here. - Is that true? Welcome.
(He greets a friend from Anyang...)
(He greets a friend from Anyang with a big hug.)
Is he from Anyang?
Congratulations.
- This is great. - Congratulations.
(Guests from Anyang get the highest power in Running Man.)
Things will be easy for him today.
- My gosh. - Regionalism and school relations.
This darn world runs on school relations and regionalism.
We have to get rid of the bad custom.
He's really happy to hear that.
He always cares about regionalism and school relations.
(The king of school and regional ties)
And he's not ashamed of it at all.
And he cares about regionalism the most.
(The best of all is the regional ties.)
I thought he seemed somewhat familiar.
I kept saying that, right? "He seems familiar."
(He likes Sang Yi the best.)
Actually, Jong Kook was eating sweet potatoes.
That's nice.
(Before he found out that Sang Yi is from Anyang,)
(he only cared about his sweet potatoes.)
He's from Anyang.
(As soon as he says he's from Anyang,)
(he became Jong Kook's favorite.)
- Really? - Come here.
(Anyang cartel)
Is he from Anyang?
- He's even blushing. - Anyang is the best.
(He suddenly blushed.)
Like I said before, Jong Kook cares...
(Jong Kook builds a relationship on regionalism without question.)
- a lot about regionalism. - Exactly.
He really does.
Although this is his first time on Running Man,
(Sang Yi)
Sang Yi is fitting in well already.
(Soft landing)
Congratulations.
- You're in Jong Kook's arms. - Congratulations.
(Polite)
Seriously.
Things will be easy for you.
- Anyang. - He's got the face of Anyang.
Anyang.
Sang Yi is also a musical actor.
He must have a lot of talents.
We have to hear him sing.
- I watched his performance. - What?
- I watched his performance. - Really?
Sang Yi performed at MONNI's concert.
(Sang Yi appeared in MONNI's music drama concert.)
- I watched it. - Really?
- In Samseong-dong? - Yes.
Do you know the members of MONNI?
Yes. I know the drummer.
She knows a lot of musicians.
(Laughing)
I see.
She knows a lot of band members.
(She's got the sensitivity of session players.)
She knows a lot of musicians.
(Performance tie after school and regional ties)
She's intimate with many musicians.
So Min is acquainted with a lot of musicians.
(Feeling proud)
I did a musical with Ahn Eun Jin.
Eun Jin? What was the musical?
(Is it a new tie?)
- They are acquainted. - We did a musical together.
- He's a friend from college. - We went to the same college.
I see.
(As she saw Sang Yi get cheers just because he's from Anyang...)
Is he from Anyang?
Isn't he amazing? He's my friend from college.
Are you two close?
We went to college together.
(She felt pressured from watching her colleague doing well.)
He really is amazing.
Sang Yi prepared a song and will play the acoustic guitar.
(Without knowing how she feels,)
(Sang Yi prepared a guitar and a song.)
- I want to watch it. - That's what So Min likes.
I want to hear him sing.
He sings really well.
- He plays the guitar? - Sang Yi was...
the winner of a YouTube Star UCC contest.
- What? - UCC?
It's "Rainism" of Anyang Arts High School.
(The UCC star is approved by his colleague.)
- He was the winner. - "Rainism"?
Sang Yi was quite popular.
He's amazing. And he was the student representative.
The student representative?
- The student representative? - He was a UCC star.
So Min is taking a few steps forward.
(So Min's getting ready to dance to the acoustic guitar.)
- All of a sudden. - She's revving up.
- She keeps coming closer. - Because...
- This is what So Min likes. - So Min likes stuff like this.
(Sang Yi knows what Jong Kook and So Min like.)
This is her favorite.
I love it.
I'll sing a little.
(How are Sang Yi's singing and guitar skills?)
Okay.
1, 2, 3, and go.
(Excited)
- He's got great skills. - This is nice.
(Skillful guitar-playing...)
He's got a sweet voice.
This is small, but I gave it a lot of thought
(Skillful guitar-playing with a baritone voice)
This is my gift for you
This is like "K-Pop Star".
Please accept it
Just take it
(He's a student representative playing the guitar.)
(They feel like they are on a school trip.)
2 times 1 is 2, 2 times 2 is 4, 2 times 4 is 8
- 2 times 2 is 4, 2 times 4 is 8 - He's singing "Iguana".
This is "Iguana".
(She loves the song, so she approaches him slowly.)
You should go close to him.
2 times 8 is 16, iguana
- 2 times 1 is 2, 2 times 2 is 4 - This is fun.
(Getting ready)
- 2 times 4 is 8 - She likes it.
(She moves her limbs to the rhythm of the acoustic guitar.)
- This is her favorite. - 2 times 5 is 10
2 times 6 is 12, 2 times 7 is 14, 2 times 8 is 16
Iguana
(Despite her dance, he shows off his singing skills.)
Yes!
I've never heard this song before.
It's "Iguana". He sang "Iguana"!
(Excited)
- I can't believe it. - How do you know this song?
I listened to "Iguana" on my way here today.
- Today? - Yes.
You think you two are meant for each other, right?
- It's just a coincidence. - Right.
(So it was a coincidence?)
- Yes, it's a coincidence. - So just calm down.
He sounded great...
- but her weird dance ruined it. - Yes, she danced like this.
(They break out of character because of Pumbaa.)
- What's wrong with your dance? - What?
I just think the lyrics are cute.
(She's still stuck on "Iguana".)
It was just like Eun Jin said.
- Yes. - He was popular back then, right?
Yes, he was very popular.
He really is talented.
- I saw him play for about 10 years. - Is that so?
- You mean this pattern? - Yes.
- I see. - So I'm familiar with his pattern.
(Eun Jin is familiar with his pattern.)
It's good to see various performances for the opening...
(Bickering)
- Excuse me. - I'm sorry.
Well, excuse me.
Are you his ex-girlfriend?
(Having a doubt for her detailed explanation)
I think it's possible.
- You know too much about him. - Things are cool between them.
(Her detailed explanation makes it natural to misunderstand.)
- Did you date each other? - No.
It's just because we went to the same school.
- We practically grew up together. - We were close.
We know everything about each other.
(They've gone through a lot together.)
- Sadly, yes. - Seriously.
We were in the same class and we even performed together.
- We're kind of tired of each other. - I see.
(Love Frog's radar starts working.)
So we've learned...
a lot about Lee Sang Yi.
(Sang Yi's performance ended in great success.)
No guest ever played the guitar and sang for the opening before.
I'm sure he would've felt sad if you hadn't asked him to do it.
(Cutting in)
See? She knows too much.
(Giggling)
- You're right. - Close enough to be his ex.
- You two went out, didn't you? - I'm sure of it.
I'm sure they dated.
You two went out, right?
Yes, they're close.
(We knew it was reasonable doubt.)
- What did I tell you? - She knows too much.
It's so obvious, right?
- I'll ask you this. - Okay.
- I didn't think you did. - Okay.
- But... - I'm sorry.
Are you trying to support him as his ex-girlfriend?
- That's right. - I knew it.
(Let's just roll with it.)
- She said yes. - So she wants to support him.
(She turned from an ex-girlfriend to an assistant.)
- She said yes. - She's a supporter.
She's supporting him as his ex-girlfriend.
I didn't plan to, but it happened.
(Given up)
- Please give him a big hand. - Yes.
(Sang Yi's introduction ends.)
He's very charming.
Next is Bae Yoon Kyung.
(The next guest is Yoon Kyung.)
And he cares about regionalism the most.
(After seeing Sang Yi's Anyang connection,)
I thought he seemed somewhat familiar.
(she contemplates.)
We know everything about each other.
(Stuck between their school connections,)
Sadly, yes.
(she tried to think of all the connections she has.)
We were in the same class and we even performed together.
We're kind of tired of each other.
So Yoon Kyung.
Do you personally know anyone here?
Have you ever bumped into anyone before?
(Is there an unknown connection who could help her?)
I've been to Kwang Soo's movie preview.
- You have? - Which movie?
(She relates to Kwang Soo thanks to a movie preview.)
"Inseparable Bros".
- Really? - Right.
- We've been to that one. - Yes, we have.
We've been there too.
Right, "Inseparable Bros".
I left in the middle because of a soccer game.
- Right, you did. - So I don't know how it ends.
- That's why I don't know the end. - Right.
(Disappointed)
How could you?
He really left in the middle. Did you watch it later?
(It was an open ending only to Jong Kook.)
No, I didn't.
I tried to send him a thank you message after the premiere.
But then I saw a picture of him playing soccer on his Instagram.
So I knew he went to play soccer.
I saw him at the premiere but he went to play soccer.
(But he definitely came to watch the film...)
So schedule the premiere earlier next time.
Because I have soccer games at that time.
(His workouts always come first.)
I actually saw Ji Hyo too.
- Where did you see Ji Hyo? - Me?
At Ms. Hong Da's wedding.
- Who? - In Jeonju?
- Yes, in Jeonju. - In Jeonju?
- In Jeonju? - You saw her in Jeonju?
(She saw Ji Hyo, who always stays at home, in Jeonju ?)
- Is that so? - Who is she?
She's my hairdresser.
Ji Hyo hosted the wedding for her hairdresser.
- Yes, I hosted the wedding. - Ji Hyo hosted the wedding?
Oh, really?
Seriously?
(What?)
Gosh.
Ji Hyo, you hosted the wedding?
(They can't believe what they heard.)
- You did? - Seriously?
- My goodness. - You?
- I can't believe it. - Why?
- She hosted the wedding? - You did?
(No one can believe Ji Hyo hosted a wedding.)
How did that happen?
Why didn't you tell us about it?
So how did it go?
It went well.
(And she says it went well?)
I've never heard that Ji Hyo hosted someone's wedding.
- I can't believe it. - Amazing.
(She learned how to host after 11 years on Running Man.)
You host weddings too?
Gosh, you're so cool.
Okay, it was Yoon Kyung.
Next is Ahn Eun Jin.
(After the surprising news, they move on to Eun Jin.)
Hello, everyone.
So you went to the same college as Sang Yi, right?
(Her alumnus gets nervous as well.)
Did she have a nickname in college?
(What was her nickname at school?)
It was "Angel Eun Duin".
She wanted everyone to call her "Angel".
- No. - She called herself "Angel"?
- That's not true. - You called yourself "Angel"?
- No, no. - You called yourself that?
It was my Buddy Buddy ID.
That's why they called me that.
(Angel Eun Duin)
Gosh, Buddy Buddy.
- I haven't heard it in a long time. - We're from the same generation.
(It's a long-lost feeling.)
- Gosh, Buddy Buddy. - That's why...
they called me "Angel Eun Duin".
- So it was your ID. - Yes.
Come on. It wasn't like that.
(Quarrelling)
- How was it like then? - You were like this.
You said, "I'm an angel. So call me Angel Eun Duin."
I was that cute in college?
- Yes. - So I was cute.
(What's with the atmosphere?)
What is this?
- My goodness. - I think...
- these two were... - Yes.
not really that close.
Maybe something went on between them.
(I think they were interested in each other.)
- Maybe a little. - Actually, I wasn't...
a very good student in college.
(No.)
But he was the class rep so he always told me to join things.
(He told her to come out?)
He was our first class representative.
He wanted us to be in all the meetings.
- He always called. - He was passionate.
So he sent you messages to attend the meetings?
I'm sure you're the only one who got those messages.
My goodness.
(Stop it!)
- I told you they didn't date. - Are you sure about that?
(Mr. Dirty Mustache is addicted to delusional romance.)
She said no.
Come on.
(Love Frog loved it.)
I love what you're insinuating.
It's like a teen drama.
So he sent her a message pretending everyone else got it.
- Right. - And he waited with flowers.
Yes, with the guitar.
(Even worse)
I love the story.
(The members are excited to hear about young people's love story.)
- Yes, ready to sing "Iguana". - I love the story.
Don't you think you're too excited?
(Getting excited about the storyline of "He Was Cool")
- I love this story. - You do, don't you?
Then he says, "You're the only one I asked to come."
So that's what happened.
- He waited alone. - Right.
Do you know what Eun Jin said?
"So that's what happened."
Give them a big hand, everyone.
(Their first introductions end filled with different connections.)
Before we start the race,
we'll divide you into teams.
Three guests will be the leaders in the first round.
(A fake rule)
(The hidden rule that the guests don't know about)
Do you see the chairs for the king over there?
We will have these chairs for them.
(Of the three chairs,)
And the one on the right will fall apart.
(the one on the right is a dud.)
The guest who picks this chair will start as a Penalty Man.
(The one sitting on the dud chair...)
(will get the penalty with Kwang Soo and So Min.)
This is fun.
The three guests will be the leaders in the first round.
(They have no idea.)
So all three of you should sit in these chairs for the leaders.
(Who will sit on the right chair?)
Please.
(They break the ice with the introduction...)
(and leads them to the game.)
You can choose the one you want.
Should we sit down?
Yes, Yoon Kyung, Sang Yi, and Eun Jin. Have a seat.
(They choose chairs without a doubt.)
(Who will do the honor of getting the penalty?)
(Sang Yi gets it.)
(He sat down confidently to become a team leader.)
(His image with all the effort breaks down at one go.)
My goodness.
So we're starting the game now?
(Goggling)
It's already started?
(A human slapstick by the school representative)
All right.
So the game has already started?
The game has already started?
(The Anyang local pretends to be okay, which is sad to see.)
How could you fall on your back like that?
So is this what this place is like?
- This wasn't that bad. - Okay.
(You have to keep doubting here.)
I guess Sang Yi was quite surprised.
It's 2021 New Year Driving Out Bad Luck Race,
(New Year Driving Out Bad Luck Race)
Take My Bad Luck Away.
(Take My Bad Luck Away)
Today, we'll let you know what the penalty is in advance.
(The penalty will be announced first today.)
Okay, what is it?
Like in the old days,
you'll go through a race under a large scale water bomb.
(The giant water bomb)
(A customized large water bomb)
- My goodness. - I really hate this.
Why is it always cold when we do something like this?
- Yes, it's cold. - It's so cold today.
The three chosen Penalty Men are on one team.
(Team Penalty Men)
And the rest of you will be divided into two teams.
(Team Eun Jin and Team Yoon Kyung)
So a total of three teams will compete in the race.
(The three teams will compete.)
(After every mission,)
After each mission,
one member of the losing team will be chosen...
(Team Penalty Men can bring one person from the last team.)
to be sent to Team Penalty.
And at the final race, Team Penalty will compete...
(The final race will be Team Penalty Men against a regular team.)
against the rest of the members.
So they'll get more members.
Through the races, Penalty Men will be able to switch teams.
(The members will be replaced by tearing name tags,)
Penalty Men will move around but at the last round,
(and the team with more Penalty Men loses at the end.)
the team with more Penalty Men will lose the race.
And Penalty Men in the losing team will get the penalty.
(Penalty Men of Team Penalty Men also gets the penalty.)
And there's a separate rule...
(There are also penalty tickets.)
of penalty tickets.
Every member will get 12 penalty tickets.
(They all start with 16 penalty tickets.)
You've just received the tickets.
So you have 4 numbers from 1 to 4 in the first digit...
and 4 numbers from 1 to 4 in the second digit.
Which means you have 16 tickets in total.
And through the missions,
(They can discard the tickets as much mission fund as they earn.)
we will give you mission funds according to the ranking.
You may use the funds to get rid of your penalty tickets.
(Anyone with the penalty ticket of the drawn number gets a penalty.)
Also, we will draw lots.
If you have the number we pick, you'll get the penalty.
All right.
(Today's penalty)
(The Penalty Men who lose in the final race and the ticket winners)
I should get rid of all the tickets then.
You're right.
Getting rid of the tickets is good?
(They have a lower chance of getting the penalty if they discard many.)
Three Penalty Men...
will divide the rest into two teams.
(Team Penalty Men, Team Eun Jin, and Team Yoon Kyung)
Each team will take a picture with their members.
A group picture?
Gosh, I wanted to use this.
(The product placement experts are ready at all times.)
Does each team get one?
2, 3.
(To save our production cost...)
Here we go. 1, 2.
Let's see. See more.
(So Min goes for a picture alone)
Portrait mode.
(Trying out different selfie functions)
There are so many functions. I'll lower it.
Here it is. Gosh.
(Following the selfie lover's lead,)
- You lowered it? - Check this out.
The background gets darker if I do this.
(they take a special selfie.)
- It's amazing. - It looks edited.
If you're done, you may change your clothes.
(They get changed and move to the first destination.)
- Haha, I'll take your picture. - Okay.
- Why don't you sit over there? - All right.
(Se Chan wants to capture Haha's younger moments.)
That's it.
Wait.
Ready?
(All wrinkles are visible.)
(He doesn't know Se Chan is filling the frame with his face.)
Yellow.
- That's it. - How is it?
(Expectant)
Check this out. I zoomed in 30 times.
Hey.
- What's this? - Just look.
(Mr. Dirty Mustache that you want to look closer)
My mustache really looks dirty.
This one is really nice.
(He's satisfied, and he goes to earn mission funds.)
Why isn't Suk Jin coming?
He's busy doing product placement.
But it won't help to promote the product at all.
(The term requires Suk Jin to not appear on the show?)
I guess they're taking a risk.
Actually...
Suk Jin is using the product.
But he's not using the camera.
Why are you taking it from far away?
(They are taking a photo, but it's a group photo.)
- Suk Jin. - Hey!
(Very far from the subject)
- Jong Kook. - 1, 2, 3.
(He takes it from afar.)
Even if it's far,
pretty people will look pretty in the picture.
(Deleting Suk Jin)
- Did you only get them in the shot? - No.
(Are you...)
But the camera is facing that way.
How can I only get them in the shot when I'm so far away?
(Yes, I only took the two of them.)
Okay. Does it look good?
- Hey, you only got... - It was very far.
(Suk Jin disappeared completely.)
But look how clear it is.
You only took a photo of them.
(Disappointed)
- 10 times? - Yes, I zoomed in 10 times.
(While these four are focused on product placement...)
Do you have rubber bands?
(What's a rubber band for?)
Thanks, Yoo Ri.
- It'll look okay with a trim. - Pull it. It's fake.
(Interested in Kwang Soo's back hair)
I think it's a hairpiece.
- Wait, Kwang Soo. - Yes.
(The prankster ties his back hair without asking.)
- Wait. - Can't believe it.
- Doesn't he look like... - Don't make him look handsome.
I have to.
- Do I really look okay? - Jae Suk cares for you.
(Looking forward to it)
He really looks nice.
He does, right?
(Stylist Yu's work is done.)
- Seriously. - But the side view doesn't.
(What is that?)
- You look great. - It's amazing.
- Really? - Yes, you look great.
(He becomes Kongsuni.)
You look much better.
(An awful combo of cute hair and an old face)
- Well, it feels cool. - You look gross.
I look gross?
- Hey. - Kwang Soo.
(His appearance may look appalling to some.)
Isn't this nice?
- It's gross. - You look great.
(Extremely content with his masterpiece)
- Kwang Soo. - Isn't this nice?
There's an emoticon like this.
- Right. - What emoticon?
(No one will actually pay to buy Kwang Soo emoticons.)
- You look really good. - There's an emoticon like that.
Isn't that a wig he's wearing?
- He grew his hair. - Really?
(Shocked)
This is much better.
- They say you look cool. - Look at them.
They are talking about you in whispers. You're so popular.
Do you like my hair?
(Naive)
Yes. You look pretty.
He's popular again.
(Forced compliments to make sure Kwang Soo keeps the hairstyle.)
- My gosh. - This is what happens all the time.
You're a star.
You should buy me a drink.
(Really?)
- It's always your best days. - Last week,
(The Celebrity Butler experiences what it's like to be a celebrity.)
- when Suk Jin... - He's popular again.
He likes it.
(Fidgeting)
That doesn't feel so bad.
(He's totally confused with superficial compliments.)
- He should've done it sooner. - It feels great.
Here's your first mission.
(First Mission: Need Communication)
It's Need Communication...
where you need to communicate with your team members.
Each team will do the mission in turn.
(All 3 teams will have 2 rounds.)
All the team members will wear headphones that play loud music.
(All the team members will wear headphones that play loud music.)
One will give questions, one will answer,
(One will give questions, one will answer.)
and the rest will sit under the balloon that grows bigger over time.
(The rest will sit under the balloon that grows bigger over time.)
Oh no.
(The person needs to explain with the headphone on.)
So it's like Shout in Silence.
If you listen to the question and answer it, you get one point.
(For each correct question, they'll get 1 point.)
If your team member gives the correct answer or passes,
(Upon answering or pass, the members will switch seats.)
the players should switch seats.
(The person who'll sit under the balloon will change.)
We give questions in turn.
I shouldn't be sitting under the balloon...
- at the last moment. - And you'll be covered...
with flour once the balloon bursts.
(The game will continue until the balloon bursts.)
Okay.
- The Penalty Men should go first. - Do it with confidence.
(Game Order, Team Penalty Men, Team Eun Jin, Team Yoon Kyung)
Good.
- All right. - Let's go.
(Team Penalty Men will go first.)
Okay.
Make sure to explain it well.
(So Min will answer first.)
- Ready. - Let's do this.
(The two will take turns to explain the answers.)
We can do this.
(Extremely eager)
Start.
(Mission starts)
(The balloon starts to be inflated.)
What?
(The first word is confession.)
I like you.
- You like me? - Yes.
(A word caught Love Frog's ear.)
- What is it called? - She got it right away.
How could she hear that right away?
- You like me? - Yes. What is it called?
(She's good at listening tests when it comes to love.)
It's a noun.
(Grinning)
What? Do you like me?
- It's a noun. - That's not it.
- It's a noun. - You should answer it.
(The Penalty Man at the back is getting anxious.)
"I like you."
It's a noun.
- Proposal. - It's something like that.
(You're close.)
- Before a proposal... - Propose.
Proposal?
- Proposal? Propose. - Something before a proposal.
- Confession. - Two syllables.
(She got the first word right quite quickly.)
This one is hard.
(The two switches seats.)
It was hard, but she got it right anyway.
(Phone number)
This is hard.
It's hard to explain.
(The second word is phone number.)
- Phone. - Phone.
- Num. - Num.
(What?)
- Ber. - Ber.
- Num. - Num.
(Is he just reading the word?)
- Phone. - Phone.
You can't do that.
You should explain the word.
(Don't read it.)
- You can't do that. - Telephone.
(He gets wrong by spitting out answers as soon as he begins.)
- Correct. - You can't do that.
(Only after "phone number," the balloon has gotten very big.)
The balloon is about to burst.
(The word is Pad Thai.)
Good.
- Vietnamese food. - No.
(Vietnamese?)
- No. - Vietnam.
(Amidst the chaos, the Thai cuisine lost its origin.)
- It's Thai food. - It's Thailand.
Whale?
(They got off on the wrong foot, so they are just wasting time.)
Bow tie. Tie. Bow tie.
- Pass it! - Tie.
Oh no.
(The balloon is getting a lot bigger.)
Pass it!
(Kwang Soo will be showered in flour if they keep wasting time.)
- Tie. - Pass it!
- It's a Vietnamese noodle dish. - What?
(But they have no intentions of passing the question.)
A Vietnamese noodle dish.
- Pass it. - A Vietnamese noodle dish.
(He waves his arms in desperation.)
- What? - Pass it!
(He stamps his feet anxiously.)
Pass the question!
(Intrigued)
Pass!
(Please! Pass!)
Pass it!
Pass!
(After making the balloon extremely big,)
- What is it? - Pass.
(he finally asks to pass.)
- Pass. - No, I want to answer it.
You can't get it right.
No, I want to answer it.
- Pass it! - He's such a fool.
(He desperately asks to pass.)
- What a fool. - Pass the question!
You don't know it. Pass it.
(It's literally a Shout in Silence.)
Do you not know a Vietnamese noodle dish?
(They're getting further away from the answer Pad Thai.)
I don't know anything.
- I don't know. Let's just pass. - I don't know?
(At the moment...)
- Pass it! - Look at him.
(The balloon is about to touch the top of his head.)
Pass!
My goodness.
(But his teammates are busy guessing the answer.)
Pass.
This is too big.
(It finally bursts.)
(No one listened to Kwang Soo's cries.)
It's too big.
(The boy with twin tails has become a wreck.)
It looks like he got hit.
(What a pity.)
It was loud.
I mean, he didn't explain it well.
(A great sacrifice for his teammates who didn't pass the question.)
You should explain it in words.
(Team Penalty Men earns 2 points.)
You shouldn't make gestures.
You should only say words.
Guys, you should explain it with your hands behind your back.
(Explaining with actions is now banned.)
- Okay. - Put your hands behind your back.
Ready. Start. You can't make any gestures.
(Team Yoon Kyung is up next.)
(Mouthwash)
(The first word is mouthwash.)
You gargle with this.
- Gargle? - You eat something...
when your breath stinks.
- Eat it? - You gargle and spit.
- Gargle? - Your mouth...
Gargle.
(Used to gargle your mouth to get rid of the mouth smell?)
- You gargle with this. - Garglin.
- Garglin? - You gargle with this.
(He just names any brands he knows.)
It's a brand name.
What is it called?
(Frustrated)
- Gargle liquid? - No.
- He doesn't know the word. - He doesn't know.
(His vocabulary does not include mouthwash.)
He doesn't know the word.
(Reasonable doubt)
No. What is it called in a fancy word?
In a fancy word?
You gargle with this. What is it called?
("Mouthwash" is a fancy word to Empty Head of Running Man.)
It's not fancy at all.
What is it called?
You gargle with this. What is it called?
(He just keeps repeating the word "gargle".)
He's so ugly.
- What is he saying? - You stupid punk.
You stupid punk.
(Extremely frustrated)
You gargle with it.
(He opens his heart taking advantage of the silence from the headphone.)
You stupid punk. You gargle with it.
You gargle with it.
(Mouthing)
No. You gargle like this. What is it called?
- Hey, just pass it. - What is this called?
(There's no way they'll get the answer.)
It's a gargle.
(After passing, the next word is skate.)
Tell me how many syllables it has.
Sam.
Gam?
- Sam. - Sam.
- Hap. - Samhap?
- Samhap? - What's in samhap?
Skate.
(He guesses it right quickly.)
- Right. - Okay.
She's good.
(Team Yoon Kyung finally earns 1 point.)
(Scandal)
She's doing a good job.
(Jae Suk should explain the word, "scandal".)
- She's doing a good job. - Hey.
What?
This is... Well...
(Clapping)
He can't explain the word.
(They're stuck with a difficult vocabulary.)
He's stuck.
It's something between a man and a woman.
What did you say?
(Stuttering)
- Well, the thing is... - What?
That's what stars have.
What is he talking about?
(For Jae Suk, a "scandal" happens...)
- Stars have... - What?
- When stars meet... - He's really bad at this.
(between a man and a woman who are stars.)
- They take pictures and... - Gestures.
(He doesn't know because he never had a scandal.)
- No gestures. - They do this thing.
(The balloon is getting bigger.)
- Don't make gestures. - What are you talking about?
Suk Jin shouldn't see anyone now.
But he sees someone.
It's something like that.
(He improvises an unrealistic hypothesis.)
Blind date.
Three syllables.
- He met someone? - I mean, Jong Kook...
- Jong Kook? - Jong Kook...
- Yoon Eun Hye. - He has a girlfriend.
(He just says the name automatically.)
What?
(Due to bad explanations, Haha passes the question.)
- Pass. What are you talking about? - This is frustrating.
- He can't explain the word. - That's cheating.
(Ingratitude)
Why can't you get it right?
(A Chinese idiom)
What is this?
- He doesn't know what it means. - It's a bad guy.
He's really...
It's a bad guy.
(Ingratitude means bad.)
He's really mean.
I mean...
(He barely explains the feeling of the word.)
- He doesn't know this word. - I'm younger than you.
- You're younger. - I'm younger than you.
I'm younger, but I call you stupid.
(He's just explaining impoliteness.)
- Mutiny. - I call you a fool.
I'm bad. I'm a jerk.
What is it called?
- Is that what it means? - It's a Chinese idiom.
The younger one is mean to the older one.
(Speaking passionately)
Oh, right. That's what you like.
What?
What's the word? It's "Fruits of diligent study".
No.
(It's a most popular idiom used whenever he's stuck.)
"Fruits of diligent study"?
What does it have to do with "Fruits of diligent study"?
What was that? Is it nangjungjichu or something?
- This is crazy. - You're so...
(Popping)
(Team Yoon Kyung gets 1 point.)
I'm startled.
(Next is Team Eun Jin.)
I'll surprise you.
I'm going to surprise you.
Ready.
(Team Eun Jin took risks and let Suk Jin answer questions.)
Start.
Suk Jin is answering.
(In-laws)
This is easy.
- I have a stomachache. - When do we start?
If he buys land...
(Your stomach hurts when your in-laws buy a piece of land!)
- Grab medicine? - Buy land.
- Catch chicken? - I get a stomachache.
- Stomach. - It's done.
- Isn't it a cousin? - Stomach.
(Isn't it for your cousins?)
I get a stomachache.
(He's explaining it wrong.)
The saying says a cousin.
- If he buys land, I get jealous. - Stomachache.
(Stubborn)
Jealous?
- In-laws. - Right.
I get jealous when my in-law buys land.
(And he got it right?)
He got it right.
He's supposed to say a cousin.
(They guessed it correctly because they both got confused.)
It's about a cousin.
The saying goes, "You get jealous when your cousin buys land."
(Next word is Joe Biden.)
- The US president. - Soap.
- Jeoktoma. - Jeoktoma.
(Song Jeoktoma explained it well.)
- The US president. - Soap.
- President? - Yes.
- Soap president? - The new president.
- Soap? - US.
- Soap president? - The US president, you fool.
(They got off on the wrong foot.)
Soap president?
- Soap? - Start over.
Aekyung?
(Is the soap president Aekyung?)
What?
- Aekyung? - Did he say Aekyung?
(The camera shakes.)
Because it's soap.
- Aekyung. - Aekyung.
(He says all the companies he knows to find the soap president.)
Aekyung?
Pass.
(He passes after his search for the soap president.)
- What's the soap president? - Why is it so hard?
(Goodness)
Jong Kook is upset. He's mad.
I mean...
(They've done only one word, but they are getting really upset.)
What on earth is the soap president?
(Pancake)
(Wiggling)
- Okay? - Eun Jin tries to look nice.
What are you doing? You should hurry.
Just hurry.
On a birthday.
(She tries to explain "cake" first.)
- Birthday. - Birthday.
You eat this.
I eat this on my birthday?
Cake.
- And... - Cake.
(There's one more syllable.)
- Cake. - There's one more syllable.
(Eun Jin keeps wiggling her fingers.)
Cake?
- Don't move your hands. - Birthday.
- Birthday? - You eat it on your birthday.
(She tries to explain again with her hands at the back.)
Cake.
- Eun Jin's face is really funny. - In front of the word.
(She explains with her face.)
Something cake.
Suk Jin can't get it right this way.
Happy birthday.
(He has no idea.)
See? He doesn't know.
But it's something cake.
Eun Jin's face is really funny.
Cheesecake?
I don't know how else to explain.
(He can only smirk.)
- Cheesecake? - A plate to put it on.
- He thinks it's a type of cake. - Pass.
(He holds a pass as he's one letter short.)
- Oh, gosh. What do we do? - Eun Jin is so funny.
(The balloon got bigger than before.)
That was hilarious.
- It's going to pop shortly. - "Soap".
(Prima donna)
- "Soap". - That's difficult.
(A prima donna is the lead female soprano singer of an opera.)
That's difficult. How should he explain it?
That's difficult.
(They can't explain the original meaning.)
Oh, boy. How will he explain it?
The US!
- Soap? - No, no.
(He says soap again.)
- Gosh, I'm so frustrated. - "Soap" again?
(The swamp of soap begins.)
- The US... - He's already tired.
She sang "Like a Virgin"!
(Singer Madonna)
"It's raining"?
The female singer!
- "Fur leather"? - From the US!
- "Tiger Mask"? - "Like a Virgin"...
(Popping)
- Time's over. - My, it's so loud.
(Time's up.)
How should I explain it? I should've passed it.
(Team Eun Jin got 1 point.)
- "Madonna". - Gosh, Suk Jin.
Why couldn't you guess Joe Biden?
- Why? When did you... - She said the US president.
The US president.
(Was it the US president?)
Why would you say a soap brand name instead?
Why did you mishear "the US" as "soap"?
Your lips and hers look different.
- Ji Hyo, how did say it? Show me. - You kept saying...
(Ji Hyo. You try it.)
"The US Ma..." Darn it. I said "Madonna".
Just say "the US".
"The US president".
- Just say "the US". - "The US".
(They suddenly started reenacting the moment.)
- "The US". - I said it more than 100 times.
- Did you pronounce it properly? - He doesn't know anyway.
(They pour their passion out on one word.)
- I mean... - Why are you getting upset at her?
- Stop fighting. - Listen to me.
- There's no way of doing it well. - You're being too sensitive.
- Why are you being so sensitive? - Why couldn't you get it?
(Suk Jin)
- Just say "the US". - It wasn't like that.
I thought there's someone called the soap president.
(Thanks to the soap president, the family breaks up.)
I'm not sure if I can explain well. Hold on a second.
(Team Penalty Men begins Round 2 first.)
- It was difficult to explain. - There you go.
- You can do it! - Wait.
Must I let him do things like this to me when he's younger than me?
"Ingratitude"!
You can do this, right?
(Loud)
You can do it!
(Everyone in here is so playful.)
Let's do this!
(Yoo Jae Suk)
This is hard to guess.
(The 1st word is Yoo Jae Suk.)
He's ugly!
(She shouted out loud to let everyone know he's ugly.)
Yoo Jae Suk!
(But Kwang Soo got it right!)
(He got the correct answer magically from a single hint "ugly".)
(I'm ugly?)
(He got the answer right so fast that her jaw dropped.)
- That was incredible. - My goodness.
(That gave everyone goosebumps.)
My goodness.
- What just happened? - How did he know?
- Gosh. - That was so funny.
How did he know?
(The next question is "unconcealable talent".)
- Fruits of diligent study! - "Fruits of diligent study"?
Another expression other than that.
There are too many.
Fruits of late-night study?
(Team Penalty Men gained 1 point in Round 2.)
To pee...
(Team Yoon Kyung begins Round 2.)
- "To pee"? - Yes!
- Anywhere! - Urinating in public!
Urinating in public. Switch your seats quickly.
(Team Yoon Kyung also gained 1 point in Round 2.)
- Let's do this. - Here I go.
(Team Eun Jin is the last to play Round 2.)
Let's do this properly.
- Jong Kook, look at us too. - Turn it around.
(Team Eun Jin has to get at least 2 questions to catch up.)
- Let's go! - Being in second place is good too.
- Ready. Go. - Hasn't it begun yet?
(How many questions will Team Eun Jin get?)
- Not yet. - Not yet?
- Go. - Oh, no. It's difficult.
(The answer is "The Way This Guy Lives".)
- It's a fast-tempo song. - It's difficult.
What? Speak slowly.
Speak slowly.
(He suddenly started singing.)
- What is he doing? - What is that?
- What's that? Are you singing? - He could just...
(He's giving a useless explanation with headphones on.)
That's not how the song goes.
- Is it a song? - It's a song!
- He's singing "Barefooted Youth". - That's ridiculous.
(He's singing "Barefooted Youth"...)
- That's "Barefooted Youth". - He's singing the wrong song?
(when the word is "The Way This Guy Lives".)
(He keeps singing the song that's not related to the answer.)
What's that? Are you singing?
(This won't work.)
That's not the song he should sing.
(Quiet)
- Is it a song? - It's a song. It has five words.
- What song is it? - What is he doing?
- I don't even know. - That's not the song.
(His courage plummeted.)
- I don't know! Pass it! - Tell me if you don't know.
- You don't know? Okay. - I don't know.
(They passed it in the end.)
- Isn't it SECHSKIES' song? - Pass.
(Firm)
- I live and die by style - What was that?
(He leaves after singing "Barefooted Youth".)
- Wasn't that "Barefooted Youth"? - Yes.
- That's Buck's song. - Gosh.
- Let's go. Let's go. - What a shame.
(Stock)
(The word is stock.)
- Samsung Elec... - I should be guessing the answer.
El?
Samsung!
- I should be guessing the answer. - Elec...
- What is she doing? - Kakao.
(Stock)
- My gosh. - What?
(She names all the famous stocks.)
Gosh. This is no joke.
You shouldn't explain it like that.
She's amazing.
- Te! - "Te"?
Tesla.
- "Tae Jin Ah"? - Te...
(She urgently said the hottest blue-chip stock.)
"Tae Jin Ah"?
(He misheard it as "Tae Jin Ah".)
(She's trying to express stock price increase.)
"Tae Jin Ah"? Did you say "Tae Jin Ah"?
(It's going up.)
(The price of the stock I have is staying the same.)
(The price of the stock she's holding hasn't changed.)
My goodness. Eun Jin is so funny.
(But Tesla keeps going up.)
- Te... - "Tae".
- S... - "Jin".
- La. - "Ah".
I bet Jong Kook can't even imagine the correct answer.
- "Tae Jin Ah"! - It's going up.
(Going up)
(Wriggling)
Yes, Tesla.
- "Tae Jin Ah"! - "Going up!"
(She uses her hands more and more.)
- Eun Jin is hilarious. - I'm sure she invested in stocks.
(Eun Jin)
- She's so funny. - Definitely.
Tae Jin Ah is going up?
Oh, wait. Is it stock?
(He gets the answer in the end.)
- Yes! - That's amazing. He got it right.
What does Tae Jin Ah have to do with stocks?
(They barely got the correct answer with company names and gestures.)
That's amazing.
Oh, wait. Is it stock?
- Yes! - That's amazing. He got it right.
(If they get another one right, they'll tie with Team Penalty Men.)
You can do it!
How many points did they score?
- That's difficult. - We're doing well!
- Of course. - It'd be even harder.
(Sweet potato)
(They must get the correct answer before the balloon pops.)
- You... - I...
- ate this... - Haha?
- earlier in the morning. - My business partner? At his house?
What?
You ate this. You ate it.
(The balloon is about to pop.)
What? At Haha's house?
(Pop)
- They got many answers right. - I did what at Haha's house?
(They fail to catch up.)
You ate it in the morning.
- Oh, sweet potato? - Eun Jin did a great job.
(Team Penalty Men is still in 1st place.)
Saying company names was a good strategy.
(Ahn Eun Jin the rookie stockholder)
- Why did you say "Tae Jin Ah"? - It's been going up.
Suk Jin, can you sing "The Way This Guy Lives" again?
No, that's...
- Barefooted youth, woo-ah, woo-ah - Woo-ah, woo-ah
- Woo-ah, woo-ah - Woo-ah, woo-ah
- Oh, right. - Why did you even sing?
(He realizes after singing with lyrics.)
Did you think he could hear you sing?
I don't know many songs either.
He tried to make it easier for him to guess.
He sang "Barefooted Youth".
I live and die by style
(This is how "The Way This Guy Lives" goes.)
- Oh, that's right. - SECHSKIES.
(Suk Jin turns around with enlightenment.)
- Darn it. - As a result,
- Team Penalty Men came in first. - Okay!
(Team Penalty Men came in 1st with 3 points.)
Team Eun Jin is in 2nd place, and Team Yoon Kyung is in 3rd place.
(Team Eun Jin is in 2nd place. Team Yoon Kyung is in 3rd place.)
What a shame.
- I'm relieved. - We did quite well.
I'm so relieved.
(According to the mission,)
As I told you earlier,
(they get a benefit.)
the more mission fund you get,
(They'll get mission funds to discard the penalty tickets.)
the more penalty tickets...
- you can get rid of. - Yes.
We'll give you the drawing board for R money.
(They can get personal mission funds from the R money drawing board.)
Each member of the teams can pick...
(1st place team)
1 out of 5 in the section of your team ranking.
(2nd place team)
I haven't done this in a long time. When I was a little boy,
(3rd place team)
- in front of schools, - Team Penalty Men.
- kids would do this after school. - Pick one.
(Members of Team Penalty Men will draw first.)
- Each of us gets 1? - Pick just 1.
- 2 of them will be left. - Everyone gets 1?
Just pick one.
Okay. Pick one.
- You want this one? - No.
Among those pieces of paper,
(They'll pick from 100, 100, 80, 60, and 0 dollars.)
2 of them are 100 dollars, the rest are 80, 60, and 0 dollars.
I think Kwang Soo picked zero.
(How much did each of the team members gain?)
Show us what you chose starting with Kwang Soo.
- Zero. - I think Kwang Soo picked zero.
(Kwang Soo will reveal the amount first.)
Show us what you chose starting with Kwang Soo.
- I think he chose zero. - Zero?
I picked zero.
(Kwang Soo gained 0.)
- Gosh. He got so unlucky. - Poor him.
(His team came in 1st, but he gained no money.)
It's so hard to believe.
80 dollars.
(Sang Yi got 80 dollars.)
(So Min got 100 dollars.)
100 dollars?
- 80 dollars. - What happens now?
That's the amount you have individually.
This is an individual fund.
Eun Jin, what about you?
(Sighing)
I got 60 dollars.
- How much? - 60 dollars.
(Team Eun Jin in 2nd place)
- 60 dollars? I got... - Suk Jin.
50 dollars.
- 40 dollars. - I see.
- Ji Hyo got 80 dollars. - I must've picked zero.
(Eun Jin got 60, Suk Jin got 40, Ji Hyo got 80, Jong Kook got 80.)
I got 80 dollars.
I thought I got no money.
Both of you got 80 dollars.
- None of us picked zero. - Exactly.
(Luckily, they drew high amounts.)
All right. Here we go!
Do not hesitate!
(It's Team Yoon Kyung's turn.)
Your team can get 60, 60, 40, 20, and 0 dollars.
- 90? Oh, 60 dollars. - That's 60 dollars.
(Se Chan got 60, Jae Suk got 40, Haha got 20.)
- You got lucky. - I got 40 dollars.
- Did I get the most among us? - Yes. I got 20 dollars.
What about you, Yoon Kyung?
(Yoon Kyung got 0 dollars.)
- Zero. - She got no money.
- I picked the highest amount. - She's in trouble.
- Right. - Yoon Kyung is in trouble.
(Current game money)
60 dollars!
Is this an individual game?
- No, but you need... - Next,
(Team Penalty Men will pick 1 person from the team that placed last.)
it's time for Team Penalty Men...
to recruit one person from the bottom place team.
- They're in the last place, right? - Yes.
Yoon Kyung is on our team too. What do you mean, "I see"?
(They found the person who was hiding in the last team.)
Yoon Kyung, you should stand here with us.
- Who should we choose? - They can choose anyone?
Just one person?
(1 person will move to Team Penalty Men.)
- Who? - Yes.
We don't know what will happen when we move to that team.
(Once they join Team Penalty Men,)
What will happen to the chosen person?
If you join Team Penalty Men,
you'll have more chances of getting a penalty at the end.
(there's more chance of getting the water bomb.)
- Oh, I get it. - We should avoid joining that team.
- It'll be someone on that team. - Exactly.
- Have you guys made up your mind? - Yes, we've made our decision.
(The choice has been made.)
Please announce it.
(Who could be the unlucky person to join Team Penalty Men?)
- Yoo Jae Suk. - Okay.
(They chose Jae Suk.)
(Jae Suk has been chosen by his senior Penalty Men.)
Nice.
- Of course. - Why me?
- Hey. - You belong to that team.
(They picked a person who suits the penalty.)
- It feels right. - You suit the team.
You're perfect for the team.
Gosh, seriously.
(They move to the next mission place with the new Penalty Man, Jae Suk.)
Now, we'll move to the next location.
If we bring Jong Kook to our team, it'll be game over.
(Everyone is getting on the bus to move to the next location.)
Kwang Soo, I have something to ask you about.
- When you look in the mirror... - Do you think you look pretty?
(They make fun of Kwang Soo's hair again.)
- and check your hair... - Do you feel pretty?
When you see your hair at the back, does it make you want to go out?
- You... Hang on. - Why?
- I don't mind if Jong Kook says it. - But...
- Checking your hair in the mirror, - I told you not to act up.
he'd say, "Good. Okay."
Is that how you react?
(Okay, okay.)
- That's... - I'm just curious.
- We're just curious. - He didn't have any intention,
- but you provoked him. - That's not true.
How do you feel?
Who inspired you?
There must be the key point of your style.
Kim Da Mi from "Itaewon Class".
(Happy now?)
(The crazy Da Mi)
(The story behind his hairstyle has finally been revealed.)
Oh, okay. That makes sense now.
- It feels great to finally hear it. - Indeed.
(Teasing)
- Have you been hiding it? - All right.
(The talk has been heated up through the story of his hairstyle.)
- Okay. - You can tell us anything.
Eun Jin did a great job at explaining the word "stock".
- I bet she's investing in stocks. - Are you, Eun Jin?
- I think so. - It's not like that.
(Modest)
- "It's not like that." - "It's not like that."
(She named the stocks in detail.)
- I know nothing about it. - It's not like that.
I don't know stock trading any terms like "Tae Jin Ah".
- It was "Tesla", not "Tae Jin Ah". - Oh, right.
Sang Yi didn't seem to be so good at playing games.
He was lousy at explaining.
(They're weak at games.)
It was unexpected.
Sang Yi and Eun Jin,
you two must've gone on a group trip together.
- Yes, we did. Sang Yi... - He's trying to put them together.
- Sang Yi arranged everything... - He's trying to put them together.
- as the student representative. - Oh, I see.
(They have a lot of memories about retreats.)
- He rented a bus and everything. - Really?
You normally play games at these things.
- Of course. - And have the orientation.
(The love story maker operates once again.)
Then you split into groups...
- And talk. - Yes, that's right.
You'll also have a few drinks and...
That's enough!
(He's too much into the forced romance all day.)
- Will you stop? - Just stop.
How is it that everything is spun that way?
- He's just lonely, that's all. - Unbelievable.
(We should be understanding.)
- He's had that expression all day. - Once...
(The face of a love story addict)
you have a few drinks...
People like you ruin brewing romances.
Right, you're only ruining it.
Did you ask her out for some fresh air?
(Firm)
Yes or no? Answer me!
I want to feel the romance.
(Say it.)
You want to what?
(Dream's father needs energy from other people's love stories.)
- He's hilarious. - He wants to feel the romance.
It's only so that he can have fun.
(Tired of it)
- No way. - I'm sick and tired of this.
What a pervert.
(Indeed)
You probably ruined...
some relationships of Jong Kook's too.
Although, I'm only speculating.
(It connects to Jong Kook's love life.)
Jong Kook? Well, he's...
His wall is put up too high.
- There's no hope for him this year. - He doesn't let anyone in.
(He gets rid of his dating cells early in January.)
He'll just stay a bachelor forever.
But...
We recently went by Jong Kook's place.
(Suk Jin and Jae Suk visited his house not long ago.)
- Yes. - That's right.
It's been a while...
since I've been to a house that felt more like a storage facility.
(A cold warehouse where no warmth could be found)
- Seriously? - I mean...
This is what I said after leaving his place.
After leaving his place,
I asked Jae Suk...
if it was only my feet that were cold.
(They almost suffered from frostbite.)
He was like, "No."
I thought I was under the weather or something.
- My feet were freezing. - How can...
(Jong Kook's frugal mind causes cold hands and feet.)
your feet be freezing when in a house?
He doesn't even turn on the lights.
It reminds you of hyeongseoljigong.
It's winter, so the sun sets around 5pm, right?
(He works out in the dark with the glow of a firefly.)
- Where's the need? - Why do you need lights?
You have to feel your way to your own bathroom.
It's not like I'm going to read.
No way.
(Respect.)
Yoon Kyung, were you...
not interested in joining the entertainment industry?
(Changing the subject)
Me? No, not at first.
- Not at all? - No.
I see hints of Kim Min Jung in your face.
- Thank you. - You should know this in advance.
(Suk Jin compliments her looks out of nowhere.)
If you get to meet Suk Jin some other time...
(Suk Jin forgets people's faces easily.)
Let me say I'm sorry.
- He might not recognize you. - I'll apologize in advance.
(Apologizing in advance)
There's a high chance of that.
I don't pay attention to faces...
when I meet new people.
No, that's a lie.
He used to remember faces like nobody's business.
- Only rich people. - Yes, exactly.
He never forgets the faces of rich people.
(Relating to it)
- When they buy meals. - So get wealthier.
(Snorting out of embarrassment)
- What are you talking about? - But it's true.
I'm good at remembering my seniors, that's all.
You never forget the 10-billion dollar guy.
- What? - 10 billion...
- Oh, him. - He's Chinese.
- He's younger than me. - Is he?
(Acting tough all of a sudden)
But you addressed him as someone older.
(Because he has 10 billion dollars?)
If they're rich, he regards them as his elder.
It's money over age.
- I'm only joking. - There's no need to say that.
(Though you're younger than me, may I address you as my elder?)
He regards them as older if they're rich.
It's only a joke.
- Let's not mention that. - I only address him that way...
as a joke.
How can you not get the joke?
(A rich people lover's capitalist joke)
Don't humiliate Suk Jin like this.
A few years ago,
(Followed by another story)
he called me for the first time...
(Kwang Soo went out after getting a call from Suk Jin.)
to treat me to a meal.
- Really? - I went out...
and he was with a group of wealthy Chinese men.
(Chinese rich men were there.)
- Really? - And...
he was serving them.
He was serving them.
(He was serving food for the rich men?)
I'm not making this up.
(Was he volunteering for the rich men?)
He didn't mention anything but just offered to buy me dinner.
Don't you lie!
Don't you remember it?
- That's enough. - Why would I have waited on them?
- But it's true. - That's enough.
- Kwang Soo, that's enough. - You were in a suit.
- That's enough. - Don't you remember that?
(The piranha bites him as if he's been waiting.)
Viewers, what he said is a lie.
I didn't wait on them.
(His rumor of being rich people's butler is full of lies.)
- That's enough. - I kept my pride, you know.
Anyway, we're going...
to play a mini-game on our way there.
(A short game in the meantime)
- Nice. - Sounds good.
(Some Penalty Men)
- Will we get to add another member? - Yes.
- Oh, dear. - Again?
(1 member of the regular team will be in Team Penalty Men after this.)
- Yes, you can. - After this game?
Jong Kook's not good at games on buses.
We can add a member to Team Penalty.
This game...
was created based on how Jae Suk kept saying "What about apples?"...
during a game in a recent episode.
This is What About Apples.
(New Year Driving Out Bad Luck Race, Second Mission, What About Apples)
What About Apples?
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Episode 539)
- I like strawberries - I like strawberries
(Suk Jin started off the strawberry game.)
- Why do you like them? - Straw...
- I like strawberries - Why do you like them?
(Jae Suk suddenly asked an unrelated question.)
- Sweet, tasty, and sour. - What about apples?
(He still answered.)
- What about apples? - Apples...
Apples are tasty but expensive.
(The game was created based on Jae Suk's ad-lib.)
It goes like this. What about apples?
(It's a variation of the strawberry game.)
- What about apples? - What about apples?
- Go ahead. - Suk Jin, four.
(When someone says, "Suk Jin Four"...)
The first and last word should be "apple,"
but the ones in between should be "elppa."
(The words in between should be said backward.)
This is too tricky.
(Those who are bad at the strawberry game are terrified.)
The weakest link is appalled by the rules.
- What about when the number is 1? - 1?
(1: Apple.)
Apple
If it's two, do you just say apple twice?
(2: Apple, apple.)
- Apple-apple - Apple-apple
That's two.
- And if it's three. - Elppa-elppa
(3: Apple, elppa, apple.)
- Apple-elppa-apple - Apple-elppa-apple
If it's four...
- Apple-elppa-elppa-apple - Apple-elppa-elppa-apple
(4: Apple, elppa, elppa, apple.)
Apple.
- Okay. - Apple-elppa-apple
- Let's do this. - What about apples?
- What about apples? - What about apples?
- It's too fast. - Kwang Soo, three.
Apple-elppa-apple
Jong Kook, four.
Apple-elppa-elppa-elppa
- Okay. - Nice!
(The last word should've been apple.)
Nicely done!
I knew you'd attack me first.
(I knew it.)
- Okay, let's go. - Don't attack teammates.
- Let's go. - Don't attack teammates.
- Jong Kook's up first. - Go ahead.
(Jong Kook will start.)
- Okay. - And go.
- What about apples? - What about apples?
- Kwang Soo, three. - Apple-elppa-apple
Jong Kook, one.
Apple
Kwang Soo, two.
Apple-apple
Suk Jin, three.
Apple-elppa-apple
Hold on a second.
(The timing was off, but not too much.)
- Wait. - I did it correctly.
Are you sure?
(They let it slide this time.)
- Really? - I'm sure.
I was on beat.
- Jae Suk, four. - Elppa-apple-elppa
(Offbeat)
(Like always, he chokes while playing the game.)
- Didn't I do all right? - Absolutely.
(Suk Jin averted a crisis thanks to Jae Suk.)
- Apple, elppa... - Yoon Kyung, go ahead.
(Yoon Kyung will go first this time.)
- What about apples? - What about apples?
Jae Suk, four.
Apple-apple-elppa-app
("Jae Suk, four" works like magic.)
- He... - Apple-elppa-apple
- Apple! - You should've clapped.
- Didn't I? - Apple!
- Didn't I do that? - No.
"Jae Suk, four" will work every time.
(A cheat code)
- What about apples? - What about apples?
(Jae Suk starts.)
Sang Yi, three.
Apple-elppa-apple
- Eun Jin, four. - Apple-elppa-elppa-apple
- Haha, four. - Apple-elppa-elppa-apple
- Jae Suk, three. - Apple-elppa-elppa-apple
What now?
(Targeting Jae Suk will guarantee a win.)
What's the matter with you?
- Wait. - "Apple, apple."
Are we allowed to kick someone off our team?
This game doesn't fit me well.
(Brazen)
Jae Suk, just get off, will you?
- I... - He keeps getting it wrong.
(Frustrated)
Just get off the bus.
(They're having an issue after bringing him as a Penalty Man.)
- This game doesn't fit me well. - We chose the wrong teammate.
- Unbelievable. - Jae Suk...
- Can't we switch fruits? - You can.
(It can be any two-syllable words other than "apple".)
How about grapefruit?
- Plum. - Yes, plum.
- Geobong. - Watermelon.
(Though he's bad at the game, he gives advice.)
- How about geobong? - How about geobong?
Jae Suk, three.
Geobong-bonggeo-bonggeo-geobong
Seriously?
(His mouth protrudes even more when he's flustered.)
Hold on a second. Let's play without him.
(The fruit may have changed but the person hasn't.)
- Jae Suk... - Can we please play without him?
- Hey. - We just can't get past him.
Please tell them I'd rather take a break.
- Just for a moment. - I'll take a break.
- Just for one round. - This game doesn't suit me.
(Team Penalty Men is on the brink of forfeiting.)
Got it?
The round always ends with him.
Geobong's a hard word.
Team Penalty is currently in last place.
(Team Penalty Men is currently at the bottom because of Jae Suk.)
Okay, good.
- What word should I say? - 5, 6, 7, 8
- How about belts? - How about belts?
Eun Jin, three.
- Belt-tleb-belt - She's good.
Kwang Soo, two.
Belt-belt
Ji Hyo, four.
Belt-tleb-tleb-belt
Safety, two.
- What? - Safety?
- Safety, two. - Safety?
(What? Safety?)
Who's Safety?
Were you talking about safety belts?
- Were you? - Unbelievable.
- That caught my attention. - No way.
(Embarrassed)
- This is what she saw. - Safety?
- She must be our driver. - Who's Safety?
- This is what she read. - Ji Hyo, what was that?
(The "safety belt" that she saw while zoned out consumed her.)
- Who's Safety? - Ji Hyo.
Is it Kim Safety or Choi Safety? Who is it?
- Who were you calling? - Mr. Safety.
(She could only let out the word, "safety".)
- I'm sorry about that. - Zoned-out Ji Hyo.
Let's end it with this round.
(Now the last round)
- We'll win anyway. - If we win this round...
- Jae Suk. - Good luck.
- Who's up? - Yoon Kyung.
(Haha will go first.)
Pomegranate will be a hard one.
Then what is that backwards?
(Which word should I use?)
1, 2
- 1, 2, 3, 4 - 1, 2, 3, 4
I like soy milk
- I like soy milk - I like soy milk
Jae Suk, four.
Soy milk-milk soy-milk soy-milk soy
- Seriously? - Unbelievable.
You know that word means nipple in Korean, right?
(You're embarrassing us.)
Why do you have three nipples?
Well, I...
(U-Doragon is seriously taken aback.)
Must you repeat that word so many times?
- I... - We only have two nipples.
He said that word on purpose.
- Actually... - Soy milk-milk soy-milk soy
(Come on!)
Unbelievable.
I can't believe you did this.
(Haha's plan worked perfectly.)
The last one should've been "soy milk."
(Shaking her head)
Eun Jin back there was like this.
No, don't.
(Eun Jin the audience still reacts to it.)
Gosh.
(U-Doragon got the grand finale.)
All right, good.
In first place...
- is Team Yoon Kyung. - Okay.
- First place? - Haha...
- We're on Yoon Kyung's team. - Yes, us.
(But we're Team Yoon Kyung.)
- Not you, Suk Jin. - Aren't you on our team?
Can you please remember your team?
(He finally checks his team 3 hours into the shoot.)
You're not on this team.
She's teamed up with Se Chan and...
Yoon Kyung, Haha, and Se Chan are in first place.
(Anyway, Team Yoon Kyung is number 1.)
We won the game.
- And in second place... - It's us.
Eun Jin, Suk Jin, and Ji Hyo.
(Team Eun Jin is number 2.)
- I'm glad. - At least we came in second.
(1 member of this team will become a Penalty Man.)
You had 4, 5, 6 points respectively.
Is Team Penalty in last place again?
(Team Penalty Men came in last.)
- That was close. - We didn't lose as a team.
Jae Suk lost it for us.
You keep making me play games that I'm bad at.
(He's going through the last stage of strawberry phobia with no cure.)
It was wrong of you to add Jae Suk to your team.
(Who is the additional Penalty Man followed by Jae Suk?)
This game just isn't the one for me.
(Meanwhile, they arrive at the final mission.)
Right.
I mean it today.
I mean it.
(He notifies them he'll play as dirty as possible.)
Kwang Soo's terrifying me today.
He'll be like a mad man in this round.
His eyes seem determined.
We're in trouble today.
(His eyes almost turned white.)
Our fates were sealed...
(They're already worried about how dirty he'll play as a Penalty Man.)
the moment he joined...
- Team Penalty. - I'll be shooting.
- I'll shoot. - He's only joking.
(The bullet he used in Episode 521)
(He creates a sense of fear with an expired bullet.)
- Guys. - Yes?
Starting with the winning team, you'll choose the money you earned.
(Time to draw the R money based on the previous round's result)
All right, let's do this.
- It's us three, right? - Right.
- Go ahead. - Back in the day,
I used to play games like this a lot.
(The results are...)
Kwang Soo earned no money last time.
- 100 dollars! - No way, I got 80 dollars.
(Haha 100 dollars, Se Chan 80 dollars, Yoon Kyung 60 dollars,)
(Jong Kook 80 dollars, Ji Hyo 80 dollars, Eun Jin 60 dollars,)
- Nice. - Unbelievable.
(Suk Jin 40 dollars, Kwang Soo 60 dollars, So Min 60 dollars,)
I have 60 dollars!
(Sang Yi 20 dollars, and Jae Suk 0 dollars)
The money...
(Their respective mission funds have been decided.)
that you blindly selected in both rounds...
- is your total amount. - Got it.
Team Penalty will choose another teammate.
(A member of Team Eun Jin will become a Penalty Man.)
We thought about this...
(Team Penalty Men's stance is...)
- and the team... - That's right.
We can't have anyone strong on this team.
- We'll be at a disadvantage. - It won't be ideal for us.
(They want an easy opponent on their side to avoid getting the penalty.)
So we should choose from the weaker links.
(We need to pick one of the weak ones.)
How about Suk Jin?
- Suk Jin... - Yes, Suk Jin.
- How about Suk Jin? - Suk Jin...
(He gets picked 1st among all the candidates?)
Wait a second.
(The byword of weakness)
You'll choose Suk Jin over Ji Hyo and Eun Jin?
- He's the weakest link. - That must be our choice.
(We need to pick the weakest member.)
- The weakest link. - You see...
We must choose the weakest link.
(He can't refute.)
The issue with Suk Jin is this.
He tries to trick his own team members.
(Suk Jin tends to...)
- So Eun Jin might be better. - Right. Eun Jin would be better.
I think she would cause us less trouble, don't you think?
- Absolutely. - She must be honest and upright.
- We'd be at a disadvantage. - Of course.
- I really hope they won't pick me. - We should choose one of them.
Okay. 1, 2, 3.
(Which of Eun Jin and Suk Jin did Team Penalty Men choose?)
- Ahn Eun Jin. - Eun Jin.
(Ahn Eun Jin has been chosen as a new member!)
Go.
(Saddened)
- Just like this? - Eun Jin will be...
- a Penalty Man in this round. - Okay.
(Eun Jin will act as the Penalty Man from this race.)
- Okay. - Eun Jin.
(Welcome to the Penalty Men world.)
We can talk about the stock market with her during the race.
(They picked Eun Jin thinking she was an easy target.)
No. Don't even think about it.
(But later on, in the race,)
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, but I have no choice.
(she'll tear the most name tags off with her tenacity and strategies.)
She's running after us.
(What change will Eun Jin make as the blue-chip name tag taker?)
Eun Jin is no joke.
Through the final race, you can change the team to get a penalty,
(They can change the team that will get the penalty.)
and gained extra mission funds. It's Switch Penalty Men.
(They can even gain extra mission funds.)
(Final Mission: Switch Penalty Men)
That's the worst.
You'll be divided into Team Penalty and Team Non-penalty.
(The mission will start with Team Penalty and Team Non-penalty.)
It'll be 5 members versus 6 members at the beginning.
Each team will wear either red caps or blue caps.
(Team Penalty wears red caps, and the other wears blue caps.)
You can switch caps and join the other team...
(They can switch the teams by taking off a name tag.)
by taking off the name tag of a member of that team.
You're allowed to take off anyone's name tag.
(Time limit: 30 minutes)
30 minutes after you begin the race,
(The team with more Penalty Men will lose.)
the team with more Penalty Men will lose.
The Penalty Men on the losing team will get a penalty.
(The Penalty Men on the losing team will get a penalty.)
(The winning team will receive extra mission funds.)
And the winning team will receive extra mission funds.
The Penalty Men on the losing team will get a penalty.
(Rules)
And the winning team will receive extra mission funds.
(1. Switch teams by removing name tags.)
If they join our team,
(2. The team with more Penalty Men will lose after the race is over.)
- we all have to move to that team. - Exactly.
That's how you can calculate.
So people wearing the same color caps don't have to fight.
(3. The Penalty Men on the losing team will get a penalty.)
Correct. Take off the name tags of people in the other color.
You have to join the team with fewer Penalty Men.
Also, we'll announce which team has more Penalty Men...
(They'll announce which team has more Penalty Men every 5 minutes.)
every five minutes.
The result will be determined in the last minute.
(The victory will be determined at the last minute.)
In the last minute.
Everyone, please leave me alone just for today.
(Begging)
- We have to move to that team. - I'm begging you.
(She's always the target in these types of races.)
Please leave me alone.
I want her cap. I call dibs on her cap.
- Please leave me alone. - She's the easiest target.
(She'll be really popular today.)
I can't predict the result because of So Min.
Exactly. So Min will be the largest variable.
Prepare 20 caps for So Min.
I don't know which team So Min will end up on.
(Even for Penalty Men, they'll have to be on the fewer side.)
I started off on the wrong foot.
Also, we hid 10-dollar mission funds in different places.
(It's also important to find the hidden mission funds.)
- You can gain extra funds that way. - Okay.
- Everyone, you may leave now. - Let's go.
(Betrayal and wits will be very common in today's race!)
- This won't be easy. - We must move to that team.
We have to try at least.
(All members of Team Penalty put on red caps!)
It will be an intense war of nerves.
No one can predict...
(All members of Team Non-penalty put on blue caps!)
what could turn the game around at the end.
It's hard to predict.
I'll be tough today. I'll run really fast too.
So please stay alert.
(He seems determined to act up like crazy today.)
Kwang Soo said he'll be tough today.
(He'll target the crazy.)
So I'm going to be tough as well.
(Meanwhile, Haha...)
Let's save as much money as possible for now.
I need money...
(Haha plans to save money to get rid of penalty tickets.)
in order to get rid of as many penalty tickets as I can.
I will never be hit by water balloons in this cold weather.
(She looks unnecessarily serious.)
(She's full of enthusiasm.)
(5 seconds until the race starts.)
The race will begin shortly.
Five.
Four.
(Switch the teams by taking off a name tag.)
Three.
Two.
(The team with fewer Penalty Men will win.)
One.
Race, start.
(Currently, all Penalty Men are on Team Red.)
(They'd be at an advantage if they move to Team Blue.)
I have no time for this. I should take off a name tag first.
(Kwang Soo is going to move to Team Blue that has no Penalty Men.)
I should take off a name tag.
(Jae Suk has the same plan.)
- Oh, my. Jae Suk. - Hey, Sebastien.
Are you going to join Team Blue?
Well... I think...
I should move to your team no matter what, right?
Yes. You need a good strategy.
- Exactly. - Yes.
Wait. Just like this? You're attacking me right away?
(Grabbing)
- You know I have no choice. - Wait.
(He's taking off Se Chan's name tag just like this?)
- I have no choice. - Wait a second.
(Ripping)
- You know... I should... - My gosh.
- There must be some confrontation. - That's unnecessary.
(Dumbfounded)
There's no need.
(Jae Suk switches to Team Blue as soon as the race starts.)
It hasn't even been 10 seconds since the race began.
- Hey. - Jae Suk...
(Jae Suk already got ripped?)
- Already? We should run away. - Let's hurry up.
(Team Red has 4 Penalty Men, Team Blue has 1 Penalty Man.)
We should run away from them.
(They're running away from the Team Red members.)
- We should run away from them. - They will probably...
Kwang Soo! Kwang Soo, come over here.
(Sang Yi found the weakest members of Team Blue.)
Let's go.
- Why? - Come over here.
(Kwang Soo joins Sang Yi.)
(Penalty Men Kwang Soo and Sang Yi want to move to Team Blue!)
Hey, stop it. What are you doing?
(They successfully capture Ji Hyo.)
Take it off now. Hurry.
- Hey! - Hurry up.
- Why are you wearing a blue cap? - I took it off!
(Ripping)
When did you join that team?
(Kwang Soo rips off Ji Hyo's name tag and joins Team Blue.)
All right.
(Team Red has 3 Penalty Men, and Team Blue has 2 now.)
Take it off! Take it off, Sang Yi!
(Meanwhile, Sang Yi was chasing after Suk Jin.)
Jae Suk, why are you wearing a blue cap?
Why... Why is it blue?
(He's about to cry.)
- Listen. - When did you join that team?
Right now...
You should take off the name tag of anyone you see.
There he is.
(In front of Penalty Man Eun Jin,)
(the weakest member of Team Blue shows up.)
- Oh, my. Hello. - Hi.
(She's very polite.)
I'm just so glad to see you here.
- Hi. Bye. - Wait.
- Wait. - Bye!
(Suk Jin from the winning Team Blue tries to run away.)
Stop!
Get him.
(The only choice Suk Jin has is to run away as fast as he can.)
(But he gets caught quickly due to his poor cardiovascular endurance.)
Oh, my gosh.
Wait.
(Eun Jin gets a chance to join Team Blue.)
- Just for a moment. I'm so tired. - You caught me,
so let's take a break.
- I'm really sorry. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(She's polite even after capturing him.)
No way.
(After a quick apology, she reaches for his name tag.)
No need to apologize because you can't take it off.
You think?
(He's bluffing when he can't do anything.)
Really? Are you sure?
Outer reaping throw!
(She politely tries an outer reaping throw.)
Gosh. I'm running out of energy.
(After repeated attempts to perform an outer reaping throw,)
(Eun Jin succeeds her 1st name tag hunt.)
(She successfully takes off the name tag of the easiest target.)
Well... I saw it coming.
(They're exchanging their caps while catching their breath.)
Here you go.
(As Eun Jin joins Team Blue, Team Blue is losing!)
I'm sorry, Suk Jin.
- You have nothing to apologize for. - I'm sorry.
(Team Red is winning with 2 Penalty Men.)
Don't be.
Jae Suk, we have to keep our caps blue.
(The members have no idea who is winning.)
- But... - We don't know the exact numbers.
- We don't know yet. - Right.
- It's pointless to take it off. - It's pointless.
(They're trying to enter a meaningless armistice.)
It's pointless right now.
Okay. Let's...
(But...)
- You see, right now... - Jae Suk, why...
Why are you wearing a blue cap?
As soon as he saw me, he ripped my name tag off.
- He was so determined to do it. - Hey.
As soon as he saw my blue cap, he attacked me.
(He was competitive on switching to Team Blue.)
I'm relieved that you two are on the same team. Let's go, Ji Hyo.
(Because Kwang Soo is now on Team Blue, the score is the same.)
- We're on the same team now. - Se Chan.
- Take Jae Suk's name tag off. - Sorry?
Then hold him down.
Take it off! Take it off now!
(Se Chan!)
(Ripping off)
- There's no point. - I didn't know she'd take mine off.
- Gosh, you. - There's no point.
You should've ripped off only one of our name tags.
- Gosh, seriously. - You should have...
(They're making a meaningless switch of caps.)
Give it to me.
- Don't put it on like that. - Put their name tags back on them.
(Penalty Men Kwang Soo and Jae Suk are back on Team Red.)
- Se Chan, let's hurry up and go. - Okay.
(Eun Jin is the only Penalty Man on Team Blue.)
Why would you do that?
(Team Red has 4 Penalty Men, and Team Blue has 1.)
Run!
(After moving Penalty Men to Team Red, they're running away.)
- Hey, we're back on Team Blue. - Run!
Let's go and find some money.
(It's an empty envelope.)
Oh, those mean people.
(Team Red has 4 Penalty Men, and Team Blue has 1.)
(While running around, she meets...)
I wish I could have a sip of water.
(The red cap duo)
(They need to move to Team Blue!)
- Eun Jin. - Oh, my gosh.
- Wait. - Eun Jin.
(She lied down to protect her name tag.)
My gosh. This can't be happening.
Hey, wait. All right.
(The red cap duo has no intention of letting her go.)
- Eun Jin. - All right. Let me...
- I'll do it by myself. I don't... - Come on.
(Ripping)
Eun Jin, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
(Jae Suk moves to Team Blue alone in the end.)
I can't stand this anymore. This is ridiculous.
He's so sly.
(Team Red has 4 Penalty Men, Team Blue has 1, Jae Suk.)
- Eun Jin, here you go. - Okay.
(Sang Yi is quietly watching them.)
This is ridiculous. He's so sly.
(He's planning to move to Team Blue by ripping Jae Suk's name tag off.)
- Jae Suk is on Team Blue now. - Eun Jin, here you go.
Kwang Soo.
(Passing him by quietly)
Which team has more Penalty Men?
(I'm here.)
(Sang Yi succeeds in escaping Team Red!)
Hey!
(Team Red has 4 Penalty Men, Team Blue has 1, Sang Yi.)
- Gosh, seriously. - Let's stop this.
- Gosh. I mean... - That was so funny.
(Ripping)
(The merciless Eun Jin takes off even a passerby's name tag.)
- Gosh. I mean... - That was so funny.
What was that?
Let me pass by, will you?
- Hey! - Let me pass by, okay?
(The 4 red caps assemble.)
- Don't stretch your cap. - I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
- This is driving me nuts. - Team Red has more Penalty Men?
(Ripping)
- I'm on your team. - He's on Team Red too.
- Oh, he's on Team Red too. - Hey.
It makes me upset for no reason.
Check the color before ripping the name tag off.
- Check the color first. - How many Penalty Men are here?
(Eun Jin leaves knowing that things can get ugly.)
I'll leave. Please give me a moment.
- Check the color first. - How many Penalty Men are here?
Only two of you are Penalty Men.
Really?
- We might be at an advantage. - That's possible.
- Let's keep it this way. - We might have fewer Penalty Men.
(We could be winning.)
- If we hide ourselves... - So Min is the problem.
so no one can find us...
Let's hurry up and go. All the four of us together.
- We should stick together. - Let's not split up.
(The 4 members move in a hassle with hope.)
- We just have to keep this number. - That's right.
I can't believe I'm on the team with you guys out of all people.
- We're all so weak. - What a band of misfits.
(The 4 form a hopeless alliance.)
- We're all so weak. - Gosh.
And 2 of us are the bottom 2 in terms of appearance.
(Weakest fighting skills, Lowest appearance ranking)
True.
I can't believe this.
(The ugly ducklings are happy to be together.)
- We must keep our caps. - Yes, we must.
- Let the others fight in there. - We have only 30 minutes.
- Why don't we... - Okay.
(Rushing)
- What is it? - Hey, wait.
(As soon as Se Chan discovers the mission funds,)
- No. Wait, wait. No. Stop. - You brat.
(the hopeless brothers chase him like hyenas.)
- Stop it. - Hey.
(Their alliance breaks down over a small sum of money.)
Let's divide the money equally.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do that.
(They're genuinely fighting.)
- Wait. - Let's put it down for now.
- I found this. - How can we work together?
- Let's put it down for now. - Okay.
- Let's put it down. - All right.
(They don't trust each other to put it down on the floor.)
- But I'm the one who found it. - Okay.
- Put it down. Come on. - Put it down.
- Gosh. I can't believe you guys. - Don't be like this.
- Seriously, they're so mean. - Put your hand down.
- Put it down. - Okay. Let's all put it down.
- Put it down. - Put it down.
(The 4 red caps finally agree to put it on the floor.)
- Okay. - Let it go on the count of three.
- This is what we'll do. - It's torn into pieces.
(The envelope is destroyed into pieces.)
- Let's put it down. - Let's just divide it by four.
(The eldest brother's wisdom)
We'll play rock-paper-scissors and let the winner have it all.
(They divide the R money under Suk Jin's leadership.)
That'll sort this out. Let's divide it by four.
- It's not valid without this piece. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- This is the most important piece. - True.
(They'll give everything to whoever wins rock-paper-scissors.)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors, and let the winner take it all.
- Do we have to go this far? - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
- I won. - Hold on.
- I won. - Gosh.
(Putting in his mouth)
- Hold on. - Darn it.
(If I can't have it, I'd rather swallow it.)
(If I can't have it, let's share it.)
Let's get rid of it.
This never happened.
- It says 10 dollars here. - It's written on that piece?
(Does this count?)
- It's written on mine too. - Hang on.
Can you see?
(They must have all the pieces.)
Mine says 10 dollars.
- But it's torn in half. - He swallowed it.
- And I even won. - Make it a whole piece.
(The four brothers became closer than ever.)
- It says 10 dollars. - You have to have our pieces too.
That's impossible.
Let me tell you the current status.
(Time for an announcement)
There are more Penalty Men...
on Team Red.
- Darn it. - We should rip off a name tag.
There are more Penalty Men...
(There are three Penalty Men on Team Red.)
- on Team Red. - Darn it.
(Team Red is losing.)
(There are two Penalty Men on Team Blue.)
Darn it.
(They run as fast as they can to find the members of Team Blue.)
There are more Penalty Men on Team Red.
(The rest of the members heard the current status as well.)
You mean there are more Penalty Men on Team Red?
(Let's switch to Team Blue.)
(The Penalty Men on Team Blue are being chased.)
Who is that?
(The man who's crazy about the blue cap)
Rock-paper... Let's play it fair.
This way.
(While the insane man and Eun Jin confront,)
- Hang on! - Suk Jin.
I'll lie on the floor.
- Be careful! - I'm being serious.
(Big Nose acts like he's worried...)
(and mercilessly ripped off Eun Jin's name tag.)
Come on, Suk Jin!
(Big Nose transfers to Team Blue that is winning.)
- I'm sorry. - Switch your caps.
You have to keep moving.
(Big Brother Big Nose leaves as soon as getting the blue cap.)
Hey, wait! You can't rip it off right away!
(Ripping off)
(Team Red, Team Blue)
It wasn't mine that got ripped off.
(Big Nose is back on Team Red in less than 10 seconds.)
There are more Penalty Men on Team Red now?
You have 10 seconds to run.
(There are two Penalty Men on Team Blue.)
How many Penalty Men are on Team Red now?
There are more Penalty Men on Team Red.
If we just wait, there will be lesser Penalty Men on Team Red.
(Cooling his heart down)
- Did you find any money? - Is your heart okay?
I'm okay. I ran too hard.
(Suk Jin's heartbeat rises high.)
- Are you okay? - No, I'm not.
I think you should sit for a while.
I think they'll come for me if I just stay in one place.
That's right. They'll just come.
(A sudden dance time when they're losing)
I like this move.
(The tour bus dance move Jae Suk fell for)
Your dance skills... I like this move.
Where did you learn that?
(The two middle-aged men are crazy about retro.)
I mean...
Where did you learn this move?
It's a move from "Saturday Night Fever".
Oh, really?
(Being cute)
I think So Min found her signature move.
This is not the time to be playing around.
(While they enjoy watching So Min's dance...)
- If we just stay in one spot, - Over here!
(In a rush)
- they'll come to us. - I got Team Blue here!
(Eun Jin yields Haha to So Min after catching him.)
I'll send you away... No, you can't!
I'm coming!
(Is So Min dashing to rip off the name tag?)
- The Penalty Man. - Okay!
You're ripping it off now?
(Penalty Man So Min is on Team Blue now.)
- So Min is on the other team now. - The Penalty Man is gone.
- So Min is on the other team. - All right.
We're winning.
(Currently, Team Red is winning.)
Jae Suk, we're winning.
(Thanks to So Min who dashed, the table is turned.)
Keep it down.
- That fool. - Keep it down.
(Eun Jin is looking for a place to hide.)
What should I do now?
I should look for the money.
(So Min got fooled by Eun Jin...)
I have no idea what's going on.
(and became the sacrifice.)
Which team has more Penalty Men?
(She's moving with red caps.)
- All right. It's time. - Eun Jin...
(Revealing the current situation)
- Okay, tell us the status. - Currently,
- Team Blue is losing. - We got this.
- Currently, Team Blue is losing. - We got this.
- Then... - We're all set, Jae Suk.
(There are more Penalty Men on Team Blue.)
We're all set. They're losing.
You mean Team Blue has more Penalty Men?
(If this continues, it's advantageous to Team Red.)
- Yes, they do. - We got this.
We got this. Let's pause then.
(Gosh.)
Team Blue is losing.
Jae Suk, what's important is...
- The three of us... - Sang Yi!
can follow So Min around.
- What? - Just follow...
(Haha wants to protect So Min and stop her from coming to Team Red.)
If we just follow So Min around, we'll never lose.
- Sang Yi, come here. - He's right.
We can be So Min's shadow.
(It's the shadow strategy.)
- We should guard So Min. - Then we'll never lose.
We should guard So Min.
(Right then, Sang Yi joined Team Red after ripping Eun Jin's name tag.)
- Kwang Soo is on Team Blue. - Look at her.
She'll end up getting the penalty, but she likes it.
(So Min doesn't exactly hate red caps' attention.)
Because she's getting all the attention.
- Since we're guarding her. - We're like your fan club.
- Jeon So Min! - Jeon So Min!
(Sang Yi joins and pretends to her fan.)
- Jeon... - Listen.
I won't get my name tag ripped,
so give me 10 dollars each.
- 10 dollars each? - I won't get it ripped.
(She tries to make a deal.)
I'll make sure to guard it and stick with you.
So Min, you don't have a choice.
In other words, you're our hostage.
(While the fan club ceremony is on,)
- So Min. - What is she talking about?
- Someone is coming. - But you can't...
(Team Blue's Penalty Man Kwang Soo appears.)
Team Blue is losing.
(So Min is seeking a chance to leave Team Blue.)
- How did you... - If we stick to these members...
(Attacking Jae Suk)
- Hey. - Is she serious?
(Se Chan is...)
(Se Chan is giving So Min a sideways glance.)
(There are two Penalty Men on Team Red now.)
(If one more goes to Team Red...)
Help me. Help me now!
- Help me! - He ripped off So Min's name tag.
(After thinking, Se Chan eliminates So Min.)
But I almost got it! I almost got it.
(As a result, there are three Penalty Men in Team Red.)
I grabbed the tip of his name tag.
(Ripping off)
Get ready to run, Kwang Soo.
(Then Sang Yi rips off Kwang Soo's name tag.)
Switch your cap with Sang Yi's.
- What's the status now? - We're back to square one.
(Team Blue is winning again.)
Back to square one.
(Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, and So Min are losing again.)
Come on!
Wait a minute. I'm on the same team as them again?
(Looking at the three people in front,)
What color is my cap? Is it red?
There are three Penalty Men on Team Red already.
(Team Blue is winning obviously.)
- We have to run. - They have more Penalty Men!
(Sang Yi and Se Chan ditch the fan club and run.)
They have more Penalty Men now!
It hasn't been 10 seconds yet!
(Table is turned. Team Red is losing again.)
- It hasn't been 10 seconds yet! - Yours wasn't ripped!
Hey, this is so tiring.
(Table is turned in no time.)
Who came up with this race?
(It's such a tiring game.)
- This is driving me crazy. - Who did?
Hey! What happened?
(At that moment, Suk Jin who has no idea appears.)
- This is so exhausting! - It's the three of us again?
This is the worst race.
(It's a familiar look.)
- This is the worst. - You know,
I'll never be able to win no matter what I do.
- We can just... - But we can't be doing nothing.
(Although he never tried hard, he gives up due to fatigue.)
make our moves a few minutes before the race is over.
(They decide to use their energy 3 minutes before the race is over.)
How do we find them?
(Right then, Eun Jin from Team Blue appears.)
(As soon as they hear Eun Jin's voice,)
(he goes at her right away.)
- I know. - We can't find them anywhere.
(Dashing)
- He's not even human. - What's...
(He goes at her without even hesitating.)
- He's not even human. - Why are you doing this?
- What's the current status? - You're not even human.
(He forgot what they just told him and just dashes.)
What's the status? Which team is losing?
- Why would you go after her? - How can I...
- Where is the money? - Which team has more Penalty Men?
(Then the scapegoat walks toward them.)
- I have no idea. - Did you find any, Eun Jin?
I found really little.
(Suk Jin loses his patience and attacks Eun Jin.)
(Ripping off)
You can't rip off mine! I'm on your team.
So now...
(3 name tags are ripped off in no time.)
- What just happened? - Let's recall what happened.
- The blue cap goes to him. - Yes, it should.
(In short,)
Eun Jin's cap goes to Suk Jin.
(Eun Jin and Suk Jin switch.)
- It's mine. - And then...
- Watch. - Then it goes to Kwang Soo.
- Why? - Because he ripped off your name.
(Suk Jin and Kwang Soo switch.)
And then it comes to me.
(The blue cap goes to Jae Suk?)
You got it, right?
(The blue cap goes to Jae Suk.)
Then...
Then I'm going to run, but you're a fool.
Why?
(What?)
- Why? - Why?
(But Team Blue is winning.)
- You sent him away. - That's right.
- That's right. Come here. - We should go.
(Eun Jin misunderstood.)
- What's happening? - What's happening?
(Is she an idiot?)
- Which team is winning? - We should go.
(Even Yoon Kyung and Jong Kook who were passing by got confused.)
- What's happening? - What's happening?
Which team is winning?
What's going on?
(Ripping)
- You ripped off his name tag? Fine. - What was that?
(Yoon Kyung ripped off Kwang Soo's name tag.)
- Fine. - What was that?
Wait.
(There are 3 Penalty Men in Team Blue.)
That's a good thing. Team Red was winning.
Why? They said Team Blue has more Penalty Men.
- No, that's not true. - I know!
(Team Eun Jin's winning by chance.)
But you're not Penalty Man.
Can you put this back on?
We're totally safe. Follow me.
(Team Red, Team Blue)
- Follow me. Hurry. - We...
We're safe. We sent the Penalty Man to Team Blue again.
(The red caps run away.)
- We are... - What a relief.
Why did Yoon Kyung rip off Kwang Soo's name tag?
(Jae Suk of Team Blue is losing again.)
Yoon Kyung ripped off my name tag.
Then we'll have more Penalty Men.
I know. If you just stay still...
(Meanwhile, a man walks by with a lot of money.)
Where did you find the money?
- Where was it? - Jae Suk.
- Hey, give me 10 dollars. - What? Don't be ridiculous.
- Hey, give me 10 dollars. - I gave out a lot.
(Someone earned a lot of mission funds.)
You should look for the money.
(The two became beggars again.)
There are more Penalty Men on our team now.
Why did you have to go after her?
No, I got mine ripped off.
Will you please use your brain?
Think before you rip off someone's name tag.
Running around like a headless chicken won't get you a win.
- Jae Suk, you're... - That's not how...
- the variety shows these days work. - Jae Suk.
(Use your brain.)
Think before you move. Think about it.
(From an idiot to an idiot)
- Okay? If you play like that, - Jae Suk.
you'll always get the penalty.
I think...
(Reserved for a water bomb)
you and I will be going home completely wet.
- We're totally safe. - We totally are.
(Meanwhile, the 3 red caps that ran away...)
They'll come rip our name tags off,
- so we should run away. - Can't we rip off theirs?
(decide to keep running away and avoid Team Blue.)
But this is a dead-end.
Let's go back to the hallway.
- Assume that they're not there. - But we are... We need...
(The weak members must gather to survive.)
two Penalty Men anyway.
- We'll be in trouble if we have... - He's coming!
He's coming!
We should run to the other side!
(Kwang Soo is chasing them.)
Run away!
(When Kwang Soo chases after them,)
Hurry! Go!
(Suk Jin goes into the room, and Yoon Kyung stays in the hall.)
- Welcome. - What?
Welcome.
(He waits on the other side and captures her.)
What?
- Welcome. - What... What is going on?
Come here.
(She tries to fight Jae Suk off.)
Yoon Kyung.
I need to rip off the name tag.
- Why? - Come on.
- I will reach behind your neck. - Walk away.
(She lies down.)
Over there,
- Suk Jin is in the room. - Where?
(Tattling)
(She gives him her team member's location.)
- That room. - You need to take me there.
- Over there. - You need to take me there.
- Where? - Over there.
That room.
Once I see him,
(She tells the direction on her back.)
- I will rip off his name tag. - Really?
- Let's go. - Then...
- I will take you to the room. - Okay. Then I will let you go.
- Open the door, okay? - Okay.
(Dragging)
- Where is he? - In there.
(Guiding kindly)
- Is he in "The Penthouse" room? - Yes.
I am serious. He is hiding in there.
(Looking around)
- I don't see him. - He is hiding in there.
Open the door.
Bring Suk Jin out.
- Really? - Yes.
(She enters the room as if nothing has happened.)
(Suk Jin is here.)
What? Did you sell me out?
Did you sell me out?
- No. - You were talking to someone.
(He has good hearing.)
- No, I wasn't. - No?
- I... - Jae Suk.
I was going to hide with you,
(Lying with her eyes wide open)
but I couldn't find you.
Where did Jae Suk go? He was chasing after us.
(Whispering)
- I don't know. - You don't know?
- He almost ripped off my name tag. - Stay in here.
(Peek-a-boo)
Where are you going?
(Due to her tattling, Jae Suk catches a red cap.)
Hey.
Hey!
Yoon Kyung, please hold him.
(The whistleblower runs away.)
What is going on?
Did you sell me out?
Come on.
(He successfully arrests the fugitive.)
I mean...
Yoon Kyung, just you wait.
(She runs away at full speed while Suk Jin threatens her.)
This is nerve-wracking.
(While Team Red is winning, there isn't much time left.)
- Team Red. - I need to go over there.
Yoon Kyung.
(He finds the target.)
- There are more on Team Blue. - Jae Suk was...
(3 Team Red members gathered including Yoon Kyung.)
on Team Red.
- He is a Penalty Man. - Yes.
- Is he on Team Red? - Yes.
There are members of Team Red. I am Team Red, right?
Am I Team Blue?
(He attacks Yoon Kyung for revenge!)
What?
(He succeeded to have his revenge.)
- How could you betray me? - It's better to be...
(Suk Jin and Yoon Kyung switch.)
on Team Red.
- It's better to be on Team Red. - Yes.
(Ji Hyo spots So Min, Team Red's Penalty Man.)
Team Blue has fewer Penalty Men.
(Penalty Men)
- Really? - Yes. We have fewer Penalty Men.
(There are fewer Penalty Men on Team Blue?)
- We have fewer Penalty Men. - Hold on.
Penalty Men!
(They spot Team Red's Penalty Men, Jae Suk and Eun Jin!)
(So Min is in Team Red too.)
- Look at that. - Team Red.
(There are more Penalty Men on Team Red.)
What?
Hey!
- We are Team Red. What is it? - What is it?
(Table is turned again.)
Hurry up.
(Team Blue is winning.)
- Why are they running away? - Kwang Soo. Hold on.
(Sang Yi and Kwang Soo are the only Penalty Men on Team Blue.)
So Min is on Team Red. That team has three Penalty Men.
We just need to protect ourselves.
(Excited)
Watch out for Jae Suk.
The Penalty Men must be at each other's throats.
Gosh, how do you know which side to join?
Haha!
Haha, we are the only Penalty Men on the team.
We just need to keep it this way.
- Our team has only two Penalty Men. - Really? Are you sure?
(Kwang Soo tells Haha that it's advantageous for them.)
The Penalty Men of that team have no reason to rip off...
(Team Red, Team Blue)
Team Blue's name tags.
Then Team Blue would have more Penalty Men.
I need to rip off Team Blue's name tag.
(Less than 7 minutes left. They must join Team Blue.)
I think I should do that.
There they are.
(He spots Team Blue.)
Team Blue members are gathered outside.
Then...
- I don't have anything. - Hey, hold on.
I can't beat you guys...
(Suk Jin wants a blue cap.)
in terms of speed or strength.
Both of you are Penalty Men, right?
(Sang Yi and Kwang Soo want to keep the blue cap.)
(Hold on.)
(It's better to have fewer Penalty Men in Team Blue.)
(In that case...)
(Suk Jin, rip off Sang Yi's name tag.)
I can't beat you guys in terms of speed or strength.
- You understood the rules, right? - I...
(Rip it off.)
You understood the rules, right?
I understood them perfectly.
(Now is the time.)
Are you going to be this way?
Hold on.
(Ripping off)
(Kwang Soo and Suk Jin got him.)
Okay. I did it.
- Let's go. - We need to run away.
- Suk Jin, So Min is coming. - 1, 2, 3,
(Suk Jin and Kwang Soo run away after seeing So Min.)
4, 5...
We are safe. We are totally safe.
(Team Blue became safer.)
(Team Blue loses Sang Yi, a Penalty Man.)
I am the only Penalty Man...
(Kwang Soo is the only Penalty Man in Team Blue!)
on Team Blue.
- 7, 8, - What's the current situation...
(Two people remain where Traitor Giraffe rampaged through.)
- nine, - for Team Red?
- 10. Okay. - What's the current situation?
How many Penalty Men are on Team Red?
(Sang Yi's out of himself after getting fooled by Kwang Soo.)
- Let's... - Let's think.
- You and me. - Let's think.
(He comes to his senses and figures out what just happened.)
- Kwang Soo is on Team Blue. - Kwang Soo is the only one...
- There are five Penalty Men, right? - Yes.
Kwang Soo is the only Penalty Man on Team Blue.
(Unfortunately, Kwang Soo's winning.)
- Jae Suk is on Team Red. - The other four are on Team Red.
Then...
This is...
I figured this out after running around for 10 minutes.
(Shocked)
I trusted Kwang Soo.
Why did you trust Kwang Soo?
(Yoon Kyung, a member of the Team Blue, is walking around by herself.)
(Hiding)
(She spots Jae Suk.)
Yoon Kyung.
(Yoon Kyung doesn't know that Team Blue is winning.)
What is going on?
It's more advantageous for you to join Team Red.
Why?
Team Blue currently has more Penalty Men.
(False information)
- So I will switch teams with you. - Why would you do that?
(Absolute lie)
- It's 3 versus 2, - Okay.
so it doesn't affect me that much to switch teams with you.
I will do it for you.
But we don't know...
(Jae Suk tries to fool her,)
the current situation.
(and Yoon Kyung suspects him.)
That's why I want to try switching teams.
(He fools her with a serious face.)
It's a good idea.
Right? Let me rip off your name tag.
Or you can rip mine off.
(The name tag)
You can rip off mine.
- I will rip off yours. - Okay.
(Fooled by Jae Suk, she reaches for his name tag.)
(Running away)
(She pretends to rip it off then runs away.)
I have had it with you.
(Yoon Kyung suspects Jae Suk and runs away.)
Listen.
(She soon gets caught as she's slow.)
What is your problem?
(Yoon Kyung tends to be suspicious.)
Why...
It's either you rip off my name tag or I rip off yours. I have no time.
(But Jae Suk's lie continues.)
All right. Gosh, it's stiff.
(She falls for it and offers her name tag.)
- No one ripped it off before. - Yes.
- The race ends in five minutes. - Really?
(Only 5 minutes left.)
Will you give us the current situation now?
(Revealing the current situation)
- Yes. - Okay.
All right. Team Blue...
Team Blue is winning.
(Excuse me?)
(Laughing)
(You can sense her rage from the back.)
Oh, that hurts!
(The cheater runs away.)
He is too fast!
(Crying)
He is too fast.
(Jae Suk manages to lose her.)
He fooled me.
Team Red is losing.
(So Min, Team Red's Penalty Man, hears the news.)
This is driving me crazy.
What should I do?
Is there no way to win?
(Less than 5 minutes remaining)
I see Team Blue.
(At this rate, Team Blue will win.)
Someone is over there, right?
(Either knock them down...)
Hey!
Team Blue... I am Team Blue, right?
(or hide...)
Where is everyone hiding?
(or chase them.)
Everyone must be hiding.
(Blue caps try to protect their victory.)
If Team Blue members scatter, we will win for sure.
30 seconds remain.
(30 seconds before the race ends)
Run away, Team Blue!
(The last 30 seconds to determine to result)
She is coming after us!
I need to keep this cap.
(My cap)
I need to keep this cap no matter what.
15 seconds remain. 15 seconds.
(15 seconds before the race ends)
(Kwang Soo in a blue cap is looking for a place to hide.)
Jae Suk!
What? Why are you on Team Blue?
Why are you... Hold on!
(There are two blue caps.)
Why are you on Team Blue?
(Why is Sang Yi in a blue cap as well?)
(3 Penalty Men in Team Blue)
- Hold on! What? - Hey!
- Hey! - What is...
(At that moment,)
Hold on!
(Suk Jin appears in a red cap.)
- There are so many of them. - What?
- Hey! - What is going on?
(At this rate, Team Blue will lose.)
So Min!
(Where is she?)
(So Min of Team Red is hiding.)
Team Red has fewer Penalty Men.
Team Blue has more, right?
What is going on?
(Then their target is Suk Jin.)
5, 4, 3...
(The last 5 seconds will determine the result.)
5, 4...
- Three... - Get him!
(If the race ends this way, Penalty Men of Team Blue will lose.)
5, 4, 3...
Get him!
(Ripping)
(Kwang Soo ripped off Suk Jin's name tag!)
(The race ends.)
(Each team currently has 2 Penalty Men.)
Please gather around.
Hey, Sang Yi is a Penalty Man!
(Team Red, Team Blue)
(The Non-penalty Men's cap colors get revealed.)
What happened?
What?
It's blue.
(There are only two people left.)
Did Team Blue win?
We don't know yet.
(Jong Kook and Eun Jin will determine the result.)
Blue...
Which color is Eun Jin's cap?
(Since Eun Jin is a Penalty Man, her team will lose.)
(What are their cap colors?)
Hey.
Eun Jin is on Team Blue.
(Eun Jin, a Penalty Man, is wearing a blue cap.)
- We lost. - Team Red won!
(There are 3 Penalty Men in Team Blue.)
Team Red won.
Okay!
(Team Red won.)
(We were winning.)
At the last moment...
Kwang Soo came out of nowhere.
(Kwang Soo made the right choice by ripping off Suk Jin's name tag!)
Team Red won!
What?
(What?)
When did this happen?
Jong Kook is on Team Red.
(Jong Kook is wearing a red cap.)
(What happened?)
What happened?
She is coming after us!
(Right before the end of the race)
I got you, Muscle Monster!
(Eun Jin caught Protein Monster by chasing him fiercely.)
It's better for me to rip off the name tag.
(But both Ji Hyo and Yoon Kyung had a red cap.)
It's better for me to switch teams.
I should switch over to Team Red.
Okay.
(If 3 out of 5 members are Non-penalty Men in Team Red...)
I should switch over to Team Red.
(Jong Kook noticed that if he joins Team Red, he'll win.)
Rip it off.
(Thus, he gave up his blue cap!)
(He sent Eun Jin to Team Blue and solidified his victory.)
Jong Kook, did you switch teams at the last moment?
Jong Kook.
(Protein Monster can strategize now.)
We lost because of Jong Kook.
- I did it. - Jong Kook.
Let's move to the ending location.
(They move to the ending location for the finale penalty!)
Shall we go?
All right, everyone.
Thanks to Kwang Soo's buzzer-beater,
(Team Red won!)
Team Blue lost.
Thus, Team Blue's...
(Sang Yi, Jae Suk, and Eun Jin will carry out the penalty.)
Eun Jin, Sang Yi, and Jae Suk...
will get the penalty.
- The decision is final. - Yes.
Here is what the rest of you will do.
(But it's not over yet.)
the winning team...
will select the R money one last time.
(Team Red who won will draw R money one last time.)
Really?
(Crying)
Pick one each.
Gosh, I picked 10 dollars.
Look at Ji Hyo.
Four dollars.
How about you, Yoon Kyung?
(How much money did Yoon Kyung pick?)
What's the number?
Is it zero?
(Again?)
(She got zero again.)
(She picked zero all day today.)
You got zero all day long.
- What is up with her today? - We will get the penalty together.
She is really bad at games.
Before the penalty ticket lottery,
(Before the penalty ticket lottery,)
you can use the mission fund...
(they now have the chance to discard their penalty tickets...)
- to discard your penalty tickets. - Okay.
(using the mission funds they acquired.)
You remember the 16 penalty tickets, right?
(16 penalty tickets range from 11 to 44.)
- Yes. - Yes.
You can discard 1 penalty ticket for 20 dollars.
(They can discard 1 penalty ticket for 20 dollars.)
- 20 dollars? - We can't discard that many.
(Discard more tickets to decrease the chance of getting the penalty!)
Pay up and pick the numbers you want to discard.
(Afterward, two numbers will be chosen by lottery.)
Discard the number you think will get chosen.
(The one with the penalty number will receive the penalty.)
(The final Penalty Men will be hit with a strong water bomb!)
(The penalty number)
I don't know which number will get chosen.
It's impossible to know.
(He doesn't know which number to discard.)
There are so many.
It wasn't my goal to rip off the name tags.
(She has a lot of R money.)
I will discard these tickets.
(She discards 14 tickets with 280 dollars.)
Okay. If you leave them there, we will take them.
I have two tickets left. I won't get chosen, right?
(The remaining tickets)
I bet you do.
I will pay up 320 dollars.
(Jong Kook pays 320 dollars.)
- 320 dollars. - 320 dollars?
(Even the staff members are surprised.)
Yes. Count them.
Did he discard all the tickets?
- Did you discard all the tickets? - Do you still have money left?
(He still has some money left even after discarding all tickets.)
Yes, I do.
Jong Kook discarded all the tickets.
(Jong Kook is now exempted from the penalty.)
- I have 40 dollars left. - What?
- You have to turn it in. - Really?
(He leisurely turns in the remaining 40 dollars.)
- How did he do that? - What?
(What's with him?)
(Impressive)
He is so frugal.
Is he the production crew or what?
(Did you print R money?)
While you guys focused on the cap, I searched for the R money.
(Jong Kook only focused on collecting R money.)
People pretended not to see him when they ran into him.
(Protein Monster, we didn't see anything.)
- Seriously. - He is too scary.
Did you acknowledge him?
(How about you?)
(He's the first one to turn a blind eye.)
I pretended not to see him.
Show us your tickets.
(The status on the penalty tickets is revealed.)
Please let the number be three.
- Please. - Please let the number be three.
Kwang Soo has a high chance of getting the penalty.
Why do I have so many penalty tickets?
(Filled)
Hey, I have more.
(Out of the 7 of them, who will receive the penalty?)
I have the most number of penalty tickets.
I will pick the first digit.
(The staff will pick the first digit.)
- Please. The 1st digit. - 3.
(The first digit...)
2 or 3.
(can increase or decrease the chances of the penalty!)
All right. The first digit.
(What's the first digit?)
Please don't let it be one.
- Two. - Okay!
Okay!
He is set.
I am set. I am safe.
(So Min who only had numbers starting with 1 is safe.)
- I have 2 numbers left. - The 1st digit.
(Ji Hyo is also exempted.)
23 and 22.
Haha, you and I have the same numbers.
(Se Chan and Haha both still have chances.)
- You and I have the same numbers. - 21 and 22?
Please let it be 3 or 4.
(The last digit)
- 3 or 4. - 3 or 4.
(Suk Jin's numbers are included.)
- My numbers are 21 and 22 too. - Really?
- 3 or 4. - My numbers are 21 and 22 too.
(Yoon Kyung's numbers are included.)
3 or 4.
- 3 or 4. - Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo still has 2 numbers.)
Hey.
- No, no. - You shouldn't celebrate yet.
(He was too hasty in congratulating himself.)
I thought you were set.
- Okay, okay. - 3 or 4.
(The fate now is in the hands of the last digit.)
- 3 or 4. - 3 or 4.
- I picked it. - Two.
(He caught the ball.)
3 or 4.
(Who will get to experience the water bomb?)
Please let it be four. Then no one will be picked.
- 3 or 4. - 3 or 4.
- Two. - Bo Pil!
All right.
22.
(I'm done.)
Kwang Soo is ruined!
(Congratulations on getting chosen.)
- That was quick. - All right.
(Speechless)
Okay, okay.
22.
(Yoon Kyung avoided getting picked for the penalty!)
- That was quick. - All right.
(Let's get the penalty together.)
Okay, okay.
- Did you pick it on purpose? - No, I didn't.
Pick again.
(They can't believe the probability.)
This makes no sense.
- Yoon Kyung, how about you? - I didn't get picked.
- She has so many tickets. - Excuse me?
(She didn't get picked amid so many numbers?)
How did that happen?
How did she avoid getting picked?
She is good at games.
- She is the master. - Yoon Kyung is good at games.
- She is the master. - Okay.
(She gets lucky in the end.)
(I'm so happy.)
Everyone I had hoped for will receive the penalty.
(I'm happy.)
This makes no sense.
You and I will be going home completely wet.
(Kwang Soo's prediction came true.)
(Driving Out Bad Luck Penalty)
2021 New Year Driving Out Bad Luck Race.
Driving out bad luck.
(Se Chan got exempted thanks to the Relief Chance.)
2021 New Year Driving Out Bad Luck Race.
Driving out bad luck.
1, 2, 3.
(The water bomb is ready.)
(Staggering)
That was incredible.
(The water bomb hit them hard!)
(He looks ugly.)
That was incredible.
That's it!
(Highly satisfied)
(Retching)
(They can't help but become affected.)
That's it.
- That's it. - I just gargled.
- It was like a disaster movie. - That's it.
(They all got showered at once.)
- That's it. - Thank you for your hard work.
(They drove out bad luck for 2021.)
(We thank Eun Jin, Sang Yi, and Yoon Kyung...)
(for joining the 2021 New Year Driving Out Bad Luck Race.)
(Running Gym)
Catch him!
- Stop being flippant! - It doesn't work now.
(This is the home ground of the most mischievous members.)
- I won! - From the penthouse...
(Will the gym get new visitors?)
in a nearby neighborhood,
(3 guests from "The Penthouse")
- people came to join. - Yoon Jong Hun.
(Yoon Jong Hun)
Logan Lee.
(Park Eun Seok)
- Agency. - Agency.
(Ha Do Kwon)
Do Kwon, are you here to get Jong Kook?
I have no greed today.
He will win.
(Dual)
What is he doing?
(He returns to being the game changer right away.)
I just heard his switch getting flipped on.
- Next. 2, 1. - I can't remember!
(Running Man's athletic meeting starts!)
- Think! - Jong Hun.
(Shouts...)
(and theft bombard them as they get used to the show.)
I don't have it!
He slapped him in the face!
(Running Man shows them the harsh variety show environment.)
- There is blood. - Whose blood is it?
I can't trust you.
(The 3 guests move to the dark side.)
- "The Penthouse". - What is this?
This is driving me insane.
(They use upgraded fouls and adjust to the show!)
You can't do that!
Then I would've taken it off as soon as we started!
Left, right.
(The determined trio...)
What is your problem?
(and the mischievous members of Running Man have a match!)
That's good.
- Suk Jin's top ripped. - This is driving me insane.
(Which team will win the athletic meet?)
(2021 Running Man Neighborhood Athletic Meet with "The Penthouse")
Hang on until the end!