(We are realizing the value
of things that we take for granted.)
- Hello.
We're shooting the opening
in the open air after a long time.
- The weather is really nice.
- It's really good.
Weather like this doesn't
last for long.
It's a fine fall day.
- The weather is really nice.
- Look at the sky.
Se Chan broke my spirits...
- this morning.
- Why?
- He told me some bad news.
- Why? What is it?
I promised her
to set her up with a guy.
- You mean So Min?
- Yes.
But it turns out
he has a girlfriend.
(It turns out
her date has a girlfriend.)
Hey, why would you set her up
with a guy who has a girlfriend?
- I didn't know that.
- He's strange.
So here's what I think.
I think Se Chan has a crush on me.
(I think Se Chan has a crush on me.)
Gosh, this is
what you wanted to say.
- My gosh.
- He's...
- She's scary.
- You just can't stop smiling.
Gosh, no.
- I should hide my gums.
- I think he likes me.
He keeps interrupting me.
I'm not interrupting you.
I just didn't know that.
- Why did you not check it first?
- Right.
- I was going to...
- Ji Hyo is here.
- Ji Hyo is coming.
- Hello.
- Ji Hyo.
- Hi, Ji Hyo.
- Jong Kook is here too.
- He's wearing long pants.
- Hey.
- It looks like a thimble.
I was told to dress like this.
A white shirt and jeans.
- A white shirt and jeans.
- Jeans.
Right. I saw that.
What? Did you guys
compare your looks?
(Haha compared his looks
with Kwang Soo's while drunk.)
(- I look handsome.
- Me too. We looked good back then.)
(Haha versus Kwang Soo)
(That day, I just woke up
and went out without washing up.)
(Haha is good looking.)
(Kwang Soo is more handsome.)
(Haha is so cool.)
(I think Kwang Soo is better.)
- He asked who looked better.
- Haha posted it...
- on his social media.
- Why did you guys do that?
I didn't do it.
- I don't even care about him.
- We both think...
- Why did you two do such a thing?
- I didn't start it.
- I didn't even care.
- But he added a comment.
- It ended with my victory.
- Really?
Because you started it.
That's because it was your account.
He wrote comments
only to those who supported him.
(Haha is the most handsome and
fashionable member in Running Man.)
You're the worst.
- I mean...
- He's so sly.
(He manipulated the public opinion.)
He didn't say anything
to those who mentioned my name.
- I can see that.
- And...
I wasn't going to say this,
but you two can't make
a bet like that.
You guys can't even make the cut.
- Jae Suk.
- You mean their level.
You can't even be compared with us.
I have the rankings
of the members in mind.
This is frustrating.
Only those who are
high in ranks can do this.
- You're mistaken.
- It's not that you're ugly.
But you're just okay.
And you're ugly.
Gosh, no. I'm not ugly.
Actually, this is what
we've been curious about.
I wonder how the two female
members would rank their looks.
Gosh, that doesn't matter.
- Are you asking seriously?
- Objectively...
Are you being serious?
- I know. It can be subjective.
- This is hard for me.
I can't decide anything
before seeing them naked.
(I can't decide anything
before seeing them naked.)
- What is she talking about?
- My gosh.
- Hey.
- No, that's not what I mean.
- Just consider our looks.
- I mean...
You look different only with a hat.
Haha is wearing many items.
The rankings decided
by Ji Hyo and So Min...
mean nothing to me.
- That's true.
- Right?
At least I can pick
the worst member.
Who is it?
She's looking at Suk Jin.
Suk Jin.
- Come here.
- I think...
(She picks Suk Jin
with no hesitation.)
- I can't believe this. Hey!
- It's just her taste.
Hey, you're really...
- It's her taste.
- You are not objective at all.
Just admit it.
- So Suk Jin is the last.
- The fifth...
The fifth place is Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk is ranked 5th.)
Do I look worse than him?
I don't care whom she picks.
The two Petty Gang members are out.
The two members
of Petty Gang are out.
Continue. Who's next?
The fourth is Kwang Soo.
Come on.
Gosh, that can't be right.
This is getting more strange.
Gosh, thank you.
Are they the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd?
The third is Se Chan.
(He's ranked 3rd.)
The 2nd is Jong Kook,
and the 1st is Haha.
- You're the best.
- Okay.
- Third place isn't so bad.
- This is ridiculous.
- It's just absurd.
- It's not bad.
Are you guys standing
together on purpose?
(Are you guys standing
together on purpose?)
- What?
- The three ugly members.
- I'm not part of this.
- I'm out of this.
- If you feel upset about it,
it means you admit
that So Min is right.
- Okay?
- No, I don't.
You three are
the ugly dolls of 2020.
- That's not it.
- We want to do it as well.
We will rank the female members.
Stop it. Don't do that.
Number one is Ji Hyo.
- Who's the last?
- The last is...
- Jeon So Min.
Song Ji Hyo is the best.
Jeon So Min is the worst.
- Song Ji Hyo!
We're being so childish.
Jeon So Min.
Did you see So Min blushing?
She's moving.
Those with bad looks
have bad characters.
(Those with bad looks
have bad characters.)
- You should stop.
- She's serious.
Today, after the shoot,
we will wait for you in the alley.
- I will block your car.
- We will attack you.
I will stop your car.
- The ugly ones will get you.
- You'll learn your lesson.
They are unsociable.
Because they're unsociable?
Today, your choice will
decide your fate.
It's called All or Nothing Race.
You will have to make a choice
in each mission.
According to your choice, you will
get or return yut candy bars.
- Candy bars?
- The member with most candy bars...
will get a prize, and the one
with least candy bars will...
get a cumbersome
and tiring penalty.
- It's something tiresome.
- I hate it.
- I hate tiresome things.
- It's going to be hard.
- But it can be annoying.
- This is...
I hate stuff like that.
The penalty is tiresome.
And you failed the mission
in the Thief Race.
- Haha and So Min.
- I've forgotten about it.
- Right.
- If one of you...
becomes the last,
you both will get the penalty.
And if you both don't
become the last,
the last and one of you
with fewer candy bars...
- will get the penalty together.
- I'm getting a penalty today.
If Haha and So Min
get the penalty together,
it will be best for us.
- I agree.
- It's a prize for us.
It's a party.
That's the best gift.
- It's a festival.
- Okay. Good.
So now you will make
your first choice.
Your choice will determine
your costume for today.
It's called Running Man
Haute Couture.
Before the shoot,
the production crew asked you...
to bring your clothes
for another member.
You told us.
(Announcing the mission)
(Please bring an outfit
of your fashion style...)
(that you want to recommend to
this member to the next shoot.)
(They're going to wear my outfit?)
(Yes.)
(My fashion style is topless.)
(Flustered)
(Can I bring leggings?)
(You can bring anything you want.)
- Did you bring your clothes?
- Yes.
- I'm serious about this.
- You guys will soon...
choose your outfit randomly...
between what the members brought
and what your stylist prepared.
And you will be wearing the outfit
until the end of the shoot.
All day?
I hate it.
We will bring in
the outfits for you then.
- Seriously, I...
- Who brought outfits for me?
I brought a pretty one.
- Mine is pretty too.
- I brought a decent one.
- Guys.
- Mine is just fine.
- I also brought a pretty one.
- Mine is not funny.
Kwang Soo, go ahead.
What's your outfit?
- What's that?
- How do you put it on?
- What?
- Darn it.
Actually, this is...
really good.
What's that? Is it for a beggar?
It looks horrible.
This is the oldest one I have.
Is this how it's supposed to look?
No. It's worn out.
Are these moth holes?
They are not moth holes though.
There's a story behind it.
And this is a zebra pattern.
I made them myself in my 20s.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Who would wear it?
- It's sleeveless.
- Who's wearing it?
- That's what Jong Kook likes.
- Gosh, no.
- It looks cool though.
Let's see who it is for.
No way. It's Se Chan.
(Who is the vintage outfit for?)
It's Jong Kook.
(Sleeveless shirt lover, Jong Kook)
See? It's for Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, you like
sleeveless shirts.
He knew this would happen.
But this is too much.
Jong Kook loves sleeveless shirts.
- You'd look good in them.
- I do love sleeveless shirts,
- but I have a standard.
- This is your style.
They look better
when you wear them.
(Kwang Soo's look from his 20s)
Compared to what Kwang Soo brought,
- this is really pretty. I like it.
- It's pretty.
- Cycling pants?
- You wear them very often.
- I really like these clothes.
- They really are Jae Suk's style.
- Jae Suk wears them all the time.
- That's right.
- Suk Jin.
- Gosh.
(It's for Suk Jin
who loves Jae Suk.)
- That style is not bad.
- It suits you. You'll look cute.
(Jae Suk's style)
(Want-To-Be-Like-Jae Suk Style)
These are limited edition clothes.
I brought the clothes I actually
wore when I went to the airport...
that I told you about before.
(Suk Jin prepared the clothes
he wore at the airport.)
(Suk Jin's travel style is
always unpredictable.)
- Oh, those ridiculous clothes?
- Right.
They're really nice.
I remember his clothes...
- Look. These are...
- That's the worst.
I saw him in these clothes
at the airport. He looked terrible.
- This is how I usually dress.
- On a plane?
Look at the back of the pants.
- Gosh, no.
- Se Chan will wear them.
- You'll look okay.
- This is too much.
If you wear them,
- you will look great.
- Really?
Suk Jin, what's with
this yellow stain?
What's with this stain?
Why? What is there?
Why?
Of course, I washed them.
- At least, they'll be comfortable.
- I'm jealous.
First of all...
- I prepared everything...
- What's that?
Gosh. Here she goes again.
She's being over the top again.
- This isn't included.
- Look at that.
That's ridiculous.
- No way.
- Are they for Ji Hyo?
- I'm sure they're for Ji Hyo.
- She's being over the top again.
- Look at this photo.
- I customized this shirt.
I think they're for Kwang Soo.
I think they're for Kwang Soo. Gosh.
- Is that a skirt?
- It's a skirt.
Wait. No. It might not be mind.
- Actually...
- They're definitely for Kwang Soo.
I'd like you all to know that I even
made this necklace by myself.
- But why did you have to do that?
- You didn't have to do that.
- I wanted to make him look pretty.
- It's definitely Kwang Soo's.
Why would she bring a skirt?
I wanted to make him look pretty.
(Kwang Soo looks great in a skirt.)
I think he'll look pretty.
- He'll look very pretty.
- I don't care.
- Why did you bring me a skirt?
- Because you have nice legs...
- But So Min, it's a skirt...
- She brought mesh stockings too.
(So Min's style, hand-made accessory
and customized shirt)
(Kwang Soo-Is-an-Entertainer Style)
- Next.
- I think it's Jae Suk's.
- I prepared these clothes.
- I'm pretty sure it's Jae Suk's.
- What's this?
- Or maybe...
- What's that?
- Haha.
- I prepared...
- There's a wig too.
- I like this style.
- I brought...
- a suit.
- It's nice.
- I wore these...
- They must...
- fit me perfectly.
- to impersonate Yim Jae Beom.
This is nice.
- On "Comedy Big League".
- Oh, right.
(Yim Jae Beom Style
or Comedy Skit Style)
This wig must be worn as well.
- It comes with the clothes.
- Of course.
- But it must be too hot.
- Did you pick Ji Hyo?
- Did you hold onto it?
- Yes.
(Who will transform into
Yim Jae Beom? Ji Hyo will.)
Ji Hyo? I knew it.
Ji Hyo will wear them?
- Ji Hyo, try them on, okay?
- Nice.
- Good choice.
- Try them on.
It's perfect for her.
(Se Chan's style,
What-Should-I-Do Style)
(Ji Hyo's clothes will be revealed.)
Ji Hyo, who will wear yours?
Ji Hyo dresses nicely in real life.
- They're nice.
- It's pretty.
- Awesome.
- I like them.
- That's nice.
- It's pretty.
This is the best style.
- This is the ace style.
- It's really pretty.
- That's what I wanted.
- I...
- I hope it's me.
- It's so pretty.
- Oh, it's me.
- It's So Min.
- I like it.
- It's cute.
- I might wear Jong Kook's clothes.
- So Min is lucky.
She brought me mesh stockings.
But she'll wear that?
- I really like Ji Hyo's style.
- You have nice legs.
I picked something that anyone can
wear regardless of age and gender.
- Well, I...
- Let's check out Jong Kook's.
Nothing unique.
Oh, my. Look at that.
- This is...
- He brought a sleeveless shirt too.
That's what I wear to bed.
- This shirt...
- It's Jong Kook's style.
- with shorts.
- Jong Kook.
- The arm holes are too low.
- Well...
- It's a good thing.
- It looks comfortable though.
Could it be Jae Suk's?
- It's Haha.
- Gosh.
- His clothes are...
- You like this kind of clothes.
- It's a tough guy style.
- It's a sleeveless shirt.
With shorts.
- His clothes must be the worst.
- I'm curious.
- You see, I...
- I really hate his clothes.
To be honest,
I always knew...
that he's envious of me.
(Dumbfounded)
- He acts like this...
- That's ridiculous.
- Because he's envious of you.
- You know how little boys...
- hit the girl they like...
- I know what you mean.
- for no reason.
- They'd make the girl cry.
- And they interrupt a game.
- Exactly.
I realized how that must feel.
I seriously hate his clothes.
You all have seen this shirt.
I wore this for the opening.
- Actually...
- He wore that not long ago.
Actually,
you don't wear anything
under this shirt.
Are you out of your mind?
- But I was considerate of him.
- Right.
You know he has a physical flaw.
(He let Jae Suk hide
his physical flaw.)
I was considerate of him...
and decided to bring a white shirt
to wear under it.
- What about the pants?
- I brought these wide-leg pants.
What's this?
- That's cool.
- Try it on.
(Haha's look,
Conservative Boy's Deviation Style)
Here are the normal clothes
that your stylists prepared.
(The normal clothes prepared by
the members' stylists)
The person who chooses
the clothes sit in the chair.
The others hang...
the tops and bottoms
of both styles...
under number 1 or 2 as you like.
Then we could mix
the different styles.
- That's possible.
- Really?
Both the top and bottom
So Min picked for me are weird.
Cheer up. You never know.
Okay.
- Choose anything.
- My clothes are not imposing.
Is it stretchy?
Yes, it's stretchy.
It can stretch a lot.
I think Jong Kook actually
likes my clothes.
- He checked the fabric...
- Hey, it wasn't like that.
- I want to know if it fits me.
- It'll fit you.
Of course, I considered
things like that.
I don't think it'll fit me.
Trust me. It's stretchy.
Se Chan's clothes are not
so different from each other.
- They're similar.
- As for the top,
I choose number two.
And as for the bottom...
(Walking toward the clothes)
Wait. Are they allowed to change it
after I pick the number?
Can't we just pick the clothes
for you?
- But all of them are nice.
- It'll be never-ending.
So you're not allowed to change it
after the choice is made.
- They're all nice.
- As for the top,
- I choose number two.
- Okay.
And number one for pants.
- Really? You made a good choice.
- He picked my pants.
- Is it a good choice?
- Indeed.
- He picked my traveling clothes.
- He picked the whole pair.
My traveling clothes.
- This and that?
- He picked both.
Okay. That's cool.
- A celebrity's traveling style.
- Exactly.
You picked a celebrity's
traveling style.
Suk Jin posed like this
in those clothes.
(He posed as other celebrities do
in those clothes.)
His pants were slipping down.
- That's the key point.
- I see.
That's confirmed. Who's next?
- I'll go next.
- Nice. This will be interesting.
- The zebra print pants.
- Finally.
- I chose the clothes carefully.
- I hope he'll choose these.
He's going to smile happily.
- I picked them very carefully.
- They look so weird.
- He's going to smile very happily.
- How can I wear them?
- Those pants...
- Those clothes have good memories.
The sleeveless shirt is not so bad.
I hope he'll choose the pants.
I don't care about the shirt.
I really hope...
- he'll wear the zebra print pants.
- Exactly.
It's made with thick fabric.
- He can show off his fit body.
- He'll look fashionable.
If the pants don't fit you,
- you don't have to wear them.
- You can see them, right?
- Exactly.
- Just draping them?
- Make your choice wisely.
- Just like Justin Bieber.
(His choice will decide...)
(whether or not he will
turn into a zebra.)
Let's go!
- I picked the wrong ones.
- Be quiet.
We're in the middle of a shoot.
(Please choose
at least one of them.)
I have a feeling that I should
choose number one...
for both top and bottom.
(He chose number one
for top and bottom.)
- What?
- Number one?
- Number one.
- Are you sure?
We're happy with your choice.
- Number 1.
- Number one?
- Yes.
- That's nice.
- He'll look great.
I like them.
- He picked half wrong.
- That's right.
However, where should he
put his microphone?
- Right here.
- Where?
- On his back.
- Like this?
- On his forehead.
- On the back like this.
- He can put it on his back.
- Like a musical actor.
He can put it on his forehead
like a musical actor.
- Or give him a handheld microphone.
- Exactly.
I think it's inappropriate
for a TV show. Is it okay?
- Yes. Don't worry.
- I'll go next.
Look at that.
Gosh, this is...
Ji Hyo, to be honest,
Se Chan's clothes are nice.
- They're not bad.
- Really?
- Yes.
- They'll be too hot though.
They look sophisticated.
(He spoke without thinking much.)
I choose number two
from top to bottom.
- Okay.
That's perfect.
(Where are you?)
(Oh, you were all number two.)
- What should I do?
- Ji Hyo, you made a good choice.
- She picked the whole set.
- That's perfect.
- Good choice.
Ji Hyo, good job.
(The other members also
chose the clothes to wear.)
(What clothes will they wear?)
(So they've finished
choosing their clothes.)
(Walking slowly)
Someone asked me if I had
changed my clothes.
I said, "These aren't my clothes."
"I'm wearing them for the show."
They suit me so well, right?
A celebrity's travel style.
(And someone is coming in.)
The pants are
a little too big for me, right?
(It was Kwang Soo wearing
the miniskirt prepared by So Min.)
(His long, skinny legs are
covered with red mesh stockings.)
I mean...
Why must she have gone this far?
- You look great, Kwang Soo.
- He does have nice legs.
- You have such pretty legs.
- You have nice legs.
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
So Min said she wishes
to have legs like yours.
It suits you well.
You should dress like this
more often.
(Upset)
Hey, Ji Hyo.
Sing a little bit of his song.
Look at her.
- She looks great.
- What should I do?
- Ji Hyo, you look great.
- Don't I...
Don't I look like Seong Mun?
- Ji Hyo, you look great.
- I like how she looks.
Ji Hyo, you should get a short cut
only in the front like this.
You look really great. I mean it.
You look perfect.
They look like a couple.
(The flashy fashion style reminds us
of Generation X...)
Can I trust you, staff members?
(from the end of the 20th century.)
Can I?
You're the worst dresser I've seen
so far this year.
- That's a terrible style.
- Why?
(They broke the worst fashion style
record of 2020.)
(Their poses and fashion styles
remind us of the late 1990s.)
Why?
(And then, a zebra entered.)
- Jae Suk.
- You look great.
He liked those pants.
I like these pants so much,
so I borrowed them.
- Look at the pants.
- He looks like a hair stylist.
- Exactly.
- They're just like my own clothes.
They really look like
your own clothes.
- Exactly.
- You should buy those pants...
- from Jae Suk.
- They feel like my own.
- He looks like a vice president.
- These are nice pants.
Who lives in Gimpo.
(He looks like the vice president
in the IT industry.)
Look at Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is
the last one to enter.)
Look at Jong Kook.
- Why are you carrying it like that?
- What's that?
- Take the bag off.
- I'll carry it.
Put it down.
Are you going to a battlefield?
I thought it was a different type
of microphone.
No, it isn't.
I can't put it on anywhere else.
- I look the most stylish among us.
- That looks good.
- So Min looks cute.
- He's tall.
- She looks too pretty.
- So Min...
But if you look at her face...
and her head,
she looks like a baby octopus.
(She looks like a baby octopus.)
- Like the baby octopus alien?
- Exactly.
- Like the cartoon character.
- Doesn't she look like that alien?
She looks like
the baby octopus alien.
- Did I really wear them?
- I can't believe...
these are a celebrity's
traveling style.
- Suk Jin actually wore them.
- Isn't that Se Chan's?
My goodness.
- It looks like Se Chan's.
- It is shabby indeed.
(She's satisfied with
the fashion she recommended.)
It left marks on your forehead.
- I don't know how to wear it.
- Do you not wear beanies?
(They have a bonding moment
talking about their fashion.)
Suk Jin, you can
sit in the middle now.
The rest of you will
sit on the red chairs.
Why is he sitting in the middle?
- Ji Hyo, come here.
- Sit modestly.
My gosh.
(The thimble guy covers
Kwang Soo's legs in an onion net.)
It's a pantskirt.
It looks like
he's the head of a department.
I don't know which company this is,
but we're having a talent show.
Exactly.
(They are the top talents
for the talent show.)
All right. This is
your first choice.
You know the balance game
that's been popular these days?
One of you will come on up
and answer...
a question prepared for you.
The rest of you will...
guess the answer
that the member chooses.
(The rest of the members
will guess the answer chosen.)
If you get it right, you get candy
bars. If you don't, you return them.
You will pick an answer
all at the same time.
- As you count to three?
- I should pick what he'd choose.
- I will pick answers as I feel.
- Okay.
Just the way I feel.
I should read his mind.
- I think I can get it right.
- Sure.
- We know each other very well.
- That's true.
All right. Please show the question.
Okay.
- "If I were born again?"
- "A senior respected by Jae Suk".
(A senior respected by Jae Suk)
(An older brother
that Jong Kook is afraid of)
My gosh.
- It's so hard.
- Good.
"An older brother
that Jong Kook is afraid of"?
Gosh, this is too hard.
- This is tough.
- It's hard to choose.
- It's hard for me too.
- This is too hard.
You gave him this question
because he's none of them.
"A senior respected by Jae Suk"?
- Gosh, this is hard.
- A senior that Jae Suk respects...
or my older brother
whom I'm afraid of.
This is tough.
So let's say
he's having an interview.
They'd ask whom he respects
the most.
Then he'd say, "It's Ji Suk Jin."
I get to hear that.
Or I tell Jong Kook to come
to see me tomorrow by 2 p.m.
And Jong Kook is so worried.
"Why does he want to see me?"
(It can happen
only in his imagination.)
Then...
he calls Haha.
"Why do you think
Suk Jin wants to see me?"
He's so terrified that he peed
in front of your house.
- Trembling in fear.
- Gosh, it's confusing.
This is really hard.
It's interesting.
In fact, he respects me.
No. I like you,
but I don't respect you.
You fool...
He's just a friend.
- He's a good funny friend.
- A close friend.
- Right.
- I've never respected him...
not even a single time.
- Darn it.
- Seriously.
- Not even once?
- There was a time...
when I realized
that I can't respect him.
When we were younger,
we went through hard times together.
- That's what's real.
- We went around...
three used-car markets in Seoul.
- Why?
- And on our way home,
he bought a new car.
And you were there the whole time?
I did it for three days.
- It took him three days.
- Really?
This is what happened
only 30 minutes ago.
Before the opening,
I was sitting under a parasol.
- Oh, that one.
- And Hyeong Gu walked past him.
"Hyeong Gu, come here
and have a seat."
Then he stood up.
- He rarely leaves his seat.
- Right.
It turns out he picked up his chair
like this and moved to a shade.
(He picked up his chair
and moved to a shade.)
(Coincidentally, he moved to a shade
with his chair.)
He moved into the shade like that.
Hyeong Gu had no chair.
I thought he was giving
his chair to Hyeong Gu.
He brought his chair with him,
so Hyeong Gu...
had to stand there like this.
(He was standing under
the scorching sun for a long time.)
It's not like he can sit
on a transparent chair.
He was standing like this.
- Hyeong Gu, I'm sorry.
- He's the worst.
What do you think, Ji Hyo?
(What does Ji Hyo think?)
I think, if I were Suk Jin,
I would want to be someone...
- whom Jong Kook is afraid of.
- You relate to him.
- Right.
- You empathize with him.
- I will beat up Jong Kook someday.
- He didn't ask about your opinion.
That's her answer.
- What about you, Se Chan?
- I'll definitely choose Jong Kook.
(There's one more person
who'd pick option B.)
"Come here. How dare you."
"Relax your muscles."
(Se Chan, you seem excited.)
It's just my imagination.
- What about you, Haha? Is it B?
- Of course.
"Pick it up."
(They all let
their imagination run wild.)
"Yes, Haha. Here."
That's right. It sounds so good.
(Enjoy the moment.)
- I've made up my mind.
- I know his choice.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- B.
That's right.
So Min picked A.
(So Min is the only one
who got it wrong.)
Even if he respects me,
it's just useless.
But bossing him around
can be very useful.
- Exactly.
- It will be very fun.
He can be very useful.
- Let's move on.
- There's a lot to talk about this.
- What if you get to pick only one?
- "I get 100,000 dollars,"
"and Jae Suk gets 10 million
dollars without thanking me."
"None of us gets any money."
B sounds like throwing a tantrum.
B is just like throwing a tantrum.
- "I get 100,000 dollars..."
- B is just like throwing a tantrum.
(He feels excited already.)
So I get 100,000 dollars.
You will make
100,000 dollars anyway.
And Jae Suk gets
10 million dollars.
- I don't thank him at all.
- But he's not grateful to me.
- He gets the money because of you.
- Let's answer it right away.
Let's put it this way.
Suk Jin got me some information.
"Jae Suk, I heard
this one is good."
And he invested little money.
- And I invested huge money.
- So you made 10 million dollars.
That's how
you made 10 million dollars...
Suk Jin invested 10,000 dollars...
- while I invested one million.
- It increased tenfold.
That's how it feels. You talk to me.
I made 10 million dollars,
but I didn't even thank you.
I heard you invested
one million dollars.
You gave me the information.
I know. You should
at least buy me a meal.
- Or give me 30 percent...
- I invested my own money.
- It's your money, but...
- You didn't give me the money.
But I gave you the information.
It was my choice
that I made the investment.
(They just started
the skit for fun.)
(He's upset for real.)
- that I made the investment.
- Exactly.
- Your choice.
- Let's do it right away.
(Let's do it right away.)
- I can't stand this anymore.
- Count to three.
It's really upsetting to watch it.
- Please count to three.
- Did it help?
- A lot. That's enough.
1, 2, and 3.
Darn it! I'm so furious.
- Did it help?
- I'd rather not get the money.
They both shouldn't get money.
- I don't want to be jealous.
- I understand.
- That's worse.
- I would hate him.
- Right. We would starve together.
- Right.
- I'd end up hating him.
- It's Se Chan's turn.
- Is it me? Okay.
- This is fun.
- That was a good one.
Yang Se Chan.
- This is fun.
- You have to imagine it.
- Balance game.
- This is the first question.
This one is tough.
I know what he'd choose.
Gosh, this is too hard.
- What if you date one of them?
- Hang on.
This is hard
because it's so serious.
No, I'm just doing this for fun.
- This is a sensitive issue.
- By the way...
- It's only for dating.
Only for dating. Okay.
- Hang on.
- This is hard.
Gosh.
This is such a happy problem.
- You're right.
- I know. Thank you.
- You're so lucky.
- Wait. But...
This is too hard.
(Laughing)
It's only for dating.
Ji Hyo just made a cute face.
I guess she forgot
that she's wearing a wig.
It's just dating.
- You date one of them.
- I just tell my friends...
- that I'm dating her.
- Right.
I know whom you will pick.
- All right. 1, 2, and 3.
- I will support you.
I wonder which one
would make me happier.
Three.
- A.
- That's right.
- My gosh.
- Se Chan!
Thank you, Se Chan.
Why?
Look at her. So Min seems happy.
- Do you like it?
- If I date her,
I think it will be more fun.
- Of course.
- What about Ji Hyo?
If I dated Ji Hyo,
she wouldn't
even be interested in me.
She'd just go her way.
- She doesn't even answer calls.
- I know. We should play games.
How do you break up
with your boyfriend, Ji Hyo?
I just tell him that
we should stop seeing each other.
What if you say that...
and your boyfriend...
What if he asks you
to give him another chance?
I will give him a chance.
- Just once?
- Yes. Just once.
What about you, So Min?
- She is...
- I...
I give countless chances.
(She gives unlimited chances.)
- I...
- She wants to see the end of it.
I break up with someone
only after I get sick of him.
- After you get sick of him.
- Right.
- And do you take your revenge?
- I take my revenge.
- I knew it.
- To the bitter end.
That's how she dates a guy.
She takes her revenge? That's funny.
Let's move on to the next question.
- This is so fun.
- This one is really tough.
"Which situation do you hate more?"
"My girlfriend goes on an
overnight trip with a male friend."
Gosh, this is a popular question.
Which situation do I hate more?
- Both of them sound horrible.
- It's a difficult question.
I really hate it.
Going on an overnight trip?
Only two of them? That's crazy.
Hey, A is a male friend
and B is an ex-boyfriend.
How could she go on an
overnight trip with a male friend?
With an ex-boyfriend,
if something goes wrong...
An overnight trip is just as bad.
But it's her ex-boyfriend.
- But it happens...
- It's her ex-boyfriend.
- It still happens...
- Look at them.
- If her ex-boyfriend...
- Jong Kook isn't explaining it.
He's forcing him
to choose one answer.
Then you should sit there
and give your answer.
That's not it. A male friend is...
I just can't pick what I want.
Nothing might happen
with a male friend, but...
But the thing is they drink
together all night.
And the other is
going on an overnight trip.
What happens after drinking?
It doesn't say what happens next!
I know. But you can imagine.
That doesn't say
what happens afterward.
(The hairdresser explodes
with anger.)
- All night...
- Does it say that?
It just says they drink together.
But why would they drink together?
Why are you being like that
in a sleeveless shirt?
You should think about it.
We should keep the possibility open.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- A male friend doesn't sound right.
- I hate both.
- I choose A.
- My answer is A.
- A is worse.
- Really?
- Because it's an overnight trip.
I should choose what I hate more.
I was mistaken.
Now I understand why Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo... Now I know why
Ji Hyo doesn't hear what we say.
I can't hear with the beanie on.
(I can't hear with the beanie on.)
- Are you okay?
- I can't hear very well.
I just can't hear you.
- Did you feel the same?
- It's hard to hear, right?
Yes. I can't hear well.
Now I understand
why she was being like that.
This is the last question.
(What if a thug spits
on your girlfriend's face?)
You need to imagine the scene.
I know this one.
This is obvious.
He will definitely come at the thug.
(A, let it slide,
B, come at the thug.)
- One...
- Hang on.
Why are all the questions
for me like that?
All my questions are so lame.
- Because you're single.
- Because I'm single?
- Hey, just enjoy it.
- It's just a game.
It's just a game.
- Spit on her girlfriend's face?
- I'd let it slide if it's my face.
- But it's my girlfriend's.
- You're lying.
It's not going to happen
to you anyway.
So you're pretending to be tough.
(Spitting)
- Why did you do that?
- Stop it.
(Jae Suk hit him right away.)
Why did you hit me?
You said you would hold it back.
(Why did you hit me?
You said you'd hold it back.)
You said you would hold it back.
You said you'd let it slide
if someone spits in your face.
How dare you spit at me?
(Yelling)
He didn't do as he said he would.
If someone
who is dressed like that...
If someone who is dressed like that
spits at me,
- I would let it slide.
- Me too.
- I would be so scared.
- I would let it slide too.
Things like that scare me.
Se Chan, what if the thug is
as big and muscular as Jong Kook?
You should say something
before throwing a punch.
I bet he has no experience.
- It's obvious.
- You should say something first.
- Say what?
- "Hey, you punks!"
(Hey, you punks!)
(It didn't sound
intimidating at all.)
- Don't come near me.
- You would get beaten up.
You should say something
like that first.
His mouth would dry out right away
if he were in such a situation.
Because he's too nervous. "Why..."
"Hey, you punks."
(His mouth is dry.)
- That's funny.
- I bet Se Chan would let it slide.
- It's scary.
- He would let it slide.
Even if you end up getting
beaten up... If you let it slide,
- your relationship would be over.
- Absolutely.
- Right? You should do something.
- But...
maybe your girlfriend did something
to deserve being spat at.
(Maybe your girlfriend did something
to deserve being spat at.)
Suk Jin, it's not...
- For example...
- I mean...
What are you talking about?
What could she have done
to deserve it?
Let's say she said to the thug,
"Hey, you jerk!"
- My gosh.
- "What is wrong with you?"
Or she spat at the thug first.
Sometimes, when she's drunk,
- she does unusual things.
- That's possible.
- That's nonsense.
- "Hey, you scumbag!"
- Maybe she said that.
- "Stop it."
- The situation might be...
- I think he would let it slide.
Let's say So Min...
I mean, your girlfriend...
said to the thug,
"Hey, you pig with a tattoo."
- She provoked him first.
- Okay.
- I would try to stop her.
- So...
- the thug spat at her.
- "What? Did I say something wrong?"
So the thug spat at her.
Then I would spit at her too.
Hey.
(Then I would spit at her too.)
(How could you?)
Gosh.
To survive. I want to live.
- "Sir, didn't I do well?"
- "What is wrong with you?"
"Come to your senses."
(He would spit at her too.)
- One more time.
- "Take this."
"Get it together. Sir, I'll be off."
(He would save his own life
and go home.)
- Gosh.
- I can imagine that.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Okay. 1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3.
I knew it.
I wouldn't let it slide.
- This one is easy.
- Even if I get beaten up...
- What?
- Did you pick A?
I think he would let it slide.
- Nonsense.
- He wouldn't.
I would throw a fit.
- Me?
- It's Jae Suk's turn.
- I know everything about him.
- Okay.
My head itches because of the hat.
- Put it back on.
- The forehead too.
- That's why Ji Hyo scratches often.
- Right?
Ji Hyo.
She must be used to wearing a wig.
She seems comfortable.
It's so comfortable.
Let's begin.
- "Which one do you regret more?"
- "Not scolding Suk Jin."
"B, not taming Jong Kook
when starring on 'X-Man'".
- That's an interesting question.
- It's difficult.
(A, not scolding Suk Jin
when he was a newcomer)
(B, not taming Jong Kook
when starring on "X-Man")
- My gosh. Hang on.
- Which one of them...
"Not scolding Suk Jin
when he was a newcomer".
- Let me think.
- I already made my choice.
- You did?
- I made my choice.
- It's difficult.
- This is a hard one.
- How harshly would he scold him?
- How would he scold him?
Actually, I had a few chances.
- You lost your chances.
- He's your junior comedian, right?
- Yes, he is.
- That one is also funny.
- "Not taming Jong Kook".
He used to walk on eggshells
around you.
Honestly, both are right,
but if I must choose one,
I would choose this.
- Okay.
- As soon as I read it,
- I thought...
- I know his answer.
- I've been looking at the answer.
- Don't say that now.
All right.
I see which one he's looking at.
I know his answer. I'm sure of it.
- Start counting, please.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Then answer is B.
- It's A.
- Of course, it's A.
Of course, it's A.
A? No, it must be B.
Since "X-Man", Jong Kook has
always been...
- behaving well.
- I'm always polite.
Did Suk Jin address you
as his senior comedian at first?
- Or did he talk casually to you?
- No, I didn't.
At first, when we were
alone together,
- he called me by my name.
- I see.
But when our senior comedians were
with us, he said, "Hello, Mr. Yu."
- Really?
- I can't believe it.
- It's hard to believe.
- Really?
I didn't know he used to do that.
- You should've scolded him then.
- When everyone gathered.
- "Hello, Mr. Yu."
- But he didn't bow deeply.
"Hello, Mr. Yu."
Let's move on to the next question.
"How would you be born
in your next life?"
(A, an ugly but popular show host,
B, a handsome but ordinary man)
"An ugly but popular..."
That's who he is now.
- Okay.
- I think I know the answer.
- This is...
- "A handsome but ordinary man".
- "In your next life".
- I don't...
I don't like this question.
- A describes his current life.
- That's a weird question.
Hey. A is my current life?
- You're living as the A type.
- But A...
- That's my current life?
- Yes, correct.
Would you live as Yoo Jae Suk again
in your next life or...
- Hey.
- It's either your current life...
- or a different life.
- What are you talking about?
Think about it. You want to live
as an ugly man again?
You little...
- Jae Suk, that'd be boring.
- Gosh.
When we went to a club
before he became popular,
ladies hated him so much.
They didn't hate me.
- Like those losers at a club.
- They weren't interested in me.
I know how sad that feels.
- I know how that feels too.
- I wasn't...
- All right.
- Okay.
- If I could choose...
- I can relate to that.
- If I choose B,
I need some guarantee.
- Zo In Sung...
- Absolutely.
Park Bo Gum or Zo In Sung...
- If I'm as handsome as they are...
- He looks happy.
- Or Gang Dong Won.
- What?
And let's say the ugly man
in A is like...
- Kwang Soo or Suk Jin...
- No, it's you.
- Jae Suk, come on.
- It's you.
- It's not me.
Would you be Yoo Jae Suk
or Zo In Sung in your next life?
- All right.
- Okay.
- You don't even need...
- 1, 2,
- Three.
- Of course, it's B.
(Jae Suk chose B.)
- He picked B?
- Of course, he picked B.
- Of course, I picked B.
- He must want that life too.
I want to live as In Sung
or Bo Gum in my next life.
- Of course, he wants that.
- I want that kind of life.
Of course. How can he
live like this again?
- What did you just say?
- I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
- Please don't be mad.
- All right.
Here's the next question.
(A, the intelligent-looking face,
B, the perfect body for a suit)
"What makes you popular?"
- "A, the intelligent-looking face".
- What's that?
None of those is true.
- This isn't true.
- None of them is true.
Pick the one that you think
had even a little influence.
- But...
- "Intelligent-looking"?
- I mean...
That bothers me.
That word itself makes me cringe.
- "Intelligent-looking"?
- My gosh.
(It makes everyone cringe.)
The questions should be made
based on facts.
- Don't you think so?
- There's no fact in there.
Do you mean that he's good-looking?
You can say it's true
because some people...
- say that on the internet.
- That's not true.
Did you make the question
based on those silly comments?
(Did you make the question
based on those silly comments?)
Why would you call them
silly comments?
People call that kind of comment
silly comments.
Let's make it simple.
My face or my body?
- Okay.
- It's simple.
- So we can accept it.
- My...
- My face or my body?
- Or your body.
- 1...
- 1, 2, 3.
- My face. Why?
- Gosh.
(He chose his face
with confidence.)
- That's not true.
- That's total nonsense.
- You know that's not true.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Jae Suk, you can't do that.
- You must've lost your mind.
- Jae Suk. Come on.
- How could you?
- This is not right.
- Darn it.
- Have you...
- The answer should be B.
- Have you lost your mind?
- Wait.
I knew he thought that way.
- I can't believe this.
- What's the problem?
- You agreed to tell the truth.
- What's wrong with my answer?
My gosh. It turns out he was
satisfied with his face.
- What's wrong with my answer?
- I'm shocked.
- Why?
- I'm shocked too.
Wait. Se Chan, why is your chair
attached to your pants?
What?
- I've been looking for the chair.
- It's perfect for traveling.
- What happened?
- Gosh.
(The strange encounter
between the chair and his hips)
(The chair has been hanging there
like a fruit on a tree.)
(What? Where did my chair go?)
What's wrong with my answer?
(After looking for his chair
for a long while,)
(he found his chair
suffocated by his hips.)
Here goes the final question.
- It's a difficult one.
- That's easy.
(Which body part would you cover
if a public bath is on fire?)
(A, the face, B, the private part)
- He doesn't need to cover it.
- I'm sure...
My goodness.
Have you lost your mind?
- It's so cute.
- What kind of question is that?
Seriously, what kind of
question is that?
Honestly, if he comes out
covering his face,
people would think
he's a little boy...
I mean, people would know
he's an adult...
- Are you insane?
- So they would help him...
Have you lost your mind?
- I'm telling you,
- Gosh.
it wouldn't be visible
if he runs fast.
(It wouldn't be visible
if he runs fast.)
(I have a lot to say,
but I won't say anything.)
Trust me.
(The visibility would change
depending on his running speed.)
Gosh. All of you are insane.
Gosh, seriously.
Imagine that situation.
- Okay.
- 1, 2, 3.
- He would cover his face.
- It must be A.
- Of course, he'd cover his face.
- Of course.
- I thought about it.
- Why...
I would be so embarrassed
if I come out like this.
- Of course.
- Right?
- It's better to cover your face.
- Next up is Kwang Soo.
- That was ridiculous.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo...
- I think it'll be difficult.
Be honest with us, okay?
- I'll be honest.
- Be yourself.
- I promise.
- Don't lie.
- I won't.
(A, having Jong Kook bathe me
thoroughly, B, bathing Suk Jin)
- "Which situation would you avoid?"
- "Having Jong Kook..."
- "bathe me".
- My gosh.
(Which situation would you avoid?)
(A, having Jong Kook bathe me
thoroughly, B, bathing Suk Jin)
(Everyone is exclaiming
as they read the question.)
Why would Jong Kook...
bathe me thoroughly?
- That's so funny.
- What kind of question is that?
- Why must I choose any of those?
- That's hilarious.
I bathe Suk Jin?
Do I wash his entire body?
Not just his face?
Do I give him a bath?
- Don't you think that's too much?
- Can I wear rubber gloves?
- I can take a bath by myself.
- My gosh.
I just pictured it for a moment.
Wait. Excuse me.
- No.
- Just a second.
- No. Don't touch me.
- I said no.
- Let me just imagine it.
Gosh, no. Go away.
(Go away!)
- Oh, man. That's disgusting.
- Which would be worse?
- I pictured it for a moment too.
- Both are disgusting.
- Exactly. Which one should I pick?
- How disgusting.
Hey, you don't know my hands...
At least,
doing B would be fulfilling.
- I imagined the B situation.
- Yes.
I thought it could happen
in the near future.
- You're right. It'll be sad.
- Hey. That will never happen.
I can do it for him.
- That won't happen.
- It'll be sad.
- I'll be happy to do it for you.
- It will never happen.
I pick what's worse, right?
- Did you make your choice?
- Okay. Yes, I made my choice.
1, 2, 3.
- I think that would be worse.
- Of course, he picked A.
(Suk Jin feels bitter
but accepts it.)
- If I were...
- Let's move on.
- Goodness, you brat.
- Stop it!
(Scrubbing his body roughly)
This is unbearable.
- You brat.
- Stop it.
Here's the last question.
- "Which would be worse?"
- "A, playing games with So Min".
"B, listening to Jae Suk's
dating advice all night over tea".
(Which is worse?)
- Dating advice?
- A is better.
- Of course, A is better.
- This is a tough choice.
Haven't you had drinks
with her before?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm fun to be around!
- Both will be painful.
- Kwang Soo.
- I think I know his choice.
- My dating advice helped, right?
I'm fun to be around.
I know because I often
have drinks with her.
I'm good company.
Both situations are painful.
- Did you wash your face?
- Hold on.
Kwang Soo, I always give you
good dating advice.
Keep your head on straight.
What a tough choice.
You must endure it all night.
I'm fun to be around!
I can shake up the choice of teas.
Chamomile and so on and so forth.
- It's the worst!
- I can shake things up.
- The tea can be swapped.
- Still...
1, 2, 3.
- This must be it.
- A.
- What?
- It's B.
- Unbelievable.
- Seriously?
- It's disappointing.
- How can this be better?
- Why?
- I'm choosing the worse one.
- He chose you over Jae Suk.
- He chose you.
(It took her a second
to understand.)
- Right. Yes, of course.
- Drinking with her all night?
I give out great dating advice.
I haven't given you any lately...
- because you're seeing someone.
- You see,
I've actually tried both.
Personally though,
Jae Suk's advice
ruined things for me.
(Jae Suk's advice
ruined things for him.)
Just the result alone, I mean.
Kwang Soo.
Things wouldn't have gone
very far with her anyway.
Stop it!
- Ji Hyo's next.
- Right, Ji Hyo.
It'll be fun.
- She's tough to read.
- I'm clueless when it comes to her.
- She could be easier to read.
- She's hard to understand.
Ji Hyo's hard to read.
But she's also quite simple.
- Right.
- Yes, I don't think too much.
What's worse?
"A, being in a room filled
with cockroaches for an hour".
I know the answer to this. I know!
- Choosing B would be weird.
- I know!
What Ji Hyo thinks
about cockroaches...
It'd be weird if Kwang Soo
guessed B.
We don't even need time to think.
How can you compare
Kwang Soo to cockroaches?
- I mean...
- It's fine.
- You and cockroaches...
- This...
is a mistake on their part.
- Okay.
- All right.
Is it one cockroach or...
- A room full of them.
- Multiple cockroaches.
You've got this, Kwang Soo.
Ji Hyo loathes cockroaches.
- It's not like you must kiss one.
- Hold on.
Why did you ask
how many cockroaches there were?
(Why did you ask
how many cockroaches there were?)
I know for a fact
that you hate cockroaches.
You're not dating one, okay?
Wait, hold on.
Ji Hyo...
- I keep going back and forth.
- Ji Hyo, look at him.
I thought for a second
that she had to date one.
- It's Kwang Soo you're dating.
- It's only for an hour.
An hour with cockroaches
or with Kwang Soo forever.
You have to be
in that room for an hour.
You crouch and cry
when any bug approaches you.
- It's just for an hour.
- She knows.
1, 2, 3.
- Cockroaches, of course.
- She chose B?
(In a twist of events,
she chooses B.)
(Dating Kwang Soo is worse?)
She chose B?
(You hate me more
than you hate cockroaches?)
- A.
- A, of course.
Of course, she'd choose A.
Kwang Soo was extremely shocked
just now.
- I...
- I thought she really chose B.
Of course not.
- I absolutely loathe cockroaches.
- Exactly.
Here.
(Who would you marry?)
- This is a tough one.
- Who would you marry?
- It's not easy.
- Don't you hate both?
- Me too.
- They're both awful.
- Mama's boy is the worst.
- Tell me about it.
Would it be like this?
When out on a date,
- this man would call his mom.
- Right.
"Mom, I'm on a date with So Min."
"A movie or coffee?
A movie? Okay, thanks."
- For instance...
- That's how he makes up his mind.
He must go on a date
that his mom planned for him.
(That's awful.)
- But a womanizer...
- At least it means he's charming.
A womanizer is charming...
but he's seeing
about five other women.
Would that be all right?
- Suk Jin, which would you choose?
- What?
- Out of the two...
- Me?
Well, I used to be
a womanizer briefly.
That's not what I meant.
I...
When were you a womanizer exactly?
Why were you one?
- Why do you lie all the time?
- Why were you one?
It's a lie.
- Well...
- He's never been young enough.
He always looked like
a middle-aged man.
- It's true.
- You see,
it's like this.
Being popular among women...
turns you briefly into a womanizer.
I apologize to Suk Jin's wife.
I set you two up, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- So Min?
- Well...
It's too hard of a choice.
(What does the dating expert think?)
The womanizer is probably handsomer.
She...
Don't consider those variables.
- Not the looks.
- Why would you consider that?
You're not just dating this person.
- You're marrying him.
- Mama's boy is the worst.
- It's not so bad.
- This is a tough choice.
A mama's boy for life?
- One...
- You can't handle a mama's boy.
- 2, 3.
- Tell me about it.
(She chooses a mama's boy instead.)
A mama's boy is the worst though.
I hate both.
It's So Min.
Here we go.
Here's your first choice.
Who would you date?
(A, Se Chan who loves me,
B, Dong Jun whom I love)
This...
The answer is obvious.
- The answer is obvious.
- Of course, it is.
This will be easy for anyone...
- who knows me.
- Exactly.
- Come on.
- This?
I see I'm up against Dong Jun...
when someone was
up against cockroaches.
Someone had to compete
with cockroaches,
but I'm up against Dong Jun.
- Gosh, thank you so much.
- Lucky you.
Someone had to compete
with cockroaches.
- Okay, then.
- Okay.
I was up against
an hour with cockroaches.
- Okay, good.
- All right.
1, 2, 3.
(Who will So Min choose?)
- Of course, it's A.
- It was too easy.
So Min likes those
who only have eyes for her.
- Of course, it's A.
- The guy loving me...
is more important.
Ji Hyo...
She doesn't know So Min at all.
Ji Hyo?
- Did she choose Dong Jun?
- She doesn't know So Min at all.
That wig is hilarious.
I thought about what
So Min would like.
The wig and that answer
go so well together.
She looks like a thug, right?
Would you choose B?
- You'd choose A too, right?
- That's right.
Rather than the guy I like,
I'd like to date someone
who loves me.
- That's how it should be.
- Right.
Let's move on.
Which is worse?
(A, Jong Kook suspecting you
when you're the spy)
(B, Jong Kook suspecting you
when you're not the spy)
I know the feeling!
It's the worst.
I know it so well.
- My gosh.
- This...
- is the worst.
- It's hilarious though.
- It's the worst.
- It sure is.
In situation A,
- He stresses you out.
- you'd rather just die.
Remember last time?
Can't you look over this way
at least once?
Just get it over with.
We won't know until we take a look.
This...
(Just thinking about it
gives her a headache.)
1, 2, 3.
- A.
- My gosh.
Still, it's nice because
he shows interest in you.
You have no idea how angry I get...
when situation A happens.
- Recently, you and Haha...
- I...
That situation. Yes, I know it too.
- I mean it.
- Me too.
- I never let it go.
- It makes you so angry.
I wanted to claw at him.
- I never let it go.
- He checks your hands too.
Situation B only happens on camera.
Meanwhile, situation A
happens off camera too.
He keeps smirking at you.
(Smirking)
(Grinning)
It's the worst.
(Even Jong Kook admits it.)
Here's the next one.
- That was hilarious.
- What would you like...
your boyfriend to say tonight?
"A, something sexy
in a sweet voice".
"B, something sweet
in a sexy voice".
- Something sexy in a sweet voice.
- I think I know.
Something sweet in a sexy voice.
What kind of voice
do you find sexy though?
- Something sweet in a sexy voice.
- The voice...
Who has a voice...
that isn't pleasant?
- Him saying something sweet.
- There's Cho Sae Ho.
- "Hello."
- Him saying something sweet.
"Did you sleep well? I love you."
On the other hand, Lee Sun Kyun...
- will say something sweet.
- "I said I love you."
"Come on."
"I love you, darn it."
"I said I love you."
- Then we have our answer.
- Let's do it.
- Do you want an example?
- Sure.
Say "Hello" is a sweet voice
and then in a sexy voice.
- In a sweet voice?
- That's right.
- "Hello."
- Now, it a sexy voice.
(Suk Jin's sexy voice)
"Hello."
(It's overly corny!)
No, that's not it!
One would end the call immediately.
You seemed sick to me.
What's a sexy voice though?
- Jae Suk, what about you?
- What's a sweet voice?
- A sweet voice.
- My sweet voice?
- "Hello."
- He can be very sweet.
- What about your sexy voice?
- I've never tried that before.
(Exhaling)
No, that's not it.
- I'll pass.
- What's with the breathing?
That sounded disgusting.
(His unappealing heavy breathing)
Aren't I allowed to breathe?
Even his breathing sounded ugly.
- What?
- Even his breathing sounded ugly.
- You...
- From what I could hear,
- his breathing sounded ugly.
- It sounded ugly?
- That's how it sounded.
- Gosh.
Let's hear from Se Chan next.
Cover your face.
(Se Chan's sweet voice)
Your sweet voice.
"Hello."
And your sexy voice.
- Stop it!
- "Hello."
- Why are you breathing like that?
- But...
"Hello."
(Panting)
Are you awake?
- What on earth is that?
- Gosh.
- Jong Kook's sweet voice.
- "Hello."
- And your sexy voice.
- Put more thought into it.
- Actually, this...
- You shouldn't try so hard.
- I agree.
Kwang Soo, you go ahead.
- "Hello."
- Next.
Did he get it wrong or something?
(Another incident where Jae Suk...)
(comes onto Running Man
just to tease Kwang Soo)
What do you mean?
Weren't you done?
- Of course not.
- The sexy one.
- "Hello."
- And the sexy voice.
The sexy voice.
"Hello."
(In a low voice)
(Emotional)
You forgot you're in a skirt again.
- Must I wear this all day?
- Cover yourself up!
Must I wear this all day?
- Just put on some pants.
- But...
Wear the pants
you brought with you today.
- What about Haha?
- He has a nice voice.
Be sweet first.
"Hello."
- Was that your sweet voice?
- Yes.
- The sexy one.
- Your sexy voice.
- "Hello."
- Oh, that was sexy!
(A sexy low tone)
- What a great voice.
- The tone must be lower.
The sweetest voice was Jae Suk's...
while the sexiest voice
was Haha's.
(So Min's choice)
I made up my mind.
One...
The keyword is "tonight".
- Yes, tonight.
- Tonight?
- 1, 2, 3.
- The man of the night
- B.
(A, something sexy in a sweet voice,
B, something sweet in a sexy voice)
- Nice!
- I choose B.
(They all choose B.)
Since it's "tonight".
I think I'll get a full score
with Jong Kook's choices.
I'm going to keep it real...
and choose whatever I want.
What if you had to
give up just one thing?
(A, losing muscle mass,
B, staying single forever)
Gosh, this is a tricky one.
For Jong Kook, it'll be B.
- Gosh, this is a tricky one.
- Goodness.
For Jong Kook, it'll be B.
You must be honest.
The keyword is "forever".
"Losing muscle mass"
is just a funny way to put it.
- Jong Kook, look.
- How is this a hard choice?
Look at how I am.
You'll end up with my body.
(You'll end up with my body.)
No, don't show him that.
- His body...
- Your body will become like mine.
I'll think about it right now.
- If you're as muscular...
- Right away.
- as Jong Kook,
- You can't exercise forever.
- he has to continue exercising.
- I can't exercise forever.
- Isn't it better to...
- This is a good question.
Isn't it better
to have flabby arms...
- than to never date?
- This is so funny.
- You really don't know me.
- It's A.
You're contemplating it, aren't you?
You don't know how big of a deal
it is to us.
- It's really...
- Losing muscles...
This is really...
You must not understand.
If I lose that,
I'm losing everything.
This is just a game.
You don't have to get this angry.
- This is... I imagined it,
- Just imagining it upsets you?
- and it's really horrific.
- Is it?
All right, let's just do it.
- 1.
- 1, 2, 3.
- It's B.
- It's A.
- No, it's A.
- No, he said it's B.
- I have to change it.
- It's B. He doesn't understand.
- Right.
Are you giving up on love, you punk?
- Is that what you'd do?
- I'll give up on love.
- You're choosing muscles?
- I'm sorry, but this isn't...
- something I need to think about.
- Why not?
It's not logical for us.
- It's like love to Jong Kook.
- What's wrong with losing muscle?
A doesn't make sense.
- Let's move on to the next one.
- Exercising.
"A lover who uses up an entire box
of tissues when she blows her nose".
"A lover who sucks it in because
she doesn't want to waste tissues".
She sucks in her snot?
(Which lover is better?)
Hold on. This is too extreme.
- I think I know what you'll choose.
- She uses an entire box?
- Gosh, this is...
- She sucks in her snot like this.
- Like this.
- No.
Her nose is running,
but she does this.
- Or she does this.
- This?
(A snot eating show)
Seriously?
I don't want a sister-in-law
like that.
I don't like either one.
- I'll choose.
- 1, 2, 3.
- The better one?
- Gosh. It's better to use tissues.
- Seriously?
- It's B?
(Which lover is better?)
(A lover who sucks it in because
she doesn't want to waste tissues.)
- B is better?
- Isn't that cuter?
If she uses a lot of tissues,
you can recycle them.
No.
- How is that cute?
- She might have a cold.
- There's cold season.
- That's for the rest of her life.
He's not even dating anyone,
so why are you all getting
so worked up?
Was this game supposed to be
so serious?
The next person is the last person.
Haha, you're last.
I can choose really quickly.
Haha, this is your first question.
(If you had to choose one.)
"If you had to choose one, Jong Kook
will be your business partner,"
- "but it won't go well."
- This is hard.
"Don't see Jong Kook forever but
have a successful business."
Gosh.
Haha has big dreams when it comes to
running a business.
Right. He's very ambitious.
- He's ambitious.
- He is.
So he has to choose between
Jong Kook and business.
- Right.
- This is...
- It's easy.
- Is it Jong Kook or business?
- It's not hard.
- You lose Jong Kook.
- You won't see him again.
- You'll lose him as a friend.
- Will he choose money or me?
Will he choose money or me?
- He said it's money or him.
- Will he choose money or me?
He has a lot of people connected
to his business.
- Right.
- A lot of people are involved.
I'm connected to that too.
You said
you'll make your decisions quickly.
How can you do this
in your first question?
This is just the beginning.
- How big is the business?
- I'll give you two candy bars.
Pass.
- This is...
- Darn it.
- Hold on.
- Think about it realistically.
- 1, 2, 3.
(Choose one.)
(Regardless of how business goes,
will he partner with Jong Kook?)
(Or will he consider his family and
coworkers and choose business?)
- 3.
- 3. Isn't it B?
- 3. B.
- I choose A.
- Why?
- Everyone chose B.
He's trying to have
an easy day today.
- Why?
- I'm being serious.
- He wants an easy day.
- I'm being honest.
- I thought about his family.
- I can make money in other ways.
I can't imagine
not being friends with him.
While you were thinking about it,
Jong Kook crushed this.
You must've been nervous.
(Crushed)
(While Haha was thinking
about it...)
(Think about it realistically.)
(Jong Kook was the only one
who couldn't be realistic about it.)
- You must've been nervous.
- I was.
It's the next question.
(If Yang Se Chan and Jeon So Min
get married...)
"If Yang Se Chan and Jeon So Min
get married..."
Who will you attend for?
- For the congratulatory money...
- Who will you attend for?
and where you will sit.
- He can't do half and half, right?
- Right.
- This one is hard.
- I think I know.
This is for real, right?
- He must choose one no matter what.
- I'll be sincere.
Hold on. Give us a moment.
- This is a hard one.
- How can he choose one?
I think it's easy.
Who will you choose?
- This one is easy for me.
- Who will you choose?
- Suk Jin, who will you choose?
- Pardon?
- Who will you choose?
- It's not your question anyway.
- I would choose B.
- But I'm so close with him too.
I think he'd be understanding.
I'm touched.
But I am understanding too.
My gosh.
- I don't think you will be.
- I would be.
- Se Chan would be understanding.
- Me too.
I think I should choose B too.
She won't be understanding.
- Se Chan would be understanding.
- He would be.
- I'm understanding too.
- She wouldn't.
- She will write down their names,
- She'd get revenge.
and be like,
"So you didn't come, right?
- Se Chan would be understanding.
- He'd be understanding.
Right.
Okay, then. 1, 2, 3.
- B.
- It's B.
- This is the correct answer.
- Right.
Se Chan would be grateful...
- that I considered his wife.
- I would be.
He'd be very grateful.
- She's...
- It's not because you're stingy.
- I would sit on So Min's side...
- But I...
What's scary to me is...
So Min put up A.
(Getting chills)
Gosh, my image is a mess, isn't it?
No, that's not what we mean.
So Min doesn't have a lot of friends
in the entertainment industry.
Right. I really don't.
- Right.
- If I had to choose one,
- I must give So Min more support.
- You need to support her.
- I need to support her.
- Right.
- I need to...
- How nice of you.
What about Ji Hyo?
Where would you go?
- Right. Where would you go?
- I'd go for So Min.
Right. Ji Hyo would do that.
If this situation applied
to you guys,
would anyone choose Se Chan?
I think I would choose Se Chan.
Jong Kook.
- It's because of this.
- No.
(This is why everyone chose B.)
The groom's side...
Why don't you guys start by dating?
We'll sit in the middle.
The first mission is over.
I got a lot wrong.
I got all of Haha's wrong.
I had a good run before then.
- You don't know Haha well.
- Right.
- What is this?
- Aren't we doing a race today?
(It's time to do the final race
in the clear weather.)
- What is this?
- Why are we in the woods?
Hold on. Isn't this the
Reserve Forces Training Center?
1, 2.
- What is this?
- This place is for survival games.
You're right, it is.
I think we came here once
on Running Man.
- What? It's like a training center.
- It's like guerrilla training.
- Director.
- Yes?
Someone stole all of my candy bars.
That's life.
But they won't tell me who did it.
You must take care of your things.
It's either Se Chan, Haha,
or Kwang Soo.
- I told you. It isn't me.
- It's not me either.
It's not me. I never touched yours.
(Actually, between the three
of them, the real criminal is...)
(30 minutes earlier, during lunch,
Haha filmed this video.)
(He takes the candy bar
out of So Min's bag.)
(He's blinded by the desire to win,
so he filmed himself...)
(adding to his candy bars.)
(She found out later and was angry.)
Give it back.
Stop playing around
and give it back to me.
Next.
(Then he casually begins to film
someone who looks suspicious.)
I swar. It's not me.
- Did you film it?
- Yes, I did.
(He doesn't know what's going on
and gets framed.)
It's him.
(I never touched yours.)
- Don't cry and stand in your spot.
- Gosh.
It's time for the final race.
Before we start the race,
I'll give you a chance...
to get yut candy bar,
which you need for the game,
and bullets, which you will use
in the game.
- Bullets?
- We need to shoot something.
- It's a survival game.
There are chance cards
hidden around this place.
The cards state how many
yut candy bars and bullets...
- you got.
- Okay.
There are minus cards as well.
What's important here is that...
if you touch it, you must take it.
You can give it to someone else
without their knowledge.
- The minus cards?
- Yes.
- Without their knowledge?
- Whether it's their clothes or bag,
you have to give it to them
without their realization.
- You can't hold onto it.
- If you find it,
you can't throw it away.
You have to pass it on
to another person or hold onto it.
- Okay.
- You can find it easily.
(He suddenly laughs.)
Why do you keep laughing?
What? It's not that.
I can't stop thinking about
the people who just tuned in.
I feel like I need to stand next
to someone dressed like this.
You can see everything.
(There's a reason
we're dressed like this.)
Ready, set, go.
I don't think I can go up high.
(Get the good chance cards
and give the bad ones to others.)
Where are they?
(Get the good chance cards
and give the bad ones to others.)
I feel like it's somewhere here.
There's one here.
This is amazing.
"Plus one yut candy bar".
(He gets a candy bar.)
There's one here. I found one.
- Can we go up this way?
- Okay.
"Minus three bullets".
(Why did she have to
pick this chance card?)
Where did they hide it?
(She needs to give this minus
chance card to another person.)
Jeon So Min.
So Min, what happened?
Jae Suk.
- I can't see it.
- It's upsetting.
- Jae Suk.
- What, So Min?
- Gosh, there it is.
- Where is it?
(Gosh, there it is.)
(Interested)
(I see.)
(He figured out her trick.)
- Jae Suk.
- You have been waiting for me.
Forget it.
Why can't I find a single one?
There it is. I found one.
This is...
(Minus 3 bullets?)
I can give it to someone else.
There it is.
(There it is.)
(He hasn't learned much
during his 10 years on Running Man.)
He is a fool. Suk Jin is a fool.
It's a bad one, right?
We can't throw it away, right?
- You can't throw it away.
(At that moment)
(Mesh Boy with a chance card
appears.)
What? Hey, don't do that.
Hey.
(He tries to subdue Suk Jin.)
You can't do that. Hey!
You can't shove it in like that.
Hey!
(Mesh Boy leaves
after giving him a big gift.)
- There is one here.
- Where?
(His satisfied facial expression
makes the hyenas gather.)
- I can't show you.
- Let's see it.
I can't show you.
(He steals the chance card.)
(Laughing)
Come here.
(Men with the average age of 52
play tag.)
(He is happy to run around
with Jae Suk.)
My goodness.
(Tag ends on a happy note.)
It looks like they are playing
a game on their own.
There are no chance cards.
Did you find one?
(Every viewer knows
what this look in his eyes means.)
(He must have a minus chance card.)
Let's catch him.
Let's put one together.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey.
This is a chance to lose
your minus chance cards!
Give it to him!
(See-through Boy
gives one to Kwang Soo.)
What is up with him?
- A chance card dropped.
- Can I put two on him?
Run from Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin's one and only rival)
Suk Jin, don't be like that.
Don't be like that.
Don't be like that. I am serious.
- Please.
- Get him.
Please. Please.
(He bursts out in laughter
for the 3rd time.)
(In a critical situation,)
(he bursts out in laughter again.)
My goodness.
(The great men laugh
in times of struggle.)
- It dropped.
- Time's up.
- Kwang Soo, you dropped this.
- Why would you give that to me?
Why would you give that to me?
You dropped it.
Starting from Jae Suk,
show us the chance cards you have.
- I got 3.
- 3 of what?
Three bullets. Keep it.
Next, So Min.
Steal five yut candy bars
from the member of your choice.
- Kwang Soo.
- Why me?
You stole my candy bars.
I really didn't.
- Five candy bars.
- Do I give them to her now?
(So Min gets 5 yut candy bars
from Kwang Soo.)
Minus three yut candy bars.
How about the card for the bullets?
Minus 12 in total.
(Minus 3 yut candy bars
and minus 9 bullets)
- He failed to give one to me.
- Really?
It's over for him.
- Minus nine bullets.
- The card for the bullets.
- It's over for him.
- I know.
(The result
of the preliminary mission)
(Ji Hyo, Jae Suk, Se Chan,
Kwang Soo,)
(So Min, Haha, Jong Kook, Suk Jin)
You can only attack the color
of your choosing...
in the Selective Survival Game.
Choose a color
from red, blue, yellow, and black...
and wear a hat
in the beginning of the race.
Then spin the roulette...
to choose the target color.
(Spin the roulette
to choose the target color.)
You can only attack
the color you got on the roulette.
You are out
if all 10 of your balloons pop.
The colors will get taken out 1 by 1
after 20 minutes.
10 balloons?
We will give you the candy bars
in accordance with the rankings...
and decide
who gets a prize or a penalty.
- It sounds hard.
- So there are targets.
There are targets.
There is another thing.
If you want to change...
your color or the target color,
pay with a candy bar
at the voting booths...
and receive a chance to change it.
You only get 10 bullets
in the beginning,
but you can purchase more
with a candy bar.
- How many for a candy bar?
- Three bullets for a candy bar.
- Yes.
You can also pick up
other members' bullets.
I have minus candy bars.
- We get 10 bullets.
- 10 bullets.
It's best to save up on the bullets.
We need to save up on the bullets.
This is complicated.
I am conflicted.
- Please go to your respective spot.
- Okay.
(Current Number of Candy Bars)
(Jong Kook, Haha, Se Chan, Jae Suk,
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, Suk Jin, So Min)
How many bullets
do you currently have?
Minus nine bullets.
Then you will start with one bullet.
That's so annoying.
You can simply take them out.
(9 bullets get removed.)
Why... You can simply take them out.
Here you go.
Hold on.
Can I buy the bullets right away?
- The game needs to start first.
- Then I can buy the bullets.
You will first select
the color of your hat.
From red, blue, yellow, and black,
select a color.
(Select the color of your hat.)
- Red, blue, yellow, and black?
- Yes.
I choose black. I bet a lot of them
will choose black.
(The members who get black
as the target color can attack him.)
All right.
I bet people won't choose
this color.
(Haha and Jae Suk
wear a black hat as well.)
I will select blue.
This wig is so funny.
(She wears a blue hat over the wig.)
It's the color of passion.
Red.
I see why I selected red.
I had my eyes on the red hat
for some reason.
Okay.
Kwang Soo.
- We are on the same boat.
- That's right.
Now, please spin the roulette
and choose your target color.
Okay, I got it.
(The target color is decided
by spinning the roulette.)
(Jong Kook's target color is...)
(black!)
- It's black.
- Okay.
Gosh, I should have gotten red.
(Thankfully, Kwang Soo
won't be attacked by Jong Kook.)
It's red.
(Kwang Soo's target color is red.)
(Jong Kook?)
(Will Kwang Soo be able
to attack Jong Kook?)
(Everyone spins a roulette
and gets a target color.)
The race starts.
Here comes a gunman!
My target color is black.
I need to find a black hat.
If I am at the bottom,
I will use up my candy bars...
and go out with a bang.
(Suk Jin carefully enters
the battlefield.)
Where are they?
(Let's see.)
Suk Jin is wearing a black hat.
(He is my target.)
My first target is Suk Jin.
(My first target is Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin.
(They keep their target color
a secret.)
(While looking for a red hat,
Jae Suk finds Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook,
is your target color black?
What?
You kept looking this way.
I looked since your target color
could be red.
No. I am not attacking you.
(Kwang Soo
hurriedly purchases bullets.)
Then why...
(They are each other's target.)
I want to pass through.
Where are you going?
What? Can't I pass through?
Even if I am wearing a black hat,
you shouldn't shoot me now.
Excuse me?
Is there such a rule?
Are you going to shoot?
Since when did we have such a rule?
- Are you going to shoot?
- A black hat...
You aren't going to shoot, are you?
- What?
- I mean...
I guess red isn't your target color.
You shot at me!
(Jae Suk attempts to attack.)
(He can't help but go backward
since Jong Kook's guards are up.)
Hey.
(Kwang Soo finished loading up
the bullets!)
Why does it keep coming off?
This... Hey.
(He approaches quickly...)
(and shoots Jong Kook
without hesitation.)
(He takes out 3 of his balloons.)
(This is good.)
(Jae Suk uses this chance
to run away.)
(That's too bad.)
- Haha.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
Haha's color is black too.
I will take out Haha.
(I will take out Haha.)
(Haha appeared
as an easy target...)
My goodness.
(just when Jong Kook was motivated.)
(Screaming)
(He chases after him mercilessly.)
- Come on!
- Suk Jin's hat is black too.
(He hits 2 targets with 1 bullet.)
(Haha and Suk Jin quickly lose
their balloons because of him.)
Okay.
I should change my hat.
- I would like to change my hat.
- Turn in one candy bar.
I will change it...
to yellow.
(He changes to a yellow hat.)
- I will change the color of my hat.
- Okay, to which color?
- A yellow hat, please.
- I will change my hat.
I will change my hat.
Yellow.
(Yellow.)
(The symbol of the weakest members,
yellow hat)
No one is wearing a yellow hat.
- Let's be allies.
- Why are there so many yellow hats?
What?
(Why are there so many yellow hats?)
Why are there so many yellow hats?
There are so many yellow hats.
Then yellow will be
the target color.
(The lack of communication
made them all wear a yellow hat.)
All of them changed to a yellow hat.
Shall I change my target color?
How much is it?
I will change my target color.
I will take my chances.
(Jong Kook wants to change
the target color to yellow.)
I will take my chances.
1, 2... Please let it be yellow.
Yellow, yellow, yellow. Yellow.
Gosh.
(He gets red instead.)
- Did I get red?
- Your target color is red.
I can spin it again, right?
(I can spin it again, right?)
I will spin it again.
All right.
Hold on. Blue?
I don't see any blue hats.
I will spin it once more.
I see how people lose their fortune
by gambling.
This will be the last time.
(He keeps getting different colors.)
It won't be entertaining
unless I get the color.
It's black again.
This is driving me crazy.
I will spin it again.
(He lost 7 candy bars
to the roulette.)
I got yellow this time, right?
Okay. How many candy bars
did I use?
8 candy bars? 7 candy bars?
- Seven candy bars.
- For goodness' sake.
(He used 7 candy bars for a right
to attack the yellow hats.)
I should change to a blue hat.
Is he coming toward me?
Haha.
I should take out Haha.
(He charges toward Haha.)
He is coming this way!
I need to change my color!
Stop, Jong Kook.
Let me go this once.
I will give you bullets.
- I will give you a candy bar.
- How many will you give me?
- Give me candy bars.
- Two candy bars.
- I need at least 3.
- I can't give you 3.
- I used 7.
- Jong Kook.
- Let's go with 2.
- Jong Kook, I...
- Otherwise, I will take you out.
Hold on.
- 2.
- Give me 3.
Give me 3.
I will leave if you give me 3.
- Jong Kook.
- Hurry up.
- Give me three.
- I used seven.
- We run a restaurant together.
- Give me 3.
- 2 bullets and 1 candy bar.
Give me three.
You will find more yellow hats
down there.
- I know.
- Please, Jong Kook.
- Should I finish you off?
All right, all right.
(He loses 1 balloon by stalling.)
Two candy bars.
One.
- Give me 2. Hurry up and give me 2.
- What?
- Give me 2.
- 2?
- Hurry up.
- Will you give them back?
Give them to me.
- You seem like a bully.
- Give them to me.
- Then...
- I could take you out.
- All right, all right.
- Hurry up and give them to me.
- Go now.
- All right. You can go ahead.
I will be smiling.
(I will be smiling.)
It's the first time
I got candy bars stolen.
- I got two candy bars.
- This is so annoying.
Hey, I used seven candy bars.
I swear.
It was so hard to get yellow.
(He moves quickly to find
the next target.)
I didn't know you could attack
the same color.
(Ji Hyo lost 7 balloons
to Se Chan's attack.)
Ji Hyo.
I only have a few candy bars.
(It's so sad.)
(At that moment)
(Kwang Soo ambushes her.)
(He takes out
the rest of the balloons.)
(He takes Ji Hyo out instantly
and runs away.)
Who was it? Who was it?
Jong Kook?
Gosh.
(Ji Hyo is out
8 minutes into the race.)
I will spin the roulette.
Please.
(Kwang Soo's target color is...)
- Red.
(Popping)
(Why did his balloon pop?)
(His balloon got caught
on the tape.)
Why did it pop? Why?
(He becomes confused
after attacking himself.)
(While Kwang Soo is in a daze
from losing a balloon,)
Stop it.
(the two youngest members
are having a love quarrel.)
(As a result,
So Min has 1 balloon left.)
I have one balloon left.
(She accepts her fate.)
So Min is out.
(So Min is out.)
(Devastated)
So Min is out.
Look at So Min who is knocked out.
(Shooting)
(I am so annoyed.)
What should I do? I am so angry.
You lasted for a while.
(She is too upset to leave.)
(Kwang Soo approaches her.)
(He collects her bullets.)
- Stop it.
- You don't need them.
(Haha was picking up bullets
like Kwang Soo.)
Hey.
Give them to me.
Give them to me. They are mine!
How are they yours?
What is going on?
Everyone is stealing things from me.
I am sorry. I am sorry.
(20 minutes have passed.)
Now, black will disappear.
Black will disappear
among the hats and target colors.
(Black disappears
among the hats and target colors.)
(The members whose hat color
or target color is black...)
(select a different color.)
I will change my hat color too.
Was your hat color blue?
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and Se Chan
unite with a red hat.)
Let's go.
What's your target color?
- What's your target color?
- Yellow.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Is it yellow?
- Yes, I changed it.
We should take out Jong Kook first.
- But Jong Kook...
- We shouldn't fight.
- Jong Kook is on his first vest.
- Really?
- You are on your first vest, right?
- Yes.
(Suk Jin's target color
is actually red.)
I tried to pick it up earlier,
but...
Gosh, you startled me.
All right.
Change into your second vest.
Gosh, you startled me.
All right.
Change into your second vest.
Is his target color red?
Give me a vest.
(He talked about
taking out Jong Kook together.)
How...
- Change into your second vest.
- That was too low.
Jae Suk, I won't shoot you.
- Se Chan.
- My target color is yellow.
- I can't shoot you anyway.
- It's yellow, right?
It isn't red, right?
It isn't red.
My target color is yellow.
(Happy)
- Okay.
- What?
(Startled)
- Suk Jin.
- Be careful not to show your back.
Suk Jin is out.
For goodness' sake.
Is your target color red?
(After taking out Suk Jin)
I will change my hat color
to yellow.
I put in one candy bar.
(One man watches Se Chan
as he takes his chances.)
Suk Jin is out.
What?
(This man in a sleeveless top
dreams of turning the tables.)
(Haha's location)
Hold on. I will take Jae Suk out.
(5 people remain.)
All right.
(Jae Suk catches a breath.)
(One man aims his gun at him.)
(Haha's camera)
(The sniper in a sleeveless top)
(He shoots.)
We need to join forces.
- What?
- Is someone there?
Haha is there. Haha is there.
- Haha's hat is yellow.
Shall we go and take him out?
- I will enter.
- Okay.
(I totally scared them.)
(Meanwhile)
So Haha is still alive.
We need to figure out the color
of Haha and Kwang Soo's hats.
If their target color is yellow...
I mean, blue... No.
Would you go and look at the drone?
Go and look at the drone?
- I mean...
- Drone.
I mean,
find the person
who is flying the drone...
and figure out
the color of their hats.
- I see. Where is the operator?
- It's a good idea, right?
Hold on. It's coming this way.
Operator.
Where are you?
Where are you flying the drone?
He is here. The operator is here.
Sir.
Please go to the battlefield...
and see their hat colors.
This way.
(A drone gets dispatched
for the children's shooting game.)
It's like a war movie.
I just need to see their heads.
(Se Chan is the commander
who leads the drone.)
Go up higher.
There we go.
Please go closer.
I see one yellow hat.
If we go diagonally...
One blue hat.
How about the other one?
Kwang Soo still has a blue hat.
This is really good.
This must be how
they use a drone for a war.
(He observes everything
with a drone.)
Red will disappear.
- Will red disappear?
- Yes.
Red disappeared, right?
Blue still exists.
(They need to pick
between yellow and blue.)
(Now, blue and yellow
are the only colors remaining.)
(It's time to make a decisive move.)
(The ones who usually hit and run
have a face-off.)
- Okay.
- Haha.
It would be our loss
if we go against each other.
That's right.
Let's not shoot at each other.
(They pretend to have a ceasefire.)
Give me one bullet.
- Gosh!
- Okay!
(Jong Kook appears.)
(Jong Kook figured out the situation
through drone.)
(Haha is out.)
Haha is out.
Okay. Kwang Soo remains.
(His next target is Kwang Soo.)
(He tries to corner him.)
What? I have no one to shoot.
- I have no one to shoot.
- Why?
No one else has a blue hat.
Your target color is blue.
- What's your target color?
- Blue.
Are you sure?
Se Chan, take the right.
(The Drone Squad works together
one more time.)
- Okay. Go.
- Go.
- Jong Kook.
- Move out of the way.
- Let's go together.
(He approaches Kwang Soo
and shoots mercilessly.)
(But Jong Kook's balloons pop.)
Hey, you punk.
(Popping)
(Se Chan pretended to go
after Kwang Soo.)
(His real target was Jong Kook.)
(He easily takes out two balloons.)
(When he spun the roulette
for the target color earlier,)
(he got yellow.)
Yellow?
- What's your target color?
- Blue.
Are you sure?
(He fooled Jong Kook...)
(and shot at his back.)
I popped
two of Jong Kook's balloons.
Run!
(Jong Kook's first vest is over.)
- Se Chan, okay.
- Kwang Soo.
Okay, Se Chan.
- Kwang Soo, run.
- Okay, I got it.
I can't believe him.
I can't trust Se Chan anymore.
My love for Se Chan is over.
(Jong Kook becomes furious.)
(Without a care for his balloons,)
(he succeeds to take out Se Chan.)
Am I out?
Take him out.
(He takes out Kwang Soo mercilessly
when he falls down.)
Take him out.
Se Chan is out.
(Two people remain.)
Now...
Look at Jae Suk.
- Double guns.
He has double guns.
(Double muscles versus Double guns)
Let's shoot from a long distance.
- Shall we do that? Okay.
- Okay.
- I will load up on the bullets.
(There is a reason why Jae Suk
suggested a long-distance match.)
(Long-distance shooting
is Jae Suk's forte.)
(He takes out a balloon
with his double guns.)
Jae Suk's hit rate is no joke.
(He's flustered.)
(Jae Suk sometimes becomes cool
when he has guns in his hands.)
Gosh, Jae Suk. Hold on.
(Jong Kook gains energy
when he wears a sleeveless top.)
(They are neck-and-neck.)
Why are you using double guns?
(Jae Suk with 3 balloons...)
(versus Jong Kook wth 1 balloon)
(At that moment,)
(Jae Suk's balloon pops.)
(Now, it's
2 balloons versus 1 balloon.)
Okay.
(He used one of his balloons
as bait...)
(and targeted Jong Kook's
last balloon.)
(Yoo Jae Suk wins.)
Yoo Jae Suk wins, and
Kim Jong Kook is in second place.
(Jae seok, who won, and Jong Kook,
who fought from a long distance,)
(both put up a strong fight.)
- This was good.
- It was at a long distance.
(It was a fair fight which is
hard to see on Running Man.)
- It wasn't a cheap fight.
- Right. It was good.
The zebra pants I'm wearing today...
(The zebra pants were perfect
for the mission.)
I was like a zebra running around
in an open field.
I know.
(It was a clean fight
that made them proud of themselves.)
This is the final result.
Jae Suk came in 1st place,
and Jong Kook came in 2nd.
Really?
1st place gets 20 candy bars.
(The number of candy bars given)
2nd place gets 15,
and 3rd place gets 10.
- The others will get 8, 6, 4, 2, 0.
- We used a lot.
- I'll announce the results.
- Okay.
- With 32 candy bars...
- Someone got that many?
(Will the winner be among
the 1st and 2nd place winners...)
(who got 20 and 15 candy bars?)
- It's Kim Jong Kook.
- Me?
- I came in first place?
- He got a lot.
- It's Kim Jong Kook.
- Me? I came in first place?
He got a lot.
- I used a lot.
- You didn't exchange them.
- I exchanged 10.
- With 31, Jae Suk is in 2nd place.
How disappointing.
That last one.
In 3rd place... The person
in 3rd place can choose 1.
Is it me?
It's Haha, who has 26.
What?
- Really? He has that many?
- He has 20 on him.
- He didn't exchange a lot.
- Why does he have so many?
In 4th place is Se Chan with 22.
That's too bad.
In 5th place is Ji Hyo with 11.
- In 6th place, Suk Jin with 9.
- I have 11?
- Gosh.
- What?
In 7th place is Kwang Soo with 8.
In 8th place is So Min with 3.
- Hold on.
- So...
since So Min came in last place,
Haha loses his spot in 3rd place
and will get the penalty too.
- So who's in 3rd place?
- Se Chan is in 3rd place.
(1. If So Min or Haha comes in last
place, they both get the penalty.)
(2. If they don't, the one with the
lowest score will get the penalty.)
- So I don't get the penalty, right?
- You don't.
Okay!
- See? You can't steal mine.
- It's a difference of one.
Weren't we competing
against each other?
- You had to take care of her.
- You're right.
We could've avoided it
if I gave her three.
First, we'll have...
the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place winners
roll their balls first.
The tablet.
Where's the tablet?
I would like to get
the massage gun.
(Clothing care machine, tablet PC,
turntable, photo of staff, and more)
Is Kwang Soo's life-sized
cardboard cutout still here?
The photo of the staff
is much better...
than a life-sized
cardboard cutout of Kwang Soo.
I want to cheer for you guys.
I'll start now. In 1, 2, 3.
How will it go?
- Let's go.
- Go to the right.
(What will Se Chan, who came in
3rd place instead of Haha, get?)
- Go to the right. What is it?
- A dud.
(Dud)
- Serves you right.
(There are only 2 among 20,
but he got it.)
I feel better now.
- It's possible to get a dud.
- I feel better too.
I got a dud?
A dud came out among
all of these.
Ji Hyo, I'll drop one here.
What if you go more that way?
- This way.
- Drop them both at once.
Should we go for the tablet PC?
(He let go of the ball.)
- What is it?
- It's going this way.
It's coming this way.
(What will happen this time?)
Did it come this way?
It's the tablet PC.
(Did he get the tablet PC?)
- It's the tablet PC.
- What?
- Gosh.
- Gosh!
- Oh, my.
I must be going crazy.
- This is crazy.
- That's incredible.
- What's with you?
- You're lucky.
How did you get the tablet PC?
Why would you use your luck here?
How can someone unlucky get this?
This is insane.
This won't do.
- Should I go for the tablet PC?
- Of course.
- Should I go?
- Yes.
- It's heading for it.
- It's the tablet pc.
It's going to end up
at the tablet PC.
(He dropped his ball in the same
place Jae Suk did.)
- It's the tablet PC.
- It won't go there.
It's going to end up
at the tablet PC.
- It's going.
- Tablet PC.
It's the group photo.
(It's the photo of the crew...)
(which is next to the tablet PC.)
It's meaningful.
Our writers came out so nicely.
- They came out nicely.
- How does it look? Let me see.
You should've added your names.
Min Hee is sitting in the front.
We're grateful that
you care so much about us.
- That's too bad.
- This is...
- I'm going again.
- It's so funny.
- It's going in that direction.
- Right.
- Oh, no. Where are you going?
- Goodness.
- No.
- It's going far.
(It's headed toward the right.)
No.
- Dud or clothing care machine.
- Or Kwang Soo's cardboard cutout.
No.
- Dud or clothing care machine.
- Or Kwang Soo's cardboard cutout.
(What?)
(The ball is between the photo
and the clothing care machine.)
(Where will the ball go?)
- The clothing care machine.
- Really?
(His eyes open wide
just like Jae Suk.)
- Really?
- What is this?
- What will you do?
- Bo Pil is crying.
SBS will go broke.
- He's crying.
- Bo Pil is crying.
- It costs 1,500 dollars.
- Really?
What will Bo Pil do?
I'll go easy on you
and just get the massage gun.
- The massage gun is nice.
- Really?
I didn't tell you the penalty.
- What is it?
- You're right. Haha and So Min.
The penalty we've prepared
for you is...
I told you already that the penalty
is inconvenient and exhausting.
You must make mask straps
out of beads for the members.
(Make mask straps for the members
out of beads.)
- Goodness.
- Out of beads.
(It's the worst penalty of making
gifts they won't want to give.)
It really is an annoying penalty.
This is going to be hard.
Okay, then. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
- Good job everyone.
No, you don't have to give it to me.
- Take it with you.
- Right.
- Do you want the massage gun?
- Sure.
- I don't need the machine.
- It's fine.
You just need to put it in
after you design it.
You can design it
with the ones you want.
Who will you guys give it to?
I'll make it for...
(The process of making it and
the people they will give it to...)
I should make it with the big ones.
This is nice. I like it.
(will be revealed next week
during the gift giving ceremony.)