(A cool breeze is blowing.)
Hello.
(The members are happy to be here.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Ji Hyo is like the actress from the movie, "Bichunmoo".
(She got her hair done for fall.)
- A slave hunter. - It's "Bichunmoo".
She doesn't like her bangs.
Ji Hyo, you look like a school bully...
(She looks like a school bully from the 1980s.)
from the 1980s. They wear bangs like yours.
- Either put your hair up or down. - That's what old ladies did.
- Right. - They went to a salon for that.
- This is in style now. - Look at the hair claw clips.
Look at the hair claw clips.
- Look at the hair claw clips. - Earlier in the waiting room,
how did you guys hold out without talking about it?
- We were waiting. - I wanted to say it here.
(They only bite each other in front of cameras.)
I was waiting to mention it here.
- We just bite at each other. - It's the retro trend.
(She responds to nonsense.)
- I see. - She says it's retro.
That's funny.
(There's news about Jae Suk...)
It's about Jae Suk.
(taking 1st place as always.)
- He took first place again. - "Korea's most influential people".
("Yoo Jae Suk Places 1st in Variety Show Section")
- That's right. Thank you. - You're unbelievable.
("Yoo Jae Suk Absolute 1st Place Leader of Alter Egos")
"Korea's most influential people".
(Yoo Jae Suk moves Korea.)
- You're a great man. - The most influential person.
There will be a biography of him.
(Jealous)
Aren't you sick of taking first place in stuff like this?
He even ranks above BTS.
- This is unbelievable. - He's even above BTS.
(The Korean star beats the world star.)
- He got a lot more votes than them. - Even BTS?
It's not like that. Anyway,
(Shy)
it was a weekly newsmagazine.
Did you call people around you for the poll?
Who would he call?
(Suggesting a suspicion of bribe)
- What is he talking about? - Why are you being so sarcastic?
- What's wrong with you? - Just congratulate him heartily.
What's with the sarcasm?
- It just doesn't make sense. - Just be happy for him.
(How ugly of him.)
Why does it not make sense?
- This is too big a deal. - Just congratulate him.
(Gibberish)
Why is he being like this?
(I'm really disappointed.)
It's just too hard to believe.
You should be happy that he's our member.
We are very proud.
- I guess you're right. - There's one more thing.
- That's right. Suk Jin. - What?
(Suk Jin has good news.)
- He's got more than... - It's about "Ji Suk Jin World".
("Ji Suk Jin World" reached 100,000 subscribers.)
- 100,000 subscribers. - Over 100,000 subscribers?
- That's right. - He's got the silver button.
(The man with a silver button)
It's about 150,000 people now.
(Bling bling)
- The silver button... - What is it called?
(Did he get a silver button for 100,000 subscribers?)
- What? - Silver...
- Silver... - Silver town?
(He'll head to the silver town for 100,000 subscribers.)
- Isn't it a silver town? - Like a town for the aged?
- He's in a silver town. - He can show it live.
- He got into a silver town. - Did you get into a silver town?
(Selling silver town in "Ji Suk Jin World")
Why did you go to a silver town instead of getting a silver button?
Town. Haha, you have more than 100,000 subscribers.
(Haha also reached 100,000 subscribers.)
- That's true. - He does?
- Right. - When Haha...
first started his channel, he was a little...
- He did all sorts of stupid things. - Exactly.
He has a lot of painful memories about it.
(His first film only left him a scar.)
- It was ridiculous. - He feels bad about it.
He made his videos like a film, but no one watched it.
(Too much enthusiasm)
- "Daddy Free". - It didn't get him subscribers.
("Daddy Free")
- In short... - No one watched it.
(A hero film produced over a year)
He had no idea about what things were like in the field.
- He was so out of touch. - I need videos that fit YouTube.
(YouTube should be like YouTube.)
He just started it without knowing what's what.
(His passion was too much for YouTube to bear.)
I'm a YouTuber now.
I was really surprised when he started his channel.
I'll try some eating show next week.
That was funny.
Kwang Soo, you should also start something.
(Suddenly)
- Start what? - YouTube.
You should start working.
I'm working now.
(Absurd)
- Really? - I'm working now.
- These days... - Kwang Soo will...
start Haduri.
- Why would I start Haduri? - It's SkyLove.
- That was a long time ago. - He will start SkyLove.
(He will be on Haduri instead of YouTube.)
With a lighter.
Why would I start Haduri with a webcam?
(The retro sister likes it.)
You can use Cheollian.
Or Nownuri.
With the COVID-19 spreading, picking up private hobbies...
(With the COVID-19 spreading, picking up private hobbies...)
(are more important than ever these days.)
is more important than ever these days.
- I agree. - Exactly.
Today, you will get to learn different hobbies and win a lottery.
(You will get to learn different hobbies...)
(and have a chance to win a lottery.)
- A lottery? - That sounds nice.
(Lucky Hobbies Race)
It's called Lucky Hobbies Race.
"Lucky Hobbies?"
There will be three different one-day classes today.
(There will be 3 different one-day classes.)
- That's nice. - You'll be divided...
(You'll be divided into two teams for each class.)
into two teams for each class.
And we will give you lottery tickets according to your performance.
(You will get lottery tickets according to your performance.)
The lottery works in the same way as Lotto.
(The lottery works in the same way as Lotto.)
But you have numbers only from 1 to 10.
(6 numbers will be drawn from 1 to 10.)
That sounds good. How many numbers should we guess?
We will choose six numbers.
(You will get prizes...)
And you will get prizes according to the results.
(according to the results.)
- It's worth a shot. - That sounds great.
There's a way to increase the chance of winning.
The teachers of each class will select the best student.
(The teachers of each class will select the best student.)
The member who gets picked can select one of the winning numbers.
(The member who gets picked can select one of the winning numbers.)
That's really good. We can select a number?
We will draw the winning numbers with a few of them selected.
(The better you learn, the more chance of winning.)
I've never bought a lottery ticket before.
After the class, you will perform as a team.
(After the class, you will perform as a team.)
And the winner will be decided by the living legend...
of variety shows, Camera Director Kang Chan Hee.
(The legend of variety shows)
(Camera Director Kang Chan Hee)
The living legend of variety shows, Camera Director Kang Chan Hee.
(Camera Director Kang Chan Hee has 35 years of experience.)
I've seen him in variety shows for over 25 years.
(Joined KBS in 1985)
I remember seeing him in "Dream Team".
(Established Vision Production in 1998)
He will decide the winner.
(Don't talk about variety shows without Kang Chan Hee.)
He is a legend.
You should be on "Immortal Songs" soon.
(Immortal Chan Hee)
What are they going to do with his episode?
They usually have legendary singers.
(Legend of Legends)
They can sing Director Kang's favorite songs.
(Chan Hee's Favorites Episode)
- He's a legend. - He really is.
He might be a big fan of BTS.
Once Director Kang picks the winning team,
(According to the variety legend's choice,)
they will select the best student.
(the winning team selects 1 best student,)
And the losing team will select the worst student.
(and the losing team selects 1 worst student.)
- That sounds fierce. - And...
the best student gets one extra ticket while the worst returns one.
(The best student gets 1 extra ticket while the worst returns 1.)
Oh, no.
Let me show you today's prize then.
- I'm curious. - What is it?
(Revealing the prizes)
They offer great prizes these days.
The fact that they're revealing them now...
(1st place, 40g of gold)
- It's Korean beef. - What is it? Meat?
- It's gold. - Do we get gold?
(2nd place, Korean beef set)
- Seriously? - If you get all six numbers right,
(3rd place, a box of peaches)
you will get 40g of gold.
(They fall in love with gold.)
- Really? - Yes.
How much would this be?
If it's 40g, it's about 3,000 dollars.
(He knows the market well.)
If there's more than one winner, they will have to share the prize.
(If there is more than one winner, they will have to share the prize.)
We should share the gold.
Those who get five numbers right will get Korean beef.
(2nd and 3rd places will get prizes...)
(according to the number of lottery tickets.)
- Even second place is good. - And third place...
(He prefers protein.)
gets a box of peaches.
(Doubting)
- Do we really get the prizes? - Sure.
- And we don't have guests today. - We have no guests today.
(No guests, no turning back)
- These are for us. - Right.
- I'll give you three tickets each. - It will be fun.
(3 tickets per person are given.)
You get three tickets each.
Just get me one.
Three tickets per person.
(Anticipating)
- Three tickets each? - Yes.
- Here you are. - Okay.
(3 tickets)
- Here. - Thank you.
Okay.
(3 tickets)
- Are they three? - Yes.
I guess I'll get a few numbers right.
(0 tickets)
- Are they three? - Yes.
- The number... - We have leftovers.
- Really? - You didn't give me mine, you fool.
- Why are you swearing at him? - It's not like that.
Why are you so upset?
I wasn't swearing. I was being friendly.
(His expression became violent as he's disappointed.)
- You don't have to be upset. - You didn't get one?
Let's go take our first class then.
(They head to the first hobby class.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(What is the first class about?)
- Is this it? - Yes.
(What's all this?)
What's what?
What's going on?
(Some people greet the members shouting out loud.)
Hello, ma'am.
(Haha knows the teacher?)
- Who are they? - The other day...
Hello.
(The first class)
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
(Yodel)
(Lee Eun Kyung is the doyenne of Korean yodel songs.)
(Park Sung Ho became a yodel singer thanks to Lee Eun Kyung.)
(Lee Eun Kyung works to improve the status of Korean culture.)
(She was also Pengsoo and Haha's yodel teacher.)
(Kang Dong Hye and Lee Eun Kyung)
- Nice to meet you. - Hello.
- Attention. - Yes, ma'am.
(Suddenly)
(Is this a close-order drill?)
Yes, ma'am.
- Yodel. - Yodel.
- Yodel. - At ease.
(They thought they would learn how to yodel.)
- At ease. - At ease.
- At ease. - Yodel.
(The teacher...)
- Yodel. - Attention.
(seems somewhat extraordinary.)
- Attention. Yodel. - Yodel.
Bow.
(She talks to them like they're children.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Hyper)
That was so cool.
- You guys are the best. - She sounds cheerful.
(She's super hyper.)
She's very energetic.
(She's energetic from the start.)
- You guys are the best. - Thank you.
- You're the best. - So...
(Introducing the doyenne of yodel songs, Lee Eun Kyung)
Ms. Lee Eun Kyung is Pengsoo's yodel teacher.
(She's also known as Pengsoo's yodel teacher.)
- I see. - Right.
I used to be in a children's show, "Ppoppoppo".
"Ppoppoppo?"
(They can barely remember it.)
Do you remember her now?
How long have you been doing this?
(How long have you been doing this?)
It's been only 38 years.
(She has 38 years of experience in yodel.)
- Really? - Yes.
I started it when I was in her belly,
- so it's about... - Are you her daughter?
(He's shocked to hear that she's the daughter.)
- Really? - Yes, I am.
(The yodel mother and daughter)
It's three generations old.
Will you stay quiet?
(Cutting off)
(Jae Suk is on Running Man only to tease Kwang Soo.)
- Just stay still. - It's three generations.
So three generations of your family are doing this?
(Repeating what Kwang Soo said)
That's what I just said.
(Angry)
- Stay quiet. - Yes, that's right.
And you did this. What's the difference?
(Angry)
- They are yodel masters. - Right.
(With the yodel mother and daughter,)
So you're her daughter.
(let's fall for the charm of yodel.)
Yes. Nice to meet you.
Let's hear the teachers yodel first.
(They watch the teachers' demonstration before they learn.)
Let's do that.
(Excited)
(They begin with fun accordion music.)
This is really nice.
You can dance.
(Jaw-dropping)
(Clapping her hands)
My goodness.
(Her yodel captivates their eyes and ears from the beginning.)
Her falsetto voice is impressive.
(Their clear voice clears their minds.)
- She's amazing. - It's unbelievable.
(The yodel master steps up.)
All right. Let's walk together.
(It's so fun.)
(Fascinating)
(They are so into the charm of yodel.)
(They are done...)
(falling for yodel.)
Yodel! Yodel!
- Yodel! Yodel! - Yodel! Yodel!
- I love it. - I got goosebumps.
(Amazed)
- That was amazing. - Yodel!
(It's the best.)
This is really exciting.
It was the best.
(The yodel mother and daughter's amazing performance)
- Thank you. - They are great.
You will put on some costumes...
(They get changed first before they learn.)
and learn how to yodel.
So Min looks good.
(Got changed)
- You look beautiful. - It fits you nicely.
(She's changed to the Alps girl.)
She's pretty.
- Now you should learn how to yodel. - Yes.
(It's time to learn yodel.)
Yodel is all about making a good chest voice.
(The main point is to make a chest voice.)
- Yo, yo, yo. - Yo, yo, yo.
- Ya, ya, ya. - Ya, ya, ya.
- Ye, ye, ye. - Ye, ye, ye.
- This is the chest voice. - Let's do this.
This time, let the air through your nose.
(They try letting the air through the nose this time.)
(Singing together)
My goodness. That's good.
(Raising her hand)
- Perfect. That's how you do it. - Ms. Lee.
Yes, you can ask me any questions.
- Am I doing it right? - That's good.
(Raising her hand)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(The Maenggu brothers appear again.)
Hey, stop it.
You two, stay away from each other.
- Why? Are we too loud? - Se Chan, come over here.
(Forced distancing)
- Come here. - I'm sorry.
They do that whenever they're standing together.
(I'll see you again soon, my brother.)
- They're both great. That was good. - Yes.
- The most important thing is "ay". - "Ay".
(The most important thing in yodel is "Ay".)
Once you master singing "ay", you're ready to yodel.
(You're a master yodeller if you sing "Ay" well.)
- "Ay". - Watch my mouth.
(They're trying to sing as she did.)
One of you didn't smile.
(But...)
- Who? - Kwang Soo didn't smile.
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo didn't smile.
- Me? - Hey, smile a little bit, will you?
(Smiling brightly)
That's good. Great job.
You should always smile.
(The basic quality of yodel is smiling.)
- Of course. - Stop smiling.
(Committed to the fundamentals)
- You should smile while yodeling. - Stop smiling.
Se Chan, your gums might dry out.
(Close your mouth.)
What is wrong with him now? Move aside.
(The pink gums that are perfect for yodeling)
Move aside.
Repeat after me.
(They put a smile on their faces, and class began again.)
(Ho-ho-ho)
(Yo-yo)
Now, try this.
(I'm sorry to interrupt, but...)
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but do people usually learn to yodel in a large group like this?
(Usually...)
- Is this normal? - My ears hurt.
(The yodel class of the largest scale in 38 years)
(Suffering from tinnitus)
- My ears hurt so much. - I mean,
- does everyone learn this way? - I have something to say.
- I'll tell you one thing. - Go ahead.
(Haha has already taken one of her classes.)
I met her not long ago.
I took her class with six-year-old children.
And we're learning exactly the same as I did then.
(From last time...)
(Her way of teaching never changes.)
- It's exactly the same. - Can we get another teacher?
- It's exactly the same. - I know.
The average age of us is 40.
(The youngest is 35 years old.)
- That's so funny. - Together.
(Her yodel class covers all generations.)
(Inputting "Ah, eh, and oh")
This is yodeling.
You've learned everything.
(An intensive class)
All you need to learn is how to sing "ay" and "oh".
(She keeps saying we've learned everything.)
One more important thing.
"Yo-la..."
(Yo-la-la-di-oh)
- Good. You've learned everything. - Yes.
(Pressuring them to learn)
- You can start singing now. - Really?
- Are you sure? Already? - You're ready now.
(We've learned everything?)
- I don't think we're ready yet. - You've learned everything.
(It's been 10 minutes since they've begun.)
- You don't think you can? - No, I don't.
She's like a gambler.
(I realized...)
It feels like she's skipping several steps.
(The gambler, "Yo Eyed Del")
I'm so anxious. I feel like I'm being chased.
My back is sweating.
(The forced learning makes them break out in a cold sweat.)
- You see... - I'm feeling so hot right now.
- I'm sweating a lot. - She's moving on so fast.
(One hour is too short to learn how to yodel.)
- Of course. We don't have time. - That's true.
- Shall we try to sing? - Okay.
(Concentrating to learn quickly)
I bet you all have heard this song. It's a very famous yodel song.
(Learning the song to perform)
- Yes, I know this song. - It's an Austrian folk song.
(Today's song, "Yodel in the Forest")
I'll sing it for you first.
(Listen carefully since you'll perform later.)
Listen carefully.
This is the hardest part.
(The hardest part)
There she goes.
That's all.
(She sang such a difficult song effortlessly.)
- That was fantastic. - She yodels so easily.
(Impressed by her yodeling once again)
- That was beautiful. - Indeed.
- She sang it so easily. - Really?
- That tickled my ears. - That was beautiful.
(Fascinating voice)
- Really? Was it beautiful? - Yes, it was perfect.
(In the meantime...)
The two of them...
look like a newlywed couple...
who are visiting Austria on their honeymoon.
(Newlyweds on a honeymoon)
With her?
- In Austria... - He's a photographer.
(You need to take pictures on a honeymoon.)
Right?
(Honeymoon, yodel, just married, love is the best)
They look like a newlywed couple.
The husband seems rich.
- He looks rich? - He looks rich.
I'm a rich man.
(Love? I'll buy it.)
Are you going to learn how to yodel?
(They focus on the class again.)
- Yes. - I see.
You're all too talkative.
(We can't waste a second.)
- You're more talkative than us. - Focus.
(To be honest...)
- Oh, I didn't know that. - Jae Suk is right.
(One of the teachers who talk the most)
- She's our guest, but... - She keeps complaining.
(Moving on)
- Jae Suk. - Yes?
(Repeat after me.)
Oh, my. I sang with Jae Suk. I'm so happy.
- Really? - Of course.
(Favoring Jae Suk and not hiding it)
I enjoyed singing with you as well.
(The amicable teacher-student relation)
- I love you. - Likewise.
I don't think he did so well.
(Taken aback)
I see. Okay. Let's move on.
- "I see." - Let's sing.
(She responded half-heartedly.)
I see. Okay. Let's move on.
"I see."
(Kwang Soo got upset.)
- She won't listen to you. - Gosh, I'm so upset.
- I'm so jealous! - Calm down.
- She doesn't care. - Your words don't mean anything.
(The non-celebrity teachers always favor Jae Suk.)
But how could she...
- Just don't say anything. - I'm so frustrated.
(The 36-year-old Kwang Soo wants attention like a little boy.)
This song has every element of yodeling.
(She moves on.)
And what we're going to do at the end is...
to imitate animals you like.
- Animals? - Yes, animals.
(My favorite animal?)
- Any kind? - Any animal you like.
(Se Chan chooses...)
- I'll imitate an elk. - I'll do a pigeon.
(Haha likes pigeons.)
Show me. Ready, go.
(Fluttering)
That's great.
Imitate an elk for me.
(Imitating an elk)
(He's the first person to imitate an elk on a TV show.)
- An elk actually makes that sound. - It's true.
(It sounds very similar to an elk.)
- Right. - Really?
- But can the elk smile? - Yes?
(He's smiling this time.)
That's great.
- That's how an elk actually sounds. - Okay. Which animal?
(Admitting)
- I'll be an elephant. - Okay. Ready, go.
(An elephant is here!)
(Did Kwang Soo have that kind of specialty?)
- Good job. - Is this...
Is this a talent show or what?
- He's trying to impress Ms. Lee. - That's not true.
(He gets the teacher's attention by imitating an elephant.)
He's showing off.
- We're all so enthusiastic. - Which animal?
- A dolphin. - A dolphin? Ready, go.
(She's making a high-pitched scream.)
- Did you imitate Jeon Do Yeon? - That was good.
(It's somewhere between Do Yeon and a dolphin.)
I like that.
- "I can shoot you." - She's a pretty dolphin.
(After the talent show of animal impressions,)
Let us divide into teams now, Ms. Lee.
(they split into teams.)
- Will you? - Yes.
(Lee Eun Kyung and Kang Dong Hye)
Ms. Kang, please help them.
(The two teams are practicing separately.)
(They learned to sing the easy part very easily.)
- Where water flows - Where water flows
(He's making nasal sound while singing.)
(Team Jong Kook is practicing hard as well.)
(Extremely enthusiastic)
- Hey, be quiet. - What?
We're practicing here.
(Selfish)
- We're practicing too. - We're practicing here.
(Arguing)
- We're practicing too. - Do not interfere us.
Which family restaurant do you guys work at?
(Their clothes look like a family restaurant's staff uniform.)
We don't work at a restaurant.
We're preparing for the contest.
(They couldn't refute.)
- He has a point. - Outback Steakhouse.
We'll start practicing. So please keep it down.
(Taking the lead)
We need to practice too.
(It feels like they've already lost.)
- Then... - 1, 2, 3, 4.
Together.
(Team Jae Suk started practicing again excitedly.)
(After the relatively easy part...)
Let's sing the next part together.
(He sticks his tongue out while lip-syncing.)
(They've reached the first difficult part.)
(And the song continues.)
- This is really difficult. - Yes, indeed.
In 3, 4.
(They're practicing the difficult part intensively.)
(My gosh. What are they doing?)
- Do something funny instead. - Okay.
(It's too difficult.)
- How about this? - Yes, I'll do that.
Okay. We're done, right?
(While Team Jae Suk met with difficulty,)
- Next... - What's the melody in this part?
(Team Jong Kook is practicing the next part.)
Please let us listen to the melody.
(The melody sounds familiar.)
Just make sure to make plosive sounds.
It sounds like a techno song. I like it.
- 1, 2. Don't you like it? - Indeed.
(They suddenly started doing techno music dance.)
(Shy)
(The last few bars are their favorite part.)
Put emphasis on the last bar.
(I don't like the sound of them singing.)
We should practice that part too.
- Okay. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(They don't want to lose.)
(They're walking toward the other team.)
Stop. What are you doing?
(They're trying to strike sparks off each other.)
You shouldn't cross the line.
Ms. Lee, please let us do the same thing.
(They don't want to lose either.)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - Let's go.
(Counterattack)
(The elk is running forward.)
(They look like they're playing a children's game.)
(Jae Suk kicked Kwang Soo's hips.)
(Infuriated)
- All right. Good job, everyone. - That was good.
(They're practicing again after the war of nerves.)
(Looking serious)
- This is really difficult. - Shall we try singing together?
(It's not easy to learn the song in a short period of time.)
- Let's sing together. - It's so difficult.
(So Min and Se Chan are practicing the hardest part.)
(They just need to nail that part.)
That sounds so creepy.
(They're confident in singing the last part.)
- Okay. - Great.
- My, that was good. - I can sing it now.
(Which team will win the yodeling match?)
The competition will begin shortly.
Just as I said earlier,
(The winner will be decided by Cameraman Kang Chan Hee.)
Director Kang will decide the winning team.
It's Immortal Chan Hee.
(Be selected by the legend.)
- Immortal Chan Hee? - Immortal Chan Hee?
- That sounds nice. - Right?
("Immortal Chan Hee")
- Immortal Chan Hee. - Immortal Chan Hee.
(Which team will be chosen by "Immortal Chan Hee"?)
Regardless of the result, your teachers will pick the best student.
(And the two teachers will pick the top student.)
- You go first. - It's okay. Don't worry.
(Team Jong Kook will sing first.)
Oh, my. My adorable team.
(He gets nervous now that he has to sing.)
- You can do it. - Should I lift it up like this?
(They practiced as hard as they could in a short time.)
Please move a half step back.
- Will you play it for them? - We practiced with it.
(Could they be able to shine on stage?)
I'll do that.
The first performance will begin shortly.
(The long-awaited first performance)
(Flaring his nostrils)
(He doesn't look delighted.)
I sing a joyful song
(They finished the first verse smoothly under So Min's leadership.)
(Terrible wave dance)
(Why is he doing the wave dance?)
Why is he dancing like this?
(Se Chan sang Kwang Soo's part by mistake.)
It's not your part.
(He forgot his mistake and concentrated again.)
(They have reached the most difficult part.)
- I feel dizzy. - Good job.
(It's hard to catch your breath or to control your tongue.)
This is the difficult part.
(Could they pull off this part?)
(It's a total mess.)
(They lost motivation.)
(They're singing the wrong lyrics.)
This is a total mess.
(Is this a newly developed yodeling technique?)
(What's that?)
(When it's too difficult to sing, he imitates an elk instead.)
(It's a disaster.)
(Finally, they're singing the part they're confident in.)
(They recovered their confidence while dancing a techno dance.)
That's not yodeling.
(The ones that are watching them feel embarrassed.)
That's embarrassing.
(In the end,)
(Alps Girl has turned into a techno amazon.)
(A chaotic harmony)
What's this mess?
(They end with animal sounds.)
This is ridiculous.
We will show you what real yodel is.
(I'll just smile.)
Let me show you. Just move over.
(Boasting)
We will show you what real yodel is.
(Immortal Chan Hee is taken aback.)
Gosh, this is...
Do you think this is a joke?
(Admonishing)
I get that we didn't have enough time, but you can't do this.
(Team Jae Suk got confident watching their performance.)
It's harder than you think. You should try.
- I've never heard the MR. - Why did you dance techno here?
- I've never heard the MR. - Don't belittle our performance.
(Techno Amazon of the Alps)
- I didn't know when to start. - Me neither. I didn't do it right.
(It was a performance below satisfaction.)
Immortal Chan Hee, please enjoy our performance.
(They mention Chan Hee out of the blue.)
This is "Immortal Songs" with Kang Chan Hee.
(Director Kang Chan Hee, a shy guy)
We should say hello first.
(We'll greet before we begin.)
Please push the key.
(Bowing 90 degrees)
Good.
Chan Hee.
(They bowed...)
Kang Chan Hee!
(to flatter him.)
(Dumbfounded)
Why are they flattering him like that?
They are pulling off some tricks.
Why would they say Kang Chan Hee?
- You can't do this. - Why not?
(We can do whatever we want!)
Can we say hello in a yodeling way?
(No flatteries)
Bow.
(They've been saying hello for 5 minutes.)
Kang Chan Hee
(He sneaks in flatteries.)
Please live a long and healthy life
(I just want to hear yodeling now.)
Searching for a mountain valley
Where water flows
(He's too into the song.)
Gosh, it's a mess.
(They're good at singing, but their facial expressions are bad.)
I walk in the forest
My gosh.
It always makes me so happy
I sing a joyful song
(The middle-aged man with a nasal voice steps up.)
(This is exciting.)
(This is the difficult part.)
They can't pull this off.
(They are reaching the most difficult part.)
(Se Chan had a meltdown singing this part.)
This is a mess.
We will show you what real yodel is.
(They give up too soon.)
(Let's just move on like this.)
(This isn't right.)
(It's a mess.)
I can't believe this.
(This is the part they are most confident at.)
(It's time for the finale.)
Kang Chan Hee! Kang Chan Hee!
(A serenade for Kang Chan Hee)
Kang Chan Hee
That was amazing.
The best student of the winning team will get an extra ticket.
(The best student of the winning team will get an extra ticket.)
- Okay. - The worst student will return one.
(The worst student from the losing team will lose a ticket.)
All right.
Director Kang Chan Hee.
(It's time to make a choice.)
Please pick the first winning team.
(Only based on...)
Please just consider our singing abilities.
- Based on our singing abilities. - Please make a fair decision.
- With no flattery. - Sure.
He will zoom in. Be ready.
(He will pick the winning team with the camera.)
This is the old way.
(Immortal Chan Hee)
He will zoom in.
Are they the winners?
(The team caught in the camera wins.)
- Which one? - We used the MR.
Please live a long and healthy life
Which team?
(Team Jae Suk wins.)
(But we did better.)
- I think... - Kang Chan Hee
- A long and healthy life - Kang Chan Hee
(Flattering)
You can't score us based on flattery.
(Not convinced)
- Kang Chan Hee - He fell for their flattery.
(I didn't think you were that type of person.)
I didn't know you liked stuff like that.
(Feeling betrayed)
- We had no idea. - You just like to be flattered.
(Had I known...)
If I knew, I would've prepared some money.
(Feels awkward)
- Bring some money. - He's right.
He likes flattery.
(The cameraman likes to hear flatteries.)
It wasn't because of flattery.
- That's not it. - Tell us why you picked them.
(We just did better.)
Suk Jin might know this, but back then,
(Why did he choose Team Jae Suk?)
we used to have a lot of yodel show when we were young.
(He used to have a lot of yodel show when young.)
- Like children's shows. - That's true.
(The biggest charm of yodeling was its joyfulness.)
- And it was always fun. - I agree.
Both teams weren't good enough to be examined,
but Team Jae Suk made it sound more similar...
(Team Jae Suk's yodeling reminded him more of the past.)
to real yodeling songs.
Immortal Chan Hee!
Thank you
We should've done things like that.
(Utterly disappointed)
We should've made deep bows and everything.
(We're good at flatteries too.)
I should've tried something like camera dance.
(The king of flatteries)
- I should've done something. - I know.
(I didn't pick them because of the flattery.)
Okay.
Now the teachers will have a discussion...
(The best student picked from the winning team...)
and pick the top student who gets to choose a lottery number.
(by the teachers get to choose a lottery number.)
Meanwhile, the losing team will pick the best student,
(While the teachers are choosing the best student...)
(The losing team gets to pick the best student.)
and the winning team will pick the worst student.
(The winning team gets to pick the worst student.)
Then we should...
(Who will be chosen?)
Is it Se Chan or So Min?
- So Min was a little over the line. - I agree.
(They are discussing seriously.)
Let's pick someone else.
We should mention Suk Jin's name first.
They seem very serious.
(Cultural shock)
They are serious.
All right. Should we announce the best student first?
(They made their choices.)
- We were unanimous on this. - It was very close though.
(Who did they pick as the best student?)
- We picked the one who sang well. - We picked it seriously.
1, 2, and 3.
- Ji Suk Jin... - Okay. Thank you.
- is out. - is out.
- You're out. - He's out?
(It's someone else other than Ji Suk Jin.)
You're out.
- Is he out? - This is fun.
I hated it that he sang well.
- You were so good that I hated it. - That was close.
(I was happy for a second.)
- Is he out? - He made it so close.
- By only 1 vote. - By only 1 vote.
(Who is chosen as the best student to get one more ticket?)
- This one is real. - We will announce the real one.
1, 2, and 3.
- Haha! - Haha! Congratulations.
Really?
(Congratulations!)
I can't believe this.
- Well done. - What's the reason?
(Thank you.)
- Did he sing well? - He didn't show off.
(Why was he chosen as the best student?)
(He didn't cross the line or showed off excessively.)
He didn't overstep the line.
He didn't show off.
I'm disappointed.
We agonized between two members.
(It's time to choose the worst student.)
- 1, 2, and 3. - 1, 2, and 3.
(The worst student of the yodel class is Jeon So Min.)
- Jeon So Min, it's you. - Jeon So Min, it's you.
(Is it really me?)
- Me? Really? - My gosh.
Yes. We hated the techno dance.
(It's because of the ugly techno dance.)
- I hated the dance. - Why?
It's you
The thing is...
(The combination of yodel and techno was a failure.)
Right. I hate it so much.
- Me? - It didn't sound like yodel.
I agree.
What do you know about yodel?
Why are you being so serious?
(Gypsy loses temper.)
- You even bit your lips. - I know about yodel.
I learned it from these two teachers.
- I did learn it. - It's Yudel for you.
- Yudel. - Yudel? That makes sense.
(He acquired a new character called Yudel.)
So Min, you should give one ticket to Haha then.
(One of So Min's tickets goes to Haha.)
And the top student selected by the teachers...
(And the top student selected by the teachers...)
- can pick one lottery number. - This is the most important one.
(can pick one lottery number.)
You can pick one student regardless of the results.
(Who will be selected as the top student by the teachers?)
Here I go.
Who will it be?
- What? - So Min?
(The teachers picked...)
It's Jeon So Min!
(Jeon So Min, the techno Amazon.)
Let me tell you the reason.
(They valued her passion and creativity highly.)
- So Min was good though. - She was very passionate.
- And I appreciate her creativity. - Thank you.
(Her stubbornness toward techno finally bore fruit.)
It was really cool.
- Congratulations. - You're at an advantage now.
Right.
(She can now pick a lottery number.)
So Min, you can pick a number now.
You better not share it with other members.
Pick your favorite number.
(She has the privilege of picking 1 of the 6 numbers.)
So Min, pick seven.
- A number? What were the numbers? - From 1 to 10.
(The number So Min picks is...)
So Min has picked a number.
(The next class will be divided into two teams.)
You will be divided into two teams for the next class.
And here are the key words.
What are they?
You can pick either Brazil or Hawaii.
(They either have to pick between Brazil or Hawaii.)
- Samba! - Brazil.
(They each pick a keyword they like.)
(Brazil: Jae Suk, Haha, So Min, Se Chan)
(Hawaii: Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo)
(Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo picked Hawaii.)
(There's a beautiful beach...)
(next to the blue Pacific Ocean.)
- Where is it? - Over here.
(What is the class for the members who picked Hawaii?)
Okay.
(They are surprised as soon as they come in.)
- Gosh. - What?
(Hula dance teacher, Che Che)
Hello. Aloha.
- As soon as I walked in, - Hello.
- I smelled the tanning lotion. - I bet you went to a tanning shop.
(The room is filled with tanning shop aroma.)
It's the smell of a tanning shop.
(Tanning)
Did you go there today?
- Did you get tanned today? - Ma'am.
(She tanned for today's lesson.)
Yes.
- Hello. - I can smell that.
(She reminds them of Hawaii.)
It's the smell of tanning oil.
(He is shocked to see her background.)
How many awards have you won?
It's from 2008 to 2019.
(She won many awards in many competitions.)
From 2008 to 2019?
- You have an impressive record. - Thank you.
She's the best hula and Tahitian dance teacher in Korea, Che Che.
(She's the best hula and Tahitian dance teacher in Korea, Che Che.)
We're meeting a legend.
(They'll compete with Team Brazil after learning the hula dance.)
- She's Che Che. - Thank you.
I'm really curious. Can we really do this?
(Confident)
Of course you can.
Because I'm teaching you.
To be honest, all of us except one are horrible dancers.
- Who's the one? - Because...
You can do this. I will try my best to teach you.
(She doesn't lose her smile even when facing these people.)
We need to learn the basics.
Let me tell you about hula first.
(It's a 1-minute introduction to the hula dance by Che Che.)
Hula dance was considered a religious and linguistic...
(Hula dance was considered a religious and linguistic...)
performance dedicated to ancestors.
(performance dedicated to ancestors.)
Ancient Hawaiians had no letters.
- Instead of using letters... - They used body language.
Right. They communicated with gestures and songs.
(Hula dance was utilized as a form of expression instead of letters.)
About 250 years ago, they started to adopt the Western culture.
(Hula ʻauana is a modern hula dance after the 19th century...)
You know about a ukulele, right?
- We know it. - I love ukuleles.
(often accompanied by western music such as ukelele and guitars.)
They developed the hula dance with the ukulele, guitar, and piano.
(Today, they'll learn the modern hula dance.)
It's called Hula Auana. Today, you will...
Excuse me, but you're out of breath. Do you want some water?
- You're talking a lot. - You need to breathe.
(Her breaths didn't catch up with her passionate explanations.)
You can take your time.
(Have some water.)
I know you are a good speaker.
- She's speaking without resting. - I know.
(She recited the history of hula without taking a break.)
- I guess you do this a lot. - She's like a machine.
I wanted to tell you all this before I forget.
- Before you forget? - I see.
(It was a fast lecture to make sure she doesn't forget much.)
- Drink some water. - Please drink some water.
Okay. Thank you.
(She takes a sip of water that Kwang Soo gave her.)
She sounds very polite.
(Drinking)
- Well... - Gosh.
Hang on.
She's a lot of work.
She just spilled a lot of water here.
(Just now...)
She just had a sip of water,
(She spilled half of the water she just drank.)
- I know. - but she spilled almost half of it.
(Delivers a towel)
My gosh.
(Shy)
- Wipe it. - I was nervous.
I like the look on her face.
Are you always like that? Is it something you need for hula?
(Does hula dance always require you to smile?)
You can't deliver your message only with hand motions.
(Hula, as hand gestures,)
(was not enough to express everything.)
For example, do you know the word, "aloha"?
(For example, "Aloha", which means love and greet,)
This is the hand motion for "aloha".
- It's like covering your heart. - It's love.
(can be expressed by covering your chest with both hands.)
And you can't do it with a straight face.
(But a face without expression can deliver a wrong message.)
- You look scary. - It's scary, isn't it?
So you should do it with a big smile on your face.
(That's why hula uses more facial expressions...)
(to ensure the message you intended gets delivered.)
Think of your family or lover.
(Thanks to the hula class, they greet each other with a smile.)
Good. That's nice.
By the way,
why does he look so scary?
(Aloha)
- What's his problem? - He seems nervous.
- I think he looks nice. - What's with him?
(Some are impossible to express with their faces.)
- Will you dance looking like that? - You look scary.
It's terrifying.
(Before they start learning...)
The guys should wear a little makeup...
(The male students...)
for hula dance.
(will get makeups appropriate for the hula dance.)
- Really? - Hula makeup?
She will put it on you.
(Hula makeup is as important as the body movement.)
You will be performing hula later.
So I'll make you look more like Hawaiians.
(The makeup will look as Hawaiian as possible.)
- To have a strong impression. - Okay.
A strong impression.
(Excited)
I've never done this before,
- so I'm a little worried. - Should they look scary?
Hang on. I just heard you mumble.
I heard you say you're worried because this is your first time.
(Nervous)
Did I mishear it?
Because most students in my class are women...
- That's okay. - Don't worry. Relax.
(Nervous)
- It's okay. - Okay.
(She begins carefully from the eyes.)
- This is the most nerve-racking. - Oh, my.
My, it seems so difficult.
You poked my eye about 30 times in such a short moment.
(She hit his eye 30 times with micro bristles.)
I guess it really is her first time.
- I thought she has a lot of... - The eyeliner?
(It was true.)
experience as she talks so well.
- She hasn't put makeup on others. - She poked my eye 30 times.
(Che Che doesn't lie.)
Suk Jin, please sit here. I'll do it for you.
(Ji Hyo volunteers to help with putting on makeup.)
- Me? - Yes.
I think you're applying eyeliner too thick.
(Nervous)
This is how you should apply eyeliner.
- It's not bad. - I'm done.
(It's a Hawaiian warrior.)
- Hey. - Honestly, it's not bad at all.
- Suk Jin. - Am I a beggar?
- It doesn't look bad. - Darn.
(Next is Jong Kook who already looks strong.)
Jong Kook doesn't need to look any tougher than he does now.
Aren't his eyes too small to put makeup on them?
That's not true.
(She has to look for his eyes to color.)
- Really? It must be hard. - Yes.
Your eyes look really wide. It's no joke.
(The hula makeup is done.)
We thought you guys only have a vague idea of hula dance,
(Before the class,)
so before the class, she'll give a demonstration.
(Che Che will show hula.)
- She'll give a demonstration. - Yes.
- Okay. It's a beautiful dance. - I saw the dance only once...
(It's not easy to watch official hula dance.)
when I went on a trip to Hawaii.
Right? We rarely get to see it.
(What song will Team Hawaii dance to when competing against Team Brazil?)
- I even like the song too. - It's a hula song.
("Ulupalakua")
(A song about Mount Ulupalakua where a cowboy's house is)
(Her smile and gentle hand movements bring Hawaii into the studio.)
This makes me feel so relaxed.
(Relaxed)
(Smooth movements as if water flows...)
(and gentle steps that don't stop are what makes hula special.)
I've seen this dance move before.
(Hula, hula)
- Look at her smile. It's pretty. - She's amazing.
She won't stop smiling.
We're going to have to smile the whole time.
(Facial expressions to express love and gratitude...)
(are also what makes hula charming.)
(They're trying to dance like her.)
Oh, I have to lift my leg up here.
(This is "Ulupalakua", the song they'll dance to.)
- I've only seen it in a movie. - Exactly.
(Exclaiming)
If we pull this off...
(In 1 hour, they have to perform to this song.)
- But it seems so difficult. - I know.
- You use your whole body to dance. - Right.
(Now they learn hula.)
I think all of you are good at using your bodies and will learn fast.
(They'll figure out the dance movements well on their own.)
However, describing what lyrics say with your face is important too.
(Learning the facial expression for the dance matters more.)
- So we're going to practice... - We have to smile.
- doing that first. - I'm sorry,
but is he doing it right?
(Is this right?)
Gosh, what a sight.
- Gosh, seriously. - What a sight.
- I think... - That's a weird smile.
(I hate to see it.)
You look unusually ugly today.
- If you could... - Your eyes are not visible.
(Hula makeup makes Kwang Soo's beauty stand out.)
- His eyes are almost closed. - He looks so ugly.
That's funny.
That's how she looked earlier.
(Feeling proud)
I think that's a good start.
(The teacher is generous with compliments.)
I'll tell you a few different emotions...
(Hula Dance, Step 1)
so you can practice to make facial expressions to describe them.
(The facial expression is as important as the movements.)
- Understood. - Okay.
(They will begin practicing facial expressions to describe the dance.)
First, describe love, joy, and gratitude...
(Hula often describes love, joy, and gratitude.)
without using your body.
Try to describe it only with your facial expression.
- Love. - Right. Love.
(Jong Kook will express love first.)
Joy.
Gratitude.
You can't use your body.
You shouldn't use your body.
She's pickier than expected.
(She's strict when teaching.)
It's to focus on your face.
(It's to focus on your face.)
- Shall I give it a try? Love. - Yes.
(Suk Jin expresses love.)
Oh, that's how much you love your wife.
(Making fun of Suk Jin)
- I express my love just this much. - No wonder...
- you never get a call from her. - Please try to express more.
(Your wife is watching.)
Subtle expressions of love help your relationship last longer.
- Express joy again. - Joy?
(Trying "joy" again)
Imagine your wife is away to visit her parents.
(Exhilarated)
I knew it. You look so happy.
(Satisfied)
- That's how joy should look. - I did it unintentionally.
(He was able to express true joy with help.)
It's hard to describe emotions.
Ji Hyo, it's your turn. Love.
(How does Ji Hyo express love?)
(Twitching)
What's that?
- What's that? - That's love?
- That's not love. - Why are you giving a signal?
- To whom... - It's because it's all dried up.
(The look of love)
(The look of asking for love)
But I think she did a good job in making eye contact.
(Ji Hyo's love)
- I see. - I got a compliment.
- Kwang Soo. - Last but not least.
(Lastly, it's Kwang Soo.)
Love.
- Joy. - Joy.
Gratitude.
(He opened his eyes and mouth wide to show his gratitude.)
- He looks so ugly. - What's that?
(Hunched)
- What's with the hunched shoulders? - To show my gratitude.
- To show your gratitude? - Look at the hunched shoulders.
(His neck is hunched like ripened rice.)
Hey, you can't use your body.
- I didn't use my body. - I mean...
- I didn't use my body. - What has gotten into him?
(As he's told not to use his body,)
You look like you're buttering up someone.
(he spins only his neck.)
- What's with him? - I didn't use my body.
- I didn't change the pose. - Love.
- Joy. Gratitude. - Here he goes again.
(He hunches his neck when he hears gratitude.)
You shouldn't watch this when it airs.
- Seriously. - Is there something in your eyes?
- I wanted to express gratitude. - I see.
- I'm overwhelmingly touched. - Some people do that.
Exactly. I'm overwhelmingly touched.
(Bowing)
You're overwhelmingly grateful?
(Kwang Soo described gratitude in a pitiful way.)
Could you show us how to describe love, joy, and gratitude?
(How would the teacher show love, joy, and gratitude?)
- Well... - Love.
Joy.
Gratitude.
- Wait. - What's the difference?
(What's the difference?)
Gratitude.
(She repeated showing the same facial expression.)
- Wait. - What's the difference?
Wait.
Can we describe love together just once?
- Just once, please. - She's taken aback.
(Kwang Soo asks her to do it together.)
- Ready, go. - Ready, go. Love.
(Love)
(His eyelids are shaking as his heart is fluttering.)
- Joy. - Joy.
Gratitude.
(The weird look that has never been taught)
- Am I doing it right? - Kwang Soo is...
on a roll today.
- Am I doing it right? - Gosh, that's hilarious.
(Lee Kwang Soo, the maverick of hula dance)
(Kwang Soo's not discouraged even in front of the teacher.)
That's so funny.
We have to describe the emotions.
Sadness? Okay. Sadness.
(This time)
I'm excited to see Kwang Soo's facial expression.
(He tries describing "sadness" with everyone's expectation.)
It's Kwang Soo's turn.
I'm sad. I don't have to cry, right?
(His philosophy on facial expression)
- Correct. - Don't make any sound.
(How will Kwang Soo describe sadness?)
What has gotten into him?
(I am sad.)
(Stunned)
- What's with his face? - Joy.
(He changed his facial expression right away.)
Sadness. Sadness.
(He's describing sadness again.)
Joy.
You're happy and sad at the same time.
(He can describe any emotion like a vending machine.)
- My gosh. - Hey.
(The emotion is fading gradually.)
- Hey. - Sadness is hard to describe.
- You're a genius actor. - Hey.
(What do you mean?)
(They met a genius actor in a hula class.)
I bet no other actors can do it like he does.
My gosh. I'm impressed.
(He found his genius after 35 years.)
- The last one was the best. - I mean, he is...
- I tried to show a mixed feeling. - Your facial expressions...
have never been this funny.
- Really? Do I look funny? - That was impressive.
(Cheers to Kwang Soo's smile who's never felt better.)
- You look funny whatever you do. - Exactly.
- Is it because of my makeup? - He can describe a mixed emotion.
(Dumbfounded)
Your facial muscles are warmed up enough, right?
- Yes, I laughed so much. - Yes.
- That was hilarious. - Then let's begin...
(He used his muscles too much.)
- with basic steps. - Okay.
(It's time to learn the basic steps of hula.)
Basic steps.
Stand with your feet straight.
(Stand with your feet straight.)
For men, it's okay if your feet are turned slightly outward.
(For men, it's okay if your feet are turned slightly outward.)
You move to the right side first in every dance move.
(Move to the right first.)
To move to the right, rest your weight on the left side.
(To move to the right, rest your weight on the left side.)
Slide to the right side slowly, moving your weight to the right.
To the right. To the left.
To the right. To the left. Okay.
(Shift your weight to the sides,)
(and swing your waist.)
While shifting your weight to the sides,
move four steps to the right. Start with your right foot.
- Smile. - Okay. Smile.
(You should always look bright.)
- Smile. Try to look happy. - Okay.
(To the right.)
- Smile. - Okay. Smile.
(To the left.)
- Smile. Try to look happy. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo is getting ahead.)
Look at Kwang Soo's face.
- His face looks like Hahoe mask. - Exactly.
My, look at his eyes. He looks just like Hahoe mask.
(Hahoe mask dancing hula)
Open your eyes wide. Good.
(He's opening his eyes wide.)
- Okay. You're doing great. - Thank you.
(With shining eyes, they mastered the steps.)
- Next, we'll learn ha'a. - Ha'a?
(Swaying your hips movement)
This dance move...
is to sway your hips 360 degrees like when you hula hoop.
(Sway your hips in 360 degrees softly.)
Okay. 1, 2, 3, 4. 2, 2, 3, 4. 3, 2, 3, 4.
(To the count,)
(you should sway to the predetermined direction.)
Your hips should be pushed back and swayed to the left at first.
- 1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Busy dancing hula)
1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Swaying)
You're like a hula dancing machine.
(The hula machine)
He's like a machine. He's amazing.
(The hula machine was born with a flexible pelvis.)
- That's good. - I think he's a natural.
- It rarely happens. - Gosh, seriously.
(He never forgets the facial expression.)
(Grunting)
I can't look at his face.
(If you keep looking at it, it's a bit disgusting.)
- He's like a dancing machine. - This is driving me insane.
This is unbelievable.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, it's time to learn the next step.)
- Let's move on to the fifth step. - Okay.
- It's called ku'i. - Ku'i.
(Kick your foot as if you're playing jegi.)
Step with your right foot and kick with your left foot.
- Good. Step and kick. - Wait.
- Step and kick. - When you kick,
make sure to keep your upper body still and straight.
(Your upper body must not move when you kick.)
- 1, 2. - Just move the legs.
1, 2. Kick it like this.
Kwang Soo, your upper body is not moving at all.
Look at his upper body. It's not moving at all.
(Stable upper body)
(Busy lower body)
He's a hula dancing machine.
(The hula machine can do anything.)
His upper body is not moving at all.
You should get a license.
(He's smiling happily...)
- Take some private lessons. - He's discovered a new talent.
(as he discovered a new talent.)
(He's working fine.)
Exactly. You're talented.
This is so much fun.
- I mean it. - He's a natural.
Imagine a vast grassy plain.
(It's time to learn the hand movement.)
1, 2, 3. To the other side. 2, 2, 3, 4.
(The first move describes the vast plain.)
- Next, describe Mount Ulupalakua. - Yes.
- Imagine a tall mountain. - A mountain.
(This move describes the high mountain.)
You know the gesture people make. "Look at this view."
Right. And they strike this pose too.
(An elder checking out the view)
That's helpful.
- It's so easy to understand. - Good job.
You look around when you buy land.
(With Che Che's easy description, they make fast progress.)
As if your skin is tingly.
- To describe feeling cold? - It means it's cold.
(Describing cold in the alpine region)
It's cold after sunset. It's cold in the evening.
It's a fragrant flower. Move your arms down with your palms down.
(They completed smelling the fragrant flower...)
Lift them up and make flowers with your hands.
(and making flowers with their hands.)
We're going to leave in 10 minutes.
(10 minutes before the performance)
- Gosh. We're in trouble. - Oh, no.
Okay. At first...
(Let me see.)
I'm confused about the second move.
- The second move? - Move to the right and to the left.
(Ji Hyo asks questions until the last minute.)
- Ji Hyo is good at memorizing. - Oh, my.
(Exclaiming)
- She memorized the moves quickly. - They're so confusing.
(They're checking the moves they're confused about.)
What should I think while performing? That I'm beautiful?
(They practice for the last time.)
Che Che, should I think that I'm beautiful while dancing?
(Out of the blue)
"I am beautiful. I am attractive."
Suk Jin, just focus on memorizing the order.
(Feeling guilty)
- Facial expressions are important. - Don't think about anything else.
We can offset our mistakes with our facial expressions.
- "I am beautiful." - Try to enjoy it.
(Will Suk Jin's expression defeat Team Brazil?)
Let's go.
Their samba dance will be lousy too anyway.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk, Se Chan, So Min, and Haha chose Brazil.)
(The scorching sun and blue ocean!)
(Brazil, the country of passion and cheerful energy!)
(What kind of class could be waiting for them?)
- I'll go in and have a look. - Hey.
(The teachers are welcoming them with a big laugh.)
- It's been a long time. - The real deals are here.
(Expectant)
- Oh, my. - It's so good to see you again.
How have you been?
Have you been well?
- Hi, Ji Woo. It's been a while. - How have you been?
(Jae Suk and Haha say hi to Brazil teachers.)
- It's been a while. - Hello.
- It's good to see you. - It's good to see you.
- Hello. - It's Ji Woo.
(Instructor Park Ji Woo)
- It's been so long. - Ji Woo...
(Jae Suk and Haha met him on "Infinite Challenge" 13 years ago.)
Goodness.
We met him for the first time...
(They were teacher and student also at the time.)
during a Latin dance special on a variety show in 2007.
Yes, on "Infinite Challenge". I remember.
Haven't I aged a lot?
(It's been 13 years.)
- No, you're the same. - You look even better.
- Do I? - Yes.
We all say that when growing old.
(The secret of "You're the same" unfolds.)
- Among ourselves... - Not to embarrass each other.
- Among ourselves... - "You're looking good!"
- "You look even better." - "You haven't changed."
- Today, you'll learn the samba. - The samba.
(They're going to learn the samba today.)
Let me first introduce you...
- to your teachers today. - Of course.
(It's a pleasure to meet you.)
- It's good to see you. - Hello.
- They all look amazing. - Kim Ung Gyeom and Um Hye Ri.
(Kim Ung Gyeom and Um Hye Ri)
Um Hye Ri, I see.
This is Ryu Ji Won.
(Ryu Ji Won)
Hello.
- She's my wife. - Oh, really?
- I see. - How fascinating.
(Oh, my.)
I used to be her teacher.
(Shy)
That's how you got together.
(Romantic stories always intrigue the Love Frog.)
- It brought you together. - Love was in the air.
- First... - Go ahead.
- You'll be on your way to Brazil. - Yes, Brazil.
(They're going on a samba trip to Brazil with the best teachers.)
Before you dance the samba,
you should see how it's supposed to be.
(We've prepared the real samba.)
Yes, of course!
(We'd love it.)
- The two of you. - I'd love to see it.
The two over here...
are the Korean champions.
(The samba champions will show them the charms of samba.)
They'll show you what real samba is.
- Shall we? - Let's samba!
(They can't wait.)
This is going to be cool.
(Music starts.)
- To this kind of music? - No way.
Nice!
She looks like Kim Se Jeong.
How cool.
(Eyes open wide.)
(The samba energy leaves them gaping.)
My gosh.
Keep an eye on their expressions.
(Their expressions are dynamic and alive.)
This is so cool!
(Cheering)
(Stepping backward)
(However, his teeth want to step forward.)
(Amazing!)
Aren't they amazing?
(Beware of imitations.)
(This is samba.)
Samba!
(In love with samba)
- Nice. - Samba!
- I knew it. - Aren't they amazing?
- Latin dancing sure is cool. - Unbelievable.
(The energy still lingers.)
Did you see their lively expressions?
Their expressions were incredible.
That was so cool.
Their gazes were like...
(Glaring)
That's right.
(This is probably what he's mimicking.)
Their gazes were like...
It's as if they were going to eat you up.
I can hold that gaze too.
(On fire)
The samba you'll be learning today...
- is an easier version. - Of course.
What you saw earlier was for master dancers.
(The previous samba was for the professionals.)
(For us)
- He made it just for us. - Could we learn it?
You should be glad...
that you're with the skilled dancers of Running Man.
That's for me to decide.
(Flustered by hasty self-praise)
- Even the toughest choreography... - 1, 2.
(Showing off their petty steps)
Some can already do the simple steps.
(All four of them are confident in their dancing skills.)
So first, let the four of us show you...
(We'll show you what you'll be learning today.)
- what you'll be learning today. - Sure thing.
Finally, this is it.
(The two of you are...)
You're married, right?
- How beautiful. - Amazing, right?
- Yes. - You can be just like them.
- Se Chan and So Min... - Exactly.
(Shy)
They're married.
Cue, music.
(What will the members learn today?)
How cool.
Is this the samba?
Check out their lines.
- This is what we'll do? - This?
- It's too difficult. - Hold on.
(The energy of samba surprises them again.)
That's unbelievably cool.
Oh, no.
- How can we do this? - We can't possibly do this.
How on earth can we do this?
(This is what they're supposed to do?)
No way.
(The samba dance gains another fan.)
How sexy!
Seriously?
(Close distance)
(How can one do this?)
(It's all about the chemistry between the partners.)
- We can't do this. - There's no way.
We should get going.
(They can't dare try to copy it.)
- Bye, everyone. - Well done.
I still have it, don't I?
- You were gliding on the stage. - The feel of it...
(Thumbs up!)
- It was amazing. - You still have it.
- You're just the same. - You're not like others.
You were gliding just now.
This is what we also say...
- as we grow old together. - Which is what?
"You're still the same."
- Exactly. - "You've still got it."
(Though he's still the same, he's breathing heavily.)
The years were good to you.
"You haven't changed."
- How can we dance that though? - That was amazing.
It's too difficult.
Latin dancing...
(Don't worry.)
- is all about the partnership. - How can we do this though?
- This links couples together. - Yes, that happens.
- That's what happened to you. - Right.
While dancing...
(They met while dancing.)
- While dancing? - It's quite common.
- Which moment exactly... - They're sort of stuck, you see.
(Before we move on...)
You'll learn that as you dance the samba today.
(The one who experienced the spark)
- Couples... - No one can actually tell you.
(Love Frog is only interested in romance.)
Many couples end up together.
- Then... - I'm in big trouble.
- There's an issue though. - What is it?
(But they don't have enough women.)
- How can we partner up? - Beats me.
One of you guys...
needs to take on the woman's role.
We know who we're partnering up with.
(These two are fine.)
Exactly.
It'll be the two of you and those two over there.
(Only the two fathers remain.)
- His physique... - It's feminine.
- Right? - Hold on.
See? You're just as slender.
- Wait. - You have the same physique.
- I can't. - You can!
(I don't want to cross-dress.)
- You do it then. - No, you.
(While the two fathers tell each other to dress up as a woman...)
- You do it! - Anyone can tell...
- Ji Woo, you tell him. - No way.
- Are we partners? - We have no choice.
(Mr. Gums and Ms. Frog will dance together.)
I don't think I can do the moves of the female dancer.
(Se Chan's thrilled about not dressing up as a woman.)
- Lead me well. - Got it.
It's not about the moves themselves.
It's not about the moves themselves. Only the feel of them counts.
- The feel! - That's all that matters.
So to the music,
(The 3 members except for Jae Suk will be tested.)
show me how you each feel it yourselves.
- How we feel it? - Alone?
- Yes, alone. - But it'll be embarrassing.
Cue, music!
(The music plays,)
Feel it!
(but no one steps forward.)
I can't believe we'll dance the samba. Will you give it a go?
Feel it! Get ready.
(What are you three doing?)
- Go ahead. - 2, 3, 4.
(Swaying)
(The bold Jeon So Min)
(Slip!)
(Her boldness malfunctioned.)
No, please keep going.
(When boldness meets the samba)
- Bravo. - No, that's enough.
(She suddenly charges at the camera.)
Enough!
No, that's enough.
(Tension overload)
This is too much.
(I'm so excited!)
- She... - What on earth are you doing?
Stop it.
That's enough.
- Please, stop. - I can't do this.
(Dancing in techno-style in front of the camera)
Why bother Chan Hee like that?
I can't be partners with her.
What's wrong with you?
(She's as passionate as the Master of Samba.)
She always wants more.
That was the best.
(The instructor gives her thumbs up.)
I know what she's capable of now.
- Play the music for them again. - Haha.
(Haha goes second.)
Show us.
- He'll do well. - He's a good dancer.
(The arrogant Haha)
- How cool is that! - Conga!
(He captures a woman's heart.)
- Isn't he amazing? - Conga!
(He even throws off his cap.)
(Full of arrogance)
- He's really good. - He should be the female dancer.
(Requesting)
Look how good he is.
(He's taking the moves from his Z-KIRI days.)
Haha, wait.
- Hold on. - He's quite good.
- You... - How are you this good?
You're trying not to be the female dancer, right?
(His desperate dance to reject the role of a female dancer.)
It's why you're dancing with so much force.
- That's why. - Once more. Cue, music.
(Se Chan goes third.)
- Show us. - He's unbuttoning his shirt.
(Mr. Gums, Yang Se Chan)
He's unbuttoning his shirt.
(Appalled)
Give me the same song, please.
No, the one before that.
(Not this song!)
- The earlier one? - Yes, I like it more.
Se Chan knows the feeling.
Just a second. Wait.
My gosh.
(Where do you think you're going?)
I want to pat off my sweat!
Wait.
My gosh.
(He won't let his mentor pat off his sweat.)
I want to pat off my sweat!
Nicely done. Good job.
(The samba battle begins.)
(He flashes his pale complexion and challenges his instructor.)
Nice!
(Yang Se Chan, tofu vendor)
Go on.
The mouth. Look at our mouths!
(Please buy a block of tofu.)
- Nice! - Good one.
(Here's some soft tofu.)
(The body language of two geniuses)
He knows how to enjoy the music.
Nice. That was amazing.
- You were great. What was this? - Se Chan,
why were you cursing though?
No, I wasn't cursing.
My emotions were bursting out. It means I was having fun.
- You were swearing. - He was having fun!
That was hilarious.
Did you see his teeth?
(This is him having fun.)
- Se Chan's a good dancer too. - That was exhausting.
(I've put everything just now.)
Our true colors come out.
I'm curious as to who'll play the female dancer.
(Meanwhile, the whole nation knows of Jae Suk's love for samba.)
(Who will play the role of a female dancer?)
He wants to play the role of the male dancer.
The picture has been painted in my head.
We'll do as you say.
- I wonder who. - Got it.
It'll be Haha.
- What? - You were chosen.
What? Me?
- Good. - I think you'll be great.
(Haha the good dancer will play the role of a female dancer.)
- Also, Haha's a great dancer. - He is.
He's a talented one.
That much I can probably do.
(The class begins in pairs.)
We'll start with two feet together.
Step out with your left foot and come back.
(Ha Sook is ready.)
Step back with your right foot and come back.
Let me show you.
1, 2, 3.
(They begin with the basic steps.)
- 1, 2, 3. - Okay.
Next, bend your knees as you do so.
And bend.
We get it.
(It's all about the tempo control.)
Once more.
Se Chan, ready, go!
Your lips. Your beak.
He said I have a beak.
(When he criticized his beak,)
Beak? Sir.
(the two brothers with protruded mouths lose temper.)
- Sir, I have lips. - Not beak,
- My lips. - I meant lips. Get ready, start.
Look at his lips.
(Just let it be.)
- You should relax your lips a bit. - Does that look more natural?
(His mouth is now free.)
That's right. Okay.
Ready. Start.
(Mr. Gums is warming up.)
- Look at his lips. - Let's start with your left foot.
(It's time for the next move.)
Ready, start.
1, 2, 3, 4.
- 2, 2, 3, 4. - They look like Namolla Family.
They look like Namolla Family.
(They call upon Namolla Family in the middle of their lesson.)
What?
Our teacher is really funny.
- We're making progress. - We are.
He's just going through it because he doesn't have time.
(Is the Samba trickster following the yodel trickster?)
- Do you think we got it right? - He's just going through it.
Don't you know how scary he is?
- This usually takes about a week. - Right.
(Today is a 1-hour crash course.)
- Okay. The second one. - Okay.
(It's time for the couple dance.)
Partner up, and follow what we do.
Come here.
(Obedient)
He said to partner up, and I came here.
(Sync complete)
The guys will cross their arms.
Don't try to do well.
(Clenching his teeth)
- Is it annoying? - It's annoying.
Bring your outstretched hand and cross it above your head.
(Ryu Ji Won shows them the movements for girls.)
It's hard.
(Trying hard)
- You look pretty. - Put your arms behind your ears.
- You look pretty. - I can't do it.
- Stick out your bottom a bit. - It's not easy.
(A very elegant pose for a middle-aged man.)
- Stick your bottom out towards me. - The line isn't pretty.
You should look in the mirror.
(Dying)
Lower your body a bit.
Straighten one leg. Straighten this leg.
(Groaning)
- Straighten one leg. - How?
Straighten this leg. Right.
I want to knock him over with a flying side kick.
(His cuteness calls for a kick.)
Like this.
He's wearing a skirt.
(Sexy and seductive)
Okay.
- I can't look at him from behind. - He's good.
(Dream's dad is sexy and seductive Ha Sook for today.)
You look forward from here. Hold onto your partner.
- Okay. - This?
(The man must hold the woman by her waist.)
The guys will bend down, and the girls will move their left foot.
- Left foot. - What came after this, So Min?
What is this?
- This is a handle. - It's a handle?
It's so easy to hold onto.
- I can hold onto this part. - Hold tight.
(It's a handle made for an easy grab.)
- Right. - These are handles.
- I won't fall. - Handles.
You'll hold onto her waist.
Se Chan, do you remember? You have to twist her waist.
Don't twist me too much.
(I need to touch her.)
- Go easy on me. - Okay.
- If she's going left, - I'm embarrassed.
but you twist to the right, you'll be in trouble.
(Se Chan's hands can't get close.)
Okay. We'll start.
Ready, go.
(So Min doesn't mind him,)
(but he's dying of embarrassment.)
Again.
Gosh, So Min.
Can you give me some sticks?
(Out of embarrassment)
- Hey. - We'll start.
(It's the hardest for Se Chan.)
- Ready. - I'm embarrassed.
Get ready. Hold onto her waist!
I'll move. Just follow me.
- I'll do that. - Ready, go.
- Slow, slow. Quick, quick, quick. - That's right.
(Even at So Min's bold lead,)
(Se Chan exposes his gums widely as he's embarrassed.)
Start.
(The part that was particularly hard for Se Chan ends.)
Okay.
We'll start from the top until here.
I can't hold onto her waist.
Hold it. Hold onto it.
- Hold onto my waist. - I can't.
- Just hold it like this. - Oh, my.
(His gums get exposed frequently today.)
- Why can't you just hold it? - Try it.
Just hold it like this.
- Why can't you just hold it? - Go away.
(Ha Sook is suffering from the same problem.)
- Look over here. - Okay.
So Min, try it.
(Ji Woo will take Se Chan's place.)
Start with this leg first.
- It's slippery. - Ready, start.
Slow, slow. Quick, quick, quick, quick.
(What?)
Hey.
Is this dancing?
(Is this dancing?)
- She's going to break. - What was that?
(Her body doesn't listen to her mind.)
We aren't tap dancing.
(Her face expressed the passion of samba first.)
The rhythm was too fast.
Okay, then. From here,
(This is the part where the two bodies get close together.)
the girls will return to the guys.
(Turn and go into their arms.)
- Turn and hold. - Turn and hold.
(Sighing)
(It's one hardship after another.)
(He punishes Ha Sook for turning into his arms.)
He got slapped in the face.
(Coy)
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Haha. This is...
- for Se Chan and So Min. - Right.
If this were a movie, you and I are just extras here.
(They are the main casts.)
(They're just extras.)
- Right, we're extras. - Right.
- Hold my neck. - Hold her neck with your left hand.
(So Min is still leading.)
You will spin her like this.
Hold on.
(Shaking)
- Gosh. - Spin me around.
(He's shy but his legs are also very weak.)
- Spin me around. - Spin her.
- Spin me. - That's right.
(Ha Sook and Jae Suk are really trying hard too.)
- Like this. - Raise your heels.
At this point, the girls' right hands...
- will go on the guys' shoulders. - This isn't right.
What's most important here is,
(Gasping)
you have to change your hands, and the left hand will go on their neck.
Something keeps touching me.
(Extremely unpleasant)
Let's not do this.
(Goodness)
What are we doing?
I can't say anything. Gosh.
(It's unpleasant, but they can't talk about it.)
- This is so unpleasant. - Gosh, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
(Dancing the samba with friends could be unpleasant.)
- This is so unpleasant. - Face each other.
(For the next pose, they need to face each other.)
- Face each other. - Face each other.
- You have to face each other. - Okay.
Okay. Pay attention. The next movement is a body roll.
(They do a wave as they face each other.)
You will do it together.
(Gosh)
Ready, go.
(Gasping)
I've known him for a long time,
(It's a shocking closeup for the first time in 15 years.)
- but I've never been this close... - Me too.
- for this long before. - It's my first time too.
- Hurry up. We need to do it. - I've never been so close to him.
We have to do it. Hurry up.
- She's too aggressive. - We have to do it.
- Face each other. - It's out of control over here.
Se Chan became timid.
- Hey. - She's so aggressive,
(So Min is very proactive.)
so I'm so embarrassed.
My gosh, I seriously...
Your left side will show soon.
(Unlike its owner, Se Chan's left side is aggressive.)
- This is fitting for samba, right? - Hey.
(Kind)
- Let's button up a bit. - No, it needs to be open.
- Gosh, it's hot. - Let's do it again.
- You separated here. - Okay.
Three and shake it. Girls turn around.
(The samba class gets heated up.)
- 1. 1. 1. - Quick, quick, quick.
(Doing his best)
Quick, quick, start.
(What kind of samba performance will they put on?)
- Body roll. - Separate.
(After 1 hour) (Hula versus Samba)
(The practice is over. It's time for the second battle!)
- Let's go. - Okay.
I'm sure the samba will be a mess too.
- I'll be sad if I mess up. - I know. It'll be a waste.
(Nervous)
You could forget the steps all of a sudden.
(The members gather at the stage...)
Focus.
(feeling nervous.)
I'm covered in sweat.
- We only have one chance. - We only do it once?
(They only get one opportunity.)
- It's time for the second match. - Right.
(The North and South American dancers finally reunited.)
Che Che is the teacher for the hula,
and Park Ji Woo and Ryu Ji Won taught the samba.
(They're nervous as their students.)
- Park Ji Woo and Ryu Ji Won. - Nice to meet you.
I asked Director Kang,...
(According to the legend,)
what he wanted to see in advance.
(Team Hawaii will go first.)
- Right. - He wanted to see Hawaii first.
They'll have a hard time because they'll be discouraged.
(We'll go first.)
(Cuts him off.)
- Okay. - I'm excited.
I'm curious. Let's go over there.
(Attacking)
Why do you have such dark circles under your eyes?
- They did my makeup like this. - Our teacher did it.
(They get extremely competitive even before the battle.)
- We need to take our shoes off. - Goodness.
(They go barefooted to make it seem like the beaches of Hawaii.)
(Let's do it!)
Let's do it!
- We can do this. - I'm nervous.
(Don't get nervous. Smile!)
- Are we starting right away? - We're starting.
- Mind your facial expression. - Let's do it.
Are we starting right away?
(Their toes show their nervousness.)
- Mind your facial expression. - Let's do it.
Mind your facial expression. Are we starting right away?
(Smile)
- Your silhouette looks nice. - Yes.
Mind your facial expression.
(Hula)
Music, cue.
(We invite those who are restless from being home to Hawaii's beach.)
How cute.
(The scent of Hawaii spreads...)
(in Deungchon-dong Open Hall.)
They're so cute.
Aloha.
(You can feel the relaxing atmosphere of Hawaii...)
This is nice. The hula is a cool dance.
(from their fingertips.)
(Kwang Ja's face is filled with happiness.)
(Even the opponents admit it.)
They're so good.
(They might make mistakes, but their expression is professional.)
They're so cute.
(The hula mister is off-beat.)
(Come to Bugok Hawaii.)
(Even at their lacking dance, she responds with a smile.)
Their teacher is really cool.
It's really cute.
They look incredible.
(The smile of the hula swindler...)
- Their smiles. - It's so still.
(makes you zone out.)
(The members are starting to give off the smell of tanning lotion.)
They dance well now.
Isn't Suk Jin's smile awkward?
(His smile isn't awkward. He's expressing happiness.)
(They are each expressing happiness...)
(in their own unique way.)
They're good.
(Hula)
(They finish up with a perfect smile.)
(Clapping)
It didn't seem like...
(Compare to samba,)
(that's nothing.)
- a couple's dance. - It was a simple dance.
(They used their facial muscles the most.)
It was a simple dance.
We did well, right?
(Satisfied)
- We did well, right? - You know...
(It's the best.)
We did a great job.
It was the best we have done.
(He's meant to be on the stage.)
- We didn't make a mistake. - The song put us in a good mood.
(Their song and dance were therapeutic.)
The dance was nice.
- I know. - We did a great job.
- It's time for the next team. - It's our turn.
(Samba...)
(will flutter them again.)
- My goodness. - Will we able to do well?
- Let's go. - I am nervous.
(Fuss)
Then comes...
(She makes a fuss from the start.)
So Min is motivated.
So Min is motivated to do well.
(Enthusiastic)
So Min is motivated.
(She wants to become the best student twice in a row.)
So Min is motivated to do well.
She is the main dancer.
(Ha Sook, a female dancer, not the main dancer)
- Really? - Just look at So Min.
- Stop it. I will be too nervous. - I wonder what kind of dance...
(These two are the main dancers today.)
So Min and Se Chan will show.
- Se Chan, you look sexy. - I unbuttoned my shirt.
(Revealing his fair skin)
That style suits you.
You should go around that way.
- Should I go around this way? - Yes.
- It looks nice. - It looks nice.
(He has a pale chest without a single strand of hair.)
Get ready.
(They get ready for a samba performance.)
Music,
- cue. - They look like proper dancers.
(Cue)
Let's see it.
Look at Se Chan's eyes.
(Burning)
(The passionate female dancers come forward!)
(However)
Jae Suk, what are you doing with your mouth?
Stop sticking out your mouth!
(Sticking out his mouth)
Jae Suk, what are you doing with your mouth?
(Smile.)
(Se Chan and So Min look like a couple from Brazil.)
(It's the male dancers' turn!)
(They let go of their shyness...)
(and take the stage with bulging eyes.)
(And...)
(the dancers get close.)
(Her heart beats fast.)
(The youngest members' samba makes everyone smile like a mom.)
(Ha Sook steps up her game.)
(They do a wave at the same time.)
(It's my turn.)
(Wave)
(Dream's dad and Ji Ho's dad are completely absorbed.)
- They are good. - I know.
(Explosive charisma)
Yang Se Chan!
(Their passion makes them continue to do the wave.)
Look at Se Chan.
(The 4 dancers break away from their everyday lives.)
(It's like Rio de Janeiro here.)
What was that?
(The perfect finale)
It was cool.
(Perfect customer satisfaction)
It was as good as our performance.
(The passionate samba performance...)
(heated up the atmosphere.)
(The two dads did their parts as the main dancers.)
It was cool.
When I saw So Min take the stage with gritted teeth,
- I knew that she was determined. - "I will rip the stage apart."
(She had totally made up her mind.)
"This is my stage. I will give the best performance."
It was cool.
(They approve as well.)
- It was cool. - She danced with gritted teeth.
(I can give an encore performance.)
- It's time to check who won. - Okay.
(It's time to announce the result of the fierce competition.)
The legend of the variety shows, Director Kang...
(The legend of the variety shows)
Immortal Chan Hee.
(The Immortal Chan Hee time)
- He is moving the camera. - Come on!
(Immortal Chan Hee)
- Oh, yes! - Come on!
- Come on! - Se Chan and So Min are on fire!
- Come on. - Kang Chan Hee.
(Is it the therapeutic time...)
- So Min... - Where are you going?
(or the passionate time?)
The camera will go up and zoom in on the winning team.
- It will come this way. - Our performance had a story.
(What will the legend choose?)
- Come on. - There he goes.
(The passionate samba won.)
(They give a ceremony.)
(It's too bad.)
- It's all right. - My goodness.
(Stop overreacting.)
- Come on. - So Min is ridiculous.
Teachers, please pick...
(It's time for teachers...)
(to pick 1 best student.)
one top student.
Meanwhile, the teams will pick the best student...
(1 best student, 1 worst student)
and worst student.
One member stood out.
(Best samba dancer)
- That's right. - That's right.
- It will be you, So Min. - No, it will be someone else.
I was named the best student earlier.
1, 2, 3.
- So Min. - So Min.
(Is the best student So Min?)
- Actually, Se Chan. - Actually, Se Chan.
(Actually, Se Chan is the best student.)
Am I the best student? Okay!
So Min did well, but she was an eyesore.
- Thank you. - She worked too hard.
I hate that facial expression.
So Min, please stop.
Seriously.
- It's our turn. - Okay.
(The worst student is Suk Jin.)
2, 3.
- Suk Jin. - Suk Jin. It's you.
- Why is it me? - You were the worst.
(Only Suk Jin didn't see it coming.)
Why am I the worst student? I did so well.
He was the worst.
Suk Jin, that's not right. You do it on the outside.
- How could you figure that out now? - Seriously.
You aren't checking your pulse.
(He's checking his pulse instead of dancing hula.)
The dance is really hard. You should try it.
Suk Jin, give Se Chan one of your lottery tickets later.
(Suk Jin 3 tickets, Se Chan 3 tickets)
(Suk Jin 2 tickets, Se Chan 4 tickets)
- Okay. - Now, please pick...
- the top student from each team. - The top student?
(Who does Che Che pick as the best student?)
Everyone did well, but one student stood out.
(Expectant)
Despite being nervous,
(Without hesitation,)
- she practiced hard until the end. - Ji Hyo.
(she picks Ji Hyo.)
- Ji Hyo. - Yes.
(He uses his entire face to show that he is sullen.)
Ji Hyo.
Kwang Soo is sullen.
Please pick the top student from this team as well.
Taking the lead and expressing yourself matter,
(He'll pick the best samba student...)
but creating a certain vibe matters the most.
(by how one created a certain vibe.)
Thus, I will pick So Min.
(He picks soulful So Min.)
- She is cool. - She got chosen twice in a row.
- I know. - She is good.
(She gets picked twice in a row.)
- What is up with her? - Stop doing that in front of me.
(Don't show your armpits after dancing.)
- Stop showing your armpits. - Stop showing your armpits.
Stop showing your armpits. Go.
Why do you keep doing that in front of me?
- Seriously. - Am I the top student again?
(So Min, the best student twice in a row,)
I think I might be able to win today.
(gets to pick 2 numbers out of 6 already.)
- Hey. - So Min is the best...
- today. - Seriously.
- So Min might win. - At the very least,
(2nd place)
she will get the Korean beef.
- I know. - I know.
She already got two numbers.
(Ji Hyo and So Min both pick a number.)
(Ji Hyo picked 10 and So Min picked 5.)
(10 is the number So Min picked in Round 1.)
Let's give the three teachers a round of applause.
(The second class ends in success.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(Finally, it's the last class.)
It will be cool.
My goodness. Are they making the sound?
(A cappella by EXIT)
Are they making the sound?
(That's incredible.)
(It sounds like musical instruments, but it's all their voices.)
Their voices are like musical instruments.
I thought they were playing musical instruments.
(This performance consists of voices only.)
- Seriously. - They are only using their mouths.
(That's insane.)
They are building up a harmony.
(It's a treat to the ears.)
(The five voices brought the cool breeze of fall.)
(Here are the teachers for the 3rd class.)
(The voice band, EXIT)
- That was nice. - That was so cool.
Their mouths are like musical instruments.
(They are a popular group...)
(whose YouTube videos get millions of views.)
Listening to them makes me want to go...
(After seeing a short performance,)
(they want to watch more live performances.)
- to a concert. - It was so nice.
- That will be therapeutic. - Seriously.
They exceeded my expectations.
(Touched)
Please step back a little.
I was saying something important and impactful.
(Nice timing)
- No, you weren't. - I was saying something important.
(He cuts off unnecessary talks.)
It didn't sound very important.
For goodness' sake.
(It was important.)
- Their teamwork was incredible. - Seriously.
Will we be able to learn a cappella in a short amount of time?
(Will we be able to learn a cappella...)
(in a short amount of time?)
You will only learn what you can.
(No pressure)
That's good.
You will learn the OSTs of "The Lion King".
(They're going to learn one of "The Lion King" soundtracks.)
It's my absolute favorite.
(The music reminds them of the savanna.)
- We will sing the songs first. - Really?
(The demonstration song, the song they'll learn)
Then you will learn them.
("Circle of Life", OST of "The Lion King")
(They get goosebumps from the start.)
(No musical instruments were used for this performance.)
(My goodness.)
(The echo makes them feel like they are at the savanna.)
- I got goosebumps. - They are incredible.
(They all get goosebumps as a group.)
(Today, they will learn "The Lion Sleeps Tonight".)
- Yes! - This is it!
(The melody,)
(bass, drum,)
(and chorus are piled up for this song.)
(The song they will learn today is familiar and upbeat.)
(The sound of the savanna...)
(makes this giraffe miss home.)
(The animals are having a festival here.)
That was incredible.
"Isn't She Lovely" is much easier.
(They showed earlier.)
- This is too hard. - I know. This is too hard.
(The advanced jungle song discourages them.)
We heard so many animal sounds.
This one is much harder.
(They only have an hour. They have to divide the parts.)
- What are the parts? - What are the parts?
- Solo, chorus, - Solo, chorus,
(Solo, chorus, bass, drum)
- bass, and drum are the four parts. - bass.
Drum.
Is there a part you want?
- Bass. - You want to be the bass.
Then we will test your vocal range first.
(Haha who wanted to learn a cappella will try.)
He was born to be the bass.
(How's Haha's bass?)
It's his top choice.
- Do, ti - Here I go.
Lower your voice like that. 3, 4.
Do, si, la, sol, fa, mi, re, do
(His voice wavers.)
(His voice stabilizes as it goes lower.)
(He is good.)
- That was good. - You should be the bass.
(Haha becomes the bass.)
He is good.
Haha will be the bass.
(It's time to select other parts.)
- Thank you. - Let's pick the other parts.
(The next part is...)
Who wanted to beatbox earlier?
(the drum and beatbox.)
- The drum. - Se Chan, you can do it.
(I can beatbox.)
- Se Chan can do it. - Please raise the volume.
(Se Chan has many skills.)
I can do the basic beats.
- I bet he will do well. - He got it.
(The beats are basic, but he is pretty good at it.)
He got it.
I can do this much.
(Happy)
- That's more than enough. - I pass, right?
- Yes. That's more than enough. - Okay!
Can anyone in this team beatbox?
(Haha attempts to beatbox.)
That's good.
- I am jealous. - He is good.
(A broken kkwaenggwari jumps in.)
What is that?
- What is that sound? - What are you doing?
(What is he doing in front of the teachers?)
(He shows off his old trick in front of the teachers.)
What are you doing?
(Will So Min give it a try this time?)
(She is practically spitting.)
(Fake cheer)
- You are good. - You are good.
There she goes again.
(So Min)
(Greedy So Min clenches her teeth again.)
There she goes again.
- We shouldn't let her do that. - She is becoming ambitious again.
Do the drum.
(She's unbelievable.)
You are good.
- That really sounded like a drum. - Now,
(Se Chan will be the drum.)
- who will sing the melody? - Jong Kook.
(It's time to pick the melody part.)
- Jong Kook? - Jong Kook.
(Is it obviously Jong Kook...)
- I will do it. - Jong Kook can sing the melody.
From our team, Kwang Soo should sing the melody.
(and Kwang Soo?)
- I will be the bass. - Bass.
Will you be the chorus?
(She agrees without knowing what it is.)
- Chorus. - Okay.
How will you test my vocal range?
(Testing Kwang Soo's vocal range who will take the melody part)
I will check if you can do do, re, mi, fa, sol, la, ti, do.
Do
- Re - Do
Do, re, mi, fa, sol, la, ti
Do
(He is taken aback by the new vocal range.)
- Ji Hyo, why don't you try it? - Try it.
(Testing Ji Hyo instead of Kwang Soo)
You will be surprised.
Do, do, do, do
How many times...
(She runs into a problem from the first note.)
Do, do, do, do
What's the point of this?
- This won't do. - She was serious.
(Don't laugh.)
- Why did you ask her to do it? - Ji Hyo can't do it.
- I can do the chorus. - The chorus?
(Shifting gears)
Why don't you make a monkey sound?
(Why don't you make a monkey sound?)
- I can imitate a dolphin. - She is good at it.
(Her only talent)
A dolphin.
(Drum, bass, chorus, solo; Solo, chorus, bass, drum)
Let's divide the teams that way.
(Each part practices separately.)
Let's start from "In the jungle".
3, 4.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook got the melody.)
Now comes...
(Breathing hard)
Am I supposed to feel dizzy?
This song doesn't give you time to catch your breath.
(He used up the oxygen in his brain 3 minutes after practice.)
You need to breathe whenever you can.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook...)
(hits the high notes without any problems.)
(Panting)
- You don't feel dizzy, do you? - No.
Let's keep going.
(This person is as bad as Kwang Soo.)
That's do, right?
Do, re
- Do - Do, re
- Do - Do
(For 10 minutes, she has been trying to get the 1st note.)
Don't harmonize with me.
(Flustered)
You keep harmonizing with me.
(She responded with harmony to his enthusiastic lesson.)
- I am trying to find the note. - Okay.
(He plays the first note again.)
Do
(What?)
No.
Do, do
(Repeat after me.)
I am becoming weird.
- Do - Do
(Ji Hyo makes...)
(even a musician tone-deaf.)
(Thanks to the teachers who don't give up,)
(So Min and Ji Hyo learn the chorus little by little.)
(People on the drum and bass are learning diligently as well.)
(The last practice to sing as a team)
- Where is my team? - Shall we go?
- Are you guys coming? - Suk Jin.
Hold on.
What?
- You can't sing at all. - Hold on.
(Did you even practice?)
(He got exposed after singing a single line.)
- You can't sing at all. - Hold on.
I just need to drink some water.
I practiced too hard.
- Really? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo needs to do well to make the performance shine.)
Let's try it.
(Meanwhile, Team Suk Jin finishes a successful practice.)
(That was nicer than we thought.)
That was nice.
This has always been my dream.
- Really? - Haha is really excited.
(It was one of Haha's wishes to try a cappella performance.)
- He is really excited. - I was like that when I danced.
(Unlike Team Suk Jin where a wish brings them together,)
I must have been like him when I danced earlier.
(the atmosphere is serious with this team.)
Did something bad happen in the savanna?
- Was it too depressing? - Don't do that.
I wanted to build up emotions.
Did everyone else die in the savanna?
Your emotions are nice,
(The teacher cheers them up desperately.)
- but please pick up the speed. - I need to sing faster.
Let's begin.
(However)
- Hold on, Kwang Soo. - Hey.
The song doesn't sound fun when he sings it.
It's depressing.
I am trying to save my voice.
(Kwang Soo keeps saving his voice.)
- Hold on. - Hey. You are going too fast.
(Frustrated)
Are you eating ice cream or something?
- I am sorry. - What was that sound?
I can't roll my tongue.
(I'm only saving my voice.)
- I can only do it shortly. - We need to sing at the same speed.
You have less than two minutes left.
(2 minutes before the competition)
(Since 40g of gold depends on the last match,)
(the members practice hard.)
(Which team will win the a cappella match?)
Please add more echo.
(Team Jae Suk goes first.)
Please increase the volume for the bass.
(Showing off)
(They keep raising the volumes of their microphones.)
You sound like an expert.
(It's time to unleash his voice for the real match.)
It's like a concert.
- Tell us when you are ready. - We will begin.
(Ready)
We will begin.
(Their seriousness made the practice go on for longer than expected.)
- From the beginning. - Yes.
(They even prepared a dance routine for the first a cappella stage.)
- We will begin. - Okay.
(The teachers...)
(The teachers and the rivals become nervous.)
- Get your hands ready. - Okay.
("The Lion Sleeps Tonight"...)
(by Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan)
(What are you doing, Ji Hyo?)
Ji Hyo, move.
I am sorry. Please let us start over.
(Ji Hyo just stands there.)
Ji Hyo, move.
I am sorry. Please let us start over.
- You were supposed to move. - I forgot.
(Flustered)
(They don't disappoint.)
- You were supposed to move. - I forgot.
(They start with discord from the first note.)
I don't want to be the first one.
- Start over. - I don't want to be the first one.
- Go to the front. - When am I supposed to come out?
(Frustrated)
- Should I go first? - Yes.
(Having issues right from the beginning)
I will go first.
(They resume after changing the order.)
- We are sorry. - We will start over.
Start after 2, 3.
("The Lion Sleeps Tonight Final"...)
2, 3.
(by Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan)
(She stifles her laughter.)
(Ji Hyo and Jae Suk finally open their mouths.)
(Look at him.)
(It sounds like Kwang Soo will stop breathing soon.)
(The teachers can't help,)
(but hang their heads.)
(Laughing)
(Chuckling)
Hold on.
I practiced too hard.
- Give us another chance. - Listen.
- Give us another chance. - Hey.
(Shocked by terrible melody)
- Let me get a sip of water. - Listen.
I am so sorry.
- Let me get a sip of water. - Kwang Soo.
(I forgot to drink water.)
- It's over if you do badly. - It's over.
I will do better.
- Without the melody... - I could hit high notes earlier.
Say, "2, 3."
(They try for the 3rd time after Kwang Soo drinks water.)
We will do it for real.
("The Lion Sleeps Tonight, The Final Version"...)
(by Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan)
It's worse than before.
(The melody is off, but the other parts come in.)
(He is singing very diligently.)
(Let's stay calm.)
(Kwang Soo's vocal cord stopped functioning properly.)
(He begins the part he has a problem with.)
(His high notes moves "Immortal Chan Hee".)
(Singing diligently)
(Something must have happened in the jungle.)
(Other parts sound great in comparison.)
(It's the magical Kwang Soo effect.)
(He is confident.)
(Kwang Soo's high notes make the rivals grin widely.)
What is that?
(Anyone would be afraid of hearing this melody in a dream.)
(Shocked)
(Kwang Soo doesn't stop...)
(summoning a ghost.)
We are ruined.
They made it funny.
(This team)
(There must be a drought in the savanna.)
(His teammates avert their eyes as he summons a ghost.)
(The first a cappella performance ends.)
(They clap hurriedly so that he wouldn't sing more.)
- Director Kang Chan Hee! - Hey!
- What are you doing? - We love you.
- For goodness' sake. - I can't believe him.
(Chan Hee smiles now that the song is over.)
How could you lose your voice from practice?
You did well.
(With a half-hearted cheer, the group breaks up.)
I could hit the notes earlier.
We did our best.
- I can't sing anymore. - Thank you.
(I did my best.)
Hey, hey.
(Everyone is looking forward to Team Suk Jin's performance.)
(Unlike the other team, they practice in a stable way.)
Suk Jin, good luck.
- I hope Suk Jin makes a mistake. - Suk Jin.
You are confusing me. Stop it.
- Stop it. - Add it to the performance.
("Chiki chiki chak chak" in "The Lion King"?)
Suk Jin.
(The old beats stick to Suk Jin's ears.)
You are confusing me.
- The mountain rabbit. - That's right.
Hold on, I am doing this wrong.
- Are they allowed to do that? - I got it.
(Suk Jin was attacked by everyone.)
- Did you get it? - I got it.
(Will they be able to finish it safely?)
- Shall we begin? - Yes.
("The Lion Sleeps Tonight"...)
(by Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Haha, and So Min)
- His voice doesn't waver. - I added vibrations too.
(Isn't that cheating?)
(Jong Kook leads with the melody...)
(and the performance goes without a problem.)
(The birth of a 4-member a cappella group)
(My goodness.)
(Jong Kook shows the importance of the melody,)
(which leads the chorus, drum, and bass.)
(Sighing)
For goodness' sake.
(They're quite harmonious...)
(considering they just learned it.)
(She's excited.)
(The teachers are enjoying it, unlike earlier.)
(Let's add a spoonful of a sweet voice.)
(Good for you.)
(They even had the leisure to add choreography.)
(I wish we did that too.)
(Howling)
(Shouting)
(They even succeed in the difficult part.)
They're really good.
(The winner has already been decided.)
(Sighing)
Kang Chan Hee
(The a capella is complete.)
(Unlike the previous team, they didn't worry as they watched.)
Wimoweh!
Kang Chan Hee's the best.
We did so well.
(Bass Haha fulfilled his wish.)
Gosh. It was so exciting.
We did well. It wasn't bad.
(Team Suk Jin compliments each other.)
- You guys were so cool. - I got excited.
(Fake applause)
You were so cool.
Our main melody was a mess, so how could we do well?
- He can't sing, so how could we? - Our main melody...
(They rebel furiously.)
- was a complete mess. - The problem wasn't me.
He said that he's not the problem.
- He said he wasn't. - Gosh.
- With Jong Kook at the center... - We did really well.
(The importance of melody)
With Jong Kook setting everything up...
(What did the teachers think?)
We need to check who the winner is.
(It's time to decide the winners and losers.)
The team that Director Kang shoots is the winner.
(Who will Director Kang Chan Hee choose?)
We don't know how Chan Hee feels.
(We don't know yet.)
- We could be chosen out of pity. - Kang Chan Hee
It will be a controversy if he chooses them.
(No way.)
- That's right. - A controversy?
Director Kang's choice is...
(Who will Director Kang Chan Hee choose?)
- Choose the team you like more. - He's moving.
(Immortal Chan Hee)
- He's debating. - Kang Chan Hee
(All eyes are on him.)
Choose the team you like more. He's debating.
(Team Suk Jin's high quality)
(versus Team Jae Suk's scratchy voice)
Choose the team you like more. He's debating.
(Where will Director Kang Chan Hee's camera go?)
Okay!
(Team Suk Jin wins!)
(Nice!)
We got it.
(Smacking their lips)
Do we choose the best student?
This team will choose the best student first.
(Team Jae Suk will choose the best student.)
The best student?
- We have a person in mind. - 1, 2, 3.
(It's very obvious.)
- Jong Kook. - Kim Jong Kook.
(Unanimous)
Thank you.
- Thank you. - We acknowledge it.
(We admit it.)
(They pick the obvious worst student.)
1, 2, 3.
- Lee Kwang Soo. - Lee Kwang Soo.
(Worst, Lee Kwang Soo)
- The difference is in the melody. - This couldn't be helped.
(It's the result of the difference in skills between the two.)
This is the most important. The top student chosen by the teacher.
(Who is the top student chosen by the teachers?)
- They watched us carefully. - Musically,
- this part was really hard. - Right.
(Musically speaking, it was a really challenging part.)
(Kwang Soo gets ahead of himself.)
And it's hard to stay centered.
But he did a great job. It's Haha.
(Haha is the best student.)
- I knew it. - Thank you.
All right!
(Sulky)
He could become a professional bass vocalist.
(He is good enough to be a professional bass singer.)
- He was so excited. - I was really happy.
- His dream came true. He likes it. - Singing in a capella was my dream.
(It's an honor.)
- He has a great bass voice. - Thank you.
(He acquires the title with his stable low voice.)
Honestly, we were worried and wondered if the eight of you...
(The teachers were worried about dividing the parts.)
would be able to divide up into different parts.
I can't say which team is which,
but there was a team who was good musically,
and there was a team that took the music...
and changed it into an artistic satire.
I never did that.
(What are you talking about?)
- Just stay quiet. - He said we made it into satire.
(He is the only one who feels wrongly accused.)
- My gosh. - You ruined the mood.
(He expresses his anger in the air.)
It was so much fun.
- It was really fun. - We enjoyed watching it.
(He ends abruptly.)
(The third class is over.)
While you're doing that, Haha will come up and pick a number.
(Haha gets to pick a number of the lottery.)
That's right.
That could be.
(Haha wrote 1 for his winning number.)
Right? Because there are 10.
Are you choosing the numbers for the lottery randomly?
(The lottery numbers will be chosen randomly.)
- Yes, we are. - It's random?
Oh, okay then.
Gosh, I don't know. I'll just choose anything.
(Luck is as important as the number of tickets.)
I would love to come in first place just once.
(Who will be the lucky winner of the 6-digit lottery?)
- It's a miracle to get it all. - I wish I could get it once.
I'll tell you the winning numbers that you all chose first.
(It's time to announce the designated winning number.)
So Min chose two numbers.
(So Min picked 2 numbers.)
- One of them is five. - Okay.
(Number 5)
- The other is 10. - Is that what she chose?
(5 and 10 are her winning numbers.)
- The other is 10. - Okay.
I didn't choose 5 and 10 together.
(That was close.)
- Song Ji Hyo also chose 10. - Really?
(Ji Hyo also chose 10.)
I was so surprised when you said that.
(I should've told you.)
Haha chose one.
(Haha also picked 1, which means 1, 5, 10 are the winning numbers.)
In other words, 1, 5, 10 are winning numbers.
If you get all 6 of them right, we prepared 40g of gold for you.
(They'll win 40g of gold if they guess all 6 digits.)
- Gosh. - If someone gets all six right...
(Please!)
- Right. Take it. - Who could it be?
The first number is...
(The lottery starts.)
Three.
(The current winning numbers are 1, 3, 5, 10.)
I have 1, 3, 5.
Really?
We have two more numbers left.
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo guessed 3.)
I have 3, 5, 10.
If I get 1 more right, I have a total of 4.
Me too.
(They'll win 3rd place if they guess 1 more right.)
I need one more as well.
- Can I write on this? - Yes, you can.
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, So Min, and Haha already secured 3rd.)
- Six. - I'll choose the next number.
7, 8.
The fifth number is...
- 7, 8. - 7.
I got it.
(It's 7!)
(Everyone gets excited after hearing 7.)
- I got it. - My legs are weak.
- I got four. - I got it.
- I got 4. - I got 4.
Me too.
- I have 7 and 10. I just need 6. - Look. I just need 8.
(So Min and Haha only need to guess one more right.)
- If I get one more, I win. - I...
If you chose 8, I'd have won 1st place.
(It's the last number in the 6-digit lucky lottery!)
I have the ball in my hand.
(If a 6 comes out, Haha comes in 1st place.)
I just need a six.
- Please choose eight. - The last number is...
(If an 8 comes out, So Min comes in 1st place.)
Eight.
Two.
(Nobody gets the 40g of gold.)
(Disappointed)
I got the first 4 numbers right.
(That was close.)
Really?
I got the first 4 numbers right.
- I got 5, so I get the Korean beef. - Is that the prize?
(Suk Jin wins Korean beef by guessing 5 digits correctly.)
You're so lucky.
Jae Suk came in third place once.
That's too bad.
Suk Jin came in 2nd place and 3rd place.
Haha came in 2nd place 3 times.
You came in 2nd place 3 times?
(Amazing)
Haha will take home three Korean beef sets.
(Haha wins 3 sets of Korean beef as he wins 3 tickets of 2nd places.)
- That's incredible. - That's incredible.
You own a pork restaurant, so why are you taking home so much beef?
Kwang Soo came in third place twice.
Yes!
Se Chan came in third place once.
So Min came in 2nd place and 3rd place.
Ji Hyo came in third place once.
Jong Kook came in third place twice.
(The remaining prizes will be given at the next shooting.)
We'll give you your prizes during the next shoot.
Okay.
Today's winner is...
(Today's winner)
Haha.
(Haha, who won 3 tickets with 2nd places!)
He came in first place!
Nobody got the 1st place prize.
(Thanks to all yodel, hula, samba, a capella teachers...)
It's too bad, isn't it?
- Good job, everyone. - Good job, everyone.
(for joining us today!)
(A few days before the shoot in Mok-dong SBS)
- Hello? - Jae Suk?
(Jae Suk received a mysterious phone call?)
- Yes? - During the next shoot...
Please bring an outfit that...
(Bring an outfit that...)
(you would like to recommend to another member.)
you would like to recommend to...
(Haha, Gets teased for his fashion, Byword of see-through looks)
It's finally time for me to get my revenge.
(It's finally time for me to get my revenge.)
There's a fashion style I've been pushing for.
It's a pair of balloon pants and no top.
They won't be able to pull off my fashion style.
(Ji Suk Jin, Mr. Origami)
(They won't be able to pull off my fashion style.)
(I'm ahead of the times in fashion.)
I'm ahead of the times in fashion.
Can I bring leggings?
(A fashion show...)
(where they wear each other's clothes is coming soon.)
This is great. I love this kind of content.
(Fashion Choice Race, All or Nothing)