- Kim Jong Kook.
- Kook Jong.
Me? I didn't write a lot.
It's okay. Make it short.
Gosh, I think this is too formal.
"With the global fandom
beyond Korea,"
"Running Man has become the center
of Korean variety shows."
He must be shy.
He seems anxious now.
"It's the gateway
to becoming a star."
"Through talks and games
that attract viewers of all ages,"
"Korea's representative variety show
spreads K-Culture."
This is real.
He is serious about this. I love it.
It sounds like SBS wrote it.
We also need things like this.
"Yoo Jae Suk. His nickname
is 'Unchanging Goofball'."
Is that all you wrote?
The thing is...
- I wrote the others first.
- I love it.
- I was going to come back to this.
- I like it anyway.
- You like it.
- I do.
- "Unchanging Goofball".
- Good.
"Ji Suk Jin. The Lynx
of talk shows called 'Ji-rasoni'."
"He's burning the last embers
of his variety show career."
- Good.
- Hey.
When will your last passion
come to an end?
Last? It's not like...
- "The Last Leaf".
- It's like eternal youth.
- Good luck.
- Go, Ji Suk Jin!
"Kim Jong Kook. 'Anyang Tantrum'
who throws a tantrum when he's mad."
He admits it too.
"He's a singer. He sings well
and has many hit songs."
"But he's better known
as an entertainer now."
Okay.
- That was about him.
- Gosh.
"Haha. Short Guy, Small Guy,"
"Haha PD,
A Guy Who's Short but Happy".
"He's an indispensable
seasoning in Running Man."
"But he's more focused
on his YouTube these days."
Is he a seasoning?
- Seasoning.
- "Lee Kwang Soo."
"Just Crazy, Forever Star Butler."
Why do you keep saying
"Star Butler"?
"He's ugly, but he finds it
hard to accept the fact."
(He's ugly, but he finds it
hard to accept the fact.)
"His fans spoiled him."
What?
(His fans spoiled him.)
(What's that?)
- Exactly. His fans spoiled him.
- That can't be my introduction.
It's the fans.
They didn't spoil me.
They say he's handsome,
so he thinks he's handsome.
"He finds it hard
to accept the fact." It's hilarious.
- My gosh.
- He can't accept it.
- This is crazy.
- "Yang Se Chan."
"Yechani, Yang Sebastian,
and Gum Angel."
Good. I like my nicknames.
"Kim Jong Kook's favorite doll."
"But he badmouths me
behind my back."
"He's pretending to be innocent, but
once there's proof, I'll kill him."
(He's pretending to be innocent, but
once there's proof, I'll kill him.)
This is a declaration of war.
(It's a declaration of war
under the mask of an introduction.)
I didn't badmouth you.
- Who's up next?
- I made it short.
- It's simple.
- Good.
Make it short.
I was serious about
the production objective though.
This stuff can last a while.
"It's spreading to the whole world
beyond Korea? No, to outer space."
"The members make up
for each other's deficiencies."
"The piller of Korean variety shows
that the whole family can enjoy."
- Okay.
- Good.
"Piller?" Does it say "piller"?
- "Piller?"
- What?
(Piller?)
It's "pillar", you punk.
- It's a typo.
- It's not a typo.
You also said "piller".
(He confidently pronounced it
as "piller".)
- It's a typo.
- It's not acorn jelly.
It's not a dialect.
It's "pillar". Do you even know
what a pillar is?
- What?
- Do you know what it means?
It's like a support.
That's it. Just move on.
- Please change the spelling.
- It's okay.
If Kwang Soo wins,
you should go with this.
Member introductions.
"Ji Suk Jin. I'm still vigorous."
(I'm still vigorous.)
"Yoo Jae Suk."
(They love it.)
"Bring it on."
"I will stay ranked eighth
by looks no matter who comes."
(He's in first place from the end.)
- I love it.
- He's crazy.
"Kim Jong Kook.
My heart is like a soy sauce dish."
(My heart is like a soy sauce dish.)
Are you saying he's petty?
(The soy sauce dish will
teach you a lesson.)
- Good.
- "Haha. Old Fossil".
"Come to me
if you want to get an earful."
I'm talking now!
- Good.
- "Song Ji Hyo."
"Go ahead and text me."
"I'll ignore it anyway."
(Go ahead and text me.
I'll ignore it anyway.)
I love it.
(It's a short but powerful blow.)
"Jeon So Min. It's me who made
Running Man PG-15."
"I'll make it Rated R in 2021."
(She will raise the viewer rating
as well as the age limit.)
- Good.
- "Yang Se Chan."
- "Poop".
- Hey!
(He just wrote one word, "poop".)
What's that?
I lost my concentration
toward the end.
It doesn't mean anything.
It's just one word.
- I lost my concentration.
- It's funny though.
- I like it.
- How could he say that?
I like it. It's short and good.
"Lee Kwang Soo. We didn't know..."
"how charming he was."
Gosh, I hate him.
(It's true that
his fans spoiled him.)
It makes me want to vomit.
Mine is short too.
The production objective.
"Variety shows are..."
"disappearing these days."
"Running Man is Korea's favorite
variety show that's been..."
"on Sunday nights
for over 10 years."
"The members play games and clear
missions with various guest stars,"
"as they go around
to different places."
"Among various fun factors,"
"this show only
focuses on laughter."
This is the true
production objective.
I hope this will go on the website.
This is how Jae Suk thinks
of Running Man.
The writers are giving him
a big hand.
Why are you clapping your hands?
"We only care about laughter."
(We only care about laughter.)
- Cool.
- Right.
It's not like
you're submitting a report.
"Ji Suk Jin. He was going to leave
the team in the first year."
("Ji Suk Jin was going to leave
the team in the first year.")
"But now he says
Running Man is the best."
(Knocked out)
That's just a message to him.
- "His behavior is frowned upon..."
- That's just a message to him.
- Hey.
- That's basically a letter.
That's just something
we say among ourselves.
This is my introduction. It's mine.
It's like...
It's like an article
for the tabloids.
Yes, that's right. The tabloids.
It's just how I feel about him.
"His behavior
is frowned upon by many."
- It's excessive.
- It's totally for the tabloids.
- You praise the show excessively.
- He's right.
- I'm not excessive.
- And everyone hates it.
My goodness.
"Yoo Jae Suk."
"The official prankster
of Running Man, Yooruce Willis."
- Okay.
- Ji Suk Jin.
"Kim Jong Kook."
"Called 'Kim Nipple' during summer
and 'Enema Kim' in other seasons."
"Also known as 'Go Large'
and won the Grand Award in 2020."
- Congratulations!
(The other members praise
the Grand Award winner again.)
- Congratulations!
(Suk Jin is pretty annoyed.)
How long do we have to
congratulate him for the award?
"Song Ji Hyo. Real name is
Cheon Seong Im, Cheon Su Yeon."
"Nickname is 'Jeoktoma'."
"We can't say that she gets
along well with the members,"
"but we also can't say
that she doesn't."
"To cut a long story short,
Ji Hyo is funny these days."
Next is...
"Haha. He's the dad of three kids.
He's officially an old fossil now."
- "But he still doesn't know it."
- Why am I an old fossil?
"He doesn't want to admit it."
"Recently, he sent me
half-dried herring".
(Recently, he sent me
half-dried herring.)
Is it necessary to write about that
in his introduction?
I wanted to write about
things the viewers don't know.
Who is "me" in the introduction?
- That's me.
- It's you?
- You can't write about yourself.
- All right.
"Lee Kwang Soo. He can grow taller
but he doesn't try harder."
(Lee Kwang Soo. He can grow taller
but he doesn't try harder.)
You keep saying that.
- Then try harder.
- Yes, drink some milk.
- He's right.
- Why won't you try harder?
- Drink milk and play basketball.
- What are you talking about?
Next is Jeon So Min.
"I've seen her for a while
and she really is crazy."
"Yang Se Chan. Yang Se Hyeong's
brother. Has handsome gums."
"It seems he has a girlfriend."
(Suspicious of his private life
"It seems he has a girlfriend.")
- I don't.
- That's all I have.
- Okay.
It was good.
- It was very neat.
- It was, wasn't it?
I thought it'd be better
to write a lot about the show.
You wrote a lot. It's very long.
"A show that makes the entire
country, and beyond, run as one."
She's actually right.
"Running Man carries out
missions like we only live today."
"Eight members with different colors
go through many troubles..."
"to deliver a great deal of joy
and extraordinary entertainment."
She used all the fancy words
she knows.
"Stay tuned for the charm of
the eight members..."
"which we will show you anywhere
and in any situation."
- Ji Hyo, I love that. "Stay tuned".
- "Stay tuned!"
- Stay tuned.
- Okay.
Next is...
Who's the thug?
- "Kim Thug."
- Okay, "Kim Thug".
"You'll be sorry if you judge him
only by his muscles."
"No one can catch up
to his good sense and witty words."
- "All Mighty of all higher beings."
- She's right.
"He likes to reveal
his adorable side sometimes."
"He is unexpectedly charming."
- You're so right.
- Yes.
You know exactly who I am.
(What did she write about Haha?)
"Small business owner."
(President Ha,
small business owner in Mapo-gu)
"President Ha,
small business owner in Mapo-gu."
That is funny.
(His name is "President Ha,
small business owner in Mapo-gu.")
"How capable and resourceful is he?"
"He's capable of both running
a business and running on the show."
"President Ha is a greedy man
who wants it all!"
Do you think it's appropriate...
to write that
in the member introduction?
You can't write about
his personal business.
"He's capable
of running a business."
- Well, he does a lot of things.
- Hey.
It's my business.
- I wrote "a small business owner."
- She can't compliment him...
for running his business well
in the member introduction.
- What about Song Ji Hyo?
- "Song Ji Hyo."
Well, I wasn't sure
what I should say.
So I wrote, "Finally, she's
trying to step out into the world."
Maybe that's how you feel.
"She's learning how fun
it is to be out in the world."
"Song Ji Hyo
is stepping out into the world."
Congratulations!
(Song Ji Hyo
is stepping out into the world.)
Yes, you should
communicate with others.
You're finally
stepping out into the world?
Finally.
Song Communication.
Okay, Song Jeoktoma!
- Song Jeoktoma.
- Yes, come on out. And call me.
Let's have a meal together.
We're supposed to be
social distancing.
(We're supposed to be
social distancing.)
(Quickly apologizing)
- Suk Jin.
- In spirit only.
- Be with her in spirit only.
- Sure.
- In spirit only. My apologies.
- All right.
Next is Ji Suk Jin.
(Can't wait to hear what she says.
Next is Ji Suk Jin.)
"He doesn't know himself."
"He's the Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong
who pretends to love his family."
(He's the Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong
who pretends to love his family.)
(Find yourself
falling for his charm.)
I love it.
- "The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
- Today...
Ji Hyo is stepping out
into the world.
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
It was great.
"Find yourself
falling for his charm."
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
What's that?
- It's kind of ambiguous.
- Hugh Grant.
I'm not offended
but can't say I'm pleased.
It's good since it's Hugh Grant.
Hugh Grant is amazing.
Yes, it's good that
she compared me to him.
We got two amazing nicknames today.
- "The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong."
- And "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
- Yes, "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
- That's right.
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong"
is funny.
All right.
Hello, everyone.
- Hi.
- The production objective.
"The funniest show ever in Korea
and in any country in the world."
"The only show you can enjoy
both the old and the new."
"You can bite, chew, and taste.
We are the real deal."
"The one and only
semi-real variety show."
- "Semi-real variety show".
- "Semi-real".
- It's a bit more than half.
- Actually, it's 100 percent real.
- "The dealer of semi-real variety".
- "semi-real".
"We guarantee
your laughter, longevity,"
"love life, marriage,"
"and success in life."
Shouldn't it be "the leader",
not "the dealer"?
Oh, right. It's "the leader".
(The dealer of semi-real variety!)
(The leader of semi-real variety!)
- Wait a minute.
- It's "the leader".
- He's right.
- Wait a minute.
- What is "a dealer"?
- My goodness.
How can you make such a mistake?
How hard is it to make
a PowerPoint? Am I right?
- No, no. It's a typo.
- What is "the dealer"?
It's "the leader".
I knew the correct word.
I wrote "piller" as a typo too.
I thought it was written correctly.
"Piller" was a typo.
I confused "the leader"
with "the dealer".
- Whatever. That's what you wrote.
- It's "the leader".
- It's "the leader," everyone.
- Okay, what's next?
- Let's move on.
- I knew the actual word.
Next is Ji Suk Jin,
known as "The Senior".
- Gosh, it says "Ji Seok Ji".
- What's "Ji Seok Ji"?
- Gosh.
- You can't fix it now.
She can't fix it.
What's "Ji Seok Ji"?
She can't fix it now.
No, she can't.
- If she wins, I'll be "Seok Ji"?
- Sure.
You're "Ji Seok Ji"
even if you say it backwards.
It's the same
"The lucky charm, the adorable,
the youngest Jeon So Min."
"No one knows who she really is."
"Running Man unveils
her mysterious charm."
(Flinching)
"She's good at acting,
comedy, writing, and cooking."
"The perfect entertainer
this generation wants."
"The best entertainer.
How much more can she be charming?"
"We're lucky to have her!"
(We're lucky to have her!)
(And she doesn't forget
to strike a pose as she prepared.)
- It's Suk Jin's turn.
- I think...
everyone's good enough
to be picked.
- Yes, everyone's good.
- Right.
- They're not bad.
- If I win,
- mine will be posted, right?
- Yes.
All right.
The production objective.
"The new hearth of Running Man,"
- "Ji Suk Jin leads the new show."
- "Hearth"?
"The new hearth of Running Man,
Ji Suk Jin leads the new show."
- "Hearth"?
- Running Man.
- Wait.
- What?
- Are you nervous?
- No.
(Got something to mock)
- Well, I think...
- I'm not nervous.
it's been a long time since he was
in the center of attention.
You said,
"The new hearth of Running Man."
(He's so nervous
that his heart is about to burst!)
- "Every week, Ji Suk Jin..."
- Don't be nervous.
"fights against the seven losers."
Don't be so nervous.
All right.
Just hang in there.
Hugh Grant!
(Cheering for
"The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong")
- Hugh...
- Please be quiet.
"He can't be fooled,
but he pretends that he is."
"His name tag can't been ripped..."
"but he lets them rip it off."
The word spacing is terrible.
It's not "can't been ripped".
It's "can't be ripped".
Other words are wrong too.
- Just let it go.
- I can't believe him.
His grammar is terrible.
Just let it go.
"I sacrifice myself to giving hope
to the younger members."
"I is the Giving Tree,
Captain Ji."
Shouldn't it be "am" not "is"?
"I is"?
"To giving hope"?
He wrote, "to giving hope".
It's because...
the keyboard arrangement
is different from my generation.
Is it a regional dialect?
Your generation didn't even
have a keyboard.
- "The Giving Tree, Captain Ji."
- What's wrong with you?
"It's not just
a variety show anymore."
What's wrong with him?
"In the endless cold
betrayal betrayal..."
Why did you write "betrayal" twice?
What does that mean?
(In the endless cold
betrayal betrayal...)
My goodness.
You're unprepared.
Why would you write
"betrayal" twice?
My goodness. This is making me cry.
- Gosh, this is so funny.
- That's not it.
- Gosh.
- This is...
He was surprised too.
"Endless cold betrayal betrayal..."
(He froze up
when he read the second "betrayal".)
- He was like a broken record.
- Wait a minute.
I'm sorry
that I wrote the word twice.
Okay, member introductions.
What's this? "Jan Seo Min"?
I'm so sorry.
- My goodness.
- Why so many typos?
- Suk Jin.
- "Any litle?"
- It's just the order.
- It's "Any little thing."
"Any little thing can make her
go crazy. No one can control her."
- "The biggest fool on the show."
- Why did he make so many mistakes?
"Buckteeth Se Chan"
"The ugliest."
"He's all talk but no sincerity."
It's witless.
(Don't mock him with facts.)
(Pretending that he hears nothing)
Song Ji Hyo. "Zoned-out Girl."
I named her "Zoned-out Girl."
(Boring!)
It's not witty.
"Zoned-out Girl,"
the next "Young Gu".
- "Running Man's new fool."
- Wake up, Haha.
We're still filming.
(Haha, wake up.)
(Fell asleep listening to
Suk Jin's boring story)
Wait a minute. Wake up, Haha.
Jae Suk, Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk!
- We're filming.
Jae Suk, wake up!
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk
gives a perfect performance.)
Jae Suk, wake up.
- What?
- We're still filming.
Okay. Look alive, guys!
I fell asleep.
Hang in there, guys.
He's almost done.
- Gosh, I fell asleep.
- He's no fun.
- Okay. "Lee Kwang Soo."
- He's not done yet?
"Now he's 350cm tall."
- "He entered the Guinness Book."
- It's already morning.
- Haha!
- "How tall will he get?"
Okay, next.
- This is exhausting.
- "Kim Jong Kook."
- Another typo?
- "The starter of the new rase."
- There's another typo.
- "Experienced much muscle loss."
"He suddenly lost so much muscle."
"His thighs are as slim as
Suk Jin's arms now."
"Now he's the weakest member
of Running Man."
It's like the principal
is giving a speech.
- Suk Jin.
- What?
- Your face turned red.
No, no. I'm fine.
It's not funny at all.
- Suk Jin.
- Just keep your mouth shut.
- It's really not funny.
- Don't say a word.
- "It's really not funny."
- Next is Haha.
(Teasing)
I laughed so much my stomach hurts.
I'm talking about Haha, you punk.
Suk Jin, are you upset?
Yes, I am upset, you punk!
- He's embarrassed.
- Are you all right?
I'm fine.
- Okay, next page.
- My mouth hurts.
Gosh, my cheekbones hurt.
"Ji Suk Jin,
known as 'Ji-rasoni'."
- "He's there."
- Suk Jin.
Suk Jin noticed it.
He just scanned the entire room.
- Hey.
- He sensed it.
Stay quiet.
"There is no need
for further explanation."
- Is that it?
- "Yoo Jae Suk."
It says dirty.
"Yoo Jae Suk announced
his retirement this year."
"This is his last work."
- "Pay attention to him."
- He's Ji Grant.
Give me a white towel.
- We don't have a white towel.
- Get him one.
Get me a white towel.
Suk Jin is about to cry.
It's hilarious.
Gosh, it was so funny.
Suk Jin, is it over?
(Swearing)
What?
(He says bad words
half-seriously, half-jokingly.)
Why are you swearing?
(Ji-rasoni finally loses
his temper after 11 years.)
- Why are you swearing?
- Why are you taking it off?
(Swearing)
- Why are you swearing at us?
- Why are you upset?
Why?
What's wrong?
- Fine. Do what you want!
- Come here.
- It's so funny.
- Suk Jin.
- Come here.
- Don't be upset.
- Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin sulks
for the first time in 11 years.)
(Now he finally shows
his humane qualities.)
Why are you swearing?
All right. You can watch
Suk Jin swear on YouTube.
It's called "Spicy Version
Ji Suk Jin".
It's so funny.
I'm sorry I lost my temper.
I laughed a lot.
It's hilarious.
It's killing me.
This is so funny.
I want you guys to pick...
the worst introduction each.
- Can I say it?
- Hey.
- Don't do that.
- You're really mean!
(You're really mean!)
- There's no need to say.
- Do you really not know?
No need to say it.
- Why do you even ask?
- Do you really not know?
You should pick the worst one.
- 1, 2, 3.
- I can't pick.
Who picked Suk Jin?
- Me.
- Me too.
- Four people.
- 5 people.
- There are 5.
(5 out of 8 people)
Jae Suk, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo
got one vote each.
And Suk Jin got five votes.
Like I said, today's special is
Running Man Rewritten.
The winner's content will be posted
on our website.
I'll have mine go on the website.
We have two kinds of roulette here.
The first one has your names on it,
and we will spin it at the end.
It has 40 spots
with 5 name tags each.
We will spin it
to decide the winner.
And the other roulette
is about benefits.
The winners of each mission
will spin this roulette...
and win the benefit they pick.
According to the roulette,
you will have more...
or less name tags on the roulette.
And you will get paid
as much as the number...
of your name tags on the roulette.
- Really?
- Good.
If you have more name tags on
the roulette, you'll get more money.
It increases the amount of money.
We will start the first mission
once you get changed.
(They will start the mission
after getting changed.)
- What is this?
- What's that?
What is this thing?
It's getting more advanced.
I'm really curious.
Who comes up with games like this?
This is amazing.
- My goodness.
- There's flour. Is this flour?
What? Is that flour?
- I think this one is better.
- What's that thing?
- Are they marbles?
- Marbles.
It might break my head.
- It can't break your head.
- This is the worst.
I might break my head.
This one is...
It's like jelly.
It's called frogspawn.
- That's just...
- It's not hard.
How can someone be so untrusting
of our production crew?
A member like that...
I can't believe this.
You should have a meeting
and rule him out.
The production crew wouldn't put
metal marbles in there.
Hey, stop it.
I saw Suk Jin punch the wall
in the restroom earlier.
- I almost cried now.
- Why?
Suk Jin just kicked me,
but it didn't hurt at all.
Come on.
(It's like an old parent's whip
doesn't hurt at all.)
- Jae Suk, that's so sad.
- Hey.
I just kicked you gently.
- I just kicked you gently.
- What should I do?
Kook Jong, it makes my heart ache.
I know how you feel.
(When everyone worries
about Big Nose...)
This camera is only for me.
- Hey, it's not for you.
- It's not for you.
It's for all of us.
It's for a full shot.
Jong Kook should
be on the camera too.
This is for a full shot. Lean back.
We can be on the camera too.
- Don't block the camera.
- She's right.
My goodness.
We're rewriting the production
objective for the year 2021.
So we prepared missions
that require a good hunch...
and good wit which are
necessary skills for Running Man.
This is what I'm good at.
I have a good hunch.
Goofball is acting up again.
- What are you good at?
- Goofball is acting up again.
I really want to see you
do something well.
- A good hunch and what?
- I'm good at this.
I'm sure you will be covered
in a floury mess in 10 minutes.
- Hey, stay quiet.
- I'm pretty sure.
I can imagine that.
The first mission is...
Know How It Feels to Run.
You will give it a try one by one.
You will lie on the cart
and stamp your feet once...
to get as close as possible
to the wall.
And you will see...
the yellow zone, green zone,
and red zone here.
- And the cart has an arrow.
- There's an arrow.
If the arrow stops on red,
the water balloon will burst.
(Red: Water balloon)
If it stops on green,
the marble balloon will burst.
If it stops on yellow, you succeed.
If you fail to control the speed
and bump into the wall,
the bell will ring,
and the whipped cream balloon
will burst.
(If the cart hits the wall,
the cream balloon will burst.)
That's the worst.
It'd be better to try it later.
- No.
- No. That's not true.
Why are they being like that to me?
- Why?
- You two should sit apart.
- But why?
- Just sit apart.
Why do you think
it'd be better to try later?
- That's not true.
- Why is that?
What?
I mean, I can see
how hard it should be...
- Kim Grand Award. You're right.
- All right.
- I know. Why would it be better?
- This is crazy.
Only the 1st and 2nd places will...
- get to spin the roulette.
- Only the 1st and 2nd places?
- Okay.
- The order is important here.
Who will go first?
Suk Jin said he'd go first.
- Really?
- When did I say that?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- He told me that.
- When did I say that?
- Before we got in here.
- When did I?
- You did.
- I didn't say that.
- He said that.
It would be disadvantageous
for me to go first.
- Will you go first?
- Jam Hugh!
Do I get any advantages?
- Advantages?
- Any advantages?
- I need something.
- Show us what to do.
- You're the oldest one here.
- I'll go first then.
- Okay.
- Are you serious?
(Jae Suk gives it a try bravely.)
He's cool.
I will give you
a chance to practice.
- A chance to practice?
- Okay.
I'll go first then.
I'll do it.
I want to go first.
(Jam Hugh hesitated
and lost his chance to practice.)
Hey, this is... It goes like this.
- I get a practice round, right?
- Yes, you do.
Let me push it back for you.
Look at this.
This is more sensitive
than I thought.
This is for practice.
- It's a practice.
- You can practice it only once.
Right.
It's red.
- It doesn't slide well.
- It's water.
- It's red.
- You should push it hard.
In this case,
the water balloon bursts.
If it were a real round,
the water balloon would've burst.
(If it were a real round,
the water balloon would've burst.)
Did you get the hang of it?
He has no idea.
(He has no idea.)
You should stop on yellow.
Are you trying it now?
No. I'll do it later.
- Why?
- I'm not doing this.
- You practiced it already.
No. I'll do it later.
Why?
I think we should decide
the order again.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
(I'll go first.)
- Do you want to go first?
- Yes.
- I knew it. He's Kim Grand Award.
- Kim Grand Award.
Kim Grand Award steps up.
He's setting a good example
after winning the Grand Award.
A gangster to a Grand Award winner.
He's "Protein Monster".
He's the Grand Award winner indeed.
His heart is like a soy sauce dish.
- You're amazing.
- Since it's the new year,
- You're the best.
- I should change my life pattern.
- I should stop waiting.
- That sounds good.
So I should stop there.
I can look at it, right?
- You can practice once.
- Yes. This is a practice.
(Kim Grand Award gets
to practice it once.)
(Booing)
- What was that?
- Why?
- Soy sauce dish.
(He was being cowardly
as he pushed the cart.)
The practice is over.
- You should start now.
- Start.
- Here I go.
Can I start?
- It should be twice as hard.
- It slows down quickly.
(Will he clear his name...)
(and show the dignity
of a Grand Award winner?)
It's water.
- Is it marbles?
- Okay.
(Falling)
This is the best one.
What was that? It wasn't so bad.
It just feels bad.
It just hurts your feelings.
He did a good job though.
- This is pretty.
- Okay.
- Feel them.
- Didn't I succeed?
- No.
- These are the marbles.
Who's up next?
- I'll go next.
I'm ready now, so I'll go first.
You should stomp your feet hard.
You're right.
Jae Suk, you should
start immediately.
(He's tried it before,
so he gets ready quickly.)
- All right. Here I go.
- Let's go.
Will he make it to
the whipped cream?
Let's go.
(Jae Suk got the hang of it
after his practice. What about now?)
(He commits a foul.)
(With Kwang Soo's assist,)
(the cart hits the wall.)
Oh no.
(He just committed a foul
by force of habit.)
Gosh, this is...
What's that?
- Oh no.
- Gosh, this is...
(The grasshopper is
covered with whipped cream.)
(That's ugly.)
You pushed it too hard.
What's that?
(The whipped cream pack
is good for skin-brightening.)
You can't do that already.
What should the rest
of the members do now?
(I think someone just pushed me.)
- You can't do that already.
- Are you all right?
(The victim is quiet while
the assailant has a lot to say.)
You shouldn't have
pushed it too hard.
It splattered all over.
It was too hard.
What should the rest
of the members do now?
- Hey.
- You pushed it too hard.
Didn't someone kick the cart?
You pushed it too hard.
You should've done it in moderation.
I mean, I thought...
I pushed it at the speed of Mach.
(He slid into outer space
through the stratosphere.)
- You just pushed it too hard.
- It exceeded the speed of sound.
(He experienced the speed of light.)
- It was fast, wasn't it?
- He's really strong.
Didn't someone push it?
- It just feels that way.
- You have strong legs.
Gosh, I'm afraid to go next.
Suk Jin.
We shouldn't commit
a foul anymore.
- "Anymore"?
- We can't play the game this way.
We can't play the game.
- No one should stand close.
- We should play the game.
I think someone kicked me.
Me?
Ji Hyo, did someone kick me?
No. You just pushed it yourself.
Is it just my feeling?
- It's your feeling.
- You just feel that way.
I think someone kicked it.
No, you pushed it too hard.
- Really?
- It was really hard.
- Did I push it too hard?
- Yes.
So you mean it's my fault.
How many times
do you have to ask that?
Next up is Suk Jin.
I feel sad as I see him
lie down on here.
Eternal youth.
I hope you live young forever.
You need to kick a little hard
to succeed.
- Okay. Got it.
- Okay.
It's hard to reach the wall. See?
(Will he succeed just like this?)
(Pushing the cart)
(Rapid acceleration)
Oh, no. That was so close.
(He couldn't hold back
and cheated again.)
Oh, no. That was so close.
(Whipped cream fell.)
He almost succeeded.
- Is this how we'll play this game?
- Come on, Jae Suk.
- Really?
- What's the point?
I'll just volunteer to get
the whipped cream on my face.
That's a shame.
I didn't know it was
a downward slope from here.
Oh, I think you're right.
It must be sloped here.
- It's flat. Trust me.
- It seems...
Did you push me?
No, I didn't push you.
I was standing over here.
- Really?
- You kicked too hard.
Hold on. We can't...
Let's all sit on the cart
from now on.
- Right. That's a good idea.
- Someone pushed me, right?
- Hey, someone...
- This isn't fair.
- He did kick hard.
- Did someone push me?
- No one pushed you.
- Suk Jin.
- Are you sure?
- Sorry?
- You kicked hard, Suk Jin.
- Did someone push me?
By the way, my hunch was right.
I didn't know why,
but I wanted to go first.
- Exactly.
- Isn't it strange?
- Right? It's strange.
- He kicked too hard.
Did no one push me?
I think someone pushed me.
I can't get mad
because I'm not sure.
Suk Jin, you never lose
your temper.
That's true.
True.
- He never gets angry. It's amazing.
- Exactly.
- I wonder why.
- Why do you not feel anger?
If I were him, I would've
gotten angry earlier at the opening.
Suk Jin would never get angry
over things like that.
- You see...
- He has a big heart.
- It's not that I hold back...
- Let's keep provoking him.
- my anger. I don't feel anger.
- Let's make him angry.
He has such a big heart.
He plays along with any jokes.
He's great.
I would've thrown my coat
and made a scene.
He's so cool. I would've sworn
harshly at everyone.
- He's a man with good manners.
- Indeed.
- He really has a big heart.
- Absolutely.
- You know I didn't get angry.
- Of course, we know.
- I wasn't angry earlier.
- He's so cool.
(He never swears or throws his coat
on the floor because he's angry.)
(He never kicks a chair
because he's angry.)
I just did it to make you laugh.
- I know.
- He should publish a book.
- Are Suk Jin and Jae Suk out?
- Yes.
- Hang on.
- Can't you give us another chance?
It's because you guys tried it
in the beginning.
You can give us
a disadvantage instead.
- Deduct our score, for example.
- Sit down, will you?
Jae Suk, we'll give you
another chance if you want.
- I'll try again.
- Because there was cheating.
Didn't anyone really do anything
when I tried it?
- No.
- No one did anything.
- Be honest with me.
- You should kick hard, Se Chan.
Are you serious or what?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
There wasn't cheating.
I guess there was.
There was cheating.
I didn't see anything.
If Bo Pil says he didn't see it,
he didn't see it.
Next up is Song Jeoktoma.
Here comes Song Jeoktoma.
She said,
"Here comes Song Jeoktoma."
She called herself Song Jeoktoma.
- That's good, Song Jeoktoma.
- She's so funny these days.
- Song Jeoktoma, good job.
- Where? Here?
Right, Song Jeoktoma. Let's go.
Push it hard, Ji Hyo.
- Hard? Should I push it hard?
- Yes.
- Ji Hyo, this isn't a practice run.
- Okay.
(Song Jeoktoma who runs forward
carries everyone's expectation.)
- Go, Song Jeoktoma!
- Ji Hyo, kick hard.
- Here goes Song Jeoktoma.
- Kick hard.
(Song Jeoktoma runs!)
(Where will Song Jeoktoma arrive?)
- Gosh.
- Oh, boy.
She'll stop at the water balloon.
She's the first.
She got the water balloon.
Gosh.
- Song Jeoktoma.
- It's a water balloon.
(The water fell right on her belly.)
- Hey, Song Jeoktoma.
- The water fell on her belly.
- On her belly.
- That was funny.
- Gosh. My belly...
- I told you to kick hard.
- It fell on her belly.
- Song Jeoktoma.
- It hit her belly.
- It hit my belly.
- I know.
- Did you hear the sound?
- Song Jeoktoma.
It fell right on my belly.
Good job.
(Following Ji Hyo,
Se Chan, Haha, and So Min tried!)
No way.
(Only Se Chan reached
the yellow zone.)
(Haha stopped in the green zone
and came in 2nd.)
Did he succeed?
If Kwang Soo succeeds,
the 1st and 2nd places
may be changed.
(He's lying down on the cart
bending his knees.)
It feels...
- Kwang Soo, go down a little.
- Go down.
- A little more.
Kwang Soo, go down. Go down.
- Hey, stop it.
- Go down.
- I'm just giving him a signal.
- That's enough.
- Stop it.
- To tell him to go down.
- That's enough.
- Darn it.
- Okay. You're almost there.
- Stop it.
You're almost there. Okay.
- Kwang Soo, come up a little.
- What?
Move up a little.
- Go back down.
- Gosh. What are you doing?
- Go down.
- We're trying to help you.
- So you won't hurt your head.
- Exactly.
- They're helping you.
- You should trust us.
- All right.
- Kick harder than you think.
Whenever you're ready.
- Trust me.
- Kwang Soo, kick hard.
(If he succeeds, he and Se Chan
will get to spin the wheel.)
I have a feeling that he'll succeed.
- Me too.
- I think he'll do a good job.
You may begin.
(Stretching out his legs)
- That's good.
- Because he has long legs,
he's at an advantage.
Look at him.
Because he has long legs...
He looks so ugly.
His face is annoying.
My gosh.
Kwang Soo has
a well-proportioned body.
(How well could he do using his
optimal physical condition?)
(Kwang Soo started moving
by kicking the board hard.)
(Will he continue the momentum
and succeed?)
Goodbye.
(Whipped cream fell on his face.)
(The whipped cream hit the mark.)
How could it fall right on his face?
It fell right on the target.
That was perfect.
- It was placed in the right spot.
- Nice.
- Good shot.
- Kwang Soo, go back to your seat.
Good shot.
You did such a great job, Kwang Soo.
- Go on.
- I did that, right?
- Yes. You did it perfectly.
- Yes. No one touched you.
- I'm next.
- Now...
Oh, right. Jae Suk will try again.
Okay.
- Right.
- We'll give you another chance.
- Of course.
- It wouldn't be fair.
- We won't touch you.
- Right.
He's a cool guy.
Here. You should wear a nose clip.
Hey, I don't need it.
- Hey, that's okay.
- Really?
- You're such a weakling.
- But if whipped cream...
- Stop it.
- Your nose will run.
- I don't care.
Jae Suk, go down.
- After the shoot, he'll say,
- Go down.
- "The cream keeps coming out."
- Go down already.
- Go down. Come on.
- Hurry up and go down.
- Go down. Put your head on it.
- Your head.
- Go down more.
- A little more.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Watch me.
- Are you ready?
- Go, Jae Suk.
Show everyone your accuracy.
- Watch how I do this.
- That's great.
Let's go. Oh, my.
He looks so skillful.
- I think he's calculating.
- Watch me.
- Watch me closely.
- Is he calculating?
- Watch me.
- He's playing with the cart.
- Watch this. Watch how I do this.
- He's playing with it.
- Here he goes.
- Watch me.
Let's go. Bounce off of it.
1, 2, 3. Go.
Here I go.
(Here I go.)
(How well will Korea's best MC
who focuses on laugh do?)
- Come on.
- What's that, Jae Suk?
- That's disappointing.
(Calm and quiet)
What's this? It's neither funny
nor impressive.
- That's disappointing.
- Try again.
- What was that?
- Gosh.
- He's the Grand Award winner.
- He said...
(He only pursued laughter,
but he failed to make people laugh.)
I'm so disappointed.
- Neither whipped cream nor success.
- It's hard to get what you want.
It was boring.
Why did he have to try again
if he would make it so boring?
He's disappointed in himself.
- Gosh.
- I'm so upset right now.
- Oh, man.
- It wasn't funny or impressive.
- Jae Suk failed.
- Is someone in there?
Bo Pil, edit this part out.
(The 1st mission ended
as he asked to edit his part out.)
Gosh. That was disappointing.
I'll announce the result.
- Se Chan is in the first place.
- Oh, yes!
- Haha is in second place.
- All right!
Let's move to the next location
to continue the second mission.
- Okay.
- It was disappointing.
- Shall I call your stylist?
- Hey, can you...
Can you bring
a fresh team uniform...
and a T-shirt to wear under it?
Because it's wet. Hurry up.
Thank you. Okay.
- It's sticky.
- Do we have extra uniforms?
I'll call your stylist again
to tell her to come back.
- What did you say?
- Come again?
- Who pushed you?
- I heard that you pushed me.
- Yes, I pushed you at the end.
- I know.
Who pushed me? Was it Kwang Soo?
Yes, Kwang Soo did it.
(They're passing time again
confirming the truth.)
It looks like your stylists...
stepped out together
and are coming back now.
- They'll be back in 5 minutes.
- 5 minutes?
- Really? We should wait then.
- Yes.
(So they started to wait again.)
- I didn't know.
- I was surprised...
Or would you like to continue
dressing like that?
Like this?
(Like this?)
Hey... My gosh.
- I wouldn't mind, but...
- Don't they look pitiful?
- Hey!
- Don't we look awful?
- You guys look great.
- Wearing this stained shirt?
- But you look great in it.
- Answer me.
- My gosh. We...
- Then can I borrow a towel?
- To cover the neckline?
- Okay. All right. Let's do this.
- You guys look great.
- Let's do this.
- You look great.
- Those shows you direct.
I'll see how successful
they will be.
It's not like that.
You want me to be on the show
when it has yellow stains?
You're on Running Man,
so put on your running shirt.
- "Running Shirt Man".
- Gosh.
- Did you throw up while lying down?
- Why is your shirt clean?
- The clothes are here.
They're here.
Where have you been?
- Why hasn't my stylist come yet?
- I brought you fresh clothes.
Where have you been?
I'm worried.
Could I be the only one
without fresh clothes?
Suk Jin, you should...
I'll change my clothes
so we can start the shoot.
- Wait.
- Run, Jae Suk.
Let's hurry up
before Suk Jin's stylist comes.
- Come on. Hurry up.
- Change your clothes.
- Hurry up and give me the shirt.
- I look like a beggar.
Let's hurry up.
I should hurry up to prevent
Suk Jin from changing his clothes.
This is driving me crazy.
- Hurry up!
- What did you do?
(He opened the door
and got surprised.)
- Come here.
- Ji Hyo is in there?
What is wrong with you?
- Ji Hyo is in that room, Jae Suk.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, why did you come in?
- You're unbelievable.
- You startled me.
- What's wrong with you?
- Goofball.
- Are you out of your mind?
- You punk!
- Beat him up!
- Come here.
We should teach him a lesson.
- She had her clothes on.
- We'll punish you.
- Why did you do that?
- Playful Child.
- He screamed after a long time.
- I'm relieved, Ji Hyo.
- He startled me.
- Ji Hyo, I'm relieved.
- You startled me.
- She had finished changing clothes.
- Gosh, seriously.
- He hasn't screamed like that...
- in a while.
- He screamed when he opened it.
(Screaming)
What did you do?
(Goofball may be playful,
but he has a pure heart.)
I was the one who should be
screaming, but he screamed.
(It was so funny.)
(Meanwhile...)
- Gosh, Goofball.
- What is taking my stylist so long?
Suk Jin, why are you wearing
a cartridge belt during a shoot?
- Oh, this is...
- Let's begin the shoot.
- I need to change my clothes too.
- He's wearing a cartridge belt.
- Kwang Soo, isn't that my shirt?
- My stylist, where are you?
(The white T-shirt war
between Kwang Soo and Suk Jin)
Suk Jin, your uniform just arrived.
What is it?
This is what I wore earlier.
- Just put it on.
- My stylist!
Just put it on, Suk Jin.
We'll begin the shoot now.
- Where are you, my stylist?
- Let's go.
- Where are you?
- Let's begin.
- Wait. I haven't changed...
- Good. The semi-real variety show.
- That's great.
- This is a semi-real variety show.
This is unfair.
You guys changed your clothes.
- That's why I told you to wear it.
- My stylist!
- The next mission is...
- Excuse me.
(The next mission is...)
(Suk Jin got surprised.)
- Hey...
- The semi-real variety show!
- This...
- Suk Jin, wait.
- This is true entertainment.
- Nice.
- Nicely done.
- Right?
This is of a similar color.
It's Chan Hee's.
- But...
- There you go.
Unbelievable.
(An edgy style is accomplished
thanks to his friend Chan Hee.)
I love it.
- But...
- I love it.
I look like an old man
who lives alone.
I love it.
- Live forever, Suk Jin.
- Nice.
What's that?
- It suits you.
- Live forever, Suk Jin.
It suits him, doesn't it?
It's time to spin the wheel
for the first time.
Se Chan and Haha,
you will spin the wheel.
If the wheel...
lands on the section
labeled "swap name",
you'll swap others' names for yours
on the big wheel.
The one that says
"absorb all seven names"...
means that you can swap out
one of their names each...
for your own.
Land on "2 left and 2 right
of the selected",
and you'll be able...
to swap the name
in which the big wheel lands on...
as well as 2 on its left
and 2 on its right.
Some will land you
at a disadvantage though.
If you're told to add the name
of the worst member,
the worst member
you selected earlier today...
will have his or her name
replaced with yours.
Suk Jin, stop trying to look good.
- Wear it like you did earlier.
- Why?
Why did you make it look cool?
I had it on backward earlier.
The tag was on the outside.
- Gosh.
- Are you all right?
- Are you okay?
- No, and it's no thanks to you.
I can still smell the whipped cream.
You should just head home today.
I will if you do.
- Go home.
- Haha, you're up first.
Okay, let's do this.
- Here we go.
- Sure.
(Haha can win the chance to change
up to seven slots with his name.)
(It can elevate
one's chance of winning.)
Let it be the worst one.
(It can elevate
one's chance of winning.)
Okay, here we go.
No way. Not that one.
(Which will it land on?)
Is it mine?
(He gets to change
three slots in his name.)
Three slots in my name!
(Everyone's disappointed.)
- How boring.
- Could it be more boring?
- He got one of the best ones.
- How bland.
Swap out the names
of the ones you hate.
- You've gotten all boring.
- The one you hate.
Yes, the one I hate.
Why would that be me?
You called me Mr. Dirty Mustache.
- He's right.
- Darn it.
Mr. Dirty Mustache!
- Yes, take out Se Chan's name.
- Right.
- Take out Se Chan's name.
- He called me B-rated.
There's one over here.
- No, it's better over here.
- Of course.
- Why are you taking out my name?
- Of course, he should.
Se Chan, go!
- Go.
- Let's go.
Nice!
Go round and round.
Land on the one with seven slots.
That's what you'd expect
from a comedian.
Go round and round.
(Every moment is exaggerated.)
Did you see that?
- He's just like Se Hyeong.
- You're more like Boom.
(Which slot will it land on?)
- No, not that one.
- Just one slot!
(He gets to change one slot
which is even more boring.)
He only gets to change one slot.
- This is what I get for winning?
- Nice.
Take one of Haha's slots.
But it's better to have
my name up here.
Why would you take my slot?
Of course, he should.
Suk Jin's the one you hate.
- Right.
- Take both off.
Why would you take my slot?
- Take Haha's.
- He has the most right now.
Haha has the most.
- Is this you being angry?
- Of course not.
"Of course not."
That was never the case.
- I'll take this one.
- That's the correct choice.
Don't listen to others
and go with your gut.
- Okay.
- All right. Nicely done.
(Se Chan takes the slot
that Suk Jin currently occupied.)
- How are we supposed to sit?
- What's this?
We should sit in two rows.
Here's the last game.
Just like the previous games,
this one will require your wits,
your concentration, and gut feeling.
- Again?
- Concentration too?
This is
the Joint Responsibility Quiz.
- Joint Responsibility Quiz?
- A quiz?
- I'm doomed.
- Gosh...
- Okay!
- Hold on.
- All right!
Don't touch me.
I'll make him be more active.
Okay!
He's showing more excitement now.
- That's the spirit.
- Let's do this.
None of this makes me angry.
- Okay!
- Get him excited.
- I'll get him to be more active.
- All right.
(Playing the air guitar)
Like this.
(Suk Jin becomes a human guitar.)
(Big Brother Big Nose
turns 60 soon.)
That tickles!
Suk Jin's loving it.
(Big Nose enjoys his new character.)
- There. You're all good.
- You can sit back up.
- You're to stay later on.
- All right.
Why are you only
saying that to me though?
Jong Kook can just go.
The last game...
will be played in groups of 2.
You and your partner
will answer the questions...
given by the staff.
Get it right
and you'll earn 10 points.
The team with the highest score
will win this game...
and get a chance to spin the wheel.
I should at least
get a chance to spin it.
Team play is required, right?
So we must answer one each.
I won't be favored then.
You can't discuss with your partner,
so choose your partner wisely.
- We'll select the teams then.
- Sure.
We ranked you...
by how well you did
on the quizzes...
throughout 2020 on Running Man.
- Really?
- You never know.
I'll reveal the ranking
starting from up top,
so raise your hand if you wish
to partner up with that person.
The person will choose
who he or she wants as a partner.
- Okay.
- Good.
Let me reveal
who had the highest score.
I should raise my hand every time.
Getting the most answers
on quizzes in 2020 was...
It has to be Jae Suk.
(2020 Running Man Quiz, 1st place)
(Here are the candidates.)
(Hyeongseoljigong...)
(Something complex)
(A complex area?)
(He's demonstrating
hyeongseoljigong right now.)
I mean...
(During the proverb quiz)
(Quail eggs)
(Pure and innocent)
(And you'll make it out alive.)
(Be a nutjob?)
(Despite their lack of knowledge,)
(we still saw hope in 2020.)
Getting the most answers
on quizzes in 2020 was...
It has to be Jae Suk.
- It's Yoo Jae Suk.
- Okay.
Me!
- It's Yoo Jae Suk.
- Okay.
(Everyone raises their hand.)
Everyone raised their hand.
Suk Jin...
- Everyone raised their hand.
- Me.
(Reluctantly)
Suk Jin reluctantly
raised his hand.
Suk Jin raised his hand too late.
That can happen, you know.
He was late to raise his hand.
Suk Jin raised his hand late.
- That can happen, you know.
- It can't.
- Suk Jin, lower your hand.
- Lower it.
- Lower your hand.
- We all raised ours instantly.
I raised it before
hearing your name.
Our team will be too hard to beat.
- We shouldn't team up.
- Exactly.
Jong Kook is on the smarter side,
- so we shouldn't team up.
- But...
I'll probably win
if I team up with Jong Kook.
- That's a high possibility.
- We'll be unbeatable.
You should take him then.
- 1 or 2...
- It makes better sense.
Take me or Ms. Toma.
Ms. Toma or...
I should team up Ssaebssaeb,
- Ms. Toma, or...
- Kwang Soo.
- I'm not as bad as them.
- Or Haha.
- But...
- I'm not as bad as them.
There's also Haha.
- What about So Min?
- He's not as bad.
- And Haha.
It'll be either
Ssaebssaeb or Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo isn't as bad,
- so take Empty Head.
- Empty Head?
- How cool of you.
- Empty!
I love your confidence.
Shouldn't you take me with you?
Team up with me,
and if I get to swap five slots...
(If I get to swap five slots...)
Three?
(Quiet!)
Take Se Chan instead.
I was wrong just now.
(Jong Kook's touch
had him lower his hand.)
I need to take a short break.
I need to rest a bit.
Okay, raise your hand!
- 1, 2, 3.
- Me!
- I'll take Se Chan then.
- Okay!
Why didn't you raise your hand?
- Why can't you raise your hand?
- You should've raised it.
- Kwang Soo...
- Call me Kim Jong Kook.
- I choose Se Chan.
- Okay.
(Pouty Mouth Brothers unite!)
I want to team up with Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- Okay, good.
I want to team up with Suk Jin too.
I want to team up with Suk Jin.
I want Suk Jin as my partner.
(Big Nose thinks about
who he should pick.)
In second place...
is Jong Kook.
(Embarrassed)
Why did you stand up?
Why on earth did you stand up?
- Sit back down.
- His legs must be numb.
I don't understand why you stood up.
Director Choi.
- Sit back down.
- Are you sure he's in second place?
We counted all of the questions.
- But...
- This is hilarious.
Why did you stand up?
In third place...
- is So Min.
- What?
- I'm in third place?
- Really?
Are you sure
you counted this correctly?
- I'm in third place?
- Are you kidding me?
- Me?
- Hold on.
I remember her getting
a lot of them correct.
- Suk Jin's in fourth place.
- That's not so bad.
Haha's in fifth place.
In sixth place is Kwang Soo.
In seventh place is Ji Hyo.
And in eighth place is Se Chan.
Why? I already knew.
Se Chan's in eighth place?
Jae Suk, isn't it obvious?
Don't pretend to be okay with this.
- What do you mean? I'm fine.
- You're upset with the result.
Why am I in third place though?
- I...
- Se Chan, my gosh.
- So raise your hand if you want...
to team up with Jong Kook.
(Those who wish to be on Jong Kook's
team will raise their hand.)
If you want
to team up with Jong Kook.
(He's in demand.)
- Because...
- Teaming up with me though...
- Suk Jin.
- We'll be a tough team to beat.
Don't choose those
of a higher ranking.
Come on.
He's right. Don't choose
anyone of a higher ranking.
- Then...
- Choose someone in the bottom.
The one in third place
should give others a chance.
- I'll swap for you.
- Hold on.
- Choose one of these two.
- Exactly.
Either Kwang Soo or Ji Hyo.
These two are my only choice?
Kwang Soo or Ji Hyo.
Choosing Ji Hyo will humiliate me.
Jong Kook, I got Jeoktoma right.
(She makes him know that
she got Jeoktoma right.)
- Jeoktoma?
- Jeoktoma!
That's what you're bragging about?
- Why can't I?
- "I got Jeoktoma right."
That happened weeks ago though.
Team up with Mr. Mullet.
- Okay, I'll take him.
- Okay!
It's a good choice.
Please put on your vests
and sit in rows.
All right.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Out of the many categories,
- I'll reveal the first one.
- Sure.
The first...
- will be the song quiz.
- Yes!
- I love quizzes like these.
- You're good at this, right?
Yes, I am.
- I'll count on you then.
- Two songs will play...
and you will name
the artists and titles respectively.
You will hear three seconds
of the first song's intro...
and then three seconds
of the second song's outro.
- The outro of the second song?
- Yes.
The intro and outro will be...
from two different songs.
When you say that you'll answer,
I'll choose the one
who'll answer first.
- Randomly?
- Yes.
You will name the two songs...
- in that order.
- Okay.
Artist or title?
The first one is to name
the first song.
(The Pirate Roulette Game
seems to have a purpose.)
- It must have a purpose.
- It seems that way.
We don't know...
- who he'll pick first.
- All right!
The first song must be named first.
Here's the first song.
(The first round begins.)
Cue.
(The intro of song A)
(The outro of song B)
- Let me answer!
- Okay.
(The intro of song A)
(The outro of song B)
(The two partners must name
song A and song B correctly.)
- I don't know the second song.
- Let me answer.
Ji Hyo.
"Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's... You know, this dance...
- Wrong.
- Let me answer.
- We were faster.
What's the song title, Ji Hyo?
- Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.
"New Face" by PSY.
- Let me answer.
- Wrong? Really?
"New Face" by PSY.
(Is it not "New Face"?)
"Gangnam Style" by PSY.
- Let me answer.
- Wrong?
("Gangnam Style" by PSY)
- Kim... You said the wrong one.
- Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.
(Team Yellow got a chance to say
the right answer they said.)
"Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's "Gangnam Style".
- No?
- Let me answer.
Is the first song wrong?
No, I'm sure it's the one.
No. We all got the first song right.
We got it right.
(I'm so lucky)
(To have found you)
(He's starting to dance.)
The song was so popular.
(He hummed the latter part.)
We used to sing this song
whenever we went to a club.
- We sang it so many times.
- Hold on.
- The song ends like that.
- Exactly.
- We danced to the song too.
- Yes, we did.
- That's why.
- A strange woman
- I think it's PSY's "New Face".
- I think so too.
(The outro of "New Face")
(The outros of Song B and "New Face"
are slightly different!)
(The outro of Song B)
- Let me answer.
- Isn't it "Gangnam Style"?
Haha, you go first.
PSY's "Face".
- What?
- What's that song?
You should've said
Kim Jong Seo's song.
- Is it an old song?
- Let me answer.
"Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's...
- "Hwitturu Matturu".
- "Hwitturu..." Gosh.
Let me answer.
(Whenever he puts out bait,
Kwang Soo takes it.)
- Hey.
- Wait.
Let me answer.
(At that moment,
Suk Jin raised his hand again.)
"Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.
What's the point
when I don't know the second song?
Can we hear it again?
- Let's hear it again.
- We need to hear it again.
(Song B still remains a mystery.)
(The songs will be played again.)
- No.
- This is driving me nuts.
(The songs are being played.)
- I think it's the correct answer.
- Jae Suk.
Let me answer.
- I heard off-beats.
Do you know the answer?
Let me answer.
Se Chan goes first.
"Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.
PSY's "New Face".
(He said "New Face" again.)
What are you doing?
Why did you even raise your hand
when you didn't know the answer?
How many times did they tell us
it wasn't the answer?
- Why did you do that?
- Why did you say the same song?
If you didn't know the answer...
They already told us
it wasn't the answer.
I thought you knew the second song.
- But he let me answer first.
- Hey.
I still think
it's the correct answer.
- Try to guess the song.
- I have no idea.
It has been changed.
- What are you two doing?
- They're discussing.
That's not allowed.
(They got caught right away.)
- You shouldn't do that.
- Is it not allowed?
- Hey, what are you doing nay?
- You knew that.
"What are you doing nay?"
(Hey, what are you doing nay?)
- "What are you doing nay?"
- I mean, what are you doing now?
- Pardon?
- You must've lost your mind.
- "You must've lost your mind"?
- What did you say?
Don't be disrespectful
to your senior comedian.
- Why would you...
- You were whispering to each other.
- Why would you speak thoughtlessly?
- I didn't speak thoughtlessly.
Suk Jin, you've crossed the line.
How dare you?
(Playing with his glasses)
(It's the best way
to stop a squabble.)
- He played with my glasses.
- Come here.
I hate it the most.
How dare you do that?
- You've crossed the line.
- I hate it the most.
- Is that so?
- How could you...
(Jae Suk stopped the squabble
by touching his glasses.)
- If you...
- Please sit down.
- You lose points if you discuss.
- I was so surprised.
- They shouldn't get to answer.
- Let me answer.
From now on, if any team gets
caught discussing,
- the team will lose points.
- Understood.
We're not allowed to whisper
to each other in any case?
- Correct.
- Let's just say it out loud.
It's obvious.
You really shouldn't do that.
- Here goes Level Four.
- I'll go first.
- You should.
- He picks the one to go first.
(The songs are being played.)
Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo, you go first.
- But we were faster.
- Me?
- Yes.
- 3, 2,
- Kim Jong Seo's...
One.
- Okay.
- "Beautiful Restriction".
Let me answer.
Okay. Jae Suk, you go first.
"Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.
"Up and Down" by EXID.
- Okay!
Let's get ready to dance.
(They're dancing a girl group's
dance excitedly.)
Gosh. Hey.
- That's not how they dance.
- What is this?
- This is...
- That's not how they dance.
It sounded like "New Face" earlier.
(Team Yellow Green
gained 10 points.)
This is their dance move.
(Song A is "Beautiful Restriction"
by Kim Jong Seo.)
(I am so lucky)
(With the legendary song
from 1996 as background music,)
(he's doing his frivolous
celebratory move.)
He's annoying.
(He expresses the joy
through silly dance moves.)
Gosh, I'm so upset.
Gosh. He's so...
- That was good. Great.
- We did great.
(So the top and bottom duo
gained the 1st 10 points.)
Up, down, up, up, and down
I thought it was
"Like a Cat" by AOA.
Here goes the second question.
Aren't there
any common knowledge questions?
- Level 1 of the 2nd question.
- Here we go.
I love this game. It's fun.
(The intro of Song A)
(The outro of Song B)
- I love this game. It's fun.
- Let's do this.
(The songs are being played.)
Let me answer.
- Jong Kook, you go first.
- I know the first song.
Sharp's...
3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer.
- I don't know the second song.
(Time's over.)
- Okay.
- Jae Suk first.
"Tell Me, Tell Me" by Sharp.
(Imitating the sound)
- I don't know the second one.
- Let me answer.
- Gosh. That startled me.
- What's this?
(At that moment...)
(Some objects fell from upstairs!)
- What's that?
- Let me answer.
- I don't know the second song.
- What's that?
(3 mysterious balloons fell
without warning.)
- What's going on?
- What is that?
(Confused)
- Happy birthday
- What's this?
(They're singing the birthday song?)
- To you
- Wait.
Is there something
inside the balloon?
- What is it?
- That was so sudden.
(Jong Kook popped a balloon
and found something.)
He found something inside of it.
There's something in the balloons.
- He found something inside.
- What is it?
What is it? What is this for?
- What is this for?
- Can we just stick it in there?
(The pirate roulette was placed
before the mission began.)
(The quick-witted Jong Kook
found it suspicious.)
- What is this for?
- Can we just stick it in there?
Hey, wait. Wait.
(Ji Hyo popped a balloon late...)
(and found a sword too.)
It doesn't fit in the slot. Come on.
What? It doesn't fit in the slot.
I think we got the wrong swords.
There are real swords too.
See? I popped the balloon
as soon as it fell.
- I'm sure it's the right one.
- Right.
(There are real and fake swords
hidden in balloons that fall!)
(Se Chan picked up the real sword
that Ji Hyo dropped.)
- I popped it right away.
- It's a real one.
- I'm sure it's the right one.
- Right.
- You can't try several times.
- You can do it just once.
You have just one chance.
I thought... I found one...
- I didn't know... I thought...
- It doesn't fit, right?
- You have just one chance.
- Does yours fit in the slot?
- Does it fit?
- It doesn't fit, right?
It fits in the slot.
Okay. Stop it. Hey, you punk.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Gosh, you.
Okay. Stop it. Hey, you punk.
(Kwang Soo broke it.)
(The one with a fake sword
caused trouble.)
You little...
- I'll stick mine in it.
- Okay.
If it pops out,
do I get something?
Then you'll win.
Stick it in and see what happens.
- Do we get a hint?
- Maybe there's a hint.
Please. Please come out.
- Please.
- Maybe there's a hint.
(Will Jae Suk's sword
make the pirate pop out?)
Will it pop out?
(Anxious)
It won't pop out anyway.
Just get it over with.
- Please pop out.
- He's right.
- We didn't put in many swords.
- So this is how it works.
- Gosh.
- I told you so.
So we need to stick a real sword
in the right slot.
The person who makes it pop out
will win.
- Okay.
- The quiz doesn't matter.
(Finding a real sword is
the key point.)
- They tricked us.
- This is so difficult.
You get 10 points
when you get 1 question right,
and you get 50 points
when the pirate pops out.
This is a faster way to win.
Oh, boy. I should find out
what the second song is.
- Now,
- They must be waiting upstairs.
we'll play Level Two.
Wait. I'm sorry.
- I think someone just farted.
- What?
- Why are you looking at me?
- Gosh, Suk Jin.
- Hang on a second.
It can't be just a fart.
Do you have a diaper
by any chance?
I'm serious.
- I mean...
- You guys...
- Due to extreme nervousness...
- He must be embarrassed.
- He was laughing to hide it.
- Honestly, I don't think...
- Don't try to set me up.
- it was you.
- Okay.
The breeze is coming from that side.
It wasn't me.
- Was it really not you?
- No.
- What are you doing?
- Gosh.
It wasn't me.
(She tries to submit evidence.)
- Ji Hyo, what's wrong with you?
- I didn't do it.
You've been saying I smell bad
since last week, but it wasn't me.
- It wasn't you?
- Trust me. I didn't do it.
By the way, you've become
so good at improvising.
It wasn't me.
(Precious Sisters saved their skin
with Ji Hyo's wit.)
Let's move on. Play the music.
(The songs are being played.)
(Glancing up)
(Everyone seems to know Song A.)
Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo first.
- All right.
- This must be the correct answer.
- I know this song.
(It's important to guess Song B.)
- This must be the correct answer.
- I know this song.
- I know this song too.
- I listen to it very often.
"Tell Me, Tell Me" by Sharp.
"One Man" by Kim Jong Kook.
Okay!
- This is...
- I can't believe this.
- This is unfair.
- I recognized it right away.
I did great, right?
(Song B with the familiar outro
is "One Man".)
(It's Jong Kook's hit ballad song
that won women's hearts in 2004.)
(This is the outro they just heard.)
- You can't play his song.
- He's right.
What's wrong with playing my song?
- Play my song too. "I Know".
- What's wrong with it?
It was advantageous for him.
Your song wasn't a hit song,
but mine was.
- What does that have to do with it?
- No wonder it sounded familiar.
Exactly.
(Balloons fall right then.)
(As soon as the balloons fell,)
It's a fake sword.
(everyone started fighting
to get a balloon.)
(Find a real sword.)
(Meanwhile, So Min got lucky
and picked up a real sword.)
(She's going straight to the pirate
roulette to stick the sword in.)
(He threw a sword in the air!)
- It's a fake one too.
- Hey, why did you do that?
(He spread fake swords
to confuse the other members.)
- It's a fake one.
- Is it a fake sword?
- I didn't find any.
- Like I said,
don't get too excited
when you find a sword. Okay. Good.
This is a fake sword, right?
It didn't pop out.
She stuck it right into the slot.
(Song Jeoktoma pulled it off.)
I did it. I made it pop out.
- We made it.
- This is unfair.
- I'm so excited.
- This is so pointless.
It's not bad.
We're doing all right.
We won 50 points.
- Nice.
- Oh, man.
Let's take our time.
Song Jeoktoma is the best.
- What a shame.
- Song Jeoktoma made it.
You see, this is like dog training.
I can't help but look up.
Just like Pavlov's dogs drooled
when they heard the bell ringing.
- Like dog training.
- It'd be funny...
if they throw balloons
in front of us.
I don't understand.
What was the point...
of ranking us for our quiz?
It's pointless.
You didn't choose him
for the quiz anyway.
Jae Suk.
You chose me for the quiz, right?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
We won a lot of points
thanks to the game.
(He helps to boost morale
rather than solving quizzes.)
Please sit down.
You're blocking Kwang Soo.
Was he hidden from view
all this time?
- I didn't know.
- Sit up straight.
No wonder. I couldn't see anything.
Kwang Soo is better suited
for group shots anyway.
Come on!
There's no such thing.
Here comes the next quiz.
Play the music.
(The third set of songs
is being played.)
(The intro of song A)
(The outro of song B)
(Ta-da)
- Hang on.
- I know the first one.
Then answer it.
(Jae Suk always
hits the nail on the head.)
I'm not sure about the first song.
Hold on.
Can you play it longer?
Level three. Play the music.
(Music playing)
I know this song!
You do? I know the second song.
- I know the song.
- All right. I know the second song.
- I know the 2nd song too.
- You know the 2nd one?
- We got the 2nd song.
- Let me answer.
"I Have a Girlfriend"
by Park Jin Young.
("I Have a Girlfriend"
by Park Jin Young)
- "A Winter Story" by DJ DOC.
- Let me answer!
- "A Winter Story"?
- Let me answer. I was faster, no?
Go ahead, Jong Kook.
"I Have a Girlfriend"
by Park Jin Young.
"Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
That's not it. Let me answer!
- Park Jin...
- Haha, go first.
Park Jin Young's
"That House Is Mine".
Let me answer.
- What kind of song is that?
- "My House Is Yours".
- Let me answer.
- I thought he knew.
"Your Baby Is Mine Too".
- All right.
- Let me answer!
- Se Chan, go first.
- You'll all be surprised.
- Hurry up.
- 5, 4, 3,
- It's Rain's...
- 2, 1.
- "How to Avoid the Sun".
- 3, 2, 1.
- Let me answer.
"Eve's Warning" by Park Mi Kyung.
- That's it! Jae Suk!
- You gave them too much time.
- They were too slow!
- That was fantastic.
Come on.
(They're showing
an unsightly ceremony again.)
Don't throw the balloons just yet!
Watch our performance first.
(Don't throw the balloons just yet!
Watch our performance first.)
(The audience turned their backs
on the stage.)
(Desperate movements
to attract their audience)
Give them to us now!
- Watch us, Suk Jin.
- Throw them now!
(Responding to their performance
without even watching)
- Gosh.
- That one was...
- Seriously.
- You counted for too long.
- Give us a break.
- You're playing favorites.
- Don't count the second one.
- We didn't discuss at all.
- Let's not count it. It's absurd.
- You went too easy on them.
- Don't count it.
- Who didn't know the answer?
Then let's have the Grand Award
winners play rock-paper-scissors.
- With whom?
- The Grand Award winners.
Gosh, you want me to play
rock-paper-scissors with him?
So if I win against Jong Kook,
everything will be settled?
That's not it. Listen.
If Jong Kook loses,
let's not argue against it anymore.
- Okay.
- Make sure to win, Jae Suk.
- All right. Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors
- All right!
- It's the best of three.
- Come on! Stop it!
- We lined up behind him.
- All right!
- It's the best of three.
(The class of the Grand Award winner
who goes back on his word)
- Stop it.
- He said they lined up.
We even lined up!
- Goodness.
- Yangsebari, come here.
(Yangsebari, come here.)
- At least two people should play.
- I'm sorry,
- but did you win the Grand Award?
- No...
- Then he's not qualified to play.
- That's not it.
He's just a research subject.
I'm one to get vaccinated first.
You're the first one
to get vaccinated?
- If you want to play, come closer.
- You have to win one more round.
If you want to play, come closer.
- If you want to play, come closer.
- You have to win one more round.
- Why do you want to play it?
- You must come closer.
Why do you suddenly
want to play rock-paper-scissors?
Come closer if you want to play.
- Just play one more round for him!
- I mean...
- If you want to play...
- Come this way.
- I mean, if you want to play...
- If you want to play, come closer.
If you want to play,
swallow your pride and come closer.
I'm going to you.
If you want to play, follow us.
- He can win it, you know.
- It's so funny...
- He can win it.
- Suk Jin is following them.
- Let's play it.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- All right, I won. I won!
- Darn it.
He lost. Goodness.
All right, I won against him.
- He even threw away his pride.
- How annoying.
The protruding mouth brothers
are getting ahead!
- Okay.
- Just give it to them.
- But this is absurd.
- Here come the next quiz.
- Okay.
Kwang Soo, you have to listen
to the rules.
Kwang Soo, you're in charge
of the balloons.
- Okay.
- This time,
you'll be playing
the Guess Who Quiz.
We'll show you a picture
of a foreign celebrity.
You'll have to guess
their full name.
- Gosh, this is...
- Okay.
You have to take turns
saying syllable by syllable.
We have to say the syllables?
For instance,
if I tell Haha to go first...
(Bill Gates)
That's how you should
say the answer.
(Correct)
(As soon as they heard
it's about foreign celebrities,)
(they gave up.)
For instance,
if I tell Haha to go first...
Let's catch the balloons instead.
- Gosh, this is hard.
- It is.
- We have to say the full name?
- Yes, that's right.
- We excluded the middle name.
- Okay.
- There's a middle name too?
- Yes.
(There's a middle name too?)
- Okay.
- Here comes the first question.
If you call your answer,
I'll tell whom to go first.
Then you'll have to say
the syllables right away.
- Say it right away.
- We have to call to answer first.
- I'll do that.
- Let's begin.
(Joe Biden)
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Haha.
- You know who he is.
- Mister...
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Jae Suk.
- Jo.
- E.
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead, Kwang Soo.
- Joe.
- B.
- Kwang Soo.
- Ji.
- Darn it!
- Let me answer!
Go ahead, Se Chan.
- Joe.
- B.
- I.
- Den.
Darn it, you punk!
- We stole their answer!
- Darn it!
- It's Joe Biden!
- "Joe Ji"?
(They missed the balloons because
they're busy dancing frivolously.)
"Joe Ji".
- What's happening? We missed them.
- What's happening?
- Darn it.
- That's our target.
- That's ours!
- Did you get them?
(A kick that has nothing
to do with the balloons)
- Kwang Soo, we got it.
- What was that?
- Have you lost your mind?
- We got it.
- Give them to me. Hand it over.
- No.
(Kwang Soo became a wreck while
giving the swords to Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook even uses his teeth.)
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo got the chance.
He even used his teeth.
- Hold on.
- Hey, we got it.
Who put their hands in my underwear?
Someone hit me from behind
regardless of the balloons.
We have to give it a try.
Hand me one.
It was already over.
Why did they hit me?
Gosh, how unlucky of me.
- Are you upset right now?
- No, I am not upset.
I forgive you
for not getting Joe Biden.
- I got this for us.
- Yes, you did.
- I forgive you.
- The pirate will pop up.
It's a relief that
you're contributing to our team.
- All right.
- This is worth 50 points.
- You can stick one in.
- Okay.
I forgive you
for not getting Joe Biden.
- Gosh.
- I think it will pop up.
- You have one, right? Let's go.
- Yes, I have one.
- It'll be a relief if they fail.
- Give it a go.
Go ahead, trust your gut.
- Have you forgotten who you are?
- No, I'll give it a go.
You're Lee Kwang Soo,
for goodness' sake.
I should've caught one.
Just stick one in indifferently.
He's timid with things like this.
- That's it. Just stick one in.
- He has no luck with it.
- Just stick it in.
- It didn't pop up! Okay!
- Darn it.
- That was...
- That was cheap of you.
- Let's go, Kwang Soo.
- All right.
- I'll catch the next one.
- Let's move on.
- This is too much.
- Well done.
- This is too hard.
I... We...
I knew he was Biden, but I didn't
know his last name was Joe.
We weren't in a good position
to catch the balloons.
Hey, his last name is not Joe.
There's no such last name as Joe.
Then what about Joe?
His last name is Biden?
Then is Michael Jordan's
last name "Ma"?
Do you even know who he is?
Do you even watch the news?
- I mean...
- Then is his name Biden Joe?
I know he's the president of the US.
- That's right.
- He's the president-elect.
You all know
who Joe Biden is, right?
I knew who he was, but I didn't know
his last name was Joe.
I didn't know his last name was Joe.
That's not it.
His first name is Joe.
- Biden is his last name.
- Oh, it's the other way around.
- Okay, I got it.
- "The other way around"?
(It's the other way around
for westerners.)
Why would you pronounce it
like that?
You should memorize
the name of the US president.
- President Joe.
- President Joe, got it.
"President Joe".
- Then how do we call him?
- It's not President Joe.
- It's President Biden.
- Biden? Okay.
Let's settle with that.
Here's the next question.
There are two ways
of reading his name.
We'll accept both.
Of course you should.
All right. 1, 2, 3.
(Abraham Lincoln)
- Let me answer!
- Kwang Soo, go ahead.
- A.
- "A".
- Let me answer!
- Go ahead.
- A.
- B.
- Let me answer!
- Why?
- A.
- B?
- Let me answer!
A.
- Bu.
- Let me answer!
- I got it!
- What?
- A.
- Why is it wrong?
- "A".
- B.
- Ra.
- Ham.
- Lin.
- Coln.
- Correct.
- All right!
But I said the same thing!
I said "A" also.
- He didn't say that!
- That wasn't correct.
- He didn't say it.
- A, "A".
A, "A".
You can't pronounce it like that.
You pronounce it that way!
It's just another way of saying it!
- You have to say either...
- Abraham, Abraham.
"A"!
Do you have a daughter in the US?
He probably said it
with a Texan accent.
My accent is a little Texan.
According to the Korean dictionary,
there are two ways of saying it.
Why did you pronounce it that way,
you punk?
- Good job.
- Okay.
- You know,
- We did a good job.
Kwang Soo and I thought...
- Who did you think he was?
- We were like,
"Is he Einstein?"
- Einstein.
- I couldn't see the photo well.
- Me neither.
It's confusing
since it's a black and white photo.
Empty Head.
The next person.
- There must be one Korean in there.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Let me answer.
Jong Kook.
(Albert Einstein)
- E.
- In.
- Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
- 3, 2.
- What?
- Let me answer.
- He wouldn't know the first name.
- E.
- In.
- It's incorrect.
- Let me answer.
Al.
E.
- Let me answer.
- Ji Hyo.
Al.
F.
Me!
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
- Al.
- Ber.
- Ji.
- Let me answer.
Jae Suk.
- Al.
- Ber.
- T.
- Loan.
- My goodness.
- Let me answer.
(Albert Loan)
(My goodness.)
(Empty Head's wrong answer
makes Jae Suk sigh.)
(The 9th financial sector,
Empty Head's Albert Loan)
- Jong Kook.
- Al.
- Ber.
- T.
- E.
- In.
- S.
- Te.
- In.
- Okay.
For goodness' sake.
What in the world is Albert Loan?
(What in the world is Albert Loan?)
Albert.
Do you think...
he is from the financial circle?
(The balloons drop.)
- Okay. Grab it.
- Here.
- We sat down.
- We get to go.
- Here I go.
- Come on, Se Chan.
What is it?
The chance is high this time.
- It will come up.
- There are four slots left.
It didn't pop up.
It was shaken up earlier.
This is driving me crazy.
Push in another one.
We need to win 50 points.
- Please let them fail.
- The last one.
- How many knives are left?
- None?
- Let's get over this.
- There are 7 slots.
- 1 out of 7.
Then the probability is
only 15 percent.
(Will they be able to win 50 points
with the last knife?)
Then the probability is
only 15 percent.
- Okay!
- That was insane.
(They succeeded to win 50 points!)
That's so annoying.
- I didn't want to see that.
- That's so annoying.
Nice!
- Nice!
- That's so annoying.
We won with Albert Loan.
Albert Loan sounds like
a stock item.
That's so annoying.
Is it a biotech stock?
Nice!
- You changed the seats, right?
- Yes.
Do you want to change the seats?
- Okay.
- Do you want to do it?
- Yes.
- All right.
Let's change the seats. Move.
Stay there.
- They changed the seats.
- Kim Grand Award,
- change seats with him.
- All right then.
Why did you listen to him
when you didn't listen to me?
- He is a senior.
- For goodness' sake.
- A junior who won the Grand Award.
- Come on.
Jong Kook didn't even budge
when he kicked him.
You won't budge?
He is a junior
who won the Grand Award.
So you won't budge.
It looks like you won, Suk Jin.
I am dusting the cushion.
(With the cushion, he touches
the Protein Monster's face.)
He is provoking Jong Kook.
(He provokes Jong Kook
in the most timid way possible.)
Thank you for sitting still.
(Thank you for sitting still.)
(He quickly thanks Jong Kook
after provoking him.)
We are set.
It will be funny if we end it here.
Don't air my apology.
I wondered what I should do...
if you got up. Thank you.
Suk Jin hit him
with his hands trembling.
(The man who gives people
hand tremors smiles.)
- All right.
- Let's go.
This time, you will have a quiz
on capital cities.
- Capital cities.
- Capital cities?
- Yes. Capital cities.
- Okay.
I am good with capitals.
- Let's go.
- When I give you the country name,
- say a syllable...
- Let's go.
- each.
- Come on.
The first country is...
- Mongolia.
- Let me answer.
- U.
- Lan.
- Ba.
- To.
(Will they succeed?)
- R.
- Isn't it "Ulaanbaatar"?
- Is it correct?
(They get the correct answer
right away.)
- Ulan Bator.
- It was too easy.
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
Is it?
- Ulan Bator.
- It was too easy.
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
"Ulan Bator" is a correct way
of saying it.
- Is it "Ulan Bator"?
- Yes.
Jae Suk, we got it right!
Is it "Ulan Bator"?
I have good pronunciation.
Ulan Bator.
- That was great.
- It was a clean answer.
(It looks like he is ready to get
permanent residency in Mongolia.)
How could he be so annoying?
- That was so much fun.
- The next capital.
(The next question)
- Iraq.
- Let me answer.
Haha.
(The answer is Baghdad.)
- Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo.
- What?
- For goodness' sake.
"What?"
- Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
- Ja.
No, no.
- Let me answer.
- Iraq.
B.
(You should know now.)
- Io.
- Let me answer.
Bio.
- Ba.
- Gh.
- Da.
- D.
Nice!
(Kwang Soo,
I can't believe you said "Bio".)
Nice!
- We are on a roll today, Jae Suk.
- Bio!
Here come
the protruding mouth brothers!
- Let's go! Nice!
- Nice!
- It was amazing.
- We are getting everything right.
I was the master of the quiz.
Jae Suk,
I am no longer Empty Head
when I am with you.
Kwang Soo's answer was so funny.
He said "Bio".
- Seriously.
- My goodness.
Baghdad.
The Iraq War.
I remembered the Iraq War.
You are doing great today.
I wasn't Empty Head.
Bio.
Here comes the next question.
Don't you know
"Baghdad and the 50 Thieves"?
That's Ali Baba.
It isn't
"Baghdad and the 50 Thieves".
It's "Ali Baba and the 50 Thieves".
(Even Suk Jin couldn't avoid
the Empty Head Syndrome.)
The next capital.
(The next question)
Se Chan is really good at this.
- Norway.
- Let me answer.
- Haha.
- Van.
Das.
("Vandas" is incorrect.)
- Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
I don't know.
Let me answer.
- Suk Jin.
- My goodness.
Let me answer.
Suk Jin.
- Van.
- Hel.
Sing.
- That's a movie.
- Isn't "Van Helsing" a movie?
- Is it a movie?
- Isn't it a movie? Let me answer.
- Se Chan.
- Wasn't it something like that?
Van.
(Annoyed)
- Is it incorrect?
- Are you going to be like that?
- Let me answer.
Jong Kook, go ahead.
- O.
- Sl.
Ram.
- What?
- Let me answer.
You said it's Oslram.
- Se Chan.
- What?
- O.
- Sl.
- Bi.
- For goodness' sake.
("Oslbi" is incorrect.)
(Sighing)
(Empty Head's stupid answers are
more harmful than acid rain.)
Oslbi.
(He said "Oslbi".)
- Hey. Hey.
- Oslbi.
What kind of an answer is "Oslbi"?
Let me answer.
- Oslbi.
- Give me a chance. Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
- Haha, go ahead.
- O.
- Sl.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- It was Oslo.
- It's okay.
- It's okay to make a mistake.
- "Oslbi" was a funny answer.
- Oslo.
When Oslbi falls
early in the morning
- Three umbrellas walk
- Side by side
I knew it was Oslo.
Here they come.
(Balloons fall at that moment.)
- All of them popped.
- For goodness' sake.
All of them are fake!
Okay, okay. I sat down!
(Okay, okay. I sat down!)
All right.
- You can't do that.
- We sat down.
- Hold on.
- So Min.
- We sat down.
- I received a tip-off...
about the bad odor that came...
- when the balloons popped.
- No, no.
No, seriously.
When the balloons popped...
No!
(When the balloons
popped earlier...)
Jae Suk,
why do I smell something sour...
after the balloons popped?
No, seriously.
- When the balloons popped,
- No!
- I smelled something sour.
- No.
- So Min.
- It really wasn't me.
- It wasn't me.
- So Min.
- My goodness.
- I smelled something sour.
We sat down.
- Hurry up.
- We need to catch the culprit.
There's someone who smells sour
among us.
Okay. Let's try this slot.
Yes!
(Team Red fails to get 50 points!)
This is the last question
on capitals.
- Hungary.
- Let me answer.
(What's the capital of Hungary?)
(Suk Jin yelled out,
but Haha looks uncertain.)
- Haha.
- Bu.
- Da.
- Pe.
- S.
- T.
("Budapest" is correct.)
My goodness.
- The balloons...
- What?
Where are the balloons?
(The last set of balloons fall.)
(It's a ruckus.)
Hey, these are fake.
No.
Jae Suk!
I figured it out.
It's the smell of someone's feet.
(So Min proposes a theory that
it's the smell of someone's feet.)
- Someone has stinky feet.
- It's the smell of someone's feet.
- Throw it.
Haha!
It popped out!
(He made the pirate pop out.)
Did it pop out?
(The pirate that popped out
and Team Yellow won 50 points.)
We were fighting.
Seriously.
Okay, okay.
Find the person who has stinky feet.
- Who is it?
- It isn't me.
- Find the person.
- Who is it?
- It isn't me.
- Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo's feet were stinky last week.
It isn't me.
It wasn't me last week either.
Let's have Bo Pil smell our feet
for fairness.
(Bo Pil becomes the judge
of stinky feet.)
That's right.
- That's right.
That's right. Bo Pil.
- Gosh.
- No!
- Stinky feet.
- Really?
(The member with the stinky feet
gets caught.)
- Good job.
- Come here.
Come here.
- For goodness' sake.
- Gosh.
(He was the root of the sour smell.)
- For goodness' sake.
- Gosh.
(The aged smell of his stinky feet
is on another level.)
Hey, it smells like fart.
(His socks get removed.)
- Take them off.
- Hey.
Throw them outside.
(Sniffing)
Hey.
- It was Se Chan.
- It was you.
No wonder the sour smell...
kept circling me.
(They finally found
the source of the smell.)
I wondered where it was coming from.
It was coming from my feet.
- I am sorry.
- Hey.
Don't you wash your feet?
Wash your feet!
- Gosh.
- It wasn't me.
So Min and Ji Hyo, I am sorry.
- It was the smell of his feet.
- That was funny.
I suspected you guys
for a short while.
It wasn't us.
I came to my senses.
- His feet don't stink now.
- Hey.
My goodness.
There we go.
Please sit down.
The result is out.
Haha and Suk Jin placed last
with 30 points.
So Min and Ji Hyo
placed 3rd with 90 points.
The other 2 teams are co-winners
with 130 points.
The two teams will have a question
of the Guess Who Quiz.
We got a lot of questions right.
We got a lot of questions right too.
For goodness' sake.
Don't be like that, Jae Suk.
You should know better.
You have won a good award.
- You will lose, so sit down.
- Sit down.
All right. I will be objective
with this question.
- Okay.
Guess Who Quiz.
(Mark Ruffalo)
Let's go.
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo.
(If they get it right,
Team Yellow will win.)
(Mark Ruffalo)
- Let me answer.
- Kwang Soo.
Hul.
(He was thinking about Hulk.)
Does that work?
No, he has a name.
His name is... Hold on.
(The Korean Hulk can't think
of the actor's name.)
- I don't remember.
- Let me answer.
Mar.
- Is it right?
- Kwang Soo.
- Mar.
- K.
- Wal.
Come on.
- Let me answer.
- I got it.
- Jae Suk.
- Mar.
- K.
- I don't know.
- I will answer. Let me answer.
- Do I go 1st?
- Kwang Soo should go 1st.
- Mar.
- You should have let me go first.
K.
Long.
Let me answer.
Kwang Soo, go first.
Mar.
Is he going first again?
- You should give us a chance!
- Hey!
- Mar.
- Mark.
- Back.
- Again.
- Let me answer. Mar.
- K.
Ru.
- Pa.
- Let me answer.
- I figured it out.
- Mar.
- K.
- Ru.
- Hey.
(They messed up the order again.)
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
- He doesn't know the answer.
- Kwang Soo should have gone first.
- Seriously.
- Phi.
Phi.
- Is it Mark Loan? No, no.
- Mark Loan?
Why do you like loans so much?
- Mark.
It sounds like macaron.
Let me answer.
- Mar.
- K.
- Ru.
- E.
Let me answer.
- We are set.
- What's the answer?
- Mar.
- K.
- Ru.
- Ffa.
- Lo.
- Okay.
Okay!
I knew the name.
- Ruffalo.
Mark Ruffalo.
- We did it. Okay.
- Mark Ruffalo.
- Jong Kook and Kwang Soo won.
- Okay!
- Mark Ruffalo.
- Decide who will spin first.
Okay.
- Mark Ruffalo.
- We fought well.
Ruffalo.
(The two Empty Heads'
quiz battle ends.)
Who will spin the roulette first?
(The benefit roulette lets you add
your name on the main roulette.)
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook spun
the benefit roulette.)
If you add it...
(The current number of name tags
on the roulette)
(Kwang Soo, Haha, Se Chan, Ji Hyo,)
(Jae Suk, So Min,
Jong Kook, Suk Jin)
It's time to spin the roulette
one last time.
The chosen one will have
his or her comment on each member...
and project objective
on the website.
- So this is the final decision.
- Yes.
The chosen one will also receive
the prize money...
of 100 dollars per name tag
on the roulette.
It will be like a writer's pay.
(Since Kwang Soo has 8 name tags,
he could win 800 dollars.)
(Haha, Se Chan, Ji Hyo,
Jae Suk, So Min)
I have a chance.
I have a few name tags on there.
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook have
3 name tags each!)
Why don't we have a staff member
spin the roulette?
Then Sun Myung should spin it.
- Sun Myung.
- Yes.
- This is the last roulette.
- Spin it hard.
Sun Myung, let's see it.
Here it goes.
- Sun Myung!
- Let's go.
- You followed me a lot.
Get mine.
It all depends on luck.
That's right.
All right! It's me!
It's me!
(Will it be Suk Jin or Jae Suk?)
- It's me!
- Is it Jae Suk?
Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk got chosen!)
- What is this?
- Hey!
He didn't put his name tag once.
(He got chosen
with 4 name tags on the roulette.)
- This is absurd. I feel cheated!
- How did this happen?
(Jae Suk's production objective
and comments will go up.)
This is ridiculous.
I feel so dejected.
Sun Myung, thank you.
How did this happen?
This show must be
Yoo Jae Suk's Running Man.
It suits the production objective.
It's 100 dollars per name tag,
so he will receive 400 dollars
in gift cards.
Jae Suk's production objective
and comments...
will go up on the website.
If you want to add something...
I will combine
what everyone wrote...
- and use the comments I like.
- Okay.
- My production objective was nice.
- What?
- My production objective.
- All right.
Please use "Mr. Dirty Mustache".
I will add it. Don't worry.
Se Chan's feet continue to stink
even without the socks.
He needs to wash them.
Come here for a second.
I will wash your feet.
No.
- You are a celebrity.
- My shoes...
(We introduce Running Man
in Jae Suk's own words.)
Variety shows are disappearing
these days.
Running Man is Korea's favorite
variety show that's been...
on Sunday nights for over 10 years.
The members play games and clear
missions with various guest stars,
as they go around
to different places.
Among various fun factors,
this show only focuses on laughter.
Open your eyes.
Fun on a big scale will come.
Open your mouth.
Laughter on a big scale will come.
Open your heart.
A great lesson will come.
(The photos Jae Suk chose...)
(and the comments are
on the website as well.)
Yoo Jae Suk. The Unchanging Goofball
of variety shows.
He is the pride of Running Man.
Ji Suk Jin.
The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong...
who pretends to love his family.
Kim Jong Kook.
In summer, he is Kim Nipple.
In other seasons, he is Enema Kim.
Haha. Mr. Dirty Mustache
who is the worst at acting young...
among celebrities
who were born in 1979.
Song Ji Hyo. Her real name is
Cheon Seong Im, Cheon Su Yeon.
Her nickname is Jeoktoma.
Lee Kwang Soo.
The butler of A-list actors.
Jeon So Min. The Crazy Poet.
Yang Se Chan.
Yang Se Hyeong's younger brother.
Has handsome gums.
Yoo Jae Suk's production objective
and the comments on the members...
can be seen
on Running Man's website.
(Running High School is located
deep in the mountains.)
(Band club,)
(dance club,)
(and student guidance club
have come together!)
(Teachers gave up on
these delinquents.)
(A transfer student is
the loyal man of the century!)
(Kim Bo Sung, Defconn)
(They are here to save
the delinquents.)
(Thanks to
the loyal transfer students,)
(the atmosphere and spirit
liven up!)
(But the club fund disappears.)
Get your acts together, okay?
(There is a traitor among them.)
(The loyal man explodes
upon hearing about the traitor.)
(The club time is their last chance
to check the loyalty.)
(Will they stay loyal
or betray their clubs?)
(What will be the result
at the Running High School?)
Let's go!
(Race for the Club Activity Money,
The Burning 18 Again)