(In a remote building,)
It's a prison.
(there's a gray prison.)
What is this place?
Gosh, it's a prison.
(And a curious edification phrase)
"Wisdom comes with age."
I've been imprisoned so many times after I became a celebrity.
(Inmates are imprisoned together.)
I know. I wear this prison uniform too often.
We just got here, but we're told to get in.
Are we getting in there?
Get in there, inmates.
Well...
Suk Jin is relieving himself now.
Is he trying to take out the toilet and escape again?
(They are imprisoned first without Suk Jin, who is in the restroom.)
- This is nice though. - Gosh, I'm in prison again.
(He notices something.)
What is this?
I guess we have to crack the lock combination to get out of here.
(There is...)
- It's an escape room. - Someone must be coming.
(a mysterious blue drawer.)
- It's an escape game. - This is an escape room.
Let me see.
(On the other side of the prison,)
- What is this? - This is nice.
There are extra prison uniforms.
(there are 4 prison uniforms.)
I bet there will be someone else.
There are more uniforms.
(She gets ready to sleep as if she's at home.)
So Min is planning something as soon as she gets here.
Isn't it that only the head of the cell can sleep?
(What's she doing?)
Is this what we're supposed to do?
Can we lie down like that?
(Is this your first time in a prison cell?)
Look at So Min. She's lying down.
Will you hurry, you brats?
(The oldest underling relieved himself.)
This looks fun. I like stuff like this.
You're the underling here because you came late, Suk Jin.
(The order of entering)
Look.
(Look at this.)
"Wisdom comes with age."
(Making fun of the underling)
Suk Jin, time comes with age.
Isn't it that "Disease comes with age"?
Farsighted eyes.
If you need wisdom, you should come to me.
(The oldest inmate is treated contemptuously.)
I guess we have some petty criminals here.
I know.
(They're likely to be the petty offenders.)
I can see a few.
I'm pretty sure you're a petty criminal.
(It's obvious.)
(Angry)
I'm not a petty criminal. I'm...
Oh, I see. You're an economic criminal.
(Oh, I know.)
Is he a white-collar criminal?
- That sounds perfect for him. - There was a misunderstanding.
I had to come here...
(Suk Jin caused economic confusion through reckless investment.)
- Are you an economic criminal? - due to some misunderstanding.
It's very unfortunate.
You know he's a gambler, right?
- What? - He's a gambler.
- Oh, that's right. - He's a gambler.
(Kwang Soo is a card shark with a nickname Jo Kka Chi.)
- A gambler. - I'm okay with that.
He's a member of a gang.
And he's his underling.
- I'm his henchman. - His minion.
(Se Chan is Jong Kook's minion.)
- "Minion"? - A gangster and his minion.
(Jong Kook is the boss of Tiger Moth Gang from Anyang.)
(A sudden skit)
If you took good care of it, I wouldn't have come here.
- I'm sorry. It's my fault. - My gosh.
(The underling is sorry.)
What about you? Why are you...
(What's So Min's charge?)
It was a crime of passion.
(She became a criminal of passion from a dating expert.)
A crime of passion?
Are you the woman?
It was a marriage fraud.
(So Min wounded men's hearts through a marriage fraud.)
- A marriage fraud? - A marriage fraud?
She says it was a marriage fraud.
Did you get caught making fake trades?
No. I was charged with housebreaking.
Housebreaking?
(Housebreaking out of nowhere?)
Why did you do that?
- Why? - Why?
- Why? - Why did you break in?
Did you break in to sleep in there?
- Housebreaking? - I did it to steal something.
(No one expected it.)
I had no idea. She broke in.
Why did you break in?
(Ji Hyo broke and entered the audience's heart with her acting.)
I'm a real estate fraud.
I didn't ask.
- The thing is... - What about you, 2365?
(What's Jae Suk's charge?)
I'm afraid I can't talk to you guys.
(Condescending)
- It's like... - He's a petty offender.
(It's obvious.)
It's about sensitive social...
(It's about sensitive social...)
and international issues.
(and international issues.)
(From the bottom of his heart)
That's ridiculous.
It has something to do with trade...
- and stuff like that. - Trade?
(He used all professional terms to look cool.)
I guess you did something good.
- Is that why you're here? - The thing is...
It's about trade deals between countries...
Do you know stuff like that?
(So you're a pickpocket.)
So you're a pickpocket.
- A pickpocket? - I'm not a pickpocket.
(Jae Suk picked pockets in Incheon Harbor.)
I'm sure that's what he is.
A guy like him usually gets beaten up in a movie.
(In the prison)
"Let's crush him!"
(He looks like he'll get beat up as soon as he enters the prison.)
- Then he cries. - Do you know anything about WTO?
Why are we locked up in here, by the way?
(By the way)
(The inmates are locked up in here without knowing the reason.)
What?
- Someone's coming. - Who's that?
(Who's coming?)
Stay quiet.
He's the prison officer.
(A prison guard shows up.)
- Stay quiet. - He's the prison officer.
A prison guard?
(He walks in with an awkward gait.)
- He's the guard. - He's the prison officer.
- What? - He is...
- My gosh. - He's the guard.
Jae Suk, he's my junior comedian.
- Stay quiet. - What?
(Isn't he the...)
It's not like you're here for fun.
He's the one who said Se Chan can't paint a big picture.
(He's the one who said Se Chan can't draw a big picture.)
That's right.
Oh, right. It's him.
- Is that him? - That's the guy.
- It's Gyu Jin. - Stay quiet!
(Comedian Shin Gyu Jin)
- Gyu Jin. - Right.
(Se Chan and Gyu Jin perform together in "Comedy Big League".)
Se Chan, when you're alone in Running Man,
you can't paint a big picture.
(You can't draw a big picture.)
(He told Se Chan the bitter truth.)
Hey, a weekend variety show is no joke.
- You seem ashamed. - I'm not ashamed.
(He drew a big picture and joined Running Man.)
Keep quiet.
Se Chan who can't paint a big picture should be extra careful.
- Me? - Be careful.
(Officer Shin is strict only on one person.)
Okay. I will.
So you told Se Chan that he can't paint a big picture the other day.
- Yes, I did. - Right.
"Yes, I did." He sounds polite to Jae Suk.
(The sudden question breaks the prison skit.)
- Wasn't it from the script? - He's doing an interview.
(It wasn't in the script.)
Are you feeling nervous around Jae Suk?
Can I stop playing my role here?
(Confused)
No, you can't.
(Tough hazing on a variety show newbie)
He needs an interview. You should talk to him.
I'll keep playing my character.
How would you describe Se Chan?
He always asks if I had a meal whenever we meet.
(Se Chan always took care of Gyu Jin warmly.)
And he offers good ideas when we plan our skit.
He's very nice.
(What about as your senior?)
What about as your senior?
I don't think there's anything I can learn from him.
(There's nothing I can learn from him.)
(Se Chan feels hurt from his straight talk.)
- Then... - Hey... Excuse me, Officer!
Forget everything. What do you think of him...
from the perspective of a viewer of Running Man?
(How is Se Chan as a viewer of Running Man?)
As a viewer of Running Man...
For the cast members of "Comedy Big League", Se Chan is...
- almost like Jae Suk. - Really?
- Yes. - Hey, hey, hey.
(Yang Se Chan, Yoo Jae Suk of "Comedy Big League")
Don't say... I mean, Officer.
- Do you really act that way? - No.
He has absolute power over us.
(Absolute power of "Comedy Big League")
- Really? - Yes.
As a matter of fact, he has a lot of experience.
(He can't hide his joy with his bulging mouth.)
He's their senior by many years.
But seeing him on Running Man,
he's almost just like me.
He's almost just like me.
(Se Chan's junior comedian realized he was a big fish in a small pond.)
Hey, did you plan all this or what?
(Feeling a sense of crisis)
That guard is trying to trample on me.
(Composed)
I mean, just like me,
- Of course. - I can see anxiety in his eyes.
(Officer Shin feels more relaxed thanks to Se Chan.)
- I'm worried. - Anyway, Officer.
- Yes? - Is there any tip...
(Getting back into character)
on how we should behave here?
Of course, you should get along well with each other.
(Officer Shin's "Prison Playbook")
- When the newbies arrive, - Yes.
you should give them the clothes in these baskets.
(Give out the prison uniform to the newcomers.)
- We'll give the uniforms to them? - No wonder we have a changing room.
- Give them the uniforms, - Yes.
- and inform them, okay? - Understood.
(Understood)
Newbies, come on in if you're ready.
- Who could they be? - Are they here?
(Who are the cute newbies?)
- Who are they? - Are they coming in right away?
- Oh, my. - Who are they?
- They're coming... What? - I heard that actors...
- Young Min is one of them. - Who?
- And Ji Seung Hyun too. - Oh, they're...
(The newbies walk in feeling nervous.)
- I know them. - Ji Seung Hyun.
- Hello. - Oh, my.
(Welcoming the newbies)
- Yong Ji, hi. - Hello.
- Oh, my. Hello. - Hello.
- Hello, hello. - Oh, my. Hello.
(The irreplaceable scene-stealers)
Why did a lawyer come here?
(The 4 popular actors)
- Why would a lawyer end up here? - Hello.
(Ha Do Kwon, Ji Seung Hyun, Kim Yong Ji, Kim Young Min)
First, please introduce yourself.
(It's time to introduce the newbies.)
You're still wearing this when "Hot Stove League" ended long ago.
(Ha Do Kwon, from "Hot Stove League" and "The Last Empress")
(He made a big impression playing Kang Doo Ki on "Hot Stove League".)
No matter how well you throw,
you get criticized at least six times a year.
But this year,
I'll make sure to get just four.
(Ha Do Kwon, the great supporting actor)
Dreams.
(I am here...)
I am back!
(on Running Man!)
"Hot Stove League" ended long ago. Why are you still wearing it?
- He must be into his character. - Exactly.
I'm still practicing baseball hard.
(Calm)
- Are you still practicing? - Yes, I am.
He has such a great voice.
(Baritone tone)
He has a great voice.
Actually, I think he looks like a prison inmate...
- more than anyone of us. - Exactly.
(His looks perfectly suit the prison.)
Right? You see, he looks like...
an inmate who fights against Jong Kook over power.
(I can imagine.)
An inmate who fights against Jong Kook over power.
(Ha Do Kwon Clan versus Kim Jong Kook Clan)
That sounds plausible.
(Inciting them to fight)
- He looks upset. - Indeed.
I'm going to get just one person.
(Provoking)
- Oh, gosh. Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
I'm going to get just one person.
(He declared war fearlessly.)
- It's been a while... - That's good.
(Their match is already exciting.)
- since Park Sung Woong came here. - I like this.
Anyway, do you guys know...
- what your crimes are? - Yes.
(By the way...)
(What's Do Kwon's charge?)
Why are you here?
I'm imprisoned because I make people around me...
(Ha Do Kwon, for harming the traditional custom)
feel unnecessarily nervous with a menacing face.
But your face looks cute. I don't understand.
He doesn't look menacing.
(Jong Kook provokes him back.)
Look how he chuckles.
- You know, - He looks just cute.
- they already created tension. - He says you look cute.
He looks just cute. Why?
- This is real. - Yes.
But he lives in Anyang,
(Trying to get familiar)
and I used to live in Indeokwon, Anyang.
- Really? - They suddenly became friends.
- Are you younger than Jong Kook? - How old are you?
(Jong Kook suddenly likes him.)
(Active)
You're older than me. You were born in 1976, right?
- I was born in 1977. - Really?
(Jong Kook loves anyone from Anyang.)
Which school did you go to?
I went to school in Gangnam.
(Disappointed)
Oh, in Gangnam?
- Then... - Then he wouldn't like you so much.
(He passed in terms of regionalism, but not in terms of school ties.)
- His voice is so charming. - He values his school ties.
- Any school in Anyang. - He's here to live.
(Regionalism and school ties are what Jong Kook counts.)
- That's why he's here. - Jong Kook really is a big fan...
- of regionalism and school ties. - Exactly.
(A big fan of nepotism)
- I'm a big fan. - He likes people from his hometown.
(Do Kwon failed to be a part of Jong Kook's connections.)
- That's right. - Also, he...
- majored in vocal music at SNU. - Really?
(And...)
(Really?)
- Really? - Yes.
- At Seoul National University? - Oh, Seoul National University.
- What is it? - Nothing.
(He suddenly feels a distance.)
- You see, - Yes.
the point we should pay attention to is...
- that he majored in vocal music. - Oh, I see.
(He stopped listening after "Seoul National University.")
- Not the university. - It's a great university.
- He feels different from us. - His image has changed.
(He lost his fighting spirit.)
He feels completely different now.
Do Kwon, could you...
(Since we're at it...)
sing a song for us?
The weather was nice on my way here.
(Watching the clear sky during the rainy season,)
- It was sunny. - A song to sing on a day like this.
- "O Sole Mio" would be great. - "O Sole Mio"?
(it reminded him of "O Sole Mio".)
- "O Sole Mio". - I'll sing the climax.
He has such a great voice.
I've never seen anyone who graduated from SNU.
(Do Kwon's powerful voice made their jaws drop.)
(His gentle voice is resonating in the prison.)
He's amazing.
(His enchanting voice wins hearts of women.)
(The song reached its climax!)
This is the important part.
(Breathing out heavily)
(He has goosebumps.)
(The dignifying, mesmerizing voice)
- That was amazing. - And it's early morning.
- In this early morning. - I practiced a little.
(Even a singer is impressed too.)
(The charming actor who can act and sing)
It's so early. I bet his voice hadn't even been warmed up.
- He's incredible. - My gosh. That was...
(Followed by Do Kwon and his fascinating performance...)
- That was absolutely beautiful. - Next up is...
Ji Seung Hyun.
(He starred in "The Gentlemen of Wolgyesu Tailor Shop" and "Wish".)
Hi. I'm Ji Seung Hyun.
As you must know...
- Did you get hit? - I got hit here once.
(He's the actor who created the legendary scene from "Wish".)
He says he got hit.
What could be the most painful, brutal way of taking my revenge?
(He's good at emotional scenes as well as action scenes!)
To make you live with guilt for the rest of your life.
(Ji Seung Hyun, the popular scene-stealer)
- When I was in Busan, - Yes.
I was the leader of a gang group called "Monster".
(From the movie, "Wish")
- He still has that vibe. - That's exactly how he spoke.
- He still has that vibe. - He spoke like that in the movie.
(I remember.)
Awesome.
(Ji Seung Hyun is charged for joining a gang group)
- That was the name, right? - Yes.
- I'm getting nervous. - That's right.
- Seung Hyun has met... - Yes.
(Seung Hyun also knows Ji Hyo?)
Ji Hyo before. Right, Seung Hyun?
We both starred in "Lovely Horribly".
(They both starred in "Lovely Horribly".)
- "Lovely Horribly". - So did I.
- I also worked with So Min. - So Min too?
- She can't remember that. - In the drama, "Maids".
(The drama)
(Laughing)
(She really...)
- She didn't know. - "Maids".
(She told me...)
She said she had never met him before.
Apologize to him now.
(I apologize for not recognizing you.)
- I'm sorry. - So Min.
(Criticizing)
How did you not know when you starred in the same drama?
She sees only what she wants to see.
(We'll get familiar with each other.)
- I remember that now. - She forgot about him.
However...
Seung Hyun, is this your first time on a variety show?
I appeared on a variety show that you hosted.
- On another channel. - You mean, "Happy Together"?
- Hold on. He didn't remember that. - Did you just realize that?
(He got caught. He failed to get away with it.)
- He didn't remember that. - Hold on.
- You didn't remember that, right? - Jae Suk.
(Criticizing him back)
- I don't think he remembered. - He usually remembers his guests.
(You scolded me just now.)
I can't believe you.
I mean, he took a photo with him like they were friends.
(1-day Friendship Photo)
- He changed his hairstyle. - You shouldn't be like this.
- He does look different though. - I was so surprised.
(Removing the misunderstanding thanks to a photo from the past)
Next up is...
Kim Yong Ji.
(She starred in "The King: Eternal Monarch" and "Mr. Sunshine".)
(She pulled off a double role in "The King: Eternal Monarch".)
Who is Myeong Na Ri? I am Myeong Seung Ah.
(Kim Yong Ji, the rising star)
I work at the public affairs office.
(She stayed by Yoo Yeon Seok's side quietly in "Mr. Sunshine".)
(Her crime is enchanting the viewers with her irresistible charms.)
- She looked like Japanese. - Indeed.
(Yong Ji played a Japanese character in "Mr. Sunshine".)
- I thought she was Japanese. - Are you...
actually fluent in Japanese?
(A short answer)
- I can't speak Japanese. - Not at all?
- It was just her role. - I see.
(Trying to talk to her again)
- Have you ever studied overseas? - Yes, I have.
- Where? - Oh, my.
(Another short answer)
In Canada.
- That suits her. - Really?
- No wonder. - In Canada?
I have a feeling that she's good at speaking English.
- She looks like a foreigner. - We were talking about Japan.
(All of a sudden...)
Why did you say "No wonder"? Based on what...
- What made you think that way? - Just...
(He responded as a habit as the interview wasn't going well.)
- Don't say anything. - She looks like Canadian.
- Why would you ask that? - Just let me continue.
- I was starting to interview her. - "No wonder."
(The national MC's know-how: Say, "No wonder," when things are tough.)
- Don't say anything. - She looks like...
- "No wonder." - I knew it. No wonder.
(If you studied in Canada...)
You like maple syrup, right?
- Yes, very much so. - "No wonder."
- "No wonder." - "No wonder."
(The magical comment, "No wonder.")
- It suits her. - In Canada.
"No wonder."
(Somehow, it feels like she'll do well on the show.)
All right. Following Yong Ji,
our next guest is Kim Young Min.
(He starred in "A World of Married Couple"...)
(and "Crash Landing on You".)
- Do you think that can threaten me? - I wouldn't call it a mere threat.
(He played the worst husband in "A World of Married Couple".)
(His crime is stealing women's hearts with his fatal charms.)
That day, you liked it.
He played a husband who cheats on his wife many times...
(He pulled off the character who's always having affairs.)
- in "A World of Married Couple". - I see.
But in real life, he got married after dating for five years,
and he's been married for 13 years.
(He's been married for 13 years.)
What kind of husband are you in real life?
(In reality...)
I'm an obedient husband.
- Really? You are? - Yes.
(The drama)
Are you more like your character in the drama or the way you are now?
He wouldn't be like that character.
(He bursts out laughing.)
- Wouldn't it be weird if he was? - That's not what I meant.
(Criticizing him for not thinking before asking)
- Listen to me. - What kind of question was that?
- That was a bad question. - You're the worst.
(Are you serious?)
- You can't just pretend like that. - I mean, what do you even mean?
(Being ridiculous)
Trust me. He must have a little of that side in him.
(His question got lost on the way.)
- That's ridiculous. - That can't be true.
(No way.)
(He keeps being ridiculous.)
- How else could he do it so well? - Suk Jin.
- Gosh. That's ridiculous. - Think of what he did in the drama.
(The interview ends abruptly due to Suk Jin's poor question.)
That was just acting.
By the way, there's a song called "There She Is".
(Changing the subject)
- I'm so happy you're here - I know that song.
(The song you always have to sing at a karaoke place)
- When we go to karaoke, - Yes.
- this song is always the highlight. - We sing at the climax.
(Why are you bringing that up?)
I guess you sing the song often. Is it your favorite song?
(His main point)
Yes, it's one of my favorite songs.
(Shy)
I see. "There She Is" is very...
One day
(Leading the song)
- She left me - She left me
(He suddenly starts dancing.)
(No one expected him to start dancing.)
He's so cute. He's so adorable!
I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy you're here
(He's dancing like he's being electrocuted.)
(I love funny dances for variety shows.)
I'm happy you're here
(The 2nd electrocution)
She's back, she's back, she came back to me
(It's hard to breathe.)
That's his true color.
(A culture shock)
(After letting out his excitement to the end,)
That's his true color.
(he's back as the shy Young Min.)
- That's the real him. - That's the real him.
- That's his true color. - Which is?
This is the real him.
(He changes in a flash.)
- I'm so scared. - This is the real him.
- I disagree. - No. Listen.
(Looking very peaceful)
- It's his character in the drama. - No way.
- He's faking it right now. - Jae Suk, this is the real him.
(Smiling)
(His dance still lingers.)
I'm happy, I'm happy
- He acted so playful suddenly. - He reminds me of Im Chang Jung.
(Young Min has shown them an unexpected side of him.)
- "Dance with Wolf". - That was unexpected.
Okay. All right.
- We will... - You have to change your clothes.
(Getting back into character)
(Now, it's time for them to become newbies.)
You should get changed.
Newbies, please go and change your clothes.
(While the newbies get changed...)
(Going in)
- Stop it. - What?
- I'll be back shortly. - Where are you going?
(This inmate goes in and out of the bars.)
You shouldn't do that. Come back.
(Defending the universe of Running Man)
You should immerse yourself in your character. Come on in.
(It's like she's in her own house.)
What is this for?
- To hang clothes. - Hang your bag here.
Hang it there.
(Strutting)
- No, I won't. - Why?
- No, someone... - Trust me.
(While So Min becomes a bad inmate...)
There must be a thief...
(The newbies step out awkwardly.)
- among the inmates. - They're here.
There's a woman too.
- They are the newbies. - Okay.
(We are the newbies.)
Shall we begin?
(The minion)
- All of a sudden? - Good. This is nice.
(The newbies detected the strange atmosphere.)
Do you want hazing or something?
(They start to shake the blanket.)
- They are good. - I'm immersed in my role.
There you go.
It's stirring up dust!
Why are you doing it when there are people around?
We will work hard.
(They try really hard, but they are still awkward.)
- They are different. - They're good.
They're different indeed.
It looks perfect for him.
(It doesn't seem like the first day for this person.)
I know.
It looks like he's done this before.
It doesn't seem like his first day.
(Everyone stares at him.)
Do Kwon? Okay.
- Good. - Well done.
(The thief is standing in the middle.)
- What are you doing here? - Come here.
What are you doing?
- Why are you acting like the head? - He wants to be the head.
(He tries to act like a leader among the newbies.)
Don't pretend like you're the head here.
I just thought they were being quite obedient.
All right. Are you done changing your clothes?
Yes.
- You're back, Officer. - He's back.
You come here quite often.
- What do we do now? - We get to see you a lot.
There will be more than that. You'll see.
(Mumbling)
(His seniors are pleased.)
- He's good. - You guys look good in the uniform.
- Okay. - And you look beautiful.
(The novice guard is finally more relaxed now.)
So you know we're having the work program at 3pm.
(The work program is...)
(scheduled for 3pm.)
(Work Program)
- What's that? - What's the program for?
Here's a brief description of the program.
You will have a tough time so you won't commit a crime again.
(It'll be so tough that you'll never think of committing a crime again.)
Make sure to brace yourselves.
There's a rumor that Se Chan's mouth became like that after the last one.
(First time hearing it)
- I bet he got hit. - Did I get hit in the mouth?
- He got hit in the head. - You're doing this well.
(Praising)
- It was pulled out. - That's because you got hit.
(He looks more relaxed at Se Chan's compliment.)
That's why it's sticking out.
You're just like me.
- Did he get hit as well? - Don't you make fun of me.
Is that why?
It grazed his mouth.
(As they all burst into laughter, he feels at ease.)
I got hit, and you were just grazed.
(The one who was grazed, The one who got hit)
- Yours is sticking out a lot. - You're right.
- Don't even try to escape. - Okay.
(Don't even dream of escaping.)
And... Hang on.
(The novice officer picks up something.)
- What's that? - What?
- This is... - Do we have rules here?
- We have rules. - Gosh, we have partners.
(Rules of prison?)
- What? - These are the rules.
(Rules of Running Prison)
(1. Each inmate has a partner.)
- "Each inmate has a partner." - We have partners?
(2. If my partner benefits, I will benefit.)
I guess that's why we have numbers on here.
"Once my partner is eliminated, I get eliminated as well."
(Once my partner is eliminated, I get eliminated as well.)
I think we're already paired up with partners.
- What's going on? - So who's my partner?
(There are partners among inmates?)
- Do we not know that? - We don't.
- The right one? - My number is 22.
(The crowd is stirred at the news of partners.)
- I think it's the left one. - My number is 10.
We are partners.
- All right. - Is this it?
- It's a secret. - Is it 02 "diarrhea"?
- I bet there's a secret. - Are we partners?
It says 02 "diarrhea".
(Is the inmate number related to one's partner?)
- I think you're my partner. - No.
It says farsighted eyes.
You can have a chat later.
Keep quiet.
As you guys know, you should...
(He starts to recite his given lines.)
- I think you're my partner. - No.
(Loud)
- It says farsighted eyes. - What's your number?
(I still have my lines to say.)
- Farsighted eyes. - All right then.
Let me see.
I'm speaking.
(Uncomfortable)
The officer has something to say.
- I'm still talking. - You're number 10.
I'm sorry.
Se Chan! I'm reading my line.
Why is he yelling at me only?
- He wants to rely on you. - He's yelling only at me.
(The only target for the novice officer)
I'm trying to help you paint a big picture.
- Are you trying to help me? - Sure.
(He volunteers to help Se Chan draw the big picture.)
Why are your eyes so red?
- That's because he couldn't sleep. - He couldn't sleep last night.
(I couldn't sleep because I was too nervous.)
His eyes are red because he lacks sleep and feels nervous.
(Blushed)
- I know what it is. - So it's not makeup.
No. Gyu Jin, please continue.
This is a letter, but it doesn't say a sender or a recipient.
I don't know why we have it here.
(A mysterious letter has arrived at the prison.)
- What's that? - Let me see.
- Mr. Yang. - Me?
He's helping you to paint a big picture now.
(The officer asks only Se Chan to come with him.)
- It's for a big picture. - Are you serious?
(Confused)
- Follow me. - Am I becoming a star?
- It's for your big picture. - What's going on?
What is he doing?
I'll make you a star. Come here.
What?
(A birth of a star before their eyes?)
- You'll make me a star? - You'll be a star.
- What's going on? - He's going to be a star.
Can I leave, Jae Suk?
(He locks the door after he takes Se Chan to the guard's seat.)
- Go. - He just left.
- What now? - Stay right there.
- Don't turn around. - Maybe he'll get a mission.
(What is he doing there?)
- Maybe he'll be a spy. - You're not supposed to look.
- What? - I can see you from there.
Why do I have to be here?
(You can clearly see everything.)
I can see him from there.
- There must be something. - This isn't a big picture.
He's helping you paint a big picture.
(The gallery expects a big picture.)
There must be something.
I think something's going on.
(As the officer places the letter in the drawer...)
I think there's something important.
- It says 34. - Can I take a look?
(So Min and Ji Hyo silently approach him.)
Don't turn around.
Ji Hyo and So Min, come back here.
(He feels flustered...)
(as the inmates approach him.)
- What's this supposed to be? - Don't look at this.
(Stealing)
- "731". - Gosh, no.
(Shocked)
It's not fake. It's really dangerous.
Bring it back.
(Abruptly flustered)
- Take it from her. - It's real.
(His eyes get even redder at the unexpected situation.)
- What's wrong with her? - Don't act spontaneously.
- Gyu Jin is flustered. - What is she doing?
- What's wrong with her? - What is she doing?
(The thug inmate flusters the novice officer.)
So Min.
He's a rookie comedian.
(I want to escape.)
- Give it back to me. - Don't act spontaneously.
- Give me that. - What's wrong with her?
(He walks like a robot as he's flustered.)
- Why is she being like this? - It's not an imitation.
(He said this almost 10 times.)
- Give me. - Give it back to him.
(Stealing the club wasn't on the script.)
Don't be so spontaneous. He's a rookie comedian.
He'd be flustered.
He has his own script.
Why are you being like this?
Don't do anything weird.
(Begging)
Can we just do anything we want here?
(When we are in here...)
You can do anything freely.
- Hang on. - Can I get my own way?
(So Min is the jail's outlaw.)
As So Min messed with him, Do Kwon asked,
"Can we just do anything we want here?"
(So this is what we do.)
(The culture shock brought on by the thug inmate.)
- You can have your own way. - I can? I see.
- A weekend variety show is no joke. - I know. It's not easy.
(Sweating)
I'll tell you what to do. Come here.
(He barely resolves the situation and returns to the script.)
What is Se Chan doing there?
- What is Se Chan doing there? - He's getting special treatment.
(He pulls only Se Chan to the side.)
He's talking to Se Chan.
(The officer tells Se Chan something.)
Are they talking about something important?
To me? Only me?
- Yes. - Okay.
(What are these two talking about now?)
Okay. Please make me a star.
(He comes back...)
- You can do this. - Okay.
(after hearing something from the officer.)
Tell us what he said.
- This isn't what usually happens. - I know.
Why is he speaking openly about something?
Gosh, this is a good one.
- What is it? - I tried to read his lips.
(Curious)
- He said, "Only me?" - What is it?
(Was it the junior's effort...)
Did he tell you how to escape? What was it about?
(to help Se Chan draw the big picture?)
I can't tell you. I don't want to share it with everyone.
(Was it a hint on partners? Or how to escape?)
Did he tell you about your partner?
(It gets more mysterious.)
No. It wasn't about partners.
It was about a benefit.
- A benefit? - What was the letter for?
- I don't know about the letter. - He didn't hear about it.
Look at Gyu Jin. He's talking to the writer with a smile on.
I bet things went well.
Congratulations.
I'm really happy for you.
They seem happy. As soon as he leaves...
(Good job, Did I do a good job?)
(Extremely pleased)
- The writer seems satisfied. - They even slapped high-fives.
They even slapped high-fives. She thinks he did a good job.
(He successfully completes his duty in the weekend variety show.)
- They look excited. - Now he's smiling.
Gyu Jin's hands were soaked in sweat.
You made a successful debut in Running Man.
(Even the most territorial member congratulates him.)
It was successful.
You guys are inmates of Running Prison.
(They are inmates locked up in Running Prison.)
(All of them are paired up with a partner.)
And you all are paired up with your partners.
Who's my partner?
As the rules say,
(Rules of Running Prison, 1. Each inmate has a partner.)
your fates are entwined.
(2. If my partner benefits, I will benefit.)
You will receive what your partner earns,
(Once my partner is eliminated, I get eliminated as well.)
and once your partner is eliminated, you get eliminated as well.
Really?
So this is how you will find out your partners.
(For each round, they'll randomly form teams.)
You will team up randomly and play games in each round.
(The winning team will win 10 dollars as commissary money.)
And the winning teams will get the commissary money of 10 dollars.
And your partners will get the same amount of money as well.
(The corresponding partner will also get the same amount.)
If you're on the same team with your partner,
(They'll earn 10 dollars more if the partners are on the same team.)
you get another 10 dollars.
- Now I understand how it goes. - So it's important...
to make a good guess and team up with my partner.
With the prize money you earned, you can use the commissary.
(They can use the money to buy things at the commissary.)
There's a commissary.
But if your partner spends money,
(But if my partner spends money, I will lose the money as well.)
the same amount will be deducted from yours.
- So we share our destiny. - Saving money is no good.
- We should spend the money. - We should.
The amount of money you earn or spend...
(The earned or spent money will only be revealed individually.)
is not open to others.
(They must find their partners based on the amount.)
You can find out your partner using the amount.
Before the work program, find out your partner...
(Running Prison Schedule)
(They'll succeed if they find their partner and escape...)
and escape from the prison while the officer is away.
(before the work program.)
For the work program, you should follow the officer's lead.
(What's the first work activity with the prize on the line?)
Okay.
Stand in two lines.
(Officer Shin Gyu Jin guides the inmates with a comfortable voice.)
- What's all this? - Follow me.
The gym looks nice.
(There's a gym in front of their cell.)
- I agree. - It's a rugby ball.
(And even a rugby ball?)
I guess it's a rugby ball.
- Come here. - Is it rugby?
This is Jae Suk's favorite game.
- I love watching the NFL. - He really does.
(Jae Suk is an American football fan.)
I don't know the rules though.
- I'm glad that you brought it up. - All right.
(Is it really American football?)
But this is a special rugby game.
(A Special Rugby Game)
- A special rugby game? - The rules are different.
(The rules are a little different from the regular rugby.)
The men will have their hands and feet tied up.
You'll tie up our hands and feet?
(What?)
With your hands and feet tied up.
(The men will have their hands and feet tied up.)
And the women will have their feet tied up...
(The women will have only their feet tied up.)
- Only the feet? - for this game.
The men are supposed to throw the ball to score.
(The men are supposed to throw the ball to score.)
And the women can only score a touchdown.
(And the women can only score with a touchdown.)
If the men score a goal, they get three points.
(If a man scores a goal, he gets 3 points.)
(If a woman scores a touchdown, she gets 10 points.)
If the women score a touchdown, they get 10 points.
10 points?
(It's important to help women to score points.)
It's a big difference.
You'll be playing for 10 minutes.
(Each game will last for 10 minutes, and three teams will take turns.)
And the team with the highest points wins the game.
All the members of the winning team...
(The 1st place team will each get 10 dollars.)
and their partners will get the prize money of 10 dollars.
(The partners of the winning team will also win 10 dollars.)
- So I... - How do we team up?
I've already divided you guys into teams.
(It's done already.)
- You did? - You did it already?
Sure.
I split you guys into teams to make Se Chan a star.
- Really? - I planned the whole thing.
(He certainly knows how to draw the big picture.)
He's painting a big picture for Se Chan.
- Here's the first team. - Okay.
Song Ji Hyo, Ha Do Kwon,
Ji Suk Jin, and Yang Se Chan.
- This is a big picture. - Hang on. Is this a big picture?
(How will these members help him draw the big picture?)
Wait. I can't be a star this way.
This is... It's just not right.
(Dumbfounded)
I think he called my name.
This is... It's just not right. This isn't a big picture.
(They don't seem to be capable of painting even a small picture.)
This isn't a big picture.
(They are the weaker members.)
- Are we a team? - We're a team.
You can lead the team to paint a big picture.
(It's the big picture to win even with the weaker members.)
I watched all your episodes.
You always get eliminated in the beginning.
- That was a long time ago. - Are you sure?
(The teams to draw a good picture are finally formed.)
- I want to win the prize money. - With our hands and feet tied up?
(Team Green: Suk Jin, Ji Hyo, Se Chan, Do Kwon)
(Team Yellow: Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, So Min, Seung Hyun)
(Team Blue: Jong Kook, Haha, Young Min, Yong Ji)
- Ji Hyo, you can score 10 points. - You should score.
(Compared to men, women can score higher points.)
- We should pass the ball to her. - That's what we need to do.
(It's more advantageous for women to score points.)
If things don't go well, we will have to throw the ball.
All right. Let's begin the first game.
(Team Yellow versus Team Green)
We can't do this even for five minutes.
(The first round begins.)
- Go. - You're so good.
- Grab it. - You're so good.
(Team Green snatches the ball as soon as the game starts.)
Pass the ball.
Gosh, they're fast.
It's okay. Take your time.
(The American football mania plays cool so far.)
Over here.
(Team Green passes the ball to create space.)
Take your time.
- That's right, Ji Hyo. Go. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo gets through an opening.)
We're so good at this.
We have to block Ji Hyo.
(We have to block Ji Hyo.)
Block her.
(They've got Ji Hyo covered.)
- We have to block Ji Hyo. - Good.
You have to go there. Suk Jin.
(He has no choice but to pass to Suk Jin.)
Slowly.
(No one in Team Yellow marks Suk Jin.)
I'll block them.
Pass. Pass it to Do Kwon.
(Suk Jin passes the ball backward.)
No. Why are you passing it to me?
- No. - Give it to Do Kwon.
(It gets passed to Do Kwon.)
No.
(He spots Ji Hyo in the corner.)
Give it back to me.
- Touch the ground! - Touch the ground!
(He successfully passes to Ji Hyo.)
- Give it back to me. - Touch the ground!
- Yes! - Yes!
(They get a touchdown!)
(It's an unexpectedly high-quality video created by the weakest team.)
Who was it? They are really good.
We're so good. This is crazy.
(Acting like he did it)
Gosh, that was incredible.
(Ji Hyo showed off the game skill she accumulated Running Man.)
Hey.
(Team Yellow: 0, Team Green: 10)
We can do it like that too.
(They resume the game in the center.)
Let's start in the middle.
In the middle.
(But...)
(He speeds towards the goalpost.)
You said we were starting in the middle.
(He plays the game like the infamous petty offender he is.)
(Hitting)
(After a scuffle, he scores.)
- Wait. Hold on. - Okay!
Are we allowed to hit people?
So Min, you need to come inside no matter what.
(Acting like he's playing fair)
Ji Hyo, we're allowed to hit people.
(Team Yellow: 3, Team Green: 10)
- That's three points. - Ji Hyo.
- We're allowed to hit people? - Careful!
(Team Green is on offense.)
There's someone behind you.
(After Kwang Soo's scuffle,)
(Tiger Moth So Min starts getting physical.)
(At that moment, Ji Hyo gets through an opening.)
(He passes to Ji Hyo right away.)
- Ji Hyo! - Touch the ground!
Touch the ground!
(They get a touchdown.)
(She caught that?)
(With Ji Hyo's touchdown, Team Green earns 10 points.)
Hey. We're in trouble.
Touchdown!
(The ace is out of the cave after a long time.)
- Amazing. - Nice.
(Surprised)
This is really like American football.
- Really? - Yes.
(The American football mania goes crazy playing American football.)
We have to focus. We do.
(Team Yellow: 3, Team Green: 20)
- We're on a roll right now! - Let's go!
This is really like American football.
(The NFL fan finally grabs the ball.)
- Defense. - Running back, quarterback.
(He passes to So Min.)
Touch the ground!
- Touch the ground! - Hurry up!
(What's this?)
(She caught the ball, but why is she rolling on the ground?)
- No! - You're scaring me.
Go away.
What are you doing?
(Tiger Moth So Min is more concerned about fighting than getting points.)
No!
(Hitting)
Go away.
(Tiger Moth So Min is more concerned about fighting than getting points.)
What are you doing?
No!
(After a pointless scuffle,)
(she tries to get a touchdown.)
(If the ball crosses the line while she holds it, it's a touchdown.)
(She lets go of the ball.)
(Unfortunately, she failed to score.)
No, she didn't get a point.
(So Min is exhausted after a pointless scuffle.)
You should've run. That's too bad.
- So Min! Hey, So Min! - Hey!
(Why did she suddenly crawl?)
We were almost there.
(Team Green is on the offense again.)
Ji Hyo. Block Ji Hyo.
(They invoke the ace alert.)
(Kwang Soo marks her.)
(What?)
Hey. Hold on. Hey! Let go!
(He grabs her by the shirt and carries her away.)
Gosh, you're crazy!
Hey! You crazy bastard!
(Regardless of where the ball is his defense is grabbing her shirt.)
We got this. Seung Hyun, go up.
(He's amazing.)
(He returns to offense after completing the mission.)
Do it! Pass it!
(They have 2 minutes left.)
(Se Chan interferes right in front of him.)
(Hitting)
(It's a dignified play by someone who loves American football.)
(Seung Hyun fails to catch the ball.)
- Gosh. - Hey. Seung Hyun!
Do Kwon! Pass it to Ji Hyo!
(Do Kwon picks up the ball.)
(He passes it.)
(He passes the package to Ji Hyo.)
Pass it to Ji Hyo!
Ji Hyo.
Touch the ground! Nice.
(It's a game-ending touchdown.)
They're no match for us.
(He did nothing.)
(The final score is 3 to 30. Team Green wins.)
They're so good.
Pass it.
(Team Blue plays next.)
We need to practice.
- Are you practicing? - We could've done better.
(They're warming up by exchanging passes.)
- She's good at catching. - Gosh, she is.
(Smooth link)
- She's good. - Okay.
I won't look at the ball for this round.
I won't look at the ball, and I'll focus on Jong Kook.
If you get the ball, run straight. I'll grab onto Jong Kook.
- If I get the ball... - This is Do Kwon's plan.
(All he thinks about is Jong Kook.)
If I get the ball,
- I'll pass it, then grab Jong Kook. - Okay.
Jong Kook, Do Kwon is determined to get you this round.
- He just declared war on you. - Are they finally facing off?
(Determined)
Right? Look at your arms.
(Bring Jong Kook down.)
- Why are you determined to get me? - You will see...
- the ultimate scuffle. - Do Kwon finally gets his chance.
(Kim Jong Kook's Team Blue vs. Ha Do Kwon's Team Green)
Jong Kook, you have to be on your toes this round.
Okay. Ready.
I'm going to get just one person.
(Ha Do Kwon said he's here to get just one person.)
(And that chance has come.)
That's Kim Jong Kook.
(What is the result of this match?)
You're fast!
(The second round starts.)
(Do Kwon runs ferociously as soon as the game starts.)
(He misses on his 1st collision.)
Where should I pass to?
(They finally go up against each other.)
(They begin tackling each other without thinking about the ball.)
Where is it?
(Hitting)
(What?)
Do Kwon... Do Kwon...
(Do Kwon flew like a paper doll.)
Do Kwon. You took a fall.
(Bumping)
(He's moving timidly after the fall.)
He's scared. Do Kwon, don't get scared.
(Intimidated)
Over there.
(He's cute.)
Do Kwon is so funny.
Are you okay?
(He's already exhausted.)
- Are you okay? - No, I'm not.
I think Do Kwon is sulking.
- Okay. - Ready.
(The game resumes after the collision.)
Do Kwon, get over here.
Start.
(We acknowledge his determination. He's still covering Jong Kook.)
(He's not looking at the ball. He's only looking at Jong Kook.)
Come in. Haha. We have to do it fast.
(They're having a fierce battle for the ball on Team Blue's bloc.)
- Suk Jin. - Suk Jin!
(The weakest link, Suk Jin, grabs the ball.)
Suk Jin!
Suk Jin.
(He'll lose the ball soon.)
- Take it. - Let go!
(Desperate)
Suk Jin.
(What is he doing?)
Young Min is terrible at games.
(He's practically a paper doll.)
Why don't you have any strength?
(After the scuffle, Team Green successfully steals the ball.)
(He safely passes the ball to Ha Do Kwon.)
Give it to Ji Hyo.
(He can get a point if he can get it in there,)
- You. - Ji Hyo, get in there.
(but a 2nd collision occurs.)
(Flying)
(I feel bad for him.)
- It went in. - It went in.
(He still scores, and Team Green earns 3 points.)
(He exchanged his health for the points.)
Ha Do Kwon.
I feel like I've been in a car accident.
(The game starts again with Team Blue on offense.)
Block him.
(He arrives in front of the goalpost in no time.)
- Block him. What are you doing? - Block him.
- It's okay. - What are you doing?
(He's biding his time to pass to Yong Ji to get 10 points.)
Okay. You have to get it in.
Come here.
- Shoot. - You have to get it in.
(He's still covering Jong Kook.)
- Good. - Shoot.
(Because they have a tight defense, it's hard to pass.)
His facial expression is so cheeky.
(He passes it to Haha.)
(He quickly passes it to Yong Ji.)
- Do Kwon, you have to get it in. - I'm Do Kwon.
(Se Chan blocks it.)
- Hey. - Do Kwon!
I'm Do Kwon.
(The ball rolls towards Jong Kook and Do Kwon.)
- Hey. - Do Kwon!
I'm going to get just one person.
(These two people go after the ball at the same time.)
(After a complete loss, a second match was created.)
Do Kwon.
(What are the results this time?)
Block Jong Kook. Do Kwon.
(Jong Kook fell.)
Do Kwon. Block Jong Kook. Do Kwon.
(He knocks over Jong Kook and pushes the ball away.)
Do Kwon.
Pass it to Ji Hyo.
(He passes the ball to Ji Hyo.)
- Do Kwon. - Pass it to Ji Hyo.
Nice.
(Touchdown at ease)
Did she get it in?
(I finally did it!)
(I acknowledge his tenacity.)
(He won the fight against Jong Kook with his inner strength.)
He's so cool!
- Goodness. - Did she get it in?
(Thanks to Do Kwon's pass, Team Green gets 10 points.)
He's so cool! He's really cool!
My goodness.
(They're out of energy.)
Do Kwon, don't get tired. Get up!
Cover Jong Kook some more!
- He's not a human being. - Let's go!
(Jong Kook feels competitive.)
He's not a human being.
- Do Kwon is amazing. - Let's go.
(Jong Kook starts moving.)
I'm going to die here.
- That's right. - Come in.
(Jong Kook became competitive as Do Won provokes him.)
- Come here. - Over here.
(Shouting)
We're open here.
(The tiger is out of control.)
(Team Blue earns points easily.)
Does this make sense?
- Does this make sense? - Okay. We got it.
(More people are getting injured.)
Can't we end this?
(Please)
Let's end the game.
We still have that left.
(Team Blue wins.)
With a score of 40 to 13, Team Kim Yong Ji wins.
Okay.
(They prepare for the next round.)
That was good.
- You should've protected him. - Hold on.
My mic fell out. My mic keeps falling out.
Hold on. Jong Kook's mic.
(Fixing his microphone)
Hold on. It fell into the crack.
Why did you send a woman?
It fell into the crack!
(Suddenly modest)
Send a guy.
(There was a reason why Jong Kook was asking for a male staff member.)
It fell right into the crack!
- Just leave it! - Did you put it in there?
I put it there, and it went right in.
(Jong Kook's microphone fell out, and he asked Kwang Soo for help.)
Can you put my mic back in?
(He noticed the chance.)
There's no one here.
(Putting it in)
Okay. We have to get it in.
(That is the secret behind the crack.)
I put it there, and it went right in.
Why did you do that?
(Thanks to a male staff member,)
You're out of your mind.
(he rescued the microphone from his crack.)
Gosh, that was funny.
(The result of the third round)
The team that came in 1st place...
and will receive 10 dollars each in commissary money is...
(Team Blue wins 1st place with 2 wins.)
Team Kim Yong Ji.
- We won? - No way.
(Jong Kook, Haha, Young Min and Yong Ji receive 10 dollars.)
Each member of Team Kim Yong Ji will receive 10 dollars.
Their partners will also receive 10 dollars.
(If their partners are in the losing team, they received 10 dollars too.)
The correctional officer will show you the amount you have...
(You can guess your partner by checking how much money you have.)
- in your commissary account. - If your partner won?
Yes. You will get money too.
Okay. Good job everyone.
I will give you your statement for your commissary account.
Ji Suk Jin.
(They each receive a statement for their commissary account.)
After you see how much money you have,
- you have to return it to me. Yes. - We do?
- Song Ji Hyo. - I hope I have some money.
Yang Se Chan.
(He's checking his statement.)
I'm sure they have 10 dollars each.
(4 people received at least 10 dollars for winning.)
- Right. We do. - You do.
We have some money.
(The partners of these 4 members have also received 10 dollars.)
(Yong Ji, who won, is checking her statement.)
(Account statement, Kim Yong Ji, Received reward, Total: 20 dollars.)
(She got an additional 10 dollars?)
Please give it back to me after you've checked it.
Here you go, sir.
(If Yong Ji has got 20 dollars,)
Sure. Thank you.
(her partner must be either Jong Kook, Haha, or Young Min.)
Thank you.
Can one have 20 dollars?
If one of them is your partner?
(Did Jong Kook also get 20 dollars?)
Having 20 dollars will sure be reassuring.
(That means...)
(Yong Ji and Jong Kook are partners.)
(Seung Hyun and Jae Suk received 10 dollars despite losing.)
Your fates are entwined.
You will receive what your partner earns...
and once your partner is eliminated, you get eliminated as well.
(Haha and Young Min are paired with either Seung Hyun or Jae Suk.)
(While they're guessing each other's partners,)
There is a bit of time until your next work program,
- so you'll get some free time. - Free time?
(they get 30 minutes of free time.)
With the money you earned,
you can buy anything...
(They can use the commissary with their money during the break.)
- from the commissary. - All right.
If you didn't earn any money,
- you can use the time to chat. - All right.
(They can buy the items...)
- Enjoy your free time then. - Sure.
Thank you!
(or put them on their tab.)
Let's eat!
(However, what one partner spends, the other partner will lose out on.)
Hello.
(The winning team confidently walks in.)
- Thank you. - Gosh.
- What's the price range? - I should eat something.
They're all a dollar.
(They all cost a dollar each.)
- A dollar? - A dollar.
(The amount they spent will be taken off the commissary money.)
This will be two dollars.
I'll take it from your commissary money.
(Even in prison, you need to eat.)
Can you buy me one?
- Maybe a drink. - I don't have any money.
- Put it on your tab. - If I could, I would.
Put it on your tab.
(Whining)
Buy me one since we met for the first time today.
- What? - You're the older one here.
I don't have any money.
(Pestering someone he met for the first time)
I'll return the favor once I'm reborn as your junior.
Whoever earned money without winning will have definitely spent it.
(Buying at the commissary can also be a hint.)
It's not just about being physically strong.
- You need to be clever too. - I don't know.
Is it important to find your partner though?
- Of course. - Why?
(Of course.)
Because you'll be eliminated if your partner is eliminated.
I feel bad for whomever Suk Jin's partner is.
(He doesn't understand the rules again.)
- He even told our guest... - You're all clueless though.
- not to listen to the rules. - Why not?
Because you'll get the hang of it as the games go on.
Do Kwon responded by saying that's why he always gets eliminated.
(Do Kwon proves that he's a true fan of Running Man.)
I just hope that I'm not partnered with Suk Jin.
(In a low voice)
(His inner voice came shooting out.)
(But just then...)
(Se Chan secretly calls Kwang Soo over.)
Did you receive any money?
What? No.
(They exchange their opinions in a quiet voice.)
Whose on your team?
Jae Suk and...
I mean, who do you think you're partnered with?
Do you have no idea?
I didn't receive any money.
- Did you buy this though? - Yes.
- I spent a dollar. - What?
I spent a dollar.
Is that what you called me over for?
Or was it just to steal some of my chips?
(Se Chan was only after Kwang Soo's chips.)
(He played me.)
What...
(Se Chan, the con artist)
- Jae Suk... - But I was just sitting there.
- Unbelievable. - Jae Suk, hold on.
I was just sitting there when he...
(Kwang Soo tells on Se Chan.)
I thought he was going to tell me a secret,
but it was to steal my chips.
That's what he called me over for.
You can't eat our snacks without saying anything.
(Just tell me what the officer told you.)
Yes, you at least ate half of mine.
Okay, I'll tell you.
- Can I enjoy this then? - Sure, go ahead.
(Se Chan gobbles down the chips.)
(He tells Jae Suk and Kwang Soo something.)
So what was it?
Se Chan!
Why are you ostracizing us and only speaking to them?
- Let us know too. - It's just Jae Suk.
(What did Se Chan say to Jae Suk and Kwang Soo?)
What were you talking about?
Guys...
Do Kwon hasn't said a word to you...
(Jong Kook!)
after colliding with you earlier.
Are you upset about something?
I didn't know it would be this violent.
(He's upset.)
(The violent plays upset him.)
Do Kwon...
- Do Kwon... - I mean...
(Pouting his lips)
You're pouting.
- Jong Kook's not a bad person. - I said this at the beginning,
but there's something cute about him.
(Cute)
He's quite adorable.
Didn't he enter saying,
(Where did his confidence go?)
"I'm going to get just one person"?
After one game, I learned that I was wrong.
(And after the second game...)
All right,
so the second work program is over.
(The winners of the second round are...)
Suk Jin, Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Jong Kook earn 10 dollars each.
(Suk Jin, Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Jong Kook.)
(Yong Ji also earns 10 dollars thanks to her partner, Jong Kook.)
(Do Kwon, So Min, and Kwang Soo win money despite their loss.)
(Their partners are in the winning team.)
Officer!
(The inmates are one step closer to guessing who their partners are.)
I'm sure you're all hungry.
- I'm starving. - Of course.
(It's finally lunchtime.)
- Gosh. - It's already time for lunch.
A decent "lunsh" has been prepared for you.
He said "lunsh" instead of lunch.
(Let's all enjoy the delicious "lunsh".)
- Lunch time! - Stack the food on your plate...
and sit at the table after taking off your shoes.
- Thank you. - Gyu Jin.
- Take off your shoes! - You're doing...
a great job today.
Sorry?
(So Min hands the rookie officer a sausage.)
Is it for me?
I hope we get along.
My gosh. Can you believe this lunch we're having?
(The delicious lunch is the pride of Running Prison.)
Everything looks delicious.
(Polite)
Thank you for the meal.
(Don't forget what I gave you.)
(A dirty but clean deal was made.)
- Who were you gesturing to? - No one.
(To Do Kwon,)
Do Kwon, why don't you sit with Jong Kook?
(they recommend him sitting next to Jong Kook.)
- Over here. - Have a seat over here.
(It's obvious who has seniority now.)
Have you suddenly lost weight?
(Gaunt)
You look gaunt for some reason.
You can't consider him as a normal human being.
I think I've got the hang of it now.
(Speaking in the air)
He has the hang of it now.
(Do Kwon is cute.)
He's clever too.
I had no idea he'd dodge out of the way like that.
(The salad was dropped.)
(Variety show rookies Young Min and Seung Hyun...)
(are the last to pick up their food.)
I dropped it.
(A delicious lunch served at Running Prison)
- It's not as far as you think. - Exactly.
Does the food suit your palate?
(It's delicious!)
Yes!
Since you followed my orders so well earlier,
I'm going to...
(He gives them a chance to earn another 5 dollars.)
give three of you...
a chance to win five dollars for your commissary account.
(Tempting)
I can't give it away, so...
- Suk Jin. - Yes?
(He's getting green onions in the meantime.)
- I'm trying to explain something. - I needed more soup.
We're not here to have a seminar, you know.
Does that mean I can't have more soup?
Are you here on vacation?
(The officer has gotten used to his role at lunchtime.)
- Please stay seated. - Sure.
He seems like a true prison guard.
- Let me explain once again. - He does.
(The game to acquire more money in the commissary account.)
I can't give it away for free.
I'll give it to whomever says the answer that satisfies me.
(That means he'll do as he pleases.)
So here we go.
Name a celebrity that I resemble.
(A celebrity that Officer Shin resembles!)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer!
(They all speak out their answers.)
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Se Chan?
- Let me answer. - Can I go ahead?
(Loud)
(Using her sausage priority)
Just say the answer.
Park Seo Jun!
- Nicely done. - Let me answer.
(The sausage she gave him finally pays off.)
- Are you kidding me? - Let me answer.
Jung Woo Sung!
- Nicely done. - Let me answer.
V of BTS.
- That's a dangerous one. - Shouldn't I have said that?
- His fans will be mad. - You're out to get me, aren't you?
Let me answer.
- Yes, Jae Suk? - Jung Chan Sung.
- Who? - Jung Chan Sung, the Korean zombie.
(The resemblance is clear.)
Jung Chan Sung.
Nicely done!
(Correct)
What a treat.
I thought that Jung Woo Sung had walked in.
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and So Min said the answers that pleased him.)
You look a lot like Jung Chan Sung.
Thank you for that.
(The three of them get an additional 5 dollars.)
The three of you...
won't receive the money right now.
It will be put into your commissary account.
- Great. Thank you. - All right.
- Please enjoy your meal. - Hold on.
(Their partners also get 5 dollars.)
Will our partners receive the money too?
- Yes. - Our partners too?
Really?
(If any of them earned 5 dollars,)
- They'll also receive the money. - Our partners too.
(they're partners of Jae Suk, Suk Jin, or So Min.)
Just remember that my partner will receive the money.
(While they're almost done guessing the partners...)
After you enjoy your lunch,
you will participate in some more work programs.
(Now it's time to say goodbye to the rookie officer.)
Another officer will be with you for those,
- so be nice to him too. - Are you going somewhere?
Are you off to "Comedy Big League"?
(His main job)
- That's not it. - There's a rehearsal.
(A senior of "Comedy Big League")
I'll see you later.
(He suddenly bows.)
I'll show you how it's done there.
(Se Chan is a senior on "Comedy Big League".)
- What are you doing? - Just let me be.
- Gyu Jin, take care. - Enjoy your meal.
- Bye! - You did well today!
(Good work, Officer Shin.)
- Bye. - I hope you come by often.
(Enjoy the sausage.)
Everybody.
(Their commissary accounts...)
Here's your transaction history.
(have been delivered.)
- Suk Jin. - Yes?
Haha.
(They're somewhat aware of their partners now.)
This round made things clear.
Are you close to guessing your partner?
Totally.
Really?
(Haha and Seung Hyun make eye contact.)
Are you close to guessing your partner?
- Totally. - Really?
(Seung Hyun makes his way to Haha.)
Two dollars?
Why didn't you come to me sooner?
(The two share the exact same transaction report.)
(Haha and Seung Hyun are partners.)
(Seung Hyun and Haha)
(Jae Suk and Young Min)
(Yong Ji and Jong Kook)
(Suk Jin and Do Kwon)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo)
(So Min and Se Chan)
(The partners are revealed one by one.)
- Okay! - Thanks for the meal.
(Their delicious lunchtime ends.)
I'm still not sure,
(They all glance around to approach their partners.)
but I've narrowed it down.
My partner will sure know that we're partners.
You can go by the commissary for one last time.
But we had a lot to eat.
(It's their last chance to spend their money.)
We'll be notified if the money is spent.
(Young Min heads inside first.)
I...
I am here to paint a big picture.
(He's here to paint a big picture?)
- That will be 10 dollars. - I'll take it.
(He secretly buys something...)
Did you buy the water?
(and comes out of the commissary.)
Your name tag is different.
Really?
(Young Min has a different name tag?)
A different name tag?
- What? - Why?
(What?)
- What? - Hold on.
- What? - What is this?
(Young Min has...)
- What is it? - What's going on?
- Let me see. - Why is his different?
(a gold name tag?)
What is this?
It's in gold letters.
- Why is his different? - What is this?
(Young Min came back with a gold name tag.)
What is this though?
- Hey, Se Chan. - Is it to paint a big picture?
(A few hours ago)
- Se Chan? - He must be helping you out.
(Officer Shin called Se Chan aside.)
- Come on over. - Will you make me a star?
(He told only Se Chan about the secret of the prison.)
If you go into the commissary...
and say "I am here to paint a big picture" to the lady inside,
- she'll give you a Defense Right. - To me?
(You can buy the Defense Right for 10 dollars at the commissary.)
If you say to the lady...
(Sharing)
that you're here to paint a big picture,
- she'll give you a Defense Right. - What's that?
You'll have a chance to save yourself from elimination.
You'll be given an advantage...
if you say you're here to paint a big picture.
(Se Chan shared the secret to gain more influence.)
- Are you saying that... - Really?
What is this?
(The gold name tag is the Defense Right.)
Can it be bought?
(Some inmates aren't aware of the Defense Right.)
Is he irrelevant in the game now?
How did he know that though?
(Puzzled)
(Did Young Min eavesdrop on Se Chan?)
- What is this? - The Defense Right.
(The gold name tag)
I'll buy one.
- What? - What are you here to buy?
Me? I'm here for the shield.
That's not something we sell here.
Then is it Defense Right?
(If that's the case...)
We don't sell that either.
Defense...
(How do I buy it?)
Next.
(Kwang Soo approaches Yong Ji.)
What? What was that?
What's on sale?
(Whispering)
- What? What was that? - What's on sale?
Do I need to say something?
(Did Kwang Soo tell her how to buy the Defense Right?)
Go first.
(She doesn't trust him.)
- I don't have the money. - Go first.
(I only have 9 dollars.)
(She says what she's told.)
(Kwang Soo fooled her.)
(She gave the chorus of a song from the Goryeo Dynasty.)
(Innocent)
- Is it wrong? - Pretend you don't know anything.
It's wrong! It's wrong!
(Goodness)
What is it?
(Yong Ji only got an embarrassment instead of a Defense Right.)
- Did she say "Yalli yalli"? - "Yalli yalli yallashong".
Yong Ji, what did you say?
(Trying to eavesdrop)
- That's not it. - Tell me what it is.
(Another inmate asks for information.)
Open, sesame.
(Se Chan tries to fool Haha.)
I am serious. I am serious.
(It won't work with the guy with 10 years of experience.)
Why won't you believe me? That's the code.
(Do Kwon was watching without a word.)
That's the code.
(He gets up stealthily and heads over to the commissary.)
(He recites what he's told.)
Open, sesame. Open, sesame.
(He completes the dance as he has eavesdropped.)
(Why can't I get it?)
- What would you like? - What?
The name tag.
I heard that was the code.
(Confused)
(Laughing)
Open, sesame. Open, sesame.
(He even dances again.)
Is it wrong?
(My goodness.)
What was that? You looked very cute.
(Do Kwon's cute challenge ends in vain.)
Hurry up and tell me.
I am here to paint a big picture.
(It's the real code.)
Oh, okay.
(Jong Kook learns the code through Ji Hyo.)
I am here to paint a big picture.
(Jong Kook purchases a Defense Right with 10 dollars.)
- Would you buy it for 10 dollars? - Yes.
What did you say?
(He shares the method with his partner, Yong Ji.)
That was the code.
I am here to paint a big picture.
- Would you buy it for 10 dollars? - Yes.
(After Jong Kook and Yong Ji)
I am here to paint a big picture.
(Suk Jin buys it too.)
My goodness. He bought it as well.
(Young Min, Suk Jin, Jong Kook, and Yong Ji...)
(get the gold name tag.)
If there are no prison guards, can't we escape?
(After Gyu Jin, no officers are in sight.)
(Running Prison Schedule)
If you don't escape with your partner...
before the work program,
(Before Infernal Work Program, they must escape with the partner.)
you will receive a big penalty. Thus, find your partner...
and escape when the prison guards are gone.
(They must take their chance when the prison guards are gone.)
Someone else will come.
(The officer left for the transfer of duties.)
Are there no prison guards now?
(This is the perfect opportunity!)
Let's go out and lock the door.
(Kwang Soo and Do Kwon leave the room first.)
- Go out. - Is there something in here?
(There must be something in...)
What could this be?
(the mysterious letter the guard left in the drawer.)
That safe must be important.
I saw a prison guard put an envelope in it.
There must be a direction.
(But the blue drawer is locked with a lock.)
- Inside the drawer? - Yes.
- This is... Hold on. - How do you open it?
Does anyone know the combination?
Why would anyone tell you so easily?
(No one knows the password of the lock.)
There must be a hint inside.
(Somewhere in the prison...)
(lies a clue.)
(The inmates look around more meticulously.)
There must be a direction.
- Inside the drawer? - Yes.
(Jae Suk stares at the sign on the wall.)
Maybe this means something.
"Wisdom comes with age."
(Wisdom comes with age.)
- It has to mean something. - Right?
Wisdom. How old is wisdom?
- Right? - Jae Suk.
(Wisdom comes with age?)
Wisdom. How old is wisdom?
- Right? - Jae Suk. The order of age.
- That's right. - Let's stand in that order.
- This is... - The number.
Maybe something will happen if we stand in the right order.
- Let's stand in that order. - Shall I move?
This is...
(Should the inmates line up in the order of their ages?)
Maybe something will happen if we stand in the right order.
- Let's stand in the order of age. - Let's try standing that way.
- Let's stand. - Young Min is next.
(The inmates line up from the oldest to the youngest.)
- Okay. - Who is next?
(In the order of their ages: Ji Suk Jin, 22BL 2366)
- Third. - Am I next?
(Kim Young Min, 10UE 2371)
- Jong Kook comes next. - Me.
(Yoo Jae Suk, 02DRA 2365)
- No, no. - I'm next to Jae Suk.
(Kim Jong Kook, 34WER 2361)
Hurry up and come inside. Let's line up in the order of age.
- Line up. We need to escape. - Come here.
(Each inmate is assigned with an inmate number.)
(Will they get a hint if they stand in order?)
We are one today.
3, 4.
(22BL 2366, 10UE 2371, 02DRA 2365, 34WER 2361)
Blue...
(Blue drawer)
- Blue. - Blue drawer.
Blue drawer.
(Blue drawer)
- Blue drawer. - Blue drawer.
Line up.
"Com".
(Ha Do Kwon, PA)
- "Combination". - "Combination".
(Haha, SS)
Come here.
(They need other inmates' letters to complete the password.)
- Tell us from there. - Come here.
- Tell us from there. - Cover your tag.
(Sensitive)
- This is the right way. - That's right.
"Combination". We have "combination".
(Password)
- Eight. - Hurry up and tell us!
I won't let you out unless you tell us the combination.
(Opening his eyes wide)
We figured it out! Come over here.
- Put your hands down. Attention. - Cover your tag.
(The four youngest members' letters make up the password.)
- Cover your tag. - Do you want to rot in there?
- Cover your tag. - Come on out.
(Kwang Soo's gang wants only the password.)
- Combination. - Combination.
- 8. - 8.
- Come on out. - Come on out.
(They are punished with a flood of water.)
These brats. Jong Kook, get them.
(The 3-minute reign comes to an end.)
Come on out.
I didn't do anything.
(It's a typical excuse of a minion.)
You know I didn't do anything.
The youngest members.
(Once they combine the letters of the youngest four,)
- The four youngest members. - Their numbers are the combination.
(including Kwang Soo, who claims he didn't do anything...)
- 8412. - 84...
- 8412. - 84.
Let's read it together.
(The letter inside the drawer)
- Okay. Let's read it together. - Okay.
All of us can survive if we escape together.
(No credibility)
- That's what I am saying. - It will be war after we read this.
(I have a strong feeling.)
It's open.
(The blue drawer opens.)
- It's open. - It's open.
- It's open. - How did you figure this out?
- Let's read it together. - Let's read it together.
(They are supposed to read the letter together.)
- Hold on. - Let's read it together.
- For goodness' sake. - It's open.
(Calm down, everyone.)
- Come in. - Calm down.
We can survive together.
- Let's escape together. - We can survive together.
- Calm down. - This is it.
(Will there be a method of escape in the letter?)
We will learn how we can escape.
Read it out loud.
(Everyone is nervous.)
- Read it out loud. - It's our last hope.
What? Boss!
(Did it say "Boss"?)
There's a boss?
What does that mean?
"Boss, to help with your escape,"
"I sent a gang member to the prison. Did the two of you meet?"
(The recipient of the letter is the boss who's in the prison.)
"Boss, to help with your escape,"
"I sent a gang member to the prison. Did the two of you meet?"
(There is a gang member to help the boss' escape.)
There is a gang member.
"For your escape, I prepared a truck behind the gray wall."
"It will leave at 3pm sharp."
"In case this letter gets found,"
"I hid the details in the cell phone in the prison."
"Please find it and check the text message."
- Inside the prison? - Where is the cell phone hidden?
(A hidden phone?)
We need to check the text message.
(The boss and the gang member aren't partners.)
Boss, if you and your partner get on the truck, the gang will win.
(The gang will win if the boss and his partner get on...)
(the escape truck that leaves at 3pm.)
If you get eliminated,
the gang member we sent will become the next boss.
(If the boss is eliminated,)
(the gang member will become the temporary boss to escape.)
If that gang member and his or her partner escape,
(If the new boss and his partner escape, the gang still wins.)
the gang will win.
If other inmates escape,
(If regular inmates escape,)
they will receive the prize...
and the gang will lose. Please don't forget that.
(the gang will lose.)
"The work program that starts at 3pm is known to be brutal."
(Who is the boss...)
(that wants to escape before the notorious work program?)
"So please escape safely without getting eliminated."
Who is the boss?
It must be Young Min!
(The boss must be...)
He was the first one to put on the gold name tag. How did he know?
You're right. He had the information all by himself.
There is no other way Young Min found out about it.
(Is Young Min who purchased the gold name tag first the boss?)
Did you tell him?
I told Suk Jin, but I didn't tell Young Min.
(About the Defense Right...)
How did he know?
(Is Young Min the boss? Or is he a gang member?)
- His partner must have told him. - That's right.
(Or a regular inmate who eavesdropped about it?)
Come on out. It's time for a cleanup.
(The cleanup begins.)
Okay.
I will clean up when I am asked.
(They go out to clean up while dreaming of escape.)
Here.
I will take something that suits me.
(Among them are a boss and a gang member.)
I think we are partners.
- We are... - What?
Are we?
(Jae Suk first approaches his partner.)
- I think so. - We could be partners.
(If someone gets eliminated, the partner also gets eliminated.)
I think we are partners.
Why are Young Min and Jae Suk so close?
(Suspicious)
- Suk Jin. - Yes?
They could be partners, right?
I am certain Yong Ji and Jong Kook...
are partners.
(They start to clean up after they figure out their partners.)
I see my partner over there.
(The current partners)
The weather is hot.
(Suk Jin and Do Kwon, Jae Suk and Young Min)
(Jong Kook and Yong Ji, Haha and Seung Hyun,)
We need to clean up.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo, Se Chan and So Min)
(The man everyone is suspicious of, Young Min...)
(as well as Do Kwon pretend to clean up diligently.)
(But everyone is thinking about escaping.)
My partner is Seung Hyun.
(Looking around)
(Blowing)
My partner is Haha.
(Seung Hyun will be eliminated if Haha is eliminated.)
I don't know what to do next.
What's certain is that Young Min is the boss.
(A sudden change in attitude)
(He is likely to be the boss.)
I think the boss is...
one of the guests.
It's either Yong Ji...
(He suspects the guests.)
Young Min. It's either Yong Ji or Young Min.
Young Min must be...
(Yong Ji suspects Young Min too.)
either the boss or gang member.
(Young Min is under a lot of suspicions.)
(He suddenly utters a sound.)
(He shrugs.)
There must be people...
(Nasal sound)
who realized that we are partners.
Without letting them know,
I will reveal my partner's name.
As for the identity of the boss,
I have an idea.
(Does Young Min know who the boss is?)
With my partner, I will find the cell phone...
and check the text message. Then I will help...
the boss escape.
(That means...)
You are the gang member who entered the prison...
(Young Min is a gang member who entered the prison...)
to help the boss escape.
(to help the boss escape.)
I see.
(The gang member, Kim Young Min)
Before 3pm,
(He must make the boss and his or her partner escape...)
you must make the boss and his or her partner escape...
in order to bring victory to the gang.
(in order to bring victory to the gang.)
You can find out who the boss is...
(He can find out who the boss is by the mark on the insole of the shoe.)
by the mark on the sole of the shoe.
- The boss? - Yes.
(He must find the boss first!)
Gyu Han, you should eat.
(During mealtime earlier)
It's Gyu Jin.
(They took off their shoes and had a meal.)
(Dropping)
(The gang member checks the shoes by pretending to drop something.)
Let me answer! Jung Woo Sung.
(While everyone was focused on winning the commissary money...)
- You pass. - Let me answer! V of BTS!
(Dropping)
(He checked other shoes by using the same method.)
(On someone's shoes,)
As for the identity of the boss,
I have an idea.
(Young Min spotted the mark.)
Boss gave me a sign a few times.
(The boss)
I hope my clumsy concept...
(He suddenly changes.)
worked to my advantage.
I will look for my partner first.
(He goes in search of Jae Suk.)
The boss is...
(On eggshells)
Really?
(Surprised)
- How do you know? - I am the gang member.
(Revealing his identity)
You are the gang member?
(Checking again)
(Since Jae Suk is the gang member's partner,)
(he can escape the penalty only if the gang wins.)
Really?
For goodness' sake.
(Jae Suk needs to work for the victory of the gang.)
Firstly...
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin is looking for his partner.)
I should hurry up and meet Doo Kwan.
(Who?)
(Who is Doo Kwan?)
(He is Do Kwon, not Doo Kwan.)
Go to the side.
(He spots Doo Kwan, also known as Do Kwon.)
- Do Kwon. - Hello.
Suk Jin.
(He's wrong again.)
- You are my partner, right? - Of course.
(Suk Jin and Do Kwon unite.)
All right.
You used 3 dollars and I used 2 dollars.
(They're happy to find each other.)
That's right. At first, it was a dollar.
- That's right. A dollar. - Yes.
(As Do Kwon was worried, his partner is the weakest Suk Jin.)
- And at the end... - Five dollars came in last.
Then it was 10 dollars.
Who do you think is the boss?
- The boss? - Yes.
It's likely that Se Chan is the boss.
- Right? - He keeps messing up the games.
Wasn't he too forward from the start?
(Suk Jin suspects Se Chan.)
- You are right. - Right?
I think he definitely has a mission.
- Jong Kook. Jong Kook. - Yes?
(Meanwhile, people suspect Se Chan as the boss.)
So Min, I have something to say.
(He suddenly summons Jong Kook and So Min.)
The cell phone isn't the only thing we need to find.
We need to find the fake wall.
(In order to escape)
What?
"For your escape, I prepared a truck behind the gray wall."
(There was important information in the letter.)
(A truck for two behind a fake gray wall)
We must get on the truck behind the fake wall.
(They must get in the truck behind the fake gray wall to escape.)
- That's right. - Thus,
we need to find the fake wall and stop anyone from getting on.
(There's one more thing they have to find along with the fake wall.)
People will get on it as soon as they find it.
How about the cell phone?
That's another thing that is hidden. We need to find the cell phone...
(There must be important information on the phone.)
as well as the fake wall.
There is the fake wall?
(Well...)
That's right. Even in "Prison Break",
(Thinking)
the character escapes within the prison.
I think I can break most walls.
- That's not how it works. - No?
(Calm down, Jong Kook.)
- No. - This could be a fake wall too.
(Where is the fake gray wall?)
- If I use my strength... - How will we escape?
How will we escape?
- We need to think of a way. - Yes.
All right.
(Jae Suk and Kwang Soo are looking for a hint.)
It's cool in here.
(Doubting instinctively)
Hold on. The air conditioner is on in this room.
- What? - Okay.
What is it?
(Jae Suk spots something.)
(They check and see if they are alone.)
No one is here.
(What did Jae Suk find?)
I won't tell a soul. I mean it.
(Swearing)
- Really? - Yes.
I can't trust you.
(Distrust)
I won't tell a soul for real.
- Really? - Yes.
(Jae Suk takes a leap of faith...)
What is it?
(and shares information with Kwang Soo.)
Here.
(Handing over)
Air conditioner... It's an air conditioner user manual.
(He successfully makes fun of Kwang Soo.)
Why in the world did you hide an air conditioner user manual?
(Absurd)
You are the one who came.
(You are the one who came.)
I came because you seemed to be hiding something.
- For goodness' sake. - For goodness' sake.
(Jae Suk stars on Running Man in order to make fun of Kwang Soo.)
I need to carry this around.
(So Min and Ji Hyo are looking for the fake wall too.)
- Why did you pick something so big? - I don't know.
(They keep carrying brooms.)
There must be a use for this cleaning tool.
- What? - There must be a use.
There must be something here.
(When they come down the stairs, a long hallway stretches on.)
What is this place?
It's just a cool hallway.
(It's cool because it's underground.)
That door leads to the stairs.
(They keep walking to the end of the hall.)
- This door? - Yes.
(Halting)
What? It's the fake wall!
(No way.)
It's the fake wall!
(They finally found the fake gray wall.)
It's the fake wall. What is this?
(Behind the fake gray wall...)
"I prepared a truck behind the gray wall."
(awaits the 2-person truck.)
"It will leave at 3pm sharp."
(It will leave at 3pm.)
It's the fake wall. What is this?
(If they break the fake wall, they can escape.)
(She begins to break the fake wall.)
Let's break it down.
(Kicking)
(It's harder than they expected!)
What is it?
(At that time, Se Chan walks towards the fake wall.)
It's the fake wall!
(So Min is glad to see her partner.)
- What is it? - The fake wall.
- What? - The fake wall.
(If So Min and Se Chan break the wall and escape, they win.)
Really? Can we break it?
- I don't know. Try breaking it. - Try breaking it.
We kicked it, but we couldn't break it.
- It's too hard. - Maybe this isn't it.
(The fake wall is pretty firm.)
- Could it be a real wall? - This is...
Would it be okay to kick it?
(He keeps kicking.)
- Is it supposed to be this strong? - Seriously.
- Hold on. - We should call Jong Kook over.
(He asks for help.)
(In the end)
Would it be okay to work on different spots?
(They manually take off the styrofoam.)
(Will they break it before 3pm?)
- What? - Is it working?
Hold on. Let's do this instead.
(Ji Hyo has got an idea.)
Hold on.
(She uses a tool.)
I will stick it in.
Hold on.
(She uses it for leverage.)
- It's working. - Okay. It's working.
Hold on. I will stick it in there.
- One... - Ji Hyo, you are out.
(Suddenly)
(Ji Hyo is out.)
- For goodness' sake. - Go, Ji Hyo.
Whose partner were you?
(What happened?)
This is driving me crazy.
(Only Kwang Soo's bag and name tag remain.)
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are out.
(When Kwang Soo got eliminated, his partner got eliminated as well.)
Why?
Are Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo out?
(Among inmates, someone rips name tags off.)
- Really? - Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are out.
- They are out. - Really?
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo were partners.
(They must hurry.)
Be quiet. Be quiet.
- Are you okay? - Here.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo's elimination makes them work faster.)
Move out of the way.
(The fake wall finally breaks!)
We got it.
(Once they get on the truck, they will escape the prison.)
(They move past the fake wall.)
What?
(But)
There is a lock.
(The door is locked.)
What?
(The fake wall wasn't the end!)
There is a lock.
Hang on. What is this?
(They thought they could escape.)
What is this?
(Other inmates come running upon hearing the noise.)
What's here?
- No, no. - Let's see.
- What is up with them? - One of you is the boss, right?
(They're lucky.)
No.
- What is this? - There is a truck.
(There's a truck waiting outside.)
There is a truck.
Beyond that door?
But we need a lock combination.
(They must figure out the 5-digit password to unlock the door.)
I know. There is a lock.
Can't we go outside?
No, we can't.
(What's the password?)
We need to open the lock.
- We need to open the lock. - The two of you are a team.
- That's why you are together. - So Min followed me.
(He figured out that they're partners.)
The two of you are a team.
(While So Min and Se Chan are busy figuring out the password...)
Why else would you be together?
Be careful, So Min!
(Seung Hyun attacks suddenly.)
(Se Chan runs over belatedly,)
(but So Min's name tag got ripped already.)
(Seung Hyun thought Se Chan was the boss, so he attacked So Min.)
- What happens now? - The two of you are a team, right?
The two of you are a team, right?
(If Se Chan was the boss, Young Min will be the next boss.)
So Min.
It's likely that Se Chan is the boss.
(Was Se Chan the boss?)
He keeps messing up the games.
So Min and Se Chan are out.
(They simply get eliminated.)
What?
So Min and Se Chan are out.
(Se Chan wasn't the boss!)
- This is good news. - So Min, I am sorry.
(She broke the wall for them and got eliminated in vain.)
- My goodness. - Seung Hyun.
- I am sorry. - You didn't know.
(Who is the boss among the 8 remaining inmates?)
No.
(The gang member, Jae Suk)
(Suk Jin, Do Kwon, Haha, Seung Hyun, Jong Kook, and Yong Ji)
Let's get out of here. We can't find a way.
(Now that the wall is down,)
What could be the combination?
(they must find the 5-digit password.)
We need to find the cell phone to find out the combination. Let's go.
(The clue must be in the cell phone.)
(At that moment,)
(Seung Hyun approaches the lock.)
Five digits.
(He checks that the password has 5 digits.)
The combination has five digits.
Where is Seung Hyun? Why isn't he coming?
(He noticed it now.)
(Haha approaches the fake wall.)
Seung Hyun.
What is going on?
(Seung Hyun suddenly disappeared.)
What's his role?
He must have a role.
(Seung Hyun who disappeared without a word seems suspicious.)
Why else would he disappear?
- He disappeared so suddenly. - He must have a role.
It's strange, right?
(Seung Hyun's partner doubts him.)
(Seung Hyun is looking for something.)
(Why is he suddenly going around on his own?)
(Jong Kook and Yong Ji are hanging around in the lobby.)
Here comes Young Min.
We need to keep our distance. He is the most suspicious.
(He spots Young Min.)
- Be careful. - Did you find a hint?
(He acts clumsy to avoid the suspicion.)
- Did you find a hint? - No.
Don't come near. Keep your distance.
(They keep the distance.)
- Okay. - Where have you been so busily?
I followed the others to there and came back.
To there? Why did you follow them?
(Interrogating)
To find my partner.
(Giving an excuse)
Oh, your partner? Haven't you found your partner yet?
(Doubting)
Your partner or the boss?
(She gets to the point.)
- My partner. - Something isn't right.
(Everyone suspects the gang member Young Min.)
(Meanwhile, Haha)
Seung Hyun.
(He finally sees Seung Hyun again.)
I have been looking for it. I finally found it.
Hey, I like you.
(Suddenly, their bromance surges up.)
- I like you too. - I am serious.
But you are the boss!
What?
(Surprised)
(After Haha's comment,)
(his face became scary.)
If you...
(Is Ji Seung Hyun the boss as Haha predicted?)
- Where have you been? - Jae Suk.
(Jae Suk and Young Min met in the lobby.)
- I've been looking for you. - Jae Suk.
(Glad)
He's slowly approaching you.
(Jae Suk already knows that Young Min is a gang member.)
He's acting weird.
(Young Min)
Are the two of you partners? Hang on.
(He notices something is going on.)
- They're partners. - Are they?
(He finally realizes that they're partners.)
- They're partners. - We're partners, but...
What? Wait.
(On alert)
- Wait. She's a fake. - You two are partners?
That cleaner is a fake.
(At that moment)
Hold on. That cleaner looks like...
We've seen her.
(A cleaner appears out of nowhere.)
(She's the same person they saw at the commissary.)
That cleaner is a fake.
(Jong Kook instinctively sensed that the cleaner has something.)
Hold on. That cleaner looks like... We've seen her.
Is there something in here?
(They search her cleaning tools.)
Oh, yes. That's it.
(They found something!)
I was right.
(They found a brown document from the box of cleaning tools.)
- One name tag... - "Name Tag..."
He and Jae Suk... What's going on?
(The other inmates are walking toward the lobby.)
We can't let anyone else see this.
- What should we do? - What is it?
(Yong Ji is startled.)
- "A five-digit number..." - Where should we find it?
(What secret could be written in the document?)
(Name Tag Collection Log)
(A 5-digit number was given in return for 5 name tags.)
(Could the 5-digit number they traded 5 name tags for...)
(be the combination for the lock?)
"Name tags"?
(They can't understand as they haven't seen the lock yet.)
Oh, I get it. So the name tags...
- Who has it then? - It says...
Ma'am, this is a hint, right?
(The cleaner takes the log back.)
Excuse me. May I?
- No, you can't. - I can check it, right?
(Jae Suk snatches it.)
- Can we all see it? - Let me see it too.
No. You shouldn't have let them see it.
(She shouldn't show them.)
Take a look.
(Only Haha who knows it's a 5-digit code understood.)
- Is this a hint? - What does it mean?
There's someone who knows the combination.
- For now... - Excuse me.
(Then Seung Hyun appears.)
- Did anyone find the cell phone? - Come here.
- Haha. - Yes?
I found the phone.
- What? - I found it.
(Seung Hyun found the phone that everyone was looking for.)
- Where? - You shouldn't have said that.
- Sorry? - Why did you say that here?
Just tell us. How did you find it?
(Everyone pays attention.)
- Gosh. I'm so stupid. - How did he...
- Just tell us. How did you find it? - Is that it?
(Everyone is excited to find the phone that has an escape route.)
Is that the phone?
Why did you show it to them? Why?
(You fool.)
- What happens now? - We can check it.
(Inmates gather to see Seung Hyun's phone.)
- We can check it. - Let's do that.
- I already did. - Let's go in.
Close the door.
(Lock the door, so only we can see it.)
- Lock the door. - Come on in.
- Show us. - Why?
(What? Don't close the door!)
- What's going on? - Why are you here?
(Thud)
(The cameraman who was filming Do Kwon couldn't go in.)
- Why are we here? - You should let the cameraman in.
(You should let the cameraman in.)
Hey!
(What are they going to do without the cameraman?)
How could you leave the cameraman alone out here?
- 1 camera is enough for us. - It's okay. We have 1 camera.
(Excited)
- In my opinion... - You should let the cameraman in.
(They forgot that they're shooting. They share the phone hint.)
- This is... - Just read it already.
(What hint could they find on the phone?)
I can't seem to organize my thoughts.
(Boss! Go through the gray wall, and you'll find the final exit.)
(You need a 5-digit code to open it, which you can get...)
(by giving the cleaning lady 5 name tags.)
(I hope you succeed.)
(They'll get the combination if they give the cleaner 5 name tags.)
We have to get them eliminated.
What are you doing?
(He opens the door for another cameraman.)
- Why? - I'll just let the cameraman in.
What about me?
(She's trying to go into the room.)
(Let me in.)
I was the one who opened it.
Let me know too.
- Yong Ji, I'm sorry. - We can't.
- But I... - I'm really sorry. Please leave.
(Yong Ji. This is high-quality information.)
I'm sorry. I think I can tell you everything later.
(They stopped Yong Ji and let only the cameramen in.)
That's weird.
(What?)
(Jae Suk successfully sneaks in like a loach.)
That's not fair.
They all went in.
Come on in.
(Yong Ji enters in the end.)
You're the last one to come in.
Gosh, seriously.
(It's locked again.)
What just happened? Why would he...
(Ha Do Kwon. Why you little...)
You're the last one to come in.
(Jong Kook is not allowed.)
- Can't we share it with others? - No, never.
(More members share the phone hint.)
- Let me see. Or tell me. - Who are you to hold that?
My team found it.
- You should show us too. - Okay. Just a second.
(Yong Ji is happy to be shared with information.)
- Let us see it with you. - You shouldn't do that.
- It says... - Gosh. No.
(Screaming)
- No. - What's going on?
(Do Kwon suddenly attacks.)
- Go away. - I'm almost done. Hang in there.
I said, no.
- I want to do it before escaping. - What is it?
(30 minutes ago, he said he wanted to do something before escaping.)
I want to beat Jong Kook.
Don't try that.
If you do, you won't be able to escape today.
(Do Kwon was adamant, although Suk Jin dissuaded him.)
I really want to get back at him while I'm in here.
Jong Kook will find his partner.
So I'm going to aim at his partner.
That's a good idea.
Stop it. I'm serious.
(He attacks Jong Kook's partner Yong Ji to get back at Jong Kook.)
- Stop it. - I'm almost done.
- Hang in there. - I said, no.
(At that moment, he took off her name tag.)
- Defense. - He wants to...
(But...)
- get Jong Kook. - I have the Defense Right.
- You have the Defense Right? - Yes.
(she has the Defense Right.)
Yes, she has the Defense Right.
(He couldn't eliminate her. He only offended Jong Kook.)
I attacked her just to get Jong Kook.
- But she has the Defense Right. - Are you all right?
Excuse me. It's me, Young Min.
- We can never let him in. - Of course.
(Who's so polite?)
He's the last one we want to let in.
Excuse me. It's me, Young Min.
(He's asking them to let him in politely.)
- We can never let him in. - Of course.
(But they won't let him in.)
He's the last one we want to let in.
What is he doing?
Jae Suk.
(The politest gang member in the world)
That's not it. I should go.
(Yong Ji who used her Defense Right left to put on a regular name tag.)
Yong Ji, you should put on a new name tag.
- Okay. That was crazy. - Do Kwon is so energetic.
(Everyone is surprised by how enthusiastic Do Kwon is.)
Do Kwon is...
(All he wants is to defeat Jong Kook.)
He doesn't care about anything else.
- His son told him to beat him. - I think so.
(I get it.)
(Jong Kook was trying to figure out how to get the lock combination.)
- 1, 2, 3, 4... We need name tags... - Jong Kook.
Yes?
Oh, I get it.
I get it.
- I get it now. - I got eliminated once.
Really? Who did that? Was it Young Min?
- It was Do Kwon. - Do Kwon?
(What?)
- Do Kwon. - Do Kwon?
(I can't believe he did that while I was gone.)
I think I know what it means.
Is it here?
(Jong Kook figured out the secret of the log.)
So how many name tags do we need?
We need 5 name tags for a 5-digit combination.
What do you think that means?
- We should take off name tags. - Correct.
Let's go take off some name tags.
(Enthusiastic)
We need to submit five name tags...
(He must collect five name tags to get the password.)
to get the combination and get out.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk was kicked out too.)
Who is it?
(On guard)
What is it?
I'm just wondering what the text says.
Well...
(They must collect name tags to escape.)
I'm sorry, but we can't tell you that.
Let's get out of this room for now.
(He detects what's going on.)
- It turns out... - You guys are mean.
(Haha and Seung Hyun who spare themselves leave.)
- This is... - Come on out for now.
- I think he has the Defense Right. - Can you show me the phone?
(Share the information with me.)
- I'll give it back to you. - Hurry.
(While following them,)
(Young Min comes back.)
- What is it? - Boss, you should escape.
(He suddenly changes.)
Boss, you should escape.
(Did he just call Suk Jin "Boss"?)
(What is going on?)
What are you talking about?
- You see... - Is he the boss?
I heard you're the boss.
(I heard you're the boss.)
Yes. But don't tell anyone else. Why did you say that here?
Don't tell anyone else. Why did you say that here?
(Was Suk Jin the boss?)
- Hello. - Hello.
(After the shoot on the previous day)
- It's been a while. - Seeing that I'm here alone,
(The production crew called Suk Jin.)
- I guess I have a solo mission. - Correct.
You're taking a risk.
(The production crew)
(The production crew had to pluck the courage to give him a mission.)
- We mustered up the courage. - I see.
- You are... - Yes.
(Ji Suk Jin)
the boss of Petty Gang...
(The boss of Petty Gang)
(A long-term convinct)
who is currently imprisoned.
I see.
Among the new inmates whom you will meet tomorrow,
(Among the new inmates whom he will meet tomorrow,)
(there is a gang member who's come to help him escape.)
there will be a gang member who will come to get you out.
(He must figure out who the gang member is.)
And I don't know who that is?
- The identity of the gang member... - Yes.
is closely related to the letters, "Janbaripa", as in Petty Gang.
(He must focus on "Janbaripa".)
I advise you to take a careful look around the commissary...
(He can find out if he focuses on "Janbaripa"?)
and the cafeteria that will be open tomorrow.
(Boss Big Nose searched items in the commissary whenever he could.)
(He checked a drink with a name that has "jan" in it.)
(Number 2 was marked with a circle.)
(Next, he found a snack with "ba" in its name.)
(And he found number 3.)
Can I eat the whole box or just one?
(He skillfully found "ri" after that.)
(He found 7.)
(Boss Big Nose suspected green onion which is "pa" in Korean.)
(He rummaged through the green onion for a while.)
(He found number 1.)
(So he found the 4-digit number, 2371.)
(It matched the inmate number of Young Min, the gang member.)
(Tapping)
(Boss!)
- Come out here. Come on. - Didn't you find your partner?
Did you tell me to sit down?
(With his outstanding observation ability and concentration,)
- Who do you think is the boss? Yes. - The boss?
- Is it you? - It's me.
(he won over Do Kwon as well as the gang member.)
You and I are the stars of this episode.
Why? This will be over when we get out.
(Do Kwon was tempted when he said they were the stars.)
(However, Kwang Soo who was with them was a problem.)
It's a little different each time.
(He got eliminated only 10 minutes after the race began.)
(Young Min was impressed by the boss' drive.)
Kwang Soo.
You should paint a big picture.
What?
(What is he talking about?)
That's not it.
- We're off. - Take care of him, please.
(Cold-hearted)
Let's go. Let's go, Young Min.
(Now that we've taken care of him, let's go, Boss.)
(Kwang Soo was taken aback as he was eliminated too early.)
But...
(Who are the three of you?)
- Are you three on the same team? - No.
What is this?
(Giggling)
You just have to go to your cell quietly.
(Teasing)
(Spitting)
(Kwang Soo got angry and tried to get back at them.)
(Darn it. I'm so angry.)
(Kwang Soo's attack made them laugh.)
- This is the fun of doing this. - Also...
- He's the gang member. - You should know that.
(They strengthened their unity while eliminating others.)
- Okay? - He's the gang member.
- The 4 of us are on the same side. - The 4 of us are on the same side.
(Including Jae Suk, we're a family.)
We're on the same side.
- Go and tell Jae Suk. - Right. Tell him.
(Suk Jin, the boss of Petty Gang, worked actively in secret.)
What's that?
(He reveals the symbol of Petty Gang.)
I am the boss of Petty Gang.
(Rubbing)
(Warning: It can be erased easily.)
- Look here. It says I'm the boss. - You really are...
- You are the boss of Petty Gang. - And here.
(Like the boss,)
- You really are in the Petty Gang. - He's...
(Young Min appeals his loyalty.)
the gang member. He's the gang member,
- and I'm the boss. - It seems to suit him.
He looks petty, you know.
(He looks petty.)
However, I'm worried because I think...
- that Yong Ji brought Jong Kook. - Exactly.
(Do Kwon is worried about Jong Kook.)
I think Jong Kook came with her. What should we do?
Jong Kook must be...
- furious right now. - Of course, he's furious.
(He's intimidated.)
Because Do Kwon eliminated his partner.
(Anyway, they need 5 name tags to escape the prison.)
I guess we receive something if we submit name tags.
I have a lot.
He took off the name tag of everyone he saw.
(He has so many name tags.)
I lost the name tag I got, so I went back to find it.
(Here's why Do Kwon was collecting the name tags.)
It's a little different each time.
I'll take this as a souvenir because my son likes you.
- Then you'll lose it. - I know.
(For his children,)
He's taking it off.
(he collected the name tags one by one.)
I'll give these to my children.
I'll take this home too.
(I'll take this home too.)
(So he collected four name tags.)
I'm glad I collected them.
(How lucky.)
He's so lucky.
He collected the name tags for his daughter.
(His love for his children brought him a great achievement.)
He wouldn't stop collecting name tags.
I collected them only for my kids.
I had no idea.
- You're lying. - It's true.
(If Do Kwon didn't get them, they would've needed to go back.)
You're lucky.
(Did your father do a good job?)
Do Kwon is a unique case.
He's really unique.
(A father's love helped to get four name tags.)
I'm glad I collected them.
"You need 5 name tags for a 5-digit combination.
We are one short.
(They'll need one more.)
If it's too hard to get one,
we can rip off one of our own name tags and get it.
In the end?
(It's a strategy that the boss never thought.)
Of course. We'll go together.
Gosh, this punk is really smart.
(He's too immersed in his role as a gang leader.)
- Why did you call me a punk? - I was in character.
(I was too into it.)
Gang bosses usually say things like that.
(Do you think you're a real gang leader?)
I thought I was in a movie because they're here with us.
(Boss Big Nose is overly immersed as he hasn't been a boss in a while.)
Here.
(It's time to step out of the room.)
If you get eliminated, I get eliminated too.
If I get eliminated, I'll leave it to you.
(If Boss Big Nose is eliminated, the rest must escape.)
- Then... - Please take care of it.
(Meanwhile...)
It's been a while since we did this.
(Full of energy)
We have to rip off Do Kwon's name tag.
(They all now know that two of the four in the room...)
We have to rip off Do Kwon's name tag...
(are the boss and the gang member.)
and take all of his things.
(They're looking for the four people who are hiding.)
They're not here. They must've gone over there.
(At that moment...)
(Petty Gang and the inmates reunite again.)
- They were in there! - Who?
Jong Kook. You're angry, aren't you?
(They appear in a complete fear befitting of Petty Gang.)
I'm quite angry.
How many of you are there? Is it the three of you?
Do Kwon is hiding in here.
(Why did Do Kwon hide?)
- Why is he hiding? Why? - He said he's scared.
- He set up a barricade. - Do Kwon...
(My children, Dad can get scared sometimes too.)
said that he's afraid of you. That's why.
Do Kwon, come out.
(They finally persuade Do Kwon to step out of the room.)
He said he's going to apologize.
Do Kwon, why did you do it?
I wanted the gold name tag.
(Stuttering)
That name tag.
Please forgive me. I was rash.
Do you only have one name tag right now?
(It's Do Kwon's truthful pleading.)
- I only have one. - Really?
- I'm really sorry, but can we... - In a circle.
(It's now a confrontation of 4 against 4.)
- Can we talk in a wider space? - Let's stand in a circle.
(Regular members do not have any name tags,)
- Why? - Pardon?
(but inmates only need one more.)
If we go to a wider space, it would be easier to film.
- It would be easier to get beat. - No.
(He's spot on.)
Go first, and the four of us will discuss it.
(Petty Gang stands no chance in a head-to-head contest.)
- Because... - Honestly...
- If we don't have each other... - Do Kwon has a ton of name tags.
(We need to rip it fast.)
- Give us a hint. - He already has a lot.
(The remaining members know Do Kwon has many name tags.)
- He has a bunch of name tags. - We're going to talk.
(Petty Gang retreats first.)
Why did they band together?
We have to go and do it. We must rip off our own name tags.
- Right. - There's no need to face them.
(Just rip our name tags and escape.)
- The way that I see it, - Do we need to go that way?
(They are trying to use Jae Suk's strategy.)
we're going to have to face them.
Regardless, only one of the teams can survive.
(Petty Gang moves to the 2nd floor in secret.)
(Their strategy will be revealed if they take too long.)
Right. Only one team will survive.
- There. Hurry. - Where?
- The cleaning lady is there. - Where?
(They find the wandering cleaning lady.)
Hold on. Hold on a minute.
Hold on.
We have four right now.
- Let's rip off your name tag. - Okay.
(You have the Defense Right.)
- Let's rip it off. - Okay.
(They attack Young Min with the Defense Right.)
Here you go.
(They turn in 5 name tags, which include 4 regular and 1 gold.)
- This is five. - This isn't enough.
- Why? - Why?
- This isn't enough. - Why?
These two are...
(The Defense Rights are not exchangeable.)
- They're not exchangeable? - Why did we rip it off?
What do you mean by it's not exchangeable?
(They can only exchange regular name tags that are eliminated.)
- You can't exchange Defense Rights. - You can't exchange Defense Rights.
Just rip mine off. Oh, wait, Young Min dies then.
- First... - I don't die.
(Young Min and Jae Suk must be eliminated for the boss.)
Young Min and I must die here.
I think... No.
Then you need to die.
(They decide to sacrifice for the gang.)
Right, I do.
Hurry.
- We have no choice. - We have no choice.
I don't know if we'll be able to escape.
- We have to get out. - We have no choice.
(Yoo Jae Suk and his partner, Kim Young Min are eliminated.)
We have no choice. Here. There's five.
(They got five name tags.)
- Jae Suk and Young Min are out. - What?
I told you.
(They got us.)
Do you think they're trying to go down with the combination?
(Now, the remaining inmates must act fast.)
Should we go to where the combination is?
Do you think they're trying to go down?
We have to catch them and rip off their name tags then.
(In the meanwhile, Petty Gang...)
You know what I'm saying, right?
(finally acquires the password.)
- Your name tag... - 42...
- needs to be ripped off to win. - 42098.
- Okay? - Can we go down now?
(You must successfully escape!)
(Catch Petty Gang!)
Let's go up.
- We'll go out and distract them. - Okay. Distract them.
- Then go down this way. - No.
(They come together to risk their luck when...)
They're here.
(the boss has been seen.)
- Hey. - Run!
(Petty Gang has the escape password.)
Go that way!
Hold on. That way.
(If they don't catch them, Petty Gang will escape.)
- Go back. Downstairs. - Downstairs.
- Move. - Where are you going?
(Petty Gang barely gets away thanks to the gang's sacrifice.)
Hurry up.
Open the door.
Go.
They're over here!
(But they are in the front of them as well.)
- What should we do? - They're over here!
(Boss is retreating.)
- Haha. - Come here!
(Jong Kook caught him.)
Come here.
I ripped it off. He's out.
He still has a chance.
(He survived because it was protected by a Defense Right.)
I ripped it off. He's out.
(Meanwhile, Do Kwon, a man who's like fire,)
(locks the door again.)
Try opening that door.
Suk Jin's name tag.
(While Do Kwon distracts everyone, the boss disappears.)
(Escaping at full speed)
Suk Jin had two name tags.
(We are in trouble.)
10 minutes until the truck leaves.
(They have 10 minutes left before the escape car leaves.)
- He opened the door. We got him. - Open it!
(They finally open Do Kwon's door.)
Hold on! Jong Kook.
(Help us.)
- You said you'd forgive me. - We got him.
Okay.
Fine, I'll be heroic and go against Jong Kook.
Hurry.
(Ha Do Kwon versus Seung Hyun and Haha)
Get in here.
- Get in here. - What is this?
(Then...)
Okay.
- Get in here. - What is this?
(Haha is out.)
(Jong Kook eliminates Haha...)
- Okay. - Haha and Seung Hyun are out.
(and Seung Hyun first.)
Why?
(In the world of inmates, there are no eternal allies or enemies.)
Give me a second.
There aren't any cameras in here.
Let's take this outside.
(It's Jong Kook versus Do Kwon.)
Let's do it right outside.
- Yong Ji, come in here. - Jong Kook.
Let's go someplace nice.
This isn't a nice place. Let's go someplace nice.
(Do Kwon must drag time,)
(Jong Kook must eliminate him as fast as he can.)
- Let's go someplace nice, please. - Hold on.
42098. Do Kwon needs to get here.
(Boss Big Nose is nearing the escape door.)
- Let's look cool. - Hold on.
Yong Ji, follow me.
You can't go with him!
- You can't go with him! - Hurry up and follow me.
(Jong Kook and Yong Ji leave to go after the boss.)
(He's almost there.)
Do Kwon needs to get here.
(Do Kwon leaves the room to protect the boss.)
(But...)
Hold on.
(This was all a scheme orchestrated by Jong Kook.)
I'm standing backward on the stairs.
(He successfully lured Do Kwon out.)
(Ha Do Kwon versus Kim Jong Kook)
Yong Ji, come here.
(Ripping)
Hold on.
(This is a match where their pride is on the line.)
(Do Kwon isn't losing to Jong Kook.)
(At that moment, Yong Ji goes behind him...)
(and successfully rips off his name tag.)
(Ha Do Kwon is out.)
- Ha Do Kwon is out. - We did it.
- Ji Suk Jin out. - What?
(Boss Big Nose is eliminated in front of the escape door.)
- Why? - Your partner got eliminated.
(Boss Big Nose got eliminated just one step away from winning.)
This is driving me crazy.
(I almost won.)
Is it over?
- Good job. - Good job.
(Do Kwon lost but fought well.)
I wanted to face you 1 on 1.
You have less than two minutes to escape.
(But the race is over only when they successfully escape.)
(This is the memo with the passcode he hid earlier.)
(Jong Kook and Yong Ji need this number.)
(Chewing)
- No. - Hey!
(He's chewing up the only record of the passcode.)
You shouldn't eat that!
You shouldn't do that.
(What's wrong with you, Do Kwon?)
It's delicious.
- Give it to us. - Hurry.
(They only have a minute and a half left.)
- Hurry. - Hurry up and give it to us.
(Yong Ji and Jong Kook are done if they fail to escape.)
- We should go. - Share the prize.
(I need to give to my children.)
Okay. I'll give it to you.
(Urgently)
You can give it to your daughter.
(Spitting)
I'll give it to you. You can give it to your daughter.
- Don't do this. This is gross. - Let's go.
(It is 2:59pm.)
This is so gross.
(They have to get on the truck prepared for the boss to win.)
What is the number?
This is the number.
What is it?
(Do Kwon's last fight took up a lot of time.)
This is so gross.
- 2? - 42098.
- 4, 2, 0, 9, 9, 8. Yes. - 0, 9, 8.
(They enter the password 42098.)
- 9, 8. Yes. - 8.
(They unlocked the lock.)
- We got it. - We got it.
- Gosh. - Let's get on.
(They finally found Petty Gang's escape car.)
Gosh. In the back.
(After many twists and turns, they are about to escape.)
Gosh.
My goodness.
You've successfully escaped!
(Regular inmates, Jong Kook and Yong Ji, successfully escape.)
We did it. Okay.
(The race is over.)
The final result of the race.
(It's time to announce the final result of the race.)
Kim Jong Kook and Kim Yong Ji have successfully escaped.
(Kim Jong Kook and Kim Yong Ji have successfully escaped.)
I was almost there.
(I was close.)
I'll show you the prize set.
(It's a complete set of tofu to celebrate their escape.)
It's tofu.
It's really tofu.
There's even a gift card.
(A 100 dollar gift card)
- Congratulations. - There's a 100-dollar gift card.
(Are you going to give them to me?)
- Really? - Amazing.
(Congratulations.)
- We'll send you the mobile coupon. - Okay.
This supermarket is known to have a large variety.
- Right. - Is this a product placement ad?
(Is it not PPL?)
I agreed to give my prize...
to Do Kwon.
- He doesn't like it. - So he can give it to his daughter.
(This is a gift for Do Kwon, who put on a great fight.)
This is for Do Kwon.
He put the combination in his mouth and refused to give it up.
(He's persistent.)
He tried to chew it up and eat it at the end.
- Really? - Yes.
(Son, this is how hard I worked.)
(That's enough.)
- He's so nice. - Well done, everyone.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(We'd like to thank Ji Seung Hyun, Kim Young Min, Kim Yong Ji,)
(and Ha Do Kwon for running with us on this hot day.)
(August 3, 2020, at 3pm, Inside the Interrogation Room)
Hold on.
(One suspect is shedding tears.)
- What? - What is this?
- My gosh. - What is this?
(And two men are watching him.)
What's with him?
Everyone is weird all of a sudden.
(4 hours before the incident)
- Isn't this the airport? - You're right.
(International departure)
Are we going a trip somewhere?
(Security Checkpoint)
- "Morning Soccer Club"... - "Pre-season training"?
(Running Morning Soccer Club Pre-season training introduces...)
It's Kwak Do Won.
(Kwak Do Won, Kim Sang Ho, Kim Dae Myeung)
- It's Kim Sang Ho. - It's Kim Sang Ho.
You have been arrested in the act of smuggling salt.
(However,)
(they are the suspected salt smugglers...)
- You are on the suspect list. - Why does he have salt?
(and are banned from traveling.)
(Through domestic investigation,)
Why are you acting suspicious?
(they must distinguish the criminals hiding amongst them.)
Are you a police officer or a citizen?
What? Do you think it makes sense? It doesn't.
(Criminals and police officers are hidden amongst innocent citizens.)
- We have to find them. This is bad. - The criminals and police officers?
(A silent pursuit for them is starting.)
- What? - The criminal chose the criminal.
(Everyone is surprised at what happened in the investigation room.)
One of us could be the criminal.
(How will the terrible case of the salt smugglers end?)
I'm not a criminal. I'm telling you that I'm not.
I'm a police officer.
My gosh, stop being a fool.
(Operation: Clear Out the Criminals, Domestic Investigation)