- Hello.
- You're here. Hello.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
- This looks good.
- I like the color.
How was it yesterday?
- Did you go there?
- Where?
To So Min's place? I didn't.
I just talked to her on the phone.
(The prize for last week's winner)
(Invitation to So Min's house)
I called her.
- She really liked it.
- When are you going to visit her?
I should go next week.
- You should definitely go.
- We need to shoot it.
- That's right. It's a prize.
- We have to shoot it.
- Okay.
- It was a penalty.
I know. It's not a prize.
And Ji Hyo took
the Bluetooth earphones.
- Did she take them?
- I gave them to her.
She might think you got her
broken earphones.
- "It has no cords."
- "It's broken."
It will work if you stomp your foot.
I don't think she can connect
the Bluetooth earphones.
- She can't.
- I'm sure she can't do it.
Hey, adjust your clothes first.
- Hey.
- Take your time.
No rush.
(Running hurriedly)
You suddenly started
running right here.
We don't usually come
doing up the zipper like that.
Seriously, how could you...
(We don't usually come
doing up the zipper like that.)
(A 10-year veteran
shows up in a shocking way.)
Why are you zipping up
your pants like that?
How could you
come running like that?
- I was really surprised.
- I'm sorry.
Ji Hyo, you're unbelievable.
This is what makes
Ji Hyo attractive.
Today, we are going to have...
the first Running Man Quiz
for the Ultimate Winner.
(1st Running Man Quiz
for the Ultimate Winner)
- Yes!
- What?
- A quiz show?
- Why are you excited?
- Why do you like it?
- I can outperform you guys in this.
- So it's a quiz competition.
- What are you talking about?
- I can outperform you guys in this.
- He's being ridiculous.
Hey. You and you.
- Not me.
- And you. You are a stupid trio.
- What about Ji Hyo?
- A stupid trio?
- Why are you being quiet?
- He skipped Ji Hyo.
- Captain.
(She's the real captain.)
- Captain?
- There, there.
- Okay.
- Yes, Captain.
(She's on another level.)
Ji Hyo hasn't shown
what she's got yet.
- Once she opens up...
- She will be unbelievable.
- I agree.
- Ji Hyo is a little short and...
- Why are you standing there?
- I'm not like you guys.
- Come here.
- I'm not that bad.
- You're the last here.
- Seriously.
It's just like hyeongseoljigong.
- You still don't know what it is.
- I'm going.
(He tries to change the subject.)
- Come over here.
- I'm coming.
- This seems right.
- Bye.
- I know it now.
- Okay.
So today, we are going
to have special guests...
who showed off their intelligence
playing detectives.
- Detectives?
- Are they detectives?
Please come on out.
- Detectives?
- Who's here?
(What 4 actors had detective roles?)
- Did they play detective roles?
- My gosh.
It's Yeon Joo.
My gosh.
(She showed her intellectual beauty
playing a detective in "Cheo Yong".)
(As a member of Mensa, she takes
part in the quiz competition.)
Hello.
(She's acknowledged to be the best
detective. Actress Park Hyo Ju)
(She played a charismatic detective
in "The Chaser" and "Triangle".)
(Hyo Ju is a professional actress
who plays many intelligent roles.)
- Oh, hello.
- My goodness.
(Actor Kwak Si Yang specialized
in playing detective roles)
(He played a homicide squad
inspector in "Welcome2Life".)
(He's loved in many dramas with
his good looks and touch charm.)
(And lastly...)
- That's Yi Kyung.
- What's going on?
What?
- It's Yi Kyung.
- Hello.
(From the movie, "Hitman")
(Actor Lee Yi Kyung who played
a wiry detective in "Hitman".)
- Hello.
- Please stand in the middle.
- Please come over here.
You're not a detective.
You're a criminal.
Don't act like you two
are close friends.
- We are close.
- Move over.
- Go over there.
- We really are.
I'm close with Yi Kyung.
- I see.
- We're close.
Let me introduce them one by one.
First, please introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Park Hyo Ju.
Nice to meet you.
She looks like a real detective.
I know. A righteous detective.
She's an actress with 20 years of
experience. She prepared something.
It's not that I prepared it.
She will show us her salsa dance
that she learned in Cuba.
- Salsa dance?
- My gosh. Salsa?
- I've never seen it before.
- From Cuba.
She learned it from a human
cultural asset of Cuba.
- Yes.
- Really?
- My goodness.
- This is my first time to see it.
In Cuba?
- Cuba.
- My gosh.
I like the song.
- Oh dear.
- Senorita.
(Her calm and confident face
shows the vibes of Cuba.)
(The intro reminds her
of the dance lesson from Cuba.)
(They all are excited
to see her get ready.)
Havana.
(What?)
- It's a little strange.
- Isn't it Jae Suk's move?
Isn't this what Jae Suk does?
Did you learn this in Cuba?
Why did you go all the way
to Cuba to learn this?
- Hyo Ju. Hang on.
- Look at her.
Hyo Ju, wait.
- I just don't get it.
- Hang on. I'm so surprised.
It looks strange.
Wait. Hang on a second.
Please stop the music.
Hang on. I'm so surprised...
that I called her Han Hyo Ju
and Go Hyo Ju.
Is this the Cuban style?
Did she lie about Cuba?
Salsa is all about enlightenment.
When I danced salsa in Cuba,
I was told to open up my mind.
It's us who can't open up.
- We're supposed to open our minds.
- It's shut tight.
She's even worse than you, Jae Suk.
You were even worse than me.
- I just don't get it.
- Give her a big hand anyway.
- It's the Cuban style salsa.
- She's good though.
All right. Yeon Joo,
please introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Ha Yeon Joo.
- Ha Yeon Joo.
- Her last name is Ha too.
Let me tell you a bit
about Yeon Joo's filmography.
In 2016, she played the passionate
detective in "The Ghost-Seeing..."
- "Detective Cheo Yong 2".
- That's right.
In 2014, on the game show,
"The Genius: Black Garnet"...
You were on that show?
How far did you go?
- I went pretty far.
- Aren't you a member of Mensa?
I am.
- You are?
- Really?
What's your IQ score?
It's a little over 150,
but I don't remember exactly.
Haha's height is
a little over 150cm.
All of a sudden?
(Haha's height and Yeon Joo's IQ
are both a little over 150.)
We have something in common.
- Yeon Joo was in my debut sitcom.
- That's right.
(So what?)
What's with your face?
- Did I say something wrong?
- Kwang Soo...
No one seems to remember
working with Kwang Soo.
I'm sure she does.
- I do.
- She does.
- Do you remember it?
- Of course.
- Really?
- He liked me and chased me.
- She means, in the sitcom.
- In real life?
- In the sitcom.
Not in real life.
Just in the sitcom.
- I get it now.
- Gosh.
- I get it.
- Just in the sitcom.
I mean, just in the sitcom.
Next up is...
- Kwak Si Yang.
- It's been a while.
- That's right.
- I almost didn't recognize him.
Does playing a detective
come naturally to you?
No, I struggle a lot.
- Why?
- You have to think a lot.
- You have to look sharp too.
- Okay.
Which of us do you think would be
best at playing a detective?
(Who looks like a detective
to Si Yang?)
- Jong Kook totally looks like one.
- Jong Kook...
Jong Kook would make...
- a really good detective.
- He'd be good at it.
- The Violent Crimes Unit.
- Seriously...
Who looks like a petty offender?
- A petty offender...
- An extremely petty offender.
- There are many candidates.
- This can hurt your pride.
I'd rather be a financial offender.
There's someone who would be
good at playing such a role.
- Who?
- Kwang Soo.
I've played a police officer.
- Please show us.
- I've played a police officer.
Please pretend
you just got arrested.
Si Yang.
- You're being interrogated.
- What's your name?
- What did you do?
- Pardon?
- What is it?
- What?
- What are you here for?
- What do you mean?
I just made a little mistake.
You punk.
(You punk.)
(What was that?)
It suits you.
He didn't hit you hard.
- He's only a petty offender.
- He didn't hit you hard.
- It's just that I feel offended.
- Exactly.
Also, I thought he swore at me.
Am I just imagining it?
He's so good.
Next up is Lee Yi Kyung.
(Another actor known for
his detective roles)
- Hello.
- Our friend, Yi Kyung.
"Leave Work on Time".
You just released a trot album...
- Really?
- recently.
You sing trot?
- What's the name of the song?
- "Leave Work on Time".
"Leave Work on Time".
Let's hear "Leave Work on Time".
Just play it from any part.
(We're having a team dinner today)
Let's go!
(His powerful voice raises
the audience's expectations.)
(Team dinners are the worst)
(What is that?)
(Jumping)
(I can't watch this.)
- Let me come to work late
- Stop laughing.
(He obviously can't stand
team dinners.)
(I want to go home)
(He continues singing the chorus.)
(He glances at the audience.)
(I can't stand this.)
(Straightforward lyrics,
cute dance moves, and a shy charm)
- This song...
- Thank you.
His boss obviously wanted to have
some fun.
When his shoulders
moved up and down...
Why do I feel embarrassed?
(His shy shoulder movements
are burned into everyone's mind.)
Why did you feel shy doing this?
Yi Kyung's face turned red.
Let's give it up
for our four guests.
Our detectives.
Today's race is Running Man
Quiz for the Ultimate Winner.
After 4 rounds of quizzes,
the top 5 will receive prizes...
according to their places.
- The top five?
- That's easy.
- That's no problem.
- But...
there are
three illegal participants...
who know the answers
to all the questions.
- Three?
- So many?
They know the answers?
The illegal participants will win
if two or more of them...
end up in the top five.
(The illegal participants win if
2 or more of them make the top 5.)
If any of them survive
the final vote,
- they win the race,
- Any of them?
and all the prizes will be theirs.
If all of them are caught,
the prizes go to the top five
excluding the illegal participants.
- We have to catch all of them.
- Even if you know the answers,
- you should pretend you don't.
- You shouldn't show it.
There is a reason why we have actors
who have played detectives here.
After each round,
the person in sixth place
becomes a detective...
and gets to arrest a suspicious one.
If an illegal participant
ends up in sixth place,
he or she may try to arrest
someone innocent.
- They'll try to be in sixth place.
- Right.
- Sixth place?
- Sixth place.
Sixth place?
Since we haven't played
any quizzes yet,
we'll play a simple game
to decide the detective.
Pick one person, and that person
will pick another person, and so on.
The sixth person chosen
becomes the detective.
- Can you be chosen multiple times?
- Yes.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. Like that.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
- If he is a criminal...
- The person he chooses...
- If he is, he'll choose Suk Jin.
- Exactly.
Depending on who he chooses...
That person becomes
the detective, right?
If he is a criminal,
he'd choose another criminal, right?
- Six.
- That's right.
- Yi Kyung?
- That's suspicious.
- We found one.
- Yi Kyung...
- Yi Kyung is the first detective.
Put this badge on
and carry these handcuffs.
(After the round, the detective
gets to arrest 1 person.)
I'm familiar with handcuffs.
Please go change
so we can start the mission.
- Okay.
- Okay!
What's this?
Is it some kind of test?
Everyone.
Welcome to the Running Man Quiz
for the Ultimate Winner.
Gosh.
The first game is...
Write What You Hear.
- Is it dictation?
- That's hard.
(Write What You Hear)
Dictation is no problem.
- It's my specialty.
- Dictation is hard.
It's no problem.
There are two rounds,
which will be played
by 5 and 6 players respectively.
The first round is...
foreign children's song dictation.
- In English?
- Foreign children's songs?
- What?
- In English?
- How could we do that?
- We have to write in English?
Listen to a foreign children's song,
and write down as many English words
as you hear.
- It'll be easy for Yeon Joo.
- She'll hear everything.
- No, I'm not. Me?
- You're good at English, right?
She speaks other languages too.
- Really?
- How many?
I speak a bit of Chinese.
- Chinese?
- English, Chinese...
English, Chinese, Korean...
That's incredible.
I know a bit of Ancient Greek
as well.
(Ancient Greek
in addition to the 3 languages?)
I know a bit of Ancient Greek
as well.
- What's that?
- What?
- Is that a language?
- Why would you learn that?
How do you say hello
in Ancient Greek?
- What's the point?
- Why would you learn that?
How do you say thank you
in Ancient Greek?
I actually don't know.
Then what do you know?
(Shocked)
- What do you know?
- Isn't that the most basic thing?
- "Thank you..."
- Can you say hello then?
Shouldn't you be able to
at least say thank you?
What do you know then?
Seriously...
(She is trying to remember
how to say thank you.)
I know a really funny expression.
She shouldn't really say
she knows Ancient Greek, should she?
I know it, I swear.
Let's try English then.
Do you know how to say thank you?
(Can you say thank you
in English?)
You're starting to doubt her?
- You're being mean.
- Try Chinese too.
At least I know
she is a member of Mensa.
I still don't completely believe...
she knows Ancient Greek.
How could we write down the lyrics
of a foreign song?
A children's song can't be
that hard.
We picked a song
loved by preschoolers.
That hurts my pride.
Please don't say that.
Since you have kids...
- Don't say that.
- All right.
Gosh.
- Here's the first question.
- Okay.
(The first song starts.)
(Listening)
(They're to write down
as many English words as they hear.)
- What?
- They all look so serious.
(They all look serious.)
(From the Mensa member
to Ji Ho's dad, everyone frowns.)
- Gosh.
- What?
- How could we do this?
- I've never heard this song before.
This song is for preschoolers?
They must be so smart.
- He mumbles too much.
- Do you want to hear it again?
Yes, please.
- I can see they wrote many words.
- The song is too fast.
(The song starts playing again.)
(However, their hands...)
(aren't moving so much.)
What is he saying?
Is this really English?
- 1, 2, 3.
- I have no idea.
I think he said, "thumb."
I heard "kissing" too.
- Right. I heard it too.
- And then...
I heard "sing" too.
"Sing."
I heard "bro" too.
"Bro"?
- You heard "bro"?
- Is he in a gang?
I'm pretty sure I heard,
"What's up, bro?"
Haha is amazing.
"Scroll down by to home..."
"Do... My mother was say..."
It should be, "was saying."
"My mother..." What?
Gosh, he's annoying.
You heard "was"?
"My mother was saying..."
- It's hard to hear "was."
- I didn't hear it.
I'm getting suspicious.
I didn't hear "was" once,
but that's grammatically correct.
I'm wondering how you heard that.
- I just tried to make a sentence.
- Okay.
It's hard.
Can we see the lyrics?
It was too hard.
"Down by the bay"
It was "bay"?
It was "grow"?
"I dare not go"
- "For if I do"
- I hear it now.
(It wasn't "was".)
It was "will", not "was".
The words in this song
weren't that easy.
- This wasn't easy.
- Down by the bay?
- Preschoolers know this?
- Preschoolers know this song?
I won't be ashamed
for not knowing this.
What do I do?
My English is terrible.
Guys, don't forget...
that three among you
have already memorized the lyrics.
- All of it?
- When?
Yes, all of it.
We gave it to them this morning.
Hold on a second.
No one seemed like
they had memorized the lyrics.
I didn't get that feeling
from anyone either.
- Kwang Soo wrote a lot.
- It definitely isn't me.
- Here's the second song.
- Bring it on.
What? What's this?
(After an upbeat intro... What?)
I have never heard
a song like this before.
Is this English?
- Hold on.
- What?
(Shadows are cast on their faces.)
Why is he singing like a cheeky boy?
The original song is
"London Bridge Is Falling Down".
Quiet.
(The cheeky version
of "Jungle Jive" is over.)
That was easier than our song.
- But...
- I like ours more.
Why does Se Chan
have hieroglyphics written down?
He's worse than I thought.
He wrote "U" for "woo".
- Here.
- Tell us about what you wrote.
- Sure.
- I heard the "woo" part.
At least that's worth some points.
To the jungle.
There's no N in jungle.
It sounds like "Do you want to die"
in Korean.
J, U, G, L, E. Jungle.
- No, that's Jugle.
- Jugle.
"Do you have a death wish?"
I also heard "swell".
(Are you sure
we heard the same song?)
- Swell?
- That's what I heard. Swell!
The words Si Yang wrote
don't form a sentence.
I only wrote down
the words I could hear.
I, can, do, boom,
woo, and come.
He...
(He's lost for words.)
Is that the best you can do?
There's no way he's the criminal.
Hold on.
Someone did even worse than I did?
Whoever suspects Si Yang
will answer to me.
- He can't be the criminal.
- Hey.
- Anyone else...
- It can't be him.
- Ji Hyo, you're up next.
- I'm not sure about this.
Can to the...
I mean, "Come to the".
I can do the blank say...
Ji Hyo wrote down a lot
considering how she normally is.
I agree.
But this isn't even much.
(It's suspicious for the members
to know even a few words.)
I know this song because
I have a four-year-old at home.
(Hyo Ju knows the song?)
(Hyo Ju says she knows the song
thanks to her toddler.)
- You know the song?
- It's not one I know though.
No one can possibly know this song.
"Come and do the..." What's that?
(She knows the melody.)
- What's that?
- Jungle jive.
- Jive?
- Yes.
- That wasn't an easy word.
- It's Hyo Ju.
Come and do the jungle jive
- That I know.
- How did she know that?
- The following lyrics though...
- Hold on.
Hyo Ju, I'm sorry,
but Detective Lee
is already suspicious.
Before she showed us what she wrote,
I said I was suspicious of her.
The others wrote it down
while listening to the song,
- but she was thinking.
- As if to remember the lyrics.
Because she memorized them?
(Instead of listening,)
(she was trying to remember
what she memorized?)
It's because
I already knew the song.
- We'll know by seeing the footage.
- Busted.
Here's the result
for the first round.
- I'm suddenly nervous.
- Me too.
We need to be
in the top five, right?
And the one in sixth place
will be the detective.
- Right, the detective.
- Let me reveal the scores.
Haha received 110 points.
- That's quite high.
- Really?
You get 10 points
for every correct word.
- My gosh.
- He got 11 right?
110 points seem like a high score.
Jae Suk has 100 points.
- You beat Jaek Seok?
- No way.
- What?
- Something fishy's going on.
- But...
- This can't be right.
No way.
- Haha answered one more correctly.
- I got 110 points.
That puts him in first place.
Yi Kyung received 130 points.
What?
- Isn't that a higher score?
- I'm suspicious of him.
A total of 130 points isn't
really a high score either.
Yeon Joo has 140 points.
Is 140 points the best you could do?
(How can someone in Mensa
only receive 140 points?)
Kwang Soo received 130 points.
(Even Kwang Soo scored 130 points.)
Hold on a second. Seriously?
We...
- Seriously?
- Hold on.
They must be the criminals!
- Get them all.
- I got 130 points?
I scored only 10 points below
someone in Mensa?
This is absurd.
- I got the lowest score?
- He only has 100 points.
Let's move on to the next five.
Se Chan received 40 points.
You at least got some of it right.
Suk Jin has 40 points.
(Suk Jin also got 40 points
even though he jeered at Se Chan.)
(We have the same score!)
We have the same score!
Si Yang received 50 points.
- Take that.
- But...
(Am I truly as stupid as they are?)
If only I wrote one more word.
Ji Hyo received 60 points.
- What?
- No way.
She received a high score.
Jong Kook has 90 points
while Hyo Ju has 110.
(Jong Kook 90 points,
Hyo Ju 110 points)
Next, you will write down...
a foreigner reading Korean.
(Writing down Korean lines
spoken by a foreigner)
What was that again?
We'll be writing down
a foreigner reading Korean.
Listen to the Korean
said by the non-Korean actor...
and write down the words.
You will be ranked depending on...
how close your answer is.
Those who know the answer...
definitely will have
a leg-up in this round.
Of course. Or someone
who saw that movie.
We'll play the movie and
you'll write down the sentence...
that comes after the countdown.
After the countdown?
Yes, this is way easier.
Here's the first quiz.
Cue.
(Sophia,)
(they are my rich friends
from Nairobi.)
(They're quite decent.)
- 3, 2, 1.
- What?
Was that a sentence?
(What on earth is she saying?)
- All right.
- That's the quiz?
- Was that Korean?
- Yes.
- That was Korean?
- Liar.
- How...
- How was that Korean?
- They're supposed to guess that?
- It was all Korean.
- An American...
- Can we hear it again?
Sure, we'll play it again.
Please do.
Listen to what comes
after the countdown.
(Highly focused)
(The sentence is repeated.)
- What on earth was that?
- Together?
- You have 10 seconds.
- Was this Jessi?
(Sabidubidubi dubidaduba?)
That's what I heard.
Hey, write
"Sabidubidubi dubidaduba."
Is it "sabidu" or "dubisa"?
- Sabidu?
- Yes.
(The first quiz is hard to crack.)
I'm clueless.
Show us your answer. Five...
Didn't she say,
"Where are you going?"
Kwang Soo, I'm sure it's hard
to remember what you memorized.
- What are you talking about?
- Ji Hyo, show us your answer.
- Friends?
- What do you think?
Only an illegal participant
would get this right.
(What's the answer?
Is there a criminal among them?)
Are your friends rich, like you?
Where are you going?
It's the same, right?
- Si Yang?
- Do they like SEVENTEEN?
Do they like SEVENTEEN? Like you?
- What?
- SEVENTEEN?
- Do they like SEVENTEEN?
SEVENTEEN?
Blank that likes to wreak havoc.
Together?
- Wreak havoc?
- That likes to wreak havoc?
If that's correct, then...
(They're suspicious of Ji Hyo.)
They're all rich? Really?
I don't have a clue.
I guessed the rich part
since that's what was mentioned.
- Let me show you the answer.
- Sure.
(So what's the answer?)
They like to wreak havoc?
Like you?
(From the movie "Black Panther")
(No way!)
The scene was from
the movie "Black Panther".
I see.
There was such a line?
That one wasn't easy.
But Ji Hyo...
Who wrote "wreak havoc"?
- But I heard it.
- "They like to wreak havoc?"
- You heard that?
- How can one hear that?
- What?
- No way.
- It doesn't make sense.
- That's absurd.
Ji Hyo really heard that?
That doesn't make sense.
Detective, you have your culprit.
- She heard that part?
- "They like to wreak havoc?"
But I heard it clearly.
Fine, think as you wish,
- but I definitely heard it.
- You're the illegal participant.
Okay, we're next.
- This...
- That was absurd.
I'm not kidding though.
- But...
- I heard it.
Be careful not to fall for the trap.
Just so you know,
I can hear this quite clearly...
because I had a lot of friends
who spoke like this in Dongducheon.
Yes, of course.
Se Chan's from Dongducheon.
- It's why it's easier for me.
- Right.
There's not much of
a lead-in this time.
You'll hear it almost straight away.
(Yes, Father.)
- What was that?
- "Yes, Father."
(They prick up their ears.)
(Whispering)
Can you guys be quiet?
I couldn't hear the last word.
Ji Hyo whispered this in my ear.
"Okonomiyaki is to die for."
(Okonomiyaki is to die for.)
Please lift your boards.
I couldn't hear the last word.
(They're about to reveal
what they wrote.)
I couldn't hear the last word.
I couldn't hear it either.
- I couldn't hear the last word.
- I wrote what I heard though.
(What's the correct answer?)
- It all depends on the last part.
- Right.
- I'll reveal the answer.
- It was easy.
Yes, Father.
What's going on?
We're five minutes out.
(From the movie
"007: Die Another Day")
- What?
- We're five minutes out.
No way.
How can one even guess that?
- They all got it wrong.
- What?
- Five minutes...
- I heard "Who's the jerk".
We can hear it easily...
- when it's written down though.
- Tell me about it!
I could hear every single word.
It was as clear as day.
I know.
His pronunciation is perfect.
It was from the movie
"007: Die Another Day".
(No one got close
to the answer this time.)
I don't think there's
a criminal among them.
- No one's an illegal participant.
- No, not in this group.
- So the 3 are here?
- 3 out of the 6 of us?
All the criminals are on that side.
Some of them
could've deliberately got it wrong.
- No way.
- Most of them have high scores.
- Hear me out.
- Why would we...
deliberately get it wrong?
Not one of us wrote down
"We're five minutes out."
- By the way...
- But they have to get sixth place.
Why would they make a mistake
on purpose though?
Out of us...
I'm suspicious of Ji Hyo.
It's not me.
This is fun.
- This is fun.
- It is.
Here's the third question.
I'll get it right this time.
I sit here...
all day and watch people...
- get engaged and married.
- Her pronunciation is accurate.
She sounds Korean.
What about me? What about Su Mi?
When is it my turn?
I understand now.
You'll hear good news soon too.
3, 2, 1.
- What?
- What just happened?
- What was that?
(What just happened?)
Why can't he speak?
Wasn't that French at the end?
What happened?
He was speaking well before.
What just happened?
This is so wrong.
- Did he do that on purpose?
- What was that?
I can't even read this.
They want us to die.
- Write.
- Enough.
If you get this right,
you're the criminal.
He did that on purpose.
Criminals, be careful.
(Try to guess.)
Show me your answers.
- Lift it.
- I'm suspicious of Ji Hyo.
- She wrote a lot.
- She did.
Why is she so good?
Ji Hyo.
- Let's see hers.
- She's good.
Here.
- "Guess..."
- "Guess..." I mean...
- "Guess with me."
"Stay here."
"I'll do something."
- "I'll do something."
- What?
That's what I heard.
"I'll do something."
- Kwang Soo?
- Can you copy his voice?
- "Write..."
"one with me."
"Rustling paddlelomy".
"Rustling"?
"I'll give you an enema."
("I'll give you an enema.")
(They can't believe it.)
An enema?
I...
- Hey.
- "I'll give you an enema."
"Meet up with me and write it down."
"I have a best friend
who's close to blue."
What? We don't understand you.
- I don't know.
- We don't understand.
- I'm not the criminal.
We don't understand you either.
All I heard is "Write it down."
"Write something down."
Are you kidding?
My bad. I couldn't hear anything.
- She earned all her points.
- She's nervous.
- This is fake.
I couldn't hear anything.
It was a foreigner.
- Jong Kook?
- "I came with a friend."
"He's my best friend."
- What?
- "He's my best friend."
"He really trusts me."
- He wrote that much?
- He could hear all those?
Isn't it "I'll give you an enema"?
He wrote that much?
You're acting strange.
It was "trust" at the end.
I'm curious. Let's see the answer.
Do you see this woman next to me?
She's my best friend's fiancee.
She hates me.
(Answer)
(From the movie "Yes Man")
She hates me.
How were we supposed to get that?
"She hates me."
- I heard it.
- He has a good pronunciation.
You can hear it.
Funny enough,
that's exactly what he said.
He was accurate.
This is Jim Carrey's line
from "Yes Man".
That was Jim Carrey?
It sounded like
"How's Jung Jun Ha?"
Combining scores
from the 1st and 2nd questions,
first place is Yeon Joo.
See?
Second place is Jae Suk.
Jae Suk is strange too.
Third place is Kwang Soo.
(Yeon Joo in 1st place,
Jae Suk in 2nd, Kwang Soo in 3rd)
(You're in 3rd place?)
- It's you, isn't it?
- Kwang Soo is third?
Okay, I understand
why you're doubting me.
- I was surprised too.
- Fourth place is Yi Kyung.
That hasn't changed.
Fifth place is Jong Kook,
Haha, and Suk Jin.
Haha?
This is insane.
Me out of nowhere?
- Haha.
- Really?
It's more odd that
Kwang Soo is third place.
I understand why you're
suspicious of me,
- but I guessed what I can.
- Fine.
Eighth place is Si Yang and Hyo Ju.
Tenth place is Ji Hyo and Se Chan.
Ji Hyo all of a sudden?
She fell behind all of a sudden.
Detective Yi Kyung,
you need to arrest somebody.
After discussing,
please put handcuffs on somebody,
and I'll tell you their identity.
- Yes!
- Please catch them.
- Catch 1 person.
- Let's start by catching 1.
Let's start by catching one.
(He's very cautious.)
First of all,
I'm most suspicious of Yeon Joo...
Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook?)
- Is that a mission?
- He's kind. How sweet.
- What's wrong with you?
- It was untied.
What a sweet guy.
So sweet.
(What a sweet guy.)
(He's shy.)
Go ahead.
(Nobody can stop him
from being sweet.)
I didn't expect it from this guy.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
(Thanks.)
There's one reason I picked Yeon Joo.
In comparison to
her tremendous resume and skills,
she only got 140 points.
She's 1st place,
but this is a low score.
- I agree.
- I object.
- Yes?
- I'm first place,
so there's no reason for me
to do bad.
- That's true.
- True.
She should have paced herself.
I'll pick the candidates,
- and let's do the majority vote...
- Sure.
among them. Okay.
First is Ji Hyo.
- She was odd.
- I agree.
(Candidate 1. Song Ji Hyo)
(She answered a question
nobody else got.)
Hyo Ju.
(Candidate 2. Park Hyo Ju)
I swear it's not me.
(She did well
on English children's song.)
I'm not sure about her,
but that's the general consensus,
so I pick Yeon Joo.
(Candidate 3. Ha Yeon Joo,
She could have earned high points.)
So I pick Yeon Joo.
It's 1 of those 3.
- I agree.
- Just the ladies?
Detective Yi Kyung,
please arrest the first criminal.
Can you give me one wrist?
- It's from those three?
- Everybody?
- You never know.
Yi Kyung.
I'm getting disappointed.
The criminal might have messed up.
- That's true.
- You did too well.
That's why I'm doubting you.
You're putting handcuffs on me?
I'm doubting you
because you did well.
- 1, 2...
- I only...
answered fair questions.
- Ji Hyo?
- It's not Ji Hyo.
(He arrests Ji Hyo!)
- It's not her.
- He arrested her.
- It's up to him.
- Gosh.
- Hey. You. What?
- It's not her.
- He's the illegal participant.
- It's you.
It's not Ji Hyo.
He's the illegal participant.
Ji Hyo? That came out of nowhere.
- You never know though.
- That's true.
- Detective Yi Kyung picked...
- We don't know what she is.
Ji Hyo. Let's check her identity.
- Please.
Ji Hyo...
is...
(Ji Hyo is...)
an illegal participant.
I got chills.
(Ji Hyo is an illegal participant.)
(He arrests Ji Hyo,
an illegal participant.)
Her English was too good
in the beginning.
This is the first Running Man Quiz
for the Ultimate Winner.
You're illegal participants who know
the answers to all questions.
English?
"She's my best friend's fiancee."
"She hates me."
This is so hard.
I couldn't hear it.
I can't believe it.
- Exactly.
- Detective Lee.
- That was incredible.
- How did you know?
But to be honest,
I didn't memorize anything.
I couldn't.
Please hand over
the detective badge and handcuffs...
- to Suk Jin.
- Okay.
- I'll keep playing. Okay.
- You can join.
You just need to get
within fifth place.
I'm telling you.
I'll get first place.
- Okay.
- I'll get first place.
- She got the answers,
- That's possible.
so she knows, but I want to see her
get questions wrong.
I'll memorize.
- I'm not sure if she can memorize.
- I'll memorize.
- That'd be more fun.
- I'm memorizing scripts these days.
Before the second quiz,
it's time for illegal participants
to memorize.
All of you will enter the
memorization room assigned to you.
So that's the memorization room.
This is where
the illegal participants...
will memorize answers
to the next quiz.
The rest of you will listen to music
with headphones on.
Please put your headphones on.
(Everybody enters
the memorization room.)
(Illegal participant 1 is relaxed.)
This is the answer.
(This is the answer.)
This song is always good.
I feel at ease because I got caught.
(Who are the other
2 illegal participants?)
Second quiz is called
Ranking Naggers.
"Ranking Naggers"?
We conducted a survey for
men and women in their 20s to 40s.
This?
So Min is good at this.
She's a dating expert.
Dating expert.
There's a topic for each round.
Guess number 1 to 4.
This is so difficult.
Since Suk Jin is the detective
for Round Two,
you can only speak
if he gives you the chance.
That's important too.
If somebody already takes
your answer, you can't say it. True.
Ji Hyo, did you study?
Of course. I saw the answers.
I'm going to copy her.
- She really wants to spill it.
- Why?
- I want to speak.
- But...
- you know the answers.
- That's why.
I can't give you points.
But do I get a chance too?
You'll get your turn
at the very end.
Be patient.
You can't let her rise
from 10th place.
Right? You have to keep her there.
- Wait.
- Everybody,
here is the first question.
Top 5 things that make you upset
with your lover.
We need So Min for this.
Isn't it when you're sick?
- I'm sure.
- When I'm sick.
- When you need them.
- When they...
What do you think, Ji Hyo?
(What does illegal participant
Ji Hyo think?)
- I think...
- Listen to Ji Hyo.
when they care more about
somebody else.
- That's true.
- When they care about others?
That's when you feel upset.
That applies to this.
It's true though.
- But...
- I...
- But that...
- Wait, Suk Jin.
Ji Hyo was about to talk,
so let's listen to her.
Okay.
(Blinking)
- But...
- Please keep talking.
You were going to say something.
I forgot.
For goodness' sake, Suk Jin.
- Why did you do that?
- She was spilling information.
- I didn't say anything.
- It's all Suk Jin's fault.
You're the one who spoke the most.
- You should've listened to her.
- Taking care of someone.
She is trying to remember.
(She fails to remember anything.)
This one is childish,
but you become upset
with your lover...
- when the replies become short.
- Really?
- They become shorter.
- If they used to be longer...
- They become clipped.
- How about this?
The lack of emojis.
- Emojis?
- There are many things.
- Some people don't use them.
- You become upset...
when your lover doesn't use emojis.
How do you feel when your lover
only replies with emojis?
(Only emojis)
The emojis would be like...
"I am angry.
I will overturn the table."
(That person doesn't want to have
a conversation.)
I know the ones he is talking about!
Let's say you asked,
"How are you feeling?"
(Completely unrelated)
Adults do that.
Every last text
Jae Suk sends me is...
a series of strange emojis.
It's completely unrelated
to the conversation.
- He sends the bomb emoji...
- Really?
- or the smiling face emoji.
- I often send Kwang Soo...
- the angry face emoji.
- Yes.
He sends me that last
regardless of what we have said.
"See you tomorrow, Jae Suk."
Then he suddenly sends
the angry face emoji.
I reserve that emoji for two people,
Sae Ho and Kwang Soo.
I haven't received a single emoji
from him.
With Suk Jin, I write words
in a businesslike tone.
Emojis are for other people.
With Kwang Soo, Sae Ho, and Se Chan,
- I use the angry face emoji.
- The angry face emoji.
You know,
- there is something my wife hates.
- What?
- Her name is Ryu Su Jung, right?
- Yes.
Why are your palms so blue?
- I touched these jeans.
- Did your wife cane your palms?
- Why is the dye coming off so much?
- His palms are so blue.
- It's because of my jeans.
- Please be understanding.
- My goodness.
- My jeans are really blue.
- I am worried about you.
His blood doesn't reach his hands!
I thought your palms were bruised.
- You have Mongolian spots on palms.
- It's the color of my jeans.
(Everyone worries about
Suk Jin's possible illness.)
- Se Chan, what you think?
- Well,
- lovers exchange gifts...
- That's right.
- on an anniversary and such.
- Yes.
If the man paid...
this much...
About 50 dollars?
- Let's say he paid 50 dollars.
- Really?
Then the gift receives
should cost 40 or 35 dollars.
If it costs 20 or 10 dollars,
it's a bit upsetting.
It's a bit upsetting.
Isn't it great to receive
a handwritten letter?
A handwritten letter is nice.
- In exchange for this?
- A handwritten letter is nice.
Still...
I wouldn't be able to give
a nice reaction...
if I received a handwritten letter
for a 50-dollar gift.
It would make me ponder.
"How did I receive
a handwritten letter?"
That's so funny.
If I receive a handwritten letter...
- instead of a gift...
- It's a heartfelt gesture.
That would be nice, but...
We talked about
a lot of upsetting things.
It's hard to determine
the top five things.
Let's start from the bottom.
10th place, Yang Se Chan.
Everything we talked about
is plausible.
- But people in their 20s and 30s...
- I bet we guessed some.
Of course, we did.
Let's say your lover
only looks at his or her phone.
- That's right!
- That's the worst.
- They only look at their phones.
- I know how it feels.
- I will go with that one?
- Which one? The phone?
When they meet you,
they only look at their phones.
It must be on the list.
(Se Chan intercepted
Jong Kook's answer.)
(Will it be correct?)
(Correct)
I stole your answer.
What the ranking?
- That's incredible.
- Top one?
It's top one.
(He got the top one item!)
- I should have said it.
- It didn't even occur to me.
- I don't believe it.
- It makes sense.
- Who brought it up?
- Jong Kook did.
That's incredible.
Jong Kook put it out there...
and I got it right,
not an illegal participant.
You receive 50 points.
I gave him a big one.
The second person to go...
will be me.
I am not an illegal participant.
- You said we will follow an order.
- I want to go next.
- Why are you cutting in line?
Hold on. You said we will move up
from the bottom.
- You said we will follow an order.
- It's up to me.
- It's true, but...
- Suk Jin is the absolute worst.
Forgetting an anniversary.
- That makes sense.
- It's bound to be in the top five.
I don't know
if it's applicable to lovers.
- Isn't it in the top five?
- No, it isn't.
It isn't in the top five.
It isn't applicable to lovers.
- Married couples do that.
- They forget an anniversary.
Who is next?
- I am suspicious of Jae Suk.
- I am not it.
Jae Suk, I will give you a chance.
They reply...
too late.
They replay too late?
- Wait a second!
- Hold on.
What do you think you are doing?
They don't check their phones
when they go out.
That's a good one.
They don't check their phones
when they go out?
No.
Hold on.
(You Quiz on the Break)
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- How many answers are you giving?
It's just that
my thoughts aren't organized.
Then don't go.
- Let someone else go.
- Hold on.
- Do you want to go next?
- I will go now.
I think I know one.
They don't check their phones
when they meet friends and such.
Gosh, I thought it would be right.
- There must be something similar.
- My goodness.
Illegal participants,
aren't you going to make a move?
Two illegal participants remain.
Aren't you going to make a move?
Kwang Soo.
There must be something
about keeping in touch.
It's when they ignore texts.
- It's when they reply late.
- Be quiet.
They reply late.
(Is it as Jae Suk said?)
(Is it correct?)
- I knew it.
- Okay!
It's a guess though.
By the way,
why did Jae Suk give him
the answer?
Why did you give him the answer?
What is this?
(Did Jae Suk give the answer
to avoid suspicion?)
- What is this?
- He didn't mention the restroom.
("Restroom" was
the important keyword.)
Didn't someone mention
"Restroom" earlier?
- Jong Kook did.
- That's...
(When they were guessing
the answers earlier)
(Don't you go to the restroom?)
(Jong Kook mentioned "Restroom.")
I got two answers right.
He got the top 1 and 5.
- Hold on. He got the top 1 and 5.
- Jong Kook.
I simply made a guess.
Jong Kook, you became...
an illegal participant candidate.
My goodness.
He took out handcuffs.
- Listen.
- Hey,
- I just have...
- I was so surprised.
a good hunch.
- No way.
- No?
I am not an illegal participant.
We shouldn't give Ji Hyo a chance?
I should still get a chance.
You can't skip me.
We need to follow an order.
She saw the answers.
I will go with...
(It's a good chance for Ji Hyo
to move up places.)
They...
take better care of someone else.
- Ji Hyo mentioned it earlier.
- It must be an answer.
- Did she say an answer?
- It seems that way.
- Isn't it an answer?
- Is it incorrect?
It seems that way. Is it incorrect?
What is going on?
- What is up with her?
(She is an illegal participant
who doesn't remember the answers.)
- Hey.
- What is going on?
- What is up with her?
- Is she a double agent?
- How did I catch her earlier?
Are you sure
you are an illegal participant?
What kind of an illegal participant
is on the 10th place?
Does she have a mission
within a mission?
Didn't you give her the answers?
You can get the answers right.
(What is up with her?)
The production crew
is incredulous.
- What is going on?
- The producer became angry.
Ji Hyo, what's going on?
What's surprising is this.
Some people have seen the answers.
It wouldn't be strange
to get it right at this point.
It wouldn't be strange, Kwang Soo.
- I am not an illegal participant.
- Who saw the answers?
Maybe they don't know the answers.
Se Chan, you can go first.
We are moving up from the bottom.
Why do you keep letting
the bottom ones go first?
The bottom ones should go first.
Se Chan.
He keeps giving Se Chan a chance
because he won't get it right.
Aren't you going to go?
Then someone else will go.
- I will go.
- Pass.
We can give Ji Hyo a chance.
Ji Hyo, give us an answer.
What?
Ji Hyo, go ahead.
- Go ahead.
- She won't get it right.
- Ji Hyo doesn't remember.
- Her mind is blank.
Ji Hyo doesn't remember.
When you say "I love you"
and they answer halfheartedly.
That can't be... What?
Why did you give her a chance?
(A big twist)
She memorized the answers.
Why did you give her a chance?
She heard Yi Kyung's answer.
When you say "I love you"
and they don't say it back.
(She raised her hand
upon hearing Yi Kyung's words.)
She heard Yi Kyung's answer.
Did she hear Yi Kyung's answer?
- I told Se Chan.
- I was going to say it,
but you give Ji Hyo a chance.
The police gave her a chance.
You are a corrupt police officer.
You should have told me
that you have an answer in mind.
(After Ji Hyo got an answer right)
When they don't introduce you
to their family.
- That's right.
- Correct!
Okay!
When they don't side with you.
Correct.
(Kwang Soo gets the top 3 answer.)
- I should handcuff him.
- I am not it!
I am not it!
- I should handcuff him.
- I am not it!
It can't be helped.
It's obvious.
Kwang Soo is pretty suspicious.
- It's you, right?
- I am not suspicious.
I got the hints from the others.
You should be apprehended
right away.
- You should be put away.
- I know that I look suspicious.
You will end up in prison.
- Prison?
- This is...
I have no choice
but to apprehend him.
You are right.
- He got 2 out of 5 answers right.
- When he told me...
- about expressing emotions,
- That's right.
I thought to myself,
"It's a really good one."
- What?
- Massage my hand.
For goodness' sake.
He is strange.
Why are you suddenly asking me
to massage your hand?
Can't you just do it?
Listen!
Why would I massage your hand
when I am under fire?
This is driving me crazy.
(The first quiz ends.)
The next one is...
top 5 things women do
that mislead men.
I know the answers.
- I know the answers.
- I am 100 percent sure.
This is...
- I can give an answer right away.
- Me too.
- Give me a chance.
- Aren't we going to talk first?
- I will answer right away.
Give me a chance.
I will get it right.
- Okay. Give it a go.
- Okay.
You will blow your chance
if you don't get it right.
When they laugh at your words.
All right!
(He gets a correct answer
right away.)
- That one had to be up there.
- It goes without saying.
- It's top 3.
- Top 3.
That's right.
It really misleads men.
- I knew it would be up there.
- Think about it.
Kwang Soo fell for it so many times.
(Painful memories make him tear up.)
Because I told you
that she definitely likes you,
you confessed to her confidently.
(He belatedly realized
that she simply laughs a lot.)
I know something
that misleads men very easily.
I bet Se Chan knows a lot
about this.
Suddenly,
women with long hair do this.
They tie their hair in front of you.
- No!
- They do that when they are angry.
- Really?
Why would they be angry?
- They are either angry or hot.
- Isn't this one?
I am sorry, but...
Ji Hyo, how about you?
When I pass by a guy
and our eyes meet,
I do this because I feel awkward.
(Men's hearts flutter.)
"Why did she smile at me?"
It misleads them like that.
It would make men message her
that night.
- Seriously.
- "What was that?"
- "Are you asleep?"
"Ji Hyo, are you asleep?"
"What was that?"
(A smile can mislead men big time.)
- Kwang Soo gets misled a lot.
- That's right.
- I will tell you one right away.
- Let me check the rankings.
Yi Kyung is in fourth place.
Yi Kyung. Pick Yi Kyung.
Yi Kyung.
I am practically controlling
Suk Jin.
(His subconscious got taken over.)
If it's going to be that way,
sit on Jae Suk's shoulder.
- Be a parrot.
- Yi Kyung.
They ask you what you are up to
and check your schedule.
I see.
- They ask you what you are up to.
- That's right.
"What are you up to?"
- "Are you asleep?"
(Correct)
- It's top 4.
- Top 4.
(Yi Kyung got a top 4 answer!)
- "Are you asleep?"
- That's right.
"What are you doing right now?
What are you doing tomorrow?"
Why do some women do that...
- if they aren't interested?
- Seriously,
who would ask those questions
without an interest?
Doesn't it show an interest?
Ji Hyo, tell us.
Why do women ask,
"What are you up to?"
Since So Min isn't here,
I will tell you what I think.
They suddenly became curious
about something.
- Is that all?
- Suddenly.
My heart aches.
- For example...
- "What was his name?"
"What was his name?"
"How was 'The Invisible Man'?"
- "I am thinking about watching it."
- You just have a question.
Do women really do that
out of curiosity?
Let's say you wake up
and see a text that reads,
"Are you asleep?"
It's bound to wake you up.
Then you call your friend.
"Hey, I received a text..."
(Is this a confession of love?)
"while I was sleeping."
The two of you would do that.
I used to call Jae Suk
about these things.
The two of you would do that.
So I told him,
"Confess your love to her."
My goodness.
I was like,
- "What?"
- "Go! Kwang Soo, go!"
I ran forward
like a racehorse, but...
(He doesn't finish his sentence.)
She was very taken aback.
"There is no one like you."
They say that to you.
- I see.
- That's spot on.
(Ji Hyo gets a top 5 answer!)
Unnecessary touches.
(Jong Kook comes next...)
(and gets a top 1 answer!)
Oh, my goodness.
They give you small gifts.
- They look after you.
- Yes.
They look after you.
(He gets a top 2 answer as well!)
- Is it up there?
- It's top two.
- That's incredible.
Is it top two?
- Top two?
- That's incredible.
- Is it top 2?
- Top 2?
That's incredible.
- How did he get all of them right?
- It's top two.
- Top two?
- Hold on. Jong Kook is suspicious.
- Seriously.
- You are really good.
This is so confusing.
Jong Kook is suspicious.
Jong Kook is suspicious, right?
- Jong Kook, you know what?
- What?
You got the top 1 and 2 right.
- I mean...
- He suddenly behaved suspiciously.
- Even in the previous round...
- Jong Kook.
This is so confusing.
Which one is it?
- He is really suspicious.
- This is so confusing.
Kwang Soo, you would know this.
I enjoy talking about
romantic relationships.
If I were an illegal participant,
I wouldn't have tried so hard
to get all the answers.
- I wouldn't have made it obvious.
- You know,
I just collected hints
from the others.
I didn't go overboard
like Kwang Soo.
(The situation gets tight
for the two of them.)
Hold on. What?
- Give me a hand massage.
- Why do you keep asking me that?
People are suspecting me.
Why would I give you a hand massage?
- Just do it.
- He keeps asking.
Can't you do it when I am in pain?
He kept pushing his hand toward me.
- A hand massage, my foot!
- For goodness' sake.
- You know...
- Hey.
Those are the things.
- So Min has done all of them to me.
- Really?
Se Chan said...
So Min has done all of them to him.
So Min has done everything
from top 1 to 5.
She has done everything.
She smiled at me every day...
- and looked after me.
- That's right.
She always met my eyes and smiled.
"What are you up to?
Are you asleep?"
- "There is no one like you."
- That's right.
I had no choice...
but to be misled.
She has done everything.
- That's right.
- So Min.
So Min does those things.
So Min does all of those things.
The top five items are spot on.
So Min should have been here today.
She would have gotten
all of them right.
Seriously.
There are 3 members in 1st place.
(The current rankings
will be revealed.)
3 members in 1st place.
- There are 3 members in 1st place.
- Okay.
Yeon Joo, Jae Suk, and Kwang Soo.
Why me?
I didn't get any answers right.
The member in fourth place
is Jong Kook.
How many places did I move up?
- Jong Kook is on the move.
- I just moved up one place.
Since Haha is on the sixth place,
he will be the detective.
Okay. Detective Haha.
It's either Jong Kook...
or Kwang Soo.
Do you know what's suspicious
about Kwang Soo?
He didn't even answer diligently
for the second quiz.
- That's right.
- He passed over his turns.
He usually gives me a hand massage.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you know why
he didn't do it today?
His hands are sweaty
due to his nerves.
- His hands are sweaty.
- I will give you a hand massage!
- Stop it.
- He is nervous.
His hands are sweaty.
(Suk Jin touches Kwang Soo's hand.)
- His hands are sweaty.
- Right?
Right?
- Catch him.
- His hands are sweaty...
- due to his nerves.
- He usually massages my hands.
He rarely says no.
- Give me your hand!
- I just remembered something.
If we are the options,
you should go with him.
- I think it's him.
- Listen.
I simply repeated
what other people said.
The illegal participants need to be
in the top five in the last round.
So there is a chance
they are laying low right now.
- That's right.
- They wouldn't try so hard now.
Suk Jin, Jae Suk is
really suspicious.
- Jae Suk?
- Why do you say that?
- He is suspicious.
Jae Suk keeps...
- He keeps framing other people.
- Yes.
He keeps talking about
how suspicious other people are.
- Si Yang is ridiculous.
- He is right.
- He is ridiculous.
- He keeps doing that.
That's right.
He got some answers wrong
on purpose.
Sometimes, he got the correct answer
right away.
- I am not it.
- Here is the thing.
To be honest,
it's not just Kwang Soo.
- Right.
- Whenever we play a game like this,
I become suspicious of him.
- Whenever you play a game?
- I want to check his identity.
- Seriously.
- I know what you mean.
I know what you mean.
- Even if you fail...
- Even if I fail...
Why are you so suspicious of me?
Please apprehend a member.
- Please stand up.
- Okay.
- Should I stand up too?
- Yes. Please come here.
- The three of you.
- Me too?
(Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, and Jong Kook)
You are here
because you are annoying.
Seriously.
That's not true.
He is suspicious too.
He is really suspicious.
- The way he answered first...
- Yes, it was a bit strange.
And you two participated
too diligently.
- This is a good selection, right?
- Go ahead.
- There is a chance, right?
- Do what you want to do.
I don't know why
Jae Suk is so annoying.
Go ahead and make a pick.
- This is a good selection, right?
- Go ahead.
- There is a chance, right?
- Do what you want to do.
- I choose him.
- Gosh, I think it's Kwang Soo.
- There is a chance, right?
- Do what you want to do.
(He chooses Jae Suk.)
- I am not it.
- All right.
Let's check Jae Suk's identity,
the member Suk Jin has chosen.
He is putting on
the handcuffs himself.
- You look like a criminal.
- You are it, right?
- He's putting them on.
- Jae Suk's...
- This is scary.
identity is...
(Jae Suk was suspected at the end.)
He is it, right?
(Is he an illegal participant?)
He is not an illegal participant.
Really?
- Really?
- I am not an illegal participant.
I told you so.
You said Jae Suk was suspicious.
I said Kwang Soo is
more suspicious.
He behaved strangely.
Let's go
to the memorization room...
- before the third round.
- Are we going again?
(They enter the memorization room.)
All right.
Let's do this right the next time.
(Who are memorizing the answers?)
(Who are
the 2 illegal participants?)
One of them must be a guest.
That's right.
The third quiz is...
the Mute Dancing King.
What is that?
The person who gives the question...
must describe the given keyword
in one minute with a dance.
The rest needs to guess the answer.
A dance.
Since Ji Hyo got arrested,
she can answer...
only after two incorrect answers.
(Se Chan is the first one up.)
- What?
- What is that?
Is it aerobic dance?
What?
Let me answer. You were urinating,
and it spattered on you.
What?
- Watch.
- What's that?
I will make it clear this time.
- Let me answer!
- I see.
An ugly man is dancing.
A dancing squid.
(Since 2 people gave wrong answers,
Ji Hyo can try too.)
Ji Hyo.
A man who lost weight
doing belly dancing.
(Correct)
Why did she have to suck
the fun out of that?
- You stay out of this.
- I want to join you guys.
We were having fun.
(A person who falls in love
at first sight while roller skating)
You're skating.
Roller skating?
Let me answer.
While you go backward on skates,
you are surprised to see a cute guy.
Let me answer.
- While roller skating,
- And?
you fall in love at first sight.
(Correct)
- He's strange.
- This doesn't make sense.
- You got it right on the first try?
- This is crazy.
- At first sight?
- I can't believe this.
I can't do this.
(Please make a guess together.)
- You should dance.
- Dance.
- Good.
- You're doing good.
Tap dance.
(Did he spill something?)
- Let me answer!
What is it?
Go ahead.
You dropped your phone tap dancing.
- Wrong.
- My gosh.
(He gives more hints.)
- Let me answer!
While tap dancing,
you dropped your iced Americano.
- That's it.
- You dropped your iced Americano.
(Iced Americano?)
- Correct.
- Okay.
- Iced Americano?
- Was it iced Americano?
- How did you know it's iced?
Kwang Soo, how did you know that?
Iced Americano?
- Hang on.
- How did you know?
- Wait.
- Iced Americano.
- How did you know?
How did he know iced Americano?
- It's so strange.
- He knew the exact word.
- Hey.
- Iced Americano?
Was the answer iced Americano?
Hang on.
Did it say iced Americano?
Wait. No.
- It's not like that.
- I'm so upset I didn't catch you.
I'm not an illegal participant.
Oh no. He got caught.
- I'm sorry,
- This is crazy.
but will you dance
with the shackles?
Seriously, I'm not
an illegal participant.
- I'm telling you.
- I'm sure it's you.
Just handcuff him.
(The results after the third quiz)
Now it's time to arrest one.
- Let's arrest someone.
- Haha was a little strange.
- I think so.
- I swear it's not me.
(Haha gave the right answer right
away with Ji Hyo's lame gestures.)
- I think you are strange.
- What was strange?
Iced Americano is even stranger.
It was the strangest thing.
Gosh, no.
(Kwang Soo said iced Americano
of all kinds of beverages.)
Just arrest him.
(Haha is the detective
for this quiz.)
- Catch him.
- But, Haha...
(He arrests Kwang Soo immediately.)
What's that?
- Handcuff yourself.
- Seriously, it's not me.
Go ahead and put them on.
You can live at ease from now on.
Who do you think it is then?
Recommend someone.
- I understand it can be mistaken.
- So recommend someone.
What is that written on your arm?
(What is that written on your arm?)
- What?
- What is that written on your arm?
(Did he write something on his arm?)
What did you write?
(Something is written
on Kwang Soo's arm.)
Gosh, what's that?
Get off. Let go.
Hey, what is this?
- Just let go of me.
- Look at this.
Can't you memorize it?
(Something is written in red.)
(Kwang Soo is a usual suspect
with something written on his arm.)
- Let go of me.
- Let me see.
You guys are illegal participants
who know all the answers.
I know all the answers?
- Quiz?
- And...
I know the answers?
And Ji Hyo and I are here?
(He has only himself to turn to,
so he made a cheat sheet.)
Look at this.
It has all the answers.
- My gosh.
- It's him.
I can't believe this.
This is so frustrating.
I thought it didn't make sense.
I told you. He sounded strange.
Kwang Soo is...
an illegal participant...
- Can we say it all together?
- Sure.
- He is an illegal participant.
- My gosh.
Why did you write it down here?
- What does it say?
- We need one more.
My gosh. This film set is amazing.
What's all this?
- Gosh, what's this?
- It's a large-scale studio.
(It's a splendid stage...)
(for the finals
of the 11 participants.)
(It's the last place for
the Running Man Quiz Competition.)
- What is all this?
- Is it that serious?
You should've told me sooner.
(We told you earlier.)
- I'm intimidated.
- What's all this?
Is it that big a deal?
Like I said, this is our first
quiz competition in 10 years.
So we want to do
things right for the finale.
It makes me want to win.
- You want to go up there, right?
- Yes.
Forget it. We just need to pick out
the last illegal participant.
- So it's not Jae Suk.
- It's not Jae Suk.
- It's a good thing.
- It's not me.
(Who is the last
illegal participant?)
This is the first Running Man
Quiz for the Ultimate Winner,
Quiz Kingdom.
(The last round, Quiz Kingdom)
Let me explain the rules
of the final round, Quiz Kingdom.
Gosh, what's all this?
The keywords for each question
will be revealed first.
Then we will select players...
for each question randomly
using this machine.
The four selected players will go up
on the stage and give answers.
Before the quiz,
you can make a bet...
with the points you have scored.
Okay.
(If they get the right answer,
they score points.)
We shouldn't fall for the keywords.
Then let me show you
the keyword for this question.
- Okay.
- Keyword.
It's the keyword.
The keyword for this question is...
a four-character idiom.
Please. I want
to avoid this question.
A four-character idiom.
four-character idioms are difficult.
- It's quite difficult.
- It's not easy.
It's hard to guess an idiom
with its meaning.
- I know.
- All right then.
Let's select the players then.
Please show us.
Gosh, this is hard.
Don't pick me.
- Who will get picked?
- Don't pick me.
This is difficult.
The players for this question are...
- Me?
- Yang Se Chan, Lee Kwang Soo,
Lee Yi Kyung, and Yoo Jae Suk.
- Me?
- Yang Se Chan, Lee Kwang Soo,
(Besides Kwang Soo,
they all seem hesitant.)
- Good luck.
- Please come up to the stage.
Go, Jae Suk. Bet all your points.
Gosh, look at this.
I'm not sure
about four-character idioms.
You're the best one here though.
You are the best player here.
I don't know four-character idioms.
The keyword is a four-character
idiom. Make your bet.
This is crazy. How many points
should I bet here?
I'll just bet 50 points.
(9th place, Yang Se Chan,
290 points)
(3rd place, Lee Kwang Soo,
410 points)
50 points.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo...
- How many points did he bet?
He wrote 200 points.
This is what I'm best at.
four-character idioms.
- I'll write 200 points.
- Go ahead.
There are idioms
that are hard to guess.
Jae Suk, it's you.
- I'll go with 300 points.
- All right.
(Jae Suk bets 300 points
with the support from the members.)
Jae Suk bets 300 points.
- He's good.
- Go all in.
All the players are done
making their bets.
I will give you a question then.
(Is he looking at the palm
of his hand?)
He's checking his palm.
- What?
- He can't cheat.
- He's cheating.
You told him to memorize
the answers. He can't write it down.
He can't do that.
I'll erase it all.
He's like the movie, "Memento".
- He has to erase it.
- I will erase it.
- He can't even remember it.
- Let's go.
Here's the question.
If you have an ink hand at hand,
you become smeared with ink
before you know it.
And those who touch pitch
shall be defiled therewith.
What is this four-character idiom...
that emphasizes the importance
of the surrounding environment?
- I know the answer.
- He knows it.
I'm sure Jae Suk knows the answer.
(Other members
are thinking carefully.)
(What?)
(He's cheating.)
Kwang Soo! Don't look at it.
- No.
- You can't cheat.
He can't do that.
You are given 10 seconds.
Please write down your answer.
(Kwang Soo!)
(Geunmujihyung?)
Hey, Ji Hyo!
Watch Ji Hyo carefully.
Gosh, what are you doing?
Do not cheat.
Cheating is not allowed.
Please show us their answers.
(Meokjaakhaeng, inmyeonsusim,
heukhwainsaeing, geunmukjaheuk)
Se Chan's answer is meokjaakhaeng.
(Does he want to eat up
all evil deeds?)
It sounds plausible.
Kwang Soo's answer...
is inmyeonsusim.
Inmyeonsusim?
Inmyeonsusim.
Yi Kyung's answer is
heukhwainsaeing.
Lastly, Jae Suk's answer
is geunmukjaheuk.
That's right.
The answer is...
(The answer is...)
geunmukjaheuk.
Jae Suk got it right.
Yes!
Jae Suk knows
a lot of four-character idioms.
- Hang on.
- What?
Hey, can't you even cheat?
The problem is there are
too many four-character idioms.
- I only have the answers.
- He's so...
He only has answers.
He said inmyeonsusim.
Inmyeonsusim?
Why did you say inmyeonsusim now?
(Kwang Soo's
cheat sheet didn't help.)
I should've bet all my points.
No.
Why did you say inmyeonsusim?
I've never heard
of the idiom before.
Ji Hyo, did you tell him the answer?
- Yes.
- Did you know the answer?
- Apparently not.
- She didn't know it.
- What are you two doing?
- Did you tell him the wrong answer?
The keyword for this question is...
a neologism.
- Neologism?
- Neologism.
I'm good at this.
- I'm not good at this.
- We don't know many neologisms.
- The keyword is coined words.
- I don't know.
- It has to be Suk Jin.
- Don't pick me.
Kim Jong Kook, Lee Yi Kyung,
Ji Suk Jin, and Haha. Come on up.
(The 4 middle-aged men
are disappointed.)
And Haha. Come on up.
- My gosh.
- I'm in trouble.
I don't know any new words.
How difficult is it?
- It's not too difficult.
- Medium difficulty?
- Medium difficulty.
Should I turn the game around?
- Should we turn the game around?
- Medium difficulty?
- If you want to, I'm in.
- I want to.
- Let's do this.
- Are you sure?
Let's turn the game around.
Please make your bets.
Let's turn the game around!
- Jong Kook is betting 200 points?
- Let's do this.
If Jong Kook doesn't get it right...
- Yi Kyung is betting 300 points?
- 300 points?
Yi Kyung is suddenly making
such a big bet.
Jong Kook is suspicious, isn't he?
He said it's of medium difficulty.
It's supposed to be
of medium difficulty.
They've all made their bets now.
Here's the question.
The coined word is,
"oh-jeo-chi-go."
- "Oh-jeo-chi-go"?
- "Shi-go"?
- "Oh-jeo-chi-go."
- It's "chi-go."
- This isn't of medium difficulty.
- Is this of medium difficulty?
The meaning is not that difficult.
- Still...
- I mean...
It's definitely not
of medium difficulty.
If Jong Kook gets this right,
we should suspect him.
He doesn't seem to know.
Is it used by students or employees?
- It's used by them both.
- "Oh-jeo-chi-go"?
Please tell us
in which situation it's used.
- He can't tell you that.
- That'd be hyeongseoljigong.
(Se Chan doesn't know
the meaning of the expression.)
- It's totally hyeongseoljigong.
- Is it hyeongseoljigong?
Yes, definitely.
I just took a wild guess.
(No one seems to know.)
I'll write down whatever.
If any of us get it right,
- we should suspect them.
- 5, 4...
2, 1.
Please show us their answers.
"I actually have piles."
"I'll get rid of them."
(It doesn't make any sense.)
- Come on.
- Suk Jin wrote,
"Oh, what a petty, mean jerk."
Suk Jin wrote,
- "Oh, what a petty, mean jerk."
Let's see Jong Kook
and Yi Kyung's answers.
They wrote different things.
- What do you mean?
- Jong Kook and Yi Kyung.
Jong Kook wrote,
"Chicken tonight, yes or no?"
Yi Kyung wrote,
- "Chicken and beer tonight."
- That must be it.
- It's definitely one of them.
- Definitely.
- It's one of them.
- There's no way Jong Kook knows it.
- It's Yi Kyung.
It's Yi Kyung.
- They both bet all they had.
- It's one of them.
Let me announce the correct answer.
- Students...
- What's the correct answer?
(Jong Kook and Yi Kyung made
big bets and wrote similar answers.)
- The correct answer is,
- What is it?
- "Chicken..."
It's "chicken and beer," right?
- "tonight, yes or no?"
- "Chicken"?
What about...
Only Jong Kook gets the points.
- Yes!
- Jong Kook is suspicious.
This one was impossible to guess.
- I'm suspicious?
- You're suspicious.
- Me?
- You are.
- You're extremely suspicious.
- Me?
Do you even like chicken?
- This...
- Hey!
I've never seen him use new words.
And he bet 200 points.
Jong Kook is suspicious.
- Really?
- You never know.
Jong Kook is suspicious.
Here's the keyword
for the next question.
"A question Ji Hyo got wrong."
- There are too many.
- I've got many wrong.
- Ji Hyo has got many wrong.
- There are too many.
- It's too difficult.
- All right.
Let's choose four players now.
- I've got many questions wrong.
- Go!
And many of them were actually hard.
Not all of them were easy.
Lee Kwang Soo, Yang Se Chan,
- Park Hyo Ju, and Ha Yeon Joo.
- Ha Yeon Joo?
- Yeon Joo is playing.
We should keep an eye on her.
Ji Hyo got it wrong,
but I'll get it right.
Please make your bets now.
Kwang Soo made a bet first.
If Ji Hyo got it wrong...
- Yeon Joo bets 50 points.
- I don't have many points.
- Yeon Joo.
- Come on.
Make it 150.
Kwang Soo, what are you looking at?
(Kwang Soo,
what are you looking at?)
I crossed it all out.
(He fails to cheat.)
I shouldn't have
crossed out everything.
I should have just pretended.
Here's the question.
Ji Hyo got this question wrong...
in the Survival Race
in the 47th episode.
The 47th episode?
That's a long time ago.
Which river was the water
Bongyi Kim Seon Dal sold...
to the Hanyang merchants from?
- What?
- That's easy.
We should keep quiet.
Look at Kwang Soo's face.
Hey! Look at Kwang Soo!
You don't know it, Kwang Soo?
Please write down your answers.
Which river?
Which river was the water from?
- I have no idea.
- It's obvious.
- It's Julien Kang.
- It's Ahn Gil Gang.
- Is it in Seoul?
- You have 10 seconds.
(Kwang Soo sends out an SOS
to Ji Hyo.)
- The Taedong River.
- No!
Please stop them.
(Se Chan looks confident.)
Kwang Soo is cheating.
- The Ganges.
- Four,
- The Nile.
- three...
(After saying she has no idea,
Yeon Joo writes something down.)
- 2, 1.
- Bongyi Kim Seon Dal?
Please show us their answers.
(The Nakdong River,
The Hantan River)
Okay.
"The Nakdong River"?
Kwang Soo wrote,
"The Nakdong River."
- "The Hantan River"?
- It's wrong?
- Se Chan wrote, "The Hantan River."
- It's the Taedong River.
- Yeon Joo got it right.
- Hyo Ju wrote, "The Taedong River."
- She said she has no idea.
- Yeon Joo got it right.
Yeon Joo wrote, "The Taedong River."
- I wrote, "The Han River."
- She's acting.
- The correct answer is...
- Yeon Joo said she has no idea.
- She's acting.
- I wrote, "The Han River."
The Taedong River.
Park Hyo Ju and Ha Yeon Joo
wrote the correct answer.
- Yeon Joo.
- You're suspicious.
- You're busted.
- You messed up.
Se Chan, why did you write,
"The Hantan River"?
- I thought it was the Hantan River.
- It's the Taedong River.
You just have to stay where you are.
But Kwang Soo is messing up.
Jong Kook and Yeon Joo...
- They're suspicious.
- Jae Suk.
- I'm innocent.
- Are you sure?
Yeon Joo is still suspicious.
Yeon Joo is extremely suspicious.
She's suspicious.
Why did you tell me
it's the Nakdong River?
- I said, "The Taedong River."
- You did?
I said, "The Taedong River."
Say it again.
(She obviously says,
"The Taedong River.")
Kwang Soo, this is not okay.
The top five...
The keyword
for the next question is...
- a "currency swap."
- What's that?
I don't know much about it.
What does that mean?
- It's about finance.
- It's about money.
- I have no idea. This is not good.
- Kwang Soo...
The four players are,
Ha Yeon Joo, Yoo Jae Suk,
Song Ji Hyo, and Haha.
- Gosh.
- Please come up to the stage.
- Yeon Joo...
- My role model, Haha!
- Currency swaps...
- Keep an eye on Yeon Joo.
We'll keep an eye on you, Yeon Joo.
- A currency swap.
- It might not be a hard one.
I bet 200 points.
- That's a lot.
- Good job.
It'd be amazing
if Ji Hyo goes all in.
Ji Hyo, bet a lot.
- Should I bet a lot?
- Yes.
You know the answer anyway.
- You should bet a lot.
- Right.
You should get ahead of the others.
How much did she bet?
Show us the amount.
(She bets 700 points.)
That's not what I meant.
Ji Hyo bets 700 points.
- That's not what I meant.
- What?
- You said I should bet a lot.
- I didn't say you should go all in.
- It doesn't matter.
- 700 points?
She must know a lot.
- She knows.
- She definitely knows.
Then... Okay.
You can change your bets.
If I don't change my bet,
I can't catch up with Ji Hyo.
I bet 710 points.
- Okay!
- 710 points!
- Why?
- Yeon Joo keeps pretending.
Yeon Joo, if you get it right,
we'll suspect you.
- Yeon Joo bets 50 points.
- Let's go!
I'm not sure
if I'll know the answer.
Here's the question.
A currency swap is an agreement...
where two countries exchange
a certain amount of money...
and later exchange
the same amount again.
If that the case,
please spell the English word,
"country," correctly.
- "Country"?
- Gosh.
Look at Haha. He bet only 10 points.
- That was a good call.
- I got nervous for nothing.
- Gosh.
- Jae Suk, you're incredible!
- This is too easy.
I got nervous for nothing.
- I told you.
Ji Hyo, it was a good call
to go all in.
Go, Ji Hyo!
I think my answer is wrong.
Then correct it! Hurry up.
What is it? Is this right?
How can a Mensa member
not know how to spell "country"?
I'm getting confused too.
No, it's easy.
- I'm confused.
- One.
Please show us their answers.
I think my answer is wrong.
Let's see them.
Three of them wrote the same answer,
and one wrote something else.
(Haha wrote, "cuntry.")
- What's that?
- What did you do?
I changed it at the last minute.
What did you write?
I wrote, "country," at first.
You really should study.
Haha, you did a good job.
The three of them wrote
the correct answer,
and Haha wrote the wrong answer.
- I got it right at first.
- Go, Ji Hyo!
Gosh.
How could you ask
us to spell "country"?
Jae Suk has
over 1,400 points now.
We spelled "country"
for a currency swap question?
It was nothing.
The scores are changing a lot
after each question.
This time, the four players are,
Kwak Si Yang, Ha Yeon Joo,
- Kim Jong Kook, and Park Hyo Ju.
- What should I do? Let's do this.
Keep an eye
on Yeon Joo and Jong Kook.
Keep an eye on them both.
Yeon Joo is suspicious too.
She stays in the top five
without standing out too much.
- She's acting.
- I know.
They've made their bets now.
Si Yang goes all in.
Yeon Joo bets 30 points.
Jong Kook bets 40 points.
- Please.
- Hyo Ju bets 150 points.
Here's the question.
"Caution" by Tashannie
was released in 2000.
That said,
what is the business term
that means a threat...
that is predictable
after a series of warnings...
- but is easily neglected?
- Gosh.
What does that have to do
with the song?
- A business term?
- What is it?
- It's a business term?
A "gray rhino."
That's hard.
(Jae Suk knows the answer.)
- That's right.
- Right?
- A business term?
- Note, there are options.
We get to choose?
- Here are the options.
- Is it an English term?
- Okay, let's try it.
- There are options.
- I think I might know.
- I should have bet a lot.
- I think it's either number 1 or 3.
- Please write down your answers.
- I think Hyo Ju knows the answer.
- I know it.
- Luckily, they gave us options.
- Let's see their answers.
- An "elephant in the room..."
- Really?
Yeon Joo and Jong Kook got it wrong.
- I'm confused.
- These two?
The answer is...
number two, gray rhino.
Hyo Ju is correct.
That was a difficult question.
I'm glad I didn't bet everything.
I got it because
it was multiple choice.
Jae Suk knew
before he heard the options.
He got it
before the options were given.
- I know.
- It can't be Hyo Ju.
- It's not her.
- It's not.
Watch Yeon Joo
and Jong Kook carefully.
Here's the keyword
for the next question.
Kwang Soo who doesn't concentrate
on filming.
"Kwang Soo who doesn't concentrate
on filming."
What?
Please spin the slot machine.
(This is the last question!)
(Current rankings)
(Jae Suk in 1st place,
Ji Hyo in 2nd, Yeon Joo in 3rd)
(Kwang Soo can't get up there.)
(This question will decide the fates
of the illegal participants!)
Hyo Ju, Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Haha.
Please make your bets.
(Key suspects Jong Kook and Yeon Joo
are excluded.)
- Haha, how many did you bet?
- All in.
All in? Should I do that?
Do I have over 300 points?
Hold on.
Hyo Ju wrote 300.
Why is she doing that near the end?
- Why would she do that?
- Hyo Ju?
You're betting that many points?
No, I'm not attached.
- I don't care about the prize.
- I'm starting to doubt you.
Why would you bet all of a sudden?
She was a key suspect in round one.
That's true. Why now?
- In Round One.
- She was the only one who bet 150.
- 150.
- Earlier?
She was also the only one
who got gray rhino.
- Right. It's not me.
- That's odd.
- I swear it's not me.
- Hyo Ju bet 300 points,
Se Chan bet 10, Ji Hyo bet 100,
and Haha is all in.
Here's the question.
Unlike Kwang Soo who doesn't
concentrate on filming,
this is a psychological
phenomenon...
that describes
the effect of concentration...
on realizing an impossible task.
What is this phenomenon called?
- I know this.
- Good luck, Ji Hyo!
(Kwang Soo can't get
within 5th place.)
You can do it, Ji Hyo!
- I know this.
- Good luck, Ji Hyo!
This is so easy.
Let's look at
Hyo Ju's face carefully.
- She's strange.
- We have to look at her.
She sounds confident.
- I don't know this.
- Four,
3, 2, 1.
Please show us their answers.
I have no clue.
(Pygmalion effect, placebo effect)
This is easy.
Se Chan wrote placebo effect.
- Haha wrote placebo effect.
- Placebo.
- Two people wrote placebo effect,
- I think I'm right.
and the other two wrote
Pygmalion effect.
The answer is Pygmalion effect.
(Answer: Pygmalion effect)
- I lost everything.
- Good luck, Ji Hyo!
Haha, Hyo Ju is strange.
- Right?
- Why did she do that at the end?
Hyo Ju came out of nowhere.
I think it's her.
Before this, we thought it was...
- either Jong Kook or Yeon Joo.
- We did.
- It's not me.
- From gray rhino,
- I swear it's not me.
- she kept on going for it.
Everyone, the quiz is over.
Before we announce the rankings,
arrest somebody first.
- Can we get some time?
- I swear it's not me.
Sure.
- It's either Hyo Ju or Yeon Joo.
- I went for it in the end.
- I wanted to make it fun.
- Yeon Joo, Jong Kook, or Hyo Ju.
- It's not Jong Kook.
- It's 1 of the 3.
- It's not me.
- Can we talk without these three?
- Can three of you stand aside?
- Us?
Can you go over there as well?
- Why?
- Move over.
- What did we do?
- Go.
- I'm not going to do anything.
Move over.
- I swear it's not me.
- Suk Jin.
- It's not Jong Kook.
- I know.
- I was watching Hyo Ju.
- Jong Kook.
- I was doubting him at first,
- Hyo Ju came out of nowhere.
- but I don't think it's him.
- It's not.
He's capable of getting
"oh-jeo-chi-go" right.
(He gives a faint smile
after getting excluded.)
(He got many questions right
in Round 2.)
(He got number 1 and 2
that were worth many points.)
(He got "oh-jeo-chi-go" right
unexpectedly.)
(He earned 200 points
with this question!)
(They were very suspicious of him.)
(Is he trying to avoid suspicion
by acting like a victim?)
- It's not Jong Kook?
- At this point,
- we should exclude him.
- She got Pygmalion effect.
- That was three in a row.
- Taedong River was difficult too,
- but she could have known.
- That was easy.
Can you describe Pygmalion effect?
- Can you explain?
- On "Dr. Romantic",
there's an episode by that title.
- What does it mean?
- It's a term in psychology.
On "Dr. Romantic",
when Lee Sung Kyoung...
wants something,
she takes migraine medicine
and does the surgeries.
I'm right.
This is so unfair!
(They were suspicious when she knew
the foreign children's song.)
(It looked like she was trying to
remember something.)
Hyo Ju is correct.
(She got difficult questions
during the quiz as well.)
Why did she do that at the end?
(She miraculously got within
5th place at the end. Is it her?)
Under the circumstances,
it can't be her.
But look.
Yeon Joo looked awkward.
- Her too.
- She's not saying a word.
This is so difficult.
She looked clueless,
- but she got everything right.
- She did.
(She's a member of Mensa,
but in Round 1,)
(she only got 140 points.)
(That was a low score considering
her resume and skills.)
(She sounded like she didn't know
the easy questions,)
(but she got them right
and collected points.)
(Is she an illegal participant who
tried to trick others by acting?)
All three are highly likely.
Don't make a mistake.
You know.
- But in the end...
- You can tell.
Everyone,
here are the ballots.
You arrested two already,
so you only need to write
one person's name down.
- We are already done.
- You two will vote too.
- Do we vote too?
- Yes, everybody votes.
- These two too?
- We have to do this as a team.
- We have to pick one person.
- We have to pick one...
- to win.
- Yes, you have to pick one.
(Who's going to have
the highest votes?)
- Please hand them back.
- I'm done.
I have the results.
The goal of
the illegal participants was...
was to get 2 or more of them
within top 5.
First of all,
the illegal participants...
- succeeded in their mission.
- Okay!
Of course, they succeeded.
Let's go, Ji Hyo!
(Ji Hyo ended up in top 5,
but Kwang Soo didn't.)
Because those two had high scores?
No, one of them didn't.
- Did he lose points?
- There's another person.
According to the voting results,
the person
with the most votes was...
(Suspect with
the highest number of votes was...)
- Hyo Ju. Please come on up.
- Right.
Me?
(If she's an illegal participant,
the illegal participants lose.)
- I really hope it's not Yeon Joo.
- If it's Yeon Joo...
- I hope it's not Yeon Joo.
- Please, Yeon Joo.
- I really hope it's not her.
- I hope it's not Yeon Joo!
I tried my best.
We were suspicious of Yeon Joo
and Hyo Ju until the end.
- I was...
- It's not me.
I was the only person
who was suspicious of Jong Kook.
I thought it was him,
but I followed the majority.
If it's not Hyo Ju,
- I would get chills.
I would get chills.
Let's see, Hyo Ju.
- Again...
- I swear it's not me.
I'm going to rip it off.
1, 2, 3.
(Is she the illegal participant
like the voting results?)
(Or did Yeon Joo trick everybody?)
- three.
- It's her, right?
(She was the illegal participant!)
(Cheering)
(They arrested
all the illegal participants.)
I'm sorry.
(She almost fooled them.)
- I knew it.
- Jae Suk.
- Why did you think it was me?
- I know.
Of course, it wasn't him.
- You were clever.
- Of course.
- That was insane.
- I didn't know it was Hyo Ju.
- I'm sorry, Yi Kyung.
- Great work.
- Yi Kyung...
- Great job.
Great acting.
(She deserves to be applauded.)
You are illegal participants...
who know the answers
to all questions.
(Pygmalion...)
(She tried her hardest
to memorize "Pygmalion".)
The answer is "Pygmalion effect".
(She knew the answer,
so she bet large points,)
(but this became
the source of her problem.)
(It made her nervous.)
(Good job, Hyo Ju!)
(Unfortunately, she failed to
fool them until the end.)
(Arrested illegal participants)
(Arrested illegal participant)
- What's that?
- Is it meat?
1st place gets Korean beef,
2nd place gets Korean pork,
3rd place gets a speaker,
4th and 5th places get candles.
Okay!
- This is neat.
- Thank you.
- Good work.
That was fun.
(The animals got invited
to the tiger's birthday party!)
(This is a day just for Jong Kook!)
(He's the birthday boy.)
(Hyo Seong and Mingyu are here
to celebrate his birthday!)
(There is workout equipment
for Jong Kook.)
(They must win
Jong Kook's heart today.)
(He was feeling great,
and the party seemed peaceful.)
(Which animal
rubbed him the wrong way?)
(Their party becomes chaotic!)
(This is the real birthday party...)
(he doesn't know about.)
(Tiger's Birthday Party)