(One scorching hot day)
Please clap the slate once.
- One... - Shall we begin?
- Do I clap it now? - Yes.
(So Min arrived 1st.)
1, 2, and 3.
(She claps her hands once.)
Hello, everyone.
(Then she starts hosting the show.)
Hello, everyone. Welcome to Jeon So Min's Running Man.
All right. We're going to have five male guests today.
(Jeon So Min wants to be a host.)
Well...
Today's special is Win Over Jeon So Min Race.
(She comes up with her own race.)
(She's stealing the show alone.)
Which one of the handsome guests...
will be falling in love with this beautiful woman, Jeon So Min?
(Imaginary love show of So Min, by So Min, for So Min)
Please look forward to the exciting couple race.
Director, please follow me.
(Host Jeon has a lot of requests for her show.)
(Just about when she finally runs out of ideas for her show...)
Hurry, Yoo Jae Suk.
Let's start right away.
When we worked out the day before...
Hello.
(Members finally come in.)
- Hello. - Hello.
What are you doing here alone?
- I was busy working. - Hello.
- I was working. - You came early.
(As soon as the real host comes in, )
(So Min is pushed to the corner.)
- You were? - Okay.
Hello.
After the shooting yesterday, I talked to Kwang Soo.
(Se Chan has something to say.)
Apparently, he was very disappointed.
(Kwang Soo was disappointed after the last shoot.)
- Why? - Hey.
- Don't do that. - I mean...
- Why were you disappointed? - Well...
- Nothing. - The thing is,
- July 14 was Kwang Soo's birthday. - Hey.
(The day they shot the card shark special...)
- Right. - It was your birthday?
And the episode we filmed would be aired around that day.
(was close to Kwang Soo's birthday on July 14.)
So he thought we prepared some prank for him.
(He thought we prepared some prank for him.)
(Kwang Soo counted his chickens too soon.)
- But... - That's not true.
- No, it's not like that. - Nothing happened, so...
It was nothing like that!
- Kwang Soo was... - No, that's not true.
(The members didn't plan anything for Kwang Soo's birthday.)
So when I was wearing the blindfold,
I thought you guys would do something to me.
Put the blindfold on properly.
(When he was told to put on the blindfold...)
(Maybe this is some kind of prank.)
(Nothing ever happened.)
They will take everything.
(This is a little too rough for my birthday party.)
- Did you expect something? - Not really. Se Chan...
(The reason Kwang Soo expected something)
I had no idea.
The day before, he asked, "We should dress like card sharks tomorrow."
"Do you know what it is about?"
- "Am I the main star tomorrow?" - "A card shark?"
(A card shark suddenly?)
"Hang on. The episode will be aired around..."
(It will be aired around...)
"Maybe Se Chan is not supposed to tell me that."
(Kwang Soo thought Se Chan made a mistake.)
"Isn't he supposed to keep it a secret?"
(He was serious.)
- Because I didn't hear it. - He was in the movie, "Tazza".
- Right. - That's what it is.
"Hang on. The show will be aired the day after my birthday."
(Gosh, I know what is going on.)
That's ridiculous.
So during the shooting,
(Kwang Soo has been waiting for a surprise.)
I kept looking for cameras. I was sure something would happen.
Are you the only one who has a birthday?
(You're being ridiculous.)
That's not it.
- Are you the only one? - That's not it.
(You can look forward to his surprise party in a year.)
We should prepare a surprise for him.
- He was counting on it. - We had no idea.
Today,
you're going to compete in pairs.
(They'll compete in pairs with the guests.)
- Oh, my. - In pairs?
By the way, the caramels...
(Why does Jae Suk look so depressed?)
- Based on yesterday's results... - He has only three.
- What can I do with 30 cents? - You'll get 30 cents, and...
(In War of Sharks last week, )
Bring it on!
(he raised the stakes as the chairman.)
Okay. All in!
(He soon went broke and was thrown onto the floor.)
I told you not to come.
- Don't give him any money. - It's a dirty world.
(Having only 3 caramels left, )
(he'll be given 30 cents as his mission fund.)
- Pull yourself together. - Put it together.
You get 10 cents per caramel...
(Current Number of Caramels)
(Jong Kook: 6.8 dollars, Suk Jin and Haha: 5.4 dollars, )
(Kwang Soo 4.9 dollars, Se Chan: 4.8 dollars)
- as your mission fund. - Okay.
After yesterday's shoot,
(The production crew gave them a bunch of caramels.)
I was given a huge bag of caramels.
- That's all you get? - I'm sick of it.
I don't want any more caramels.
- I even found one in my sock... - Be quiet.
Hey!
Be quiet.
- The director is talking. - I never get to talk.
You know what?
- What? - There's a compilation...
of you interrupting him on the internet.
("Running Man, Jae Suk keeps cutting Kwang Soo's talks.")
- Really? - When it's all put together,
it's almost 15 minutes long.
(Just the scenes of him cutting off Kwang Soo are 15 minutes.)
For 15 minutes, he interrupts... Think about it.
- I mean... - Really?
What just happened isn't even a minute long.
(Because of Jae Suk...)
- I never get to tell stories. - There's a compilation of it.
- Cut it out. - I'm wearing this for the opening.
(I'm going to cut him off again.)
Please welcome your partners for today.
(Announcing the guests of today's race)
We're excited to have guests.
- Oh, my. - Oh, hey.
- What are you doing here? - You're finally here.
- Hi, Soyou. - Welcome.
(Soyou, Doyeon of Weki Meki, and Mijoo of Lovelyz)
- Come on in. - They're here.
(And they're followed by...)
- What are you doing here? - Soyou is here.
(Yuqi of (G)I-DLE and Won Young of IZ ONE)
- Hi, Doyeon. - Hi.
(Great to see you.)
- Hi. - Hi.
(Everyone is busy greeting each other.)
- Oh, my. - Hi.
- Hi. - Oh, hi.
(So Min looks around.)
- Oh, my. - Hi.
(Do we have any male guests?)
- Hi. - Hi.
- Oh, my. - Hi.
- Won Young, you're here. - You're tall.
(Tall)
- Who? - Won Young...
- She's really tall. - She's so tall.
(Won Young may be the youngest, but she's the tallest.)
We were just talking about how tall she's become.
I was so surprised. She's become even taller.
(Everyone is focused on the female guests.)
Everyone is avoiding her.
We have one more guest.
(Are there more guests?)
- Let's welcome the last guest. - There's one more?
- Yes. - Please come out.
(Who is the last guest?)
- Who could it be? - What's going on?
- Oh, my. It's Dong Jun. - Dong Jun.
- It's Dong Jun. - Hey, Dong Jun.
(Actor and singer, Kim Dong Jun)
- Dong Jun. - Look who's here.
- How have you been? - Hi.
- It's Dong Jun. - Hey, Dong Jun.
(They seem really happy.)
(So Min has mentioned many times...)
- Dong Jun. - Look who's here.
(that she likes guys like Dong Jun.)
- How have you been? - Hi.
("After Effect" starts playing.)
- It's automatic. - I keep feeling sad.
(She starts dancing as Dong Jun appears.)
- So Min is finally smiling. - You look so manly now.
So Min is finally smiling big.
- She's finally smiling. - He looks so manly.
- Hi. - Hi.
- What's with So Min? - She's getting her hopes up again.
- It happens every week. - She's tucking her hair back.
- She never gives up. - Good. Go for it.
- No. - Your ears will start bleeding.
(She can't even look at Dong Jun.)
- What's with So Min? - What's with her?
(She goes back to being the Love Frog.)
All right.
Let me introduce our guests one by one.
(Introducing the only male guest of the day, )
- First, Kim Dong Jun. - Dong Jun.
(Kim Dong Jun who is now a full-time actor)
- Hello. - Yes!
- Yes! - He's so good-looking.
(They welcome him enthusiastically.)
Yes!
Back in 2015... That was long ago.
(Dong Jun returned to Running Man after 5 years.)
- It's been 5 years. - It's been 5 years.
Last time, I appeared together with SHINHWA.
(5 years ago...)
- That's right. - We went to the beach, right?
(While Dong Jun's interview is going on...)
Last time, I appeared together with SHINHWA.
What? What's wrong?
- He's so good-looking. - We went to the beach, right?
(Se Chan laughs.)
What? Do you have a problem?
What's wrong?
- She says he's good-looking. - She says, "He's so good-looking."
Stop it now.
- That's why it never works out. - I never did that.
You said he's good-looking. It's been recorded.
- She can't even look at him. - Hold on. So Min, you should move.
- This is not okay. Come here. - Switch with Ji Hyo.
- No! I don't want to. - Go over there.
(Holding out)
- I don't want to! - Switch with her.
- Tears keep falling - Go over there.
(She is sent away from Dong Jun.)
Okay.
Anyway, Dong Jun, is there anyone you want to be partners with?
(The talk continues after sending So Min away.)
- There is. - Who?
I've been curious about this person.
- Who? - Tell us.
(There is someone he's been curious about?)
- Who? - Who?
- So Min. - Oh, my.
(So Min's heart skips a beat.)
This is not good. Why would you set her heart on fire?
(Her heart)
- He planned this. - Why would you...
- He planned this beforehand. - What's with her?
(She can't keep a straight face.)
- Oh, my. - "Set her heart on fire"?
You're going a bit too far there.
(And Suk Jin...)
- "Set her heart on fire"? - "Set her heart on fire"?
("Set her heart on fire"?)
- Hey. - That's exaggerated.
- Why do you exaggerate so much? - That's too dramatic.
- Be quiet. - Don't be so dramatic.
- Anyway, he agrees. - Don't exaggerate.
(Dong Jun ended up setting So Min's heart on fire.)
Don't set her heart on fire.
Don't say that if you don't mean it. She's serious.
(Dong Jun...)
I mean it. I've been really curious.
(I mean it too.)
But Dong Jun, her boyfriend is right here.
- No. - What are you talking about?
- People keep asking me... - It's not true.
(They're both falsely accused.)
- Tears keep falling - Seriously.
- Jae Suk. - People get the wrong idea.
- What are you talking about? - Se Chan is excited too.
- Really? - You're right.
- I'm excited too. - Look at him.
(Thrilled to have a couple's race)
He may not have a swim ring, but he looks like he's on a vacation.
(He's dressed as if he'll go on a vacation right now.)
- I'm taking someone with me. - Where's your swim ring?
- I see. - I'm going away today.
(Smiling)
He came prepared.
(Having false hope yet another day)
- I can see it now. - Yes.
Next up is Won Young.
(The popular Won Young of IZ ONE)
By the way, I'm sorry to ask this,
how much have you grown in the past year?
(Startled)
Since we last met, I think I've grown...
at least 2 or 3cm taller.
(Approximately...)
- Right? - So she's still growing.
Jang Doyeon should be nervous now.
- I'm getting nervous too... - Be quiet.
I'm nervous too!
Don't I get a chance to talk since they brought up Jang Doyeon?
(Frustrated)
Stop it.
- After me... - Stop it.
(A tyrant)
- During the opening... - Won Young is talking.
- Why do you cut in? - You've interrupted him twice.
("Jae Suk cutting off Kwang Soo 2" coming soon)
- Jae Suk interrupts him again. - Gosh.
Stop it.
Aren't you stressed out about people asking you...
(Going back to the height)
about your height?
(Don't you feel stressed when people keep saying how tall you are?)
They do ask me a lot.
I'm starting to get a bit stressed out.
What do they usually ask?
First, "Are you still growing?"
(What she hears the most)
Second, "I think you've grown taller."
(Jae Suk)
You just said both.
(Jae Suk said both today.)
- Hey. You hurt her. - I'm sorry.
Why did you do that?
- I... - Why do you stress her out?
(Height growth is natural at her age.)
- Seriously. - I almost didn't recognize her.
Someone walked up to me and greeted me.
(He stressed her out since the opening without intention.)
- So I said hello. - That's right.
Okay.
She's so good with her facial expressions.
Apparently, she has some tips about facial expressions on stage.
(Another charm of Won Young is...)
(that she's good with facial expressions.)
It's not easy to depict the lyrics...
- with your expressions. - No.
(What are her tips on facial expressions?)
Is there anything you think is the most important?
My part goes,
(During "Secret Story of the Swan" by IZ ONE)
"Your magic wakes me up".
If I do it the ordinary way... Should I look in this direction?
(Curious)
(This is how she practices the ordinary way.)
Your magic wakes me up.
- Something like that. - That's ordinary?
- That's ordinary? - That's supposed to be ordinary.
Then please add more emotion.
- And then... - Do it your style.
(How does she look on the stage?)
On stage, I'd do...
(Your magic wakes me up)
- It has much more emotion. - She moves her eyebrows.
- She moves her eyes a lot. - She's really good.
- It's not easy. - She's so good.
Jong Kook, what do you do to covey the lyrics?
(Sudden)
- Try it. - I don't...
My eyes are too small. They can't express anything.
(His eyes are too small to act with facial expressions.)
In the old days, the expressions were not this detailed, right?
This is all we did.
(They didn't use a lot of facial expressions.)
(Regardless of the lyrics, all the moves were exaggerated.)
I don't know how many times I did this.
Why do you always kick even when you're singing?
- What's with you? - I poked a lot too.
(The ending moves in the 20th century were very aggressive.)
But I didn't use a lot of facial expressions.
- Please give it up for Won Young. - Thank you.
(Look forward to her race!)
Let's move on.
- Next up is... Oh, my. - Who is it?
(The third guest)
This is her first time on Running Man.
- Yuqi. - Oh, yes.
(The first visit of Yuqi of (G)I-DLE)
- You're from China, right? - Yes.
(The vocalist and the lead dancer of (G)I-DLE is from China.)
This is your first time on Running Man.
How are you feeling?
Yes, I've always wanted to be on this show.
Actually, I was a host on Running Man China...
(She was a host in Running Man China.)
last year.
- Running Man China? - That's right.
- Running Man China? - Yes.
(That Yuqi is...)
Apparently, Yuqi loves giraffes.
(known for her love toward giraffes.)
- That's right. - You actually love giraffes?
(Pricking his ears up)
He's getting excited.
My dream used to be riding on a giraffe.
- Ride on it today. - Ride on it.
(Accepting)
- Try it. - She means a real giraffe!
- Ride on him. - Why would she ride on me?
- Get on the giraffe. - She means a real giraffe!
(Her wish is about to come true.)
- Just try it. - You are a giraffe.
- I mean... - Hurry up and jump on him.
- Wait. - Kwang Soo.
(His giraffe image is useful from time to time.)
- Even if I get down on all fours... - Get on his back.
- Not you. - Why would you get on?
(Trying to get a free ride)
- You should stand up. - Stand up.
(You want me to stand up?)
- The giraffe should stand up. - Like this.
Run around like a giraffe first.
(Kim Jong Kook, zookeeper)
- Try walking. - Why do I have to do this?
- Why do I have to do this? - For Yuqi...
(Flustered)
(The giraffe runs.)
- Do it for Yuqi. - A real giraffe is taller.
All right. You can get on his back now.
(The giraffe seems to be in good shape.)
(Now it's time to ride it.)
A little lower. There you go.
- Get on his back. - Seriously?
Riding on a giraffe is her dream.
She got on my back for real?
(It's her very first ride on a giraffe.)
- Giddy up! - Run!
- Run! - I mean...
- Give him the leaf. - Run!
(She even has food for the giraffe.)
- Here we go. Run! - Let's go!
The ground... Her dream is riding on a giraffe.
- Why would she get on my back? - That's enough.
- That's enough. Okay. - Good job.
(The short tour on a giraffe ends.)
- Her dream came true. - Okay.
- We're done. - How are you feeling?
- Yuqi's dream... - How does it feel?
- came true. - Her dream came true.
Thank you.
(We're available for any idol singers who have wishes.)
- We make your dream come true. - Yuqi.
Next up is Mijoo.
(Let's talk to Mijoo of Lovelyz.)
- Yes! - Mijoo!
How are you doing these days?
With the pandemic going on much longer than expected,
I guess it's hard to plan...
new albums and everything.
- That's right. - Why is the question so hard?
- Ask an easy one. - I'm not an anchor or anything.
(Asking her about the current events out of the blue)
My heart almost burst.
(Even their hearts pounded.)
- "What is he talking about?" - What do you mean?
- "How is she going to answer?" - It's not that hard.
(He discouraged Mijoo who was excited.)
- I almost hit him with my elbow. - Hey.
All Yuqi did is get on a giraffe.
(He gave Yuqi a ride on a giraffe...)
- Why would you ask her... - Mijoo...
(and asked Mijoo about the coronavirus disease.)
- about her future plans? - About the pandemic.
- She's been on the show a lot. - It's a tough time.
That's why I asked her that question.
After your appearance on Running Man,
(What did her mother say after her appearance on Running Man?)
did your mother say anything?
- I got scolded a lot. - Why?
(My mother)
- Why? - Why? You were the best!
You did a good job.
(But it was funny.)
- She was the best. - It was fun,
- It was fun. - but because I'm a girl...
(Her poses were a bit too natural.)
When my mom saw me sitting like this, she said,
"Are you crazy? Why were you sitting like that?"
(Her mom scolded her out of love.)
"Are you crazy?"
"Why were you sitting like that?"
She scolded me so much.
Mijoo takes after her mother.
(Her mother's affection makes them clap.)
"Why were you spreading your legs like that?"
- Mijoo is so funny. - I love it.
- She's very straightforward. - She's very cool.
(Her mother is as exciting.)
- Seriously... - Her mom is so cool.
(You're doing great.)
Isn't she amazing?
She said my face looked so big.
Won Young is the one panicking the most right now.
- I'm sorry. - Right?
(Feeling sorry for flustering her)
Mijoo is an idol group member too.
(There are different types of girl group singer seniors.)
- But she's so straightforward. - Not all members are the same.
- Of course. - Of course.
Variety shows love people like Mijoo.
(Thumbs up)
Won Young keeps giving her a meaningless thumbs-up.
- I mean... - Why is she doing that?
Why are you doing that?
(You put two thumbs up when you don't know what to say.)
All right.
- Next up is Soyou. - Soyou.
(The summer reminds you of her, Soyou)
It's been a while, Soyou.
Her real name is Kang Ji Hyun.
(Soyou, real name: Kang Ji Hyun)
- How did you know? - Really?
Actually, this is what we say...
(Every summer, )
- every summer. - SISTAR?
SISTAR is...
(we dearly miss SISTAR.)
- I know. - That's true.
We have no girl groups for summer anymore.
Do you still get that a lot?
(Do you hear that a lot?)
I do get that a lot. So a new album is coming out.
So a new album is coming out.
(Is SISTAR releasing a new album?)
- Really? - It's big news!
(Everyone is excited at this breaking news.)
Jae Suk.
- See? - The three of you?
- I'm doing it alone. - Alone? Hang on.
(What's wrong with you? I'm doing it solo, not as SISTAR.)
- Hey. - You seem too disappointed.
Why did you talk about yourself when we asked about SISTAR?
(Why would you talk about solo when we asked about SISTAR?)
- Suk Jin! Why are you doing this? - I'm a member of SISTAR.
- I know you're SISTAR, but we... - Soyou.
(We are really happy to hear that you are releasing your solo.)
- I'm sorry about that. - Please understand him.
- I'm quite upset. - You should understand him.
I'm sorry about that.
(The flow of the conversation...)
- But we were talking about... - It's the flow of the conversation.
(was confusing enough for people to mistake it as SISTAR.)
It sounded like SISTAR was going to release a new album.
I misunderstood it as well. I thought it was about SISTAR.
(Listeners who misunderstood are embarrassed.)
- See? - I'm sorry. It's my fault.
(Soyou is embarrassed too.)
So you're releasing a new summer song.
(The good news is Soyou is releasing a summer song.)
Yes. It will be a cool summer song.
As you just said, your new summer song...
- is coming out soon. - Right.
(It's Soyou's new song coming out in two days)
We should hear it then.
("Gotta Go")
Soyou has a nice voice.
(Surprised)
("Gotto Go" by Soyou)
This is it.
- It's summer. - I love it!
(The first verse already reminds them of cool summer.)
It sounds great from the beginning.
Let's go.
It's nice.
Head.
- Head. - Shoulder.
We need a song like this in summer.
(Soyou's "Gotta go" will fill in for SISTAR's absence.)
- All right. - This is a summer song.
Now it feels like summer.
- It feels so cool. - We definitely need this.
(This is the true summer song.)
- She's really good. - It's really cool.
She's different.
(The last guest after summer queen Soyou)
Now we have Doyeon here.
(Performance Queen and Characterful Actress, Doyeon of Weki Meki)
We have Jang Doyeon for comedy.
(Jang Doyeon for comedy)
- And we have Kim Doyeon for K-pop. - Right.
(Kim Doyeon for K-pop)
How have you been, Doyeon?
I've been getting ready for my new drama.
(She's preparing for a drama after Weki Meki.)
- I see. - You're starting a drama.
She appeared in a drama before.
(She gained popularity after starring in "Be Melodramatic".)
- It was "Be Melodramatic". - "Be Melodramatic".
That's right.
You watched the drama. You liked it.
- I did. I really liked it. - You should say that.
Aren't you going to work?
No, that's not it.
(Her concentration dropped rapidly after Dong Jun appeared.)
You should work. Talk about the drama.
You're lost in admiration.
Gosh, no.
Dong Jun, you should wait outside.
(Please stay outside so So Min can get to work.)
- That's not true. - Look at her.
So we have Doyeon here.
(Unique 6 partners are ready for today's race.)
Please give a round of applause to the six guests...
who are joining us today.
Today, we're going to have Don't Worry Be Happy Partner Race.
(Today's Race: Don't Worry Be Happy Partner Race)
The eight members of Running Man acquired the mission fund...
(The 8 members acquired mission funds...)
according to the results of last week's missions.
(according to the results of last week's missions.)
- I feel bad for my partner. - The guests will choose...
(The guests will choose...)
their partners without knowing the amount the members have.
(their partners without knowing the amount they have.)
There's definitely a dud.
So you'd better try to choose a partner...
(The guests ought to try to choose a partner...)
who seems to have a lot of money for the race.
(who seems to have a lot of money for the race.)
Since the guests don't have the mission fund,
(The guests...)
- we will give them 10 dollars each. - 10 dollars?
(get the mission fund of 10 dollars each.)
We will give them 10 dollars each.
- 10 dollars? - Are they getting 10 dollars?
(Particularly happy)
- It's no problem then. - What?
He seems pretty happy.
(Jae Suk...)
- Now I don't feel pressure. - I bet Jae Suk has no money.
(Jae Suk feels less burdened.)
My goodness.
(He seems very happy.)
- He's happy. - 10 dollars is big money.
- Do you have no money? - What?
(Straightforward)
- Do you not have any money? - That's not true.
- He doesn't. - I guess he has no money.
(They can sense poverty without looking any closer.)
- He's completely broke. - He's totally penniless.
You will play Dice Proposal to decide partners.
(The partners will be decided using Dice Proposal.)
The seven men will get a blank dice each.
(All 7 male members will be given a dice.)
And they will take turns to find a partner.
(And they will take turns to find a partner.)
Once a man comes out, women will put a sticker...
(The women will put stickers on the dice of a man they want.)
on his dice if they like him.
And you will pay a dollar every time you put a sticker.
(Each sticker will cost a dollar.)
If they want to be picked, they will spend a lot of money.
You can put stickers on six faces if you want.
(You can use all 6 stickers for the male partner you want.)
- Gosh, So Min. - Don't look at me.
(So Min, Soyou, Mijoo)
(Ji Hyo, Won Young, Doyeon, Yuqi)
If you want to be Ji Suk Jin's partner,
(Suk Jin will go first.)
please raise your hand and tell me how many stickers you need.
(Those who want to be his partner must raise their hand...)
- This is cruel. - Soyou is moving.
(and express how many stickers they wish to buy.)
The girls are busy.
- Mijoo is going through her bag. - They're going through their bags.
(Silent)
Everyone.
(Bustling)
Ji Hyo is opening her bag now.
- She makes a lot of gestures now. - She's opening it.
(Ji Hyo is the only one who's very busy.)
- Look at him. - I have some money.
(Thanks to Suk Jin's proactive proposal, )
- He has a lot of money. - Can he show his money like that?
- I'll buy six stickers. - All right.
(Ji Hyo responds with 6 stickers.)
Six stickers?
- You're buying all the stickers? - Do you have to do that?
(Flustered)
She wants to make sure.
- He's got a lot of money. - Just stay still.
(My style)
- You have a lot of money. - Just stay quiet!
(I can't be the 1st one.)
I'm doing this for money.
- I told you to just stay still. - Look at them.
(Everyone is rooting for the two to be partners.)
- I said I'm buying them all. - Song Ji Hyo!
- Song Ji Hyo! - Song Ji Hyo!
If there's anyone else who wants to buy it, Suk Jin gets to choose.
But there's no one.
Who knows? You should give them some time.
(You never know.)
- He likes it. - There's no one. Don't look back.
- Hey. - No one wants you.
Mijoo, did you just shake your arm?
(She just expressed her feelings.)
Ji Hyo is the big player here.
- I think so. - I know. She's so cool.
(It's the meeting of Big Nose and Big Player.)
Two.
- One. - Suk Jin.
All right. It's settled.
(As expected, Suk Jin and Ji Hyo have become partners.)
He did this.
Yes!
(The first couple is set amid everyone's blessing.)
- Who's next? - Dong Jun.
If you want to be Dong Jun's partner,
- please tell me. - She's about to sell her soul.
(She silently raises her hand to participate.)
Look at her face.
There's one woman who's raising her hand bashfully.
(One, please.)
- She's willing to sell her soul. - So Min.
- She's acting cute. - Why are you being so shy?
- How many do you want? - I'll buy one sticker.
Just one?
- One is enough. - Then I'll buy the rest five.
- What? So suddenly? - Can I do that?
No. I'll buy six.
(Surprised)
I'll buy six stickers.
For whom are you buying five stickers?
For So Min.
(It's all for So Min.)
What?
(Was it all for me?)
- Can I do that? - I didn't know.
- What was that? - My gosh.
For So Min?
(Not happy)
- Why are you doing that? - He's so nice.
- Hang on. - What is going on?
- He's sweet. - We're just...
playing games with partners.
This is just a game.
(This is Jeon So Min's Running Man she hoped for.)
This isn't about dating someone.
- Isn't this "X-Man"? - This isn't "X-Man".
You might not see her ever again after this show.
Exactly.
I'll just buy six stickers.
(So Min buys 6 stickers.)
Is there anyone else who wants to join?
That's not possible.
- You two are partners now. - Okay. I bought six stickers.
(So Min and Dong Jun are partners.)
So Min and Dong Jun are partners.
How can I play games spontaneously when he's being like this?
Come here.
Hello.
(And the rest of them chose partners as well.)
Hello. Let's do this.
(Se Chan and Doyeon, Kwang Soo and Won Young)
(Jong Kook and Soyou, Haha and Mijoo)
(Jae Suk and Yuqi)
So your partners are decided now.
(They decided on their partners.)
I'll give you prize money according to the results after each round.
(The prize money will be distributed according to the result per round.)
The top two partners with the most money...
(The top 2 partners with the most amount of money can buy prizes.)
can buy any items we prepared...
with your prize money.
- Really? - Yuqi, this is the day.
- It's the day. - This is the day.
And the partners with the least money...
(The partners with the least amount of money will receive a penalty.)
- will get a penalty. - There's a penalty as well.
- Oh, the team that comes in last... - Once you put on your team uniform,
(It's time to put on the team uniform and head for the mission.)
- we will start the mission. - Let's go!
Let's bring it on!
(They've changed into the team uniform.)
(So Min is the first one to show up.)
She came early again.
- What? - You're early again.
Why?
(She fixes her makeup.)
(She rubs her hands.)
It's cool in here.
(This is what she always does, but she seems somewhat nervous.)
I guess we're doing something.
Are we dancing? Dance?
(No way.)
(As soon as she hears about dancing, )
(she starts to stretch feeling shy.)
(Nasal)
I can't dance.
I have a bad back.
(She says she can't dance.)
I have no money. I'm broke.
(A sudden change in attitude)
But I don't want my partner to get a penalty.
(This is her true intention.)
I'd feel bad if he got a penalty here.
(She circumvented to express her will to do her best for Dong Jun.)
Please gather around.
(The first mission for So Min to work hard on)
- Okay. - Yes.
Here's the first mission.
It's an extreme battle between a defender and an attacker.
(An extreme battle between a defender and an attacker)
Freeze Tag Dancing King.
(The First Mission: Freeze Tag Dancing King)
I bet Jong Kook will be good at it.
(If it's about power, Jong Kook has an advantage.)
- It's done. We're ready. - You'll be divided into two groups.
(Feeling nervous already)
(They'll be divided into two groups of 3 and 4 teams.)
And each team will dance in the red zone in turn.
(Each team will dance on the red zone in turn.)
Once I point out the best dancers, the music will stop.
(The crew will call out the team with best dancers.)
(The team must push the other teams out in 10 seconds.)
Then they can push out the opponents for 10 seconds.
And we will give them money for the number of members pushed out.
(The prize money will be the number of teams they pushed out.)
- We have to be strong. - Jong Kook must be good at this.
(They must not only be powerful but be good dancers to be chosen.)
- Soyou is just as strong. - And we should dance well.
(They are the most powerful partners.)
That's right.
The important thing is the list of matches.
(The most important thing is to choose the right opponent.)
We have seven spoons divided into two groups.
You will pick one. Those with the same color will dance together.
(They will pick out of 4 yellow and 3 blue spoons to decide.)
- Yuqi, you must pick a good group. - Really?
We can't be in the same group with Jong Kook and Soyou.
(Almighty partners)
You have only 30 cents anyway.
You will see who smiles at the end.
(Bluffing)
But you have only 30 cents.
(They all picked a spoon.)
- My gosh. - They all are really strong.
(Team Blue, Team Yellow)
Let's begin then.
(Se Chan and Doyeon, Kwang Soo and Won Young, )
If you're pushed out, you're not eliminated.
(Jong Kook and Soyou, So Min and Dong Jun will go first.)
You will just lose your money every time you're pushed out.
(They will acquire prize money only when they get picked.)
How far can we go when we push out the opponents?
(Intimidating)
Why would you ask a question like that, Soyou?
Soyou, just don't kill them.
- It can be as hard as you can. - What is she doing with her hand?
(Her hand gestures are very intimidating.)
You can also tickle them.
(Violence is not the only option.)
I don't feel ticklish.
(Not humane)
- He's not tickled either. - I'm not ticklish.
(Me too.)
- Really? - I feel nothing.
- How can I play games with them? - I'm not ticklish at all.
(Shaking his head)
Jong Kook and Soyou...
look like trainers at a gym.
- That's true. - We should open a gym.
(The two owners of fitness clubs.)
- It's so funny. - We should open a gym.
I think we should hug each other to win.
(Cautiously)
(Giggling)
No, that's not what I meant.
- Hang on. - I'm sorry.
- Wait. - Don't say that.
(Please!)
- I made a slip of the tongue. - Se Chan...
- told Doyeon, - Stop it.
(Despite Se Chan's begging, Kwang Soo testifies.)
"I think we should hug each other to win."
(Se Chan says...)
No, it was a slip of the tongue.
(Se Chan wants to use this as his personal opportunity.)
- I didn't mean it. - Hey.
(Wake up, Yang Se Chan.)
- What was that? - I mean we should stick together.
What are you trying to pull off?
(Everyone boos Se Chan.)
What are you doing?
I just meant we should stick together.
(It was my mistake.)
Don't be ridiculous.
It's not like that.
It's a mistake. I meant to say we should stick together.
(I knew that you meant that we should stick together.)
- Look at him. - Let's hold together, okay?
- Gosh, I was surprised. - I tried to ignore it.
(He barely calms down.)
He's painting a big picture.
- We should stand together. - You know what?
We've never seen Se Chan so happy for the past year.
He's so energetic.
(His smile is the biggest one in a year.)
- He's smiling broadly. - He's smiling a lot.
You look bright today.
I'm happy today.
(1st round is about to start.)
I'll play the music then.
Music, please.
(Music starts.)
Dong Jun is a good dancer.
(Everyone looks forward to Dong Jun's dance.)
I bet Dong Jun is good.
(No one is excited about Kwang Soo's dance.)
(Warming up)
Mijoo is on fire.
(The audience is excited too.)
- Show us what you've got. - Hey, Jong Kook.
(The two fitness partners come forward first.)
- There they are. - Show us your dance.
The music is too slow.
Show us the workout dance.
(It's their theme.)
Go ahead and do bench presses.
They are lifting dumbbells. It's a dumbbell dance.
(They warm up with a quick dumbbell dance.)
- Go ahead and do bench presses. - Okay.
(It's a new fitness dance.)
- List it up. - Okay.
(It's a dance dedicated to lifting 500kg of...)
(squat, deadlift, and bench press combined.)
Let's do some bench presses.
Okay.
(You can do aerobic exercise and exercise your muscles.)
- Okay. - It suits you.
- I know. - Okay.
(They look good together.)
(Kwang Soo and Won Young step up.)
(The music changes.)
There they go.
What are they doing?
(The dance that Kwang Soo and Won Young will do is...)
(The 1st step is a fatal gaze.)
(The 2nd step is various model poses using their long arms and legs.)
(Bugged)
What are they doing instead of dancing?
Stop doing model poses.
(It doesn't suit you.)
What are they doing instead of dancing?
(He's not bothered and continues being annoying.)
(Jae Suk comes up to him...)
What is he doing?
(and punishes him with a headlock.)
Why is he doing this?
Why?
(This is the cost of acting cool instead of dancing.)
(Just you wait.)
Gosh, that was so annoying.
It was really annoying.
(Jae Suk makes justice for the viewers.)
(The next song is...)
("Shake It" by SISTAR)
(As soon as she hears the song, )
(Se Chan and Doyeon step up.)
- SISTAR! - Is it SISTAR's song?
(She dances to SISTAR's choreography perfectly.)
Wait.
She's really good at dancing.
She only came up to show off.
(Shake it, shake it.)
Nice.
(They do a couple-wave dance.)
(Doing his best)
I think Se Chan...
(That's hilarious.)
- is so funny. - Hey, Se Chan...
Se Chan looks like her helper.
He's serious.
(Yang Helper does his best.)
(Even if she doesn't look at him, he does his best behind her.)
(The music changes.)
(The look in his eyes changes.)
(So Min and Dong Jun step up carefully.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(She's shy.)
- Let's go! - Goodness.
(He begins breakdancing.)
(His coolness explodes.)
- Did you see that? - All of a sudden.
(The idol singer of 11 years rips apart the stage.)
(She fell for him.)
Did you see that?
(There's no break to her heart as she watches him breakdancing.)
So Min!
- So Min, pull yourself together! - So Min!
(She loses her mind and lets go of herself.)
(The frog lets go of herself without any breaks.)
She's break dancing too.
So Min, pull yourself together!
(Jumping)
Pull yourself together!
3, 2,
(The couple with the best dance will be called on.)
One. Dong Jun and So Min.
- Dong Jun. - Hold on.
(The couple that is called on will get prize money...)
3, 2, 1.
(according to how many people they push out in 10 seconds.)
- Dong Jun and So Min. - Dong Jun.
(So Min and Dong Jun were called on.)
Dong Jun.
- Hold onto me. - Pull them out. Okay!
(They go after Se Chan who is in front of them.)
- I'm frozen. - He's frozen.
(He's telling himself.)
I'm frozen. I'm frozen!
(Is he getting dismembered?)
- He's almost out. - I'm sorry, Se Chan.
(He grabbed Se Chan's belt and pulled him out.)
I'm sorry, Se Chan.
He's out.
(Dong Jun is incredible.)
(He's shattered by the belt attack.)
- I'm sorry, Se Chan. - Sit down.
(Dong Jun's next target is...)
- No. - I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
(He apologizes first then attacks.)
- No. - Wait. This is... Hey!
- No! - Hey!
(This time he goes for Kwang Soo's belt.)
Gosh, this is...
(Kwang Soo endures it, and the time ends.)
(So Min and Dong Jun got one person out.)
Se Chan...
- Se Chan... - You almost hung him.
(Se Chan almost got hacked to pieces.)
- Se Chan almost got hung. - Where did he grab?
(Sorry, Se Chan.)
He grabbed me at a weird place.
(Dong Jun. How could you?)
- Get up. - So...
- There's no place to grab, so... - It's okay...
(It's okay to pull the pants if it's necessary.)
- to grab us by our pants, - It was too...
but why would you put your fingers in between my cheeks?
(Exaggerating)
He tried to rip them off.
(A bad hand)
When Se Chan and Doyeon were dancing,
(By the way)
it looked like a guy who was dating a girl that's out of his league.
(I'm undeserving of such a girlfriend.)
- It's hard for him to handle her. - Right.
She's a girl that's out of his league.
(The 1st round ends with Se Chan and his undeserving girlfriend.)
This is the second round of the mission. Cue the music.
(The music starts.)
("After Effect" by ZE: A)
You should go up.
(Anticipating)
I don't know your dance.
Just do this.
(All Dong Jun did was dance, )
(but she can't stop laughing.)
I can't do it.
Look at So Min.
(Why does she keep laughing?)
(She can't dance because she can't stop laughing.)
- What are they doing? - Come over here.
- Why are they dating here? - Seriously.
(Pull yourself together, So Min.)
Hold on. Wait.
(In the end, the music stops.)
Hold on. So Min is really...
in the middle of date right now. I'm serious.
(The frog is not working, but she's on a date.)
(Shy)
- My goodness. - So Min. Enough already.
(So Min is so cute.)
- So Min is... - Don't date here.
It's not that. Dong Jun looks at people with warm eyes.
(The reason So Min keeps laughing)
Do we look at you with cold eyes?
(My goodness.)
Yes.
Look at his eyes. They're so warm.
(She doesn't hear anything.)
- You're too much. - No.
(Warm)
Gosh, it's so hot.
(They put their date on hold and get back to work.)
(What's this song?)
Whose song is this?
(Kwang Soo and Won Young step up immediately.)
(Flapping around)
Gosh. Doesn't he look like a bug?
He really does.
(A new kind of bug dance)
It's true. He looks like a bug.
He looks like a bug.
(He gets rid of the bug.)
- What now? - You're so annoying!
(I was doing great.)
- Why? - Goodness.
(A retro dance music plays.)
- What song is this? - We should go up.
(Back to the Millennium)
Is this it?
- How do you do this? - Soyou is really good.
Oh, my.
(Soyou is really good.)
(He grabs a tray in front of him.)
How do you do that?
(It's a retro dance that minimizes muscle loss.)
- It's over. - They're good.
- It's over. - Do it harder.
(They're busy doing the retro dance.)
It's over.
(An event balloon intrudes.)
(Jang Won Young the balloon begins spinning her sangmo.)
(Won Young is so cute.)
Jeon So Min. Why is she going up?
(So Min barges in.)
(I shouldn't sit out during a retro dance.)
Look at So Min.
(A retro dance party featuring event balloons)
Okay. 3, 2,
(The dance is about to be over.)
One. Kim Jong Kook and Soyou.
(Jong Kook and Soyou are called on.)
Oh, my gosh.
Kim Jong Kook and Soyou.
(As soon as they are called on, Won Young goes flying.)
(Kwang Soo's out in no time.)
Oh, my.
(Scared)
Gosh, that surprised me.
(Soyou is incredibly strong.)
You shouldn't do this.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
(So Min is out without a chance to resist.)
I'm sorry, guys.
He keeps grabbing me in a weird place.
(Dong Jun grabbed his belt again.)
(Dong Jun is holding on to anything he can lay his hands on.)
- Oh, my. - Gosh, this is incredible.
Gosh, this is incredible.
(Trainer Kook can pull two people at once with his strength.)
(Being dragged)
He's so cool.
(The couple with an amazing power)
- Amazing. - There you go.
- Jong Kook! - We did it.
(Clean)
It's clean.
How can we beat them?
(How are we supposed to beat them?)
They're too strong.
(I'm glad I didn't play with them.)
That was nice and neat.
- They got six dollars. - That was nice.
(Jong Kook and Soyou earned 6 dollars for getting 6 people out.)
I thought he was a bulldozer.
(Stuttering)
An adult joined a game with kids.
So Min and Dong Jun got 1 dollar. Jong Kook and Soyou got 6 dollars.
(6 dollars for Jong Kook and Soyou, 1 dollar for So Min and Dong Jun)
(0 dollars for Kwang Soo and Won Young, Se Chan and Doyeon)
Okay.
(The second group will go next.)
She's warming up.
This is going to be interesting because of Mijoo.
(She's ready to play.)
- Nice. - Hey.
(Jae Suk and Yuqi step out as soon as they hear the music.)
Why didn't we get songs like this?
(They get into the rhythm.)
They came up.
They played this song a lot on "X-Man".
(It's not an easy song to dance to.)
- This song is hard to dance to. - It is.
(She warms up a little...)
That's right.
(and releases her dancing instincts.)
(Behind her cute appearance, her powerful dance skills were hidden.)
That's it.
(Making a fuss)
What is this?
(Agitated)
Why are you dancing for so long? Go back in.
(Acting frivolously)
(Stopping)
You wanted to do something, but you couldn't, right?
(He figured out instantly.)
(Nodding)
(The next song is...)
("Gang".)
It's "Gang".
(The look in her eyes changes as soon as she hears the song.)
(Flashing lights wrap around me)
- "Gang". - Hey.
Mijoo, you look so cool.
(Mijoo's version of "Gang")
She's good.
(Let's have some fun.)
She's good at it.
What was that?
(Haha is crawling on the floor.)
Do you know what that is?
- What is that? - That's not how you do it.
(Haha obviously doesn't know.)
That's not how you do it.
(She does it perfectly. She must watch it 3 times a day.)
(The Rain Effect is when you entrust your body...)
(to the "Gang" rhythm.)
(At that moment)
(The reason why everyone is cracking up)
(She suddenly transforms into a gorilla.)
("Gang" has reached its limit.)
We should've done it.
(It's a bummer.)
Why are you going that far?
(Her tenacious DNA goes beyond "Gang".)
(Mijoo never lets you down.)
She's incredible. Just as I expected her to be.
(At that time, the music changes.)
- You guys should go. - Ji Hyo, let's go.
(How will Suk Jin and Ji Hyo dance?)
Suk Jin looks so cheesy.
(Slow dancing)
What are they doing?
What is this?
- Suk Jin, what is this? - What is this?
(Slow dance to EDM music?)
(They finish up with a perfect ending.)
What is this?
(The music changes.)
- Yes! - There you go. Go ahead and dance.
(Haha and Mijoo step up.)
- They know how to have fun. - You should go.
It's KOYOTE's song.
(They reject the normal.)
(It's a surprising dance that goes beyond our expectations.)
Gosh, Mijoo.
She's unbelievable. Seriously.
(He approves.)
Her energy is unbelievable. Oh, my. She's unbelievable.
(Her hair came out?)
- Her energy is unbelievable. - What is that?
She's unbelievable. Seriously.
(The fantastic outing of her hair extensions)
What is that?
- What is this? - What is this?
(Jaw dropping)
What is this?
(She's doing her best.)
What?
- Mijoo. - She ripped out her hair.
(My goodness.)
Who's going to beat her?
Nobody can beat her.
- Who's going to beat her? - Who's going to beat her?
(Her dance discourages others.)
- What's with her prop? - Who's going to beat her?
- Is that necessary? - What is going on?
- She's doing her best to win. - How can anyone beat her?
Just give her the win.
(Just call on Mijoo already.)
Mijoo, stop!
(Please)
She's the best.
(She can't stop herself.)
What did she pull out of her hair?
(No one can keep up with her.)
- Why did she rip out her hair? - She's the best.
(In the end...)
Are you okay? Hey.
(Yuqi also takes out her extensions.)
This isn't a game where you rip out your hair!
(Calm down.)
Do you have any? Do you?
(Ji Hyo.)
(She joins the gang with disheveled hair.)
(You can't escape the insane hair party.)
(What on earth is this?)
(We didn't come up with this game to see this.)
Mijoo is incredible.
(It was a feast of unexpected dances.)
- That's enough. - Three,
(Which couple will be called on?)
2, 1. Haha and Mijoo.
- Are they coming again? - Yes.
Why are you so strong?
(Haha goes after Jae Suk who is outside.)
He got him. He's dragging him out, but he's not coming along.
(Jae Suk endures it.)
They're strong.
(Since Jae Suk isn't easy, )
The other side. Goodness.
(he switches his target to Ji Hyo.)
What is this?
(Song Ji Hyo is out.)
Song Ji Hyo is out.
(Time is up after Ji Hyo gets dragged out.)
It was a close call, but we came to that decision.
It's impossible to beat Mijoo.
(Astonished)
- We can't beat her. - She's unrivaled.
(Mijoo tried her best to be funny.)
How can they beat her?
I don't think you can meet with your mom for a while again.
Will your mother be okay with this?
(The professional entertainer chooses to be funny.)
She'll call me crazy again.
- What? - That's what she'd say.
Why do K-pop idols always have additional hair?
(Interested)
- Right. - I'm fascinated...
(Even without a mirror)
by her reattaching it.
- Is she reattaching it? - I didn't know it was possible.
(The result of the first mission)
Here are the results for the second group.
(Current Amount by Partners)
Jae Suk and Yuqi got 4 dollars. Haha and Mijoo got 3 dollars.
(Jong Kook and Soyou 16.8 dollars, Se Chan and Doyeon 11.8 dollars, )
(Haha and Mijoo 9.4 dollars, Kwang Soo and Won Young 8.9 dollars)
- Suk Jin and Ji Hyo got none. - Three dollars?
I bet you're hungry now.
- Right. - We are.
You'll play...
(It's a chance to get lunch with the mission funds.)
for the dish you want with the money you earned.
This is Random Delivery.
(Random Delivery)
- Goodness. - What now?
Inside the 10 delivery cases are 10 different dishes.
(Inside the 10 delivery cases are 10 different dishes.)
Each team will come forward...
(One team will choose a delivery case...)
and choose a delivery case.
In secret, the team will check what's inside.
(and check what's inside in secret.)
The other teams, while not knowing what's inside,
(The rest of the teams can bid after asking questions.)
will ask questions about the dish...
(But the couple has to answer truthfully.)
to decide how much they'll bid.
The team with the highest bid will win the dish.
(The team with the highest bid will win the dish.)
- My gosh. - We have to bid on the dishes.
Some dishes are enough for the both of you,
(Some dishes are enough and some are not.)
but some will leave you hungry.
We need to fool them so that they'd bid on a small portion.
(Strategy)
- Right. - We need to fool them.
Let's set up the cases first.
(What kind of food are in the cases?)
- We'll now begin the auction. - Sure.
Please come forward, choose a case,
(So Min and Dong Jun will first choose a delivery case.)
and check what's inside.
Watch carefully when they pick it up.
Which one? Take your pick.
(After pondering, )
(he chooses case number 9.)
- Case number nine. - It must be light.
(Let's see.)
- Dong Jun, it seems light. - It's not.
Your shoulder is still relaxed.
(Is it light as Jae Suk said?)
It must be light.
Please check what's inside.
(Checking by themselves)
Look at them stalling.
- So Min... - Check So Min out.
The dish is on the upper shelf.
(Telling by their eyes...)
That means the dish isn't of a big portion.
- Exactly. - Really?
So Min, please describe the taste.
(It's time to ask questions.)
Well...
It's sweet and heavy.
- Right. - Right?
It must be a dessert. I say it's yogurt.
- Yes, a dessert. - It must be.
- A piece of cake? - A dessert.
It must be.
- Dong Jun seems flustered. - Hold on.
Like we said, it's sweet but heavy.
(Is he pretending to be flustered?)
- Then it's a dessert. - A dessert.
- It's not a main dish. - Something sweet?
(Obviously...)
To be honest, it's not a main dish.
(Ambiguous)
But it can be served as a starter.
Right, but it can also be a main dish.
- Of course. - It can?
So Min, who would you enjoy it with the most?
With me.
(Her level of happiness is at 200 percent.)
Dong Jun, stop playing with her heart.
He's mean, isn't he?
- Dong Jun... - I didn't think he'd be like this.
(Love Frog is swamped with happiness.)
- He... - Look at you being all cheeky.
- Have at it then. - He's unbelievable.
So Min, have a seat. We'll keep the questions coming.
(Oh, my heart.)
Don't. My gosh.
Dong Jun, can we focus on our work?
(You're killing me here.)
- Gosh. - She wants to work.
(A professional romanticist)
- What a player. - You're the worst.
He's the kind of type to not let go.
- Right. - I need him to promise something.
If you don't call me after today...
She's right.
(Frozen)
I guess you didn't know what she's like.
Dong Jun, you should rush out of here once we're done.
(After shooting...)
"Start the van. Drive. Drive!"
(Right now)
But So Min will chase him.
(He will be escaping for his life.)
"Get him!"
I'll buy her this when we meet again.
- The next time? - You'll buy her this?
(Something he wants to buy So Min?)
Really?
(Seeing an opportunity)
There's a place where they serve a tasty one in my neighborhood.
Sounds good.
It must be a waffle!
(That makes sense.)
- Where she lives... - It could be that.
(Near So Min's place)
There are famous waffle shops near Sookmyung Women's University.
- A waffle. - It must be a waffle.
It could be ice cream. Something like vanilla ice cream.
It's the whole package.
- So please don't bid on it. - He's right.
It's like one of those snack packages.
(Something like a snack package?)
I want a main dish though.
(Losing interest)
The auction will begin.
(They'll start bidding now.)
Dong Jun and So Min will bid first.
This will tell us.
(So Min and Dong Jun will go first.)
They could bid less just to throw us off.
- How about a dollar? - How much will it be?
- A dollar? - 1.5 dollars?
1.5 dollars? A dollar?
- A dollar. - So it's a dollar.
(It seems...)
You don't seem pleased at all.
- Can't we resell this? - Sure.
(Starting the bid with a dollar)
- But this... - It's not appealing, right?
- Not really. - Me neither.
I can guarantee you this though.
- Jae Suk loves this dish too. - Really?
I've seen him eat this a lot.
(Tempted by Dong Jun's words)
- Really? - What about me?
I can bet all 10 fingers on the fact that...
Suk Jin loves this dish.
1.7 dollars.
(Right away)
You won't regret it.
(Suk Jin bids 70 cents more.)
1.7 dollars.
Let me remind you that you only have 50 cents.
- What? - Really?
(He participated in the auction with a small amount of money.)
- You didn't know? - We do?
- Seriously? - And you're coveting the food?
(You're broke.)
- What are you talking about? - You're broke!
You can't have the food for free.
- We have the money. - You spent it all on the dice.
(The auction participant doesn't know his place.)
As far as we know, you have 50 cents.
You guys are broke.
This is because you bought all six sides.
(Blaming his partner)
So they're out of the bidding war, right?
- But we can take out a loan. - Sure you can.
However, you'll have a higher chance of coming in last.
(They have a higher chance of coming in last if they get a loan.)
Sure. But we should still eat first.
Then 1.7 dollars.
- We'll bid two dollars. - No!
(Resenting looks)
I won't go any higher.
- Don't be this way. - Got it.
- Did they bid two dollars? - Right.
- Then we bid 2.5 dollars. - Sure, 2.5.
(Then we bid...)
- Hold on. - We don't have to eat,
- but we bid 2.7 dollars. - Stop it!
(Why are you doing this?)
That's our last bid. I mean it.
Then we bid 2.8 dollars.
- Right. - 2.8 dollars.
Three dollars!
(Let's go.)
- 3.1 dollars. - My goodness.
(I want in.)
We'll bid 3.5 dollars.
- Then we bid 3.6 dollars. - 3.6 dollars.
(It rose to 3.6 dollars.)
That's too high for us to compete with.
(That's too high.)
Don't you dare bid anymore. This is ours to keep.
They're trying to trick us.
- Suk Jin, bid four dollars. - They want it for themselves.
(Coaxing)
Zip it, will you? Stop encouraging him!
You know how it is.
(They try to get Suk Jin to raise the price.)
- Don't fall for it. - Stop that.
(Getting impatient)
Let me add this then.
Suk Jin has taken many photos of this dish.
3.8 dollars!
(All right.)
(Smack!)
(He bids big for the pig in a poke.)
3.8 dollars!
(That earns him a smack on the head.)
(You still haven't come to your senses.)
What's wrong?
You're being smacked around today.
We're seeing a truly battered spouse.
(A comedy skit, "The Battered Husband")
Are you kidding me?
I promise to make up for it by earning more.
(Crawling)
It's just...
(I'll do better from now on.)
I promise to make up for it by earning more.
(The skit ends with his promise of earning more money.)
I'll bring you a fatter paycheck.
- You bid 3.8 dollars. - 3.8.
(The highest bid is 3.8 dollars.)
- It's too expensive. - It's too high.
3.8 dollars is too much.
I can feel it, you know.
The dish is something worth eating.
5, 4, 3...
(5 seconds to the successful bid)
Four dollars. I swear, that's my last bid.
(Not again!)
- I'll leave this with you now. - You already promised.
(He has lost his reason already.)
No way!
- Listen to Won Young. - No, no.
This will be my last bid.
(Satisfied)
- So Min's delighted. - We can't even bid any higher.
Kwang Soo and Won Young bid four dollars.
(The other teams stop bidding.)
5, 4,
(If it's a bad one...)
- 3, 2, 1. - Unbelievable.
(Kwang Soo and Won Young, 4 dollars)
(Sold to Kwang Soo and Won Young for 4 dollars.)
- Okay! - Four dollars.
Suk Jin added a photo of this to his profile page.
- His profile page? - Mine?
- Yes, that's right. - It's of lamb chops.
- 1, 2, 3. - 2, 3.
(What did Kwang Soo bid 4 dollars on?)
(TFS set: Tteokbokki, fritters, and sundae)
You see?
(Nice!)
- It's not bad! - I said you'd like this.
(Suk Jin gave up at the last minute and he thinks it's unfair.)
- What did I tell you? - It's not bad.
What the...
(Sad)
- This is my favorite. - It was a good one.
(Kwang Soo and Won Young get the TFS set.)
- They look delicious. - What did I tell you?
(Patronizing)
- They look tasty. - I need to take a break.
(I should have listened to you.)
- Are you okay? - Yes, of course.
(The couple promises to be in harmony, and we move on.)
- I'm sorry, Suk Jin. - Don't be.
(Haha and Mijoo are up next.)
Sniffing isn't allowed.
- That's equal to cheating. - Don't you dare.
(Highly sensitive)
I can't believe we lost the last round.
(After pondering, )
(they choose case number 3.)
- It's light. - It must be.
- It's light. - It sure is.
(It's obviously a bad one.)
Can we sit this one out?
(Acting like he dislocated his shoulder a bit too late)
- It's light. - No, it's heavy!
- It's light. - It's extremely light.
(It's obvious.)
His arm didn't show any kind of tension.
It really must be light.
(After carrying it over with difficulty, )
(they drop it.)
I doubt it.
(Gosh, it's heavy.)
(Light)
- I think they're snacks. - Take a look.
I could tell by Haha's face.
(They cautiously check what's inside.)
(Awesome.)
- No way. - That was brief.
I can tell that he's putting on an act.
He said, "No way" though.
Is it hot or cold?
(Is it hot or cold?)
- I like it when it's cold. - Me too.
Tell us its color at the same time.
(Tell us the color at the same time.)
At the same time?
- 1, 2, 3. - 2, 3.
- Green. - Green.
(They weren't in sync.)
Green.
- Say it simultaneously. - Why?
- I don't like green food. - What food is green?
(What's a green dish?)
It must be a salad.
A salad?
Is it a salad?
He said he likes it better when it's cold.
- Maybe it's broccoli. - I hate that.
(Green and cold. Is it a vegetable?)
It could be two pieces of broccoli.
Mijoo, when did you have it last?
(When was the last time you ate this?)
About two years ago.
- Two years ago? - It's not favored.
She doesn't eat it often.
I don't get to eat it often because it's so good.
Eating this leads to catching a cold.
- They're trying awfully hard. - Something green?
(It's probably not that good.)
- I doubt it's anything good. - I don't think so either.
Also, what can be green?
(They're not that interested.)
Nothing I know that's green is tasty.
It's time to bid.
Say something good about it.
Although, I doubt it'll lead to a bid.
Guys...
- We'll start at 10 cents. - See?
(He starts with the minimum bid.)
He could be bluffing.
No way.
It's too late for that.
(Well...)
We bid a dollar.
A dollar. That sounds good, right?
(Will someone get a tranquilizer?)
Won Young isn't pleased.
Won Young, they're bluffing.
- I think I chose the wrong partner. - It sounds like a good deal. No.
- Over a dollar? - You're just learning that?
(She didn't know he was this unreasonable.)
- I just realized it. - Over a dollar?
(Addicted to auctions)
- Come on. It's not bad. - What's wrong with you?
- A dollar? - Yes, a dollar.
- What's wrong with you? - Over here.
What if we end up having broccolis?
(Blocking)
Over here.
(Shut that hole.)
She hit him for real.
(Stopping her husband by covering his mouth)
- She hit him. - She actually hit him.
1.1 dollars.
(Firm)
- 1.1 dollars? - Yes.
1.1 dollars.
Suk Jin, we'll go bankrupt because of you.
You have five seconds.
- Unbelievable. - Five.
(It's about to be auctioned off at the price of 1.1 dollars.)
- You can bid more. - Four.
3, 2.
Two dollars!
(The price has gone up twice.)
- How much was it? - What?
- They bid 2 dollars. - 2 dollars?
- 2 dollars? - Yes, 2 dollars.
(What?)
- 2 dollars. - 5...
(They might be raising the price to waste others' money.)
- We're serious. - Four.
Over here. I bid 2.3 dollars.
Are you insane?
- Darn you. - She hit him again.
(Shouting as if her husband stood surety)
- Ji Hyo's furious. - What's your problem?
(Seething)
- I want to eat that. - It could be anything!
- But... - Is it worth taking out a loan?
(What do you think this is?)
I mean...
This is a marital spat.
(The real-life version of "A World of Married Couple")
- Tell me about it. - They're like a bickering couple.
The money we have is enough for just that.
(The immature husband)
This is our only chance to eat anything.
(The frustrated wife)
All right.
I'll say this again.
- Should we get it? - Children love it.
(The final appeal)
- 2.3 dollars. - 2.3 dollars.
(Is it a really good food worth fighting for?)
Let's buy this.
The fact Haha keeps saying good things about it...
(Or is it all Haha's bluffing?)
Five,
four,
- three, - Won't you bid more money?
- 2, - Won't you bid 2.40 dollars?
(Sitting still)
one.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo's 2.3 dollars)
Congratulations.
(Wins the bidding)
What is it?
Congratulations!
(2 bottles of banana milk?)
(Laughing)
I feel so bad.
(She gave up.)
He paid the proper price.
- These are nice. - He paid the proper price.
- Ji Hyo. - Thank goodness.
Thank goodness.
(Lifting)
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo.
(He got banana milk as well as the delivery case.)
These are nice.
Ji Hyo, banana milk is good for the skin.
(An immature husband who doesn't understand the situation)
It's good for the skin.
You can take the delivery case too.
(As a skit couple, they end in a skit.)
Thank goodness.
It could have ended badly.
Kwang Soo, we are in your care.
(Kwang Soo and Won Young are up next.)
- Kwang Soo, we are in your care. - Kwang Soo.
I will tell you honestly.
We have to buy from now on.
- Case number seven? - Sure.
- We choose case number seven. - Okay.
(He chooses case number seven.)
- It seems to be heavy. - There is food inside.
It's heavy.
We should eat it.
(It seems heavy.)
It's swaying too much.
(A great acting of the Baeksang Arts Awards winner.)
- It's heavy. - May I take a look?
- Of course not. - It's swaying.
I hear the rattling sound.
(Thump)
If there are no worries about spilling, it can't be anything good.
(They scan the food first.)
Say the color of the food at the same time.
(My goodness.)
1, 2, 3.
- Beige. - Yellow mountain.
(A yellow mountain?)
What did you say?
Mountain?
- It's beige. - Yellow.
- Mountain? - I would say it's yellow.
(If it's yellow...)
Is it curry?
- Beige? Cream pasta? - Yellow?
(Or...)
It must be pickled radish.
(Confident)
It must be!
It must be pickled radish that comes with jjajangmyeon.
(That's right.)
- Pickled radish is yellow or beige. - Yellow or beige.
- You are right. - That must be the case.
(Strongly denies)
- For goodness' sake. - That's not it.
Say how many words are in the name of the dish.
(Say how many words are in the name of the dish.)
1, 2, 3.
Two.
(Four?)
Won Young says two.
One.
(She changes the fingers.)
Won Young says two.
(The innocent soul is increasingly taking after her partner.)
- 2? - Won Young says 2.
The name of the dish can be two words.
(He tries to cover it up.)
- Really? - One word.
- It's something you crave. - It's on the expensive side.
- Is it on the expensive side? - Yes.
Let's start the bid now.
(The bidding starts.)
You won't be disappointed.
How much is the starting bid?
We will start at three dollars.
That seems excessive. It's too expensive, right?
(The starting point is 3 dollars?)
It's too expensive.
For some reason, I don't want to bid on their dish.
Seriously.
Haha, shall all of us forgo a bid?
- Let's do that. - The starting bid is three dollars.
- We haven't forgone a bid before. - Shall we do that this time?
(No one wants to bid for this expensive food.)
The starting bid is three dollars.
- Pay three dollars and eat it. - It's too expensive.
(What's going on?)
- Shall we stay this way? - In that case,
we will start at two dollars.
In that case, we will start at two dollars.
(He abruptly tries to lower the amount.)
- You can't do that. - What are you doing?
(You can't change it.)
- Wait a minute. - You already said three dollars.
- Let's see the next one. - You can have it.
(Forget it.)
There are many delivery cases left.
- Enjoy the dish. - Three dollars. Enjoy it.
(Everyone decides to stay.)
Take a look at the dish.
Thank you.
(His eyes lost focus.)
Stay.
- Stay. - 5, 4,
- 3... - We will bid 3.5 dollars.
- Okay. Go ahead and eat it. - 3.5 dollars.
(Okay.)
- Everyone, stay. - Stay.
(We won't bid no matter what price you ask for.)
We will give you one more chance.
(You won't?)
- 3.5 dollars? - Are you sure you don't want it?
(What?)
3.5 dollars.
- 3.5 dollars. - Why don't you want it?
3.7 dollars.
- 3.7 dollars. - 5,
- 4, - Take it if you don't have food.
(Despite their desperate gestures and stares, )
three,
(the remaining customers don't even budge.)
two...
You really should take it.
- Okay. - What could it be?
(Sold to Kwang Soo and Won Young for 3.7 dollars.)
Okay.
- What is it? - What is it?
- Look at Won Young's face. - Did you see her face?
(The look on Won Young's face is a bit strange.)
Look at her face.
- She is swearing with her eyes. - What is it?
- Why didn't he stop at 3 dollars? - Seriously.
- He raised the bid. - Why did he raise the bid?
(Are they fools?)
- Why did he... - What is it?
(What's the food that Kwang Soo bet 3.7 dollars?)
Why did he raise the bid?
- Is there no food? - Pickled radish.
Boiled eggs.
(4 boiled eggs)
(Mr. Boss)
Good shot. Good shot.
(He ended up spending 3.70 dollars on eggs.)
They are perfect with the TFS set.
Good shot.
- It's a health dish. - Okay.
(Great teamwork)
We did well.
- Okay, okay. - We did well.
Why did he raise the bid?
(He fell for his own trap.)
Se Chan almost fell for it.
(I told you so.)
That's too bad.
Let's bid this time.
(It must be a good one.)
Why did he do that?
Suk Jin's dish looks like a good one.
(It's Suk Jin and Ji Hyo's turn.)
- We should bid this time. - I know.
(It's about time.)
It's about time we get a nice dish.
(She maintains a poker face as she looks inside.)
- The bottom shelf must be full. - The bottom shelf must be full.
- Her eyes moved down. - What could it be?
(Their gazes suggest...)
- The bottom shelf must be full. - I know.
Ask us questions.
Say the color of the food at the same time.
(Say the color of the food at the same time.)
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- Brown. - Beige.
- Beige. - Brown.
Brown.
- Is it curry? - Is it chicken?
(If it's brown, is it curry or chicken?)
- Curry? - It could be chicken.
- Chicken. - How many words are in the name?
(Simultaneously)
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- 1 word. - 1 word.
(They say it in unison.)
- Chicken. - Chicken.
(We were right.)
- Is it really chicken? - I am not sure.
(Is it really chicken?)
Gimbap?
(If not...)
- What? - Gimbap.
Are you asking me if it's gimbap?
I think it's gimbap. I'm just talking to myself.
(Why are you listening in?)
- I am talking to myself. - But you spoke so loudly.
- I am talking to myself. - You spoke so loudly.
I have a loud voice, okay?
Let's start bidding.
(They start to bid.)
How much is the starting bid?
(What's the starting bidding amount?)
Shall we make it two dollars?
- 1.5 dollars? - 1.5 dollars.
Let's start at 1.5 dollars.
They will make us spend money.
(What kind of food has the starting bid of 1.5 dollars?)
(Hardtack)
I bet it's something tasty.
(They are totally fooled.)
When they made the starting bid 1.5 dollars,
their eyes met.
- Ji Hyo was unwavering. - Ji Hyo...
agreed with the price.
- We will bid 2 dollars. - 2 dollars.
It's about time we get something nice.
(They all think it's good food.)
We will bid 2.5 dollars.
- 2.5 dollars. - 2.8 dollars.
(It's getting competitive.)
- 2.8 dollars. - 3 dollars.
- Stop. - 3.2 dollars.
3.2 dollars.
- 3.5 dollars. - 3.5 dollars.
- 4 dollars. - 4 dollars.
(It now reached 4 dollars.)
- Four dollars? - Let's wait.
(Trick 1)
Let's bid 4.5 dollars and eat the dish.
No, no.
(Trick 2)
Let's wait. The price might go up.
We will bid 4.5 dollars.
(Join me.)
Five,
(Everyone is hesitant because the amount is already too high.)
four,
- three, - We will eat it.
two,
one.
- 4.5 dollars. - 4.5 dollars?
- Really? - Then how much are they in debt?
4.5 dollars is a hefty price.
They are in a lot of debt.
Then they will be at the very bottom.
We have no hopes of winning.
- That's right. - We will have a good meal.
We will have a good meal before we go down.
- We will have a good meal. - We will have a good meal.
They are in a lot of debt.
Then they will be at the very bottom.
- Shall we join forces again and... - Stay?
- Stay. - Stay.
Would it be okay if we join forces?
That's a good idea.
(We don't know what it is, but we'll make you go bankrupt.)
Let's give them tasty food.
- Okay. - What?
- Eat. - It's 4.5 dollars.
You should eat tasty food.
(Come on guys.)
- Hold on. - You deserve to eat.
You should bid more money.
(Please.)
- You should eat tasty food. - No, no.
(We shall all stay.)
- Stay. - You can have it.
Why are you controlling them, you punk?
(He's angry.)
- He is trying to back down. - You can have it.
If you bid five dollars, we might give up.
(Please bid more.)
It's important to make them use a lot of money.
(They don't intend to bid anymore.)
- They used a lot of money. - Let's make them use more.
- 5, - If we spend 4.5 dollars on it...
- four, - Let's just eat it.
(They can't recuperate anymore.)
- three, - Doesn't anyone want to bid?
two...
(No, we won't bid.)
- It must be something tasty. - I know.
(It's sold at 4.5 dollars...)
One.
(for Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.)
Okay. Let's enjoy the food.
That's right. It will be nice to eat tasty food.
(Has he gone insane?)
It will fill us up.
(We are in trouble.)
Thank goodness we stayed!
Okay!
It was hardtack.
We did well by raising the bid.
- What is this? - We did well by raising the bid.
You should have let another team spend four dollars.
(The investment fairy fell for his own trap.)
I thought someone would outbid us.
You should have let another team spend four dollars.
I thought someone would bid five dollars.
Suk Jin and I don't get along.
(We are too different.)
It's hard to make people spend more than four dollars.
Hardtack is...
(Have as much as you want.)
very filling.
If you drink water with it,
(He purchases the tear-soaked hardtack.)
(The remaining members make a bid for other cases.)
you will be full.
(Current Amount by Partners)
(Jong Kook and Soyou 13.3 dollars, Se Chan and Doyeon 8.8 dollars, )
(Jae Suk and Yuqi 8.3 dollars, Kwang Soo and Won Young 1.2 dollars)
- It's tasty. - You got jjajangmyeon.
(They finish their lunch.)
- I am full. - Let's go.
(They are waiting inside the car before they move.)
Your song is nice.
(What?)
Shall we take a selfie together?
What?
I was taking a selfie.
(Embarrassed)
- When I looked to the side... - I was taking a selfie.
(A pretty angle)
Shall we take a selfie together?
(She's cute.)
(It's an unexpected selfie.)
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
- Shall I send it to you? - Sure.
(The photo)
How do I send it to you?
(I'll need her number to get the photo.)
(He's preparing to get her number.)
What?
(Shall I share it via AirDrop?)
Shall I share it via AirDrop?
(Kids these days share photos via AirDrop.)
How do I do it?
That must be my phone.
I share photos this way.
(Embarrassed)
(The old and the young share a photo.)
Hold on tight. We will hit the road.
(They move for the last mission.)
Se Chan is in good condition.
Yes.
(By the way)
Yuqi, where are you from?
- Beijing. - Beijing?
- Beijing? - Yes, Beijing.
(Pretending to know)
- She is from Beijing. - I know the city well.
I visited it so many times. I visited it as if it were my home.
(Showing off)
- You mean Beijing? - Yes.
(Like your home?)
- I see. - One time,
Jong Kook got on the plane by chance...
with other girl groups.
(Jong Kook and Soyou got on the same plane for work.)
We were going to an event in China.
As soon as he got off,
(Jong Kook's Chinese fans filled the airport.)
his fans crowded the airport.
- His fans crowded the airport. - He is a Korean Wave star.
(He proved that he's a K-wave star with the crowd.)
- Seriously. - "Jong Kook!"
They thought the same thing would happen with Suk Jin,
so 20 bodyguards came for him.
They were as relaxed as ever.
They seemed confused.
(The airport was too quiet.)
- It was the easiest job. - It was the easiest job.
That's right.
(Suk Jin's the number 1 celebrity who bodyguards love.)
I told them to go back.
Seriously.
The bodyguarding agency goes wild when Suk Jin is coming.
"I will take the job!"
(Protecting Suk Jin is the best job for the work-life balance.)
- It's the easiest job. - "The easiest job".
Mijoo, what will you do from now on?
(By the way)
- Me? - Yes.
Will you keep going that way?
Will you switch over to the variety shows?
- You should. - You should.
I should.
(Curious)
Do you have a role model in variety shows?
- Lee Hyo Lee. - Lee Hyo Lee? I see.
(Mijoo's role model is Lee Hyo Lee.)
- Lee Hyo Lee. - How about you, Doyeon?
(Then)
Who is your role model?
I admire Lim Soo Jung.
(Doyeon's role model is Actress Lim Soo Jung.)
- An actress. - I see the resemblance.
She was in "Lump of Sugar".
- That's such an old movie. - That's such an old movie.
(Why "Lump of Sugar" when she starred in many works after that?)
"Lump of Sugar" came out ages ago.
- "Lump of Sugar". - It's a really old movie.
(Lim Soo Jung starred in "Lump of Sugar" in 2006.)
Out of all the movies she was in...
I watched "Lump of Sugar".
(This time)
How about you, Dong Jun?
Dong Jun is going into acting.
- He is going into acting. - Acting.
My role model is Jong Kook, of course.
- I want to bulk up. - What are you saying?
(Happy)
- He wants a body like Jong Kook's. - I guess you like to work out.
Do you want to own a gym?
- When I worked out a lot... - Listen.
If Dong Jun has a nicer body to go with that face,
he would look incredible.
Women don't like a man whose body is too perfect.
- What? - That's right.
- If his body is too bulky... - You shouldn't enforce your idea.
(Clenching his teeth)
I am serious.
You just touched a raw nerve.
(So Min)
- You... - It's okay, Jong Kook.
(Trying to keep calm)
- Don't tease him. - He hates those words the most.
Jong Kook is a bit angry.
(He's a bit angry.)
- He is proud of his body. - All right.
All right. It's okay. It's not wrong to think that.
(Repressing anger)
Jong Kook got annoyed with So Min for the first time in a long while.
(Twitching)
How about you, Won Young?
(The role model)
I admire Jun Ji Hyun.
Oh, Jun Ji Hyun?
- She has that vibe. - Ji Hyun.
- She has that vibe. - Are you close to her?
- What? - Don't you know Jun Ji Hyun well?
Have you met her or not?
We once filmed a commercial together.
(They filmed a commercial together.)
- Which commercial was it? - She must be the only one...
(She's a famous celebrity.)
you can't call by her first name.
- What? - You can't call her Ji Hyun, right?
(He is sure of it.)
No, I can't.
- You can't call her Ji Hyun, right? - No, I can't.
- Really? - Really? I want to see that.
(Jun Ji Hyun is not easy to approach even for Jae Suk.)
I can't speak casually to her.
- Really? - Yes.
(It's hard for him too.)
- I want to see that. - I can't speak casually to her.
- I see. - I can't do that with Jun Ji Hyun.
I can speak casually to Won Young,
(Jae Suk usually gets along with anyone.)
but it's different with Jun Ji Hyun.
(He can barely meet Ji Hyun. She's an exception.)
Kwang Soo, who is your role model?
(Kwang Soo. Who is your role model?)
- Isn't it Han Gi Beom? - It must be Han Gi Beom.
(Isn't it obvious?)
- Han Gi Beom. - I like him,
(Han Gi Beom, the basketball player version of Lee Kwang Soo)
but he isn't my role model. He is an athlete.
- How about an actor? - Yao Ming!
Hey!
A basketball player.
Why would Yao Ming be my role model?
(Yao Ming, the Chinese version of Kwang Soo)
(I do like him but why?)
Since he's very tall...
Why would Yao Ming be my role model?
(They look alike.)
- Yao Ming. - Your face reminds me...
of the Chinese version of "Produce 101".
That trainee.
(He looks like the Chinese trainee.)
There is one trainee who looks exactly like you.
There is one comment I remember.
What is it?
"I can't stand seeing someone with Kwang Soo's face act cool."
(Kwang Soo can't argue with that.)
For goodness' sake.
I still refuse to believe he is a different person.
- He is Kwang Soo. - It's so funny.
How did you go back and forth?
What are you talking about?
(Flustered)
- It was you. - It was you.
(He's sure it's the same person.)
When did you learn Chinese?
- What? - You spoke Chinese like a native.
What are you talking about?
(The rumor on Kwang Soo having two jobs is spreading.)
That trainee looked exactly like you.
(By the way)
I think Doyeon is pretty happy to be Se Chan's partner.
- Doyeon is. - Me?
- Me? - Doyeon,
have you always been a fan of Se Chan?
- Yes. - Really?
- Why do you like him? - We have...
(Doyeon loves Se Chan's jokes.)
- a similar sense of humor. - Really?
- Really? - I guess you like it...
when comedians paint on their faces.
- How do you see him as a man? - I am curious.
What do you think?
(She's surprised to see him up close.)
- My goodness. - Did you just laugh?
She became so startled.
How would you rate my looks from 1 to 10?
(Serious)
Why would you ask her that?
(Flustered)
- Why would you ask her that? - Your looks can't be rated...
(That's a configuration error.)
from 1 to 10.
Why not? Why not?
(He can't be rated with a natural number.)
- You need to go lower. - There is one.
- We need negative numbers. - We need negative numbers.
(Shaking his head)
You can just pick a number.
Se Chan is a junior I really cherish.
Overall, he is a good man.
(Supporting)
He is really fine when you see him from afar.
When you see him from 4km away...
(He looks handsome from 4km away.)
- 4km? - Seriously.
- That's ridiculous. - Then he wouldn't be visible.
(You look pretty from far away.)
He is handsome when he wears a mask.
That's right. He looks cool when he wears a mask.
Se Chan isn't half bad.
- That's right. - He is fine.
- Se Chan isn't half bad. - He is nice.
We are talking among ourselves.
(Only the original members compliment Se Chan.)
None of the guests are agreeing.
- None of the guests are agreeing. - Seriously.
(The guests stay silent.)
"That's right."
"He has nice looks." You could have said that once.
(Say something even if you don't mean it.)
We are talking among ourselves.
I saw everyone look outside the window.
All the members are nice.
(He's proud of his members.)
- That's right. - Jong Kook is nice.
- All of us are kind. - So Min too.
(They arrive at the last mission spot complimenting themselves.)
- All of us have a nice personality. - Kwang Soo too.
They want us to come this way.
(The pool is filled with the smell of flour.)
What is this?
I don't know. Is this soy milk?
- Is it flour? - Is it flour?
Flour is good for the skin.
I think my skin will improve.
(She has a feeling that it's good.)
It's good for brightening the skin.
I am optimistic, right?
Why aren't the others coming?
(Regardless of the mission, they're excited.)
It will be funny if we fall over.
- This is fun. - You might fall backward.
(This is fun.)
If I were close to you, I would have pushed you.
- You would have pushed me? - Of course.
(She should be glad that they're not close.)
(They gather around one by one.)
My goodness.
- What's taking them so long? - I know.
(What is going on?)
(Surprised)
Ji Hyo is mischievous.
Come on.
(She couldn't help but pull a prank.)
(She's happy after pulling a prank.)
Okay. Okay.
(Now she knows what it's like here.)
Ji Hyo found someone in her weight division today.
(Finally)
(The rest of the members enter.)
It's flour.
(What's this?)
Oh, it's flour?
If we fry Kwang Soo in there,
he will look like a fried loach.
If we fry Kwang Soo in there, he will look like a fried loach.
- Why would you fry me in there? - He looks like a loach.
Se Chan will be fried catfish.
(Today's last mission with a loach)
This is the last mission for the prize money,
(Sinking 3-Legged Race)
the Sinking Three-Legged Race.
What?
In each round of the tournament, two couples will participate.
(In each round of the tournament, two couples will participate.)
You will get the prize money in accordance with the results.
(You will get the prize money in accordance with the results.)
In 100 seconds, the couples will tie their feet...
(In 100 seconds, the couples will tie their feet...)
and move as many balls from the other team's area...
(and move as many balls from the other team's area...)
to their basket.
(to their basket to win.)
The team that moves more balls will win...
(The team that moves more balls will move on to the next round.)
and move on to the next round.
If you lose, it's over.
Yes. The prize money you receive will reflect the results.
(Regardless of the result, they'll get a dollar per ball.)
- The prize money. - The winners will get more money...
(The more they play, the more chance to get money.)
since they can move on to the next round.
So it's important to avoid Jong Kook's team...
in the preliminaries.
I'm sorry, but are you talking with your back to us?
- How could you do that? - He refuses to go against them.
Are you talking with your back to us?
(They detect the threat with instinct.)
The healthy couple is scary.
(They're scary.)
- For goodness' sake. - This is the starch pool.
(The special characteristic of the starch pool)
If you run fast, it will feel like the ground.
(If you run fast, it will feel like the ordinary ground.)
If you stay still, your feet will sink.
(If you stay still, it hardens.)
- Really? - Yes.
So it's important to run fast.
(So it's important to be agile for the final mission.)
It has nothing to do with strength.
We need to move fast.
Stop turning your back to us. It has nothing to do with strength.
Soyou, stop hitting me when you talk to me.
(You're scaring me.)
- Stand like this. - Female members, take a pick.
(The girls will pick their opponents.)
The teams with the same number will go against each other.
Number four will win by default.
(Current Amount by Partners, Jong Kook and Soyou 22 dollars)
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo versus Haha and Mijoo)
(So Min and Dong Jun versus Jong Kook and Soyou)
- Please. - We need to win.
It'll be good to pick number four and win by default.
(Se Chan and Doyeon versus Jae Suk and Yuqi)
(They enter the arena for the game.)
All right.
- Okay. - What?
(What?)
What is it?
(What is this?)
- What? - What is it?
Make sure your feet touch the ground.
(She's surprised by the touch she has never felt before.)
You need to move fast.
- I can't move. - Is it okay if you run fast?
- It's like the mudflat. - I can't take my feet out.
(It's like the mudflat.)
(Look at her.)
She is good!
- It's like the mudflat. - I can't take my feet out.
(Mijoo adjusts quickly.)
She is good!
It's like the mudflat.
There you go.
- 1, 2, 1, 2. - Keep moving. Don't rest.
(When they run, it feels like the ordinary ground.)
(As soon as they stop, starch pulls their feet.)
Don't rest.
We will start right away when you stop moving.
(They start in a standing position.)
Get ready.
(Haha and Mijoo versus Suk Jin and Ji Hyo)
- 1, 2, 1, 2. - 1, 2, 1, 2.
(You win by having more balls in your basket after 100 seconds.)
(Their starting speed is about the same.)
Grab a lot of balls.
(Picking up fast)
Let's go. Let's go.
Are you okay?
(But)
- What is going on? - What?
For goodness' sake! Haha!
(Their feet got stuck because they stopped briefly.)
Haha!
You can get up!
This is ridiculous.
- It's over for them! - What are we going to do?
(It's that sticky?)
It's over for them!
- What are they going to do? - Is it that bad?
(They got stuck in the starch swamp.)
- Is it that bad? - They are done.
It looks that way.
(We should keep moving.)
- They are done. - It looks that way.
(Thick starch wraps around me.)
Hold on.
- Is it that bad? - Get going.
(It's chaos.)
What is going on?
Suk Jin, give me a pull.
- I am stuck. - 1, 2.
What a bunch of amateurs!
(Talking big)
- 1, 2. - Look at Haha.
(Worried)
Is it that bad? My goodness.
Is it that bad?
My goodness.
(After a long struggle, they finally got out.)
- Is it that bad? - This is insane.
Let's take more balls.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are trying their best to turn the table.)
- Come on. - Where are you going?
It will be over if you fail to put those balls in the basket.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo, Haha and Mijoo)
- Good luck. - This is hard.
(During the struggle, )
(an armed conflict occurs.)
How could you slap me?
Don't hit me!
(It's getting worse.)
They are the absolute worst.
(The weaklings are exhausted already.)
Let's keep going.
- Ji Hyo is winning. - Let's go.
(It's humiliating to lose to each other.)
- 1, 2. - My goodness.
(Which team put more balls in the basket?)
One.
(100 seconds are up.)
- This basket has more balls. - Please come on out.
- Seriously. - Gosh, how tiring.
(Already exhausted)
- I am exhausted. - Really?
- Seriously. - Is it that bad?
I really can't move.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo earn 9 dollars for 9 balls.)
This team has nine balls.
This team has five balls.
(Haha and Mijoo earn 5 dollars for 5 balls.)
Five balls.
Suk Jin's team will move on to the next round.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo will move on to the next round.)
Okay.
All right.
(So Min and Dong Jun versus Jong Kook and Soyou)
They have know-hows now.
My feet keep sinking.
(Toddling)
(So Min takes tiny steps.)
This is no joke.
Okay! Never stop moving, Dong Jun.
(Excited)
Keep moving all the time.
(So Min and Dong Jun are struggling to get used to the starch.)
Unbelievable. This feels like a penalty.
- Look at how she walks. - What?
(Eyes opening wide)
Se Chan, can you keep my glasses for me?
Jong Kook, it's not that hard.
(Striding)
- Look at how she walks. - What?
(The two trainers have adjusted perfectly.)
- Soyou, what's going on? - Me too.
- You can walk like that? - Really?
Oh, your feet keep sinking.
(How do they do that?)
What's going on?
- Those two... - Jong Kook.
(The speedy couple So Min and Dong Jun...)
- It's different from walking alone. - Their strength is speed.
(compete against the powerful couple.)
- Speed rather than energy. - Our strength is speed.
Dong Jun is competitive too.
- Right. - He's good.
(He's pretty competitive.)
- He's very fast too. - He's very athletic.
- He's not an easy opponent. - I feel bad...
that I'm his partner.
- No. I'm happy. - I feel so bad.
You've never apologized to me once.
I'm already tired.
(Whispering)
It's nothing once you get out.
Exactly.
(Observing)
He's so sweet. After saying something,
- he gazes at the person. - Right.
"I didn't do it."
(He copies Dong Jun.)
Right?
Dong Jun says something and gazes at the person.
(Like this?)
I learned something today.
That's what I learned as a kid.
I was told to look the person in the eye.
That's why I feel so shy. He keeps looking me in the eye.
- Seriously. - I should do it too.
I think this couple is too unrealistic,
(Actually, the couple with a chance is...)
but I really hope those two will become a couple.
(Jong Kook and Soyou.)
(He is anaerobic. She is aerobic. It is a love story in Starch Fitness.)
- For real? - Yes, for real.
What about us?
All four of you, please stand up.
(They will begin in a standing position.)
- Three. - This is so uncomfortable.
- Two. - This is...
(Their feet are sinking.)
- It must be hard. - One.
(The game starts.)
- Are you ready? - It's exhausting.
- 1, 2, 1, 2... - My legs feel weak.
(Their starting speed is about the same.)
- They're good. - We don't know who will win yet.
- We don't know who will win yet. - Look at that.
- We don't know yet. - They're neck-and-neck.
(The couple with power versus the couple with speed)
- They're both good. - Both teams are good.
- What are they doing? - What?
(Team Speed's strategy: Remove all balls from the basket.)
- What's going on? - They're throwing all the balls?
- Is it okay? - It's okay to remove all the balls.
But you can only throw them from the middle.
That doesn't seem so smart.
(Team Power's strategy: Move the balls themselves.)
You can pick them up on your way.
- That's not a good strategy. - Hang in there.
- Oh, my. - That's not a good strategy.
(Jong Kook and Soyou move the balls safely.)
It takes too long.
We can do this.
(They put the balls in the basket.)
- Pick these up. - They can't pick them up.
- 1, 2... - Oh, my.
(Now it's a head-on competition.)
(The gym master...)
(and the rising star go head-to-head.)
- Dong Jun, you're doing great. - Dong Jun!
- Oh, no! - Oh, my.
- Dong Jun, you're doing great. - Oh, no!
(Jong Kook grabs Dong Jun.)
- My goodness. - No!
Oh, my.
(Jong Kook throws them with one hand.)
- It's over now. - Oh, no.
That's it. Goodbye!
(He ends the situation at once.)
Goodbye!
Dong Jun, good job!
Good job.
So Min, aren't you tired?
(Meanwhile, Soyou scores one ball.)
- Be careful. - Okay.
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
(Speed can't beat power.)
Is it over?
- Stay calm. - You can do this!
It feels like I'm hugging a telephone pole.
Jong Kook!
Hold on. Hey.
So Min is grabbing Jong Kook's neck.
(So Min counterattacks by grabbing Jong Kook's neck.)
Hold on. Hey.
So Min is grabbing Jong Kook's neck.
(Jong Kook and Soyou are stranded by So Min.)
- We don't know yet. - So Min.
So Min, we don't know yet.
- Oh, my! - This is getting so messy!
So Min looks like squid in batter.
It looks so messy.
(The deep-fried squid counterattacks.)
Oh, my.
- My goodness. - So Min, what are you doing?
So Min!
(The deep-fried squid attacks like a UFC player.)
Is this the UFC?
- You're all covered in batter! - Is this the UFC?
(The human deep-fried squid covers Soyou in the batter.)
- Why are you dipping her in there? - So Min...
- Is this how you play this game? - She's blowing air into my ears.
(The breath of fritter)
Your hair...
- Do something about your hair! - Dong Jun...
(She's soaked in batter.)
Soyou's hair looks like deep-fried seaweed rolls.
- Soyou... - Gosh.
(Deep-fried seaweed rolls and squid)
Oh, my.
(Time is up.)
- Let's do this. - Unbelievable.
- Gosh. - Are you okay?
(They're exhausted by the fierce battle.)
Does it have to be this fierce?
- They have 17 balls. - 17.
(Who's the winner of this fritter battle?)
- What about the other team? - They have seven.
Seven.
(Jong Kook and Soyou: 17, So Min and Dong Jun 7)
Jong Kook and Soyou win.
(Jong Kook and Soyou win.)
- Are you okay? - Oh, my.
- Does my hair look okay? - What is she going to do?
- It looks like a seaweed roll. - It's covered in batter.
(Deep-fried seaweed hair hardened.)
- What is this? - Oh, my.
What is she going to do?
Soyou, will you be okay?
There's nothing I can do.
(Touching)
Oh, my cap is attached to my hair!
No. Your cap is over here.
That's not your cap.
No. Your cap is over here. That's not your cap.
(Isn't this a cap?)
- That's not your cap. - That's your hair.
- That's your hair. - That's not your cap.
Don't try to take it off.
What is this then?
Soyou, your cap is here! Your cap...
Your cap is here.
(So Min digs up something that's supposed to be Soyou's cap.)
Will you be able to use it again?
You can untie it. Give me a second.
- Do you want to wash your feet? - This cap has been sponsored.
(It's savory.)
- It's a seaweed roll cap. - Is that a cap?
(Jong Kook and Soyou)
Next up are Team Suk Jin and Team Jong Kook.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo versus Jong Kook and Soyou)
This round will be...
(Jong Kook and Soyou versus Suk Jin and Ji Hyo)
really messy.
(A dirty but lopsided game is expected.)
I'm scared.
Team Suk Jin, if you make it to the finals,
you can end up at the top.
- Right? - If we make it to the finals?
Bo Pil, you're so mean.
(At the top rankings?)
- We don't know yet. - We don't know yet.
("We don't know yet" is a spell that moves Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin, we don't know yet.
- We don't know if they win. - Jong Kook, don't feel sorry.
- We don't know what will happen. - Please.
(Only Suk Jin doesn't know.)
Who knows if he'll get stuck in the starch?
Everyone...
Our strategy is...
(Enthusiastic)
Suk Jin is coming up with a strategy.
A strategy?
- From here... - I wonder what his strategy is.
I can't wait.
Do you know Mike Tyson's famous quote?
"Everybody has a plan until they get punched in the mouth."
(Everybody has a plan until they get punched in the mouth.)
Everybody has a plan.
(That's a brutal famous saying.)
Until they get punched?
Hey, don't say that.
Is Suk Jin finally getting punched today?
It's about time.
He should be brought to his senses.
(Suk Jin will turn into powder today.)
- There is a good reason too. - Of course. It's a game.
I'll keep what you said deep inside my left chest.
Okay? Please understand if I get aggressive.
Sure.
(The absolute strong in starch versus the deity of enthusiasm)
3, 2, 1.
(The semifinal begin.)
Keep taking steps.
Gosh, why are they so fast?
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo have outstanding teamwork.)
They have surprisingly good teamwork.
- I'm their fan. - They're good at the game too.
(Throwing, collecting)
- I'm a fan. - Oh, my.
We don't know which strategy works better.
(We don't know yet.)
- Right. - Not yet.
- Oh, my. - It's not easy.
- I'll focus. - No.
- The balls are stuck. - They're stuck.
Jong Kook's strategy works better.
Right. We should do that too.
(They're superior in both strategy and strength.)
They make it look so easy.
- I think it's over. - This won't work. Give up.
(Even if they pick up all the balls on the floor, )
- The balls are stuck. - It's harder than it looks.
(Jong Kook and Soyou have more.)
In the beginning...
They're guarding their balls. The gate is locked now.
- It's locked. - It's locked.
- The gate is locked now. - It's locked.
(Locked)
(It's locked?)
It's locked.
- Unbelievable. - Suk Jin is going to get punched.
(A shield that no spear can pierce)
"Everybody has a plan until they get punched in the mouth."
Suk Jin is going to get punched.
(A dull spear that can't even pierce tofu)
Please understand if I get aggressive.
- Here we go! - He's going to get punched!
(Who will be the winner of this game?)
- Suk Jin-Punching Show. - He's going to get punched.
- Has it started? - All right.
(This is exciting.)
Suk Jin, it's time to...
Suk Jin, it's time to carry out your strategy now!
But since there's Ji Hyo...
- You'll turn into a plaster figure. - Ji Hyo, don't be so weak.
Don't be so weak!
(He raised his voice, )
What's with you?
(but he shows how weak he is.)
- You should thank Ji Hyo. - What are you doing?
What are you doing?
(He's too weak.)
Come on. We should at least give it a try.
Here we go.
(Working together)
- Hold on. 1, 2, 1, 2. - Gosh.
(The dull spear and the muscular shield...)
(go head-to-head.)
Here we go.
(As soon as they start, )
- Oh, my. - Here we go.
(they get thrown.)
- Unbelievable. - Is this professional wrestling?
Left, right.
(Suk Jin is folded in half by their attack.)
Why did he have to compete with Jong Kook?
- Oh, my. - Jong Kook...
(My goodness.)
- Jong Kook... - Oh, no.
- He's being covered in batter. - No!
- He's dipped in the batter. - Oh, my.
He's being covered in batter.
(Flavorful)
(Crisp)
- Please. - Ji Hyo, stand up!
(Humiliating)
Stand up!
Stop!
(A starch man is born.)
Stand up!
Ji Hyo, stand up!
(The starch man screams.)
Stop! Stand up!
- Stop! - Stop!
Hey, stand up!
- Stop! - This is too sad.
- Stand up! - This is sad.
Hold on. Give me a second.
- Hurry up and stand up! - This is too sad.
(He got covered in the batter...)
This is too sad.
(without a chance to show off his strength.)
- Stand up! - This is too sad.
Hold on. Give me a second.
- Hurry up and stand up! - Spare them!
Are you okay?
Gosh, I can't believe you.
(Ji Hyo is angry at her incompetent partner.)
- Why are you doing this? - I can't believe you.
Why are you doing this?
(The starch-covered fighter)
I'm fighting against our opponent!
(The starch-covered fighter tries his best until the end.)
You should stop Suk Jin!
Suk Jin, don't give up!
- Here we go again. - Here we go again.
(Jong Kook suppresses him instantly.)
- Oh, my. - Are they okay?
This will happen to whoever makes it to the finals.
(Making everyone scared of the final, the game is over.)
- What? - Suk Jin, are those your tears?
- Suk Jin is crying! - Are those your tears?
Suk Jin!
(It's the strategy he's been saving.)
- Is he crying? Are they tears? - He's crying.
(He launches the tear strategy.)
He's crying.
Here we go.
(The monstrous team helps Ji Hyo and Suk Jin up.)
- Here we go. - Here we go.
- Stand up. - Okay.
You're amazing.
You fought so well.
(Jong Kook and Soyou: 17, Suk Jin and Ji Hyo: 9)
Your strategy worked.
I'm impressed.
(Respect for Suk Jin)
You weren't embarrassing.
(You lost, but you fought well.)
- Seriously. - You fought well.
- I admit it. - You lost, but you fought well.
Guys, Jong Kook...
is impossible to beat. Just give up.
Suk Jin.
(Jae Suk and Yuqi compete with Se Chan and Doyeon.)
(Jong Kook and Soyou)
(Jae Suk and Yuqi)
This round is going to be interesting.
(Kwang Soo and Won Young versus Jae Suk and Yuqi)
- I can't wait. It's a big match. - This is going to be fun.
- It's going to be a dog fight. - Yuqi...
(There will never be a match like this again.)
- Let me tell you. - Get in here.
I'll do my best, but I won't go to the finals.
It's going to be so fun.
(Because of him...)
He'll do his best, but he won't...
- I won't go to the finals. - He gives up.
(Boycotting the final)
- Do you understand? - I think I do.
Soyou, do we go first?
(Won Young puts her feet in the starch.)
It's starch that's flowing down my face.
- So this is how it feels. - It's going to be interesting.
I can't wait. It's a big match.
(Sticky)
- You win by losing. - It's going to be a dog fight.
It's going to be interesting.
I can't wait. It's a big match.
(Long arms and legs versus the original cheater)
It's going to be a dog fight.
3, 2, 1.
(The game starts.)
- Let's go! - 1, 2...
- 1, 2, 1, 2... - 1, 2, 1, 2...
(It's a head-on match from the start.)
- 1, 2, 1, 2... - How can you grab us already?
Already?
(The two kings of cheaters fight from the start.)
- If you fall, it's over. - Let's wait just a minute.
- Just a minute. - If you fall, it's over.
(It's a neck and neck match.)
- Let's wait just a minute. - If you fall, it's over.
- Just a minute. - Oh, my.
(Jae Suk attacks first using his teeth.)
- I didn't know... - You better fall!
(Hitting)
(Kwang Soo misaimed his water strider kick.)
Let's go. 1, 2, 1, 2...
(He abandons Jae Suk who fell and moves forward.)
1, 2, 1, 2...
He kicked for real.
- He does that. - He kicked for real.
(Kwang Soo and Won Young are ahead thanks to the kick.)
They're taking all the balls.
- How... - 1, 2, 1, 2...
(They grab the balls using their long arms, )
- Slowly. 1, 2, 1, 2... - 1, 2, 1, 2...
(and move fast with their long legs.)
- Wait! - 1, 2, 1, 2...
- His legs are so long. - His legs are so long.
His legs are long, so he's fast.
(Usain Bolt running across a pool of starch)
No!
Please don't grab us.
(Kwang Soo and Won Young protect their basket.)
Don't grab us!
(Yuqi squeezes in.)
Goodness.
- Yuqi is unbelievable too. - Don't do this.
Don't do this.
(While Yuqi blocks Kwang Soo and Won Young, )
Yuqi.
(Jae Suk quickly removes balls from the basket.)
Kwang Soo's strategy...
(This time, Kwang Soo bites him.)
(Kwang Soo, a young man with strong teeth, best at cheating)
Did you hear that?
The prize money isn't worth doing this over.
(Screaming)
(What's this noise?)
The prize money isn't worth doing this over.
(He retaliates with his front teeth.)
(It's the class of the original teeth attacker.)
Do they have to go this far?
Don't do this.
(Don't try to cheat.)
What are you talking about?
- Where are you going? - It will end like this then.
(Team Jae Suk will win if they get rid of Team Kwang Soo's balls.)
- It will end like this. - It will end like this.
It's over.
It looks like Team Jae Suk is going to go to the finals.
Hey, Jae Suk.
If you do that, you'll end up going to the finals.
Won Young. Grab him.
(That's right.)
Yuqi, we can't go to the finals.
Hold on.
- Hold on. - Yuqi.
(The 2020 Summer Horror Special, The Final Round)
You'll be in trouble if you go up to the finals.
There's 1, 2.
We don't have to.
- Don't you have to take them out? - Put it in their basket.
- In their basket? - We can't go to the finals.
What is he saying?
(She refills Kwang Soo's basket.)
He said they can't go to the finals.
(The final phobia created by the powerful couple.)
Give it to me. I'll put them in.
He said they can't go to the finals.
We can't go to the finals.
(We'll die if we move up to the final round.)
If we go to the finals, we're going to die.
Where are we supposed to put these?
(He pretends he's confused then puts them in Jae Suk's.)
Over there.
Wait, Kwang Soo.
(They blatantly push for Kwang Soo's victory.)
I'm going to send them to the finals.
Who knows? You could end up going.
(They're putting the balls into opponent's basket.)
- This is hilarious. - This is how it's going to be.
This is a game to avoid winning.
- You have to lose this game, right? - Right.
(An unprecedented game to lose)
(Soaked)
- I know. - I'm scared.
- We have to put it in. - He looks so scary.
(The Starch Man thrashes about.)
Won Young is crying.
(Is it here or there?)
- Won Young is crying. - He looks terrifying.
He looks so scary right now.
(He is now starting to get confused.)
Where do we put the balls?
- My gosh. - Over there.
Over there.
(At this rate, Kwang Soo's team will go to the finals.)
How many do we have?
At this rate, Kwang Soo will win.
- Kwang Soo will win. - We have a lot, but we must lose.
- Come here. - We have a lot, but we must lose.
- 1. - 1, 2.
(Leave 1 at Jae Suk's basket and take everything out from yours.)
Just put one in there and take all of yours out.
You have 30 seconds left.
(He puts 1 ball in Jae Suk's basket.)
- Take it out. - Take it out and go up.
(Jae Suk and Yuqi are protecting Kwang Soo's basket.)
- You look like a ghost. - 1, 2.
One.
Are they really playing to lose?
(If they empty Kwang Soo's basket, Jae Suk's team will win.)
(This is the chance!)
Won Young, take them out!
(Won Young uses her long arms!)
It's nice that they're exhausted as they're going up against us next.
- I'm exhausted. - Don't take them out.
- No. - Don't take them out.
It hurts.
(Who will win this desperate battle to stay away from the finals?)
Don't take them out.
It hurts.
- It hurts. - Don't take them out.
(There's 1 ball in Jae Suk and Yuqi's basket.)
- Here. It hurts. - 10 seconds left.
(There's also 1 ball in Kwang Soo and Won Young's basket.)
Gosh, I'm confused. Who's going to win?
Won Young!
(Please, Won Young.)
- I'm working on it. - I'll put one in.
Jae Suk is likely to win.
(She locks after the last ball is removed from the basket.)
- I took them all out. - How many do we have?
(The whistle is blown.)
(The last ball leaves Yuqi's hands.)
There were so many balls in there.
I took them all out.
(If it doesn't go in, Jae Suk will go to the final round.)
- I took them all out. - How many do we have?
- I took them all out. - We have to have something.
Jae Suk wins!
(It didn't go in.)
- Yoo Jae Suk's team wins. - Darn it!
Let's go right away.
(We tried so hard to lose.)
- Why? - No.
(Why are we moving up?)
Why are we going to the finals?
(They are the intimidating opponents of the final round.)
Okay. Let's continue.
You've won.
Okay. Congratulations.
(They lost but they won.)
- It was a dramatic win. - I can't do this.
I couldn't even laugh.
Kwang Soo was too... Gosh.
(Noise)
- Did you fart? - No, I didn't.
Did you just fart?
No, I didn't. I swear.
(It's from the floor.)
- Kwang Soo. - It wasn't me.
(No one believes him.)
- I heard it. - I didn't fart.
Why would you fart?
(Even if you are so desperate...)
It was my foot.
Why would you fart in front of idol singers?
Does that make sense?
- Where did the towel on my head go? - Why would you fart?
It's because he's no longer under pressure.
Sometimes you fart after being under pressure. It's okay.
(It could happen after being under great pressure.)
- Hey. - It's because your legs are weak.
(His legs are weak too.)
- This... - Since it turned out this way,
- Move after releasing your legs. - Yuqi, let's win in the finals.
(Hitting)
I told you to release your legs before you moved.
(There was a collision accident because Kwang Soo's legs are weak.)
- Goodness. - Jae Suk is going to sleep well.
My goodness.
(It was a messy win, just like everyone expected.)
This is a complete mess.
(He has no strength to control his body.)
I guess Kwang Soo really used up all his energy.
Let's go up, Kwang Soo.
(They move Kwang Soo, who has no energy.)
3. 1, 2, 3.
- Oh, no. - Move your legs.
No. You should try to get up. Don't just lie there.
(His eyes lost focus.)
What do I have to do?
Get up.
Kwang Soo, get up.
- That's not easy. - 1, 2, 3.
(They try to lift his head up first.)
His hair is going to get ripped out.
Be careful. He got hair plugs in the back of his head.
(Why would I implant back hairs?)
Don't you get hair plugs in the front of your head?
Why would you get hair plugs in the back?
He got some hair from the front and implanted them in the back.
Why would he do that?
He wanted to look cool.
- He wanted to do that. - Really?
(He's full of coolness and hair in the back of the head.)
He wanted to be hip.
- Kwang Soo. - You have no energy.
It was another dirty game today.
(An exhausted water strider)
- Stay still. - Oh, my. Come here.
- Goodness. - My pants.
I got your pants.
- She grabbed them. - Hey.
I'm sorry, Won Young.
I'm sorry, Won Young!
This is a line guys always say.
(A popular line by a drunken guy, "I'm sorry.")
They say "I'm sorry" after they drink.
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry."
(Drunk with starch, "Won Young, be Jong Kook's partner next time.")
- "I'm going to go." - "I'm sorry I'm so pathetic."
Come get him.
Next time you're here,
- team up with Jong Kook. - No, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
- Oh, my. - He's insane.
(I want to be on your team next time too.)
(It's the grand final round.)
- I'm going. - "I'm sorry I'm so pathetic."
(Jong Kook and Soyou versus Jae Suk and Yuqi)
Come and catch us if you can.
He looks like the ghost in "Ju-on: The Grudge".
(As the rankings continue to fluctuate, )
(Team Jae Suk can move up to the 2nd place after this round.)
The results of this game can change...
- the rankings significantly. - Right.
We didn't put in a lot of balls in the last round.
You have this round to make up for it.
Do you think we stand a chance?
I'm just doing it because I made it to the finals.
(This is so funny.)
My gosh, this is...
I didn't want to go up into the final round.
(He's aggressively protesting with a very white face.)
I think I know what will happen. I think I saw a preview of this.
(I think I know the result already.)
I saw you getting stuck in the starch.
3, 2, 1.
(The final round begins.)
They're off to a good start.
(The two teams sprint across the starch. Who will win?)
Both teams are showing manners.
(They throw the balls out while the others gather the balls.)
- They're throwing their balls out. - They're emptying their baskets.
They're gathering them, and they're throwing them out.
I don't think throwing them out is a good strategy. We did that.
(Speaking from experience)
I think gathering is better too.
They're really good.
(They are picking up the balls they threw out.)
(A sound of a fart)
- But... - But...
(What?)
I didn't fart.
- Maybe Kwang Soo didn't fart. - Hey.
- Yuqi. - Was that fart?
I told you it wasn't me. It came from Yuqi's direction.
(He claims his innocence.)
- It really wasn't me. - Yuqi.
- You must be healthy. - It'll become the talk of the town.
(It's so much fun to tease her.)
But you shouldn't do this to do that.
Yuqi's fart sounds healthy.
(Yuqi's healthiness is revealed with the sound.)
The sound is a bit...
- It was a healthy sound. - This is better.
(Wait a minute.)
- They're neck and neck. - Let's go.
(Is Jae Suk and Yuqi winning?)
- It's similar. - I think Jae Suk...
I think Jae Suk's team is winning.
(An unexpected turn of events)
Who?
- Who's winning? - Your team!
- We are? - Yes.
Then we need to stick ourselves into the starch.
What?
- Okay. - Really?
(The powerful couple is exhausted from 3 consecutive games.)
They're going to do that?
- We're here. - If you do that, you'll win.
(They might be able to win if they lock it right.)
- They're coming. Do it. - They're coming.
- Do it! - Here they come.
- Get yourselves in the starch. - They're coming. Do it.
(We're going to open up the locked door.)
- Lock yourselves in the starch! - We have to get through.
(Shaking)
(They successfully take over Jae Suk's basket upon arrival.)
The balls are coming out so quickly.
This is the scene that I saw.
(This scene)
- Hey! - It's over.
Is this how you're going to be?
(He doesn't even get a chance to pull Jong Kook in properly.)
He can't get up.
(He ended up getting sucked in.)
He got sucked in.
- He got sucked in. - Goodness.
- Oh, gosh! - Goodness.
(I know how it feels.)
- He got sucked in. It's over. - Goodness.
- I'm sorry. - It's over.
(He's soaked from the head to toe.)
Just end it!
Don't do that.
You dirty guy!
- Hey! - Okay!
(As his last-ditch effort, )
It's done!
(he puts his aggressive teeth into play.)
Just end it quickly.
Jae Suk's biting.
Don't bite me.
(I'm going to leave a mark on your chest muscles.)
He's still biting him.
(Even though he tries to rip the name tag in vain, )
(the outcome of the game is very clear.)
(Jong Kook and Soyou win the game.)
We did it.
(Worn out)
I...
- This is like a penalty. - Gosh.
Are you okay, Jae Suk?
- Are you okay? - Goodness, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk is crying too.
(The final round can be this bad for your health.)
- Oh, no. - Jae Suk.
Gosh, that's too bad. I feel so bad for him.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
- Jae Suk. - "I'm sorry."
Was I like that too?
I'm sorry, Yuqi.
I just heard someone fart again.
(A confession of a senior on top of the starch floor.)
Right?
I'm sorry you had to meet such a pathetic senior.
(The 3rd mission is over with Jong Kook and Soyou's victory.)
I'm sorry, Yuqi.
Okay, everyone. Thanks to you, an intense match occurred.
(The final mission is over.)
And the ranks have changed a lot.
(The rankings have changed thanks to the competitive matches.)
As I told you before, the teams in 1st and 2nd place...
(The top 2 couples can purchase the gifts with the prize money.)
can use the prize money to purchase the prize we prepared.
(The couple with the least amount of money will face a penalty.)
The team in last place will get a penalty.
- What? - I hope we're not in last place.
The penalty for the last place team is for them to lie in here...
(The penalty)
- while we make our closing remarks. - That's easy.
(Lay down on the starch floor as we shoot the ending.)
They have to lie in there until the end and get out by themselves.
(You need to lay still and escape without help.)
- That's hard. - After being in there for a while?
I see. That's hard.
The team that came in last place is...
(The penalty is to enjoy this starch swamp until the end.)
With a difference of 80 cents,
(Which couple lost by 80 cents?)
(It's So Min and Dong Jun.)
it's Kim Dong Jun and Jeon So Min.
- Yes! - Yes!
It's Kim Dong Jun and Jeon So Min.
(We are doomed.)
- Oh, no. - It was 80 cents?
That was the difference?
How much did we have?
(Kwang Soo and Won Young, 8.1 dollars, )
7.30 dollars.
(So Min and Dong Jun, 7.3 dollars)
7 dollars?
(Only if we didn't eat that tteokbokki...)
If only you didn't get tteokbokki.
- That's true. - If we didn't eat...
(We're saved.)
- We only played two games... - Please go in.
I'm sorry, Dong Jun.
- I'm sorry, Dong Jun. - "I'm sorry."
- It's all my fault. - It's okay.
(Please forgive me.)
I'm sorry!
So Min, just imagine that you're on a date.
- Gosh, I waited for this. - This is like a scene from...
(At a glimpse, it looks like a scene from a movie.)
- "Love Letter". No, "Love story". - You're right.
A scene from "Love Story".
It's like a field of snow.
(It's a field of starch instead of a field of snow.)
In first place is Kim Jong Kook and Soyou.
(The winner today...)
(is Jong Kook and Soyou.)
- Right. - They got 62.10 dollars.
(Jong Kook and Soyou won 62.1 dollars.)
- What? - 62.10 dollars?
- That's a lot. - You guys are rich.
(They are clearly the winners.)
We're like Mansour.
The second place team can get a prize,
(2nd place can win prizes, )
but the third place team can't.
(while 3rd place can't win any.)
But the difference between the 2 teams is 20 cents.
(The difference between the two teams...)
(is only 20 cents.)
- 20 cents? - It must be Yuqi and Jae Suk.
With 16.7 dollars, this team is in 2nd place...
(Which couple ranked 2nd place...)
and can get a prize. It is...
(and wins prizes by a small margin?)
(It's Jae Suk and Yuqi with 16.7 dollars.)
Jae Suk and Yuqi.
They got more money at the end for going to the finals.
(Jong Kook and Soyou 62.1 dollars, Jae Suk and Yuqi 16.7 dollars)
Okay!
(Se Chan and Doyeon 16.5 dollars, Haha and Mijoo 14.5 dollars)
Let's bring in the prizes.
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo 11.7 dollars, Kwang Soo and Won Young 8.1 dollars)
(So Min and Dong Jun 7.3 dollars)
- What is this? - Summer blankets and sweet corn.
(Summer bedding, robot vacuum, super sweet corn)
- Corn. - This is nice.
They even have corn.
(Prices: Summer bedding 30 dollars, Robot vacuum 15 dollars)
As a result, the 1st place team can get all three of them.
(Super sweet corn 10 dollars)
And the team in second can pick either summer bedding...
or sweet corn.
I want summer bedding.
- Summer bedding it is. - Summer bedding it is.
(Jae Suk and Yuqi got summer bedding.)
Dong Jun, how did you like it today?
I don't want to be rude, but my head...
Go ahead and do it.
How can you talk to us lying down like that?
(Joking)
He's lying down in a TV show.
I can't believe he's doing this.
Answer me.
Thank you for today, So Min.
(The proceeds from the 10th anniversary...)
Dong Jun, you did a good job. We had a lot of fun.
(and "Running Man's meet-and-greet"...)
(were donated to children's charity.)
(They get a call one day.)
- Hello? - Hello?
Hello, this is Running High School.
(They have to find their youngest sibling who skipped school.)
Where are you going? You didn't go to school.
Jong Kook!
(Solar of MAMAMOO, Jessi)
I'm not doing it.
(Lee Young Ji, Jeon So Mi)
I'll be an idol artist who brings glory to my country.
(They are the younger sisters who want to be idols.)
- You should at least graduate. - What's the use of graduating?
- She should get a scodling. - Are you sure it's her?
(They never get to know who's the real sister.)
- Lock the door! - Where are you going?
- Shut it. - Calm down, Jessi.
(The sisters are a little tough.)
- You're out of your mind! - What's wrong with you?
I said I'd go to an Ivy League college.
- I have no time to lose. - You should at least go to school.
(But the sisters are doing something else in their rooms.)
(There's only one way.)
Do you not trust me?
(They should either believe their sisters...)
Forget it.
(or doubt them.)
- It's a misunderstanding. - I don't like this.
- This is a mess. - She's crazy.
(They start to have doubts.)
(And they even have family squabbles.)
- Run away! - This has become a dinosaur game.
- Be careful! - Over here!
(No matter what they do, )
(they are still family.)
- What's all this? - Oh, my gosh.
- We're siblings. - We're siblings.
(Family Search Race, Unstoppable Sisters)
This is no joke.