(One March day at a restaurant in Mapo-gu)
Hello.
(Haha is the first one to arrive.)
- Is this your first time here? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Things are somewhat different than usual for the opening.)
- Hello. - I know it.
(He receives a mission bag from the start.)
I pretend to know everyone's name.
Namkoong is a unique name.
- Can I go in? - Yes, please.
(He goes into the filming room.)
What is this?
(It's an empty room with no one around.)
What's going on? Why is no one here?
(The table setting is unlike usual.)
These are seats for the guests.
(There's not even a crew member.)
Why am I alone?
(Feeling anxious)
(A sense of anxiety comes over him.)
What's going on? Hey, why are you here so early?
(Jong Kook enters.)
- I was asked to come early. - You got a mission, didn't you?
(You got here first.)
- Not at all. - I'm sure you did.
(He's innocent.)
(He's misunderstood just because he came early.)
- Gosh, this is... - Just tell me the truth.
- Haha. - This is crazy.
(They don't trust each other as things are different from usual.)
- I'm serious. - Hello.
- Haha. - Will you lie to us?
- Hello. - He was sitting here alone.
(Haha's suspicious.)
- He's a spy. - It doesn't make sense.
(Clearly)
- I was on the fourth floor. - This is strange.
(It feels strange.)
- What? Are we eating? - Hello.
- I guess we're eating. - I think Haha got a mission.
(Haha looks suspicious today.)
- He came early. - He was sitting here alone.
What about Haha?
- He was waiting for us. - What's going on?
(Haha's in trouble for coming to work early.)
- What? - He was here waiting.
- He's being suspicious. - We get a bag like this...
(Buzzing)
all the time.
What?
(Surprised)
Since when did we have cameras that moved like this?
This is amazing. The camera is moving.
- So Min. - Don't be silly.
(It's amazing.)
Is this your first time seeing that?
So Min dyed her hair.
Oh, right.
Doesn't she look Russian?
So Min, can you show us?
- Eastern Europe. - Right. Eastern Europe.
(Tetris dance)
She looks like a woman from Eastern Europe.
(She looks like a woman from Eastern Europe.)
I agree.
- Press it. - Do we have R coins already?
(There are R coins in their bags.)
What?
What? When did we get this?
(Dropping)
Hey, if someone picks these up...
(Ji Hyo releases all her R coins.)
- So Min. - Jae Suk.
We haven't started yet. You can't do this.
(You thief.)
Give me that. Hey.
- Give it back to me. - This is mine.
- Give it here, punk. - It's mine.
- So Min, your hair... - Don't lie to me.
(She suspects him first.)
- That's not true. - You can count them.
How many do you have?
Last time,
(Everyone's having a good time chatting.)
- I got gum. - That's terrible.
- It's the worst. - Seriously, this is mine.
(Ji Hyo doesn't trust Kwang Soo.)
- Hang on. - Guys, please help me.
(He pleads innocence.)
What's wrong with her? I didn't take your coins.
- What's wrong? - I didn't take your coins.
(He's innocent.)
You can check my bag.
- Jae Suk hid his. - Why?
(Get up.)
- Stand up. - We should be a team.
I can't trust you.
- I'm 36 years old now. - I saw that.
(Goodness.)
(What really happened?)
Hey, if someone picks these up...
(While Ji Hyo looked away, )
- So Min. - Jae Suk.
(he stole 2 coins.)
(As he tried to put them in his bag, )
We haven't started yet. You can't do this.
(she gets a glimpse.)
Give me that. Hey.
(Ji Hyo ended up losing 1 coin.)
It's not over yet.
(Did I get everything back?)
- It's not started yet. - We should wait.
Did you watch their commercial?
(Meanwhile, they're talking about Se Chan and So Min's commercial.)
- They did a commercial together. - Did you watch it?
I have 18 coins and he has 21.
(On the other side, they're still fighting over R coins.)
- Give it to her. Let me count mine. - We're talking at the same time.
(This is hectic.)
(Tired)
You have 21 coins while we have 20.
(It's hectic when they're by themselves.)
I guess we're doing something here.
Let me see.
- You should watch it. - This is open at the bottom.
(After chatting for a while...)
Why are we doing this?
(What are we doing today?)
I was asked not to eat before I come.
- This is a little awkward. - What?
(Their suspicion grows.)
- I had a big meal earlier. - I didn't eat.
(Two women are approaching.)
- Excuse me. - Gosh.
(Today's guests)
- Hyun Hee. - Hello.
(Comedians Hong Hyun Hee and Kim Ji Min)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Welcome)
- Ji Min. - You've lost a lot of weight.
(Hyun Hee lost a lot of weight.)
- She looks different. - Hello.
- Hello. - She's become so prettier.
(Surprised)
(Shy)
I haven't changed that much.
- Have a seat. - You've lost a lot of weight.
You look so much better. Your face is so small.
(Exclaiming)
You look healthy.
- I like your hair. It looks good. - Now that I lost weight,
- the wave looks better. - You look pretty.
(Everyone pays attention to Hyun Hee.)
You look perfect.
She has a pretty face.
(I'm a guest too. Will you pay attention to me too?)
You're so pretty. You look cute.
My features?
Why did you lose weight? They don't even care about me.
(She's upset that Hyun Hee gets all the attention.)
- Ji Min. - So this is how it feels.
(This is what it feels like to be a celebrity.)
- Ji Min. - It feels so good.
- We will talk to you too. - We should talk to Ji Min.
(Now they pay attention to Ji Min.)
Ji Min's wearing snakeskin.
Right. That's what I'm wearing.
(I'm wearing snakeskin for this.)
It looks unique.
(Welcome, Ji Min.)
Is it a jacket?
I just got goosebumps as I looked to the right.
I just saw Se Chan's face.
(Hyun Hee's shocked to see Se Chan.)
After I lost weight, I gained confidence.
(She and her husband used the app that switches faces.)
So my husband and I tried this app where you can switch faces.
And my face was switched to Se Chan's.
(Surprised)
(Hyun Hee looks like Se Chan when she loses weight?)
Really?
- Seriously? - Because I have a protruding mouth.
- They look alike. - She kept getting Se Chan's face.
(The app)
- I think they look alike. - See? I look just like him.
(Let me show you.)
Gosh, look at this.
- This is Se Chan. - Se Chan!
(What is Se Chan doing in there?)
- This is Se Chan's face. - Se Chan.
- It's unbelievable. - My gosh.
(Se Chan is even more surprised.)
Hey! Hyun Hee.
If you keep using this app, you'll get more photos of Se Chan.
This is scary.
(Copies of Se Chan)
- I guess my gene... - Se Chan.
- My gene is very strong. - It's really strong.
(His jaw is developed.)
To be honest, Se Chan has become ugly these days.
Why?
- He just looks ugly. - I feel offended.
(Enraged)
Why would you feel offended?
- Never mind. - She didn't mean you.
She didn't say that to you.
You don't have to be mad.
(Se Chan's clone gets angry.)
- No. - She wasn't talking to you.
- You look good these days. - I feel offended.
I got mad as she said Se Chan is ugly.
(She was too absorbed in it.)
(She was absorbed in it.)
You two look good together though.
- Hello. - We should place an order.
(It's time to order.)
Thank you.
- Are we eating here? - Yes.
- What are we doing? - Are we eating here?
(We're just going to eat?)
Is this it?
- This is the beginning. - There must be something.
(Suspicious)
- I'm sure something's going on. - We're here to eat.
(Fumbling around as he feels suspicious)
- Hey, are we teams like this? - That will be fine.
(Something doesn't feel right.)
I guess we're a team.
- Really? - Two teams like this?
Let's just eat.
- Hang on. - Wait. Why is he...
(Doubting)
(All of a sudden)
Why are you trying to lead us?
- Did you get a mission? - He's being strange.
Haha is being strange.
(Everyone feels suspicious as the show starts differently.)
He was sitting here alone waiting for us.
- I just came early. - He usually doesn't come early.
I just got here early.
(What is going on?)
- I'll have hairtail. - Me too.
(They'll stop doubting and order first.)
- I'll have grilled hairtail. - Grilled hairtail.
Two grilled hairtails, please.
It feels like we're having a get-together.
Give us some soju and beer.
We're not having a party.
(So Min lets go of herself as she hears it's a get-together.)
Beer and soju, please.
It's so loud when we're together.
(Since it's just us...)
It's not like we're having a party. What are we doing here?
(They finished ordering for now.)
This is nice though.
- It's very nice to eat together. - This is our first time.
(Puzzled)
- There's no trash can in here. - What?
(Garbage)
- I can't throw this way. - Give me that.
I will...
(Jae Suk goes out to throw away the garbage.)
And Se Chan would say okay.
(Since I'm out here...)
Can we get some water, please?
(He keeps asking for something, )
Could you get us some water?
(but it's quiet.)
(Something's strange.)
What is going on?
- Jae Suk. - Yes?
- Give us five coins. - Why?
Today is a Race of Wits.
We will get five coins from members who leave the room in an hour.
(Those who leave the room will hand in 5 coins.)
- My gosh. - Since you're out,
- you need to give us five coins. - I'm just here to get some water.
It will be advantageous to you if you let other members leave.
(He must lure others to survive.)
This is ridiculous.
You left the room without focusing on the shoot. Give us the coins.
I just came out to throw out some garbage and get some water.
(He gets in trouble for coming out to throw trash out.)
Everyone's thirsty.
We'd like you to focus more on the shoot.
(Frustrated)
All right. So this is how it's going to be.
(Spilling)
Five coins.
(He just spilled R coins feeling frustrated.)
Gosh, I'm so upset.
I can't believe this.
They are so funny when they're together.
(They all are chatting away without knowing anything.)
- You mean Jason could do better. - That's what I thought at first.
- He's funny. - He's really funny.
(He sits down quietly.)
Of course.
(He taps Kwang Soo quietly with his leg.)
You know you're my wife's favorite comedienne.
You've gotten so pretty.
(What?)
You know you're my wife's favorite comedienne.
(Check outside, Kwang Soo.)
She really liked you in your play.
(Kwang Soo sensed something.)
I know. She came to watch my play.
- My wife really likes her play. - Really?
(And he leaves quietly.)
(What is it? I guess something's going on.)
I won't give it.
(Looking forward to something)
Jae Suk told me to come out.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- You've failed your mission. - What?
We'd like you to hand in five R coins.
(He doesn't understand what's going on.)
Why?
Because you didn't focus on the shoot.
(He realizes it too late...)
(and he's stunned.)
So you need to hand in five coins.
Jae Suk tapped me with his leg and told me to leave.
(Frustrated)
You left the room without focusing on the shoot.
(All right. Give me the R coins.)
That's not true.
You may go back now.
(Kwang Soo lost 5 coins.)
- I talked to them. - Why aren't they giving us water?
(They're all peaceful without knowing what's going on outside.)
- Suk Jin. - What?
The garbage.
The garbage?
(He lures Suk Jin outside using the trash as an excuse.)
- Give me that. - There's a trash can out there.
Go throw it away.
Thank you.
(He suddenly gives it to Ji Hyo.)
(That's not right.)
- Here, I'll go. - Ji Hyo.
Let Suk Jin throw it away.
- Why? - Ji Hyo does it a lot.
(What's the matter?)
- You should do this. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(Then...)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Suk Jin wins.)
You should do it.
(Just do it.)
You do it. Ji Hyo does it all the time.
(Jae Suk just kicks him out.)
- Really? - No.
(Suk Jin is forced to go outside.)
Where can I throw this away?
- This is crazy. - There's something here.
(He must have been fooled too.)
- What? - My gosh.
- What's going on? - Suk Jin.
- Yes? - You've failed your mission.
We'd like you to hand in five R coins.
We'll take five coins.
(He also loses 5 coins because of Jae Suk.)
This is ridiculous.
I should tell them to come out then.
(I can't be the only one losing the coins.)
I knew it was strange.
(Kwang Soo comes back after losing his coins.)
- Where did you go? - What?
(He smiles after fooling him.)
I'm not like that.
- Where did you go, Kwang Soo? - He got his mission.
(Suspicious)
(It's obvious.)
Where is Suk Jin?
- Is he on a mission? - He's out to throw away garbage.
(Suk Jin)
And why did you go out?
(With all the questions, )
- I went to ask for water. - I see.
(he calmly defends himself.)
(I should fool Se Chan this time.)
- Se Chan, go ask for water. - Okay.
(Let me get my bag first.)
- I asked earlier, but... - I know.
Why are you taking that with you?
(Doubting)
Hey, why are you taking the bag?
You'd steal my coins. I can't let that happen.
(Preventing the bag from getting stolen)
I have to keep my coins.
(Kwang Soo tries to fool Jong Kook.)
- I think... - Why are you taking that with you?
(You should go out.)
You'd steal my coins. I can't let that happen.
(Okay.)
I have to keep my coins.
You can just ring the bell. Why would you go out?
(The 2 people who are deceived leave the room.)
This is strange. Why are they all leaving?
- What's going on? - I just...
need to go to the bathroom.
(Are we supposed to leave the room?)
I almost passed out.
Kwang Soo just went out with his injured leg.
- Why are they leaving? - Why did you do that?
If you're curious, you should go out.
- So Min. - What's going on?
(You should go out.)
(Should I go out?)
(Standing up)
- So Min. - What's going on?
(As Suk Jin sends a signal, )
(Ji Hyo gets up too.)
(They feel like they shouldn't be the last one to leave.)
- So Min. - What's going on?
(Haha gets up too.)
(We got them.)
Why are they leaving?
(They just can't hide their smiles.)
- Is something going on? - What?
What's going on?
(Snorting)
Is this a prank?
(While Jae Suk gives a snort in joy...)
Se Chan and Jong Kook.
You've failed your mission. Hand in five R coins.
(Se Chan and Jong Kook also lose 5 coins.)
- What? - Jae Suk came out, so...
(Realizing)
Because he came out.
When Jae Suk came back, I thought he didn't look happy.
Hand in five coins.
(So Min and Ji Hyo lose 5 coins too.)
Haha, you've failed your mission.
Give us five R coins.
(He hears the bad news as soon as he gets out.)
I can't believe this.
I'll get them later.
- We have one person left. - So all the members left the room?
- Yes. - What? Why?
(Hitting)
(He smacks Kwang Soo in anger.)
One more person needs to go out.
(Why are you clapping? You're the same.)
Why did you do that to us?
(Snorting)
Come here.
- I can't believe this. - Gosh.
What?
(What's going on?)
- What? - I had no idea.
(Ji Min and Hyun Hee couldn't help wondering, )
- Go ask for water. - Okay, I'll go get some water.
(and they also step out.)
Where do I go?
I was surprised when I went out there.
(You guys are awful.)
You all are unbelievable.
- I know. - Nice.
(They're of one mind when they need to deceive others.)
- So it's reset. - I'm so disappointed.
- You are evil. - You're so mean.
(You're so mean.)
If one of us leaves...
- You're the worst. - It could happen.
- I shouldn't have left. - You left because it was strange.
(They were all fooled as they didn't see it coming.)
We did it out of greed. We wanted to get something.
We should've stayed here.
(There's one more victim.)
(They've all left the room including Hyun Hee.)
- Welcome back. - Hyun Hee. Did you order water?
- So we're starting over again. - See?
(They were all deducted 5 coins.)
I shouldn't have left.
It was so funny. When I came back,
I just tapped Kwang Soo with a foot without saying anything.
(He tapped Kwang Soo, )
(and he fell for it right away.)
His face seemed serious. I had to believe him.
You thought he was only talking to you.
(Jae Suk's face phishing is scarier than voice phishing.)
So I was very moved.
(He was moved as he thought Jae Suk was being nice to him.)
I was deeply touched.
I'm cautious about what I do. What would be next?
If we go out of the room again, do we have to pay again?
- I don't know. - I'm not sure about that.
If you leave again, something good might happen.
(Or it could be something good if you leave this time.)
It might be something good.
I should go out then.
(Gullible)
- I will. - Hey.
(Standing up)
- I should go out then. - I will.
(As Jae Suk tries to leave, )
(Kwang Soo sprints out.)
Hey. I should go.
- That was quick. - Is his leg okay?
Is his leg okay?
- Why is he so fast? - He's just like before he got hurt.
(Before he was injured)
He walks fine.
- It's because you're a cripple. - I want to know if you can.
(He's like Keyser Soze from "The Usual Suspects".)
Hey. I should go.
(Keyser Kwang Soo)
(He hurries his steps as if he needs to go to the bathroom.)
(Looking forward to it)
Kwang Soo, you are out again.
Since you didn't focus on the shoot,
I'll get another five coins from you.
(Sighing)
Give me your coins.
You did it before.
(He has come all the way here with his injured leg.)
Are you serious?
(Wasn't it a good thing?)
He's back. Look at his face.
(Putting on a face)
Okay? He said okay.
(It's obvious.)
You lost another five coins, right?
No.
Let me tell you one thing.
- It's begun. - We don't have much time.
- It's done. - There's not much time.
(Who do you think you're fooling?)
- Just have a seat. - Okay.
As he came back in...
I'm curious though.
Because...
- it might be a double fake. - That's right.
- That's what I'm afraid of. - A double fake.
(Yes, I almost got them.)
There might be something good.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors and let the loser go out.
(He fails to hold himself back and gets up.)
What if we get 10 R coins?
(Is it really something good?)
What if they give 20 R coins?
Is that it?
We might get all the coins they collected earlier.
(From earlier)
(Tempted)
- What? - They got five coins from us each.
I'm telling you this because I can't go out again anyway.
I can't go out again.
(Method acting)
But there aren't many chances left.
No.
(Suk Jin also tries to escape as he hears the news.)
Wait, Suk Jin.
- Wait. - Let me go.
The unlucky ones are moving now. It means it's not good.
(Feeling unlucky)
I'm serious.
(Arguing)
I'm only saying this because I can't go out again.
The unlucky ones are moving now.
(Throwing)
I pushed him out.
(He forces Suk Jin out.)
It was your plan.
- I let Suk Jin out. - You pushed him out.
(He wasn't sure, so he sacrificed Suk Jin.)
Good job.
It was like when you pretend to throw a ball...
and your dog would fall for it.
- He looked just like that. - He fooled Suk Jin.
Is it a good thing or not?
Just be honest with us.
(They start interrogating him.)
It's not good.
- It's a good thing. - Is it good?
(Acting from the inside)
You'll see it on Suk Jin's face.
We should wait and see how Suk Jin reacts.
Since you didn't focus again, I'll get another five coins.
(It must be a good thing, right?)
(No, it's not good.)
(His blood pressure is going up.)
Please stay focused.
(Sad)
This is a war of wits.
I know. It's like "believe it or not."
It's not a good thing.
(Feigned smile)
He smiled as soon as he got in. He's bitter.
(A keen wit)
He's smiling because it's something absurd.
- He's mad. - How can I put this?
(I won't get fooled.)
(Everybody is looking at him.)
- Is nobody else going? - No.
- That's not it. - Let's just see what happens.
(Let's just leave him.)
- Are you going again? - Are you seriously not going?
(Hesitant)
Leave him.
- Are you going again? - Are you seriously not going?
(No, we're not going.)
Leave him.
- We're not going. - He just said...
(He isn't making any sense.)
- he can't go more than twice. - He did.
Why are you trying to...
(What?)
- aggravate us? - Are you really not going?
(His memory is weaker than his acting skills.)
- I'm serious. - You said you can't go again.
- You said you can't go again. - Go ahead.
Why are you going again? He has the door open. Go.
(Gullible Jae Suk takes off again.)
- Stop it. - Why are you doing this?
- Are you not going? - Hey, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
- Move. - What?
(Okay! I fooled Jae Suk.)
But...
- He got tricked. - Sit down.
Just sit.
Sit down. Just sit.
(It sounds like he's acting.)
That makes me actually want to sit.
What was that for?
(Why did you spoil that?)
What's wrong with you?
I was about to go out.
I was about to go, but I sat down because of Suk Jin.
"Just sit."
(He grabbed the empty bottle because he was too flustered.)
He never shares anything good.
I'm relieved. It's not here yet.
(I almost had them.)
"Just sit."
(Teasing)
Focus. Why do you keep going back and forth?
- That's why you're losing coins. - Focus!
(Maybe it's really a good thing this time.)
- That was too obvious. - Sit.
- Are you sure? Okay. - We're not going.
(He goes out for the 3rd time.)
What's going on?
- He's trying to trick us. - It's a race.
(I won't get fooled.)
- It's something good. - He said he can't go out again.
(No.)
(When she said it must be a good thing, )
He would have gone back and forth already then.
(Jae Suk falls for it again.)
- It doesn't make sense. - You can't go more than twice.
Jae Suk is so gullible.
(Gullible)
Do you want to go?
Are you sure about this?
(Jae Suk goes out for the 3rd time.)
I'm not sure.
Move over. I can't resist.
(I am too curious.)
- Throw out one of them. - I can't resist.
Are they both going?
(Kwang Soo came out first.)
Kwang Soo...
Since you didn't focus on filming for the third time,
so you must pay five coins.
So you must pay five coins.
(Kwang Soo slaps him in fury.)
- Does this keep going? - When will you focus?
(For goodness' sake.)
Focus? I'm focusing.
(Are you kidding me?)
I'm focusing on the mission.
(How can you play me 3 times?)
Please focus on the conversation.
(He pays 5 more coins for a total of 15 coins.)
(He looks lonely from the back.)
I couldn't resist.
(2 more guests come.)
Since you didn't focus on filming again, you must pay five coins.
- I thought we'd get something good. - It's not.
(He is in denial.)
Please focus.
(Repeating for the 3rd time)
Why did you push me?
My gosh.
(They take out 5 coins to pay.)
(Dropping)
(A coin drops from Ji Hyo's bag.)
(He picks it up quickly...)
(and pays as if it was his.)
(Thanks, Ji Hyo.)
Why do I only have eight?
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo doesn't have wits too.)
That's weird.
(While Cavewoman Ji Hyo is confused, )
(Jae Suk returns disappointed.)
This time...
Your front teeth are protruded.
(His smile looks stiff.)
- He's dejected. - Let's watch.
He doesn't look happy.
I'll tell you that there aren't that many spots left.
(He lies for the last time.)
I believe that.
(Se Chan gets up.)
Jong Kook, I'll go and decide for myself.
(The food arrived.)
- Our food is here. Let's eat first. - What's that?
(The result of the first Game of Wits)
Let's eat.
(Current Number of Coins)
There must be a mission about food.
(He suspects first.)
That's possible,
(They wouldn't just give us food.)
but what could it be?
Shouldn't we just enjoy our food?
(He feels somewhat suspicious.)
Maybe you're not supposed to talk with food on the table.
(Could it be...)
That's possible. No talking while eating.
No, that's the wrong etiquette.
(The most knowledgable man about politeness says...)
You have to laugh while you eat for good digestion.
(She rationalizes herself.)
- We can enjoy our food, right? - Thank you.
(Let's worry about the mission after the food.)
- Yes. - Really?
- I want to go out so badly. - This grilled hairtail is huge.
(It looks really good.)
It's so good.
(Grilled hairtail is full of meat.)
(Yellow corvina is a perfect dish that goes well with rice.)
It's delicious.
It's good.
- This is delicious. - It's good.
(He eats a piece of yellow corvina, then a spoonful of rice.)
- Thank you. - It's amazing.
It's good.
(It's really good.)
(They forget about the mission and gobble down the food.)
This is good.
It's delicious.
(Slowly)
- Didn't you order grilled fish? - I know.
(Suk Jin.)
Kwang Soo and I ordered the braised fish.
(Don't steal our food.)
Let's share.
Share?
(Ji Suk Jin Dictionary)
What language was that?
(He says "share" when he steals other people's food.)
People who went already are eating quietly.
(She becomes doubtful again.)
I don't know about Jae Suk.
(They are particularly quiet and keep eating food.)
- I'm curious. This drives me nuts. - Me too.
(What's going on?)
I don't think I can digest my food.
(Putting food down on his bowl)
It makes me think.
(What's going on?)
- Ask Ji Hyo. - Should I go?
Listen to her voice. She sounds different.
(Are they showing their affection officially now?)
- That's not right. - That's not right.
(Try this, Se Chan.)
- When she lies, you can tell. - No.
(He rejects her.)
It's nothing.
- I'm just giving it to you. - I don't want it.
(Goodness.)
It's not a mission.
She gave me her yellow corvina. What am I supposed to do?
(He is full of mistrust.)
Do I need to eat it?
(I thought something else for a moment.)
That was great.
(Done with the meal)
- I didn't eat from the bowl. - I'll take it then.
- That was good. - That was delicious.
(He pushes his chair to the back.)
(At that moment, the producer comes up to the door.)
- That was good. - That was sweet.
The hairtail was good.
(I see somebody moving.)
Do you have any white radish left? Can you give me one?
(Jae Suk approaches the door carefully.)
Jae Suk, don't look too serious.
- Come out, Jae Suk. - Why?
(Everyone is flustered.)
- He's calling you. - You finished eating first.
(Why does he want me to come out?)
- Why is he calling you? - You put down your spoon first.
He made eye contact with the producer.
(Guess 1: He made eye contact with the producer.)
Because we can't go out.
(What is it?)
If the person in front of you is still eating,
(Guess 2: He had bad table manners.)
- it's bad table manners to leave. - You know what, Kwang Soo?
He got up.
I understand up to two times.
(There are many speculations as Jae Suk leaves the room.)
Why? I didn't do anything wrong this time.
(Why did he call me?)
- It's not me this time. - Jae Suk.
(After a while)
Can I have some more?
(Jae Suk's expression is hard to tell.)
Sure. The head?
- He looks happy. - My gosh.
(What?)
Jae Suk, you got up when we didn't finish.
(They think he lost more coins.)
Come out, Suk Jin,
(The producer calls Suk Jin too.)
- Sure. - Why?
What's going on?
(What is the mission?)
Do you get more coins if you go out early?
(Maybe)
I think so.
I think you're right.
(He walks to the producer nervously.)
- Suk Jin. - Yes.
(What happened to Suk Jin and Jae Suk?)
Maybe not. I think something happened.
(Looking)
- I think these two are done. - What is it?
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin)
Who?
Come out, Jong Kook.
- Who? - Who was that?
- He called Jong Kook. - Who was that?
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, then Jong Kook)
Jong Kook.
That was so random.
(What did the three do to be called by the producer?)
- Me? - What is it? The water?
He didn't finish his food.
(She suspects everything.)
- He didn't go out. - What is it?
(What could it be?)
Are we not supposed to have leftovers?
(Maybe)
I think so.
(They can't tell from these two's faces.)
(He's very intrigued.)
- Jong Kook. - What is it? Yes.
For a smooth resumption of filming,
three people who finished eating first will receive R coins.
(3 people who finished eating fast will...)
(receive R coins.)
You got third place.
(That's what it was.)
I want a little more.
(They were eating just 5 minutes ago.)
(He's done eating.)
- That was great. - I didn't eat from the bowl.
- Right? - Yes.
(His plate is clean.)
(Jae Suk finished eating first.)
That was delicious.
(After Jae Suk, )
(Suk Jin put down his spoon.)
It's obvious now.
(Jong Kook was next.)
(His plates are clean.)
(They received 10 R coins each!)
- Oh, dear. - 10?
(Meanwhile, members who don't have any clues...)
This is becoming...
- What is it? - Why? Did you lose some?
(are dying of curiosity.)
What did he do again?
He doesn't look happy.
I know. He used his chopsticks incorrectly.
(He makes a bad guess.)
My chopstick skills are by the book.
(That's not it, Se Chan.)
It's by the book. I'm so good.
(His chopstick skills are by the book.)
- You're actually good. - Anyhow.
(They are relaxed because they know what's going on.)
I don't know what it is.
Picky eaters.
Picky eaters?
Was it people who were picky eaters?
(He also makes a bad guess.)
- I ate everything that was here. - Me too.
(Se Chan appeals himself.)
I did.
(Should I tease him a little?)
I'm full.
- I'm full. - I'm full.
I'm full too.
(They are all suddenly playing Race of Wits.)
I don't think this is it.
- What is it? - What is it?
(I am really curious.)
Look at his face.
We can't help it.
(He gets playful.)
It has to do with coins.
They look like people who lost coins.
Can we only go out if we get called?
(Touching)
You ate as much as you wanted to.
(Jae Suk, is this a sign?)
He kicked him.
(Of course, Kwang Soo.)
You can't just go.
(He gets up immediately.)
How many times has he gone out?
(He received Jae Suk's sign, )
(so he excitedly goes to the production crews.)
Why did you come? Your name wasn't called.
- Sorry? - I didn't call you.
Jae Suk sent me a sign.
(Jae Suk gave me a sign.)
No?
He tricked you.
Jae Suk, he asked me why I came when he didn't call me.
(Feeling betrayed)
Why did you send me a sign?
It doesn't work that way.
(It's fun making fun of Kwang Soo.)
I know now. You can't go even if you get called.
(He is still making guesses.)
We're not done eating.
(That's not it.)
I got goosebumps.
Haha. Wasn't that observant?
(Se Chan praises himself.)
- I finished eating. - The person next to you.
(At that moment)
- They're here. - What?
- What's going on? - What's going on?
(Production crews come in after 1 hour.)
- Is it over? - It's over. It's done.
(Is it over?)
Like Se Chan said.
(They misunderstand that crews came because Se Chan guessed right.)
We weren't supposed to go out, right?
What am I supposed to do?
You met up in this restaurant and had breakfast...
(The producer explains the mission.)
while the staff conducted a hidden Game of Wits.
(She is still eating.)
(Ji Hyo is still eating too.)
The first mission was...
to focus on your peers during filming...
(The first mission was to focus on peers and not to leave the room.)
and not to leave the room.
People who left got coins deducted according to the number of times.
(People who left got coins deducted according to the number of times.)
Kwang Soo must be broke.
Did you pay?
- But then... - That's insane.
(Kwang Soo left multiple times to fool his peers, but he is broke.)
He said "this time," so I thought it would be different next time.
- Why did he do that? - That's awful.
- What was the 2nd one? - The 2nd mission was...
(Really curious)
for a smooth resumption of filming,
(The second mission was to give R coins to 3 people...)
three people who finished eating first...
(who finished eating first.)
- All right! - received R coins.
(That's what it was.)
People who finished eating first?
There were also people who finished late and delayed filming.
(There were also people who finished late and delayed filming.)
So Min and Ji Hyo will have to pay five coins each.
(So Min and Ji Hyo have to pay 5 coins each.)
They were slow.
- What's going on? - What's going on?
(While the crew was coming in, )
You met up in this restaurant and had breakfast.
(Ji Hyo and So Min were still eating.)
Why did you eat so slowly?
I always eat slow.
(They delayed filming.)
- I eat slow. - They were nibbling on their food.
There were hints in this room regarding the missions.
(There were hints on the mission in the room.)
- Here? - Where?
There were inside napkins and so on, but we'll tell you later.
- We used all the napkins. - Really?
(What?)
I have the napkins.
Why do you have them?
(She monopolized napkins.)
There's something written here.
What does it say?
"Within this hour, it's more beneficial for you..."
- "if other members leave." - I see it.
Is it written on it?
- They printed this on the napkins? - Nobody looked.
(Unbelievable)
- You should've shared these. - Seriously?
(Ji Hyo. Don't keep the napkins all to yourself.)
I took them because I have a runny nose.
I was told to come on an empty stomach.
(Haha was the first to arrive.)
Gosh, I'm starving. Why is this here?
(He pushed the napkins away that contained clues.)
- Gosh, I'm hungry. - There isn't much.
Here's the food. Let's eat first.
(Ji Hyo took the napkins that Haha pushed away.)
What we take is ours, right?
(She wiped her nose with the clues.)
(Then she kept them all to herself.)
Yes.
- But... - We need to inspect our pockets.
(After the shoot)
- The napkins... - She took them all.
She stashed them for herself.
(The clue is gone with her snot.)
We should check our pockets from now on.
- The napkins... - On the napkins?
(The hint was on the napkin.)
- Unbelievable. - Just like you experienced,
(As they notice from 2 Games of Wits, )
you will be rewarded today depending on how witty you are.
(they'll get more coins depending on how witty they are.)
The race is called Hey, You Can Find Out Too!
(Hey, You Can Find Out Too!)
The missions will pop up randomly.
(The missions will pop up randomly.)
Depending on your actions, you will either lose or gain coins.
(Depending on their actions, they will either lose or gain coins.)
The two with the most amount of coins...
(The 2 with the most amount of coins...)
(will be given a chance to pick an ungraded prize.)
will be given a chance to pick an ungraded prize.
An upgraded prize?
(They feel competitive for the upgraded prize.)
You'll now change outfits and then head to the next location.
(They head to the next location.)
- Got it. - Sure thing.
Let's get on the bus.
(They gathered in front of the bus to move.)
- Understand? - Many were tested.
- Yes. - What a twist.
- Hold on. - Don't you agree?
(What's this?)
What's this?
(Who's waiting for the members?)
(Assistant Director Son is holding up his hand.)
(What would you do if you saw him?)
(His hands have been sanitized.)
(Kwang Soo runs forward...)
(and slaps his hand.)
- Wait. - What's this?
(Jae Suk was going to pass him.)
I think we need to high-five him.
(Slap)
Hold on.
I think we need to high-five him.
(Haha slaps his hand.)
I walked right past him.
- I was first. - I was third.
(Se Chan slaps his hand.)
- I walked right past him. - I was first.
(Whatever the mission is)
I was second.
(Does the order matter?)
(Suk Jin also slaps his hand.)
Just get on the bus.
(Hyun Hee gives him a hug.)
(Goodness.)
Wait, what now?
(Peck)
(Hyun Hee slaps his hand after taking other actions.)
(Ji Min gives him a hug but doesn't slap his hand.)
Shouldn't we bump his hand with our elbow?
(Ji Hyo bumps her elbow.)
- Really? - Of course not.
(So Min lets out scissors.)
(It could be a game of rock-paper-scissors.)
Just get on the bus.
(She then slaps his hand.)
(And then she hugs him.)
Have you been here all this time?
This seems like another hidden mission.
(What on earth is this?)
Everything feels like a mission.
(What kind of mission is this?)
I swear!
(Was he in the Boy Scouts?)
Okay.
(Jong Kook gets on the bus without slapping his hand.)
Please buckle in. Actually, this bus seems new.
This seems like another hidden mission.
(What was the mission?)
I think I was able to get it right.
I think he's about to tell us.
(Finally)
- The high-five... - Is that what we should've done?
(Assistant Director's mission will now be revealed.)
No, you shouldn't have.
- I was first. - You see...
Let me reveal the result of the third Game of Wits.
- Was there another one? - We shouldn't have done anything.
(Curious)
Some of you high-fived Assistant Director Son.
(People who high-fived Assistant Director before getting on the bus)
- That's right. - I wasn't going to,
(They're Jae Suk, Kwang Soo, Se Chan, Haha, Suk Jin, )
but Kwang Soo made me question my decision.
- It could be a good thing. - I shouldn't have.
(Hyun Hee, and So Min.)
Ji Min, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo didn't slap his hand.
(Ji Min, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo didn't high-five him.)
We value how you didn't kiss up to the staff...
and that wins you two R coins each.
- What? - Nice!
(They get 2 coins each for not kissing up to the production crew.)
Okay!
(Honest to a fault)
Are you kidding me?
How is a high-five considered as kissing up to someone?
(He can't believe it.)
(Kwang Soo ran over even with his injured leg.)
(The other 7 members kissed up to the production crew.)
We're friends, so a high-five meant nothing!
(Flatterer)
I can't believe you'd put it that way.
(How could you call that kissing up?)
We didn't give him a high-five to kiss up to him.
(Flatterers explode.)
I only high-fived him so that he wouldn't feel awkward.
So everything is linked to a mission.
(He finally understands the rule.)
You can't keep punishing those who are willing to take action.
(Jae Suk thinks it's unfair.)
I hate how you put it as "kissing up" to him.
- Exactly. - That's hardly the case.
- He's right. - Besides,
(Soo Yong is the youngest director.)
why would we kiss up to Soo Yong?
- Tell me about it. - Why would we?
(He suffers a loss for some reason.)
Anyway, you shouldn't do anything that has nothing to do...
(By the way, the bus won't move.)
with the show.
- Okay. - I hope we get going.
Let's go!
- There's more. - We commend...
Se Chan's active participation of yelling "Let's go"...
and reward him with five R coins.
We reward him with five R coins.
(Se Chan receives 5 R coins.)
(He's very enthusiastic.)
- What on earth? - Let's go!
Nice!
(He gets 5 coins for saying "Let's go"?)
- Are you kidding me? - Five coins?
- Five coins? - This is too random!
(Glowing)
- Let's go. - Let's begin filming!
(He becomes enthusiastic.)
- You're too late. - We're already filming,
- so why would you say that? - We're already filming.
Sir, please drive safely.
(She enthusiastically encourages the driver.)
That's you kissing up to him.
The director is...
(He doesn't trust the producer.)
giving out random missions whenever he feels like it.
- That's not the case. - The rules are set.
(Game of Wits is already set.)
We already set the rules and have filmed that separately.
They're not random.
(Kissing up)
There's no way he'd do things on the fly.
- Unbelievable. - Be wittier, Kwang Soo.
(Showing off)
- My gosh. - So now...
Se Chan, for some reason, you look like a sardine today.
(In a bad mood)
A sardine? What's that?
(They somewhat look alike.)
- Don't you know what it is? - Isn't that bait?
- Sardines. - The kind that you pickle?
Don't you know what is it? It's the fish you feed dolphins.
(We use sardine to catch big fish.)
- As bait. - Bait?
No, it's food.
- It's bait used to catch big fish. - Yes, it's used as bait.
(They keep talking about the same thing over sardine.)
But still...
(He suddenly bursts into laughter.)
- What's going on? - I'm actively reacting.
(He's actively reacting in case it's a mission.)
I doubt that's one of the missions.
You never know. It could've been.
(He desperately tries to win R coins.)
You never know, right?
Gosh, what a bummer.
(This is how dangerous R coins are.)
My gosh.
I'd like to receive some R coins.
There's no way to know what the missions are.
- I'm completely broke. - I don't have many either.
Ji Hyo, are you broke?
Yes.
Then forfeit the game.
Jae Suk, don't be ridiculous.
(The harmful effect of R coins)
Unbelievable.
You guys...
Look at you all trying to win R coins.
(A moment ago, they were upset by the word "kissing up".)
What I said made sure...
(They're trying desperately...)
(to win the production crew's love for R coins.)
that Ji Hyo and I didn't get edited out.
(Too many explanations)
Also, did you check out my reaction?
- Isn't that worth R coins? - You did well.
(That's his purpose.)
- There you go. - He commended you.
(He gets a compliment instead of an R coin.)
- Congratulations. - Just a compliment?
- Good job. - It's as if he's teasing us.
(He's an active flatterer.)
How do we get him to pay us R coins?
(Curious)
(What do we do to get R coins?)
- Why would you put it like that? - We're not in Sangam-dong yet.
(The next place is SBS in Sangam-dong.)
We're going somewhere else. Something must be up.
(It looks like they're going somewhere else.)
Get ready for the next mission.
Sir, we're not in Sangam-dong!
(He's enthusiastic.)
You're going the wrong way.
(They share opinions actively for R coins.)
- Unbelievable. - I know what it is.
We're taking the wrong path.
Let's not be silly.
- What was that? - What did you say?
(What did he just say?)
- Wasn't that it? - Kwang Soo...
(He sounded like a translation device.)
You sounded like a translation device.
I'll drive!
(Jong Kook joins.)
- We're all taking action. - I'll drive.
It's all right, sir. Drive as safely as you want.
(They've never been this proactive before.)
- It's all right. - It's all right.
(Running Man has changed thanks to R coins.)
- Go, sir! - It's all right.
- This is great. - Everyone makes mistakes.
Why don't we sing songs just like we do on picnics?
(She makes a proactive suggestion.)
Cherry blossoms fly
(In the spring breeze)
In the spring breeze
(They sing along in hopes of winning R coins.)
The song is sung on the streets
(Jong Kook is the most proactive.)
And the two of us walk along it
(The R Coin Effect)
- It is spring for sure. - It's nice to be with you all.
(Before they're over the song about spring...)
Can we hear Yu San Seul's song?
(Hyun Hee makes a request.)
And the two of us
(All of it)
- Hold on. - Just redevelop it
(Just redevelop it)
I bet this isn't just for the R coins.
(The R coins bring out their party DNA.)
- From head to toe - Any more requests?
We're all doing our best to earn a few coins.
I mean, just take a look at Jong Kook!
(Jong Kook has changed.)
- He's on a roll. - What's gotten into him?
(The R Coin Effect continues.)
You'll be mine, my love is only for you
- What's next? - I'm happier
(He was furious about being told that he kissed up to someone.)
Suk Jin makes it sound like an oldie though.
(Suk Jin makes it sound like an oldie though.)
- You're mine, ha! - You're mine, ha!
(You're mine, ha!)
- Gosh. - It sounds so old-fashioned.
(What Game of Wits is waiting for them next?)
I love it when songs are changed up that way.
We'll soon arrive at the broadcasting station.
(They're about to arrive at the next mission place.)
We're almost there.
Where are we heading then?
- So we're almost there. - We have arrived!
(Is this it?)
You will get off the bus with the person you trust the most.
(That's not it.)
- Please team up. - A team of two?
(The person I trust the most?)
- Yes, a team of two. - So Min,
Kwang Soo, and...
(People have no trust in those 3.)
- Jae Suk too. - Yes, him.
- You included. - As you know, I'm trustworthy.
(It's not easy to pick the most reliable person.)
Ji Min, how would you describe yourself?
I'm quite witty.
(Appealing)
- Then I choose Ji Min. - Sure.
(Haha picks Ji Min.)
How about we team up?
- Jong Kook, what do you say? - Ji Min and I.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan will partner up.)
- I'd love to team up with Se Chan. - I choose Jong Kook too.
Of course, I'd choose my comfort doll.
I'll team up with whoever wants me.
- And I... - Me!
(Hyun Hee picks him.)
I...
(She volunteers to partner up with Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo... - I promise.
- Should I take it back? - You'll be with Kwang Soo?
(Kwang Soo's flustered.)
Yes, Kwang Soo.
(She trusts me?)
Gosh, I'm grateful.
I'm teaming up with Ji Min.
(Ji Hyo picks Suk Jin.)
- Suk Jin, you and me? - Sure thing.
I'll team up with Ji Hyo.
- I... - Who else?
Your name hasn't come up yet, so stay put.
- Jae Suk... - Jae Suk,
I'll team up with you for one R coin.
I have no intention of doing that.
(Don't be ridiculous.)
Let's hurry then.
Jong Kook and Se Chan can leave first.
(While they're taking too long to choose a partner, )
(Jong Kook and Se Chan leave first.)
All right. Get ready for Kook and Chan.
Kook and Chan, here we come!
(What kind of mission awaits them?)
Kook and Chan!
(SBS Prism Tower, Sangam-dong)
They're filming from a distance, so let's say hello.
(They say hello to the camera politely.)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Among the flowers - Among the flowers
- I smell the scent of your shampoo - I smell the scent of your shampoo
(Their energy runs too high because of today's mission.)
There's another camera filming from afar.
I wonder what they have in store for us.
(Are you listening, production crew?)
- I'm curious. - I'm excited.
- My heart's pounding. - Mine too.
(Kook and Chan couldn't be more excited.)
I wonder what game we'll be playing.
- I'd love to get to work. - Where are we headed?
(They try to figure out what the mission is.)
I can't wait to start filming.
I can't wait.
Third floor. Here we are.
(They arrive at the studio on the 3rd floor.)
- Where are we supposed to go? - This way. What now?
(There must be a mission here.)
- We need to start filming already. - I know.
I wonder what's going on. Don't forget the hand sanitizer.
- Once more? - Of course.
(Is using the hand sanitizer their mission?)
(They enter the studio without anything in particular.)
- Does it work? - Yes, a lot comes out.
Okay. Let's go.
- Se Chan. - What is it?
- I see R coins. - What?
(R coins are dropped on the floor.)
(The location of R coins looks too suspicious to pass them.)
- Didn't you see it? - I didn't.
- This... - Hold on.
(This must be a mission!)
- Se Chan. - I didn't see it.
(What do we do about it?)
Are we supposed to split these? Say we're filming.
These are props used by our show only.
- Let's say someone dropped them. - Right.
(The production crew dropped the item by mistake.)
- So taking them... - Okay.
(So taking them would be a bad move.)
would be a bad move.
- Still... - Yes?
They could be here...
(R coins could be there for them to take.)
for us to take though.
As a reward for paying attention?
(Maybe Se Chan is right.)
There is more than one coin, right?
So if we split them...
(Shall we split them?)
- No, wait. - We shouldn't take them?
To me,
these look like...
they were dropped.
Someone dropped them by mistake?
It doesn't say anywhere that we should take them.
- Right. - We shouldn't do anything...
(We shouldn't do anything...)
that the staff doesn't want us to do.
(that the production crew didn't tell us to do.)
You're right.
- What do you say? - You're right today.
(Persuaded)
What Director Choi...
(Jong Kook is aware of the production crew.)
doesn't tell us to do...
Why are you brimming with energy today?
- We shouldn't take them. - Right.
We came here to shoot, and they said, "Please go up."
(They start role-playing to make the final decision.)
So we came up here. Wait.
There are coins on the floor. Is there anything written here?
(Looking around)
Did our producer leave a note? No.
- Should we just go? - We should leave them here.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They just go as the production crews aren't ordering anything.)
I think you got it perfectly right.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan enter without touching the coin.)
All right.
(Confident)
- Here come good citizens. - Yes.
- Only do what you're told to do. - We're good citizens.
(Good Jong Kook and Se Chan's turn ends.)
- Jong Kook to the Assembly! - Yes!
Don't stab me in the back.
(Suk Jin and Jae Suk follow.)
No way.
Don't stab me in the back, seriously.
You can't stab me in the back,
but I can stab you in the back, so be careful.
You know I'm smart, right?
(The smart boy and the old boy enter the hallway.)
Right?
I'm pretty smart.
Don't even think of stabbing me in the back.
(Welcome)
- These days... - What's that?
- What is it? - Oh, my.
(Whatever it is, I'll pick it up.)
- What's that? - Unbelievable.
(The old boy takes the coin without hesitation.)
What's that?
(Why would there be R coins?)
I can't believe this.
(Suk Jin sounds excited.)
We're not supposed to take it, are we?
(But...)
- We should just leave it here. - Right?
(They're quite timid compared to their greed.)
You shouldn't take something that doesn't belong to you.
- I shouldn't... - It doesn't belong to you.
- I don't think I should take this. - No.
(I shouldn't take them, right?)
Right?
I don't believe in...
- unexpected good luck. - But...
I don't know what to do.
I'm slow-witted.
I hate these things.
(They don't feel like leaving it either.)
It bothers me.
- There are 30 coins. - Gosh.
With these, you'll move up to the first place.
(With these coins...)
- Let's split them 50-50. - Okay.
It's no big deal if they take them away.
(They fail to let go of their greed.)
- Hi. - Hi.
Did you take something that isn't yours or not?
- Who says it's not ours? - Who knows if it's just good luck?
(Honorable)
Who knows if it's unexpected good luck?
The staff...
(The two teams have completely different tendencies.)
- never told us to take them. - It shows your personality.
We should trust each other.
(The third team is Haha and Ji Min.)
Why would we not trust each other?
- Right? Always trust each other. - Definitely.
(We'll trust each other.)
Can I...
(Haha steps on the coins.)
(Haha finally notices the coins.)
Gosh, that's bad luck. You dropped your coins?
(Ji Min thinks Haha dropped his coins.)
Gosh, why did I drop them?
What happened?
(Smiling)
(Haha pretends the coins belong to him.)
You and... Who is it?
- Ji Min? What did you do? - What did you do?
(Taken aback)
- What do you mean? - What did you do?
Did you find anything on the floor?
(Be quiet.)
- Did you find them? - What did you do?
- We know you did. - We know you did.
(Please be quiet, guys.)
We all found them.
Ji Min, did you pick anything up from the floor?
Did you pick?
- I didn't... - What happened?
(What happened between these two?)
You took them without telling Ji Min?
I thought they dropped from your bag.
(Insisting)
They did.
- Gosh. - Unbelievable.
- You're so mean. - I...
(The good citizen has never imagined this scenario.)
- They dropped from my bag. - We're supposed to take them.
(Now that I think about it...)
They told us to team up with a trustworthy person.
- We're supposed to take them. - That makes sense.
(They think it was right to take the coins because of Haha.)
- Even if you pick them up first... - Even if you pick them up first...
(I'm sorry, Ji Min.)
I mean...
They dropped from my bag.
(Ji Min is betrayed by her partner.)
(The fourth team appears while talking about trust.)
- Trust me. - Hey.
So Min, you have to trust me today.
- We have to trust each other. - Okay.
- Wait. What is that? - What is that?
(A bag of coins appears in their way.)
Well...
I guess they're for us.
(Naive)
- They're for us? - Yes.
We're probably doing something with these.
It's a test.
Let's return them to the staff.
They were on the floor.
- They don't belong to us. - We should return them.
(It seems that we should return them to the production crew.)
- Let's find out who they belong to. - We should do the right thing.
(In the empty hallway, )
We want to find out who these belong to.
(they look for the owner of the coins.)
- Why is no one answering? - But there are so many.
(Ji Hyo.)
Should we take just one?
Hey, you shouldn't do this.
They won't even be able to tell. Let's just take one each.
Hey, we shouldn't do this.
- There are so many. - No way.
(She gets a bit greedy.)
- You're being ridiculous. - You don't have so many coins.
- How many do you have? - Still, we shouldn't take these.
(Their opinions are divided over one coin.)
I know that, but...
- no one will know if we take one. - We can't.
(Stubborn)
You're being dishonest.
It won't even show.
(Greedy)
What are you talking about?
Let's just count how many there are.
I knew it.
- Let's just count them. - You want to take them, don't you?
- You want to. Be honest. - I'm just counting them.
(She can't deny it.)
So Min is persuading Ji Hyo.
(I can hear everything.)
She's persuading Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is getting sneaky these days too.
- Don't take anything secretly. - I won't.
(They've been arguing for over 5 minutes.)
Don't take anything.
I'm good at these tests.
(They decide to return them in the end.)
I never cheat on tests.
(Unlike her words, she keeps touching the coins.)
We just found them on the floor.
(I want to take just 1.)
They don't belong to us.
We should go in here.
- They're finally here. - Those two...
(There they come.)
We decided to return these to the staff.
- Yes, we're returning them. - We just picked them up.
We're returning these.
(They return the bag of coins to the production crew.)
- You're returning them? - Yes, we'd like to return them.
(The last pair appears.)
Why is no one here?
For this game, we have to trust each other.
(We'll trust each other no matter what.)
- We should rely on each other... - Exactly.
(Of course.)
and help each other out.
(As soon as he sees the coins, )
(he picks them up and runs away.)
(3 seconds ago, they were talking about trust.)
We should trust...
(This is ridiculous.)
(When Hyun Hee picked Kwang Soo, )
Give them to me.
(everyone expected this to happen.)
- Wait. - It's started.
Seriously.
(What are they doing?)
- He took everything? - Is this a comedy show?
- He took everything. - Give them to me.
(Kwang Soo loses control again.)
Good.
Did you two fight?
- Yes, a little. - Did you pick those up?
(Feeling better)
You said we're a team.
(This is absurd.)
We are.
(Kwang Soo takes all 30 of them, )
What's going on?
(and the result of the mission is revealed.)
- On your way here, - Yes.
- did you all see the coins? - Yes.
This mission was about...
(Fourth Game of Wits)
sharing happiness together without suspecting each other.
(Sharing happiness together without suspecting each other)
- Okay. - You can keep the coins.
(They may keep their coins.)
- Okay! - Okay!
The one who took the coins...
- "Okay"? - Don't worry.
(I'll give you some.)
What are you talking about? Give them to me right now.
Seriously, don't worry.
I mean...
If you pick up something on the street,
you're supposed to return it to its owner.
We returned them to you. Shouldn't we get at least one?
(The good citizens think it's unfair.)
You're too nice.
At least show me. I didn't even see them.
At least show me.
(At least show me those coins.)
I'm glad I didn't pick Kwang Soo or Haha.
(Fine.)
Gosh, we're a team.
(Hyun Hee and Kwang Soo finish the game...)
(looking silly.)
Should I carry them for you?
You can win more R coins in this mission.
(They'll move on to the next mission while keeping the coins.)
- It's called Break the Basket. - What's that?
(Hey, You Can Find Out Too! The first mission, Break the Basket)
The winning team can win R coins...
from the box of wits.
(The winning team can win R coins from the box of wits...)
(after every mission.)
(One member of each team will be seated under the basket.)
One member of each team...
will sit under the team's basket.
Two members of each team will put on gloves and put a gym ball...
(The other two members will wear gloves and gym balls.)
under their shirts and deliver bean pouches...
(The two will deliver the bean pouches, )
to the members under the baskets.
They can push others outside the lines with their bellies.
(and they can push others outside the lines.)
(When one is pushed out, one must stop for 10 seconds.)
When you're pushed out, you have to pause for 10 seconds.
Each basket contains 100 ping pong balls,
(Ping pong balls will fall as the basket opens.)
which will be exchanged with coins.
The number of the ping pong balls you catch from the basket...
(They'll open the boxes of wits to the amount...)
plus 25 will be the number of coins you can receive.
(of the ping pong balls they get plus 25.)
(They divide into teams.)
Divide into teams.
(Team White: Ji Min, Jae Suk, Haha, So Min, and Se Chan)
(Team Blue: Hyun Hee, Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo)
Are you allowed to punch others?
(Haha, Se Chan, and Jae Suk versus Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, and Suk Jin)
He's intimidating us.
(Do you have a problem?)
He's glaring at us.
Se Chan, you can beat Jong Kook.
(He has no chance.)
I like it.
(He's reliable.)
- Go! - Let's start.
(The game finally begins.)
- Let's do this! - Let's do this!
(Go and get a lot of coins.)
- You can do this! - Ready.
- You can do this! - Knock him down.
(Break the Basket starts.)
They're targeting you.
- No! - It hurts.
(Jong Kook pushes 2 people at once.)
(Se Chan picks up a handful of bean pouches.)
Push Suk Jin!
- What are you doing? - What's going on?
Get the bean pouches!
(Se Chan tries to deliver bean pouches to Haha.)
- Gosh. - Oh, no.
(He gets blocked by Jong Kook.)
Get the bean pouches!
I can't pick them up.
(All you have to do is toss the bean pouches.)
(But it turns into wrestling.)
Wait. I have to toss it like this?
- Like this? - Hurry up.
(Is this supposed to be played this way?)
- Suk Jin, bring me bean pouches! - No!
(Suk Jin, you have to deliver them!)
Jong Kook has to defend.
Why can't I pick them up?
Suk Jin!
(Frustrated)
Either defend or bring me bean pouches!
- Come on! - Push him out!
(He gets pushed out...)
- Hey! - He's out.
(without doing anything.)
- Come on! - Push him out!
- Suk Jin is out! - Now!
(Frustrated)
(They're staying outside longer than they're playing.)
Goodness, Suk Jin!
Why are you on our team?
(In the end, Jong Kook uses force.)
Se Chan is out. Let's finish him off.
(With Suk Jin out, Jong Kook successfully delivers bean pouches.)
One more time!
Aim higher, Kwang Soo!
(But...)
(he misses the basket.)
(Team Jong Kook's hope is thrown away.)
(Kwang Soo turns out to be a bigger problem than Suk Jin.)
Way to go!
I figured it out.
(Even though Haha doesn't have many bean pouches, )
(he hits the basket every time.)
- Hang in there! - Haha.
(Dream's father meets a game that he's good at.)
You're almost there.
(All his 3 bean pouches hit the basket.)
You're almost there. Keep going.
- It's starting to break. - It's breaking.
(Wait!)
(The basket finally breaks.)
(His team can win as many coins as the ping pong balls he catches.)
The number of ping pong balls you catch with the basket...
will be the number of coins you receive.
(How many ping pong balls will Haha catch?)
- Gosh. - Oh, no.
(Clumsy)
- Okay! - Haha!
(What is he doing?)
- What did you do? - You should have caught them.
(How many did you get?)
- How many did you catch? - You should have caught them!
What did you do?
What's with you?
(He only got 6 ping pong balls.)
I mean...
I was so focused on breaking the basket.
(Embarrassed)
(It's only the first box of wits.)
The losing team also has a chance to win coins.
(The losing team still has a chance.)
What's that?
- What's that? - Is it like drawing lots?
(6 boxes of wits are brought in.)
We get to select a number.
- "Take coins from the other team"? - Yes!
(What is this?)
The rules are simple.
(Box of wits with opportunities to gain R coins)
The losing team will distribute the balls the winning team caught...
(The losing team will distribute the ping pong balls...)
(of the winning team in the boxes of wits from number 1 to 6.)
among the six boxes of wits in secret.
Each member of the winning team will choose a box...
(The 5 members of the winning team will choose a box to earn coins.)
and get to keep the coins in the box.
(The last remaining box will be given to the losing team.)
The coins in the remaining box will go to the losing team.
Okay.
There are 31 ping pong balls in total.
(If they distribute them well, they still have a chance.)
The losing team will distribute them now. Please turn around.
- Okay. - Turn around. Go away.
(They need to put at least one in each box.)
Put at least one ball in each box.
- Put 1 ball in each box first. - Put 1 in each.
Put one in each.
(They put one ping pong ball in each box.)
- Do it quietly. - You can't hear anything.
- Suk Jin, I'd like to ask a favor. - Keep calm.
(Earnest)
- Please don't say anything. - Right.
- Don't even touch the balls. - I can't say anything?
(It's bad luck.)
I can't say anything?
- Don't say anything. - When they choose boxes,
(Also earnest)
can you step out for a moment?
- Please. - I can't do that.
(Refusing)
How about putting all of them in one box?
(Suk Jin suggests.)
- Seriously? - In one box?
- Should we... - Or in two boxes?
(Or...)
- Let's put them in two boxes. - That'd be better.
(How will the losing team distribute the ping pong balls?)
Or one?
You didn't put all of them in one box, did you?
(Sounding out)
- What? - We can't tell you.
(Startled)
- I think they did. - You put all of them in one box?
(I think they put all of them in one box.)
- Each box has at least one ball. - I know.
- The rest would be in one box. - Exactly.
(The winning team guesses they're all in one box.)
- We didn't discriminate. - One box has all the balls.
If you look inside, you will suffer dismemberment.
- Let me... What? - What? Dismemberment?
(They can't believe what they just heard.)
Do you even know what dismemberment means?
Isn't it some kind of harassment?
(He has no idea.)
Suk Jin.
- It involves cutting off the limbs. - It involves cutting off the limbs.
(Horrific)
- Is it that bad? - Yes.
(He apologizes immediately.)
- I was so startled. - Your limbs get pulled off.
(Dismemberment is a penalty to cut off a criminal's limbs.)
It was a punishment for treason back in the days.
I lack the vocabulary.
(Let's move on.)
I choose...
number two.
(Se Chan chooses number 2.)
Number two. Please pick a box each.
(Controlling her facial expression)
I need to figure out what they are thinking.
I bet...
(He pretends to be sharp.)
Jong Kook made the decision.
I bet the four of them blindly followed his decision.
(Everyone must've followed Jong Kook's opinion.)
How did you know? Did you take a peek?
(I'm shocked.)
- All right. - Did you hear us talk?
(It's as if Jae Suk took part in the team discussion.)
All right. I choose number five.
(Jae Suk chooses number 5.)
I choose number five.
- Haha. - Number four.
(Haha chooses number 4.)
I choose number six.
(So Min chooses number 6.)
Number 6? Then you are number 1.
(Ji Min chooses number 1.)
I don't have a choice.
(Was their poker face strategy successful?)
- Open the boxes from number one. - Shall we do that?
- Number one. - Yes.
(They first start with Ji Min.)
(She opens the box first.)
1, 2, 3.
(How many balls are inside?)
How many balls are there?
There are a lot.
- How many balls are there? - There are a lot.
(Full of balls)
- Are there many? - 5, 6, 7, 8,
(We are in trouble.)
- 9, 10, 11. - There are many.
They put all the balls in there.
(11 balls are in box number 1.)
Yes. They put all the balls in there.
- Number 2. - Number 2.
(Se Chan chose number 2.)
(He opens his box.)
There is one.
(Disappointed)
Did they put all the balls in the middle box?
(Jae Suk chose number 5.)
Number five.
(He opens the box.)
(It's a jackpot.)
- There are a lot. - Number five has a lot.
(Satisfied)
- How many balls are there? - In my box?
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
(There are 16 balls in box number 5.)
- 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16. - There are a lot.
- 15, 16. - We will check.
(So Min chose number 6.)
You got a lot of balls.
- I got 1 ball. - Shall we open number 3?
(There's only one.)
Number 3 has 1 ball.
(1 ball that was in box number 3 goes to the other team.)
Okay.
We should have put the balls in different boxes.
(That was close.)
I suggested the boxes in the middle.
I told you that we should choose boxes number 3 and 4.
Why didn't they choose the middle one?
(The remaining ball)
Who will take the ball in box number three?
(Kwang Soo's arm is in box number 3.)
Kwang Soo is taking the ball.
Suk Jin should have it.
(What is Ji Hyo doing?)
(He is a little too late.)
The ball in box number three is ours, right?
It's yours.
(Meanwhile, he doesn't have a clue.)
Where did it go?
- Ji Hyo has it. - Here. Play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Who doesn't have a ball? - Just take it. It's only one.
(The real ball...)
- Okay. - What are you doing?
(Please change.)
Change it.
He is asking the staff to change it to an R coin.
(You are amazing.)
Ji Hyo.
(He slyly finishes the deal.)
I am sorry, but he already made the exchange.
- What? When? - I am sorry.
I am sorry,
but Ji Hyo stole my ball.
(A robbery report)
(Me?)
She put her hand inside and took a ball.
Is it yours?
Did Kwang Soo take the ball?
(Ji Hyo took Haha's ball thinking that it belonged to her team.)
Ji Hyo must have thought it was ours.
This is mine.
(Thank you.)
Give me the R coin.
How could you allow this?
(Dumbfounded)
- Didn't you give her the ball? - Why would I do that?
(Come on!)
She took my ball.
Would it be okay if I take other people's ball?
Put it back.
(Sensitive)
Jae Suk must be in the first place.
(He checks until the last minute.)
I am not in the first place yet.
Race of Wits. One.
- 2. - 2.
(What is going on?)
Three.
The 2 of you should pay up 2 coins each.
What is your problem?
(2. Randomly start Race of Wits. Those who say the same number...)
Are you keep going to stress us out this way?
Why did you yell "Two"?
(will need to pay 2 coins, those who say the last number pay 2 coins.)
Why did you?
I wanted to win coins.
(Haha and Se Chan will have to pay 2 coins.)
- I did it without thinking. - I wanted to win coins.
- Let's play it one more time. - Does it count...
(As long as it's not me.)
as a game?
(Flustered)
- I am annoyed it's in the script. - I know.
(The day will end while everyone is trying to read others.)
Is it really in the script?
We will now play a game that is popular...
among university students.
(Hey, You Can Find Out Too! Projector Game)
It's the Projector Game.
What is that?
You make the shape of the projector...
(Make the shape of the projector with your arms first.)
- with your arms first. - Okay.
(Then pick a person by reciting a movie title.)
Then you pick a person.
"Jae Suk, 'The Face Reader'." Then in five seconds,
(The person must say a line or a scene from that movie...)
Jae Suk needs to say a line or act out a scene.
(within 5 seconds.)
- "Do I have the face of a king?" - That's right.
- Projector. - Projector.
(That's why it's a projector.)
- Yes. - Projector.
Who wants to go first?
(Suk Jin...)
- Should I go first? - Yes.
(will start the game.)
All right. Let's begin.
- Projector - Projector
Se Chan, "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial".
(The signature pose of E.T.)
- Projector - Projector
Suk Jin, I can't believe you.
(E.T is a very old movie.)
Why did you start the game with "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"?
- What? - Seriously.
(Suk Jin...)
Why do you keep making the game so boring?
- What? - It's an ancient movie.
(It's a movie from 40 years ago.)
I gave him the hard one.
"E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial" was too much.
- Projector - Projector
(They resume the game in a younger spirit.)
- Did this count as an answer? - Projector
Jae Suk, "RoboCop".
(Is it "RoboCop" this time?)
"RoboCop" came out ages ago.
- Don't you know any modern movies? - It's an ancient movie.
("RoboCop" is from 1987.)
Name a modern movie.
"RoboCop" is an easy one.
(Isn't "RoboCop" relatively new?)
This is getting boring. Let me start first.
- Which movie isn't boring? - I knew the answer,
(That is really old.)
but I didn't want to do this.
- This is so frustrating. - I can't think of anything.
(They change the member and resume the game.)
Let's begin.
- Projector - Projector
Se Chan, "Veteran".
- "This is unbelievable." - That's right.
- Projector - Projector
Haha, "Exit".
(You can imitate a motion in the movie.)
- That's good. - That's good.
- That's good. - Projector
- Projector - Projector
Se Chan, "Extreme Job".
"Why is the business going so well?"
(Se Chan is good.)
- Projector - Projector
Suk Jin, "Young Gu and Daeng Chil".
(Suk Jin knows the old works the best.)
- Projector - Projector
So Min, "The Wailing".
"What's the most important?"
- Projector - Projector
Ji Min, "A Violent Prosecutor".
"I..."
She watched the movie. It's in the movie.
- "The accused..." - That's right.
"Your Honor."
(She guesses it right by reciting plausible lines.)
That's right. That's right.
- Projector - Projector
Jae Suk, "Joker".
(What?)
What is that?
(It looks more like the Korean mask dance.)
- That wasn't "Joker." - That was an executioner.
- That was an executioner. - What was that?
(That's not "Joker".)
All right. All right.
(Even I know that.)
- I will pay up. - An executioner!
- I will pay up. - I haven't watched the movie.
(Jae Suk pays 3 coins.)
Okay.
- I should have a movie in mind. - Let's go. Let's begin.
- Projector - Projector
Hyun Hee, "Alien".
(Growling)
That has to be correct.
- Correct. - That has to be correct.
Correct.
(That was perfect.)
- Projector - Projector
Ji Hyo, "Miracle in Cell No. Seven".
(It isn't a difficult one.)
This one is really easy. I gave you an easy one.
(A hint)
Think of the daughter's name.
- I didn't watch the movie. - What?
- 10 million people watched it. - 10 million people.
(It's the movie chosen by 10 million people.)
- "I didn't watch the movie." - What do you do for fun?
(She continues to isolate herself from the world.)
Ji Hyo, pay up.
Every Korean watched that movie.
(They resume the game after Cavewoman Ji Hyo pays 3 coins.)
Ji Hyo, pay up.
Let's begin.
- Projector - Projector
- Jae Suk, "Train to Busan". - "Train to Busan".
(Groaning)
My goodness.
(That was a good performance.)
- Good job. Good job. - That was perfect.
- Projector - Projector
Suk Jin, "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial".
- What is he doing? - "E.T."
He sounds perfect. That's the sound of E.T.
(He is best suited for movies from the 70s to 80s.)
He is a fossil.
- Projector - Projector
Hyun Hee, "Armageddon".
(Screeching)
(Screeching again)
- What are you doing? - Incorrect.
(Is this not it?)
She is on some kind of a planet.
(Is that "Alien"?)
- There aren't aliens. - There aren't monsters.
There aren't aliens in "Armageddon".
- There aren't aliens. - It's a Bruce Willis movie.
("Armageddon" is a movie about preventing a small asteroid...)
- Really? - Yes.
(colliding against the Earth. There are no aliens.)
- It's about saving the earth. - I didn't watch it.
I didn't watch the movie.
(Hyun Hee pays 3 coins.)
Let's keep going.
- Projector - Projector
Suk Jin, "Riverbank Legends".
What?
"I went to great lengths to build this riverbank."
- Suk Jin. - It's "Riverbank Legends".
("Riverbank Legends"...)
- It's not that kind of a movie. - It's "Riverbank Legends".
"Legends", not "Construction".
(became "Riverbank Construction".)
(Is it a movie for a construction company?)
- "Riverbank Legends". - "Riverbank Legends".
"Legends", not "Construction".
- My goodness. - Construction.
(Where is "construction" coming from?)
(Suk Jin can only do for movies from the 20th century.)
I have never heard of the movie.
- I almost cried. - Suk Jin.
(They resume the game after Suk Jin pays 3 coins.)
- Projector - Projector
Suk Jin, "A T. Rex Claw".
("A T. Rex Claw" is a comedy movie Suk Jin starred in as an extra...)
(about dinosaurs and primitive men.)
Suk Jin, "A T. Rex Claw".
- There is no such scene. - Suk Jin, that's wrong.
- There is no such scene. - You played a primitive man.
- Hold on. - You played a dead man.
Suk Jin. Hold on.
There is no such scene.
What? I am imitating a dinosaur.
I played the 16th primitive man.
(In fact)
(He must be one of these.)
(Suk Jin passed by imitating one of the characters.)
- Okay. - There are dinosaurs.
- Projector - Projector
Se Chan, "Ratatouille."
"Ratatouille"?
"Rata, Rata, Ratatouille!"
- Nice job. - "Rata, Rata, Ratatouille!"
(He makes one up.)
("Ratatouille" is a cute animation.)
- What? "Rata, Rata," - That's not it.
"Ratatouille!" What's wrong?
(Correct.)
- That's not it. - It did come out!
Check the movie!
(Plausible)
- The 44-minute mark! - No.
(The producer finally realized.)
"Rata..." No one knows.
(His great acting fooled the production crew.)
- That didn't come out. - "Rata, Rata, Ratatouille!"
- That's wrong. - "Rata, Rata..."
("Ratatouille" is an animation released in 2007...)
- But... - It's a movie about cooking.
(about a gourmet mouse becoming a chef.)
It's about a mouse that cooks.
(Projector Game ends.)
- I see. - That's what it's about.
- He's so cute. - Let's wrap it up.
Suk Jin's construction skit was hilarious.
(Afterglow)
One.
- 1. - 2.
(Suddenly, another game is played.)
Two.
- 3! - 4.
(After reading atmosphere)
Five.
(Incorrect)
- This was a game of 3, 6, 9. - What?
- What? - It was a game of 3, 6, 9.
(It wasn't a Race of Wits?)
- Really? - That was round two.
(Feeling ashamed)
(A person who loses a game of 3, 6, 9 should pay 2 coins.)
- This is hilarious. - I like how...
- that was sudden. - That was funny.
- That was hilarious. - Goodness.
- That was humiliating. - I wrote it down.
This is interesting.
(You deserve it.)
- Give it to me. - How dare you humiliate me?
(Kwang Soo who played the wrong game pays 2 coins.)
- How many coins? - Two.
- Poor thing. - He just had to say three.
(Kwang Soo always falls for something like this.)
- I thought it was a Race of Wits. - Poor him.
I'll announce the results.
(The result of this mission will be announced.)
Okay.
The couple that lost the most will be able to hide theirs in here.
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin will hide the coins in the box.)
It was Jae Suk and Suk Jin.
- It's us? - Yes.
- You two will hide... - Gosh.
(Jae Suk and Suk Jin will hide...)
all 66 coins, and the rest will pick.
(66 coins in the boxes.)
- There are 66 coins? - Yes.
- Goodness. - We could win.
(If we're lucky)
- Let's turn the tables. - "Turn the tables"?
- Let's put in one each. - Okay.
(They must put at least 1 coin in each box.)
You're good with things like this. You should do it.
(They come up with a plan.)
- Hold on. - I put them in.
Let's not divide them.
- Let's put them all in one box. - Okay.
(They decide to put all the coins in one box.)
How about the middle one?
Weren't they in here before?
(Number 3)
We shouldn't put them in there.
How about here?
(They're in a dilemma between number 3 and number 4.)
- Let's put it in here. - Okay.
- All right. - I don't care anymore.
(They pick number 4.)
Please turn around.
(Then Jae Suk takes out all the coins.)
- So Min. - Turn around.
- Turn around. - Okay.
(On alert)
- We're putting them in right now. - We are.
(If they choose well, they can obtain all the coins.)
(Which box will they pick?)
Gather, please.
Let's go.
We need to pick the right one.
The couple with the most money will go first.
Haha and Ji Min will go first.
(Haha and Ji Min with the most coins will go first.)
Pick.
Okay.
- We pick number two. - Okay.
(They pick box number 2.)
- Please! - 1, 2...
- Please! - I'm sorry.
- Why? - There are none.
(Box number 2 has 1 coin.)
- None? - There's one.
- 1? - 1.
If you're sorry, then I'll take it.
(Meanwhile, Haha takes the coin.)
I'm not that sorry.
We've lost two competitors.
(One less to worry about)
Next.
- We pick number 1. - Kwang Soo picked number 1.
(Kwang Soo and Hyun Hee pick box number 1.)
Come on. Let's go.
(They only find 1 coin.)
- There's 1 coin. - Just 1?
Open it.
(Box number 5 has 1 coin.)
- There's 1 coin. What a bummer. - Just 1?
- What a bummer. - Are they all in one box?
Are they all in one box?
1 of these 2 boxes is a jackpot.
(Then)
So Min, I feel hopeful.
(We might be able to turn the tables.)
- That was a smart move. - Seriously?
(Box number 3 and 4 are the only remaining boxes.)
(Ji Hyo and So Min pick box number 4.)
- We pick number four. - Next up...
is So Min and Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - 1, 2, 3.
(1 of the boxes has 62 coins.)
1, 2, 3.
(They could turn the tables.)
Three.
- Look at it first. - Will they get it?
What? There's just one.
(There's just 1 coin.)
(We did it.)
I said it was number three.
- No way. - They were so lucky.
(They get all 62 coins in box number 3.)
- They're in first place. - We should've picked the other one.
Right?
(They get 31 coins each.)
- Right? - Whose idea was this?
- No way. - It was the middle box.
You must've been surprised when I wanted to pick number three.
(After getting 31 coins each, )
Yes, we were shocked.
(Jae Suk places 1st and Suk Jin places 2nd...)
- We did it. - This is unbelievable.
(in Hey, You Can Find Out Too!)
Lucky you.
(Jealous)
Go, Suk Jin.
(1st and 2nd places get to pick a prize.)
Let's get rid of these.
This too. Where's the "laptop"?
(They put 30 prizes on the number board...)
- It's here. - Right.
(and take the prize for the number they pick.)
- It'll be number 38. - Number 19.
Let's put "Massage from Jong Kook" down here.
(He puts the bad one far away.)
- And... - You'll probably get that one.
Pick.
The staff is determined to give us gifts.
(He carefully picks a number.)
Give me the "laptop."
(Careful)
- They're all good prizes. - I hope it's a dud.
Let's see.
Dud, dud, dud
(Suk Jin picks number 45.)
- Number 45. - Number 45.
(What?)
(He picked "Massage from Jong Kook".)
"Massage from Jong Kook".
(As Jong Kook cursed, Suk Jin gets a massage from Jong Kook.)
He picked that one?
- All right. - No way!
(It's unbelievable.)
- No way! - I can't believe he picked it.
- This feels surreal. - I'll give you a hip massage.
(Jong Kook the physiotherapist)
- "Hip massage"? - Lie down.
- I'll give you a hip massage. - Massage my shoulders instead.
No.
- Just do my shoulders. - That's a nice prize.
- This is a rare opportunity. - Lie sideways.
(Jong Kook's massage shop opens.)
- What is this? - This will make you healthier.
(He lies down to enjoy Jong Kook's hip massage.)
- Right. I'm good at this. - What is this?
- It'll loosen up your muscles. - It's good for your hips.
- Okay? I'll start now. - Okay.
- How many seconds? - Ready, set, go.
(He presses down.)
(Slapping)
My gosh.
(Jong Kook dodged.)
He dodged.
Gosh, seriously!
(Suk Jin becomes energized from the start.)
Jong Kook, aren't you supposed to be massaging him.
- I did. - This is his prize.
- You need to loosen them. - It's acupressure.
- How is it? - It's so painful.
(Are you sure this is a prize?)
- I bet it is. - How was it?
Not bad.
- "Not bad"? - Yes.
(It's time for Jae Suk to pick a number.)
- I hope you get it. - I'm cheering for him.
Number 41.
- It's a dud. - It's a dud.
(He gets a dud.)
(He's still not lucky enough.)
- Okay! - Dud
(Jae Suk used up all his luck in becoming the 1st place.)
- Dud, dud - This is great!
- Jae Suk. - I can't believe this.
This was the only empty one.
- He wasted his luck on this! - I can't believe it.
(Everyone is happy, and the race ends.)
You're so unlucky.
(It's springtime, and the flowers greet us.)
Hello, everyone. Good morning.
It's been a while since you started the race by yourself.
You're right. Here I am once again.
- Hello. - This is simple.
(Why are they starting in different places?)
Hello.
What are we doing today?
(Curious)
Before you arrive at the opening venue,
you must pick an angel and a devil...
(They must pick an angel and a devil...)
among the members while excluding yourself.
(among the members while excluding themselves.)
- An angel and a devil? - Yes.
(What's going on?)
The devil may face disadvantages in the upcoming race,
(The devil may face disadvantages in the upcoming race.)
so please pick wisely.
This is hard.
(This isn't easy.)
Judging by their appearances,
don't Se Chan and Kwang Soo look like a devil?
I'll give up.
(He thinks back on the things he's done.)
I can't. An angel and a devil?
I need to pick a devil?
(She listens to the rules and gets in the car.)
Hello, sir.
(Who will be the angel and who will be the devil?)
- Hello. - Hello.
An angel and a devil?
An angel?
Once the filming is over, they're all angels.
But during the filming, all the angels disappear.
Hello, Mr. Angel.
(An angel appears.)
Hello, Angel Jee.
(Laughing)
Let's pick each other as the angel.
(Let's not play a trick.)
- Shall we? - We can do that.
(They're making a deal to pick each other as the angel.)
We can just pick each other.
Then pick me.
- Okay. - Because...
I can't think of anyone to pick.
- Exactly. - Right.
(Is the deal made already?)
I can't think of anyone either, so let's just pick each other...
- Okay. - and not get humiliated.
Let's do that.
- Okay. - Bye.
(They promise to pick each other and hang up.)
I could use this strategy.
(He's got a plan.)
This will help me become an angel.
Angel Lee.
(He gets on the move.)
- Angel Lee. - Hi.
You do know that no one will pick you, right?
I do.
So let's just pick each other.
(Suk Jin's using the same scheme.)
We can do that.
I will change your name saved on my phone...
as Angel Jee.
As Angel Jee.
(Hold on.)
What did you say?
- Hey. - Don't get me wrong.
Isn't that an antidiarrheal?
- That's not what I meant. - It's an antidiarrheal.
(He's smarter than I thought.)
I will pick you no matter what.
Okay. I'll pick you too, Angel Lee.
(Angels end the call.)
Let's do that then.
Gosh, there are no angels among us.
There really aren't any.
(He receives a call from Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook is calling.
(Brazen)
Why, hello, Angel Kim.
- Hello, Angel Jee. - You know what?
(Here's another angel.)
- My lovely. - I was just about to call you.
(Lying)
I'm serious. What a coincidence.
Hey, what about we just pick each other?
(Brazen)
- I'll pick you. - That's a promise.
(He earns another vote from Jong Kook.)
Yes, I promise.
- Hello, Angel Song. - Hello, Angel Jee.
I'm going to pick the person who deserves it. And who is that?
(Suk Jin starts luring Ji Hyo.)
It's you, Angel Song.
Why have you become so kind?
(What's going on?)
It's nothing. I just decided to be a better person from this week on.
- I'll pick you. - Okay.
(Will he get one more vote?)
You should pick me too.
Angel Ha.
Hello, my role model.
My guardian angel.
- Hey. - Yes?
How about we pick each other?
Are you going to betray me?
- You'll only hurt me. - I won't.
Life is all about getting betrayed. Even my stocks have betrayed me.
Hey, life is all about betrayals.
Hey.
You can't always have it easy.
(Wisdom coming out of experience)
His stocks have betrayed him.
I feel so bad for you. I'll pick you.
(Haha feels sorry for him.)
- All right. - Okay.
Let's just pick each other.
Okay.
Gosh, I think he's really going to pick me.
Am I just naive?
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk calls someone.)
Is this Angel Yu?
Goodness, it is you.
Gosh, where are you?
I'm on my way.
(They're calling each other angels.)
I truly think you're an angel.
- I really do. - Why?
- Because... - Yes?
(He's flustered by the unexpected question.)
Let's see. It's because...
What? You're disqualified!
- No, hear me out. - You're disqualified.
(So Min figured him out after one question.)
You're done. You had no plans to pick me.
To be honest, you're a devil candidate.
Please, Jae Suk. I need to be an angel.
(He decides to threaten her.)
- Please remember that. - All right.
- I'll pick you then. - Okay?
(Threatening)
You truly are an angel.
(I'm an angel.)
All right. Goodbye.
(Obedient)
Bye.
It feels awkward to say it.
It feels awkward saying, "I am an angel."
(She instinctively rejects to be an angel.)
(It's time to decide on the angel and the devil.)
I am torn. This is driving me crazy.
The angel is my angel.
My angel is...
(Se Chan's angel is...)
I will pick Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook is my angel.
I did promise him earlier.
Besides, he isn't much of a threat to me.
I will choose Suk Jin.
(Jong Kook chooses Suk Jin as the angel.)
The angel is Ji Hyo.
(Suk Jin chooses Ji Hyo as the angel...)
The devil is...
Jae Suk.
(and Jae Suk as the devil.)
Would Suk Jin pick me as the angel?
I highly doubt that. That's why he is the devil.
The devil is...
(They all made their decisions on the angel and the devil.)
Jong Kook or Jae Suk?
Suk Jin.
Today,
(The rules are explained.)
you will need to identify the devil among the members...
though the Devil's Whisper Race.
(Devil's Whisper Race)
Depending on the results of the first vote,
(Depending on the results of the 1st vote, )
you will either gain or lose ballots...
from the five you were originally given.
(they will either gain or lose ballots from the 5 they were given.)
So there are more angels.
Let's say you received three angel votes...
(They'll gain 3 ballots for 3 angel votes...)
(and lose 1 ballot for 1 devil vote.)
and one devil vote.
Then you will receive two more ballots...
(That's 2 more ballots.)
(So they get 7 ballots in total.)
and come to have seven ballots in total.
I will attach something to your head.
(This vote will determine the angel and the devil.)
Make sure you don't see it.
(The current number of votes is attached to the head.)
Should I turn around? I can see my reflection.
(I shouldn't see it?)
Shall we go here?
Isn't this an angelic deed?
- So that I wouldn't see it... - Okay.
(He's showing off after doing 1 good thing.)
So that I wouldn't see the reflection, I turned around.
I could have seen it.
But only a devil would do that.
(He refuses any dark intentions.)
- Please turn around. - Okay.
- I will face the wall. - Okay.
(Imposing)
This puts me at ease. This puts my mind at ease.
I don't know why. I was like this since childhood.
I was like this since birth.
(After showing off, he puts on the result.)
If you come this way, I will put it on your head.
(He wears a hat with the result of the 1st vote.)
(0 angel vote and 0 devil vote)
Don't look at the reflection.
(1 angel vote and 5 devil votes)
(5 devil votes?)
- The devil is... - Jae Suk.
(5 out of 8 people voted him for the devil.)
- The devil is Jae Suk. - Jae Suk.
- The result is on your head. - Okay.
(He doesn't know the result yet.)
Will you accept...
(Will they accept...)
(the original result or the reversed result?)
the original result or the reversed result?
(The original result: 1 ballot)
Why would you do something like this?
(The reversed result: 9 ballots)
(Is there a reflection?)
Maybe I can see it.
(He's full of dark intentions.)
This is...
(If Ji Hyo accepts the original result, she'll get 7 ballots.)
(If she accepts the reversed result, she'll get 3 ballots.)
I should go with my gut feeling, right?
There is no way I got the angel votes.
(He's wrong.)
Why would they do that?
They wouldn't do that.
I bet I have many angel votes.
(He's also wrong.)
I will go with the original result.
(Suk Jin gets 5 ballots for accepting the original result.)
- Really? - Yes.
(Tell me.)
(He is fishing for information.)
What are you doing?
What?
- What? - Hurry up and pick one.
(Playing innocent)
What?
Not many people would pick me as the devil.
(He's bad at making a deduction.)
I am sure the devil votes went to a select few people.
(The devil knows nothing.)
I doubt I have many devil votes.
Please make a decision.
(He is a strong devil candidate without any deducting skills.)
(What will be his decision?)
O.
What does that mean?
- I choose the original result. - The original result.
- That's your choice, right? - Yes.
Please check the result now.
(It's time for Jae Suk to face reality.)
My goodness.
(What is this?)
This is the worst.
Did I really get five devil votes?
(I should've reversed it.)
I should have gone with the reversed result.
Do I get zero ballots?
No. Since you had 5 ballots, we will give you 1.
(Jae Suk gets 1 ballot.)
For goodness' sake.
(I can't believe them.)
I bet I have more devil votes.
(Everyone's getting wrong.)
I will go with the reversed result.
- The reversed result? - Yes.
There is no way people picked me as the angel.
(She will go with the reversed result.)
I will check the result.
1, 2, 3.
Who picked me as the angel?
Who did that?
(So Min gets 4 ballots.)
I just came back from a two-week hiatus.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo got no votes.)
(He diligently makes deductions.)
So I doubt they picked me as the devil.
- The original result. - The original result?
No. Hold on.
I bet I received some devil votes.
(This is meaningless.)
Someone must have voted for me.
(Since no one gave him a vote, )
(the result will stay the same either way.)
- The reversed result. - The reversed result?
(He worries and changes his mind in a meaningless fashion.)
The original result. I won't change my mind again.
The original result.
(He decides to accept the original result.)
- The original result. - Yes.
(Then he checks the result.)
The original result was the way to go, right?
It's the same either way.
(I see.)
There is no change.
I got zero votes.
This is upsetting.
(He has no sense of presence.)
Today, I will show you what a true devil is.
(He's become dark.)
I shouldn't have expected much.
(The number of ballots)
(Jae Suk 1, Suk Jin 5, Se Chan 4, Haha 6, So Min 4, Jong Kook 6)
They are too much.
(Kwang Soo 5, Ji Hyo 7)
Now, you can make the final vote using the ballots you have acquired.
(They'll make the final vote using the ballots they acquired.)
There are ballot boxes with the members' names.
(There are ballot boxes with the members' names.)
Write down the name other than your own...
(They have to write in a name other than their own...)
and put it in that member's ballot box.
(and put it in that member's ballot box.)
Use the white side to vote for someone as the angel.
(They have to use the white side to vote for someone as the angel...)
Use the side that's black...
(or use the dark side to vote for someone as the devil.)
to vote for someone as the devil.
(The 3 with most devil votes will be the devils.)
What am I going to do with a single vote?
(He's a minority.)
We have a pouch for the ballots, but since you have only one...
(You don't need it, right?)
Give it to me.
(He gets everything he can.)
This is so annoying.
- Do I go and vote now? - Ballot boxes are here and there.
(Everyone sets out for the ballot box.)
They are here and there?
- Jong Kook. - Suk Jin.
Your angel vote came from me.
Didn't you get an angel vote?
(Did Jong Kook and Suk Jin vote for each other as the angel?)
- I did. - It came from me.
Really?
- Our deal worked out. - I know.
(Thank you for voting for me.)
- I voted for you. - I voted for you.
That was me. Thank you.
- Don't be. I only kept my promise. - Seriously.
I will pick Jong Kook.
(Actually Se Chan gave Jong Kook an angel vote.)
Jong Kook is my angel.
The angel is Ji Hyo.
I knew you would need one angel vote.
(Suk Jin relies on the secret vote rule and shows off.)
Thank you. I mean it.
(Jong Kook has no idea.)
Ji Suk Jin World.
- My mind is at ease... - Right?
- to be in the Ji Suk Jin World. - That's right.
This is great.
Hey.
(Suk Jin gets things easy in his life.)
Let's vote for each other.
(While we're at it)
- I will write your name. - As the angel?
(Suk Jin makes a deal for an angel vote again.)
- Yes. - I will do the same.
I have many ballots.
(He fells for it again.)
- I have many ballots. - I have many ballots.
(Jong Kook trusts sneaky Suk Jin.)
That's right. I can use one for you.
- Kim Jong Kook. I wrote it. - Okay.
- Your handwriting is nice. - I know.
(Compliment)
Here.
(They write each other's names in and head to the ballot box.)
- Ji Suk Jin. - We can use one for each other.
- Of course. Where is yours? - Go.
- It's over there. - Why is it in a corner?
My goodness.
Why is it in a corner?
(Complaining)
- "Corner Suk Jin" is my nickname. - You are right.
- Corner Suk Jin. - Yes?
(He's voting for Suk Jin.)
I will cast this vote.
Okay, okay.
All right.
He stayed loyal since the beginning,
(Suk Jin earns 1 angel vote.)
so I will use a ballot for him.
(Meanwhile)
(Hesitant)
Let's save it for now.
(He knows how to make use of the secret vote rule.)
Let's save it for now. I will hide it.
Who is that? Suk Jin!
- Suk Jin. - Hey.
(He spots the next target.)
What happened?
- You had one angel vote, right? - What?
(It's the same scheme.)
You had one angel vote, right?
- Did it come from you? - That's right.
Didn't you vote for me?
I voted for you.
(Lying)
That didn't sound too convincing.
(Suk Jin tries to manipulate Jae Suk.)
I voted for you.
- Right? That's how it is. - Yes.
In that case,
how about this?
(Let's start by writing each other's name as an angel.)
Let's start with a ballot.
- For whom? - You.
Please give me an angel vote.
- You should vote for me too. - Okay.
You have a ballot, right?
(Do you have a ballot?)
For goodness' sake.
(I have one.)
- What are you talking about? - You have a ballot, right?
- You have a ballot. - Of course.
(It's not true.)
I have many ballots.
I will write your name.
(Suk Jin writes Jae Suk's name in front of him again.)
Thank you so much.
- Write my name. - I will write your name.
(Jae Suk trusts Suk Jin and writes his name.)
I will write your name.
- Let's vote for each other. - Okay.
- I wrote your name. - I wrote your name too. Okay.
(Everyone's listening to me today.)
My ballot box is there.
(Kind)
- Where? - Over there.
Put it in there. I will go and find your ballot box.
(The moment he says goodbye, he gets into action.)
- Make sure you put it in there. - Of course.
For goodness' sake.
Ballots keep coming back to my pouch.
(Dark intention)
This is the second one.
(The ballots keep coming back into Suk Jin's pouch.)
- Okay. - Jong Kook, how was the result?
- It was good. - It was heartwarming, right?
(Se Chan bows to him.)
Okay.
My guardian angel.
(Everyone's trying to persuade Jong Kook.)
You are my angel.
- My guardian angel. - You saw the result, right?
It was from me.
(Many of them argue that they voted him as an angel.)
You saw the result, right? I am serious.
- Move out of the way. - My angel.
- I will keep it short. - Did you receive my vote?
(Suk Jin voted for me.)
There is no way you didn't get any angel votes.
He had more than one angel votes.
He had more than one angel votes because I voted for him.
- Stop lying. - I am not lying.
(He doesn't trust them.)
Watch the episode when it airs!
(But it's true.)
- Stop lying. - Please.
Jae Suk.
(Devil Jae Suk appears with the most votes.)
The result was nice, right?
- My goodness. - You are here.
(He looks like he got elected.)
We have someone impressive here.
- Jae Suk. - He is impressive.
- I think... - Excuse me.
Do you even have ballots?
(A cliche question)
I bet he doesn't have any.
- Of course, I have ballots. - Really?
(Jae Suk has one ballot.)
- I have ballots. - Really?
Of course.
Do you know...
what's happening right now?
- We are headed that way. - Why?
(What's there?)
- Why are you headed that way? - Is everyone here?
(Flustered)
(Jae Suk's ballot box is wildly popular.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Walking over)
Let's go.
- You can't vote for yourself. - Is everyone here?
- Hold on. - I have already been there.
(Hold on.)
- Kwang Soo. - You can't vote for yourself.
(His supporters have never been so enthusiastic.)
- Where are you going? - I'm standing in line.
Why would you go there?
This is the red carpet.
(They have to line up for this hot place.)
Why would you go there?
- Put one in there. - Jae Suk, hold on.
- Put one in there. - Hold on.
Apparently, you can vote for the same person again.
- Really? - Really?
(The passionate supporter returns to vote for Jae Suk again.)
- What... - My goodness.
Why would you vote for me?
(Jae Suk can't stop smiling at the high polling rate.)
Apparently, you can vote for the same person again.
I will go all in.
(People show passion for him.)
- I didn't know. - I don't want to go anywhere else.
- Will you give me an angel vote? - Jae Suk.
(He's likely to be the devil.)
You can vote for the same person again.
- Please put this in the ballot box. - Really?
(Enthusiastic supporter)
Why do you have so many?
It doesn't look like you're voting.
- Have you run out of ballots? - I'm going to vote.
- Do you have some? - Of course.
(He shyly takes out a vote.)
- You do have some. - You do.
He has one.
I have a couple.
Jae Suk, if you run, you'll win for sure.
Fine.
(He cries in vain.)
I'll vote for you.
- Is Jae Suk popular? - Are you lining up?
- We're lining up. - Is this the trend?
- Yes. - Voting for him.
Excuse me. Why are you butting the line?
- Why are you butting the line? - My bad.
- You cut in very naturally. - Is this the devil's den?
(I heard that it was the devil's den.)
- Go back. - Is this the devil's den?
- It's popular. - It is.
(They are waiting.)
I set up a tent and slept here last night.
I stayed 3 days and 2 nights.
People fight here a lot...
(Jae Suk's place is popular among bloggers.)
because they butt the line.
He only has one left.
(The voters are unperturbed.)
Leave him be.
I don't have ballots, so this is unfortunate.
Right. You reap what you sow.
(Inside Jae Suk's voting booth)
He's an angel behind the cameras,
but this is Running Man, so you can't help it.
- There was 1 person. - I think there was 1 ballot.
(Haha gives 2 devil votes to Jae Suk.)
If I get one vote, I won't do it.
(The box is already full.)
It's full inside.
I'm sorry,
- but this is sold out. - Why?
- Why? - No!
- The ballot box is full. - I lined up for days.
- It's totally full. - What?
- I want to go in. - There's no more space.
(I have waited so long to vote!)
- I want to go in. - It's totally full.
- Can you open it back up? - It's totally full.
(An uproar)
Is this break time? Can you open it?
(He's uncomfortable with his own popularity.)
Can I buy some ballots?
I wish I could get around nine.
- Jae Suk. - Yes?
(Sneaky Suk Jin is done analyzing the market.)
I think...
you're a devil.
They are...
(They're lining up to vote.)
They're lining up. It's a popular place.
Do you have one?
(Sharp)
Hey.
- Be quiet. - You have one.
- I made the wrong decision. - Why?
(The regret of a strong candidate for the devil)
I should have went the opposite way.
You should have.
(Criticizing)
- I would have had nine then. - Right.
You should have went the opposite way.
Didn't you know?
Didn't you have a feeling?
Hey, couldn't you tell?
You have no intuition.
My gosh.
(When did I stoop down to his level?)
I'll see you later.
Where is he?
(Are there any other popular places?)
Do you want to check out this new and upcoming place?
(A food review blogger)
- What is it? - It's up here.
(Where?)
This is like Gyeongridan-gil. It's Kwangridan-gil.
- It's called Kwangridan-gil. - No.
- It's not this way. - Let's go to Kwangridan-gil.
(Kwangridan-gil for trendy people)
- Let's go to Kwangridan-gil. - What are you talking about?
Is this Kwangridan-gil?
(At this rate, )
- Yes. - Let's go!
(he is an advocate of Kwangridan-gil.)
- Let's go to Kwangridan-gil. - Everybody,
- this is Kwangridan-gil. - No.
It's a popular spot.
(It's proven by trendy people.)
- You must be a tour guide. - I am. Follow me.
This place is very popular.
(They follow So Min's guide.)
- Is it? - Yes, it's Kwangridan-gil.
This is pretty.
Jong Kook, Kwangridan-gil is so nice.
- This is nice. There's a lamp. - This is not Kwangridan-gil.
(The spring has come to Kwangridan-gil.)
There are flowers too. This is so nice.
This is nice.
- This is it. - This is Se Chan district.
(Everyone passes by Se Chan District.)
- It's Se Chan district. - Please keep going.
- Isn't the air good? It's spacious. - Please pass by Se Chan district.
(A crowd gathers.)
Jong Kook.
(Are these people trying to buy land?)
- This is nice. - It's great.
- Here it is. - This is great.
(According to topography, )
- There's the sun too. - Everybody.
(the location of Kwangridan-gil is perfect.)
This is a new tour.
- I'll check it out first. - Welcome, everybody.
(So Min enters without any hesitance.)
- You went in already. - Yes.
- Of course. - You were fast.
(Will So Min give Kwang Soo an angel or devil vote?)
I'm going to vote for you. I have many ballots.
Kwang Soo,
I can't believe you think of me that way. Look.
(She wrote Kwang Soo's name on the angel vote.)
So Min, you're an angel.
What are you talking about? What's wrong with you?
So Min.
(This world is still a good place to live.)
What are you talking about? What's wrong with you?
So Min.
(Scratching)
Hey, I heard you crossing it out.
(She erases his name and turns it into a devil vote.)
- Hey. - Even I heard it.
(Who made the scratching noise?)
I heard it too.
(Rattling)
- That was so loud. - That was too loud, So Min.
What was that?
Is there a microphone on the pen?
You just need to erase one letter.
(Everyone heard the sound of betrayal.)
Why were you crossing it out so hard?
That was too loud.
I thought there was a fly. What was that sound?
- She crossed it out too hard. - I can't trust her.
Do you have one?
(It was a good meal.)
That was tasty.
That was delicious.
- Did you enjoy? - That was delicious.
(So Min had a devil set menu at Kwang Soo's restaurant.)
My gosh.
That was amazing, everybody.
That was the best restaurant I've tried.
Where's Jeonridan-gil?
I want to go there all of a sudden.
(Jeonridan-gil becomes popular for the next destination.)
- Jeonridan-gil does not exist. - Jeonridan-gil.
- You have three minutes left. - Where is Jeonridan-gil?
You lose the ballots you don't use.
(Remaining votes become void if they don't use them.)
- Really? - I have one ballot left.
Tell me where Jeonridan-gil is.
(Everyone is in haste.)
I'm going to Haha's.
- He's a weasel. - Wait.
He repeatedly said I was his role model.
(Suk Jin moves to Haha's ballot box.)
Haha.
(Jeonridan-gil is very popular.)
Okay.
There's a lot.
Where's Jong Kook's?
Excuse me.
Do you know where Kook Francisco is?
- Where? - Kook Francisco.
- It's over here. - Where?
- Over here. - I see.
(He asked around for Kook Francisco.)
(Kwang Soo casts a vote.)
- Se Chan. - You're confirmed.
- I'm done. - You're a devil.
Okay, this is what I think.
(The devil decides to accept his fate.)
Even if I had many ballots, I would have become a devil.
- I'm certain. - Okay.
Is he voting for Jong Kook?
(Mumbling)
For devils,
it's better to vote for Jong Kook.
Be quiet. Let me enjoy spring.
(A devil is enjoying spring?)
Hey.
Who cares how many votes Jong Kook has?
(The devil is enjoying the spring sunlight.)
Se Chan.
Jae Suk, don't try to look composed.
- He's shaking right now. - Se Chan.
Enjoy life.
(This is the bluff of a devil.)
Jae Suk.
This is a perfect day to be a devil.
(The polls close for angels and devils.)
I would like to tell those who will become devils.
- If you... - Excuse me.
He went to the bathroom. He'll be back soon.
(Jae Suk didn't arrive yet.)
The devil is not here yet.
- He's not here yet. - Right.
- Here comes the devil. - Here he is.
Jae Suk, he's announcing who the devils are.
There's an announcement.
(There is an announcement that the devil must hear.)
- Devil. - Relax, relax.
(The potential devil is not calm as he walks to listen to the notice.)
He told me to enjoy spring.
He's going to make an announcement about the devils.
Relax.
- He's announcing the winners. - Relax.
Let me tell you who will become devils.
(Even when your identity as the devil is revealed, )
Even if your identity is revealed, you should protect other devils.
(it's more beneficial to protect the identities of other devils.)
We need to hide our identities.
(The key is to hide the identities of devils.)
I see.
- We know already. - We know.
(But they all know who the devil is.)
- We know. - Jae Suk.
- His place was sold out. - This is meaningless.
There were more angel votes than expected.
- Really? - That was unexpected.
(The angel vote can cancel out the devil vote.)
- Really? - There were angel votes?
- See? - This is warm.
(Is there an unexpected change?)
- Right. You never know. - It's spring.
I used one angel vote.
- He's getting started again. - I'm serious.
He even shaved.
- I'm serious. - He'll pay for it.
Did you shave?
- Did you? - That's why you looked weird.
- It looks weird. - He looks so ugly.
(He exposes his bare skin under the spring sun.)
Your face looks really weird.
- His beard made him look good. - Did somebody hit you?
Hey, I told you before you look weird without a beard.
After I shaved, I went home,
and my son is like, "What's wrong with your face, Dad?"
What's wrong with your face?
(His son is not used to his father's bare face.)
He was not used to it.
(Embarrassed)
I'm embarrassed.
He looks weird.
We all know who the devils are.
There might be a lot of angel votes.
You never know how this will turn out.
- No. - Don't say something weird.
Shut your mouth.
Shut your mouth. What do you know?
(He is already into the role of the devil.)
- He's a devil. He sounds like one. - He's a devil.
He flipped.
(His evil nature)
He must be nervous right now.
Look at his hands.
(His hands are nervous.)
- He's a devil. - Kid's hands.
- He's mad. - When kids get mad.
(Children clench their hands when they get mad.)
"What do you..."
"What do you know?"
We'll distribute the envelopes.
(It's time to reveal the poll result.)
Read the content on your own.
(Jae Suk pretends as if he is desperate.)
- Okay. - Jae Suk.
- Stop acting. - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - It's him.
Please take the envelope with your name on it.
(It's very important to have your identities hidden.)
Devils, it's beneficial for you to act like you are angels.
Look.
(No matter what he says, )
The cherry blossoms have bloomed.
- We know. - On a good day like this...
(no one is listening.)
My gosh.
(Jae Suk is...)
(No surprise there.)
It's your fault.
My gosh.
(Jae Suk is a devil. Who are the remaining 2?)
Is this "The Voice of Korea"?
(The Voice of Running Man with angels and devils.)
- I'm curious. - Who is it?
(Is this a blind audition...)
I'm going to press it! I don't care.
(where you only compete with your voice?)
I'm curious. I'm so curious.
(The members are surprised to see these four popular actors!)
- I really want to know. - This is unbelievable.
(Ahn Bo Hyun, Ji Eui Soo)
(Song Jin Woo, Lee Joo Young)
There's a devil on our team.
(The race between angels and devils starts now.)
- Go for it. - You're scary.
You got it.
- Why were you branded as a devil? - It's not me. You're mistaken.
(A desperate struggle to escape the branding as a devil)
(The devils have been decided already.)
There has to be a devil on that team.
Why?
(Meanwhile, the devils advocate for themselves.)
- It's not me, Bo Hyun. - I won't go easy.
What are you? What are you, Jae Suk?
(When the devils are on the move, )
(they can destroy a team?)
- I have to kill them all. - This is the devil's town.
What am I supposed to do?
(It's a close tug-of-war...)
- Pay attention. - I caught them! This is huge!
(between the angels and the invisible devils.)
(Which angels will protect their team from the 3 devils?)
- Keep coming. - This sounds fun.
I won't stay still.
(I Saw the Angels and Devils: The Devils' Advocates)