- Hello.
Hey.
- This is pretty.
- This place looks like a cafe.
- Hello.
It also looks like an escape room.
- This is pretty.
- Look at that.
This is so nice.
We have a flasher here.
Shouldn't it be X-rated?
- What?
- He looks like a flasher.
Hey, listen.
Kwang Soo, do you have
a problem with your stylist?
Why? It's my style.
- Are you wearing underpants?
- Aren't they too short?
- No.
- Which one are your pants?
- He tries so hard.
- Seriously.
You're so gutty.
What did you say?
He told me earlier...
that this is what a celebrity should
wear. But with the camera on,
- he says "You're so gutty."
- He woke up.
Isn't that what
Sherlock Holmes wears?
- The checked jacket.
- It's similar.
- You need a hat though.
- His pants are too short.
You look better without the jacket.
- Right. This is much better.
- I like that.
You look more
sophisticated this way.
You look better
without the jacket on.
My goodness.
I'll just wear a white shirt
and jeans next week.
- I know.
- This is a lot better.
That's how you end up.
Today, we have
special guests waiting.
- Wow.
- I see.
Let's bring in the guests then.
- Who are they?
- I guess there are a lot.
- I just hope...
- What?
Hey.
- My goodness.
- They all are here.
(Who are the special guests
that surprised everyone?)
(More and more diverse charms)
(TWICE full of charms)
- What's going on?
- They all are here.
- What are you guys doing here?
- I can't believe this.
This is amazing.
- Hello, guys.
- My goodness.
- This way.
- They all are here.
- When did you come?
- Hello.
(TWICE performs their new song
as soon as they show up.)
("More and More" by TWICE)
This is crazy.
Let's go!
They've become even prettier.
There weren't any articles
about them.
- I know.
- Move over!
- It was a secret.
Back off.
- This is amazing.
- They've become even prettier.
(So one more time)
My gosh.
TWICE! TWICE!
- They dance so well.
- They are amazing.
I love them.
(Addictive beats)
They are so cool.
(Everyone's addicted to the song.)
They all are great dancers.
They are really good.
(TWICE's fresh performance makes
people want to watch it again.)
(Truly impressed)
That was great.
- What's going on?
- I'm really surprised.
I had no idea.
- Me neither.
- How did you come?
When TWICE comes,
they usually release articles first.
- I know.
- Please say hello first.
Okay.
It's been a long time.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- One in a million.
- Hello, we are TWICE.
It's TWICE!
Today's going to be fun.
I'm very thankful...
that they visit our show
like this every time.
First of all... Hang on.
Ji Hyo and So Min are
being too quiet now.
Why are you so deflated?
- So Min, you're dressed like TWICE.
- You look like them.
- Look at the color.
- Stand next to Tzuyu.
- Stand here.
- Go ahead and do it.
You look like their manager.
- I know.
- That's true.
- Look at her.
- So Min.
Ji Hyo, stand next to them.
- You're wearing similar colors.
- I'm their road manager.
She's a road manager.
- Right.
- TWICE is our guests for today.
- It's a TWICE special.
I'm really glad to see them.
The nine members
of TWICE are back...
on Running Man after two years.
I wish I knew about it.
Right. We would've
gotten ready for this.
We would've worn outfits
that match theirs.
What would you do
if you knew about it?
If I knew, I would've
dressed like a hippie.
- I would've worn...
- I would've worn matching ones.
- Kwang Soo is like a hippie.
- All right then.
Please say hello
to our viewers one by one.
Hello. I'm Tzuyu of TWICE.
Tzuyu.
She's Tzuyu. Tzuyu is...
I remember something
about Tzuyu. Thanks to her...
Stay quiet.
This is an interesting story!
This is really funny,
but I'm not going to tell you.
That's enough.
- This is hilarious.
- This situation is funny.
- I'll hear it in the waiting room.
- We want to hear TWICE's voice.
- I don't want to hear your voice.
- He's right!
Do you not want
my funny story? Okay.
I guess it's a funny story.
Tell us about it.
It can't be fun this way!
Don't say it then.
If it's a funny story,
it will still sound funny this way.
We need to hear TWICE's voice.
I don't want you to cut in.
- I'm sorry.
- It was my mistake.
Stay focused.
- Okay.
- Please say hello.
Hello. I'm Sana of TWICE.
- All right.
- Sana.
Sana for today and tomorrow.
Don't make silly jokes
like "shy shy shy".
- It's old-fashioned.
- What's "shy shy shy"?
- Do you not know it?
- I don't know.
He means "shy shy shy".
- "Shy shy shy".
- He sounded like "Sa sa sa".
The word is "shy".
I'm sorry, but we seem
a little nervous now.
Don't be nervous.
It's okay. We all are friends.
Relax. It's okay.
- We are celebrities too.
- Don't feel nervous.
- Just relax.
- It's all right.
Don't be nervous. Relax.
- We are celebrities too.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- Let's do this.
- We need to show them.
- Relax.
- It's all right.
- Hey, act natural.
- We are celebrities.
- Act natural.
- Okay.
- Hey, relax.
- About Sana.
Whatever Sana sings
becomes the highlight.
It's like "shy shy shy".
It's actually nothing special.
It could've been something normal.
But it sounds special
when Sana sings it.
It wouldn't have been special
if she just said shy shy shy.
How did you do it? Can you show us?
I don't remember.
(I was seeing my friends,
so I was shy shy shy)
- This is it.
- My gosh.
This is what we call a highlight.
I think So Min can do this.
- Try it.
- "I was seeing my friends".
(I was seeing my friends,
so I was shy shy shy)
Oh, dear.
(Groaning)
- That's not it.
- Shy shy shy
- Ji Hyo, give it a try.
- Ji Hyo.
- Shy shy shy?
- Yes.
(Excited)
(I was seeing my friends,
so I was shy shy shy)
(Slurring the end of her song)
(He can't control
the look on his face.)
- She's got her own vibes.
- Right.
It shows how experienced she is.
- She seems experienced.
- Hey.
I'm just afraid her makeup
would get on my jacket.
My goodness.
I can do it in a sexy way.
(I was seeing my friends,
so I was shy shy shy)
(They don't know how to react.)
Okay. So Min is trying hard.
- There you go, So Min.
- Well done.
It's not good, but I appreciate it.
I think you all are
in good condition today.
But don't do anything
that I didn't ask for.
- At least during the opening. Okay?
- You need to control yourself.
So Sana just showed us
her part for "shy shy shy".
Then why don't you sing
one of Turbo's songs?
What? Jae Suk.
- "Goodbye Yesterday" by Turbo.
- All of a sudden?
- "Goodbye Yesterday".
- Let them sing it.
- Let them sing "Black Cat" instead.
- Maybe I loved you
That would be better.
- Show us the original dance moves.
- Black cat Nero
- It goes like this, right?
- Start.
Who dances like that?
Who are you talking about?
- What was that?
- This isn't just right.
- What is it then?
- Black cat Nero
(The point is catchy moves
that anyone can easily follow.)
- This is it.
- All right.
This cute friend of mine
It is a black cat
This is it.
Please try it
with your own feelings for us.
She'll be cute.
Start.
(Cute)
- She's so cute.
- She's lovely.
(Black cat Nero)
(My friend is a cat.)
- "My friend is a cat."
My mom is a cat too.
Next up is Chaeyoung.
Let me ask her a question.
Fans say she can do
an impression of Lim Kim.
- Please show us.
- That sounds nice.
Please do an impression of Lim Kim.
This is quite old though.
(I'm all right these days)
(What?)
- It's really old.
- It is.
("All Right" by Lim Kim
was released in 2013.)
- It is.
- It was about 10 years ago.
- It was from "Superstar K".
- I thought of something else.
Isn't it about 10 years old?
She prepared something new.
- She does?
- Yes.
We just got a report. What is it?
It's from "A World
of Married Couple".
- That's a good one.
- Nice.
- It's new.
- It's popular.
I can imitate
the facial expressions.
- Who can you imitate?
- Yeo Da Kyung.
- Yeo Da Kyung?
- It's Yeo Da Kyung. Nice.
- This is when she's upset.
- Okay.
Her hair is like this.
- Exactly.
- Right. She looks like that.
- That's it.
She has the look.
Half of her face looks the same.
- I know what it is.
- She looks exactly like her.
- You know what it is, right?
And this is how Lee Tae Oh looks
when he's in trouble.
(He does look like Lee Tae Oh
for some reason.)
Try it together.
(Everyone thinks it's so funny.)
- Wait. Suk Jin.
- What?
You didn't watch the show.
Do you know what this is?
- To be honest, I don't.
- Then why did you laugh?
Should I cry then?
(Should I cry when everyone
else is laughing?)
- Why did you laugh?
- I mean...
- Should I...
- Why...
It's just that I didn't laugh
that hard.
- You should be honest on TV.
- I should be honest?
- Should I cry? Should I frown?
- Why did you laugh?
You don't even know what this is.
I just laughed
because everyone else did.
- He should laugh with us.
- Of course.
All right. Next up is...
Sana.
- Sana already talked.
- You can do this!
- What's with you?
(He just talked to Sana.)
- You can do this!
- Let's give him a hug.
- Give him a hug.
- You're too nervous.
- You don't have to be nervous.
- It's okay.
(Embarrassed, he gulps down water.)
- We can do this!
(We can do this too!)
(TWICE is full of energy.)
- Should we throw in the towel?
- Today...
It's okay.
We're at war with TWICE today.
We can do this.
All right. Next up is Nayeon.
Fans say that some idol singers
look like juicy fruits.
Can you compare
the Running Man members to fruits?
Me?
We've been compared to animals
and many other things,
but never fruits.
- That's right.
- That'd be fun.
Can't I compare you guys
to vegetables?
- Vegetables are okay too.
- Vegetables count too.
- Just tell us what you think.
- Okay.
- It's just the appearance.
- Vegetables or fruits.
- This is going to be interesting.
- I can't wait.
What does Jae Suk look like?
- What do I look like?
- Jae Suk.
- Bean sprouts.
- Bean sprouts?
You do look like them.
- You slightly look like them.
- You look like them.
- You look like bean sprouts.
- You do look like them.
- Okay.
- You look like them.
- I had bean sprouts this morning.
- Dried-up bean sprouts.
- Bean sprouts.
- All right.
What about Haha?
What's that called?
Pickled radishes
you eat with fried chicken.
- Pickled radishes?
(Pickled radishes)
It smells bad.
- I love that.
- They're very nice and refreshing.
They're nice. They go very well
with fried chicken.
They're a perfect match.
- Pickled radishes?
- I love that.
- I've never heard that before.
- Even the juice is tasty.
- That's hilarious.
- Right.
What about Se Chan?
- No one has compared me to fruit.
- It's not going to be a good one.
A durian?
A guava?
(They recommend tropical fruits.)
- A blueberry.
- A blueberry?
- Se Chan looks like a blueberry?
- Why?
Aren't you being too mean?
Why would you call him a blueberry?
- Why do I look like a blueberry?
- Why does he look like a blueberry?
Well...
She doesn't like blueberries.
(No one questions it anymore.)
What were you expecting?
For a second...
It was because she doesn't like me.
Now I understand.
- Now I understand.
- That feels a lot better.
I didn't understand at first.
- Okay.
- Now I understand.
- Please step back.
- There was a reason.
I think I know
what Kwang Soo looks like.
- Really?
- What does Kwang Soo look like?
A yam.
(A yam)
- I was thinking of that.
- A yam?
Seriously...
- I was thinking of that.
- He looks like it.
- Unbelievable.
- He looks like a yam.
That's hilarious.
That's so funny.
- Unbelievable.
- He looks like a yam.
- That makes sense.
- Goodness.
A yam was perfect.
- Everything she said makes sense.
- Totally.
Everything was perfect.
By the way, I'm so happy...
- to have all members here.
- It's great.
Today, the mission fund
and the captains are very important.
It's the Running Man Captain Race.
According to the results of each
round, each team will receive...
an amount between 500 dollars
and minus 200 dollars.
The money will be distributed
among the members by the captain.
The captains can give all the money
to one member if they want,
which makes the captains
absolutely powerful.
And everyone can see
how the money is distributed.
After the money is distributed,
you can stand up to your captain...
by trying to take
the captain position away.
You can try to become
the next captain...
using your money in the next round.
Whoever bets the biggest amount
becomes the next captain.
After the race,
the top five people...
with the most money
will receive prizes.
The bottom three will be penalized.
- The top 5?
Teams will be decided randomly.
(Team Selection Result)
- Sana!
- Okay! Chaeyoung and Momo!
- Yes!
- And Mina.
- Mina.
- Yes!
- All right!
Each team will go
to a different place...
to decide the captain.
- Please change first.
- Okay.
(They'll change and
move to different places...)
(to decide the captains.)
The captains have more power.
Who should be the captain?
While you were away,
I tried to win their support.
I told them,
"If you choose me, I'll..."
"You can wait and see."
- Today...
- It's TWICE's day.
- They should decide.
- Right.
We have a shared bank account,
- and Jihyo manages it.
- Really?
- That's perfect.
- Then it's decided.
Are you the general affairs manager?
And no money has ever disappeared?
It's happened,
but I always put the money back.
- It's happened?
(Shocked)
For example, when I buy
a birthday cake for a member,
- I use our money first.
- You use the team's money.
- But you put it back?
- Yes.
- That's understandable.
- Right.
- We could take turns.
- Really?
- Every round?
- All right.
- If we bet...
- Exactly.
So Min is touching this.
- Because it's so pretty.
- Be careful.
I'm touching it
because it's pretty.
So Min has...
Sticky fingers?
(Kwang Soo is slapped.)
(So Min slaps Kwang Soo
so that he can't say anything.)
If it disappears, suspect So Min.
You'll find it in her pocket.
- He's so annoying.
- I'm serious.
She touched it because she likes it.
- I just think it's pretty.
- I mean it.
Before you know it,
it'll be replaced with
some plastic bag. I'm serious.
- Stop buttering her up.
- What?
- You're buttering her up.
- I'm buttering her up?
Yes, you are.
He's buttering her up, right?
Should we decide the captain here?
I just don't want to end up
in the bottom three.
- Guys.
- Yes?
We're going to start...
the Cheer Up! Unexpected
Name Tag Elimination.
- What are you saying?
- Already?
- We'll start Name Tag Elimination.
- What?
(Name tag elimination
all of a sudden?)
As soon as we start?
- What?
But we're a team, right?
We're going to start the Cheer Up!
Unexpected Name Tag Elimination.
(Grabbing)
- What?
- What's going on?
(As soon as she hears
the announcement,)
(So Min rips off
Jeongyeon's name tag.)
- We haven't started yet.
- See?
Jeongyeon, did you see that?
(There will be an announcement.)
- So Min!
- Did you see that?
- That's how she is.
- How could you...
- I was trying to protect you.
Did you see how I was
trying to protect you?
- So Min.
- Jeongyeon, you got the wrong idea.
- Jeongyeon.
- Can you eliminate...
a team member?
- So Min should be out!
- Gosh, this is crazy.
All right.
Let's hear the rules now.
All teams will play Name Tag
Elimination at the same time.
A team is out of the game
when all members are eliminated.
Money will be distributed according
to how long each team lasts.
We have Jong Kook.
Whoever survives longest
in each team becomes the captain...
regardless of the team's result.
(Whoever survives longest
in each team becomes the captain.)
(To become the captain
with the right to distribute money,)
(survive longer
than your team members.)
If you think your team is
going to lose,
you could try to become
the captain instead...
by eliminating your team members.
(You can become the captain
by eliminating your team members.)
- Can we eliminate our team members?
- Yes.
- That's too mean.
- Hold on.
- That's too...
- We couldn't do that.
No way.
- We couldn't do that, could we?
- Never.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- We shouldn't eliminate each other.
- Not yet.
You should try to survive
for a long time...
to become the captain...
and save the team.
Haha, Chaeyoung keeps calculating.
- Really?
- Chaeyoung.
If you keep calculating,
I'll rip off your name tag first.
- You shouldn't do that. Not yet.
- Stop thinking.
There are envelopes
hidden all over the place.
The envelopes have money in them,
which belongs to the person
who finds it.
- The person who finds it?
- Yes.
Try to find as much money as
you can before you get eliminated.
At the same time,
try to become the captain.
Do you understand what he said?
- Rip off others' name tags.
- Okay.
You can rip off the name tags
of your team members too.
(Se Chan adds.)
No, don't do that.
You can eliminate
your team members too.
- Let's say two of us are left.
- Let me see.
Can we start now?
- Not yet.
- You saw something?
- Is someone out there?
- No one.
- Did you find money?
- No.
Okay, there it is.
Whoever picks that up,
I'll eliminate that person.
How about we play
rock-paper-scissors?
- Okay.
- That's a good idea.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Yes!
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- No!
(Se Chan wins and gets the money.)
I'll have 10 more dollars
from the beginning.
- I can try to pick it up, right?
- Of course.
Hey, wait. You can't do that.
Why did we even play
rock-paper-scissors?
- Dahyun has a point.
- Right?
Let's start the race.
5, 4...
- Hold on.
- Why...
- Here we go.
- 5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
The race starts.
(The race starts.)
Stay away from the money.
- Gosh.
- I can't believe her.
- Yes!
- Seriously.
- How much is it?
(In the envelope...)
- It's 10 dollars.
- That's not bad.
Put it in your bag.
I shouldn't lose it, right?
- Put it in your bag.
- Put it in your pocket.
- We should try to find money.
- Right.
It might be hidden around here.
(Where is the money?)
(A surprise attack)
- Be careful of these attacks.
- This is...
I just wanted to try.
I wanted to tell you to be careful.
(I thought he was
ripping off my name tag.)
- I don't want to be eliminated.
- My heart is racing.
My heart is suddenly
beating so fast.
There it is.
(Jeongyeon has good eyesight.)
(She found an envelope
on the 1st floor.)
I want to go downstairs.
Don't go off on your own.
- What?
- You shouldn't be alone.
You're scary.
- I...
- Don't come any closer.
(He's too fast that it doesn't seem
like he's protecting her.)
(They run at full speed
toward the money Jeongyeon spotted.)
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, how could you?
(What?)
Sorry, it's empty.
What is this?
There's nothing in there, right?
(Se Chan arrives right then!)
It's empty.
- Jeongyeon...
- Tzuyu, this way.
Shouldn't we look
for the money first?
Exactly. We should
gather the money first.
It's Tzuyu.
I see Jae Suk.
It's Jae Suk.
There are too many people.
I counted at least three.
We should hide.
(They decide to run away
from Team White.)
- It's blocked.
- What?
You've got to be kidding me.
This is bad.
Guys, over here.
- Don't be like this.
- Why?
- You...
- I want to participate in the race.
- The three of you...
- You can't be all cute.
It's unfair to have 3 people
gang up on 2.
You guys go ahead. I'll watch.
I think I hear our teammates.
- I promise.
- Come on.
You can't...
Be careful!
(Ripping off)
(So Min's surprise attack)
What's going on?
What?
(Jae Suk joins them.)
Hurry!
Dahyun, you're out.
Rip So Min's name tag off.
(Jae Suk rips off
So Min's name tag.)
- So Min, you're out.
- I still...
- eliminated someone.
- There's no other way.
- Get her name tag. Gosh, Nayeon.
- She got it.
Nayeon, you're out.
- Good.
(Nayeon of Team Orange is out.)
- Are you all right?
- Are you okay?
(She suddenly bursts out laughing.)
My hair was ripped out!
- What?
(My hair was ripped out!)
- What the...
- What is that?
(Her name tag was ripped off
and so was her hair.)
Why did you rip out her hair?
It was So Min.
- My hair was ripped out.
- Sorry.
Jeongyeon, don't go there.
- Jeongyeon...
- We should help our team.
Forget about them.
What do you mean?
- But...
- Forget about them.
- Don't bother.
- We must help them!
Just forget about them!
Why did you rip out her hair?
It was So Min.
- Kwang Soo's coming.
- Sorry.
(Kwang Soo bulldozes forward
to assess the situation.)
It's 3 against 2. Let's get them!
(We have the advantage.)
(He makes a run for it.)
(What's going on?)
(He runs for it
leaving Jeongyeon behind.)
(If Jeongyeon is eliminated,
Kwang Soo will be the captain.)
- There's Jeongyeon.
- Let's get her. Come here!
I also see Haha.
Nice.
It's a death trap.
(I'll be eliminated there.)
All that matters
is that I stay alive.
- Haha...
- Watch your backs.
You guys can eliminate Jeongyeon.
- No, please don't.
- We don't have a choice.
- Please help me.
- We'll help.
- No, no.
- Let us help.
Jeongyeon, be careful.
Come any closer
and I'll go after you.
Where on earth did Kwang Soo go?
Hasn't Jeongyeon
been eliminated yet?
(He checks again.)
Why hasn't she been
when she's surrounded?
Let's call a truce.
- We'll go after Kwang Soo first.
- Sure.
Let's make Jeongyeon team captain
and go after Kwang Soo first.
Jeongyeon, what do you say?
- I'd love that.
- Okay.
Okay, gather around then.
Jeongyeon, isn't it in
your best interest...
to be team captain too?
- Exactly.
- You can rip off his name tag.
Do you get what I mean?
- Eliminate him yourself.
- Go ahead.
You should get going, Jeongyeon.
- All right.
- Let's trust one another.
- Of course.
- You go first.
No, you go first.
There's no need to worry.
Just look at the members
on this team.
The others will choose to run away.
Over here. Jihyo, here you go.
(They even share
the money they find.)
(Suk Jin wrecks the mood.)
I'll give it back.
I only played a joke
to keep you alerted.
(It's an envelope!)
(Suk Jin constantly trains them
to be on high alert.)
Jihyo!
(Thanks to Suk Jin,
they collect a lot of money.)
You guys are good at spotting these.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo
searches for the money.)
Where is he?
Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo!
Why weren't you eliminated?
I can't believe
you just left me there.
- I didn't run away.
- You traitor.
- I didn't...
- You wanted to be the captain.
I was trying
to draw them away from you.
As if.
You ran away and left me there.
Jeongyeon, let's go.
(Just then...)
Jeongyeon, run!
- Run!
- See?
He's leaving me behind again.
(Kwang Soo runs off once again.)
Jeongyeon, hurry.
Why don't we go up?
- Is that possible?
- Sure.
(Grabbing)
(That was close.)
(She's suddenly embarrassed.)
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
(So this is how it feels
to be betrayed.)
Can we make up?
Do you consider us a team?
Let's make up.
We have to be a team
for the entire day.
- Right.
- Must you be this way?
- I won't.
- What will become of us?
Let's get going then.
I won't betray you again. I promise.
We'll walk side by side.
(Reaching out)
(He can't help be
the traitor he is.)
Okay, fine.
Let's go upstairs for now.
(Running)
(Kwang Soo spots an envelope.)
(He then suddenly
runs off somewhere.)
(Meanwhile, Jeongyeon
runs the other way.)
(She runs into Team Gray.)
(Kwang Soo makes a run for it
using Jeongyeon as bait.)
- No...
- Guys, get her.
- Please don't.
- Finish her.
Eliminate her.
(Jeongyeon tries
to fight the inevitable.)
Be careful though.
Kwang Soo...
Kwang Soo ran away again.
It's every man for himself.
- Sorry about this.
- Kwang Soo...
- We're sorry.
- You should've been alone.
(Poor Jeongyeon's name tag
was ripped off.)
(Jeongyeon of Team Orange
is eliminated.)
Gosh.
- Kwang Soo...
- He ran away.
We should teach him a lesson then.
Let's go.
That traitor.
(Kwang Soo has been decided
as Team Orange's captain.)
Was she eliminated?
Was Jeongyeon eliminated?
Okay!
You're the last to survive
on your team...
which makes you the captain.
(He gathers his hands.)
(Glancing)
This is my mourning for Jeongyeon.
I feel terrible.
Nice. Let's do this!
It's 5 against 3.
- We'll eliminate all of you.
- Go ahead!
- We're dead serious.
- I am too.
- No.
- Bring it on.
You're so cool, Haha.
Hold your ground, guys.
Wait, who's that?
Someone's here.
- Jeongyeon, did you get him?
- It's over.
Did you eliminate him?
- She got eliminated.
- She was eliminated instead.
- Oh, dear.
- Who was it?
Team Gray.
What the...
(Ripping off)
I did well, right?
Haha, you're out.
- You four can get going.
- Go ahead.
Get going.
Did you have to do it this way?
Instead...
- We can go together.
- Let go of me!
Let's start over.
I'll let you eliminate me,
so make it look like it was 1 on 1.
- This just isn't right.
- Let's go to the prison.
- Must I be eliminated this way?
- Bye.
- Haha...
- Jeongyeon, wait.
You acted all tough
but was caught off guard.
Must I be eliminated this way?
Unbelievable, this is upsetting.
Haha...
It was 5 against 3.
- It was 4 against 2 for us.
- Yes, 4 against 2.
2 guys and 2 girls.
(Sighing deeply)
What's wrong?
Nothing is going my way.
- Same here.
- Absolutely nothing.
Exactly. Nothing's
going my way either.
I mean it.
No one calls me anymore.
(Depressed)
- Give me your number.
- Me too.
- Really? Can you text me sometime?
- Sure.
I like texting others.
I would've given out my number
if they had been male guests.
(Since they're girls, she'll only
accept their gracious offer.)
Can't you see that
I'm not pulling out my phone?
Not one guest on this show
has asked me for my number...
for three whole years.
Can you believe it?
- Isn't it insane, Jeongyeon?
- Does that normally happen though?
- Exactly.
- I've never heard of it.
Still...
(When a guy and a girl meet...)
Was there someone
you were particularly fond of?
(She definitely liked someone.)
There was.
I think I know who it was.
- Didn't you like Jinyoung?
- Yes, Jinyoung.
- Isn't he super handsome?
- He is.
It was the first time
I felt my heart do a flip.
He was incredibly handsome.
Why didn't you ask
for his number instead?
- Exactly.
- You could've asked him first.
What?
She was rejected.
He openly rejected her.
When did that happen?
That never happened.
Why would he reject
someone as sweet as you?
Which celebrity had
your heart beating the fastest?
- How can I answer that?
- It's more fun in here.
(He's intrigued.)
It's a talk show...
which is what I love.
How can I name all of them?
There were so many.
Which celebrity
is close to your dream guy?
There must be an actor or singer...
whom you thought
was cool or handsome.
For me, it was Yang Se Hyeong.
- What?
- That's right. She said it before.
And yet you asked me that question?
- Se Hyeong?
- Yes.
- Do you like Se Chan too?
But in person, he's quite ugly.
(They're dazzled
by her brutal opinion.)
(She strikes with hard facts.)
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo...)
Since the team captain
will be put to a vote afterward,
this will be my last time as one.
I'll collect what I can
while I have the chance...
and leave for good.
I'm sure he's here somewhere.
- Over there.
- Where?
Here's Kwang Soo.
(They found the traitor.)
He's here.
Kwang Soo!
(The others finally
caught up with Kwang Soo.)
(He runs at high speed
for over 5 minutes.)
(Kwang Soo's cameraman
has given up on filming him.)
Where is he going
without his cameraman?
Yes.
Give up.
(Kwang Soo stops at a dead end.)
You're in first place anyway.
Jae Suk.
(When Se Chan is about to
eliminate him,)
Kwang Soo.
(he takes out 10 dollars
from his pocket.)
I'll let you go.
I'll rip Jae Suk's name tag.
Okay, let's rip his.
Jae Suk, Kwang Soo gave me
10 dollars.
Hey, you're doing this
over 10 dollars?
(Petty offenders are easily
swayed by small amounts of money.)
Kwang Soo, if you give Jae Suk
10 dollars too, we'll let you go.
- What?
- Give him 10 dollars.
Or he might rip yours.
That's not what you said.
- Give him 10 dollars.
- If I give away 20 dollars...
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo hesitated,
but he pays 10 more dollars.)
Grab him.
We'll hold him,
- and Tzuyu can eliminate him.
- She can.
(We'll hold him,
and Tzuyu can eliminate him.)
- She can.
- We won't rip yours.
- Oh, gosh.
- Tzuyu, you can rip his name tag.
- Hold on!
- Do it.
- I'll give you money.
- Rip his name tag.
- Tzuyu, rip it.
- Do it.
- Rip it now.
- I'll give you 10 dollars.
10 dollars.
I'll give you 10 dollars, Tzuyu!
Good.
- We kept our promise.
- Okay.
- I'll give you 10 dollars, Tzuyu!
- Good.
(He justifies himself.)
- I'm sorry.
We didn't rip yours.
- Good.
- Good job, Tzuyu.
Go inside, you brat.
You thought
you could convince us with money?
- I didn't get swayed by 10 dollars.
- Let's go.
Kwang Soo is out,
and his entire team is out.
- Okay.
- What a messy game.
- Right?
- We didn't die.
This is great.
Welcome.
Our team was cool.
We all got eliminated,
but you guys were the best.
- We argued so much.
- Seriously.
They're not disappointed
in you anymore.
(He shows off.)
Anyhow, I'm the captain.
(While Kwang Soo shows off
about being a captain...)
- Look at her.
- Thanks.
I could give away money...
or keep all the money for myself.
We have a minus balance.
Okay.
Why did you give it away?
Let me say this.
I have minus 200 dollars.
I'm going to give it to one person.
Let's give up.
That's more terrifying.
"Let's give up."
She's so cool about it.
- You can't do it.
- They did a survey on their own.
You got voted as the worst man
on Running Man.
(Kwang Soo got voted
as the worst man on Running Man.)
They think you look old.
I do?
I look old?
Were you just gossiping?
(Gossip on TV)
This is so funny.
I don't see anybody.
We've been looking,
and we can't find anybody either.
They must be in the other building.
Have a seat.
We keep missing each other.
We haven't met anyone.
Who's hoping to be the captain
on your team? Who wants to be it?
We're rooting for Jihyo.
- You planned it out.
- Jihyo?
Yes, because she usually
takes the secretary role on TWICE.
- I see.
- She's fair.
(No, I'll do it.)
Don't exchange glances.
- What are you talking about?
- They're here.
- It's Momo.
- There they are.
Ji Hyo, this is a ceasefire.
Ceasefire. Where's Se Chan?
- I'm over here.
- Oh, right.
(Ripping)
Hey.
(Suk Jin ripped
Chaeyoung's name tag?)
- Good job.
- Right?
That was the most swift
you've been in 10 years.
I played dumb. I stayed still.
(Team Gray gains momentum.
Their next target is Team Purple.)
I got her.
- I did it. Okay.
- Okay.
(Ji Hyo is out in an instant.)
My gosh. What now?
Let's clean this up.
We don't have an option.
- Right?
- We have to attack.
We don't have a choice.
We have to finish round one.
(Shouting)
(Se Chan fails to ambush.)
(Help me, Jae Suk!)
- My gosh.
- Come over here!
- Hurry, Jihyo.
- Oh, dear.
(Se Chan gets out of danger. What?)
Hey! Jae Suk!
(I can be the captain.)
Come here.
I'll grab him, and you can rip his.
- Do it.
- Hey.
- Come here.
- Rip it.
- We did it.
(Jae Suk is out!
Tzuyu is the captain of Team White.)
- We did it.
- Hey. Tzuyu.
- Mina first.
- He's out.
Let's take care of her first.
Come here. Mina first. Come inside.
Come here.
Let's take care of her first.
(What?)
(Suk Jin eliminated Jong Kook?)
My bad. I want to be the captain.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
- Jihyo.
We'll be in first place.
- Girls.
- We will be.
My bad.
(With Jong Kook gone,
Suk Jin is the strongest.)
(Mina is out.)
- Okay, good job. Rip it.
- What's this?
(Sana ripped it!)
- Rip it.
- She's so tough.
(At that moment,)
(he attacks Sana.)
My bad. I'm sorry. Wait. I'm sorry.
I think this is a disease.
(I'm sorry.
I think this is a disease.)
I'm sorry.
Jihyo, you and I can dominate.
- Let's go, Sana.
- You have to keep your promise.
(Team Gray is the only team with
2 left. Their 1st target is Momo.)
(Momo is out,
and Team Purple is in 3rd place.)
- Jihyo! Jihyo!
- Okay.
(They attack Tzuyu next,
who is their last target.)
(Team White is in 2nd place.)
- Tzuyu is out.
(The only people left are...)
(Jihyo and me.)
- I'm sorry.
- I shouldn't have trusted you.
I'm sorry.
Let's not make this messy.
(Jihyo is out.)
Jihyo is out.
Suk Jin is the ultimate winner.
(Team Gray wins.
Suk Jin is their captain.)
Everybody, Cheer Up! Unexpected
Name Tag Elimination is over.
Fourth place team is
Team Kwang Soo.
- Team Kwang Soo.
- Last place.
Their captain is Kwang Soo.
- Yes!
- Sadly.
- He's always like that.
- That team...
is in the last place,
and they have the worst captain.
He's deceitful.
- What are you talking about?
- He won't keep any.
He'll be in trouble.
Third place is Team Haha.
Their captain is Momo.
Momo.
I knew you'd be the captain.
She will distribute
minus 100 dollars.
Second place is Team Jae Suk.
Tzuyu is the captain.
- Okay.
- Captain Tzuyu.
- Good job.
- Captain.
- First place is Team Suk Jin.
They have 500 dollars,
and Suk Jin is the captain.
(Team Gray's captain: Suk Jin,
obtained team money: 500 dollars)
Suk Jin is the captain.
- This is going to be fun.
- Thank you.
- What's this?
- I'm looking forward to this.
Suk Jin is so good these days.
Please be understanding of me.
I think I have a disease.
Please be understanding.
That's all fine.
Just distribute the money fairly.
- Of course.
- Pay attention.
Of course.
I'll distribute it fairly.
We'll distribute the money now.
First place team,
Captain Suk Jin will go first.
- I'm looking forward to this.
- But...
- we picked a good captain.
- I agree.
If it were you or me,
it would have been bad.
It was part of my plan.
Will it be one-on-one later?
Yes.
Can we trust you?
We'll show you a board
with the amounts written down.
(Current Dollar Amounts)
How do you have 130 dollars?
We're all around the same.
Suk Jin, keep 200
and give us 100 each.
Do the right thing.
- Right.
- Okay, I'm trying to.
- This is not hard.
- I didn't achieve this alone.
This is not a difficult decision
to make.
I know you don't do that. No way.
We might become the captain later.
Of course. I know.
Momo has a lot of money.
- This is not hard.
- Or...
make everybody 0. Deduct 10 from me,
deduct 20 from Mina,
and deduct 10 from Chaeyoung.
There's 70 left then.
If you take that, you still have 30.
- You'll still be the captain.
- Is this a secret?
Yes, that sounds good.
- Isn't that good?
- Yes.
Isn't that really cool?
You'll be all over social media.
Because she's nice?
My gosh.
Think about it. Everybody will
have 0, and she'll have 30.
You'll still be the captain.
Please applaud.
(Please applaud.)
- That sounds great.
- Captains, please come on up.
We have no expectations
from Kwang Soo.
- We trust Captain Tzuyu.
- We trust you.
Momo will be all over social media.
(However, Captain Suk Jin is
still hesitating.)
Do you need that much time to think?
- What?
- We already talked about this.
- You can't do this.
- I need to calculate this.
I want to calculate this...
so that you don't end up
in the last place.
If you don't do this properly,
Jong Kook will drive your car home.
Suk Jin, you live
in that apartment, right?
(Suk Jin, you live
in that apartment, right?)
He does. How did you know?
- My gosh.
- Of course I know.
I'm going to give him one for that.
I'm going to give you one for that.
- Stop it.
- Hurry up.
Round one is over.
Please come up one by one.
(It's time to check
their individual amounts.)
(Captain Kwang Soo's Team Orange
goes first.)
She glared at him.
She glared at Kwang Soo.
She's mad.
- I knew he would take all.
- She glared at him.
- He probably turned her into zero.
(Avoiding her eyes)
Was it a lot?
I guess you lost a lot.
- This is just the beginning.
- Kwang Soo.
She's criticizing him.
I'm really curious what Tzuyu did.
(Haha has minus 100,
and everybody else has 0.)
(He's flustered.)
What's this?
(I'm the only one
who has minus 100?)
Darn it.
(She avoids his eyes.)
- Laugh and get over it.
- This is one-on-one.
- We're barely starting.
- Laugh.
Laugh.
That was wild.
Right?
Okay.
Loyalty.
(Se Chan has 30,
and everybody else has 90.)
What? That's all she gave me?
(Result according to
Captain Tzuyu's distribution)
(That's all she gave me?)
(Tzuyu?)
- That's all you gave me?
- You still got some.
You still have some money.
That's still a lot.
- It's a lot.
- Okay.
I'm satisfied.
Great job, Tzuyu.
- Tzuyu.
- I knew it.
I like Captain Tzuyu.
Next team.
(This is the result according to
Captain Suk Jin's distribution.)
(Suk Jin has 290,
and everybody else has 70.)
He gave us some.
- It's tricky.
- But he gave us more...
than I thought.
(Rankings After Distribution)
(So Min, Jeongyeon, and Haha
will be receiving penalties.)
We'll pick captains...
- for round two.
- What?
Here are the rules.
Each of you can bet
as much money as you want...
within the amount you own in secret.
And we will reveal the money
you bet all at the same time.
Those with the largest bet
will be the second captains.
What if we have a negative balance?
If you have a negative balance
or no money to bet,
we offer the loan service...
- called Running Man Surety System.
- We have a loan system?
- By how much?
- Regardless of your team,
you can get a loan from
the production crew with one surety.
You can get 200 dollars per surety.
(They can get a loan of 200 dollars
per surety regardless of teams.)
When the race is over,
if the debtors pay their debts,
the sureties also get
the interest of 50 dollars.
- That's nice.
- If the debtors don't pay it back,
the sureties will have to
settle the debt.
- That's not good.
- Who would stand surety then?
- I'd never do that.
- We can't trust anyone.
No matter what happens,
you should never stand surety.
I never stand surety no matter what.
I can lend my own money,
but I can't stand surety.
- You know how much you have, right?
- Yes.
Now you will make a bet.
Does anyone of you need a loan?
Name your surety.
Chairman Jee, please help me.
What are you doing?
(Haha goes to Chairman Ji ranked
number 1 in financial circles.)
- Please guarantee my debt.
- How much do you need?
- That's what matters.
- Momo now has 100 dollars.
You get a loan of 200 dollars
in all cases.
- It's 200 dollars.
- 200 dollars?
Gosh, that's a lot of money.
If the amount is too high,
we can make it 100 dollars
with the interest of 30 dollars.
Okay. 100 dollars sounds better.
- I need 200 dollars though.
- Why?
I need to beat Momo.
- Just trust me this once.
- How much does she have?
- I've been with you for 10 years.
- How much does Momo have?
- She has 100 dollars.
- I'm sure...
he will definitely pay his debt.
I know what he's like.
I'll do this right.
Just trust me this once.
- Okay! I can do this.
- Okay!
All right. I'll stand
surety for Haha.
- You're like my brother.
- You're so generous.
I'll stand surety for him.
It's 200 dollars.
- Thank you so much.
- You need 200 dollars.
- Thank you, Suk Jin.
- All right.
(He gets the surety name tag.)
Let's do this. Okay.
I have to do this right.
(Who will be the captain
of Team Purple?)
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
- Can I get some money?
- What?
I need some money.
I'll send 200 dollars
to your account now.
(They can exchange money for real?)
Kwang Soo, you're not
supposed to do this.
Why would you send money
to my account?
- Real money?
- He says he'll send me real money.
Send me your account number.
Listen, Se Chan. I'm sure I can win.
- Hang on.
- On the name of TWICE.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
I swear.
- You swear on the name of TWICE?
- Yes.
(Why is she so serious
about no big deal like this?)
I'll stand surety for Nayeon.
- You're standing surety for her?
- Yes, I'm the guarantor.
She possessed me to do this.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Se Chan. Can you stand
surety for me too?
I have no money.
- Se Chan.
- It's over.
Se Chan, please.
What did she say?
- Aren't you two friends?
- We're friends.
She's even a few months
older than me.
Is she crazy?
- Go find someone else.
- What are you talking about?
Go ask Suk Jin.
This is a mess.
(While everyone is busy
standing surety...)
- You're the captain, Momo.
- Can I get a loan?
- You're the captain now.
- I have to be the captain again.
Otherwise, Haha will be
the new captain.
Hold on, Momo.
(He just can't believe
what's happening.)
Is Momo talking to Jong Kook now?
- My gosh.
- Hey.
I thought they were having
a private talk.
You're the captain now.
I see. You want to be the captain?
I think he will bet a lot of money.
I need a loan.
Momo.
- Why would you...
- You've got 30 seconds left.
(Hesitating)
Do you really have to do this?
This is crazy. Hold on.
It's driving me crazy.
Why are you coming out?
Have you lost your mind?
- Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- My gosh.
- Are you standing surety for Momo?
I was told not to stand
surety no matter what.
You shouldn't do this.
You can't do it.
Is this what Momo
is up to? All right.
- Chairman Jee.
- How much do you have?
I'm asking you for the last time.
Suk Jin, we're in the same team.
It means one of us will be doomed.
- If we keep doing this, she will...
- We can't do this.
- Right.
- Are you here to stand surety?
- No, I'm still thinking about it.
- I can't believe you're doing this.
If you want to do this,
you can stand surety for me.
My gosh.
You were talking to Se Chan.
- She's got a lot of money.
- She does?
- That's not true.
- Hang on.
My goodness.
- Look at Momo. Look at her eyes.
- Momo.
Momo. All right then.
- I'll do it for her.
- Thank you.
Of course I should do this for Momo.
My gosh.
- Did you just stand surety for her?
- Chairman Jee!
I should never
let my mom watch this.
Wait. Listen.
Kwang Soo will stand surety for me.
- Is it true, Kwang Soo?
- What?
What about me?
So Min just got 200 dollars
with Kwang Soo as the surety.
I'm standing surety for So Min?
- What nonsense is this?
- Stand surety for each other.
- I'm trying to borrow money here.
- No, Kwang Soo.
- I'm looking for a surety now.
- Just come here.
- Why would I...
- Are you crazy, Kwang Soo?
- It's not like that.
- Are you insane?
- Listen to me.
- Why would I do that?
Just stand surety for me.
I won't bet my money
to become the captain.
Once I pay the money back,
you'll make 50 dollars.
Or I can get a loan of 100 dollars.
Round One is over. Please sit down.
Wait. He said yes.
I'll leave my phone with you.
I don't need your phone.
Just get me 100 dollars.
Okay. I'll do it for you, So Min.
Just get 100 dollars.
Only 100 dollars.
I'll try my best.
I'll be good.
Everyone, now you should make a bet.
Those with the largest bet will be
the captain using the money.
The rest of you will
get your money back.
- We get the money back?
- Yes.
If you bet a large amount of money,
the captain will have to
spend more money.
That's right.
You should think about it.
You won't bet your money anyway.
I need to become the captain now.
Let me be honest with you.
I love my team members.
(Let me be honest with you.
I love my team members.)
I'll take good care of you guys.
Just stay out of this.
I'll make you get your money back
by being in second place, at least.
- Are you serious?
- I'll be the captain.
- Nayeon, you have to be a captain.
- Sure.
I'm smart. Don't worry, Se Chan.
I'll pay your money back.
Really? Thank you.
Even if I fail, I'll pay
your money back anyway.
But Jihyo doesn't agree.
Are you serious? Okay.
- Okay.
- Nayeon sings the first part.
And the lyrics go like this. "I'm
not going to please you anymore."
- Seriously?
- Dahyun, you're amazing.
Is that the lyrics you sing?
(I'm not going
to please you anymore.)
Even if I fail, I'll pay
your money back anyway.
Is that the lyrics you sing?
(The surety is worried
because of the lyrics now.)
- Let me announce the results.
- Okay.
First, Team White.
Who is it?
The captain for Round Two is...
(Who's the captain of Team White?)
Yoo Jae Suk who bet 10 dollars.
(Yoo Jae Suk who bet 10 dollars)
We helped him become the captain.
Did you not stop him?
It's amazing that he became
the captain only with 10 dollars.
- It's the best, right?
- It is.
- He's so lucky.
- This is easy.
All right. The captain
of Team Gray is...
Ji Suk Jin who bet 110 dollars.
You said you didn't bet much money.
Jihyo bet 50 dollars,
and Sana bet 30 dollars.
Jong Kook didn't bet his money.
How much?
- Did you not bet your money?
- No.
- You needed only 50 dollars.
- I think...
- he will get a penalty today.
- No. The thing is...
they have about 100 dollars.
Chairman Jee.
I'll pay your money
back immediately.
- Okay.
- All right. Team Purple.
(The result of Team Purple
is announced.)
(Momo and Haha got loans
to become the new captain.)
(How did it go?)
Momo who bet 220 dollars
is the captain.
(Momo who bet 220 dollars
is the captain.)
(This is why I use money.)
But...
Haha didn't bet his money.
(Haha didn't bet his money.)
(Haha made Momo spend a lot of
money to become the next captain.)
- He's so mean.
- He's so...
- He's really nasty.
- Haha!
- Next round.
- Help me in the next round.
She spent 220 dollars
to become the captain?
- This is unbelievable.
- It's too expensive.
She spent a lot.
- Momo has to win.
- 220 dollars to become the captain.
Team Orange.
- I'm curious about this team.
- Nayeon should be the captain.
Nayeon who bet 20 dollars
is the captain.
Yes!
(Nayeon who bet 20 dollars)
(The surety is happy.)
Kwang Soo bet 10 dollars,
and the rest of them didn't bet.
- Why did you not make a bet?
- So Min, why did you not do it?
- You got a loan.
I just got a loan to keep the money.
(Having cash is the best.)
(What?)
What is she up to?
Hey, what you're doing is...
- like getting a loan for saving.
- But once I...
Once I pay the money back,
you'll get the interest.
Why would you get a loan
and save it up?
- This isn't about the game.
- What are you doing?
She's making money in her own way.
I don't want to lose.
This is Round Two.
This round is for differential
prize money and lunch menu.
The second mission is
Graceful Signal Dance.
Momo has to try hard in this round.
She has to win.
I have to try hard.
- You must be hungry now.
- Right.
So we prepared lunch for you.
You'll hear various signal songs.
Listen to the songs carefully...
and show dance moves
that are suitable for them.
You can give it a try
in any order you like.
Once you're done dancing,
the three judges will...
lift up the color
of the best dancer.
If you get one or more votes,
- you can get the menu for lunch.
- Okay.
We have an advantage here.
And you will get differential rates
of prize money...
according to the number
of dishes you win.
- Let's do this.
- Let me play...
- the first song then.
- Shall we dance together?
- We should try hard.
- Cue.
(The first song)
(A combination of trot and EDM,
"Amor Fati")
Go ahead and dance.
(Dahyun of Team White steps up.)
- She's doing it.
- You can do this by yourself.
- Dance with your guts.
- You can do this.
(The random dance machine
of TWICE, Dahyun goes first.)
Good, Dahyun.
- Chaeyoung.
- Go.
Good job, Chaeyoung.
Mina, that's good.
Dahyun's face is so funny.
(She's the master
of facial expressions.)
She makes the same expression,
but she looks different.
Momo, you should show something.
Show us.
How would we beat her?
Good.
It's so cool.
(Momo joins them dancing poppin.)
Great.
(The battle for the center
has begun.)
That's nice.
They are fighting.
That's really good.
(She expresses
how she lost her confidence.)
Why would she dance like that
to a song like this?
Momo, that's great.
I love it.
Okay.
(The first song is over
after the battle for the center.)
When Dahyun takes the stage,
I can't go out there.
She has that air about her.
Dahyun is too strong.
She is too scary.
I am afraid of her.
Raise the color of the team
whose dance you liked the most.
(Will it be Momo who is
desperate for high scores...)
(or Dahyun who has
a variety of facial expressions?)
Three.
(They voted unanimously
for Team White.)
- Okay!
- Yes!
It's okay.
- Dahyun, you did it.
- You did it.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Good job.
The second signal song is
for bulgogi and mushroom hot pot.
That's all we need.
Music, cue.
(The song begins.)
Hold on. Isn't that the song?
(Hold on. This song is...)
(Haha and Jae Suk
react automatically.)
"Infinite Challenge".
My goodness.
Isn't this a song
for "Infinite Challenge"?
(They heard this song a lot
in their "Infinite Challenge" days.)
(Their teamwork on Saturdays
became a fond memory.)
"Infinite Challenge"!
(The former members party
as if their time has come.)
There you go. There you go.
This song is for Jae Suk and Haha.
How could you play this song?
(She is more excited
than the former members.)
- Haha and Jae Suk will take it.
- There you go, Sana.
(Sana and Suk Jin are dancing
like an old couple.)
There you go, Sana.
(The "Infinite Challenge" song sends
the ballroom into chaos.)
- The dance needs to suit the song.
- That was great.
Our team will win.
- Haha and Jae Suk.
- I haven't done this dance.
I haven't done this dance.
The round was
for bulgogi and mushroom hot pot.
It was a song
for "Infinite Challenge".
1, 2, 3.
Okay.
(Team Gray and Team White
get the dish!)
(You should have danced better.)
Good job.
- Haha danced with Jae Suk.
- He danced too.
Didn't he get a vote?
Haha danced too.
Is this because I am not
on "Hangout with Yoo"?
Haha danced too.
(He is on a variety show
on both days of the weekend.)
- Okay.
- The decision is objective.
This one is for the rolled omelet.
- Rolled omelet.
- Let's take it.
- Music,
- The two of us will go out first.
- cue.
- Run out shortly afterward.
Let's go.
All right, Jae Suk.
(They charge to the stage.)
- This step looks weird.
- Try to look cool.
(They grab each other's neck
and dance in a cool way.)
Why did you guys come to us?
- What is this?
- Why did you guys come to us?
(Why are you passing through here?)
(Peek-a-boo)
- What is this?
- Why did you guys come to us?
- Hold on.
- What is this?
Hold on.
Why did you guys come to us?
What are you guys doing?
- Why did you guys come to us?
- What is going on?
Hold on. Guys. Guys.
The teams should take turns.
- Why did you take over the stage?
- Seriously.
(Amidst the chaos)
- Why did you take over the stage?
- Seriously.
- This isn't a collaboration.
- What is this?
- The teams should take turns.
- That's right.
So Min, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
- The teams should take turns.
- Look at So Min.
What is So Min doing?
What are you doing?
Hey!
You should focus on
paying off the debt!
- I am working hard.
- All right. Okay.
Gosh, this song is...
Let's go.
(Is it "Honey" by Park Jin Young?)
- It's Park Jin Young's song.
- They know the dance.
- Go out there.
- JYP Entertainment.
They are like a machine.
(All members of TWICE dance
to Park Jin Young's song.)
All of them know the dance.
(The master dancer
jumps onto the stage again.)
They all know the dance.
There are more members
of other teams.
This is...
(She commands the stage.)
- Dahyun.
- Look at Dahyun.
- No one can take the center.
It's Dahyun's spot.
No one can go
near Dahyun or Momo.
Dahyun.
Momo, go to the front.
(The 2nd war
to take the center begins.)
Let's see what happens.
Hold on.
Why do you keep trying
to go to the front?
Why are you going to the front?
That was incredible.
- We did it.
- What was that?
Dahyun, what kind of dance was that?
This result reflects the dance
you have shown so far.
All right.
- Dahyun should get a vote.
- She was the best.
1, 2, 3.
(Team Orange and Team White
succeed to get a side dish.)
(Bowing)
Where are you going?
Thank you.
Kwang Soo's team has 100 dollars.
Team Gray has minus 200 dollars.
(Current Rankings)
(Team White, Team Purple,
Team Orange, and Team Gray)
Captains, come on out...
- and distribute the money.
- Do they distribute the money?
- Nayeon.
- Nayeon, I have no doubt.
- Me neither. I trust you.
- I have no doubt.
Suk Jin, do this right.
We can't place last.
Minus 200 dollars?
Wait right there.
- Don't worry.
- We showed great teamwork.
(Momo turns in
the distribution plan first.)
Turn it in if you are ready.
(The 4 captains
finish distributing the money.)
I will give you the money.
Write down the amount here.
Kwang Soo's team, take the money.
(Kwang Soo checks the amount.)
(Kwang Soo got 0 dollars.)
What? What?
- Why do I have 230 dollars?
- What?
Didn't we have 100 dollars?
(The dividend rate is 0 percent.)
Okay. Here.
(How did Captain Suk Jin divide
minus 200 dollars?)
(Jong Kook got minus 200 dollars.)
(Suk Jin, Sana, and Jihyo got
0 dollars.)
- This is driving me crazy.
- It's fun this way.
- He gave all of it to you, right?
- This is driving me crazy.
I didn't take any money
from you guys.
(He tries to win their approval.)
- This round was so hard.
- Hey.
- Why did I get so much?
- I know. Why did I get so much?
Why did I get so much?
You gave money to everyone
except for me.
I will give you money later.
I will give you
a lot of money later.
(Rankings After Distribution)
(So Min, Momo, Dahyun, Tzuyu,
and Nayeon will get a prize.)
(Kwang Soo, Jeongyeon,
and Jong Kook will get a penalty.)
Now, write down the money
you want to bet to be the captain.
Who wants to be the captain
this time?
Do you want to be the captain?
Sure. I will be it.
- Go ahead.
- Team Jae Suk is done, and...
Can I take out a loan?
Then you will get 50 dollars anyway.
- 40, 40, 40, 40 dollars.
- Can we take out a loan?
I will stand surety for 100 dollars.
- 200 dollars.
- 200 dollars?
For how much did you stand surety?
- He wanted 200 dollars.
- 200 dollars?
- Make me the captain this time.
- Sure thing, Dahyun.
Okay. So we write down zero dollars.
It will be okay.
(They agree to write down
0 dollars except for Dahyun.)
To make Dahyun the captain,
everyone else wrote down
zero dollars.
- Okay?
- Dahyun, write 10 dollars.
(Team White agrees to write down
zero dollars.)
You wrote down zero dollars, right?
All right.
- We will announce the results.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk's team.
- Tzuyu bet zero dollars.
- See?
- Jae Suk bet zero dollars.
- That's right.
- Se Chan bet 20 dollars.
- Okay!
(Se Chan bet 20 dollars.)
Okay!
That's...
- He is unbelievable.
- That's...
- Dahyun bet 30 dollars.
- What?
30 dollars.
Dahyun bet 30 dollars.
(She is scolding him with her eyes.)
- What?
- I knew this would happen!
- Dahyun didn't trust you.
- That's incredible.
- He isn't...
a part of the team.
- How could you be like that?
- I am sorry, Captain.
- How did you know?
- All right. Just you wait.
Dahyun is the captain.
Captain, please remember this
when you distribute the money.
- I will do that.
- This is a disaster.
(Se Chan's treason failed.)
Unbelievable.
Ji Hyo and Mina bet zero dollars.
- Chaeyoung bet 10 dollars.
- Really?
- She is ambitious.
- You gave it a try.
Momo bet 220 dollars,
and Haha bet 50 dollars.
Darn it!
(Momo bet 220 dollars,
and Haha bet 50 dollars.)
When did you write down 220 dollars?
- Did she bet 220 dollars again?
- 220 dollars?
Does she have that much money?
How will you pay back the money?
- Please give me some time.
- Seriously.
- We have the last round.
- I lent you 300 dollars.
220 dollars?
How did Momo bet 220 dollars?
Haha!
Suk Jin's team.
Jong Kook, Sana, and Jihyo
bet zero dollars.
Suk Jin bet 30 dollars.
Suk Jin.
You keep being the captain.
He is in power for a long time.
I have never seen Jihyo and Sana
make that kind of a face.
What is wrong with you?
Kwang Soo's team is last.
Jeongyeon bet zero dollars.
- You didn't bet any money?
- No.
Nayeon bet 30 dollars.
(Kwang Soo even took out a loan
to become the captain.)
Kwang Soo bet 220 dollars,
and So Min bet 230 dollars.
(Kwang Soo bet 220 dollars,
and So Min bet 230 dollars.)
(So Min stood surety
and backstabbed him.)
She went all in.
She is unbelievable.
Even if she comes in last...
(She is savoring the happiness
10 dollars brought her.)
I wanted to be the captain for once.
- So Min, you are unbelievable.
- You are incredible.
- Now,
let's have lunch.
We will bring in the food.
- Okay.
- I can't eat right now.
I lost my appetite.
Eat up, everyone.
- Enjoy the food.
(They enjoy a meal
with the side dishes they earned.)
- What is this?
This is amazing. What is this?
It smells good, right?
It's the scent of shampoo.
(The scent of shampoo welcomes them
at the site of the third mission.)
Oh, my sponsor is here. Mr. Sponsor.
- So Min.
- Yes?
You need to pay me back soon.
Mr. Sponsor.
(Staring)
(She approaches Kwang Soo.)
(Ripping)
I wanted to rip it once.
What is...
- She ripped it off.
- Why...
You did a good job.
You ripped it off tastefully.
I was sad that it ended so quickly.
- You didn't get to rip one off.
- No.
- This is the final mission.
- Okay.
The final mission is
Touch More and More.
They're witty.
(She loves it.)
It will be like a tournament.
The 2 representatives of 2 teams
will play the game first.
On the slippery pyramid
that is made of Styrofoam,
they will play tag
on offense or defense.
Both players will start
with paint on the gloves.
If the offensive team touches
the defensive team's name tag...
and gets paint on it,
that person is out.
The moment one member is out,
another member
of the same team will enter.
The offense and defense
change every 30 seconds.
You win when everyone
in the opposing team is eliminated.
It will be hard.
We just need to touch the name tag.
That's right. You just need to get
some paint on the name tag.
The female members will go first.
Tzuyu and Dahyun need a hair tie.
Thank you.
Let's see how slippery it is.
(Sliding)
(Smiling)
I look cool, right?
Don't I look cool?
Haha.
(Haha, look at me.)
(Faking his reaction)
It's seriously cool.
I got goosebumps.
That's incredible.
(For whom is she putting on
a performance?)
(She is cute.)
- That's incredible.
- Why am I doing this?
Seriously. I got goosebumps.
Please put paint on your gloves.
Okay.
Give me a pair of gloves.
I have gloves right here.
(I have gloves right here.)
(Throwing)
(Hurling)
I am sorry.
(His feelings are hurt.)
- I got flustered too.
- I could have gone to you.
I got flustered too. I'm sorry.
It looked like you were throwing
a snack to a dog.
He was on his way to you too.
I am sorry. I got flustered.
That was too...
(I didn't think
you would be like that.)
My goodness.
(Dahyun is putting paint
on her gloves.)
There we go.
Put enough paint on the gloves.
Dahyun is putting a lot of paint
on them.
That's good.
Are you dying your gloves?
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
(Their enthusiasm is at its max.)
Please enter.
Dahyun, are you on your way
to perform surgery?
Will you perform surgery?
Dahyun, perform surgery.
We are on offense, right?
I will blow the whistle
after 30 seconds...
to change the offense and defense.
I am scared. I am scared.
Get ready. Set.
(The 1st round starts.)
Set.
Hang in there for 30 seconds.
The positions change
when the whistle sounds.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Oh, my goodness.
- That's good.
- She is good.
- Hang in there for 30 seconds.
- Jeongyeon, let's go.
- Jeongyeon.
She is almost there.
- She is almost there.
- Come on down.
Hang in there for 30 seconds. No!
Come on.
(Will Jeongyeon get eliminated
right away?)
Tzuyu, she is coming down.
Jeongyeon!
Hang in there for 30 seconds. No!
- I got her!
- Jeongyeon!
- She is out!
- No!
(I got her!)
(Jeongyeon is out.)
- Jeongyeon is out.
- Go in there, So Min.
(So Min goes in.)
This is...
She is over there.
So Min, eliminate someone.
- Get her.
(With the sound of whistle,
Dahyun moves to attack!)
(She isn't too far from So Min.)
(Will she eliminate So Min
after Jeongyeon?)
Hang in there for 30 seconds.
That's good.
(She shows slapstick comedy
on her way down.)
- Are you okay, Dahyun?
- That was great.
Dahyun.
Dahyun brought out
the best of this game.
(This is fun.)
I haven't seen that in a while.
(Her instinct to attack
doesn't subside.)
- So Min, you are much faster.
- Tzuyu, get So Min.
No, no. What are you doing?
(She hands in her name tag.)
I got her! I got her!
- I got paint on her name tag.
- You can slide in your hand...
- since the floor is slippery.
- Kwang Soo, come on in.
Both of them are good.
(Kwang Soo gets a chance
to attack...)
Run away!
(as soon as he enters!)
(He takes big steps
with his long legs.)
- Kwang Soo is fast.
- Here comes Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
- Are we on offense?
Yes. Why are you running away?
- Yes.
(She runs away
by bouncing on her butt.)
(This master of slapstick comedy
has a bright future.)
Run away.
(He falls on his side.)
(Thanks to Kwang Soo's hard work,)
(Tzuyu is out.)
Kwang Soo, are you okay?
Tzuyu is out. Tzuyu is out.
He is scary.
(He gives a big bow.)
(The viewers find it entertaining.)
(Kwang Soo gives a lesson...)
(to the rising star
of slapstick comedy.)
Dahyun is out!
- Go.
- Go in there, Jae Suk.
Go in there, Jae Suk.
Hurry up. Kwang Soo is right there.
You need to catch Kwang Soo.
Eliminate Kwang Soo first.
- Kwang Soo is on the roll.
- Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Are we on defense?
- We are on offense.
- The other way!
Hurry up and attack him!
(My goodness!)
(He slides down the pyramid
to attack.)
Kwang Soo is running away well.
He is fast.
(He slides down
and blocks Kwang Soo.)
Jae Suk, this way.
(The positions change.)
My goodness.
Go, go. Catch him.
(Decalcomania slapstick comedy)
- His legs are too long.
- Hurry up!
Push him.
(The positions change!)
The positions changed, right?
- Yes.
- Did it change?
(The tables have turned.)
(Jae Suk paints his face.)
The positions changed.
(Se Chan quickly joins.)
Put your hand under his back.
Come on.
I touched it.
- Kwang Soo is out.
- He did it.
We are on defense now.
(Nayeon is the only member left.)
Nayeon, attack!
Attack.
Nayeon, I am sorry!
(Look at his face.)
Nayeon, we need to place first.
(I am scared.)
- Nayeon.
- Come on.
Kwang Soo.
Run away! Run away!
(Take this!)
(They create wind with their butts.)
Okay. We did it.
I am scared.
Jae Suk's team wins
the first round.
Okay.
We are up next.
Sana and Jihyo's team
will attack first.
The two members...
She is so scary.
- No, one member goes in at a time.
- She is scary.
Jihyo is so scary.
(Just you wait.)
Let's go.
Let's begin. Get ready. Set.
(The 2nd round starts.)
(Both teams move to the top.)
- They are going up.
- Why is Jihyo so fast?
Jihyo is so fast.
(Ji Hyo and Chaeyoung
hurriedly run away.)
Jihyo.
Ji Hyo is out!
(She slides down...)
(and quickly paints
Ji Hyo's name tag!)
You are doing great!
- She is incredible.
- Go in there.
Go in there, Momo.
Go in there. Go in there, Momo.
(Momo's team will attack now.)
(Jihyo was chasing after Chaeyoung.)
Get her. Go this way, Momo.
- Get her.
- Go this way.
Over there.
(The baby beasts have a face-off.)
Get her.
I got her!
- Really? Did it get on my name tag?
- Jihyo is out.
- Jihyo was fast.
- Go in there.
Do I go in there?
- Get him.
- Do I need to run away?
Run away, Jong Kook.
- Did Jong Kook enter already?
Jong Kook is fast.
(Suk Jin's team will attack now.)
- Attack.
- Run away!
Run away!
(The final boss
makes everyone panic.)
What is Chaeyoung doing?
- Let's go to the final round.
- I am sorry.
- No!
- Chaeyoung is out.
Chaeyoung is out.
Take her out.
- There you go.
- Good job.
Let's go to the final round.
This is the last batch already.
Did Momo go in?
(Momo's team will attack now!)
Corner him.
- Corner him.
Who is out?
Look at Jong Kook.
You need to take Jong Kook out
right now.
- My goodness.
- Mina, I am sorry.
This is your last chance.
Mina, I am sorry.
(Slipping)
(Mina spots a chance!)
She did it!
(Will Mina's attack be successful?)
Mina, I am sorry.
(Jong Kook is out.)
Jong Kook is out.
- Jong Kook is out.
- Jong Kook, what was that?
Mina, good job.
(The positions change
as Suk Jin enter!)
Are we attacking now?
Mina, be careful.
Be careful.
(Falling down)
(His weak legs
made people shed tears.)
(His arms are even weaker.)
Mina, hang in there.
She will beat Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin and Mina have
a fierce match.)
(Slipping)
Suk Jin.
(It's Mina's turn to attack.)
Look at Suk Jin.
- Attack!
- Suk Jin is so fast.
- That's hilarious.
- Suk Jin can crawl so fast.
That's cute.
(Crawling on four
helps Suk Jin move faster.)
Suk Jin is so fast.
Suk Jin is out.
- That was hilarious.
- Suk Jin, what was that?
That was hilarious.
(Sana is the last member
of Team Suk Jin.)
- She's going up.
- Sana, it's your turn to attack!
(It's Sana's turn to attack.)
- She's fast.
You can do this. Be careful.
- No!
- Run away.
- Slide!
- Haha is out.
(A jump shot)
(Haha is out.)
Haha is out.
- Go, Sana!
- Incredible!
Will Sana save us?
(If Sana eliminates Mina,
Team Suk Jin will win.)
Why is she so fast?
(Sana, the predator on the Styrofoam
pyramid, charges at Mina.)
(Will she eliminate Mina...)
Will Sana save us?
(and dramatically
turn the game around?)
Sana will...
(Touch!)
Will Sana save us?
- Mina is out.
We won!
- Sana!
- Sana saved us!
- Yes!
(Sana made up for
Suk Jin's lousy performance.)
- Sana saved them.
- Unbelievable.
Let's start
the third-place match now.
Team Haha will attack first.
(Team Momo attacks first.)
Kwang Soo, come over here.
Hey, what's that?
Why are you wearing your name tag
on the front?
(So Min is wearing her name tag
on the front?)
(What's wrong?)
- So Min.
- Don't do that!
- Go ahead and rip it off.
- What are you doing?
She hasn't changed a bit.
- She's even meaner now.
- She's become even weirder.
- Wear it on the back.
- You can't do that.
While she was away from the show...
What happened to her?
Chaeyoung is out.
Song Ji Hyo is out.
Momo is out.
Go in, Nayeon.
What am I supposed to do?
- Run away.
- You're on defense.
- Attack!
- You're on offense.
- Haha!
- Yes?
Go away.
(Nayeon hit Haha?)
(Haha is hit on the head.)
She hit me.
You're pathetic.
Haha, you're...
- You're pathetic.
- Run away!
(Jeongyeon eliminates Mina.)
Run away!
(Haha, left alone,
is determined to win.)
Jeongyeon is out!
- Am I out?
- Haha is pathetic.
Kick him!
(Following Jong Kook's advice,
Nayeon uses her feet.)
Haha!
(A proper low kick)
He told me to kick you.
Jong Kook told me to kick you.
- He told me to kick you.
- Rip off his name tag!
(She's laughing so hard
that she can't breathe.)
Hey! Timeout!
His big toe got in!
I had no idea.
(Shameless)
That's hilarious.
Look at Kwang Soo's face.
I can't believe him.
- Haha, you're still in the game.
- Let's do this!
- Let's attack!
- We're attacking now.
Attack! Get him!
(Kwang Soo slides down
with a blank look on his face.)
- Okay!
- Haha is out.
(Haha is out.)
(An angry headlock)
We won!
- We won!
- We're in third place.
Team Haha is at the bottom.
They're at the bottom.
- Let's start the finals!
- It's the finals.
- Let's win!
- Let's do this.
You guys are attacking first.
- We are?
- Yes.
- We're attacking first? Okay.
- We're attacking first.
Ready.
(We have to win 1st place.)
Get set.
(The finals...)
(start.)
Slowly. 30 seconds is short.
(They're aggressive
from the beginning.)
Way to go, Sana!
- Run away!
- Go, Sana!
- Sana is so good.
- Way to go!
- Sana is amazing.
- Okay!
- Sana is running!
- Nice!
(The pyramid is extremely slippery.)
How can she...
No!
- This way!
- My gosh!
- Hold on.
- Be careful.
You're not out yet.
- Tzuyu!
- Attack!
- No!
- Gosh.
Dahyun.
(Dahyun slides down,
and Sana runs down.)
Dahyun is out.
(Se Chan goes in.)
Run away. Don't attack yet.
- Tzuyu!
We're going to win.
When Tzuyu is out...
(They did touch
Tzuyu's name tag, but...)
- I touched it!
- The whistle was blown first.
- Wait!
- Tzuyu is not out.
- She's not out.
- Why not?
- The whistle was blown first.
- Don't attack yet.
- Hey, not yet!
- It hasn't started.
We were talking. You should wait.
- Why...
- Why are you angry?
- Why is he so serious?
- Why is he angry?
Why is he so bossy?
Why are you angry?
- I mean...
- Why are you so bossy?
- We were deciding if she was out.
- Why are you angry?
- He looked so serious.
Of course, I'm angry.
You shouldn't have approached her
at that moment, you punk.
Why...
Why are you so serious?
What's with you?
- Let's continue.
- All right.
You shouldn't have hit her
while we were talking.
Team White is on offense.
Okay. Tzuyu is still in the game.
Let's go.
Ready, go.
- Nice!
- There you go.
- Hey.
- Se Chan.
- Go up! Sana is so good.
- There you go.
(The pyramid is my playground.)
Look at them.
(Sliding)
(Jihyo barely saves herself.)
(But Se Chan slides down too.)
- Kick him!
- She's out.
Jihyo is out.
Jihyo was incredible.
Should I go in?
- Go in!
- Go, Tzuyu!
- Tzuyu, you're on defense.
- Run!
(Jong Kook eliminates Tzuyu
right away.)
- Tzuyu, you're on defense.
- Run!
Tzuyu is out.
- Jae Suk, come in!
- It's my turn.
You can do this!
(Just when Jae Suk and Se Chan
are pushed into a corner...)
The positions have been changed!
(I have to get to the top.)
We have to get to the top!
We have to...
(Jong Kook kicks everyone away
from the top.)
Way to go!
This is unfair.
- They can't do anything.
- They won't get to the top.
- Way to go!
- We want to go up.
We have to get to the top.
Nice!
(Jong Kook Fortress)
Gosh.
That's so unfair.
(They keep rolling down
the pyramid.)
We're going to win!
Gosh, this is not okay.
(I've been waiting for this moment.)
Hold on!
From the other direction, Sana.
Attack from the other direction,
Sana.
- From the other direction.
- They're surrounded.
(Sana tries to intercept Se Chan.)
- It's over.
- She caught him.
(But she fails.)
She failed.
- Am I out?
- No.
- No?
(Jong Kook's target changes
from Jae Suk to Se Chan.)
(The whistle blows again.)
(Jumping down)
(His eyes, nostrils, and mouth
open wide.)
Jong Kook!
(Jong Kook is surrounded.)
(What should I do?)
Gosh.
I can't believe this.
(The airplane takes off.)
(Where are you going, sir?)
Good job.
(The customer is
200 percent satisfied.)
Not even Ji Ho does that anymore.
Good job.
(The airplane takes off again.)
(Fly with Jong Kook Air.)
Good job.
- Let's run away.
- Go away.
Change!
(They're all exhausted,
and it's time to change positions.)
This is hilarious.
(They compete
to get to the top first.)
She's getting him.
(Jae Suk is eliminated
while catching his breath.)
(The last survivor, Se Chan,
is exhausted too.)
(Se Chan is out.)
We won!
Team Gray wins!
(Team Suk Jin wins!)
I won without even playing.
I've only played airplane
with my nephews before.
This is humiliating.
Everyone,
according to
the final mission results,
Team Suk Jin wins 500 dollars.
500 dollars? We won 500 dollars!
Team Dahyun wins 300 dollars.
(Team Dahyun, in 2nd place,
wins 300 dollars.)
Team So Min wins 100 dollars.
(Team So Min, in 3rd place,
wins 100 dollars.)
Lastly, Team Momo wins...
minus 200 dollars.
- Oh, my gosh.
- 200 dollars?
- Minus 200 dollars.
- We won 100 dollars.
Please distribute the money.
(The money is distributed.)
- I'll divide it equally.
- Really?
Doesn't it hurt?
Dahyun, I trust you.
You can trust me.
Do you want to win prizes?
Sana and Jihyo,
do you want to win prizes?
- That'd be nice.
- Of course.
(That goes without saying.)
I don't...
expect anything from him.
I'll be different this time.
As the oldest member... Of course.
The top three might come
from our team.
If the money is distributed
in the right way...
Suk Jin spent too much money.
Haha, pay me back.
Are you going to pay me back or not?
I'm sorry.
(Shameless)
Then I have a negative amount.
Let me announce how the money
will be distributed in this round.
Suk Jin is giving...
300 dollars to Jong Kook
and 200 dollars to himself.
What? Really?
Why?
He doesn't want to get in trouble.
Suk Jin doesn't want to
get in trouble with Jong Kook.
- So Min is giving...
- I had no choice.
50 dollars to herself,
20 dollars each
to Nayeon and Jeongyeon,
and 10 dollars to Kwang Soo.
- That's not bad.
- Right?
- I...
- That's pretty fair.
- That's nice of her.
- Next up is Dahyun.
- Our captain, Dahyun.
- It'll be simple.
She's giving 70 dollars each
to Jae Suk and Se Chan...
and 80 dollars each
to Dahyun and Tzuyu.
- That's not bad.
- Unbelievable.
- What is this?
- I like it.
- Se Chan.
- That's enough.
That's more than enough.
Why is this team so peaceful?
Captain Momo got...
minus 200 dollars.
It all goes to Haha.
(Haha gets minus 200 dollars.)
It all goes to Haha?
- Seriously...
- Haha gets minus 200 dollars?
- She's very consistent.
- Gosh.
- She's incredible.
- She's unbelievable.
- Momo is amazing.
- I'm sorry.
If Haha gets minus 200 dollars...
- He'll definitely be penalized.
- Definitely.
All right.
Nayeon has paid Se Chan back
200 dollars.
Se Chan also gets 50 dollars
in interest.
So Min borrowed money
from Jae Suk and Kwang Soo,
but she can pay back
only one person.
And she chose to pay back Jae Suk.
- What about Kwang Soo?
- What happens to me?
Jae Suk gets 30 dollars
in interest.
And we'll deduct the deficit
from Kwang Soo's money.
What?
- What do you mean?
- I had...
- no other way.
- You're going to deduct 200?
Haha owed Suk Jin 300.
- He can't pay it back.
- I have to pay it back.
- 300 dollars?
- Yes.
- Why did you lend him so much?
- I might get the penalty.
First, I'll reveal prizes...
- perfect for the summer.
- That sounds great.
I wonder what it is.
It feels cool already.
Third place gets a circulator,
second place gets
a portable refrigerator,
and first place gets a wine cooler.
It's a wine cooler.
It's a cooler.
- Is that for wine?
- You're giving these away?
I have the results.
Top five will win prizes,
and the lowest three
will get penalties.
- 1st place is...
- 1st place.
Se Chan with 340 dollars.
Really?
That's awesome.
- I get to have a wine cooler?
- You don't even drink wine.
You'll put kimchi in there.
- I'll put something in it.
- He doesn't drink wine.
Am I in first place?
If Haha paid me back,
I would have been in first place.
That's true.
Second place is...
Jae Suk with 320 dollars.
Jae Suk. What happened to our team?
Third place is Tzuyu
with 310 dollars.
(3rd place is Tzuyu.)
Fourth place is Dahyun
with 300 dollars.
(4th place is Dahyun.)
We took it all.
- Thank you.
What happened to them?
Why did they have so much money?
Besides the harmonious team,
there's one other person
getting a prize.
- Is it Momo?
- It's Suk Jin with 270 dollars.
Sir.
Congratulations, Mr. Jee.
- Where did you get 270 dollars?
- Do I have 270?
Sixth place was a tie.
With 100 dollars,
Sana and Jihyo.
(Sana and Jihyo tied in 6th place.)
It still feels good.
I'll give you the fan. Take it.
- It's okay.
- It's okay. We don't need it.
Please take it.
Tied in eighth place were...
Mina and Nayeon with 60 dollars.
- Nayeon.
- How?
- Chaeyoung had 50 dollars.
- Chaeyoung.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo had 40.
I got 40?
Jeongyeon had 30.
There are four people left.
Momo, Kwang Soo, So Min, and Haha.
Three of you are getting penalties.
In the last place is...
Haha with minus 290 dollars.
I'm sorry, Mr. Jee.
- It's your fault.
- I'm sorry.
16th place.
Momo, you have to join me.
So Min with minus 200 dollars.
(16th place So Min will also be
getting the penalty.)
Am I exempt?
(She misheard.)
- You're getting the penalty.
- It's a penalty.
(You're wrong.)
Okay!
- What's wrong with her?
- I thought I was exempt.
- So Min, that includes you.
We have 14th and 15th places left.
- What happened?
- 14th place is exempt.
Who's exempt then?
1 person has minus 160,
and the other person has minus 170.
- Okay, it's a 10-dollar difference.
- My gosh.
In 14th place
with minus 160 dollars is...
Congratulations,
Momo.
- Count again!
- Okay.
- Congratulations, Momo.
- You did great.
Is it because she got 10 dollars
near the end?
That's true.
- You saved her.
- Let's do the penalties.
- What is it?
- What's the penalty?
- What do they do?
- Here's today's penalty.
There are 3 buckets.
1 contains flower petals,
one contains water, and
the last one contains black paint.
This is insane.
Please choose a number randomly.
Let Momo choose for me.
Number two.
Number two? Okay.
- Kwang Soo, I'll choose yours.
- Okay.
Number three for Kwang Soo.
I want...
number three.
- Do rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay, we'll get the penalty
in this order.
1, 2, 3, okay?
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
- I'm sorry.
- One,
- It's okay.
- two...
- This is not me.
Three.
Flower petals!
What?
(Black and white)
- So Min.
My gosh!
- Why is it always you?
- So Min.
- Why did you choose that one?
- Wipe your eyes.
Why did you choose that one?
I said I wanted number three!
It was great seeing all of you
after a while.
TWICE, please come to the middle.
Let's hear what Momo has to say.
- Momo?
- Yes.
I'm sorry to his fans.
That's a relief.
I don't have too many fans.
- Hey.
- What?
What are you talking about?
We'll do our best
with our new song "More and More",
so please check it out
and send lots of love.
Also, Running Man was so much fun.
See you again!
- Thank you.
(We would like to thank TWICE
for joining us today.)
(Running Man
convenience store is open.)
(4 store managers are here to
protect the convenience store.)
(Ji Chang Wook, Kim Yoo Jung,
Han Sunhwa, Do Sang Woo)
(An intense competition to obtain
the best convenience store items!)
(All of a sudden,)
(somebody is screaming
inside the convenience store.)
(It's a secret robbery...)
(away from the eyes
of the store managers!)
(They must steal the hot items
without anybody finding out!)
(Their territory tightens.)
(Those who try to steal
the hot items,)
(and those who are ready
for new deals)
(Their fates are
in their own hands now.)
(The temptations can come any time.
They cannot let their guards down!)
(A secret deal from the broker.
What will be the result?)
(Secret Broker Race:
Hot Items from Convenience Store)