- Hello.
- Hi.
- My goodness.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- We're filming at a fancy building.
- Hello.
- This is a cute building.
- Gosh.
- Seriously.
- I'd love to come with my family.
Right. The bread smells
really good downstairs.
- It's not product placement.
- This isn't product placement.
- It's not?
- No.
- You should have told us.
- It's still pretty.
We came up with the lines ourselves.
- You should've told us in advance.
- Hello.
- Suk Jin.
- My gosh.
Suk Jin, is this
one of your buildings?
(Suk Jin enters as
if he owns the place.)
Suk Jin, is this
one of your buildings?
Are you the CEO?
- I didn't know it was all set up.
- Yes.
- I thought you were the CEO.
- I had no idea.
Here comes
the recipient of the award.
- Yu San Seul!
- The Rookie Award.
- The Grand Award from SBS.
- Thank you.
- The Rookie Award from MBC.
He won both the Grand Award
and the Rookie Award.
I didn't expect it at all, but I won
the Rookie Award yesterday.
With that, I managed to win
awards from every category.
- No, you need one more award.
- Good for you.
(Is there an award
Jae Suk still needs to win?)
- Which award is that?
- The SNS Star Award.
(It's the award Kwang Soo won.)
- There's an award I really want.
- That's not from SBS.
- What is it?
- The Chungjungone Award.
(Jae Suk wants
the Chungjungone Award.)
Why?
- That award?
- No one ever heard of my awards.
Thank you.
The Chungjungone Award.
Jong Kook won
the Top Excellence Award.
(Jong Kook won
the Top Excellence Award.)
- That was his first.
- Congratulations.
Se Chan won
the Excellence Award too.
- Right.
- Gosh.
- But I...
- Yes.
- You didn't cry.
- Right.
Your girlfriend cried,
but you didn't.
- But...
- My girlfriend?
(It looked like
So Min was wiping her tears.)
- Did you cry?
- But Jae Suk,
I'll tell you what Se Chan told me
after he got drunk at the party.
- What did he say?
- He got drunk and told me this.
He told me that
he would follow his heart...
and do whatever he wants to So Min.
(He would follow his heart
and do whatever he wants to So Min.)
(He'll follow his heart?)
I'm serious. I swear.
- Don't lie.
- I'm serious.
- There you go again.
- I swear.
- Stop forcing them.
- I can't believe this.
- Don't force it.
- Right.
- Since we all won big awards...
- That's right.
even before our 10th anniversary
at the year-end awards ceremony,
we'd like to say
thank you once again.
- Thank you.
- So you got a coffee truck.
- Yes.
- Right.
- It was from the show.
- Thank you.
- Who sent the truck?
Everyone on the show?
- All of us did?
- But no one knows who sent it.
- Just be quiet.
- We won't talk about this?
I sent the truck, but I sent it
under the name of the show.
- Shouldn't we all pay for it?
- Hey.
- Send him 200 dollars.
- Should we give you 200 dollars?
- Wait, no one knew about this?
- Wire him 200 dollars.
(Wait, no one knew about this?)
- I had no idea.
- No.
- I didn't know.
I was so grateful.
- It was from just you?
- Yes.
You should have told us at least.
When I thanked them,
they didn't say anything about this.
It didn't come from one person.
We all sent him the truck.
- Right. We got the truck.
- Yes.
(Anyway, thank you.)
Se Chan went to Jong Kook's concert.
- You were on stage for 19 minutes?
- 19 minutes?
- You were there for 19 minutes?
- So...
- 19 minutes?
- It was more than 19 minutes.
If you only count the soundtrack,
it ran for 19 minutes.
If you combine acts here and there,
it's about 25 minutes.
- Wait.
- I thought it was my concert.
- I was flustered too.
- When he walks around,
he talks to himself.
I thought he was possessed.
You were practicing singing.
- Se Chan is Jong Kook's butler.
- I had no time.
Yes, I'm practically his butler.
Guys who used
to be his sidekick are...
- Haha and Kwang Soo.
- Haha.
- They can't do it anymore.
- When he grows up,
- I'll let him go.
- You will.
- Hang in there more.
- Yes, sir.
Just like you get discharged
from the army,
you get discharged from me too.
(He can be discharged
from his position.)
- Is it two years or longer?
- Yes.
- There's a time limit.
- I see.
Hey, you need to get out of there.
Before we start the race,
some guests will be
joining you today.
We've invited popular stars
who are expected...
- to have a great year in 2020.
- Popular stars.
- Please come on out.
- Come on out. Who are the guests?
- Isn't that Sae Rok?
- She's coming up the stairs.
- Hello.
- Gosh, Sae Rok.
- It's been a while.
(Keum Sae Rok:
She'll shine even more in 2020.)
(She ruled the movie industry
with her unique performance.)
(Last time, she showed
her unique charms on the show.)
(She made everyone
burst into laughter.)
(What kind of performance
will the rising star put on today?)
- It was for the orientation trip.
- Right.
(And another guest enters.)
- She worked with Kwang Soo.
- Ju Young.
- My gosh.
- Hello.
- Hi.
It's you today? Gosh.
(A new star in the movie industry,
Lee Ju Young)
(This scene-stealer grabbed
people's attention in "Believer".)
(She's friends with Kwang Soo
as they were in the same drama.)
- Hello.
- Come this way, Ju Young.
- She's the same age as Kwang Soo.
- Hi.
- Gosh.
- Nice to meet you.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Your hair grew a lot.
- It's been a while, Ju Young.
- Yes.
I thought
she was Kwang Soo's sister.
- Why?
- You resemble each other.
- You look alike when you smile.
- We get that often.
- She resembles him when she smiles.
- Yes.
Let us bring in one more guest.
Who is it?
- Who is it?
- Hello.
(Chorong of Apink:
She always shows us new charms.)
(Lovely Chorong helped
Running Man throw a great party.)
- It's been a while.
- Chorong.
(It's been a while
since the fan-meet.)
Anyway, she's joining us too.
- We have one last guest.
- There's more?
I just got the script.
(He's about to introduce the guest.)
What is it?
(What? Why are they laughing?)
(Who is the guest?)
It's Kang Han Na.
- Han Na.
- Hey.
(Han Na: She's family now.)
(Giving her a warm welcome)
- Yes, you're here.
- Wait.
- Han Na.
- Did you know who was coming?
- We didn't know.
- Hello.
- Well, she's...
- She's not a guest anymore.
- Han Na.
- Will she join us in the end?
- This is great.
No, stand in the middle.
- Han Na.
- You dyed your hair.
Your strategy is pretty good.
What strategy?
Are you trying
to sneak into the show?
- In a casual way?
- Very smoothly.
Your plan is to join us
among these four guests...
like you're part of the cast.
- Just like that. It'd be great.
- Yes.
These four guests will join us
today. Nice to meet you.
(4 guests who will have
a better year in 2020 are here.)
- Nice!
Let's say hello to each guest.
I heard that you and Sae Rok
are very close.
- Yes.
- We filmed "Believer" together.
Right.
- "Believer"?
- Yes.
Sae Rok told the staff
that she joined our show...
with the guests
she wasn't close with,
so she couldn't have fun
to the fullest.
- Really?
- You said you felt awkward.
- You stood out.
- Is that true?
It was my first variety show,
so I was nervous.
This time, I told them I wanted to
join you guys with a close friend.
Sae Rok managed to get her friend on
the show in her second appearance.
(She got her friend on the show
in her second appearance.)
- She did.
- She brought Ju Young here.
- She's influential.
- She is, isn't she?
- Indeed, she is.
Suk Jin has been on the show
for 10 years,
but he has never managed
to get his friends...
- on the show.
- I've never done that.
I'm barely hanging by a thread here.
Things aren't stable
for Suk Jin either.
His spot on the show
isn't guaranteed.
Come here.
- Come here.
- You should come.
- Do you want a beating today?
- This is hilarious.
You told him to come to you.
Why did you go?
(Laughing)
- I knew he wouldn't come.
- He knew Jae Suk wouldn't come.
By the way,
Sae Rok, did you take dance lessons?
I thought I was a good dancer,
but I was terrible.
He won the TV competition,
"Dancing 9."
I worked on "The Fiery Priest"
with Um Mun Suk.
- Mun Suk?
- Jang Ryong.
I had a one-day lesson from Mun Suk.
Can you show us?
- Yes. But I'm really bad.
- Give her a round of applause.
- This only involved my shoulders.
- That's great.
- Great.
- I can't wait.
Only your shoulders will move?
- Only her shoulders?
- Right.
- Is it something like this?
(The music starts right away.)
- She startled me.
- What was that?
Isn't this "Bad Guy"?
- Yes, "Bad Guy".
- "Bad Guy".
(The song is "Bad Guy"
by Billie Eilish.)
She prepared a nice one.
- She was good before too.
- Yes.
(She moves lightly to the rhythm
of the heavy bass guitar.)
That's the dance she learned
from the winner of "Dancing 9."
(This is the shoulder dance
Sae Rok talked about.)
I like her facial expression.
(She's chopping the beat
with her shoulders.)
She's using her shoulders a lot.
Look at her face.
- Look at her face.
- She came determined.
(She warmed up her shoulders.)
(Her shoulder dance is in full swing
all of a sudden.)
I mean...
(Will she dislocate her shoulders?)
She came determined.
She prepared a nice one.
Gosh, Sae Rok.
Sae Rok.
(She starts again.)
(Until when will you make her
dance with her shoulders?)
Look at her face.
- She's dancing with her shoulders.
- Great.
- He taught her a good one.
- Right.
- Great.
- It's straight up shoulder dance.
This is why it's called
the shoulder dance.
- She uses her shoulders a lot.
- Great job.
- The shoulder dance.
- That was great.
(She wraps up the dance
by shaking off her shoulders.)
(She's good.)
- She's good.
- You were great.
You're good
given you learned it within a day.
- You were great.
- Wasn't that great?
- I only danced with my shoulders.
- Great.
- Ju Young.
- Yes?
- Do you want to try this? Yes.
- Me?
I'm terrible at dancing.
- You should still try it.
- Just do it with your shoulders.
I was in "Just Dance."
Right.
- It was a drama.
- It was about ballroom dancing.
- I was in that drama last year.
- Really?
- Actually...
- Can you do ballroom dancing?
I can do the cha-cha-cha.
That's great.
Can you play the song for that?
I'm really good at this.
- I'm only good at this.
- It's ballroom dancing.
- Play the music.
- I think she'll be good at it.
She took lessons, right?
Gosh, Ju Young.
(The music starts.)
She did this in her drama.
(It's a fancy start
like her confidence.)
(She carefully takes her steps
as if she's walking on thin ice.)
(But...)
(She's...)
(Something is off.)
(Why is she suddenly kicking?)
There it is.
Wait, I don't think
she's an expert at it.
- I mean...
- She looks stiff.
- She's good, but it's weird.
- Something seems off.
It looks like...
a wooden toll is dancing.
Right.
(She reminds them
of a broken marionette.)
(She safely finishes her dance
without hurting herself.)
- She's good, but it's weird.
- This was so random.
Well done.
- For now...
- Wasn't I good?
Here's what I liked about her dance.
I liked stiff body rolls.
(That's what Jae Suk likes.)
And when she did this move,
she staggered.
- That was great.
- She staggered.
- It was strange.
- That was great.
Give a round of applause
to these actresses.
(Like best friends, both of them
prepared unique dance routines.)
All right. Next, we have Chorong.
(It's time to interview Chorong.)
It's time to party, Chorong
We talked about this before.
She learned hapkido for eight years.
- Hapkido? For eight years?
- So...
she's very good at martial arts.
Can you demonstrate for us?
Instead of kicking,
- I'll show you a cartwheel.
- A cartwheel.
- She'll do the cartwheel.
- That's not an easy move.
- Warm up first. Are you okay?
- What?
You should warm up first.
(Flexible)
You know,
there are stances in hapkido.
- Can you show us these moves?
- What is that?
- This isn't one of them?
- That's so wrong.
- What is this?
- Isn't that what drunk old men do?
What is this?
(On the other hand,
her stance is sharp.)
Gosh, look at that.
- That's the stance.
- Did you see that?
- She can do the stance.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- But it's been...
- Has it been a while?
- a while since I tried this.
- Okay.
I'm sure your body will remember.
(She takes off her shoes.)
- My gosh.
- What?
That was no joke.
- Was that a one-handed cartwheel?
- Hey.
It was a one-handed cartwheel,
right?
You did it with one hand.
I had no idea that you'd do this.
- Let me try again.
- She's really good.
The first was great.
I just thought she was going
to do a regular one.
- My gosh.
- She's got the pose.
(She puts only one hand
on the floor.)
With just one hand.
(And she comes back up.)
(A perfect cartwheel)
(Impressed)
You can do this?
- That was real.
- Chorong.
- You're a hero.
- Seriously.
- That was so cool.
- That's so cool.
- Great.
Please give a round
of applause to Chorong.
We don't need
to interview Han Na.
- You see,
- We're family now.
- we've interviewed her often.
- It's not necessary.
- She's a radio host.
- We don't need to interview her.
- You're a radio host?
- Aren't you a radio host?
- That's right.
- A radio host?
(She became a radio host.)
(So Min was her first guest.)
It's called "Raise the Volume."
- "Raise the Volume"?
- Yes.
Have you been practicing?
I wanted to ask Suk Jin
for some tips.
- A radio host should feel...
- What should I do?
comfortable.
- You shouldn't be pressured.
- He's right.
Relax.
Like he said,
he was very relaxed...
when he was a radio host.
And that's how he quit.
(He did exactly what he just said.)
(He attacks him with the truth.)
That's right.
You need to feel pressured
to do well.
Don't talk too sternly
as if you're on the news.
- Han Na.
- Should I not?
- Should I not feel pressured?
- Talk as if...
- you're talking to a friend...
- A friend?
- or a girlfriend.
- He was reprimanded for that.
The guests weren't his friends.
But he was too comfortable
with them.
- They were offended.
- Right.
- They weren't his friends.
All right. These four guests...
have joined us.
Give them a round of applause.
(Welcome to our show!)
Welcome.
For today's race, you need to have
great bonds with your partners.
- Let's decide on your partners.
- Partners?
It will be called Here I Am.
A male member will sit
with his back toward the females.
He will say his ideal type.
If you think you're that type
or just interested,
you can come up
and try to become his partner.
The male will hand the doll
to the female of his choice.
I'm going to pick the woman
who shows interest in me.
The men will be here,
and the women will be over there.
This is similar to that show.
- "Match Made from Above".
There's no need to rush.
- All the men are the same.
- We're the same?
Come on.
- We're just playing a game.
- That's right.
I like this.
- It's just a game.
- I'm the center of attention.
- Se Chan, go first.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Hey.
You only look good
because you're among us.
Right.
- You look handsome.
- This is nice.
All right.
I don't ask for much.
I'd like someone who has
a pretty wink to come up.
- Why?
- Because winking is...
- It's not time yet.
- Hey, hey.
I'd like someone who has
a pretty wink to come up.
(Are you calling for me?)
(So Min approaches him.)
- Hold on.
- No.
Do you remember what color
the woman you're interested in...
is wearing?
- What about her hairstyle?
- Her hairstyle?
- To be frank,
- Bob cut?
- I love bob cuts.
- Really?
Do you?
- It would be nice...
- Bob cuts?
if someone with a bob cut
came out.
You like bob cuts.
(She grabs her hair.)
- Because of what you said...
- What about a bob cut...
but with her hair tied?
- What about that?
- I don't like that.
- You don't?
- No.
I like hair that's this long.
- A bob cut.
- You like bob cuts?
Many of them have that hairstyle.
On the count of three,
look behind you.
One,
two,
three.
(Her heart flutters
just by watching them.)
Three.
I knew it.
(Hi, Se Chan.)
(I have a pretty wink
and a bob cut.)
(He sees her winking...)
(and bursts into laughter.)
- He loves it.
- Are you just pretending?
I'm confused too.
Decide whether or not
you're going to give her that doll.
I don't have to give it?
(Oh, right.)
(He can choose.)
Then I'll wait a bit more.
(He plays hard to get.)
(She's irritated.)
- What?
- I'll wait.
You will?
First, we'll count.
One...
- Let me see her wink.
- Okay.
- You do that.
- I think...
- 1, 2, 3.
- She's going to wink.
(She tries to win his heart
by winking at him.)
- 1, 2, 3.
- She's going to wink.
(Giggling)
You're enjoying this.
He's right. We know you like her.
Don't pretend like you don't.
- One...
- Why are you blushing?
Didn't you say that
you'd listen to your heart?
To whom does your heart belong?
1, 2, 3.
(To whom does his heart belong?)
(For whom does his heart beat?)
I'll listen to my heart.
(His heart calls out to So Min.)
- What is going on?
- What is this?
(What is going on?)
- It's unbelievable.
- What is this?
Don't do this! This is boring!
- Hey!
- It's boring for her.
- So Min doesn't like it.
- Why are you mad at me?
- I don't like this.
- You had a pretty wink.
- It was nice.
- By the way...
- He was serious.
- What's going on here?
What is this? Are you playing
hard to get?
We have no idea
what's going on between them.
- I was joking around,
- I'm serious. What's with them?
- but he actually chose me.
- She had a pretty wink.
You were bashing him
for giving you the doll,
- but you seemed really happy.
- He gave it to you for fun.
It looked like
you were being proposed to.
(It looked like
she was being proposed to.)
(Her heart fluttered.)
(She was smiling.)
- Let's do this. Okay.
- Okay.
- Come over here.
- What? You're partners?
- Yes, we are.
- Of course, they are.
- Really?
- Do you not get this?
I do.
Do you know where we are?
- Do you?
I know.
This really feels like
"Match Made from Above."
- Right.
- Many of them actually dated.
(He finds his target.)
- After shooting those...
- There were actual couples.
matchmaking programs,
- some dated in real life.
- Right.
Right.
(I'm talking about you.)
What?
- That was out of the blue.
- Talk, will you?
- Me?
- Weren't you one of them?
What?
(He fails to make him spill.)
- What are you talking about?
- I don't know the story.
I only focused on working.
- Really?
- Of course.
I can vouch for Jae Suk.
- He's good at matchmaking.
- I am.
My wife and I broke up back then,
but he helped us get back together.
- That's how we got married.
- That's right.
That's why I cut ties with him
for two years.
We had broken up for good.
What would that make of Hyun Woo?
(Whispering)
I'm just joking around.
Dad's just joking.
- Whom are you pointing at?
- You're the fruit of our love.
(Hyun Woo, you're the fruit
of our love.)
He is?
- You know you are, right?
- He's the fruit of your love?
(He can relate to him
as a father himself.)
- You are.
- He's the fruit?
Your mom and dad loved
each other so much.
Hyun Woo is the fruit of their love
- Next is Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- I bet he's popular.
- It's been a while.
He was always matched with women.
- He used to be.
- Right.
But he's taking a break for now.
- It's a long break.
- Yes.
What's your ideal type?
I'd like someone who's fun
to come out.
Right.
I want us to have similar humor.
- That's important.
- All right.
- Come out if you're fun...
- I'm not fun.
and think you two
have similar humor.
Come out if your friends
have told you that you're fun.
Let's begin.
1, 2, 3.
(No one's coming out.)
- This is unexpected.
(Have I been taking a break
for too long?)
It seems like those
who are coming out right now...
- Right.
- want to be matched with him.
- Jong Kook.
- What is this?
(The others come out as well.)
This is it.
- I loved my friend's friend
- They have come out.
From the way I see it,
the lady who came later...
- is feeling competitive.
- Right.
That's the only explanation.
Right. It's obvious.
(Sae Rok and her friend, Ju Young,
have both come out.)
- This is unexpected.
- Really?
- 1, 2, 3.
- I'm surprised.
(They have chosen
love over friendship.)
Three.
Hold on a minute.
(He's flustered and doesn't know
what to do.)
- This is unbelievable.
- Two of them have come out.
- Goodness, Jong Kook.
- You two are close.
Fill me up with love
- I don't know what to do.
- Kim Jong Kook.
I'm glad that they came out.
- Why did you come out?
- Why?
I wanted to win.
So this is strictly business?
- And you, Sae Rok?
- Did I make a mistake?
I think if we're partners,
we'll have fun and win.
And I personally really like him.
I have a question.
What do you think about Ju Young?
- Is she funny?
- I don't think she's fun.
(She gives a cold reply.)
(Shocked)
- You're so mean.
- Did you hear that?
- This is hilarious.
- We're not close.
In your opinion,
is she funny or not?
- Not even a bit.
- Not even a bit?
(She counterattacks.)
- This is a competition.
- How fascinating.
If you're both boring...
(Han Na stands up.)
- Han Na stood up.
- Han Na's here.
- What was that?
- She's here.
(She mimics her.)
(She tries to be interesting
by mimicking her.)
- I'm fun. No? Don't go?
- What?
- Come out.
- Go?
- What took you so long?
- Bring your cushion.
- I'll be back.
- Is he interested in Han Na?
- Look at his face.
- I think he is.
He winked at her
and told her to come out.
He was giving me a sign.
You should've come out sooner.
(Will these two become a couple?)
He gave you a sign.
However, you came out
after the time was up,
- so you need to go back.
- Really?
(It's a shame.)
She was too late.
- She needs to follow the rules.
- She was too late.
- You must.
She needs to follow the rules.
- She was too late.
- What does that make me?
- She's too late. I'm sorry.
- I see.
- I was late.
- All right, then.
They don't look too happy.
- This is your last chance.
- By the way,
how did Jong Kook look
when Han Na came out?
That's enough!
(Shut that mouth of yours.)
- That's enough!
- He just hit you.
- Stop it.
- He flew back.
- You just got hit.
- I'm fine.
- He flew.
- What are you talking about?
- Know when to stop.
- He hit you.
I don't think he hit me,
so why are you saying he did?
- Exactly. It's what you believe.
- Right.
To each his own.
You must give one of them
the doll.
Five,
four...
(Han Na lost her chance
to come out.)
(Will he choose one of them?)
- I'll protect their friendship.
- Three...
(He values loyalty.)
(But they've lost
both love and friendship.)
They dissed each other so much.
- I'd like to protect it.
- Good work.
(She returns to her place quickly.)
- By the way,
- They're flustered.
they showed different reactions.
Sae Rok returned
in a blink of an eye.
"Forget it."
"It's not like I liked you anyway."
- It's funny.
- However,
Ju Young seemed to be shocked.
Jong Kook hates it the most
when people try to win him over.
- They wanted to win me over.
- They just want your power.
- I'm not a tool.
- Exactly.
That's what slightly upset you?
I'm afraid so.
If Han Na doesn't choose you again,
it's over for you.
From what I can tell,
a rumor has spread among them.
- Exactly.
- You're doomed.
- That he's not a gentleman.
- That he's picky.
That he's the worst.
They all know that
he's not a gentleman.
- He's a dirtbag.
- Exactly.
A dirtbag.
Anyway, Suk Jin, you're up.
Here you go.
- I'll just tell you one thing.
- That isn't necessary, so sit down.
That isn't necessary.
Don't take the liberty
of doing anything.
Han Na gained fame thanks to me.
- Just sit.
- You're right.
- Right?
- That's right.
- Right.
- Just sit down.
He thinks I owe him.
- So Suk Jin is up next.
- Yes.
Who do you want as a partner?
I'd like someone feminine,
someone who doesn't get angry,
and someone who doesn't nag.
I'd also appreciate it
if she didn't mind my clumsiness.
So someone who isn't
like your wife...
(Your wife's opposite?)
Is that what I meant?
Then I said it wrong.
- I didn't mean that.
- Someone who isn't like your wife.
- That's not what I meant.
- I see.
I just want someone
who won't suddenly yell.
Forget all of
the other things he said.
He just wants someone
who doesn't get angry. 1, 2, 3.
- Please come on out.
- Gosh.
What do they find
charming about him?
Are you playing a prank on him?
No way!
This is wrong.
What's going on?
- Is this a prank?
- Is this my lucky day?
- Your lucky day?
- It sure is.
I'll speed things up before
they change their minds. 1, 2, 3.
(He can't help but exclaim.)
This is absurd.
Just how sweet are you two?
- Look at them.
- Why are you sitting like that?
She wants to look like a lady.
Can I ask why you're out here?
It's because I heard how
he made Han Na a star.
- Who?
- I wanted that.
- Because you wanted to be a star?
- That's the reason?
That's why?
- You want to be a star?
- Yes.
- She's seeing the bigger picture.
- It's a lie, you know.
Han Na achieved that all by herself.
- Say something, Han Na.
- Must I be his partner twice then?
- It was all Han Na.
- Suk Jin did nothing for her.
Han Na took care
of Suk Jin that day.
You thought he helped Han Na?
That's news to me. What do you
mean Suk Jin helped her?
Chorong, what brought you out here?
Partnering up with you
seemed less burdening.
I see.
She's approaching this
from a business standpoint.
- So...
- I mean...
She finds him easy.
I'm the one
who's choosing, you know.
I'm bad at playing games too.
- She just wants to have fun.
- I'll feel less burdened...
- to be with someone like me.
- I see.
Try to persuade me
with your gaze then.
Suk Jin's taking advantage
of the situation.
- He's having fun.
- He's enjoying this.
You have three seconds to choose.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Chorong?)
(Or Sae Rok?)
(Suk Jin chooses Sae Rok.)
- Chorong was declined.
- I'll make you a star.
I'm counting on you.
Are you an idiot?
He held Han Na back that day.
Well...
- I can't believe it.
- Exactly.
How can you be this tactless?
Han Na had to take a break
after being partnered with him.
Exactly!
I have a bad feeling about this.
- Mr. Shiny Jacket.
- Yes.
Who do you want as your partner?
- Today...
- You're dressed well today.
Anyone who wishes to only
partner up with me today...
should come forward.
So anyone who wants
to be your partner.
Come on out then.
In 1, 2, 3.
All right.
All these ladies?
- No way.
- Seriously?
Why didn't anyone
show interest in me like this?
No wonder he won the SNS Star Award.
- The winner of the SNS Star Award.
- Look at him.
- He's dressed for the occasion.
- I know.
- You're right.
- Right.
Please turned around in 1, 2, 3.
(Ju Young comes forward
for the 2nd time.)
(Kwang Soo has his hopes up.)
(But then he's disappointed.)
- What?
- Why won't you look at her?
- Who are you looking at?
- What's wrong with you?
Just look at who's in front of you.
- Don't look away.
- Don't be like that.
Ju Young, why are you out here?
I want to be a lot of fun today,
so being with someone I know...
Someone she knows.
So you only want
to be partners with him...
because you want to be funny today.
What?
So 1, 2, 3. What's your choice?
(Will Kwang Soo choose Ju Young?)
(Or will he decline her offer?)
I'll try again later.
(His pride is hurt.)
What...
Why?
What's wrong with you?
- Am I not allowed to do that?
- Why are you trying to be funny?
- I'm allowed to decline.
- Gosh.
- Ju Young.
- Stay seated.
You can stay seated.
- Drag her back.
- Ju Young...
Goodness.
What she said made me so sad.
- Why?
- She said,
"It's fine.
I'm quite popular, you know."
(Just a moment ago)
It's fine.
I'm quite popular, you know.
(It's fine.
I'm quite popular, you know.)
(Only Jae Suk heard
her lonely statement.)
No one asked her...
and no one said she wasn't popular.
- Goodness.
- Ju Young, oh, dear.
It's not because you're not popular.
Haha, you're next.
Well, just as a partner...
Why can I already see it?
- See what?
- Who you'll be teamed up with.
One of the ladies has been
passionately gazing at you.
I've never seen her
be like this before.
That gaze of hers...
It's not something
she shows every day.
- It's a first in 10 years.
- From what I can tell,
the others will have to stay back.
Remember what we said
at our team dinner?
We wished for something fresh
in the new year.
If anyone fits that bill,
please come forward.
- I think someone will.
- 1, 2, 3.
Someone new...
(Tossing)
(A fresh entrance)
That's new.
- She's here.
- That was fresh.
- But still...
- It's nice.
- You never know.
- Haha, you never know.
- Good.
- 1, 2, 3. Turn around.
(Peek-a-boo!)
(He's disgusted.)
I'll ask you one last time.
Why do you find me so charming?
Stop being this way
just because Gary's gone.
Forget about him.
Who on earth is he anyway?
Unbelievable.
- Gary?
- You've got to be kidding me.
Do you know what's more annoying?
My wife actually
acknowledges her now.
Byul, don't worry.
I'll keep him in check.
Unbelievable.
In 1, 2...
(The official couple that's
acknowledged by his wife)
(Will they welcome
a second couple on the show?)
(What's Haha's decision?)
This is your last chance.
(There you go.)
- Nice.
- This is great.
(Congratulations!)
- Of course.
- I'm glad.
- I'm happy too.
You're killing me, you know that?
Why are you doing this to me?
- Is it Jae Suk's turn next?
- Yes.
There's only one thing
I look for in a partner.
If you can't help yourself
from partying,
- then join me today.
- There's movement already.
- The ladies...
- Everyone except...
for one person is ready to party.
Their shoulders
are already bouncing.
Join me if you love partying.
In 1, 2, 3.
Go ahead.
That's all I look for in a partner.
I'm not exactly the life of a party.
Then please stay back.
- What?
- Please stay back.
(They suddenly put on the brakes.)
You shouldn't have said that.
(You shouldn't have said that.)
If you're the least bit interested
in partying...
(He corrects his condition.)
- Anyone who's interested...
- I'll lower my standard.
- So anyone who's interested?
- That's right.
Even if you aren't
the life of a party,
- if you're interested...
- That much you'll accept.
The candidates have all shown up.
All right.
(Startled)
Ju Young?
(He can't believe his eyes.)
(Ju Young openly stated
that she doesn't party.)
(I saw how you were earlier.)
But... Hold on.
(She steals the stuffed animal
away from him.)
You can't steal it.
- What about Chorong then?
- What?
Don't be like this!
Seriously. Don't be this way.
- No way.
- Don't do this.
I had no idea
Ju Young would show up.
- I...
- Why not?
Well...
I mean...
Chorong likes to party though.
- That's right.
- Right?
It's a tough choice.
All right.
(Jae Suk will now choose.)
It's my turn to choose
and I have someone in mind.
(Will he choose Ju Young who
could have the party DNA in her?)
All right.
(Who will Jae Suk choose?)
I choose Ju Young.
(He chooses
the partygoer in the making.)
- Nice!
- I choose Ju Young.
- I knew it.
- Just so you know,
- that was her third attempt.
- Chorong was rejected again.
- Gosh.
- This time,
the ladies will choose.
- Right.
- The ladies will choose this time.
I'd like to hear a cute
acrostic poem.
All right.
- To Kang Han Na.
- I once did the same...
for Jong Kook.
- That's right.
- He coldly rejected me.
(He coldly rejected me.)
(Looking adorable)
(She did her best to be his partner
in episode 472.)
(He chose Seol In Ah instead.)
(You rejected me?)
(Jong Kook,
I will never forget this.)
(He deeply regrets it.)
All right then.
It will be done to Kang Han Na.
Kang.
Kang Han Na.
- Han.
Han Na.
- Na.
- Have eyes only for me.
(Have eyes only for me.)
(Han Na, have eyes only for me.)
(I'm going to vomit.)
- No way.
- Unbelievable.
- This is hard to watch.
- Did you see what he just did?
You've got to be kidding me.
- Gosh.
- Keep that in mind then.
- Right.
- Kwang Soo, you're next.
- Sure.
- Kang.
(Kwang Soo will come up
with a poem next.)
Kang Han Na.
- What on earth?
- Look at him squirming.
- Are you kidding me?
- Han.
I'll only say this one thing.
Na.
I want to be your partner.
(I want to be your partner.)
You've got to be kidding me.
(Screaming in pain)
Why?
(He tried to look too adorable.)
(He is arrested for
bringing harm to the viewers' eyes.)
I was supposed to look cute.
(Even though
they tortured the viewers,)
(their poems were successful.)
- Have you chosen?
- Yes.
Hand the stuffed animal
to one of them.
In 1, 2, 3.
(She heads straight over to...)
And now Chorong...
(And now Chorong...)
You're allowed
to object to their partnership.
- Actually...
- Well...
- Yes?
- Actually...
(Chorong seems to have
something to say.)
(Does Jong Kook have his hopes up?)
(I...)
I'll just be partnered
with whoever's left.
(I'll just be partnered
with whoever's left.)
I'm okay with anyone left over.
Hey.
"Anyone left over."
- She said, "anyone left over."
- "Anyone left over"?
The way she said was a bit...
- "Anyone left over."
- I'm left over too.
All right.
Kwang Soo and Chorong are a team.
"Anyone left over."
That's hilarious.
That's so funny.
(Finally, all couples are decided.)
(Jae Suk and Ju Young, Se Chan
and So Min, Suk Jin and Sae Rok)
(Haha and Ji Hyo, Jong Kook and
Han Na, Kwang Soo and Chorong)
Depending on the combination
of cards held at the end,
each couple will be
either rewarded or penalized.
- The race is called Switch Cards.
- Cards?
The deck consists of pairs of
water, fire, wind, and tree cards,
which are element cards,
and two prize cards
and two penalty cards,
which are special cards.
Each member
will randomly pick one card...
and pair it with
his or her partner's.
For example, a couple with
a water card and a prize card...
wins abalone as a prize.
A couple with a water card
and a penalty card...
will be penalized
with the water cannon.
A couple with a penalty card
and a prize card...
will only be penalized.
I want abalone!
A water cannon in this weather?
After each round,
the top two couples...
get to choose a couple...
and see whether they hold
element cards or special cards.
They can also switch cards
with a member of their choice.
The couple in second place
can switch cards...
with any couple except
for the couple in first place.
After three rounds,
each couple will be...
either rewarded or penalized...
according to
their card combinations.
Come forward and pick two cards.
Are we going to pick cards?
Go to the table.
These are the only ones who may
become a couple in real life.
(So Min and Se Chan
pick cards first.)
- I hope they'll go out.
- So do I.
(Which cards did they pick?)
(Penalty)
(A water card and a penalty card
mean the water cannon.)
Good job.
I tend to be unlucky
with these things.
Let's see.
You can show your card.
(Prize, fire)
(A fire card and a prize card mean
a Korean beef bulgogi set.)
(Jae Suk holds back his smile.)
Jae Suk must have picked
a bad one.
He doesn't look happy.
- Does it show?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- What was mine?
(All couples have picked cards.)
(Card Distribution)
Let's hurry up.
- It's raining.
- Let's do that!
In the first mission,
you will compete as two teams.
This couple foot volleyball game
is called...
Foot Volleyball with You.
(Foot Volleyball with You)
- Foot Volleyball with You.
- Foot Volleyball...
with You.
Each team consists of 3 couples.
Pick 2 couples for each round.
The same foot volleyball
rules apply.
The ball has to go over the net
within three hits.
A ball is out
if it lands outside the lines.
The ball can't be hit
by the same player twice in a row.
- No two hits in a row.
- No?
These are the basic rules.
One member of each couple
will use his or her feet...
while the other will use a tool...
from the prop truck.
Once a member chooses a tool,
it can't be taken away.
We always have these special rules.
First place and second place will be
chosen from the winning team.
- Okay.
- Let's win first place.
First...
Which couple should we compete with?
(He thinks they're competing
one on one.)
Three couples become a team.
- Three couples become a team.
So we have two teams.
Oh, he got it wrong.
He thought
we were competing separately.
Is that what we're doing?
All right.
- We're divided into two teams?
- Yes.
Let's start.
(Team Unmarried versus Team Married)
- Ready.
- Avoid the bamboo wife.
- Ji Hyo.
- Get set.
(Most of them are female.)
No!
(Due to Ju Young's leg injury,
Jae Suk participates instead.)
Move!
(Han Na chooses a paddle.)
Good choice!
(Ji Hyo chooses a frying pan.)
So Min, good job!
What is So Min doing?
(What did So Min choose?)
(Huge)
- What is So Min doing?
- So Min!
Good job.
(So Min chooses a huge
air mattress.)
It's very hard.
Isn't this nice?
- Yes, this is perfect.
- Right?
(Sae Rok chooses a giant hand.)
This is the best.
- That looks nice.
- You can't change tools now.
They all look pretty good.
Here we go.
Let's go!
Should we practice?
Go. Start.
I should serve like this.
- Hey!
- Gosh.
(Kwang Soo receives the serve
with his face.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Your face...
- Kwang Soo!
- You might hurt yourself.
Are you okay?
- Kwang Soo.
- What did he do?
Are you stupid?
He's not a fool.
- Let's get started.
- The first round is important.
(The main game starts.)
- Let's start!
- Okay.
- The game starts now.
- Let's do this!
- Haha, go.
- It's mine.
(It's mine.)
(He's too short.)
(The direction was good,
but he couldn't reach it.)
- Gosh.
- Hey!
What are you doing?
- It suddenly...
- He doesn't know how short he is.
- What are you doing?
- It suddenly went up.
We were lucky.
- Yes!
- Nice!
- Did we score a point?
- We were lucky.
- Let's start again. Let's do this!
- Let's do this!
- Let's start.
- Let's go.
Relax.
I'll get it.
(Sae Rok smashes the ball
with her giant hand.)
- What are you doing?
- Way to go!
- Two.
- Calm down.
Okay!
(A cheerful full swing)
- Chorong, good job.
- Shout, "I'll get it".
- Good job, Sae Rok.
- She's good.
Good job.
She's an ace.
- Can you see my face?
- You have to say, "I'll get it".
Is So Min just standing there?
I'm playing too.
I'm doing my best.
Block the ball here.
(She chose the biggest tool,
hoping to contribute to her team.)
(But she can't even hold it up.)
(While she struggles to even
hold it, the score becomes 1 to 1.)
But...
you can hit the ball
before it bounces.
(So Min is doing her best.)
So Min is getting in the way.
(Swinging)
She's getting in our way too.
- We can't see anything.
So Min, you shouldn't
block the serve.
- Okay.
- It's so annoying.
(The game restarts
with Suk Jin's serve.)
That was accurate.
- Mine!
- That was accurate.
Okay. Go!
- Okay!
- What are you doing?
(Standing still)
- It's...
Why didn't you hit the ball?
- So Min!
- I can't do that.
- I can only block the ball.
- It's like a wall.
(I can only block the ball.)
I can only block the ball.
- Okay.
- You should hit it the second time.
We can't even see So Min's face.
We can't see you.
It's okay. Let's continue.
I'll show you.
Se Chan is laughing at you.
(The score is 1 to 2,
and Se Chan serves.)
(The air mattress finally
blocks the ball?)
(Defense is the air mattress's
only function.)
(But...)
Sae Rok!
I can't see anything!
(They lose another point.)
- It doesn't work.
- So Min.
- Yes!
- Sae Rok!
- Sae Rok is our ace.
- We don't have to do anything.
So Min.
You should just stand still.
Let's do this!
- Okay!
- There you go.
Kwang Soo, get ready.
- Kwang Soo!
- Come in!
(Kwang Soo, here you go.)
- Gosh.
- Hey!
(What?)
- Why did you do that?
- Hey!
Kwang Soo, can't you do better?
- What's with you?
- I mean...
- Why did you do that?
- Okay.
Okay.
By the way, is So Min...
on vacation?
- Are you on vacation?
- Jae Suk.
- We're all on vacation.
- Put it down.
- Is your team...
- I'm doing my best.
on vacation?
Lie down for a minute.
We can't see anything.
Lie down for just one round.
Let's play!
So Min, just a second.
She should be outside the court.
- I can finally see something.
- Let's play!
- So Min, just a second.
I can finally see you guys.
(The score is 1 to 4.
Team Married serves.)
Kwang Soo, get ready.
- Get ready.
- Good!
Kwang Soo!
Attack!
(Team Unmarried loses
another point.)
(Because of Kwang Soo's lousy pass,
his team loses a point.)
- Kwang Soo!
- He's so bad.
For Chorong to be able to hit it,
the ball should be high.
- The ball should go above the net.
- I get it now.
- He gets it now.
- Chorong can stay still.
- I can't see anything again.
- It's annoying.
- I shouldn't have chosen this.
- Move forward.
So Min, move. I can't see anything.
So Min!
(While So Min is blocking the view,)
(the other team suddenly attacks.)
I can't see anything.
(It's a mess.)
So Min!
I can't see a thing!
So Min, move.
- So Min, look at this.
- I mean...
So Min.
- Stay outside the lines.
- So Min is on our team.
- Go in only when the ball comes.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- I got it.
- I mean...
- Stay outside the lines.
Okay.
I feel sorry for So Min.
Hold on.
So Min is blocking the camera.
(Hold on.
So Min is blocking the camera.)
- Hey!
- Move!
- Go to the other side!
- I want to be on camera too.
- I want to be on camera.
- You can stay here.
(So Min is now standing
farthest away from the camera.)
The cameraman rarely
says something like that.
Stand here...
and put it on the ground.
Why did you choose this?
(Exploding)
(The air mattress was
the beginning of trouble.)
Calm down.
- Stand here.
- You can't even hold it.
You can't even hold it?
- Hold it. It's on your back.
- It's on her back.
Okay. Let's play!
(We can finally play.)
I can see everything now.
- Calm down.
- How have you been?
- The real game starts now.
- I missed you.
I can't give up.
I still can't give up.
Can we change tools?
- You can only change players.
- Okay.
- Why?
- Do you want to try?
- I want to.
- All right.
So Min, you can just stay here.
(So Min gets replaced.)
Hey!
- I haven't done anything.
- Yes, you have.
You've done a lot.
- Let's go.
- Okay!
Here we go.
- Chorong.
- Chorong, hit it!
Hit it!
(What?)
(Defensive heading)
(For once, Suk Jin scores a point.)
- Good job.
- This is so easy.
Good job.
- The ball came right to me.
- Foot volleyball is so easy.
- We'll go in now.
- Go ahead.
- Who should play?
- Kwang Soo.
- Come in.
- Can I play one round?
- Here we go.
- Let's go!
(Will Team Married be able to
sustain their momentum?)
I'll get it.
Okay.
- Hey!
- It's out.
- It's ours.
Hey!
- It's out.
- It's ours.
- You need to hit it lightly.
- Okay.
- That team...
- I got it now.
needs to send Kwang Soo away.
The biggest problem is Kwang Soo,
not So Min.
- No, no.
- I am serious.
- Kwang Soo.
- You might think that.
- Kwang Soo, you are like an X-man.
- I watched him play.
- He...
- Don't tell them that.
- What?
Ju Young said,
"Don't tell them that."
She wants to win.
She is competitive.
I will show you what I can do.
(Everyone knows that
he is a lousy player.)
(Team Unmarried has 1 point
and Team Married has 8 points.)
Let's go. I'll get it.
- Kwang Soo, use your head.
- Kwang Soo.
- Here.
- Hit it.
- Han Na!
- Okay, that's good.
(She scoops up the ball.)
Okay.
That's good.
All right!
(Dancing)
(Laughing)
That was good.
What was that?
Was that a mask dance?
Jae Suk did this.
My left foot...
You did a good job, Ji Hyo.
It was my mistake.
- Okay.
- Okay. Han Na, you are doing well.
(They improved with Han Na.
What will happen this time?)
(My goodness!)
Hey!
(Dancing)
Hey, come on out.
- My goodness.
- What was that?
He is worse than Dream.
- Come on out.
- That's it.
- Hold on.
Remember
what I have done so far, okay?
- What are you doing?
- It was a mistake.
You did the mask dance too.
(Haha is happy
to see a fellow dancer.)
Are we taking a mask dance class?
Why are we keep doing
the mask dance?
We need to do better.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
(Jong Kook serves...)
(and Jae Suk touches the ball.)
Nice serve!
(His anger explodes.)
This is no fun!
The two of you should sit out.
This is ridiculous.
Suk Jin should play.
For goodness' sake.
This won't do. Come on out.
- This won't do.
- Come on out.
- Sae Rok, you should play.
- No, no. Hold on.
I have a suggestion. From now on,
- you are out if you make a mistake.
- Come on out.
- Let's do that.
- You are out if you make a mistake.
(Team Unmarried has 4 points
and Team Married has 8 points.)
That was short.
(Team Unmarried
loses a point again.)
Someone who made a mistake
should be switched.
(This is my chance.)
Someone who made a mistake
should be switched, Jong Kook.
Ms. Bed, come over here.
- Hold on.
- I...
- You are blocking people's views.
- I want to play.
- I'm outside now for So Min.
- So Min, you can play.
- Move that signboard.
- Let's go.
Gosh, I can't see anything.
- Okay.
- Jong Kook, kick.
- Okay. That's good, So Min.
- Kick.
- That's good, So Min.
- Hold it up.
(Shouting)
Mine! Mine! Mine!
(Mine! Mine! Mine!)
I...
(He acts like
he was going to kneel.)
Sae Rok could have sent it
over the net!
Why didn't you do it?
- He pushed Sae Rok.
- He said, "Mine! Mine! Mine!"
- He pushed her and yelled, "Mine!"
I could have sent it over the net.
Hold on.
Are we a dance club?
I am a dancer!
Seriously.
(They create dance moves
of all genres.)
This is ridiculous.
- You should stand over here.
- I am sorry,
but how many people are there?
(Swarming)
- How many people are there?
- Seriously.
I am sorry.
Follow the rules, okay?
- Let's put out hands together.
- We can win.
- Sae Rok, come here.
- Let's go!
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
- What are you doing?
- Suk Jin.
- I did it from here.
- You only had to take...
- a few steps.
- I did it from here.
- Let's begin.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Okay.
That's good.
All right.
We got this.
So Min, let's go.
- Han Na, there you go!
- You are good.
(Han Na's smash)
That's good.
So Min, what are you doing? So Min!
(Help the team.)
- So Min!
- Get up!
(Take this!)
- So Min!
- Get up!
I mean...
- You have an air mattress.
- You can't kick it.
- "Take this!"
- You need to use your weapon.
- I mean...
- You should have been ready.
- Jong Kook.
- She tried to kick it.
- I can't...
- Go home and lie down on a bed.
I can't control it as I want.
I can't...
- Okay. I will try harder.
- We are doing very well.
- So Min, you know what to do.
- Yes, Jong Kook.
- Block when I tell you to.
- Okay.
- Get it.
- You can do it.
Come on.
- Nice! Jong Kook!
- Come on.
(What?)
- Nice! Jong Kook!
- Come on.
(Jong Kook heads the ball
into the net.)
Had you kicked it,
it would have gone over the net.
Hold on.
- Are you going to overlook it?
- It was hilarious.
(Jong Kook's rare mistake
makes the members very happy.)
- His head almost went into the net!
- Use your leg.
I thought the ball was higher.
- You should have used your leg.
- I thought the ball was higher,
so I used my head.
- I burst out laughing.
- That was hilarious.
That was hilarious.
- For goodness' sake.
- Let's resume.
Let's win. Let's finish them off.
Let's go.
(The current score is 11 to 5.
Jae Suk continues to serve.)
That's good.
- Han Na.
- Send it over the net.
That's it!
- Han Na.
- Send it over the net.
(A strong spike)
- Han Na!
- Yes!
- Send it over the net.
- That's it!
(Team Married fails to block
Han Na's strong spike.)
- Han Na!
- So Min, good job.
- That was good.
- You are incredible.
- So Min, good job.
So Min, stay still.
- Han Na, that was amazing.
- Han Na.
- So Min, you are doing great.
- I want to play!
She spiked the ball.
Han Na is athletic.
This is good.
- Mine!
- Okay.
- That's good.
Han Na, get ready.
Han Na, hit it!
- There you go!
- All right!
That's it.
(Han Na's strong spike)
- Hit it!
- Ju Young, that's it.
(Ji Hyo and Ju Young
manage to receive.)
- That's it.
- All right.
Move out of the way.
- That's it.
- So Min, move out of the way.
That's it.
- Han Na.
- So Min.
- There you go.
- No!
- He touched the ball twice!
- There you go.
You did it.
- So Min, you did it.
- Good job.
(So Min and the air mattress
did it.)
(So Min blocked the ball
for the first time.)
(So Min, good job!)
- You did it.
- So Min, you did it.
(She was scorned
outside the stadium.)
- Good job.
- You did it.
- Seriously.
- You succeeded.
- You finally contributed.
- The air mattress did all the work.
- Seriously.
Was my face visible?
This is exhausting.
It was incredible.
- Let's go.
- This is good.
- You will get it, right?
- He will kick it.
- Hey!
- Out! Okay.
(Haha makes a mistake
as soon as he starts playing.)
(Dejected)
- Haha, focus.
- Switch me out.
- You should have used your leg.
- I can't do it.
The floor is slippery. Sit here.
Okay.
That's good.
(Jong Kook serves nicely.)
That's beautiful.
(What?)
(He used his shoulder in haste.)
For goodness' sake.
- Why did you do the shoulder dance?
- What?
Until when will you make me do
the shoulder dance?
We are a dance club.
This won't do.
Did Jae Suk get kicked out
after one try?
after using his shoulder?
- Good.
- Good. Nice serve!
It's beautiful.
- You are out.
- How strange!
We don't want you in his stead.
We will play on our own.
(The three of us will play
on our own.)
- Move.
- That's hilarious.
- Play.
- Sae Rok, play.
(Team Unmarried
is just 1 point behind.)
- Let's win!
- Mine.
Kwang Soo, get ready.
Move out of the way.
(My goodness!)
(Floundering)
- What?
- Did you use your leg?
That was an acrobatic move.
- He was like Ronaldinho.
- He was like a pigeon.
- Jong Kook.
- What was that?
- I am sorry.
- He was like Son Yeon Jae.
(Team Married serves.)
- Mine.
- No, no.
Kwang Soo.
- Nice!
- Good job.
(Han Na's high-quality attack)
Okay!
(Sae Rok receives the ball,
but it hits the net.)
- Han Na.
- Han Na, you are good.
- You are doing all the work.
Sae Rok.
Getting it over the net
isn't the only option. You can pass.
I will pass it to you.
That's volleyball.
(That's volleyball.)
Hold on. Suk Jin,
we aren't playing volleyball.
- Explain yourself.
- Hey.
Did you hear him? "Sae Rok."
"You can pass. That's volleyball."
"That's volleyball."
That's a volleyball rule.
Didn't you know?
Foot volleyball follows
the volleyball rules.
Don't try so hard to get it
over the net. You can pass.
- Yes, Sir.
- "That's volleyball."
- Let's begin.
- Let's go!
(This attack could be crucial.)
- Do you want to serve?
- Shall I do it?
(He wants to serve
and receive the spotlight.)
Let's go!
He is so greedy.
(The icon of petty greed
serves with greed.)
All right.
- He should have moved back.
- Okay!
- My goodness.
- Okay.
- Kwang Soo, use your head.
- Kwang Soo.
- Come on!
- Han Na!
- There you go!
- That's it!
That's it!
(What?)
- There you go!
- That's it!
(Suk Jin receives the ball
with his hand.)
You aren't playing volleyball!
This isn't volleyball!
I did it without thinking.
Why did you use your hand?
I was in a hurry.
(He gets switched out
after a foul play.)
- We will win a point this time.
- Okay.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Here I go.
(Both teams have 3 points left.)
- Okay. Han Na.
- Han Na.
- Go slow.
- Han Na, hit it!
- There you go!
- Let's go!
- Come on.
- That was good.
Hold on.
(So Min blocks the ball!)
- Nice!
- What was that?
- Out.
- That was good.
So Min, hold it up!
(She holds up the air mattress
and blocks the ball.)
- There you go!
- Nice!
(They are leading the game now!)
- I am sorry. I didn't expect that.
- It's okay.
- I was thinking.
- You got this!
- What did I tell you?
- That's it!
- Hey!
That's how you play!
- You were so cool.
- Seriously.
You were so cool.
- Good job.
- You were so cool.
If we lose...
- Three men should play.
- Let's do that.
And...
(They get three men on the court...)
(and get Ju Young's tray.)
Hold on.
Jae Suk, what are you doing?
- What do you mean?
- What are you doing?
- There are three men.
- Hold on.
- What was that?
- What are you doing?
- I can use this, right?
- What?
Are you going to use the giant hand?
Suk Jin, you told Sae Rok
about 30 minutes ago...
that you will make her a star.
Then you stole her giant hand.
- It's okay.
- You said you will make her a star.
He meant she'll leave this field.
- Is that what he meant?
- You got a lot of solo shots.
You drew enough attention.
It's fine.
(He wants attention, so making her
a star is not his priority.)
- I'm going to take off my jacket.
- What? You getting serious?
- Are you taking your jacket off?
- I'll show you.
I'll show you
my foot volleyball skills.
You're going to catch a cold.
Put it back on.
- You got it? Okay.
- Okay.
Let's get started.
What's this?
- Give me a minute.
- So Min, stand up!
- Hold it up.
- Hold it.
- Block it.
- The Great Wall.
- Hold it up.
- Hold it.
(It's Jae Suk's turn to attack.)
(Hitting)
(He attacks his own face.)
What was that?
Is that what you wanted to show us?
- Is that it?
- Was that comedy?
- This...
- What was that?
- That wasn't funny.
- You know it was a foul, right?
They made a foul before that.
So Min touched the net, right?
Jae Suk, your face is red.
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
All right. Let's go.
- So Min is good.
- This is match point.
Match point.
One point left.
- Don't worry.
- Good luck.
So Min, hold it up.
The Great Wall.
(Jae Suk kicks it toward
So Min's inflatable tube.)
- So Min, hold it up.
- The Great Wall.
- Nice!
(She got used to it.)
- So Min.
- She's good.
Chorong, get ready.
- Chorong.
- Excuse me!
Chorong!
(She hit it kind of hard.
What's he doing?)
It's out.
(Did it hit his hand then go out?)
Good one, So Min.
That was the right timing.
(He sounded awkward.)
It's out.
- Didn't you touch it?
- No.
- This is not volleyball.
- Be quiet.
- Wait. Didn't you touch it?
- The ball bounced off.
Be quiet.
- They don't know.
- Let's get started.
- We need one more.
- Okay.
- So Min.
- Slow down. Use your head.
- Oh, gosh.
- Get up, So Min.
(Kwang Soo received it
with his face.)
Get up, So Min.
- Leave it.
- All right.
- Get up.
- Leave it.
(That was close, but it went out.)
- All right.
- Out. It went out.
- That was in.
- In!
- It went out.
It wasn't in.
It came in this direction
and went out completely.
- No.
- It went out.
- Doesn't it have to be on the line?
- Excuse me.
If you admit that it was out,
I'll give you another chance.
- It went out.
- Okay.
(That took 0.5 seconds.)
One more chance.
Excellent.
- It went out completely.
- Then?
- It went out.
- Good.
This is better than a tricky call.
All right.
- That went out completely.
- Good luck.
- Okay!
Hey, Han Na.
Stand up, So Min.
(Han Na's shot is successful.)
- Good job, Han Na.
- Stand up.
- Good job. Here.
- Stand up!
- I kept it alive.
(Will it be Suk Jin's foot,
a spear that can't pierce anything?)
(Or will it be So Min's inflatable,
a shield that can't block anything?)
Stand up! Okay!
(Team Married loses 15 to 13.)
- No.
- Did we win?
(That was a long and dirty match.)
Did we win?
That didn't work.
- Good game.
- Good job.
- We almost had it.
- That was close.
Let's think about something good.
- We warmed up too late.
- You need 1st and 2nd place.
That's true.
Everybody will do
rock-paper-scissors.
- Everybody?
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Jong Kook and Se Chan win.)
- Okay, us 2.
- Us 2.
They're 1st and 2nd place.
- 1st and 2nd place.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- We won.
- Okay!
We're first place.
Good job.
- It's okay.
- We're second.
Then, let's have
the first-place couple come up.
Okay.
- First place.
- Let's keep this up.
We won regardless.
Oh, dear.
You can pick one couple.
For example, I'll say they have
1 element card and 1 special card.
Are special cards prizes?
We won't know? I see.
I see.
When Kwang Soo lost
rock-paper-scissors,
he didn't look too happy.
We shouldn't pick his team.
- A different team?
- We get to find out.
- He'll tell us.
- For all teams?
No, one team.
- Han Na.
- My bad.
- Look at the mountains.
- I exercised too much.
- Stare at it for a minute.
- I'm not in my right mind.
Look far away. Can you see?
- My head cleared up a bit.
- I see. Let's try that again.
(My head cleared up a bit.)
- Let's try that again.
- Let's go.
- I'll try again.
- Okay.
- Then...
- One team.
let's pick a team
that looks the happiest.
Which one's that?
- So Min. She's at ease.
- So Min?
- Should we ask for hers?
- Yes.
Se Chan and So Min have...
1 element card and 1 special card.
(They have "water"
and a penalty card.)
We don't know if that's a prize.
We can take our chance.
- Should we try?
- I don't care.
Then let's switch
Jong Kook's card...
(In the beginning, their draw...)
(had neither a prize
nor a penalty card.)
(If they switch with So Min,
they'll get a penalty card.)
Se Chan's.
Jong Kook and Se Chan will
switch their cards.
With yours?
Let's switch. Come this way.
Is that good?
So Min, this is going very well.
- Right?
- This is excellent.
- Let's go.
- This is what we want.
Okay.
It wasn't a prize card.
(They're disappointed
it's not a prize card.)
We have this.
You can ask about anybody
besides the first-place team.
Kwang Soo doesn't have it.
- Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo's team.
Kwang Soo and Chorong have...
two special cards.
(Kwang Soo and Chorong have
2 special cards.)
(There are 2 prize cards
and 2 penalty cards.)
(So Min has 1 penalty card,)
(and Jae Suk has the other.)
(Since Kwang Soo's team has
2 special cards,)
(that means they have 1 prize card
and 1 penalty card.)
(But they don't know that.)
- Which special cards?
- You don't know.
- But there are two prize cards.
- I think it's a prize.
We have one penalty card.
Let's switch yours.
- For Chorong's? Kwang Soo's?
- Chorong.
- No.
- Chorong?
Chorong.
(They pick Chorong's card.)
- Chorong's.
- With So Min's.
With mine.
Se Chan and So Min will
switch So Min's card for Chorong's.
Please switch.
(They smile mysteriously.)
Come here, Chorong.
What is it?
- Let's do it privately.
- Privately.
- So Min had a penalty card.
- Come here.
- What a relief.
- I know.
So Min, don't let it show.
(So Min switches her penalty card
with Chorong's card.)
(Is Chorong's card...)
(a prize or penalty card?)
(Swallowing)
Gosh.
(They chuckle
after seeing the card.)
- So Min.
- Did you switch?
- Hey, it's a penalty card.
- Let me see.
It's a penalty card.
- Let's see.
- It's a penalty card.
- We got another penalty card.
- Really?
(Kwang Soo and Chorong had
1 prize card and 1 penalty card.)
(Chorong's was the penalty card.)
(She gave up her penalty card
and got somebody else's.)
(They still have a penalty card,
so they might get the penalty.)
Something doesn't look right.
So round one is over.
Let's get going for round two.
Yes!
That was too bad.
(Card Distribution)
- Good job.
- I was looking forward to it.
(Card Distribution)
This is a perfect day
to stay home and lie in bed.
I know.
I want a car date.
It's really nice on a rainy day.
With music on.
- What do you do?
- I drink rice wine at home.
Rice wine?
- That sounds good.
- What do you do, Chorong?
I stay at home like any other day.
"Like any other day".
I stay at home...
(She has no energy.)
We were all happy
before you said that.
- What do you do at home?
- What do you do?
Do you live by yourself, Ju Young?
- No.
- Then?
I live with my grandma,
dad,
sister and her husband.
- Really?
- You have a huge family.
Really?
- It's a two-story house.
- It's a two-story house?
- Is it a cool house?
- "A cool house"?
(It's a two-story house?
Is it a cool house?)
"A cool house"?
My dream is to live
in a two-story house.
- That wasn't appropriate.
- What was that?
- What's cool and uncool?
- It's old.
This is the second mission
where you can switch your cards.
(Second mission to switch cards)
It's Speed Initial Game.
One couple will play at a time.
The first person listens
to the initials...
and says a two-syllable word
that is not a repeat.
The next person takes the syllables,
flips it around,
and says a two-syllable word.
For example, if I say "Ghana,"
Kwang Soo can say, "poverty."
Then Chorong has to flip
the initials around.
1st and 2nd place couples...
- can switch their cards.
- Okay.
It's only 1st and 2nd place.
Which couple shall we start with?
Should we go first?
(Should we go first?)
What's up with you today?
Nothing.
We usually start from the back.
- "Should we go first?"
- He's so ambitious today.
They're the only real couple here.
- That's not true.
- Real.
- We're going to start.
- Power!
Let's get started.
Speed Initial Game.
- Start.
Pyeongchang.
Pingchang.
(Pingchang?)
(What on earth is that?)
You could have gone with "Award."
- "Award".
- "Pingchang"!
What on earth is "Pingchang"?
- What on earth is "Pingchang"?
- I am sorry.
This is an easy game.
Since he went first,
we will give him another chance.
Speed Initial Game!
- Start.
Student.
Plea.
(Correct)
(Now, Se Chan needs to say
a word...)
(that starts with shiot and hieut
in Korean.)
Primary school.
(He got the right initials.)
- You are right.
- What's the meaning?
(It's a sudden question.)
- It's like small happiness.
No.
(It's like small happiness.)
- The spelling is different.
- That is spelled differently.
Don't you know the word?
Primary school.
You lost your chance. It's over.
- The next couple.
- We will go next.
- Suk Jin, this isn't easy.
- Do you want to go first?
You need to succeed first, okay?
Speed Initial Game!
- Start.
Name.
Iran.
(He needs to say a word
that starts with rieul and ieung.)
Luna.
(The initials are wrong.)
Ieung!
It's an Ieung!
- This is too hard.
- Suk Jin,
exactly how will you make
Sae Rok a star?
(From the way you are acting,
it seems impossible.)
You need to make her stand out.
You already placed fourth
on the top keywords search list.
(I am sure you didn't know.)
You already placed fourth.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, you placed fourth.
- Because she is good at the game?
- That's right.
When you are next to me,
you appear to be good at the game.
She became popular that way.
When you are next to me,
you appear to be good at the game.
Han Na has always been good
at games.
Had you not been Suk Jin's partner,
you would have placed second.
You are stuck in fourth place.
(She moved down two places
because of Suk Jin's wrong answer.)
Let's resume.
Speed Initial Game!
- Start.
Socks.
Oma.
- What's "Oma"?
- "Oma"?
Countryside.
Nongpang!
Graduation.
- Haha.
- What? It's your turn!
Scholar.
Defense.
Secretary.
You succeeded.
(Jae Suk and Ju Young place 1st
and Haha and Ji Hyo place 2nd.)
- Haha!
- We did it!
- This is incredible.
First place.
First place, come on up.
It's us.
I can't believe
Jae Suk placed first.
I placed first too.
(Jae Suk and Ju Young start
to switch cards.)
Let's watch their reactions
and decide.
(With the current cards,
they can win the beef bulgogi set.)
We want to check
Sae Rok and Suk Jin's cards.
Suk Jin and Sae Rok.
(They check
Sae Rok and Suk Jin's cards.)
This is bad.
Both of them have an element card.
(Both of them have an element card.)
(Suk Jin and Sae Rok have
2 unknown element cards.)
Would you like to switch cards?
(If they switch an element card,
their prize will change.)
Let's switch cards.
Let's switch your card with theirs.
I will switch my card.
(They currently qualify
for the beef bulgogi set.)
I want Sae Rok's card.
Ju Young will switch her card
with Sae Rok's.
- Sae Rok's card.
Ju Young and Sae Rok
will switch cards.
Ju Young will switch her card
with Sae Rok's.
(Sae Rok's card could change
the couple's prize.)
(Sae Rok's card is...)
(tree.)
Sae Rok, you can do back.
Ju Young, check the card
with Jae Suk.
Sae Rok doesn't look happy.
Come here.
(I can't believe
the prize became the bamboo wife.)
(Suk Jin and Sae Rok still have
2 element cards.)
- It's not too bad.
- I know.
We want to check
Team Jong Kook's cards.
- Right?
- Yes.
Jong Kook and Han Na have...
two element cards.
They don't have a special card.
(Sighing)
(Since Ji Hyo and Haha have
2 element cards,)
We should have picked
a different team.
(switching cards with Jong Kook
and Han Na would be meaningless.)
Let's take a wild guess.
We will take a wild guess.
(We will take a wild guess.)
Chorong. Chorong.
Chorong?
Should I switch my card with hers?
(Will he switch his card
with Chorong's?)
(So Min switched her bad card
with Chorong's,)
(but they didn't see it.)
Ji Hyo will switch her card
with Chorong's.
I guess Chorong has a nice card.
(Didn't So Min give her a bad card?)
(Laughing)
Really?
I think he is acting.
Kwang Soo can't control his face.
Kwang Soo, you look happy.
- Of course not.
- Is he happy?
I am not happy.
He looks awkward.
I can tell that he is happy.
- He looks so happy.
- He is happy.
(Let's see.)
Is it good?
Chorong is happy.
(They lose an element card
and get a penalty card.)
- She is overjoyed.
- Why did they pick us?
(He scans the prizes.)
Kwang Soo,
your gaze stayed on the top.
You checked out the prizes, right?
- I got you.
- Kwang Soo is overjoyed.
Chorong looks happy.
(Haha and Ji Hyo's sacrifice
shines.)
(The second switch ends.)
The last mission that will give you
a chance to switch cards is...
I Can See Your Movements.
(The last mission,
I Can See Your Movements)
I Can See Your Movements.
Two couples will compete
in each round of the tournament.
It's a tournament.
The offense and defense will stand
with a wall in the middle.
The defense will freely lay
16 pads...
of four different colors,
red, blue, yellow, and green.
Without a visual on the defense,
the offense...
will pick four colors in turn.
The members on the defense
need to touch...
the corresponding pads
without collapsing.
Once you touch a pad,
you can't switch to a different one.
The members on defense
must start out from the same pad.
(The members of the defense
must start out from the same pad.)
Kwang Soo has an advantage
since he is tall.
I am jealous.
The offense will throw
three water balloons over the wall.
If they hit a member,
they win a point.
The team with the highest score
will win.
- I see.
- It sounds scary.
If the water balloon doesn't burst,
it doesn't count.
- Okay.
- It needs to burst.
We can catch it, right?
You be touching the pads,
so it will be hard.
You won't be able to catch it
when your hands are on the pads.
Suk Jin doesn't understand
how the game works.
Do you understand? Do you?
Yes, I do.
Now, it's time to check
which team you will go against.
- This is important.
Let's see.
(The list of matches)
- Let's go first.
- Shall we do that?
All right.
- Okay.
- We will be the defense first.
Okay. Let's go to the other side.
They are bound to be at the center.
- Do we start now?
- Do what you want to do.
(It's time to lay the pads
as they want.)
I will do it. What do you want?
This one?
Yes. The red one.
It sticks because of the water.
- Here.
- This one?
(They listen to them.)
It shouldn't be
at the corner, right?
- Shall we do this?
- Which one?
- These two? Okay.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Now...
How about this one?
- Like this?
- They look good together.
- You are right.
- Right?
They look very good together.
- They look like a couple.
- Seriously.
Han Na, in which year were you born?
- 1989.
- 1989?
- Were you born in 1989?
- Okay. She passes.
What? I pass?
Okay. She passes.
(There he goes again.)
I acknowledge her
as my sister-in-law.
There are like 30 girls
he calls "Sister-in-law."
(Haha and 30 sisters-in-law)
- There are like 30 girls.
- 30 sisters-in-law.
- Like this? Is this perfect?
- I think it's perfect.
(They finish placing the mats
under Han Na's directions.)
- Let's begin.
- Okay. Let's go.
Say the first color.
Red.
- Red?
- Red.
- It should be this one, right?
- Yes.
(They start from the same pad!)
You are the worst at this.
You are the worst at this. Stop.
We will say the next color.
Red.
Red, red.
It's not too bad.
(Each one of them needs to pick
from the 3 remaining red pads.)
Hold on. Hold on.
She picked.
(She picks a pad.)
No take-backs.
Let's keep going.
- No, no.
- Hold on.
My goodness.
(Jong Kook chooses a red pad.)
(A forced onscreen relationship
isn't complete...)
Give him a back hug!
(without the audience's reaction.)
You look good!
- What's the next color?
- Blue.
- What?
- Yes.
(Han Na touches the pad.)
- Okay.
- Here comes the last one.
- Blue.
My goodness.
How will they do it?
- How will they do it?
- What will they do?
(Is this possible?)
(It's relatively easy for Han Na.)
You can't switch hands.
- What?
- You can't switch hands.
This hand needs to go there.
Jong Kook, hold on.
Should I pull out this hand?
How will it go there?
It's the only way.
Maybe I need to break this arm.
- How will you do this?
- What should we do?
It hurts.
- Still...
- Try it. I think it will work.
- Move this foot a bit.
- Hold on. I will try it.
Move this foot a bit more.
Will it work?
(Will it work?)
- I will do this.
- It's touching the red pad.
All right.
(He moved his foot a little.)
Will it work?
(He touches the blue pad!)
(In 2020, Jong Kook has
flexibility as well.)
They are making a cross!
- They look good together.
- There you go!
- Cross!
You are doing great.
Is this the power of love?
- I will throw a balloon now.
- Okay.
(Jae Suk attacks first
with a water balloon!)
(Will Jae Suk's water balloon...)
(hit the cross of love?)
(What will happen?)
(It hits Han Na.)
(It hits Han Na on the back.)
I guess it hit someone.
- Did it hit someone?
- That was incredible.
- One water balloon.
That was incredible.
Here comes the second one.
(Here comes
the second water balloon!)
(It hits Han Na again!)
(Han Na got hit twice in a row.)
Oh, my goodness.
You have to throw it far.
(She's soaked.)
They already got the penalty.
Next. This is the last one.
My hands are about to slip.
(This is the last water balloon!)
(It floats like a butterfly
and stings Han Na like a bee.)
Please draw the curtains.
Jong Kook didn't get a drop on him.
When we talk, they can hear us.
- Did you get hit?
- Han Na got it all.
- She got it all.
- That's so much.
I thought somebody had punched
the back of my neck.
The back of my neck.
I didn't know what it was.
You earned three points.
(Jae Suk and Ju Young earn
3 points.)
He was precise.
Exactly.
- Let's get started.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook and Han Na earn 1 point.)
You earned one point.
Jae Suk advances.
(Jae Suk and Ju Young's team won.)
I got them.
(Suk Jin and Sae Rok won next.)
(Ji Hyo and Haha also won.)
We won.
That was no joke.
Jae Suk, Suk Jin,
and Haha's teams won,
so this is the final match
to decide 1st and 2nd place.
Rules don't change.
One person from each team
will attack...
and the other person will defend.
If you throw the water balloon
at your teammate,
- you lose two points.
- Okay.
We have to be good.
- This is the real game.
- We'll be good.
- Good luck.
- Ju Young.
Play well.
First color.
Let's start with yellow.
(First color is yellow.)
(They start on different squares.)
- I pick blue.
- Blue.
(Second color is blue.)
Yellow and blue.
Suk Jin is next.
I'll pick green.
(Suk Jin picks green.)
Here's the last one. Yellow.
(Last one is yellow.)
(I'm going for this one.)
(Ji Hyo got there first.)
(She has to go for the one behind.)
- Can't I do this?
- You can.
- Who was that?
- That was Sae Rok.
Are you good to go?
We're going to throw it.
Sae Rok, I'll avoid you.
If I hit you, it's minus two points.
I have to do well.
Go.
(Sae Rok, we'll win the game,)
(and I'll turn you into a star.)
I hit somebody.
(Suk Jin's water balloon
got somebody.)
(What now?)
- I hit somebody.
- Wasn't that Sae Rok?
- Wasn't that Sae Rok's voice?
- Sae Rok.
- Was it Sae Rok?
(A moment ago)
(He said
he wouldn't throw it at her.)
(He got Sae Rok on the dot.)
I hit somebody.
(Shaking)
(She's speechless.)
- That was her voice.
- Really?
- Sae Rok.
- Next is Haha.
- Me.
- I'm in big trouble.
You went for the center.
That was the cry of a pterosaur.
That was Sae Rok's voice.
- That could have been Ji Hyo.
- I'm going.
We pointed her out.
It's far.
(Where will Haha's balloon go?)
(2nd hit)
(She let out a single cry.)
- She's right in the front.
- Who is it?
This is...
Are you all right?
Let's just exclude her.
Please get her a white towel.
Sae Rok, it's not you, right?
- Sae Rok.
- Hold on.
I'm next.
- She's up close.
- Right in front.
(As they thought.)
(Crying)
(It's an echo of the cry
they just heard.)
Sae Rok, tell me it's not you.
It's not you, right?
Oh, my goodness.
Sae Rok.
Sae Rok, it's not you, right?
- Sae Rok. Sae Rok.
- I'm going.
Sae Rok, I'm going.
(At this point)
Let's become a star.
(Take this and become a star.
I'll turn you into one.)
- Oh, my goodness.
- It didn't hit her.
Let's become a star.
(All the other water balloons
popped.)
He can't even make this work.
Jong Kook.
It didn't hit her.
She's right up close.
I'm going.
(He easily hits the target.)
(Groaning)
(She lets out a shriek
from deep in her throat.)
Please stop!
What sound was that?
(Please save Sae Rok.)
Stop it!
If these were bombs, not a trace
would have remained.
What sound was that?
- Sae Rok. Who was that?
- Who was that?
Whose voice was that?
Sae Rok, that wasn't you, right?
- Sae Rok.
- Please tell me it wasn't you.
This is my last one.
Last one. She's right over here.
(Groaning)
(She has a great singing voice now.)
Just kill her.
We're coming.
Who was it?
Sae Rok, it wasn't you, right?
- Was it you?
- Was it Sae Rok?
She got like four water balloons.
Really?
How does this work then?
Are we in last place?
You are in last place.
You've been eliminated.
Haha and Jae Suk both have
two points each.
Two points?
But that was a great sound.
This is how
Sae Rok will become a star.
I knew it.
I told you I'd turn you into a star.
The ending segment is yours.
Okay.
That was amazing.
First place team, come here.
They can't touch us.
- They can't touch us, right?
- No.
Which team
would you like to know about?
We...
Ours is the worst right now.
(Tree card and prize card
gives a bamboo wife.)
Right?
Or instead...
Suk Jin has an element card.
He has the other one.
- Let's get his.
- That's true.
(Switch with Suk Jin
for a better prize?)
That's right.
We'll switch...
with Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin and Ju Young will switch.
- Okay.
- With me?
- Yes.
This is very important.
(Jae Suk's team switched with
Suk Jin. What will they win now?)
(Bamboo wife)
(This card is!)
(What is it?)
(The element card Suk Jin had...)
(was water.)
(Water card and prize card
gives the abalone set.)
It should have been wind.
Second place team,
please come forward.
(Jae Suk and Ju Young won
the abalone set instead.)
You can't switch with
the first place team.
Which team would you like to know?
It doesn't matter
which cards we get.
Hold on.
(They have to find out which teams
don't have penalty cards.)
We know what Chorong has.
(That was originally Ji Hyo's card.)
- Right?
- Yes.
Which team's information
would you like to know?
(Ji Hyo switched her card
with Chorong in the last round.)
- Okay.
- Chorong is happy.
(Ji Hyo got the penalty card.)
- She's so happy.
- Why do we...
(Their eyes went
to the prize section.)
- She's so happy.
- Why is your gaze up?
He looked at the prize section.
- Kwang Soo is so happy.
- I saw you.
Kwang Soo, you look happy.
- What?
- Were you happy?
I wasn't.
He's so happy.
(He couldn't hide
where he was looking.)
Kwang Soo and Chorong's team.
It doesn't matter who.
We can get any.
(They predict that Kwang Soo
and Chorong have a prize card.)
(Chorong has a tree card,
Kwang Soo has a prize card.)
Kwang Soo and Chorong have...
one element card
and one prize card.
(They have one prize card.)
(Ji Hyo and Haha can't hide
their smiles.)
(They have no idea
what's about to happen to them.)
Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo will switch.
(They think
Kwang Soo has the prize card.)
It's 100 percent.
Right.
Ji Hyo will switch with Kwang Soo.
(What?)
I think Kwang Soo got
the penalty card at the end.
Good work.
(Ji Hyo and Haha obtain
a prize card.)
(Kwang Soo and Chorong obtain
a penalty card.)
Okay.
Kwang Soo got the penalty.
I'll reveal the cards.
Is it over?
- Yes, it's over.
- Is this over?
We're done?
(Same ending,
different facial expressions)
- Do we go outside?
- Is this over?
- But then...
- I said there were three rounds.
- He said it was over.
- He said it was the last round.
Please take turns
and reveal your cards.
Ji Hyo is the queen.
- Did you get it?
- She's the queen of luck.
Wind and...
Prize!
(Prize card and wind card
gives an air purifier.)
- That was amazing.
- It's an air purifier.
- You won an air purifier.
- I wanted it.
We wanted that one.
We didn't know where wind was.
Did you have wind?
No.
Prize card.
(Thanks for the prize card.)
We got a penalty card at the end.
We had the prize card all day,
but it changed at the end.
That's too bad.
Tree.
Next.
- I had wind.
- That's where it was.
It's a penalty.
All right.
(It's time for
the prizes and penalties.)
I'll hand out the prizes first.
Take the abalone set.
This is for Ju Young's big family.
Her grandma,
sister, and sister's husband.
- It's alive.
- Have an abalone party.
- This too.
- Thank you.
This wasn't ours.
This is for...
- Ju Young's big family.
- That's so nice.
Running Man is so warm.
- This is great.
- She just moved.
We'll give the whipped cream penalty
to Ju Young too.
We'll give it to her.
- We'll give up the flogging too.
- For Ju Young...
who has a big family.
We'll give her two whipped creams.
We'll do the flogging penalty first.
Kwang Soo and Chorong are up.
Jae Suk and Ju Young will do
the flogging.
- Us?
- Yes.
Okay, I'll hit Kwang Soo then.
- Jae Suk, show us.
- I will.
Now for our star from
"Tazza: One-Eyed Jacks."
- Of course.
- What?
- Hurry.
- Why did you mention that...
- when I'm getting the penalty?
- Is that the famous movie?
- Yes, it is.
It has to look puffy.
- Yes, I'll take care of that.
- It looks too flat.
What do you mean?
- I'll make it look puffy.
- Yes, do that.
- It has to show depth.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
- Watch this, Ju Young.
If Jae Suk doesn't do this...
(She's shocked.)
(The high-roller gets the stick.)
(Jae Suk wants him to perform
better with his bottom.)
"One-Eyed Jacks".
- "One-Eyed Jacks".
- Hit it hard like this.
Let's finish up with the penalty.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- I wonder what will happen to them.
- It might go to the side.
- We can't be together.
- We are breaking up today.
- We are not a match.
- We'll break up.
- Yes.
- Great. 1, 2, 3.
(The blue whipped cream
is launched!)
(I hope these Genies can
make your dream come true.)
- It's colored.
- My gosh.
- What?
- I got it all over my face.
(Thank you for joining us
on a cold day.)
Good job.
- Good work.
- Great job.
Good work.
(As for this year...)
(The members get together to get
their fortunes read for 2020.)
(Their fortunes make them smile...)
(and cry.)
(The fortune-reading
brings them shock and horror.)
(They make an awful pair?)
(The members prayed
for good luck in 2020.)
(But...)
(they have the biggest crisis.)
(The main MC, Jae Suk,
has vanished?)
(And a mysterious briefcase
remains alone.)
(The one who has
the secret briefcase...)
(will get the biggest luck in 2020.)
(What is the shocking secret
in this tightly closed briefcase?)
(The Rat Holds
the Briefcase with Money)