(Sanjicheon on Jeju Island
with the blue sea and blue sky)
(There's Sanjitmul Park
next to Sanjicheon.)
My gosh.
Hello, guys.
(The members are
gathering at the park.)
Seok Sam.
(Seok Sam.)
- Excuse me.
- Seok Sam.
- Come here, Seok Sam.
You haven't taught me anything
for the past 15 years.
(Human Cultural Asset Jae Suk,
and his pupil, Seok Sam)
- Do you want me to leave?
- Stay quiet, Seok Sam.
- This is just...
- Don't talk too much.
You just let me do the laundry.
So you're Seok Sam.
- He's Ji Seok Sam.
- Hello.
(Assistant Manager Haha,
new recruit Jong Kook)
Hello.
- Hello.
(Math Olympiad winner Ji Hyo,
Math Olympiad runner-up Kwang Soo)
Nice to meet you.
(Se Chan and So Min are
wearing matching outfits.)
Nice to meet you.
(A newly married couple,
Se Chan and So Min)
Nice to meet you.
I guess you are married.
- Right.
- We've been married for a year.
So you're on a trip to Jeju Island.
But the husband...
Is the husband rich?
(Is the husband rich?)
What's that supposed to mean?
He's a rich man with a lot of teeth.
I do have many teeth.
- So...
- What did you do for a living?
- I ran my own business.
- What business?
I used to handle big money.
What did you do?
He runs a restaurant.
- A restaurant?
- Spicy catfish stew.
- A restaurant.
- Do you live in Paju?
- Yes. How did you know?
He sells spicy catfish
and Korean bullhead stew.
- It tastes really good.
- You should visit my restaurant.
I'll offer a discount of 15 percent.
So what brings you two here?
I said I didn't want
to come to Jeju Island.
Don't raise your voice
when there are people around.
- Honey...
- My goodness.
- I mean...
- Don't embarrass me.
I'm sorry, but who picked out
your sunglasses?
Why? Aren't they nice?
I picked them.
- You look pretty.
- Honey.
You look great.
- You two...
- You're so pretty.
Don't make fun of her.
She looks pretty.
Why did you marry him?
- Seok Sam.
- Yes?
- Don't be nosy.
- What? Hey.
I like their skit.
Seok Sam is too nosy.
- I'm sorry.
- You should talk to him.
Sir, I just said 1 word
while you said 5.
Seok Sam, just stay quiet.
- Seok Sam.
- Watch your language.
- Is his name Seok Sam?
- Yes.
- Like how you count numbers.
- I see.
- Seok Sam means three.
- That's what it means.
I've never seen him paint.
- I've never seen his work.
- I do an ink-and-wash painting.
- An ink painting.
- I just saw him draw a mustache.
Sure. It's a kind of ink painting.
- He does draw pictures.
- Sure.
- Are you sure?
- Don't worry.
Are you Math Olympiad winners?
It sounds far-fetched.
- I was a runner-up.
- I was the winner.
I know this is a skit,
but it should be plausible.
- What's wrong about this?
- All right then.
Since you are
the Math Olympiad winners,
please tell us about
the Pythagorean theorem.
Or the quadratic formula.
Just anything.
It's not something
anyone can understand.
- What is she talking about?
- It's not easy.
She says things that aren't
relevant to the question.
Do you know what an equation is?
You should make it more convincing.
- This is far-fetched.
- I know.
And all we can say about math
is an equation and...
- And quadratic formula.
- Quadratic formula.
What is 3.14?
- Pi.
- That's enough.
- Stop it.
- Root.
He's acting as if he knows a lot.
My goodness.
- What did you say?
- I was talking to myself.
- What was that?
- Well...
You should speak clearly.
- It's my bad. I'm sorry.
- You understand?
- Are you a new recruit?
- Yes, I'm a newbie.
So he's your superior.
- That's right. He's my subordinate.
- He's an assistant manager.
And I'm a newbie.
But what kind of
assistant manager are you?
- Do you have other work experience?
- With your hands in your pockets.
I guess you used to be
in a different business.
- Right. I made a career change.
- I knew it.
I was in a different business.
That's right. Our company is
known for giving a second chance.
He has broad shoulders.
His shoulders look different.
That's right. We are gangsters.
(That's right. We are gangsters.)
- But he looks so nice and kind.
- He's nice.
- He seems good-natured.
- They're not intimidating.
We're in charge of debt collection.
(We can help you
with debt collection.)
Today, you guys are here
for a package tour.
You are groups of two,
and you guys don't know each other.
Now you will take a Running
package tour around Jeju Island.
So you should pay
for the tour package.
You have 50 dollars
in your mission bags now.
- 50 dollars?
- You will scatter...
and put the amount you are willing
to pay in an envelope secretly.
The mission fund is very important
for today's race.
So you should think carefully
before you pay.
Is there the minimum amount
we have to pay?
Can I not pay at all?
It's up to you. Just put the amount
you want in an envelope.
He's not telling us if we should
pay a lot or not.
I guess we should pay
a reasonable amount.
- It might be better to pay a lot.
- That might be better.
I think we should pay a lot.
(I think we should pay a lot.)
- Make it big.
- I was going to do that.
(The newlyweds decided
to pay a lot.)
Gosh, I should put some money
in here.
(Passing by)
- It's very thin.
- For this once, I should...
Why did you pay so much?
- Do you know something?
- Well...
I thought about it, and if you
calculate it mathematically,
multiplying it by 2 or 3
should work best.
- That's nonsense.
- "That's nonsense"?
Why would a human cultural asset...
I paid a moderate amount.
I also paid a moderate amount.
(People who paid a little,
People who paid a lot)
You paid a lot.
I thought we should pay a lot.
- We collected all entry fees.
- Yes.
Today is
the You Must Do Everything...
If You Get Caught
Package Option Trip Race
The two people who are on the same
package trip are a team today.
The entry fee you just submitted...
will be your team money.
(People who paid a little,
People who paid a lot)
You will start your trip
with the total amount submitted.
- Yes!
- Nice! How much did you pay?
You must return
the rest of the money.
(In other words,
it's advantageous to pay a lot.)
(Honey, you did a good job!)
I'm in trouble. I didn't pay a lot.
How much did you pay?
- I'm worried.
- I also paid quite a bit.
The team with the most money is...
the newlyweds, So Min and Se Chan,
who paid 60 dollars.
Why did you pay so much?
Did you pay 40 dollars?
Next are Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo
with 41 dollars.
(Team Olympiad 41 dollars)
- You almost paid nothing.
- They paid 36 and 5 dollars.
I paid a little.
Team Asst. Manager Ha
and the New Recruit...
paid 5 dollars each,
and have a total of 10 dollars.
- Gosh.
- Look at that.
Hey High Schooler,
I'll be in your debt after today.
What are you talking about?
Team Ink-and-Wash Painting Human
Cultural Asset and pupil...
paid 5 dollars and 2 dollars
and have a total of 7 dollars.
Oh, my.
That's...
- That's cutting it close.
- That's amazing.
You suit each other.
- I'm going to owe you a favor.
- He's a real human cultural asset.
- He's a human cultural asset.
- I'm going to owe you a favor.
What kind of human cultural asset...
brings seven dollars to Jeju Island?
- I'm a human cultural asset.
- I'm...
I'm going to owe you a favor.
I brought much more money
with me when I was in high school.
You could have a bowl of
pork and rice soup each, and leave.
Today,
you can go back to Seoul...
after taking the course our travel
agency has prepared for you.
There will be all kinds of options
and extra fees.
First, each course has...
a set number of people
that can go sightseeing.
Regardless of the teams,
that number will be decided...
- after playing games.
- Okay.
The people who get
the chance to go sightseeing...
will be able to enjoy all
the course offers limitlessly...
which includes buying
food, gifts, and extra options.
They will get a stamp each
during that course.
However, for the people excluded
from going sightseeing,
one loser will be decided after
playing a simple game each time.
Also, the loser will cover
the entire cost of that course...
using their team money.
- They will pay up the whole amount.
- We should do our best then.
- Your team might end up in debt.
- Yes.
The teams who don't have a lot of
money should join forces.
- Okay.
- Let's join forces.
- Let's target them.
- This is good.
- We should also join forces.
- Okay.
The top three people who have
the most stamps...
when the package trip is over
will get a prize.
- This is regardless of teams.
- Really?
There will be a penalty for the team
that has the least team money.
- Okay.
You could also get the prize
and penalty at the same time.
Starting now,
you will have to even pay
for the water you drink.
- That's too harsh.
- You're tight.
I should have drunk
some water beforehand.
The fee you use in the car
on the way to the course...
will also be counted.
I will give each team their team
money and individual stamp passport.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
The first schedule is...
- Yes?
- the highlight of package trips.
It's forced shopping.
- Shopping?
- Forced shopping?
- Okay.
- They disappeared a lot these days.
- Shop with seven dollars?
We will go to a shopping street,
a Jeju Island tourist attraction.
Only three people can participate.
(The number of Force Shopping
participants: 3 people)
The first game is...
Noise Complaint Apartment,
which we played last time.
For each round,
one team leader must come out,
and a total of four team leaders
will play the game.
They will shout the game chant
at the same time,
and they will use both hands to
pile a hand tower after the chant.
If you make a sound while getting
slapped, you will be out.
One person
must come from each team.
- You must go unconditionally.
- Gosh.
(Jong Kook competes for
Team Running Trading Company.)
So Min, you should go first
since Jong Kook is there.
You should go after Jong Kook.
- It hurts.
- Jong Kook won't slap you hard.
Jong Kook won't slap you hard.
- He won't let me off.
- No, he will let you off this time.
Kwang Soo, do you want to go?
(He has no intention of going.)
(The Palm Tyson says, "Welcome.")
Gosh...
- You can do it.
- Come out.
Shop as much as you want.
You're really despicable.
New Recruit Kim, you can do it!
While you sing, I will...
- 1, 2.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Cross the starry bridge
(The package trip participants
know how to have fun.)
(Tiger mouth bounce, Catfish bounce)
- Pass by the windy reed field
(The newlywed bride used to have
fun on a tourist bus.)
- Seok Sam is energetic.
- You always
(Seok Sam is an
energetic cultural asset.)
He's energetic.
Seok Sam is energetic.
(Seok Sam's back hunches
whenever he's excited.)
- Let's go
- 12th floor!
- Okay.
I'm in trouble.
My hand is underneath her hand.
- We will start from the bottom.
- Will we start...
- from the bottom?
- Start from the 12th floor.
You will be eliminated
if you make a sound from now on.
So Min, endure it.
(They will be eliminated
if they make a sound from now on.)
(So Min must endure
Suk Jin's smashing.)
- Gosh, So Min took it.
- What happened?
(So Min passed.)
Second floor.
(2nd floor,
Ji Hyo will slap Suk Jin.)
- It's my turn to slap, right?
- Yes.
Ji Hyo, let's send him away
this time.
Don't make any sounds.
- Good job.
- Second floor.
(The Pupil passed.)
It's his turn.
(3rd floor,
Jong Kook will slap Ji Hyo.)
- Is it Jong Kook's turn?
- It's Jong Kook's turn.
- It's over.
- Why did you put your hand there?
- I didn't know.
- Take it.
Ji Hyo is shrewd,
so she's good at holding it in.
(Ji Hyo is shrewd,
so she's good at holding it in.)
(He succeeded at changing
jobs with his sole palm strength.)
(Will Ji Hyo be able to endure
his monstrous smashing?)
(Smashing)
(Enduring)
- Other people...
- I'm in pain.
- will also be eliminated.
- No.
- So Min, you must endure it.
- How could the pain...
also reach me
when Ji Hyo was slapped?
Fourth floor.
We have 10 floors left now.
We have eight floors left.
He's really bad at math.
- Weren't you in second place?
- I was mistaken.
How could you be mistaken?
- Are you a foreigner?
- I just got this problem wrong.
- That's why.
- You can't do addition.
Endure it. Let's go!
(The math geniuses are especially
weak when it comes to subtraction.)
- Send him away.
- It's So Min. That was...
(5th floor,
Jong Kook will slap So Min.)
My palm hurts.
(It's the new recruit's turn again.)
- It's Jong Kook's right hand.
- Jong Kook...
- Your...
- Yes?
wife will be eliminated now.
No, she can endure it.
- Endure it.
- Two people must be eliminated.
- It can't be helped.
- Of course, it's a game.
(Avoiding)
- She avoided him.
- She's eliminated.
Why did you make a sound
when you weren't even slapped?
Good job.
- Did you see the look in his eyes?
- Yes?
- I thought you were going to die.
(The catfish husband is
a romanticist.)
- Just endure it this once.
- I can't watch this.
- I will also...
- It will just smart once.
No. Your bone might break, Ji Hyo.
It will just hurt once,
and it will be over.
(She's the Olympiad winner who has
the most patience.)
(The Palm Tyson is controlling
his breathing.)
The new recruit is angry.
(She took her hand out.)
(Shouting)
(The math genius took her hand out
at the crucial moment.)
I think you made a sound.
- He made a sound.
- Can you take your hand out?
She...
She took her hand out.
Can you take your hand out?
She...
- Isn't that cheating?
- Can you take your hand out?
(She's not good at subtracting, but
she's good at taking her hand out.)
My fingers aren't
moving "automatically".
- Do you mean "automatically"?
- What?
- I'm sorry.
(So Min, Ji Hyo, Suk Jin got
eliminated in the first round.)
Okay, the next group should go.
The people who didn't play
should come out.
- Okay, three people should go.
- Se Chan, I can only trust you.
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
- You need to do a good job.
(Their excitement
engine is starting.)
- It's doable.
- Let's go
(Let's go)
(Insurance king Assistant Manager Ha
is showing off his karaoke skills.)
(Bounce)
- You always...
- 9th floor.
- 9th floor. That's it.
- Let's go.
- No, come here.
- Come here.
- Let's do it quickly.
- Do it quickly.
- Okay.
- Haha.
(1st floor,
Kwang Soo will slap Haha.)
(They will get eliminated right away
if they make a sound.)
Isn't this school violence?
- Hurry up.
- It won't hurt at all.
It doesn't hurt.
It didn't hurt, did it?
(Enduring)
- Didn't you make a sound?
- You're a man.
- It's okay, Assistant Manager Ha.
- It's okay.
Wait a minute, Recruit Kim,
are you the owner?
(The new recruit is full of
a sense of ownership.)
- It's okay, Assistant Manager Ha.
- Okay.
I thought you were the owner.
- Do it.
- Okay, the second floor should go.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
At first,
I had no idea how it will be.
Is it still the third floor?
Whose turn is it? Who will slap now?
(The representative scaredy-cats are
gathered, so the game's quite slow.)
- He's the human cultural asset.
- Of course.
(Should I slap him or not?)
- He has a different rhythm.
- He's rhythmical.
They became really close
to each other.
The four of them became really close
(The hip-hop waterwheel is
suddenly turning.)
- Beat everyone
- Bam
(The four scaredy-cats are using
all kinds of methods to buy time.)
- Let's go.
- They're finally doing it.
(He starts slapping after preparing
for a long time.)
(In pain)
That was intense.
(He succeeded at defending
while giving his face up.)
- That was intense.
- It didn't hurt at all.
- What floor are we on?
- You have six floors left.
- You're on the sixth floor.
- Se Chan.
- Endure it.
(Se Chan smashes his hand
toward Jae Suk's hand.)
That's it. You can endure it.
It doesn't hurt.
Everyone is so well-behaved.
- Okay, next.
- Seventh floor.
It's Kwang Soo's right hand
this time.
He's going to use his right hand.
Se Chan, endure it.
- He's merciless.
- Let's fly away.
You can't lose
to a high school student.
You must endure it.
(Kwang Soo just slapped Se Chan
using his fist.)
He slapped with his fist.
(He doesn't want to lose, so he
endured it with clenched teeth.)
- You're going to be eliminated.
- Why did you slap with your first?
When did I?
- Young punk!
- Why?
How dare you slap me...
- Why are you hitting me?
- with your fist?
How dare you slap me
with your fist?
- Right now, you...
- Is that not allowed?
Shouldn't he be eliminated?
- He's eliminated.
Why?
- No wonder, even I was hurting.
- He's eliminated.
Even I was hurting.
If Jae Suk makes a sound,
Haha will win.
If Jae Suk doesn't make
a sound, Jae Suk will win.
- Oh, I will be okay then.
- That's right.
- You will be okay.
- You did a good job.
Look at Jae Suk right now.
Look at the face
of the human cultural asset.
You should slap him hard.
- I do not know pain.
- Lay it down hard.
He might wet himself.
- Just do it already.
- Get it over with.
I can't watch!
- Darn it hurts.
- It wasn't a direct hit.
Haha, you're out.
- He only hurt his own hand.
(The human cultural asset
endured the pain with willpower.)
- He only hurt his own hand.
- It slipped.
Unbelievable.
(Thankfully, the airplane
flies over them at the right time.)
- It wasn't a direct hit.
- A plane is flying over us.
(Everyone's happy
to film near an airport.)
I'm good now.
He's good.
Perfect timing.
Nice timing!
- It was nothing.
- We couldn't hear a thing.
You heard wrong.
The three will go shopping...
and one out of the rest...
will pay for the expenses
from the team's budget.
Just so you know,
Jong Kook is quite the spender.
I'm unleashing my shopaholic side.
Let's get going then.
Sure, let's head to the van.
Let's go.
Come on.
(Let's head off to see
Jong Kook waste money.)
Hello.
- It's good to see you.
- Shopping...
While on the trip,
- you could get hungry or thirsty.
- Right.
That's why we prepared
coffee, beverages, and water.
- Coffee too?
- Chips, chocolate, jelly...
are prepared for you too.
Beverages will cost three dollars...
while the snacks are five dollars.
Whatever you buy
will be added to the tab...
which will be paid
by the one paying...
- for the first schedule.
- Really?
- Hold on.
- Which will be paid...
(One will pay for everything.)
That means the three of us
can eat whatever we want.
If your teammate has to pay,
then it'll take a toll on you too.
There's nothing more to life anyway.
We'll think of
the consequences later.
- We'll get going then.
- Sure.
Can I get a bag of chips?
How about some coffee?
- Should we have some coffee?
- Please get So Min some coffee.
I'd like a refreshing beverage too.
- Coffee...
- That'll be three dollars each.
- Sure.
- They're not cheap.
Is there a cup too?
- One with ice.
- Nice.
This will be three dollars too.
- Sure thing.
- This too?
- Just hand it out.
- Can I get some jelly too?
- I'd like some ice too.
- Black coffee.
A cup of ice, please!
Black coffee.
- Unbelievable.
- This chance might not come again.
That's for me.
- This...
- Go ahead.
Thank you.
Can you get that for me?
We shouldn't be stingy
when on a vacation.
- Exactly.
- Nicely said.
This is the reason we save money up.
Everyone's spending money
like crazy.
Are there any chips?
I'll get some to you.
You're eating a lot today.
Shouldn't you stop?
- All right!
- Can we stop eating now?
One team might start off
as bankrupt.
We don't know who'll have to pay,
so let's eat.
- Unbelievable.
- This is wrong.
You've spent 63 dollars.
One team will go bankrupt.
- For sure.
- No matter which team pays,
- it will be a lot.
- One team will go bankrupt.
Any team will go bankrupt.
As long as it's not our team.
That's just how it is.
Don't you have any
sweet or savory snacks?
So tell me. What's your dream?
(Out of the blue)
That's right. What's your dream?
- It's to be a scientist.
- A scientist?
Who's your favorite scientist?
Nobel?
- Einstein.
- Who?
- Nobel.
- Einstein.
Honey, what was your dream
growing up?
- Me?
- He's my mentor.
My dream was to meet
a pretty lady...
- Then your dream came true.
- and live with her forever.
No, not quite.
(Darn it.)
- So we're at our first location.
- Right.
Yes, let's spend some money!
(Chilseongro, a shopping district
in Jeju with a long history)
I'm going to buy you a few things.
This is life, I guess.
- Right.
- I'll spend at least 1,000 dollars.
(The shopping district connects us
to various tourist attractions.)
The three of you...
will have 10 minutes to shop...
for yourself or your teammate.
The three of you will get off now.
- Can we go shopping now?
- Yes.
Please put on your masks.
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes?
Buy something for
my daughter, will you?
Your daughter?
Human cultural asset,
- can you get me something too?
- Okay.
Let's go shopping then.
(They head out after
receiving various requests.)
- Hello.
Hello, everyone!
I'm here to spend some money.
(Big spender Mr. Yang
arrives at the shopping district.)
I'm here to spend money.
I need to buy clothes
for Haha's daughter.
Hello.
(The human cultural asset...)
(has ladies coming up to greet him
in a heartbeat.)
- Hello, everyone.
- Hi!
Hello.
Hi.
Hold on a second.
(He's warmly welcomed
into a clothing store.)
Hello.
(He picks a cardigan
that suits the modernized hanbok.)
Is it for your pupil?
(Is it for your pupil?)
No, it's for me.
Why would I get my pupil anything?
(The pupil is trained
under harsh circumstances.)
- Guys.
- Yes?
We will now see...
- who pays for everything.
- Sure.
You'll play a series
of random silent games.
Quite a few of them actually.
Silent 007,
Silent 3, 6, 9,
or Silent Word Chain.
You will choose the game
you wish to play.
- How do you play Silent Word Chain?
- Silent Word Chain?
You'll explain the words
with body language.
(In Silent Word Chain,
body language will be used.)
- Nice.
- Like "bicycle"...
This sounds like fun.
If you lose the round
or get it wrong,
you'll be met with a punishment.
The one with the highest
number of points will pay.
You'll now fall silent.
And go.
Starting with Kwang Soo,
you'll play your desired game.
(Silent 3, 6, 9)
(Clap)
(Silent 3, 6, 9
isn't that difficult.)
(There aren't any hitches so far.)
(Clap)
(Clap!)
Wrong!
(We knew the pupil
would mess up first.)
Pound on his back.
Suk Jin receives a point.
(He doesn't know what he got wrong.)
(They switch it up
to Silent 007 next.)
(Bang!)
(0, 7, bang!)
(Argh! Argh!)
(0)
(0, 7, bang!)
(Argh! Argh!)
(0)
(0, 7, bang!)
(Argh! Argh! Argh?)
(Why would the pupil be shocked?)
Suk Jin got it wrong.
(Seok Sam gets it wrong
twice in a row.)
Suk Jin now has two points.
(Let's slow down a bit.)
(The speed is too fast
for the pupil.)
(Seok Sam needs time to adjust.)
(We'll go with Silent Word Chain.)
(We'll go this way.)
(Hopping)
(Frog noted.)
(Frog)
(A word that starts
with the Korean syllable "ri")
(He's delicately describing
a ribbon.)
(Ribbon noted.)
(Easy, right?)
(What on earth was that?)
(You didn't get it?)
Ji Hyo.
(Blinking)
3, 2, 1.
Ji Hyo receives a point too.
(Time's up and
Ji Hyo receives a point.)
The three already spent
400 dollars while shopping.
(They already spent 400 dollars.)
(Se Chan takes his time.)
Can a woman wear this too?
I'll buy one for So Min.
(The newlywed buys an item
for his wife.)
Meanwhile,
I'll buy this for myself.
I'll take this one.
Sure.
Seriously?
("Hapjeong Station, Exit Five"
by the human cultural asset)
(Chorus by newlywed Yangsebari)
All right, come on!
I'll take two!
I'm here to spend money, people.
(He seems to have experience
being in a chorus.)
How much have I spent so far?
Your total is at 180 dollars.
180 dollars?
I'll take one that 20 dollars then!
I'll spend a total of 200 dollars.
(He goes big
by spending 200 dollars.)
Since it's winter,
I should get something warm.
How adorable.
I'll take this one.
Look how cute it is.
(He isn't even checking the price.)
How adorable.
I'm glad I have all these gifts
for Haha's daughter.
(Uncle Jong Kook goes big
to help small businesses.)
This is great.
Let me see.
(The human cultural asset
values the fit of clothes.)
- I'll take this then.
- Sure thing.
- Can I get an unopened one?
- Sure.
So everything we buy...
will be paid for by the losing team?
Oh, dear.
The points are 2, 1, and 1.
This will be the last game you play.
If the two don't get it wrong,
will I end up paying?
That's right.
- I'll kick off the word chain.
- Sure.
So Min will go first.
The first word is "jean."
(A Korean word that starts
with the syllable "ji")
(Worm)
(A Korean word that starts
with the syllable "yi")
(Teeth)
(Teeth noted.)
Suk Jin, you're up.
(A Korean word that starts
with the syllable "bbal")
(- Let's pretend not to get it.
- Sure thing.)
(The Korean word that starts
with the syllable "bbal"!)
(I don't get it.)
(Being as frustrated as he is,)
(he starts rubbing his clothes.)
(Poor Suk Jin)
(Kwang Soo still pretends
not to know.)
(Are you still going to play dumb?)
Noted.
(Laundry noted.)
(The Korean word that starts
with the syllable "rae")
(He calmly starts expressing
the word that begins with "rae.")
(Haha gets it right away.)
(This seems to be
what he's describing.)
(Everyone seems to get it.)
Kwang Soo, you're out.
That begins with
the Korean syllable "re."
("Re" not "Rae)
(Embarrassed)
It wasn't the correct syllable.
(It serves you right
for teasing others!)
- "Rae" was the correct syllable.
- "Rae" not "re."
(The math genius lacks
in the language department.)
- It's "rae."
- Really?
What you described starts with "re."
And my word ended with "rae."
(Final score: Suk Jin 2, So Min 1,
Ji Hyo 1, Kwang Soo 1)
- It was the wrong syllable?
- Goodness.
- Rae.
- It was "rae."
- We'll conclude the game.
- Okay.
- Sure.
- You're back.
- Look.
- You bought a lot.
- Sure.
I bought a full set.
My gosh, that's heavy.
- Are you serious?
- Sure. I bought a full set.
- He's open-handed.
- I also bought shoes.
- My goodness.
- That looks great.
- It's adorable.
- It's so pretty.
I wonder what the human
cultural asset bought.
Is this enough?
- He also bought something good.
- Show us.
Thank you.
- This is crazy.
- I appreciate it.
- I bought a cardigan.
- For who? Is it for me?
It's for me.
I bought a cardigan
which was 199 dollars.
Good. That's the exact amount.
You bought one expensive item.
Sure. I got a good one.
- Honey, what did you buy?
- I bought a lot.
You should buy things for me.
He bought them for real.
You should wear this.
You should buy things only for me.
- And this is...
- A sweatsuit? My gosh.
How could he buy...
- Just wear it.
- But this is...
- This is...
- Is this a team uniform?
A team uniform?
And this is for the pupil.
Thank you.
Did you buy something for Seok Sam?
(As he receives
the unexpected gift,)
(he can't stop smiling.)
This is...
(He can't stop smiling.)
- Seok Sam must be happy.
- Seok Sam, that's cute.
I bought a shirt for him.
- That's nice.
- I need something that's worth...
- 20 dollars.
- It's a shirt.
This is nice.
- It's pretty.
- I love this shirt. It's cute.
I'll tell you about the amount.
The transportation cost
is 63 dollars.
And the amount spent
on shopping is 599 dollars.
- So it's 662 dollars in total.
- My goodness.
The person who will pay
662 dollars is...
What do we do?
(Ji Suk Jin)
- Ji Suk Jin.
- My gosh.
(Staring at him sharply)
We can do better next time.
- We can do better next time.
- That's a lot of money.
Let me tell you
about the second course.
- Okay.
- Good.
Why are you so bad at playing games?
You should try it yourself.
They are so good.
- "You should try it yourself."
- They play games so quickly.
There's no way I can beat them.
The second course is
the best photo zone on Jeju Island.
That sounds great.
It has a lovely view.
(There are spots for the best photos
along the beach.)
That's nice.
We've found many good places.
- I want to see rapeseed flowers.
- Okay.
And the next game is...
- Hello, It's Me.
- What?
- Hello, it's me
- Is it about this song?
(Is the game about
making a phone call?)
(She's tearing up.)
It's a team game.
Each team will select a player
to make a phone call.
- And?
- You can make a call...
- To a friend?
- to your family or friend.
And one of you will talk on the
phone pretending to be the player.
- I'm in trouble.
- And you shouldn't get caught.
- If I get caught quickly, I lose?
- Right.
So if they say,
"What's wrong? Is it really you?"
- Then I lose.
- Exactly.
- "Who is this?"
- I should call my brother.
If the person on the phone
sounds suspicious, you fail.
First, you need to decide
whom to call.
- I should call my dad.
- I'll call Se Hyeong.
- One from each team will call.
- How do you call your dad?
- "Dad." I just do this.
- Who should we call?
Hang on. Who should we call?
Who should it be?
Should I call my wife?
- She will notice it immediately.
- She will.
When we tried, we got caught
in less than a minute.
Really? How did they know?
But...
- Hey.
- I wasn't like that.
My wife is calling me.
Do you want to try talking to her?
(He got a call from Chaser.)
- Just talk to her. Don't whisper.
- Let me try.
You don't have to whisper.
Stay quiet.
Where are you, honey?
- Suk Jin?
- Where are you?
I was surprised by your voice.
(Was she surprised?)
(I thought it was someone else.)
I thought it was someone else.
I'm on my way home now.
- Where are you going?
- Home.
Did you have a nice day?
Gosh, you're Jae Suk.
(He gets caught only in 10 seconds.)
(Happy)
Jae Suk, my gosh.
- How did she know?
How did she know?
Su Jung, how did you know?
He sounded just like you.
I know. So you like your husband's
voice better, right?
- Sure.
- I knew it.
My gosh.
But why is your wife
saved as Chaser?
Su Jung.
(It's a sweet but scary name.)
- I didn't know that.
- Don't say that.
- Why is your wife a chaser?
- It's just...
- Okay.
- Su Jung.
- She's saved as Chaser.
- You should change it to runaway.
Su Jung.
Why are you with them?
Are you shooting the show?
- We're filming...
- She didn't know we were shooting.
(She didn't know about the shoot.)
She didn't know that. My gosh.
- She thought you were home.
- We're shooting Running Man now.
- She thought Suk Jin was at home.
- Su Jung.
Let's stop talking.
Hey.
Are they separated or what?
The more we talk,
the more I feel hurt.
- Okay.
- Bye.
I'll see you later, Su Jung.
Drive safely.
- She fell for it at first.
- She didn't know.
But she recognized you right away.
- Only in three seconds.
- That was funny.
- Who should we call?
- She has quick wits.
I'll call my dad,
and Ji Hyo will talk to him.
Ji Hyo.
But Ji Hyo's voice is...
- Ji Hyo has a unique voice.
- Gosh, this is...
There's no one in the world
who sounds like Ji Hyo.
Are you making a call right away?
Don't you need to practice?
- Ji Hyo is doing it.
- I rarely call my dad.
Hello, So Min.
Mom?
Yes. Why did you call?
(Her mom answered the phone
instead of her dad.)
Mom, where's Dad?
Your dad? Why?
Well...
Is this a mission?
(Your dad? Why? Is this a mission?)
(A mission?)
(She just thinks it's a mission.)
Yes, it's a mission.
You need to answer my question.
No, let your dad do it.
(She turns it over to her husband.)
- Hello?
- Dad.
- Yes.
- Dad, what's my nickname?
(Dad, what's my nickname?)
- Your nickname?
- My nickname.
- You have many. Parrot.
- Parrot?
(He's talking to the fake parrot
with no doubt.)
- Why?
- Ask him about his blood type.
What's your blood type?
Type AB.
What about me?
Yours is also type AB.
You take after me.
- I can't believe this.
- What?
Dad.
Who's your favorite member
in Running Man?
I like Song Ji Hyo.
(I like Song Ji Hyo.)
It's her.
(He likes Ji Hyo, but he doesn't
recognize her voice.)
He doesn't know.
What a coincidence.
I think she can talk to him
for three hours.
- She can do it for three hours.
- You know I like her.
All right. It's been nine minutes.
Dad, it wasn't me. It was Ji Hyo.
- Hello, sir.
- Dad.
I guess he wanted to be in our show
for a long time.
- I mean...
- He wanted to be on TV.
- He was so excited to be on TV.
- I think...
he was too excited
to notice her voice.
- I can't believe this.
- I didn't see this coming.
If she kept talking,
it would last for an hour.
It wasn't me. It was Ji Hyo.
I see. She sounded just like you.
What?
- Sir.
- I thought it would end right away.
- Hello, sir.
- How is it possible?
That was unbelievable.
You must be proud of your daughter.
I'm always proud of her
whether she's successful or not.
That's so nice.
I know. You're so proud of her,
but you don't recognize her voice.
I hope we will meet someday.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Thank you.
That was really good.
- Is it that Ji Hyo did a good job?
- I'm disappointed.
- I'm disappointed with Dad.
- That was fun.
It's important
not to get caught at first.
Then it goes well.
Shall we call Sae Ho?
- Sae Ho?
- Let's call Sae Ho. Who'll speak?
Who wants to try?
Who will talk to Sae Ho?
- You'll call Sae Ho?
- Yes.
- Hang on.
- Or we could try this.
"Hello?" As if he's pulling a joke.
- "Hello."
- As if he inhaled helium.
- Good idea.
- "Hello?"
So who will talk to him?
- Kwang Soo, you should try.
- Kwang Soo?
I think he'll notice it right away.
- I think he will.
- I think so.
- We don't know it yet.
- It's okay.
- Hello, Jae Suk.
- Where are you, Sae Ho?
I'm shooting a TV show now.
Really? Are you on a break now?
- Pardon?
- Can you talk now?
Yes. I can talk now.
You should go outside now.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
- I'm out.
- I'm going to...
give you a quiz,
so you should answer.
- What?
- I'm shooting Running Man now.
Okay.
First, say hello to our viewers.
- To viewers?
- Yes. Say hello to them.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Thank you so much.
I'm Cho Sae Ho,
and I was shooting a TV show.
I'm on a break now.
- I'm glad to talk to...
- Lower your voice.
- Sae Ho.
- Yes?
Lower your voice.
Okay. Nice to meet you.
Thank you so much.
(Obedient)
I'm Comedian Cho Sae Ho.
I'm glad to talk to you.
Sae Ho, make an acrostic poem
with my name.
- What?
- An acrostic poem with my name.
- An acrostic poem with your name?
- Yes. Yu.
Yu.
(You are so...)
(He starts singing right away.)
(He sings a serenade of
an acrostic poem moanfully.)
You should stop him. It's over.
I must say he succeeded.
- Hey, Sae Ho.
- Yes.
- How did you not know my voice?
- I can't believe this.
- It was Kwang Soo.
- Hello, I'm Kwang Soo.
That's not it. You suddenly
called me. What is going on?
- Do you not know what's going on?
- Sae Ho.
How could you
not recognize my voice?
- Well done, Sae Ho.
- Good job.
Sae Ho, you weren't so funny today.
It's not easy to be funny
while getting a perm.
- Okay. Thank you anyway.
- Sae Ho.
- Have a nice day.
- Thank you.
- Sae Ho.
- Nice.
- I'll call you again, Sae Ho.
- Good job.
- Thanks.
- So who won?
- Who will win this game?
- My gosh.
- And So Min...
- Do you want to call Hyuk?
- Let's call Hyuk.
- Do you want to try?
What do you usually say to him?
I won't tell you.
Why not? Hey.
You should tell me what to do.
- "What are you doing?"
- "What's up?"
- "What's up? Where are you?"
- "Hello? Where are you?"
- "It's me."
"Hey, where are you?
Where are you now?"
Don't do that.
- Don't you sound too sly?
- Wait a minute.
- Is that how you think of me?
- No, it's not like that.
- No, I don't think he's mean.
- How dare you.
Were you imitating Jong Kook?
- I was just focusing on your tone.
- Okay, try it again.
"Hello? Hey, where are you?"
- Aren't you mad, Jong Kook?
- "Did you eat?"
Do I sound that vulgar?
(Jong Kook's angry
to hear his vulgar tone.)
- Se Chan, you try calling Hyuk.
- All right.
- "Hello?"
- I think you can fake his voice.
Here's the ring tone.
Put it on speakerphone.
Look at it shaking.
Hey, Jong Kook.
Hyuk, where are you?
Me?
I'm on Olympic Boulevard
Expressway right now.
Where are you headed?
I just dropped the kid off.
I need to go home first
then I have to go to Gangneung.
So you're going to Gangneung?
Yes.
Have you eaten?
I will on my way to Gangneung.
You will on the way?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
I'm on Jeju Island.
The weather is great here.
You're in Jeju Island?
Yes, I finished filming.
The weather is so good.
Hey, doesn't Tae Hyun
call you these days?
Gosh, he keeps calling me.
I'm going out of my mind.
(He starts having small talk.)
Why does he call me
whenever he's drunk?
That's what he does these days.
(He starts to spin a yarn.)
I think he's obsessed with it.
Because I'm not answering his calls.
Is that right?
It's just making me go crazy.
I was dragged by him
a couple of times though.
- Gosh, he dragged you?
- He sure did.
(His reaction is so sloppy.
"Gosh, he dragged you?")
Hyuk, where are you?
- Who is this?
- "Who is this?"
Hyuk, where are you?
(There's no way they're going to
complete the mission anyway.)
Who is this?
I'm Jae Suk.
- He didn't know it was me.
- Hey.
- He really didn't know.
- Gosh, Hyuk.
- Even when I talked in my tone.
- I can't believe it.
- He really didn't know.
- Hyuk.
- It's so funny.
- Yes.
You've been talking to Se Chan.
There's no way
he sounded like Jong Kook.
I talked in my own tone.
- A voice he's never heard before.
- Hyuk.
- It's hilarious.
- Yes.
- How can he not know?
How can you
not know it's someone else?
(He still thinks it was Jong Kook.)
So who was I talking to?
- You were talking to Se Chan.
- I think he thinks you're me.
And you're talking to
Jae Suk right now.
Hyuk, please get it together!
- Hyuk!
(Laughing)
Hyuk.
How can you not recognize
Jong Kook's voice?
The truth is we're not that close.
What?
- Hey, you ruined my mission.
- I did?
It's not you, is it?
It is me!
(It is me!)
It's me, you fool!
(He's all confused now and
still can't recognize his voice.)
He can't trust anyone now.
Hyuk, you're so funny.
- Thanks. I'll talk to you soon.
- Thank you, Hyuk.
- All right. Bye.
- Thank you!
Take care of yourself.
I can't believe him.
- This is so funny.
- He talked so smoothly.
It's so easy to fool him.
Se Chan, call someone you know.
(Se Chan from Team Newlyweds
will try calling his friends.)
Who should I call?
How about calling Jae Joon?
- Kang Jae Joon?
- Yes.
- Jae Joon will notice it's not me.
- All right.
- Why don't Jong Kook call him?
- What do you usually call him?
- Do you speak casually with him?
- No, I speak formally.
- "Hello, sir?" Like this?
- As soon as he answers...
he says, "My goodness."
- "My goodness."
- "Where are you?"
- "I'm off work now."
- "My goodness."
- "Where are you?"
Jong Kook, sounds like him.
- "Jong Kook."
- Oh, that's it.
- You're good.
- That's good.
Then you should try calling him.
- Yes, you try it.
- Yes.
It's on speaker.
- My goodness.
- Where are you?
Are you home?
I'm somewhere I don't want to be.
Oh, gosh.
You mean you're home?
I'm at the office
of Comedy Big League.
I see.
- Wait a minute.
- I...
- Your voice is... Is this Se Chan?
- My gosh.
(Wait a minute. Is this Se Chan?)
- My goodness.
- It wasn't Se Chan.
- It wasn't him.
- It's me. I'm Jong Kook.
- Hey.
- Jong Kook, how have you been?
- Good.
We're on a mission right now.
Jae Joon, you recognized it too fast
so our mission is ruined.
(Let me talk to him.)
I'll let you talk to Se Chan.
Just a minute.
- All right.
- Bye.
My goodness.
Wait. This isn't him either.
- He noticed again.
- It's so hard to fool him.
- My goodness.
Hey, it's me. It's Se Chan.
Stop lying to me!
No, it's really is me!
- Come on. It's me!
- He doesn't...
- It's me!
- recognize the real one either.
- Jae Joon.
- He's suspicious of everyone.
(So Min talks to Ji Hyo's brother.)
(Playing word chain game with him
instead of carrying out the mission)
How can her family member
not notice her voice?
- I'll talk to you later.
- Thank you, Sung Moon.
- Here's the result of the mission.
- Okay.
Se Chan and So Min's team
completed the mission in 15 seconds.
But the others failed.
One more team can join them.
So pick one team
to take them with you.
This is good.
We won so we don't have to
pay for it though, right?
- Yes, you can save your money.
- That's right.
Then you should take...
these penniless guys with you.
- Yes, the old guys.
- These guys?
Yes, we should
take the old guys with us.
- Take pity on them.
- Yes, take them.
- Yes, take us.
- All right.
All right then.
- Chosen members should get off.
- All right.
- It's pretty.
- Wear your masks.
All right.
- The four can get off the bus.
- All right.
Have fun, guys.
We'll go take some pictures.
- See you.
- This is so nice.
So Min, it's this way.
Gosh, this is nice.
- It's amazing.
- It's so pretty.
I think it's this spot.
Photo of A Lifetime Course.
- Where?
- There.
Yes, this is it.
- There's something to eat too.
- We should take photos here.
Gosh, that's tangerine juice.
It's really delicious.
There's a Polaroid camera too.
Gosh, what's this?
You may choose the services.
The prices are listed on the menu.
So Min, you can buy that.
But come here first.
It's tangerine bread, isn't it?
- Let's buy the couples' bracelets.
- Okay.
- Choose one.
- Okay. It's pretty.
It costs 30 dollars.
I'll take two for me and my wife.
You said you're not married.
- I have a wife.
- Now he was a wife.
I'll buy these
for Ji Hyo and Na Eun.
- Then take two. Three?
- I will buy...
photo of your lifetime taken
by Chan Hee. It’s 50 dollars.
That's good.
We will take
the immortal photo of...
- The Polaroid camera.
- your lifetime taken by Chan Hee.
- Yes, I'd like that.
- I want photos from Chan Hee.
(Kang Chan Hee, Camera director
"Running Man", "Family Outing")
("X man", "Love Letter", "2 Days
and 1 Night", "Happy Together")
- Yes, Chan Hee will take photos.
- Okay.
Here we go.
Shouldn't the apprentice
be stand up?
Gosh, sit here then.
Shouldn't the apprentice
be standing up?
- I'll hold up the reflector.
- Okay.
What's with these two shots?
Smile at least.
What is this?
Is it done?
1, 2, 3.
(Clicking)
- You take one alone.
- All right.
- You need one for your funeral.
- For his funeral?
(His apprentice is
planning for his funeral?)
- Here it is.
- Yes.
I wonder how it came out.
I wish my bubbles are in it.
Here.
This looks like...
they're going to die soon.
Is it a photo of their spirits?
- Are we ghosts?
- Why did it come out like this?
It looks like
we're going to die soon.
- And it costs 50 dollars?
- Gosh.
Gosh, Chan Hee.
- Immortal photo?
- Where's your immortal photo?
What is this?
How can you make us
look like we're about to die?
Let me see it.
Gosh, this makes me sad.
- You two get a photo.
- Yes, we should.
- Hold up the reflector.
- All right. The reflector.
- Blow some bubbles too.
- Okay.
Blow some bubbles, please.
Hey, Mr. Human Cultural Asset.
- Help us out.
- All right.
(What a friendly
human cultural asset.)
- Seok Sam.
- Yes, sir.
(But he's strict
with his apprentice.)
"Seok Sam."
- "Hold this up."
- Okay.
Here we go.
Se Chan, move towards So Min.
- Okay.
- Look towards her.
Look towards her.
Wait a minute.
(His face turns
as red as his scarlet gums.)
Just do it.
Can't you take off your sunglasses?
- That looks nice.
- Gosh, the bubbles.
1, 2...
- Wait.
- Do you usually press on two?
1, 2.
(He pressed the shutter
on the count of two.)
- Wait.
- Do you usually press on two?
- Do you usually do that?
- You should press on three.
Is it normal to go on two?
Again.
- Here we go.
- Suk Jin, you're too close.
- I am?
- Get out of the way.
- Suk Jin, you're too close.
- Okay.
Only two of us
should be in the picture.
Suk Jin.
- Here we go.
- Ready.
1, 2, 3.
- This one will be good.
- Great.
- I'm sure of it.
- Yes, I'm sure.
- So Min.
- Yes?
I think you're really enjoying this.
(Look at this.)
- Let me see.
- Look at the photo.
- What is this?
- What's this?
This looks really weird.
What do I do?
It's weird.
We look too close.
- It's like you're really on a trip.
- Yes, this looks real.
- Come on. This isn't right.
- You two look real.
- Looks like you're really in love.
- Yes, they're in love.
You two look like
a couple on a honeymoon trip.
And you took a photo of us
looking like we're about to die?
- Come on.
- What's with our photo?
How can you make it look like
it's the end of our world?
- Their picture is so much nicer.
- What about our photo?
- Thank you.
- This photo's so funny.
- The photo is...
We spent 250 dollars on photos.
- How much did we spend?
- We can...
- How much?
- We can spend more.
Everyone, please get off.
(The other members are
where they can't see the ocean.)
Four of you can't take photos here.
But one of you will have
to pay for the photos.
You'll play Tumbling Tug-of-War
to decide who will pay.
- Tug-of-war?
It's a one on one tournament.
Two members will wear...
belts attached
at each end of the spring.
You have one minute...
to make the CD in the middle
move towards your opponent.
- Towards your opponent's side?
- Yes.
You lose if the CD is close to you.
The one who loses until the end...
will pay for the photos.
So the CD
should be far away from me?
- That's right.
- Okay.
Let's start
with Lee Kwang Soo and Haha.
- Ready.
- How do I do this?
- The black mark is the middle.
- Set.
(Nervous)
(Game begins)
Haha, you're doing great.
That's it! Great!
(Swinging his hips quickly)
Okay! That's great.
(Seems like the CD likes Kwang Soo)
(Mathematics genius
learned games from book.)
(This is fun.)
Gosh, Kwang Soo!
Great. Swing it more.
(This isn't working.)
(Disgusting hip movements)
(His moves are embarrassing.)
No, you can't let him win.
Okay. There you go.
You can't use your wrists like that.
Okay. Again.
- No.
- You can do this.
- 4, 3...
- We need to go!
(Will Kwang Soo win like this?)
(Game over)
(The whistle was blown.)
What is happening?
(Centerline)
(The CD moved toward Kwang Soo
beyond the centerline.)
(What? Why is it coming toward me?)
(Assistant Manager Ha won after
an unexpected buzzer beater.)
- It passed the centerline.
- But this is...
- The finishing point matters.
- Yes.
- Kwang Soo.
- Gosh.
- Gosh, this is...
- This is so funny.
- Why am I dizzy?
- Should I go?
- Ji Hyo, you must win.
(Round 2,
Jong Kook versus Ji Hyo)
This is amazing, Jong Kook.
We just have to win this round.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
It's over for us
if you lose this round, Ji Hyo.
Let's win.
- Ready.
- Move your hand away from it.
(It's a game
on the edge of a cliff.)
We must win.
- Do it the other way.
- That's it.
Do it the other way.
- Ji Hyo.
- Gosh.
- Jong Kook.
- Do it the other way.
(He's clenching his molars hard.)
Jong Kook, don't use your strength
too much from the beginning.
- Ji Hyo, you're doing a good job.
- What!
- Don't come toward me!
- Ji Hyo!
- Go the other way! You got this!
No.
- Don't come toward me.
- The other way!
That's right.
End it now.
Ji Hyo, endure it.
Endure it.
You're winning right now!
- Don't come toward me.
- You can do it!
(Don't come toward me.)
- Ji Hyo.
- Endure it until we win.
Please...
Four...
- 3, 2.
- Ji Hyo, don't give up.
That's it!
(Game over)
Why did you keep coming at me?
- Okay!
That's it.
- New Recruit Kim!
- He did it on purpose.
Our company's name is
actually "New Recruit".
Team Olympiad lost.
You will have to pay for everything.
- Okay.
- We're going to win.
- We might come in first.
- I know.
I think it will cost a lot of money.
- We lost.
- That's right.
We will take everything like
family and group photos.
(They spent money for no reason
without even seeing the sea.)
- Come here, let's take a photo.
- Okay.
(They're posing like partners.)
Come here.
(Ji Hyo also joined the selfie.)
Kwang Soo.
Aren't you going to join them?
- Let Lee Kwang Soo in the photo.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
We're done. We're done
taking photos.
- Let's go.
- We're done.
We're done taking photos.
We took a lovely photo.
- The sky is lovely.
- Hurry up.
- There's no airplane passing by?
- No.
Kwang Soo, hurry up and leave.
(He just spits out harsh words.)
(They heard everything.)
An airplane passed by.
- It was an airplane.
- Where?
- There's an airplane over there.
- Kwang Soo.
It already passed by far away.
(The course ended by just leaving
several wounds on Kwang Soo.)
- Okay.
- Please get in the car.
- This is so funny.
- That's right.
- Did you take photos?
- It's so funny. What should I do?
- Take a look.
- You should try one of these.
- This is so...
- But you look really...
- close and lovely in the photo.
- Who wants some tangerine juice?
- Me.
- I want some.
- Try this.
- This is funny. "Newlyweds."
We'll get going now.
This is really good.
- It looks good.
- You gave him the good picture.
- The total fee we used is...
- Yes?
We spent a lot.
You became sentimental.
Take a look at that.
Look at the horizon.
Look at the sunset.
(While everyone is immersed
in the scenery,)
(Suk Jin is stealing snacks.)
(Gosh, Suk Jin.)
(The pupil is not romantic since
he's worn out from the hardships.)
The sky is really beautiful.
We're on our way
to eat something good.
- Really? You should eat this.
- Yes.
This time...
(He returns the snack right away.)
- Suk Jin...
- Are you serious?
- His tone was...
- "You should eat this."
so detestable.
It's obvious that he was serious.
But he's...
- being serious.
- I was joking.
- Were you joking?
- You were serious.
- He wasn't trying to be funny.
- "You should eat this."
- He's serious.
He's being real.
I'm dumbfounded by the timing
I said that.
I'm sorry.
"You should eat this."
- Look at this view.
- Gosh,
look at this panorama. It's so nice.
Since the sun is setting,
it's making me slightly sentimental.
- Yes, my heart is...
- Do you know that?
- This is the third schedule.
- Yes.
We will enjoy playing
Jeju Island Full Course Feast...
with a clear ocean view
as the background.
Braised hairtail, which is a dish
that represents Jeju Island,
and all kinds of fresh seafood
have been prepared.
I'm going to eat this.
The number of people who will
enjoy the feast is five people.
- Let's eat.
- The number is too little.
- Five people...
- That's a lot.
It's out of eight people.
- Five people are doable.
- Yes, it is.
This game is Half Proverb Quiz.
It will be an individual match.
(The game will proceed
as an individual match.)
- It's not a team match.
- We shouldn't do proverbs.
It's advantageous to Team Olympiad.
That's possible.
- That's right.
- Proverbs are...
Five questions will be given
to each person continuously.
Listen to the last part
of the sentence...
- of the proverb we say.
- Okay.
Complete the front part
within three seconds.
- That's hard.
- Proverbs.
- You'll tell us the last part only?
- Only the last part?
If we say the last part,
you have the get the first part.
- The front part?
- There are a lot of hard proverbs.
- We will start right away.
- Okay.
- Let's start with this side.
If you can't say it
after we say "1, 2, 3.",
- you will be out.
- Okay.
Ready,
go!
It's better to get beaten...
1, 2, 3.
(It's better to get beaten...)
Okay.
- "It's better to get beaten"?
It's better to get beaten first.
- "It's better to get beaten first."
- I couldn't think of it.
This is confusing though.
- I'm not sure about this.
- This is hard.
- It's better to get beaten...
- This is the second question.
"The best side dish..."
1, 2, 3.
- Quail eggs!
- Hunger!
(Quail eggs?)
- "Quail eggs"?
- What do you mean by "quail eggs"?
- Is it "quail eggs"?
- It was "Hunger."
- Quail eggs...
- Quail eggs are also a side dish.
Quail eggs are a side dish.
- Please give us a little more.
- This is hard.
It's too far back.
- This is the third question.
- Okay.
This is hard though.
Spraying ashes on...
Cooked rice.
(Spraying ashes on cooked rice.)
(The members figured out
the answer right away.)
- Spraying ashes on cooked rice.
- No way.
(Timeout)
(It was close, but she failed.)
How could we not answer
even one question?
But I think this is doable.
- Okay.
- We got zero points.
- I really don't know what it is...
- In my opinion...
- If we just get two right, we win.
- Here we go.
It's Lee Kwang Soo's turn.
I can't think of anything.
Don't even look at...
Trees you can't climb.
(Correct!)
(What happened to Kwang Soo?)
Even dogs won't catch...
Winter colds.
Summer colds.
(Even dogs won't catch
winter colds?)
- Summer colds.
- It's "summer".
- Winter colds?
A lot of people catch colds
in the winter.
- Winter colds
- Okay.
- I was close, but I got it wrong.
They say it's rustling...
(They say it's rustling...)
(It's a question that's even hard
for proverb expert Jae Suk.)
Effortlessly?
What is that?
(They say it's rustling
effortlessly?)
- That's not it.
- What is it?
What was it? It was something
related to sound.
The oak leaf says that
the pine leaf is rustling.
- That's right.
- That's it.
- I knew it.
- This is important.
- That's right.
- This difficulty will be intense.
This is hard.
- This is hard.
- This is the last question.
The sister-in-law is
more irritating...
Than the mother-in-law
who hits you.
- That's not it.
- It's "who stops the fight is..."
The sister-in-law who stops
the fight is...
The mother-in-law who hits you.
In my opinion, we will get to eat
if we get one question right.
- You will get to eat.
- It's Kim Jong Kook's turn.
- Okay, I'll try.
- It's really hard.
- I think Jong Kook will be good.
- I'm not sure.
- It's hard.
- Let's get going.
Your crotch will get ripped...
Crane legs will also...
It's "storks".
The crotch of crow-tits will get
ripped if they follow storks.
- It's "storks".
- Storks.
Crow-tits were following storks.
- I get what you're talking about.
- Crane legs.
I knew what it was.
- This is the second question.
- This is hard.
You can't see through
someone's mind...
Even if you know
1,000 fathoms of water,
you can't see through
someone's mind.
- It's "10 fathoms of water".
- 10 fathoms of water.
(It was close,
but it's a wrong answer.)
(Even if you know
10 fathoms of water,)
(you can't see through
someone's mind.)
- It's "10 fathoms of water".
- It's confusing.
- Gosh.
Please be quiet by his side.
I said it after the bell was struck.
"I said it after..."
- It's "10 fathoms of water".
This is the last question.
Jong Kook's proverbs are hard.
We will get to eat
if we get one question right.
You will get first place
if you get two questions right.
Rice cakes...
Give one more rice cake to
the child you hate? That's not it.
(Incorrect!)
- Rice cakes you can't eat...
- Rice cakes in drawings.
(He couldn't answer
such an easy question.)
But this is...
- They just gave this to you.
- Gosh.
- The last part is not enough.
- It's hard. I can't think of it.
It's easy after you hear the answer.
You don't know what it is.
I'm currently in first place.
- It's Haha's turn.
- Haha.
I'm getting confident though.
To sow the wind...
And reap the whirlwind!
(Correct!)
He's going to eat.
There will be a hole to survive...
Needle.
Needle!
(Because of So Min's distraction,
he says "needle".)
- Did you say that?
- Even mouse holes...
Even if the sky collapses,
there will be a hole to survive.
- It's not "mouse hole".
- Gosh.
- I'm angry.
- How could you not know this?
- This is a famous proverb.
This is the third question.
To deceive yourself...
- Cover your eyes!
- This was easy.
(Correct!)
- Cover your eyes...
- Haha is in first place.
- to deceive yourself.
To be honest,
his questions are too easy.
- My questions were too hard.
- That's right.
- Ji Hyo's was tough too.
- Okay, I got two.
The difficulty is too...
- There's too much of a difference.
- How hard it will be for me?
- Yes, it's like that.
- Yes.
Haha, you're in first place.
Whose turn is it now?
Se Chan or So Min?
- It's So Min's turn.
- That's right.
Junsobari.
- I don't think I'll get it right.
- So Min.
They will go on top
of the stove first...
A whimsical calf!
(Whimsical So Min said
the wrong answer.)
It's "well-behaved cat".
So Min, you...
- I...
- What did she say?
I suddenly didn't remember it.
- A whimsical calf?
- She's really whimsical.
Wait a minute. Yes.
This is the second question.
A well-behaved cat?
You will survive
if you recover your senses...
- A crazy man...
- What?
(She blatantly throws out
wrong answers.)
- It's "if you're in a tiger's den".
- Wait a minute.
- It's "a tiger's den", isn't it?
- A tiger's den.
- This was too easy.
- How could you not know this?
- Even if you're in a tiger's den...
This is the third question.
You can't give it to dogs...
- Someone else's habits!
- What is this?
- It's "your habits".
- Your habits.
- This was too easy.
- To someone else?
- To dogs.
- In my opinion, the meanings...
- It's easy when you hear it.
- of what I said are similar.
- That's right.
- Only the details were wrong.
- "A well-behaved cat"...
and "An eccentric cow"
are entirely different.
I said the first thing that came
to my mind.
- Let's go.
- You become dazed.
- Se Chan.
- Here I go.
- Let's go.
- Try to get one right.
Out of the blue.
(He just needs to get
one question right in order to eat!)
- A squid.
- A bolt!
(A bolt out of the blue)
- A bolt.
- Hey, it was a really easy one.
I will have no expectations.
I have zero expectations.
I can't tease him
because it's unbelievable.
You know how it is.
I couldn't say what I know
due to nerves.
A goby also jumps.
When a pencil squid jumps,
a goby also jumps.
(When a pencil squid jumps,
a goby also jumps.)
(He sounds like a pencil squid
that is upset.)
- When a gray mullet jumps...
- Is it a gray mullet?
- Yes, it's a gray mullet.
- It isn't a pencil squid.
I thought it was a pencil squid.
This is the last question.
He didn't get
a single question right.
With acorns.
(With acorns)
(He must get this question right
in order to eat!)
Comparing the heights.
(Comparing the heights!)
- That's wrong.
- It's "With acorns".
Dog food.
(Dog food with acorns)
- It's so embarrassing.
- The production crew is laughing.
Comparing the heights!
- The newlyweds are out.
- That was hilarious.
- Excuse me.
- Suk Jin.
I will show you the perfect score.
- Okay.
Suk Jin knows a lot of proverbs.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
Looks at the roof.
Dog... Dr. Dog.
(Looks at the roof)
- Dr. Dog?
He said he can get
all the proverbs right.
Hold on. Gosh.
I knew it had something to do
with "Dog".
I couldn't think of it.
- I didn't know...
- A dog that was chasing a chicken.
- what kind of dog it was.
- Let's go.
You glare at the Han River.
After scowling.
(After scowling,
you glare at the Han River.)
- Isn't it "After getting slapped"?
- After getting slapped at Jongno.
Is that it?
Where did "After scowling" come
from?
I couldn't think of it.
You kept going,
"How could you not know that?"
- "After scowling"?
- After scowling.
I suddenly couldn't remember it.
- Let's resume.
- Okay.
- A chicken.
- A dog that was chasing a chicken!
(A dog that was chasing a chicken!)
- My goodness.
- What is it?
What is the answer?
- Not a pheasant, but a chicken.
- What is up with you?
- You should try it!
You shouldn't have been so snobby.
- You should try it.
- After getting the same proverb,
you went,
"A dog that was chasing a chicken!"
This is the last question.
To Gangnam.
(Will he be able
to get the first part right?)
- You follow your friend.
- That was easy.
Hold on!
(You follow your friend to Gangnam.)
Hold on! Why did he get
such an easy one?
- Okay.
- It was too easy.
- Seriously.
- I mean...
- It was too easy.
I will go next.
- Jae Suk.
- All right.
- Let's see how well you can do.
- You know,
I need to get
1 or 2 questions right.
You only get three seconds.
You just need to get
one question right.
Let's begin.
And meat is for chewing.
(He often flaunted his knowledge
to other members.)
(Will the human cultural asset
get it right?)
- What?
- Song Dae Kwan.
- Insadol.
- What?
(- Song Dae Kwan.
- Insadol.)
You need strong teeth.
- Song Dae Kwan.
- Insadol.
Which proverb ends
with "And meat is for chewing"?
- What is that?
Words are for talking
and meat is for chewing.
- That sounds familiar.
- It's so difficult.
Why is it so difficult?
The difficulty level is too high.
Gets no wind.
This one is easy.
- It's easy.
- What was it? A household?
A household?
You were being so cocky earlier.
- What is it?
- A tree with many branches.
Gosh, I knew this proverb.
I have to get one right.
You only remember it
after you hear the answer.
- Okay.
- That was funny.
He might not be able to eat.
Keep you awake all night long.
- This one is easy.
- Late-learned thieving skills...
keep you awake all night long.
I thought it was
"Thieving for the first time".
Who came in last?
There must be many people.
- We came in last.
- 4 people got 0 questions right.
- 4 people?
- There is space for 1 more person.
Why don't the four of you play
rock-paper-scissors?
Why don't you give us
the same question?
- The one who answers should eat.
- Shall we do that?
Let's go.
And he asks to give you his bag.
(And he asks to give you his bag.)
Talk to a porter
and he asks to give you his bag.
(Talk to a porter
and he asks to give you his bag.)
(And he asks to give you his bag.)
(Se Chan is out.)
- Gosh, it's so easy.
- Do you know it?
You spare a man
and he asks to give you his bag.
Save a man from drowning
- There you go.
- That's right.
(Save a man from drowning
and he asks to give you his bag.)
- Okay.
- Is that the first part?
- The first part.
- Save a man from drowning.
- That's right.
- Jong Kook succeeded.
Why isn't it about a porter?
Save a man from drowning
and he asks to give you his bag.
It's about a drowning man.
Thus,
five members except for Ji Hyo,
So Min, and Se Chan will eat.
Okay.
(They acquire a stamp.)
What is this?
Oh, my goodness!
- It's the braised hairtail.
- What is this?
This is a meal you must eat.
It's tasty.
(Running Tour provides
a proper meal.)
- It's so tasty.
- Thank you.
Thank you for the meal.
- We got this dish.
- Let's mix it with rice.
Do you want some hairtail?
- Yes!
- Do you want some hairtail?
Please give us some.
Please give us a piece.
Then you should get
a question right.
What question?
I will give you three seconds.
Can I decide on a member?
- Devotion will touch the sky.
- I mean...
- Can I decide on a member?
- Devotion...
(The proverb quiz
left Se Chan traumatized.)
He asked if he can decide on
the member.
- I will decide on Ji Hyo.
- Okay.
Travels 400km.
A foot without words...
(A foot without words?)
- A word without feet...
- A foot without words!
- I am sorry.
- A word without feet.
I am sorry.
I can't believe she said,
"A foot without words".
- A word without feet...
- A foot without words!
- She was in a hurry.
The wrong proverb suits Ji Hyo.
The losers will play a game
to decide who will pay.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Thank goodness both of us won.
- I know.
- I will give you the game.
- Okay.
Se Chan will pay.
Okay!
- You lost.
- That was pretty far.
- The total of the meal is...
- How much is it?
- 374 dollars.
- What?
(374 dollars!)
It isn't as expensive as I thought.
The first place was
the most expensive.
You ate a lot.
The total is 370 dollars.
We will get coffee to go...
- and move on to the last mission.
- Okay.
- We should turn the tables.
- Let's do that.
(They completed the course.)
What comes now isn't a mission.
You just need to go to the cafe
and order coffee to go.
- Really?
- Who wants to go?
We will go.
No, no. My pupil is here.
- Your pupil.
- Seok Sam can go.
- Listen.
I have a few pupils too.
- Like who?
- What?
Didn't you say
you were born in 2002?
- He was born in 2004.
- 2004.
In which year were you born?
2001.
- He is older.
- You are older.
Why are you speaking so casually
to an older boy?
- Seok Sam.
- Why do I need to...
Why did I become someone
who was born in 2004?
Seok Sam, I can't believe you!
Do you want me to whip your legs?
What about my legs?
- He is polite to Jae Suk.
- Listen.
You look young. Why don't you go?
(Are you interested in me?)
Are you interested in me?
(Laughing)
He is happy.
- He is happy.
- He is single.
He said earlier that he is single.
Since I am going through puberty,
I am interested.
- Seok Sam, stay in your lane.
- He is going through puberty!
- This is insane.
The newlyweds and Seok Sam
should go.
That's a good idea.
We will go together.
Seok Sam, let's go together.
Okay, Seok Sam.
Why did I become a boy
who was born in 2004?
- Wait for us.
- Seok Sam, wait for us.
Okay.
- How pretty!
- Seom and Some.
- Hello.
- How pretty! It's pretty here.
I really like this.
Let's buy some bread too.
- Let's do that.
- Shall we get the corn sticks?
Two cups of iced chamomile tea.
The bread is incredible.
This is where you take photos.
Where?
- My goodness.
- Hey.
- How pretty!
- Shall I take a photo of you guys?
It would look really beautiful
during the day.
This is where you take photos.
I will take a photo of you guys.
- Okay.
- My goodness.
This is an amazing spot.
1, 2, 3.
(We are newlyweds for the day.
Seok Sam, take nice photos.)
- Give me the phone now.
- You should get your photos taken.
Should I keep my mask on?
- Smile.
- 1, 2, 3.
(He poses like he went to college
in the 80s and 90s,)
1, 2, 3. Let's do this.
Smile.
- Smile.
- 1, 2, 3.
(He is taking selfies.)
1, 2, 3. Let's move a bit here.
- Let's take it like this.
- It's prettier.
1, 2, 3.
(Seok Sam is excited.)
(Making a V-sign)
It came out really well.
(He is excited to see the photos.)
(Se Chan runs away
after fooling him.)
- This is nice.
- When you come to Jeju Island,
you should take a lot of photos.
Hold on. Hey.
Did you guys take selfies?
You took selfies. Okay.
It's okay.
It's okay to take selfies like that.
That's what you do
when you are newlyweds.
This place is the best.
The two of you should sit here.
Here?
What a shot!
Make a heart over your heads.
- That's so old.
- Go ahead and make a heart.
- Come on.
One... Go ahead and do it.
1, 2, 3.
- I should work with cameras.
- Why?
Are you good at taking photos?
This is a work of art.
- You take good photos.
- That's a nice photo.
- You take good photos of your wife.
- Yes, I do.
- I will take your photos for real.
- No.
- I am serious.
- Suk Jin.
- I don't need photos.
- I am serious.
I will take them for real.
- You need photos from here.
- I don't want to do that.
I don't like what I am wearing.
(Despite the complaints,
he poses in an old-fashioned way.)
- It's a good shot.
- One...
(He zoomed in on Suk Jin's face.)
I will focus on your face.
(This photographer eliminated
the background.)
Okay. You don't need to take
many photos.
(You can't tell if he is
in Jeju Island or Yeouido.)
He is handsome.
Suk Jin is handsome, isn't he?
I focus on the face
when I take photos.
I see.
- I don't focus on the background.
- It's nice.
- What do you think?
- You...
You zoomed in too much.
I focused on the face.
- I focused on the face.
- You zoomed in too much.
Be careful.
Let's get going now.
Is our order ready?
(They are waiting inside the bus.)
(Wriggling)
(He is distracted.)
You aren't a human cultural asset,
are you?
(He is too unfocused
to be a human cultural asset.)
What do you do for a living?
Aren't you a human problem?
- I am a human cultural asset.
- A human problem.
My drawing of an orchid...
costs 20,000 to 30,000 dollars.
You are an artist.
- Do you have a nickname?
- What?
- A pen name?
- Something like a pen name.
How could you call it a nickname?
A nickname?
You make it sound like a nickname
from school days.
Something like a silly goose.
A nickname! A nickname!
What's your pen name?
Do I really need to reveal it
to someone like him?
I am not sure
if you would know, but...
Do you know
who Johns Hopkins is?
- That came out of nowhere.
- Johns Hopkins.
- He is a famous painter.
- That's right, I respect him a lot.
(Reading the room)
Did you just say Johns Hopkins is
a famous painter?
- This is insane.
I can't have a conversation
with them.
- What?
- Johns Hopkins.
- He is a famous painter, right?
- Is he a stock investor?
- What?
He asked if he is a stock investor.
Seriously.
Johns Hopkins.
Do you have a favorite work of his?
- Yes.
- What is it?
"Deviation".
My favorite is "Jonathan's River".
"Jonathan's River".
- "Jonathan's River".
- It draws you in.
It's so frustrating to talk to them.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you laughing
because you understand it?
Of course.
- I respect him.
- You respect him.
All right. Make light work.
(A sudden quiz)
Let's.
(That's ingenious.)
That works too.
- She is witty.
She is witty.
- That cafe is a work of art.
- Why?
It's so nice.
Is it by the sea?
It's more than that. It's so big.
Here you go.
The packaging is pretty.
Thank you.
- Okay.
- Who is paying for this?
Seok Sam, thank you for the coffee.
- Okay.
- Is Seok Sam paying for this?
It will be included in the total.
The total wasn't that big.
(They go to the location
of the last mission!)
Are you satisfied with the trip?
- Yes.
- It's perfect.
I will now explain
which course remains.
Give us a chance to turn the tables.
- You can turn the tables.
- Really?
All right.
The best part of flying is...
- the in-flight duty-free shop.
- Yes.
On the bus,
- you can purchase a souvenir.
- Really?
- Each team can choose 1 souvenir.
- 1?
There is something
I need to tell you in advance.
Since we don't have time to visit
a souvenir shop,
So Min will sacrifice her free time
and go with us tomorrow.
- Good job.
- If you agree, we will give her...
- a penalty exemption card.
- I will go tomorrow.
- So Min?
- Yes.
- She is staying another day.
- We will give it to her.
- Okay.
- A penalty exemption card.
- Really?
- You will have a shoot tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- If you don't want it...
- I want it. Give it to me.
- It's yours.
Choose a souvenir
So Min will buy it tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Let's see.
Let's see.
- The hairtail set.
- It's expensive.
It's the real deal.
I want to buy wine.
- I like tilefish.
- Tilefish is the best.
- It has a long face.
- Then...
you should take a hairtail set
to your parents.
Thank you.
- It's for you, Seok Sam.
- The hairtail.
Yes, the hairtail.
We want tangerine wine.
- Tangerine wine.
- Let's drink wine.
We also want tangerine wine.
- Let's eat cheonhyehyang.
- Aren't you a student?
- Seriously.
- That's wrong.
- Hey, hey.
- Get the hairtail set.
Get the hairtail set.
- Seaweed chips.
- Eat hairtail.
He looks like seaweed chips,
so that should be his souvenir.
- Hairtail.
- How could you say that?
- You look like seaweed chips.
- It's your hair.
- I will get the hairtail set.
- Hairtail.
The total cost of the coffee...
and the expensive souvenirs
you have chosen is...
- 773 dollars.
- What?
That's the worst.
I forgot about the coffee.
The last mission will change
the rankings.
- I will explain the last mission.
- Okay.
- Soon, we will arrive at a cafe.
(Soon, they will arrive at a cafe.)
Two team members
will decide on the order...
and enter the cafe every one minute.
It's your mission to stay
without getting recognized.
- By whom?
- Only the cafe owner knows.
The part-timers and customers
don't know about the shoot.
- I have an advantage.
- How about the cameras?
The staff members
are already hiding in the cafe.
(The staff members
are ready to film!)
Two members will enter the cafe
at a time.
The 2nd team will enter
after 1 minute.
If your name gets called,
you are out.
That team will get the penalty.
(You are so-and-so, right?)
What if someone says,
"You look familiar?"
- No, your name has to be called.
- Your name.
Wait until everyone enters the cafe.
If all eight members enter
without any names being called,
then you need to take turns
to order the drinks too.
- Can I take off my glasses?
- Of course.
- People don't recognize me.
- We are allowed...
- to cover our faces, right?
- Can we wear...
- a hat?
- You can wear a mask and a hat.
Can we wear sunglasses?
But I am wearing modern hanbok.
It will catch people's eyes.
- You should wear a jacket.
- This is bad.
Let's play Race of Wits
for the order.
- The losers go first.
- Yes.
- It's Race of Wits.
- Race of Wits.
Don't stand up. Call out the number.
- Get ready.
- Set.
- I will go first.
- I will go fourth.
- Go.
One.
- 2.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
- 6.
- 2.
- 3.
- 4.
- 5.
- 6.
- 7.
Okay.
(Seok Sam and Kwang Soo lose.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
He is so cute.
- Kwang Soo is cute.
- He is cute.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Team Olympiad will go first.)
- Okay.
- What happens if Kwang Soo goes...
and gets caught?
- Then it's game over.
- Is it game over?
That won't do.
Don't send in Kwang Soo first.
No, no. You just need to hang in
for a minute.
Okay.
A hat and a mask, right?
Let's do this.
My hair at the back of my head
is too long.
Kwang Soo,
you look suspicious already.
(They even turned off the light.)
Should I put on a cap?
You look suspicious.
People will recognize you
as soon as you enter.
Kwang Soo, it's game over.
- You should know that.
- No.
- I will show you.
- Don't get your hopes up.
- Do you have a cap?
- Where is it?
(The 1st team,
Team Olympiad gets off.)
People rarely recognize me,
but you are too recognizable.
I am wearing a school uniform too.
(Anyone will be able to tell
that he is Lee Kwang Soo.)
I am too tall to be a high schooler.
You are too tall
to be a high schooler.
We need to go that way.
Isn't that the cafe?
(They act natural
and approach the cafe.)
(However)
Why are there so many people?
(Since it's 7:30 p.m. on a weekday,
the cafe is packed...)
(with students and office workers.)
Let's sit down first.
(Safely filmed
in adherence to the guidelines)
(The two students enter.)
(The cafe is packed with customers.)
(A customer looks at Kwang Soo
as soon as he enters.)
(Thankfully, he didn't recognize
Kwang Soo.)
(A staff member's cell phone)
(They walk past the customers
without ordering.)
Let's sit over there.
(They arrive at a secluded place.)
This table is perfect.
No one will look at us.
(At that moment,)
(a customer looks at Ji Hyo!)
(She turns her head away.)
We look natural.
(Team Olympiad sneaked in
pretty well.)
(Staring)
I see more seats over there.
(What?)
(Is she looking at Kwang Soo?)
(Kwang Soo was looking
for a more secluded spot...)
(when a female customer looked
in his direction!)
(Did she recognize Kwang Soo?)
(Uninterested)
(She resumes talking to her friend.)
Let's not move.
(This high school student
who is 2m tall can't even stand up.)
Let's not move.
(While Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo
overcame many crises...)
- What?
- That's too obvious. I'm not lying.
Really?
(Jong Kook and Haha can't
hide themselves.)
- We need to cover the mic.
- What?
(They look like they're here
to take over the cafe.)
Is it here?
- Hello.
- They're here.
- Jong Kook and Haha are here.
- They're here?
(Staff's phone)
Hello.
(Humming)
- Hello.
(Jong Kook tries to act normal
by humming.)
(To be safe,
they must grab a seat first.)
(Jong Kook sits down.)
(Haha moves to the other side.)
(They're going to split up
to avoid suspicion.)
(Jong Kook, Haha)
(They safely grab a seat.)
(After 1 minute...)
- What?
- Hey.
Don't worry.
- Is it here?
- Look at our pants.
Our pants are...
- Is it here?
- I think so.
- It's here.
- Seriously.
(Staff's phone)
(2 people in weird hanboks appear
in a cafe full of young people.)
Your pants are embarrassing.
Jae Suk.
That's so weird.
That's obviously Jae Suk.
He looks weird.
(They steal people's attention.)
(As they walk, they can feel
people looking at them.)
Let's go somewhere else.
I didn't know it was this bright.
(People in the cafe are stirred.)
Why is it so bright?
(They move in a rush.)
(What?)
(They enter a room.)
What's this place?
- Why is it so bright?
- What's this room?
I didn't expect it
to be this bright.
- What's this room?
- What's this?
I think some people recognized us.
- What?
- Some people recognized us.
I think they recognized us.
I noticed my pants...
I saw you from the back.
You look like a martial arts player.
You should go place an order.
- I was so flustered.
- People here don't know.
(However,)
(someone's approaching them.)
She's looking at Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- I think she's looking at us.
This is bad.
(Glancing)
(Please don't come.)
(Jong Kook's glancing at them.)
People here don't know yet.
Should I sit somewhere else?
I think some people noticed.
They're here.
Who are they?
Se Chan and So Min.
(After 1 minute...)
They're here.
They covered their faces perfectly.
- Hello.
Don't they look weird?
- They look suspicious.
- They're wearing matching.
- They look so weird.
- My goodness.
They're wearing matching clothes.
That's so weird.
- They're wearing matching clothes.
- What's up with them?
Are they placing an order?
Are they?
(Staff's phone)
What are you having?
I'll sit over there.
(So Min's going to place an order
to avoid suspicion.)
What would you like?
Well...
(While So Min's ordering,
Se Chan sits in the corner.)
They're ordering something.
Well...
I'll have two iced tea.
(The employee raises his head...)
(upon hearing So Min's voice.)
(Will he notice that it's So Min?)
- Two iced tea?
- Yes.
- For here?
- That's 5.8 dollars.
I got so nervous
that I ordered iced tea.
- Good job.
- Because I was so nervous.
I was so nervous.
I didn't know what to order.
- Let's go over there. Let's move.
- Is there a table?
- Let's move over there.
Okay.
- Over there.
- Let's go.
(They feel pressured
since it's open.)
(They quietly move
to the partitioned area.)
(What?)
(A glass wall?)
There's a glass wall.
Why is there glass?
(He almost broke a glass
for trusting Seok Sam.)
There's glass.
You said there's a door.
It's glass.
There's a table. We have to go now.
We have to go now.
- We have to go.
- Let's go.
(They try to move
to the partitioned area again.)
(Running Man members think...)
(they look natural if they put
their hands in the pockets.)
(They all grabbed a seat.)
You have to place an order.
We have to order.
(Since all 4 teams are here,
they have to order from Team 1.)
He's ordering something.
Kwang Soo is too obvious.
He's too obvious.
Do I look weird?
Look at me. Do I look weird?
Do we look weird?
Your order.
Do you have money?
Hello. What would you like?
- Peppermint...
- Hot chocolate...
(Despite altering his voice,)
(people focus on the 2m tall
high school student.)
Is it just one drink?
We're going to share.
Just one, please.
(When two students barely
place an order,)
(one customer gets up
and approaches them.)
(He approaches Kwang Soo.)
Excuse me.
(Excuse me.)
(He tries to talk to Kwang Soo
and Ji Hyo.)
(If a customer says their names,
they fail.)
Are you Lee Kwang Soo?
(Being careful)
(Pretending not to hear him)
Are you Song Ji Hyo?
You failed the mission. Come back.
(Team Olympiad fails the mission.)
(Oh, it's Lee Kwang Soo
and Song Ji Hyo.)
Kwang Soo got caught.
Right. He got caught.
- They got caught.
- Their mission is over.
They got caught.
(Hello.)
- Kwang Soo got caught.
- He got caught.
My goodness.
Kwang Soo. Did you get caught?
(The 2m tall high school student's
shoulders sag after failing.)
(A "V" for the win)
I told you not to open your eyes
like that.
Lee Kwang Soo got caught.
(Kwang Soo's arrest is delivered
to suspicious people.)
Is it over?
- It's over.
- Is it over?
- Did someone get caught?
- Yes.
(It's a surprise that
they didn't get caught.)
Did Kwang Soo get caught?
- He did.
- I saw it.
Who got caught?
Kwang Soo got caught.
- Okay, okay.
- That's a relief.
I was wrong to think...
- Where were you?
- I didn't see you. Where were you?
- I didn't see you.
- But...
- We were in a room.
- You don't know,
- but you all looked weird.
- Really?
- It's really suspicious.
- You were really weird.
When you walked in,
I almost called the police.
They looked so weird.
We were surprised.
It was so bright.
We were like, "My goodness."
- And our pants were flapping.
- That's funny.
- We all looked weird.
- We were all suspicious.
- Let's get in the car.
- Get in the car.
It's worth calling the police.
Here's the result
of the last mission.
- I will announce three winners.
- Who are they?
It's based on the number of stamps.
- Okay.
- Oh, stamps.
First place goes to...
(1st place completed 4 courses.)
Yoo Jae Suk.
- Really? You placed first?
- That's amazing.
- Me?
- Is it an individual play?
- He played a lot.
- Yes.
Second place goes to...
Ji Suk Jin, Kim Jong Kook
and Yang Se Chan.
- Oh, really?
- Me too?
- That's awesome.
- I didn't know.
We'll give these four people
a prize.
So Min will purchase the prize
tomorrow.
- Am I buying them tomorrow?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Goodness.
Now, I have to announce the penalty.
Do we receive the penalty as a team?
Yes.
It's an opening penalty.
(There will be an opening related
penalty in a month.)
Lately, the opening penalty's
getting weird.
It's getting weird.
- It's getting really weird.
- It's very childish.
- You have to come early.
- It's a hassle.
- It's troublesome.
- It's such a hassle.
Jae Suk and Suk Jin's
Team Human Cultural Asset...
has negative 655 dollars.
We spent a lot.
Team Asst. Manager Ha
and the New Recruit...
kept 10 dollars.
Team Newlyweds has negative
314 dollars.
Next, Team Olympiad...
has negative 1,212 dollars.
So they will have
the opening penalty.
- Lee Kwang Soo. Seriously...
- Come on.
That's the end of Part Two of
Jeju Island Special.
Thank you.
(The next day)
This place is really big.
I didn't know there was a duty free
in south of Jeju Island.
(Shopping completes the trip.)
I should pick what best suits them.
I heard lately Suk Jin enjoys wine.
This is perfect for Jae Suk.
(Sweet snacks for Jae Suk
who loves snacks)
I'll get cosmetics for Se Chan
and Jong Kook.
I'll make sure to deliver them
to Seoul.
(It's fall, the season of food.)
(Old restaurant tour in Seoul)
(Famous food lover idols,
Bo Mi and Nam Joo)
(People you want to eat with,
Hoshi and Mingyu)
(People you want to feed,
Kim Soo Yong and Nam Chang Hee)
(Find the real old restaurant
in Seoul with history.)
(If Soo Yong and Suk Jin go,
it's an old restaurant.)
It's 200 years old.
(No area...)
(or menu...)
(is set.)
(They must cast the place
themselves.)
We should go here.
(Hangover soup
with 84 years of history)
It's 100 years old.
(Ramyeon with 49 years of history)
(The older the restaurant is,
the younger they become.)
(They fight to eat...)
(and to reduce their ages.)
(What's the result of
the old restaurant tour in Seoul?)
(History of Old Restaurants)