(It's a summer day
with drizzling rain.)
Hello.
It's a cloudy morning.
Hello. Good morning.
I'm in Yangpyeong now.
(All the members start
the shooting separately.)
It wasn't raining
until just a few minutes ago.
I know.
(The phone rings
right at the moment.)
What's going on?
Answer it.
What?
Why are you calling me when you're
standing right in front of me?
Just pick it up.
(The director calls Kwang Soo
who stands right in front of him.)
Hello?
What are you doing?
What is going on?
Hello. This is Running High School.
I hear double voices.
Hello?
Hello. This is Running High School.
What? High school?
What did you say?
Running High School?
Your youngest sister, who's a model
student of Running High School...
and expected to go
to a prestigious university,
skipped school saying she would
take an audition to be a singer.
Darn it.
Please find your sister
and send her to school.
My youngest sister skipped school?
My youngest sister is
acting up again.
She wants to give up school
to become a singer.
- Exactly.
- I actually support her dream.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
That's what I did.
Today, we're going to have
Unstoppable Sisters Race.
There will be 4 teams of 3 members.
Suk Jin, your goal is to collect
as many academic points...
as possible with your siblings.
And you should make
the top two teams...
to have your sister graduate...
and get exempted from the penalty.
So there will be a penalty today.
At the same time,
your youngest sister...
can collect audition points
without her siblings.
The youngest sister
with the highest audition points...
will win a prize and
get exempted from the penalty.
And the second place
will also win a prize.
You should keep your sister
from winning audition points.
She will definitely try to get
more audition points and win.
Among the four sisters,
you should find your real sister
and send her to school.
Then you will get academic points
by the order of arrival.
Including the youngest sister,
once three siblings get together,
your siblinghood will be judged.
You should hold each other's
hands and say "We are siblings."
If you say it with a fake sister,
the sister will get
10 audition points.
(Once the 3 siblings get together,
they can move to the opening place.)
(If they are not real siblings,
the sister gets 10 audition points.)
If we pick a wrong person,
we will be helping her
pass the audition.
They are going to lie to us
to get 10 points.
They all are going to say
they are my sisters.
This is the cue card that has
your sister's location and number.
Ennik and Yong Sun?
(Hyun Ju, Young Ji,
Ennik, Yong Sun)
I don't have a sister
with such names.
Are these their real names?
- They are their real names.
- Really?
Yong Sun?
I'm in trouble.
I don't know any of them.
Is Young Ji a member of Jewelry?
Gosh, there's no way
I can go to an Ivy League college.
I'll just try my best.
(A high school rapper
with a sweet voice, Lee Young Ji)
(Popular rapper Lee Young Ji
is known for her sweatsuit.)
Can I just pick anything I want?
(They randomly picked
their siblings before the race.)
Can I take a look at it?
(Who are Young Ji's siblings?)
(Laughing)
(Haha and Lee Kwang Soo)
(Young Ji's siblings are
Haha and Kwang Soo.)
Nino Maximus Keyser Soze
(She seems really excited
even before the race.)
All right.
Hang on. Hyun Ju?
I think I know who she is.
(The second sister Hyun Ju is...)
One of the sisters already
picked her team.
Please pick one of the three cards.
(Jessi picks a card among three.)
Yoo Jae Suk!
(Yoo Jae Suk!)
(Jessi's brothers are
Jae Suk and Se Chan.)
Yang Se Chan.
(Jessi's brothers are
Jae Suk and Se Chan.)
(She's the natural enemy
of Jae Suk and Se Chan.)
(She's a Korean American
with a strong pride, Jessi.)
My goodness.
(Her natural enemies
are her family for today.)
I found it.
(The third sister,
Ennik's identity is revealed.)
Ennik is Jeon So Mi, right?
(Jeon So Mi, Ennik Somi Douma)
(So Mi is back with her new song,
"What You Waiting For".)
(Today, she's a daring sister
who never listens to her brothers.)
Oh, no.
(Who on earth are her siblings?)
Am I supposed to be happy about it?
I picked Jong Kook and Suk Jin.
So Jong Kook
is coming to catch me...
while shouting "Sparta"?
(He's a scary brother
with a big build.)
Can I just go back to school?
(She became a model student again.)
Yong Sun? Who's Yong Sun?
It means a ship for the king.
(Yong Sun is...)
Hello.
(Solar of MAMAMOO.)
(Solar has an enthusiastic zest
and brilliant charisma.)
(This is her first time
to join Running Man alone.)
(Solar's siblings are
Ji Hyo and So Min.)
Solar, your siblings are...
Song Ji Hyo and Jeon So Min.
Okay.
(Jae Suk, Jessi, Se Chan,
Jong Kook, So Mi, Suk Jin)
(Ji Hyo, Solar, So Min,
Haha, Young Ji, Kwang Soo)
This is what I'm going to do.
They all are my family.
Okay? The problem is
they will recognize my voice...
once I call them.
Hang on.
Hello? It didn't sound like me.
It was like a guy.
Hello?
I should fake my voice.
Hello? Right. I'm your sister.
Can I say I'm their sister?
Okay. Gosh.
- Hello?
Is this Hyun Ju speaking?
Yes.
Are you Ms. Baek Hyun Ju?
Yes, I am.
- I see. It's you.
- Right.
I know who you are.
You're a member of SEEART.
- Right?
- Yes.
It's you. I know everything
about SEEART.
I already know everything
about today's guests.
Because Hyun Ju is my sister.
Suk Jin, I'm your sister.
- Shall we go together then?
- Let's do that.
- All right then.
- Okay.
- Bye.
(He totally fell for my lie.)
My gosh.
(She gets another call
while feeling excited.)
What? It's Kwang Soo.
Hello?
- Hello?
What...
Isn't it Jessi?
(Isn't it Jessi?)
What was that? He hung up on me.
I'm very offended.
Jessi, I'm sorry.
Why did you hang up on me like that?
I'm so sorry, Jessi.
I was just surprised.
Did you pick two members?
Yes. I picked two members.
Who are they? Am I one of them?
You are one of them.
And there's one more.
Who is it?
Well... It's Suk Jin.
(She lies to Kwang Soo.)
What? My gosh.
What was that? He hung... Hey!
Hang on. It's Jae Suk.
(It's Jae Suk's call.)
Hello?
(She changes her voice
even when she talks to her brother.)
Hello?
- Yes?
- Hyun Ju.
Yes.
Hyun Ju, are you my sister?
I'm your family. Come over here.
You're Jessi, aren't you?
(You're Jessi, aren't you?)
(Laughing)
I told you you shouldn't say,
"Hyun Ju".
It said, "Hyun Ju",
so I thought that was your name.
I didn't know you were Jessi.
I mean...
Hurry up and come over here.
You're my family.
- Hurry up.
- Come on.
Come on. Hurry up. It's raining,
and I have a stomachache.
My T-shirt is too tight.
Hey.
It's not like I picked it out.
Why are you complaining to me?
Anyway, come over here.
You're my brother.
Are you sure?
- Okay. I'll come over.
- There's one more person.
- I trust you. Okay, see you.
- See you.
(Meanwhile, Solar...)
- The phone is ringing.
- Take it.
- Hello.
Hello. Hi.
Do you even know who I am?
(Solar's siblings:
Ji Hyo and So Min)
Is this Haha?
(Is this Haha?)
Wait, Solar.
I'm obviously not your brother.
That's not it. You are. That's why.
To me, you totally sound...
like you're lying.
(You totally sound like
you're lying.)
I'm not your brother,
- but you want 10 points.
- That's not it.
(Solar sounds like she's lying.)
You're one of my siblings.
- So just come over here.
- Okay.
Anyway,
just come.
I can't really tell from your voice,
so let's meet.
Okay.
(It worked.)
Where are you, my precious sister?
- What are you doing?
- Hi, Se Chan.
- Hi.
- Should I go out?
- You're wearing a school uniform.
Yes.
I'm not going to school.
All of a sudden?
(She suddenly starts acting?)
- What are you talking about?
- I mean...
- You brat.
- I'm not going to school!
Come on, Solar. Your brother...
has been looking everywhere for you.
Hold on.
- Hello.
- She's always looked down on me.
Hello.
- Who is it?
- Yong Sun.
(The second person
who fell for Solar's lie appears.)
- Yong Sun!
- Her eyes... Oh, Haha is here too.
- I'm sorry. I have to go.
- Hey.
- Yong Sun!
- Yong Sun, please don't do this.
- I'm not going to school!
- Hey.
- I'm not going!
Think of how Mom raised us.
Go away!
I'm not going to school!
Are you insane?
- Don't hit her.
- How dare you...
The thing is, we somehow
look like each other.
- Kind of.
- Right?
You look like both of us,
but in a good way.
(You look like both of us,
but in a good way.)
- Don't you admit it?
- You're right.
All right. I'm sure we're siblings.
- Yes, definitely.
- Definitely.
- 1, 2, 3.
- We're siblings.
You're not real siblings.
- Gosh!
(She fooled us!)
What happened?
It's raining.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
Solar, you gained
10 audition points.
- Unbelievable.
- Yes!
You... Okay, I get it now.
- Goodbye.
- You should become a good singer.
(After getting what she wants,
Solar says goodbye to them.)
Neither of us is her sibling?
(Running)
Let's run.
- Solar wasn't my sister.
- Gosh.
(They start looking for
their real siblings.)
I have this nagging feeling
that Jessi is my sister.
I wish So Mi was my sister.
Please.
She's in the van?
(Kwang Soo came to meet Jessi.)
(Happy to see her,
he bursts out laughing.)
- Come on, get in.
- You're wearing a school uniform?
This school uniform
is way too tight.
- Get in.
- I mean...
Is no one else here?
Too much is happening right now.
Hyun Ju!
(Her real brother, Jae Suk,
appears.)
- Jae Suk is here.
- Hyun Ju...
He's not my brother.
- Tell him he is.
Hi, Jae Suk.
Why is it so crowded here?
- Is it really Hyun Ju?
- I just got here.
Hyun Ju.
Why are you wearing so much perfume?
A girl should smell good.
I mean...
Gosh, it's giving me a headache.
I'm dizzy. I breathed
through my mouth in the car.
My shirt is too tight.
I can't breathe.
- You're the one who tightened it.
- Hey.
- Loosen it.
- Unbelievable.
- It's tight around here.
- I mean...
- Hey, come on.
- It's tight in the armpits.
You tightened the shirt yourself.
It's tight around here.
I get it. Stop.
- Gosh.
- Okay.
Why did you only tuck your shirt
in the front?
- It's a style.
- Why would you do that?
- What is that?
You're unbelievably tall.
How can you say that
to your big brother?
How can she say that
to her big brother,
- looking him up and down?
- "You're unbelievably tall."
Let's give it a go.
- No. Hold on.
- No?
I'm not sure if you're my sister.
She's been saying this
the whole time.
She told me you were her brother.
- To tell you the truth,
- Gosh.
you guys are my siblings.
We are siblings.
- Let's give it a try.
- Okay.
- What are we supposed to do?
- Say, "We're siblings."
- Let's hold hands.
- We're siblings.
1, 2, 3.
(We're siblings.)
You're...
- not real siblings.
- See?
See? I told you.
She told me
you weren't her brother.
(What?)
- Bye.
- Suk Jin and I are her brothers.
Gosh, why are you doing this?
I don't know.
- So you are her brother?
- Yes.
- My goodness.
- From the beginning...
Why didn't you tell me?
- I'm leaving.
- How does this work?
Just wander around
in the rain for a bit...
- and be penalized later.
- This is so annoying.
(I'll call you again soon.)
Should I try with Young Ji?
(Jessi's real brother, Jae Suk,
hurries to the next person.)
Young Ji, are you sure
I'm your brother?
- Is this Jae Suk?
- Yes, that's right.
Oh, my. Jae Suk.
Nice to meet you. Hello.
From the way you talk to me,
- I can tell we're not siblings.
- Right? No.
Don't I totally sound
like your little sister?
We're family.
All right, Young Ji.
Who is your other sibling then?
- My siblings are...
- Okay.
you and...
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo says
he is Jessi's brother.
What? Why would he do that?
Can you bring him over to me?
- Is Kwang Soo your brother?
- Yes.
Jessi says he's her brother.
- If someone comes...
- Jae Suk is calling me.
Hi, Jae Suk.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- Listen carefully.
- Okay.
(Whispering)
You're not Jessi's brother.
(You're not Jessi's brother.)
- What?
- Young Ji...
- Just keep quiet and listen to me.
- Okay.
I'm listening. I'm right here.
(He gets caught by Jessi.)
- Hey, I mean...
- Who is it again?
- We're on the phone.
- Who is it?
Just because you whisper
doesn't mean she can't hear you.
You hang up!
Hold on. Hello?
Gosh, they hung up on me.
They hung up on me.
Be honest with me.
- Seriously.
- Ji Hyo is not my sister.
- So who is it?
- I'd feel bad if she comes.
- Who is it?
- Kwang Soo, where are you?
I'm with Jessi.
She's driving me crazy.
- What's his name?
- The thing is...
I'm in trouble.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Why?
I can neither stay nor leave.
(Meanwhile...)
(Haha came to meet...)
(So Mi, who isn't his sister.)
- Haha!
- Ennik!
(My little sister, Ennik!)
Am I...
You're my brother, seriously.
- Are you sure?
- I swear.
Ennik!
(Se Chan arrives,
who isn't her brother.)
You...
- You...
- Hurry!
When did you run out?
Hold on.
Se Chan is running to her. Gosh.
- Four people...
- Hold on. Let's wait for Jong Kook.
- Hurry!
- Hold on.
- So Mi!
- What's going on?
- I'm scared. Let's say it already.
- What's with him?
So Mi!
Why are you not going to school?
He's getting into it. Look at him.
- These guys...
- Look at him.
- We're siblings.
- You brats...
You're hanging out with So Mi?
- No, we aren't.
- She should go to school.
(Let my little sister go.)
- You little...
- Hold on.
- You know me, right?
- You two might be brothers.
- I'm your little brother.
I'm your little brother.
- All right.
- You're my big brother.
- Gosh.
- She's trying to win points.
- I'm sure she's my little sister.
- We're siblings. In 1, 2...
- We're siblings.
- No.
- You're not siblings.
We aren't siblings.
- Move.
- Wait. I'm not her brother?
- You're not.
- Neither of us?
Jong Kook, hold her hand.
- You gained 10 audition points.
- So Mi.
- I'm your brother, right?
- Yes, you are.
I'm pretty sure.
- Let's give it a try.
- Ready, go.
- We're siblings.
You're not siblings.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
You're not siblings.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
- But...
- So Mi.
- Wait, is Jong Kook your brother?
- You gained 10 audition points.
- I must be her brother.
- Yes.
- Really? I am?
- You three...
- Go away, you punks!
- Go away!
- How dare you mess with my sister?
You're a bad influence.
Hey, you and I might be brothers.
Se Chan and I might be brothers.
- Let's try.
- Hold hands.
- They're only getting her points.
Let's try.
- We're siblings.
- No.
- You're not siblings.
That was a good idea, right, So Mi?
- Good job.
- Right?
Go away.
Jae Suk.
Se Chan.
- Hey.
- Go away!
I'm with So Mi,
and she's not my sister.
She's not?
No. The problem is,
I might end up with Hyun Ju.
Gosh, this is bad.
I don't want to be siblings
with Jessi.
Even if she's my little sister,
I'm scared of her.
- Hey, Brother!
- Hi!
- Hyun Ju!
- My brother!
- My little sister!
- This is real.
- Seriously...
- Finally...
- Why did you not listen to me?
- All my siblings are here.
- We're siblings, right?
- Suk Jin. Gosh.
Here we are, finally.
- The three of us.
- I mean...
- She said it from the beginning.
- I know.
- To be honest...
- You didn't sound so convincing.
Also, she doesn't know the rules.
Be quiet.
- Let's give it a go.
- Let's try. Stand here.
- Stand in the middle.
- If we're siblings...
- Say, "We're siblings."
- All right.
- We're siblings.
You're...
We're siblings.
not real siblings.
Hey, you.
- You're not my brother.
- This is driving me crazy.
To be honest,
- you're not. Go now.
- Hey.
- You're not my brother.
- Hey!
- Who is it then?
- I ran all the way here.
- Am I your brother?
- Yes.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- You said it was him and me.
Gosh, I'm leaving. Hey.
You're not her brother either,
you fool.
- You're not.
- You said from the beginning.
- Suk Jin isn't my brother.
He's a fool.
- Where are you?
- Jong Kook, where are you?
Where are you now?
I'm with So Mi now.
(His real brother, Jong Kook
calls him right on time.)
I'm with So Mi.
I don't want to study.
You should at least graduate.
What's the use of graduating?
Hang on. Your second
sister is coming, you brat.
Gosh, you are unbelievable.
If you're my sister,
you'll be doomed.
- Hello, Ji Hyo. Hi!
- So Min.
Hello, So Min.
Wait... Well... You...
Hang on.
If she insists that we're
her sisters, that means we're not.
- They're here.
- I just abandoned So Mi.
All right. We are...
You should say it with me.
- We are siblings.
Hang on. I just saw Yong Sun's eyes.
- No, I'm serious!
- Her glaring eyes.
Seriously, I'm your sister.
Look at her.
- She seems very excited.
- Hang on.
- This is strange.
- That's because I'm your sister.
- Hang on.
- Because it's true.
- This is crazy.
- We are...
- We are siblings.
Are we siblings?
- Please say that again.
- Should we say we're siblings?
Yes.
- We are siblings.
The three of you are...
(Their relationship is
finally being revealed.)
siblings.
- Really?
- Yes, we are!
(Solar is the first one
who met her siblings.)
I'm your sister!
All right. I got you. Let's go home.
- Let's go.
- No. I'm not going home.
- You should graduate.
- I'm not going, sisters.
Come on.
- Ennik.
- Suk Jin.
- Where have you been?
- What took you so long?
- We are siblings.
The three of you are...
- siblings.
- Yes!
- She is our sister.
- Let's hurry.
- You are my sister.
- Yes, I am!
Let's go.
- Hello, Jae Suk.
- Young Ji.
(They have no time to waste.)
- It's nice to see you.
- Are you my sister?
Of course I am. Isn't it obvious?
I look like your sister.
You do?
- Young Ji!
- Yes?
Young Ji.
Hey, Young Ji.
I've been looking for you.
Can I hold your hands once?
- Just once.
- Why are you...
- Are you sure?
- Let's do this.
You said Kwang Soo and I
were your brothers earlier.
- That's not true.
- You said that to me too.
No. Just hold my hands first.
- Did she say that to you too?
- I'm serious.
- Are you lying to me?
- Gosh, no.
Just hold my hands.
- Is she lying to me?
- We're siblings of the same blood.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- We are siblings.
The three of you are...
- not siblings.
- Darn it.
It's Haha.
- It's Haha.
- Are you serious?
- Haha and Kwang Soo.
- Is that true?
- Haha and Kwang Soo, forever!
- I'm serious.
- Are you serious?
- I am.
- Can you swear?
- Is it true?
- Young Ji.
- Feeling! Cross!
- Intuition!
- Am I Intuition? All the sudden?
- Yes.
Young Ji! I can't believe this.
Hold on.
- We need Kwang Soo now.
- Hold on. Then I should...
We should hurry.
We need Kwang Soo.
- Okay. I'll call him.
- Where is he?
Come right away.
I just sent Jae Suk away.
(Kwang Soo gets a call from Haha.)
I'm on my way.
Jessi lied to you
to earn more points.
I should get going now.
Haha, this is a good chance
to run away from her.
I'll be right there.
(While Jessi talks to Jae Suk,
Kwang Soo tries to escape.)
(He gets in the van hurriedly.)
Lock the door!
Please start the car.
Don't open the door! Never!
Hey! What is she doing?
Call the police.
- Call the police now.
- Kwang Soo.
You are my brother! I told you.
No, I'm not.
I'm serious. Wait.
(Jessi never gives up.)
(She threatens her brother
knocking on the door.)
- You're not my sister.
- Hey, you're my brother.
- Come on out.
- Why are you being so scary?
- That's not true.
- Kwang Soo.
- Why did you jump at the car?
- Just come on out.
- We are not siblings.
Yes, we are.
Get out.
Why is she being like this?
It's Jae Suk.
Hello?
- Why? You have to trust me.
- Please start the car.
I'm on my way.
- Hey!
- Hurry up.
I told you to come here.
(I finally escaped... What?)
You should hurry.
(Where are you going?)
Jessi was sticking to my car.
- You have to hurry.
- Come right away, Kwang Soo.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk just left.
I just started off
on the wrong foot.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk
went to see Jessi.)
- My gosh.
- Hey, come on!
- It's Ho Hyun Ju.
- You have to hurry.
- I was...
- It's raining.
And call Se Chan.
Hello, Jae Suk.
Se Chan, hurry and come over.
I told you to hurry.
Jae Suk, I'm almost there.
I'm only 1km away.
- Are you sure I'm your brother?
- Definitely.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
(Nino Maximus Keyser Soze)
(Sonador and Sparta)
(She tries to prove that she's
his sister singing his hit song.)
- I'm so touched.
- See? I'm your sister.
- Okay. I'll keep calling Kwang Soo.
- Thank you.
Hey, bro!
- Come on!
- Hurry. What took you so long?
What have you been doing?
Jessi, why did you lie to me?
We are...
(As soon as Se Chan arrives,
they ask about their siblinghood.)
- He's here.
- Hurry.
- Hurry and come on out.
- Hold my hand first.
Hold our hands.
- We are siblings.
(They don't even say hello.)
(The two families shouted it out
almost at the same time.)
The three of you are...
- siblings.
- Gosh.
- Hey, Jessi.
- See? Why did you not trust me?
- Earlier, you said...
- You three are siblings.
- Yes!
- I told you to hurry.
Why were you there
for such a long time?
- Nice to meet you.
- It was a long time.
- Let's go.
- Get in the car.
You are my sister.
Gosh, this is so fun.
- Why did you not trust me?
- We have to hurry.
We have to get there
as soon as possible.
I had no idea.
(Who is the first one to arrive
at the opening place?)
Gosh, Ho Hyun Ju.
It's good to see you again.
(It's good to see you again.)
(Jessi sounds cute
when she feels happy.)
You sound quite moody.
- I really like Jae Suk.
- You do?
He's like my real brother.
Anyway, don't look down
on Korean Americans.
When did I look down on them?
- I'd never do that.
- You know what? That day...
I respect them.
- When did I do that?
- You did look down on me that day.
- I was deeply hurt back then.
- Were you hurt?
I was also hurt because
I didn't understand your English.
- Why?
- I'm a native Korean,
and I was hurt.
- You looked down on me.
- You're lying.
No. Seriously,
you looked down on me.
- They are so funny.
- Whatever.
- Now that we're here...
- It is going to be a long day.
- I'm feeling dizzy already.
- I'm dizzy too.
In fact, the production crew
wouldn't let me team up with Haha.
- Kwang Soo and me.
- Because we're too good.
- I see.
- It's not fair.
- You two are too good together.
- We're just too good.
- So it's forbidden.
- Yes.
It's like a team
of Hulk Hogan and Warrior.
- Okay. I get it.
- You don't know them, do you?
Of course I don't know.
That's disappointing.
She's like a machine.
- She just answers.
- She's a machine.
- She's...
- That's true.
She's from a factory.
Young Ji, I think you got
yourself a perfect character.
It just suits you perfectly.
You're still a great musician.
You're like Lee Kwang Soo
in the world of rappers.
(She sounds hesitant and confused.)
She's been showing machinelike
reactions, but she just stopped it.
I'm honored.
He still wins awards as an actor.
That's nice.
- You didn't hear me, did you?
- No.
Jessi's team is around here.
Really?
- We have to run.
- Are they behind us?
(The team who finishes
in 3rd place gets 20 points.)
(The 4th place gets only 10 points.)
Please stop here.
(They start running immediately.)
Where is the flag?
Where is it?
(Young Ji's team finally arrives
at the opening place.)
Are we the last one to come?
- Are we the last?
- You're in fourth place.
- I told you to hurry.
- Are we in fourth place?
What's with your hair?
What's wrong with you?
- Kwang Soo.
- Are we in fourth place?
I can't believe this.
Like I said before,
you can get academic points
and audition points today.
You will get
academic points as a team.
The two teams
with the lowest academic points...
will get a penalty.
Isn't it just for the fourth?
Both the 3rd and 4th
will get a penalty.
And the youngest sisters will get
audition points as an individual.
The top two sisters
will get a prize.
And the one with the highest points
will be exempted from the penalty.
- Really?
- That's great.
- Wow.
- Okay.
Solar, Ji Hyo, and So Min
who arrived first get 40 points.
(Team Solar gets 40 points.)
- Wow, you liar!
- Yes.
What?
So Mi, Jong Kook, and Suk Jin
who came in second get 30 points.
- I'm envious.
- That's not bad.
You liar!
20 points
for Jessi, Jae Suk, and Se Chan.
- Come on!
And 10 points for Young Ji,
Haha, and Kwang Soo.
(4th place,
Team Young Ji, 10 points)
- Look at her.
- This is so upsetting.
- I thought Jessi was my sister.
- It's his fault.
And your sisters got...
audition points
according to the number of times...
- they fooled you.
- Okay.
Jessi fooled you twice,
so she got 20 points.
- What? Only twice?
- Yes.
That's not much. You'll see.
- Isn't it big?
- No. It's not a big number.
Solar got 10 points.
Solar lied only once?
So Mi got 30 points.
(So Mi got 30 audition points.)
(She fooled them 3 times?)
I helped her with it.
And Young Ji got 30 points.
- Okay!
- That's a lot.
- You did a good job.
It's all from me.
How did they get so many points?
Jessi, why did you send me away?
I didn't tell you to leave.
Hey.
They got together again.
It will be uproarious today.
They are so loud.
- Hey.
- He seems embarrassed.
It's loud already.
Come on.
Let me introduce
our guests one by one.
We have Solar here.
(Solar of MAMAMOO
with a delightful voice)
What's with your hair, by the way?
Are you shooting
a historical drama or something?
(Her hair is neatly combed
straight back in half.)
This is the real
Korean-American style.
(She pokes Jae Suk
with her fingernail.)
(It stings.)
This is the real
Korean-American style.
- Is it a Korean-American style?
- This is the Korean-American style.
- No.
- Yong Sun...
- is from Daejeon, I think.
- It's Korean-American style.
- I'm from Seoul.
- You're from Seoul?
Stop acting like a know-it-all.
Don't act like a know-it-all.
- Seoul.
- She's from Korea.
I'm sorry.
- But you look prettier like that.
- This is...
Be quiet. Come on.
I'm not going to talk anymore.
You still say
what's on your mind though.
- Right.
- This is nice.
You look so pretty.
- So pretty.
- I heard...
Solar's personal channel
for posting videos...
- has...
- She has a lot of subscribers.
2.25 million subscribers?
- Yes, I do.
- That's insane.
- That's incredible.
- She's a queen.
2.25 million subscribers?
That's incredible.
She's a queen.
What did you just do?
This is my signature greeting.
Can you do it for us?
Sol, la, ti, do
- Sol, la, ti, do
- How cute.
- My goodness.
- I guess that's necessary.
- Yes.
- It's a YouTube special.
I should start a channel too.
- You should.
- You could make a channel too.
- I'm going to.
- It will do well.
Let's do it.
- What was that?
- Hold on.
(He smashes down
with a fly swatter.)
There was a fly.
- Did I get it?
- Yes, you did.
- Was there really a fly?
- There was really a fly there.
- Did you get it?
- I did.
- I got it. Look.
- He really did.
- Here it is.
- Gosh.
(Catch and release)
(Flying away)
- It's still alive.
- Was there really a fly?
- There really was one.
- There was.
- Luckily, it survived.
- It did.
- It survived.
- Thank goodness.
I think you hit me a bit too hard.
- No.
- You were hitting the fly, right?
- That's how you kill a fly.
- Right?
It wouldn't die
if you hit it lightly.
The next person is Ennik.
Ennik.
Didn't you recently release
a new song, Ennik?
That's right. I released a new song.
It's coming out as a single.
You've returned with a single.
What's your song called?
"What You Waiting For".
- What are you waiting for?
- We should hear her new song.
- Let's see it.
Let's go!
(Very excited)
("What You Waiting For"
by Jeon So Mi)
Let's go, So Mi!
The song is so good!
- It's so good!
- They're all great dancers!
(It's a great combination of a fresh
melody and powerful choreography.)
(Is he cold?)
It's fast.
(It's hard to wait for
Jeon So Mi's charms.)
So Mi's "What You Waiting For".
Waiting for.
It was so good.
- "What You Waiting For".
- She's really good.
- It's okay.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- This is not a competition.
- I know. This is not a competition.
- Yes. Okay.
- Let's go. Okay.
- Okay.
Jessi is coming out
with a new song too.
My album is coming out on the 30th.
- Your album is?
- Yes, my new album.
What's your song called?
"Nunu Nana".
- "Nunu Nana"?
- "Nunu Nana".
- Let's hear Jessi's new song.
- Okay. Let's do it.
- "Nunu Nana".
- Let's go!
- We don't have expectations.
- "Nunu Nana".
- Please turn up the music.
Yes, Jessi!
("Nunu Nana" by Jessi)
(A groove full of vibes)
- "Nunu Nana".
- Aren't you doing this?
(She rushes towards Se Chan
all of a sudden.)
"Nunu Nana". Why are you
looking at me? Look at the cameras.
Hey, listen!
(She shows off her true swag
by turning her back to the cameras.)
- 1, 2...
- Look over there.
Why was she looking at me?
- That's right!
- Here we go.
(She flexes her coolness.)
This is so cool.
Put it up, put it up.
(It's a powerful groove
from the charismatic singer.)
(He's cold again.)
The song is good.
(She finishes with a spin.)
(She's not done yet.)
(My performance starts now.)
(Stop the music.)
(She ignores him and continues.)
How long is she going to
promote her song?
Nobody can stop her.
(In a trance)
- Enough.
- Cut!
- Cut "Nunu Nana".
Okay!
- Hey.
- Hey!
- Hold on.
- That was amazing.
They told me to do it
for one minute.
- No. It was 30 seconds.
- It was good.
Why is everyone so scared of her?
- I purposely went to Se Chan.
- Why?
- I know why.
- In the lyrics...
Every time she forgot
the lyrics, she turned around.
No.
- It's true. You didn't sing...
- That's not true.
- until you remembered the lyrics.
There is no choreography here.
But here, I sing,
What did you say?
What are you saying?
Okay. That was "Nunu Nana".
- Come on.
- Wow.
- It's okay.
Come on. Wait.
You're the youngest
of three siblings?
You have two older brothers?
- Yes. I have two older brothers.
- This is exactly the same then.
- It's exactly like that right now.
- Right.
But my brothers aren't like them.
What do your brothers
do for a living?
- One of them...
- Your oldest brother.
This is my first time hearing this.
- One of them...
- It's interesting.
- What does one of them do?
- One of them...
I'm not really sure what he does.
- Is he unemployed?
- No.
- He's not unemployed.
- It's okay if he is.
- No.
- Are you not in touch with him?
He's an entrepreneur.
He does a lot of different things.
He does various things.
My other brother works at the top
for Samsung.
He works at the top?
He works for Samsung in the US.
- Semiconductors?
- At the top?
- Does he have a high position?
- He works in finance there.
- Semiconductors?
I couldn't remember what it was.
- I got confused.
- Was that supposed to be English?
- Semiconductors.
He works for a big company.
Do your brothers worry about you...
working here in Korea?
No.
They raised me to be strong
ever since I was young.
- I could tell.
- Ever since I was young,
they told me I would do well
and that they weren't worried.
What did they see in you?
What do you mean by that?
(She has a straight face.)
Don't get so upset.
- Can't I ask you a question?
- Don't look down on her.
I can ask, can't I?
Don't look down on Korean-Americans.
- When did I look down on her?
- Hey!
Why do you think they said that?
- I was asking a serious question.
- Don't look down on her.
I don't. Don't worry.
- Okay.
- It's been a while,
- but we are...
- Is this how it's ending?
Yes.
This is enough.
- So I guess if you get serious,
- Jessi, that's enough.
- it ends like this.
- No.
I'm sorry, but I'm getting exhausted
just watching you guys.
- I'm exhausted too.
- My stomach hurts.
- I'm getting dizzy.
- Me too.
- "Nunu Nana".
- Why are you dizzy?
There isn't enough oxygen.
Okay. The next guest is
Lee Young Ji.
Lee Young Ji!
Nice to meet you all.
You may all know Young Ji
from "High School Rapper".
Yes.
- First...
- She's going to tear up the stage.
She's really amazing.
Since Young Ji has joined us,
we would love to hear you rap.
- Let's see it.
- Our eardrums are in for a treat.
("I Am Lee Young Ji"
by Lee Young Ji)
(It's amazing from the start.)
(Is he shadow boxing?)
(They regrouped as Z-KIRI.)
(Her rap makes everyone groove
from side to side.)
(I'm Lee Young Ji!)
Young Ji!
(Exclaiming)
She's good.
(Young Ji's rap cleaned
our eardrums.)
The younger kids are really good.
- They're good.
- They are.
- Her style is different from Jessi.
- So Mi...
and Young Ji are the only ones
born in the 21st century.
- 21st century.
- That's right.
We're a new generation.
We're Generation Z.
- You're Generation Z?
- I'm Generation X.
- No, you're not.
- I am.
How are you Generation X?
I'm Generation X.
- You're Generation 50.
- You're from the Joseon era.
- Generation 50? You punk.
- Yes.
You're from the generation
of acoustic guitars.
Yes, you are.
- C'est Si Bon.
- You are.
- You grew up in that era.
I'm Generation X.
You and I are Generation X.
No. Generation X is...
- C'est Si Bon.
(A, B, C, D, E, F, G)
(He calls upon Song Chang Sik,
a member of C'est Si Bon.)
It suits him.
(He sings the best hit
from his era.)
- This is it.
- He made it work.
(He made everyone laugh.)
Why do I know all the lyrics?
Only the people who know
Song Chang Sik's song...
laughed at this.
- I know.
- Right.
- They don't know the song.
- Everyone.
You guys got academic points
by finding your sisters.
The scores haven't been added
to your team's score.
We're going to have a time
called Sister's Room...
with the points you gained
after every mission ends.
What's Sister's Room?
During every time we have
Sister's Room, the sisters will...
go into their classrooms...
and have a choice to either...
answer an essay question...
or film an audition tape.
If the little sister decides
to answer the essay question,
the points they will get will be
added to your academic points.
However, if she chooses
to film an audition tape,
then the points will go to her
audition points.
If the older siblings
don't trust their younger sister,
you can open the classroom door
and go in to find out.
We can find out if they're answering
the question or filming an audition.
If they're filming an audition tape,
the points received will go to the
team as academic points.
(They will get academic points
for catching her filming.)
But if they were answering
the essay question,
you will lose all the points
you have gotten.
You have to be smart.
We need to work well together.
(The Possibilities
for Sister's Room)
(Trust, Find Out)
(The team's point changes depending
on whether or not you trust her.)
- This is insane.
- You have to use your wits.
If you trust
your little sister later,
go to the place where you leave
your stamp on the classroom door...
and mark it with a good job stamp...
- and come back.
- Look at her.
If you don't trust her,
you can open the door.
You're a broadcasting machine.
The little sisters will go to
their classrooms.
Are we starting right away?
Do I have to do this for my team
or for myself?
We are a family.
We're a family, so my happiness
is your happiness.
Don't you agree?
My brothers... What should I do?
(All the sisters
have entered their rooms.)
Shall we go?
- Yes.
- Let's go together.
I can't figure out
what Young Ji is going to do.
(They have arrived in front of their
sister's rooms with headphones on.)
(What is Jessi doing?)
(Ho Hyun Ju's room)
(Is Jessi answering
the essay question?)
(Or is she filming
an audition tape?)
Jong Kook, this is So Mi's room.
(What did So Mi
finally decide to do?)
Can we open it now?
Yes, you can.
(Their siblings plan
outside their doors.)
Jessi won't be bothered
to film an audition tape.
I doubt she'll film one.
(They decide to trust her.)
(If she's answering the question,
they'll receive 30 academic points.)
My brothers
put their trust in me, right?
(She's answering
the essay question.)
(Team Jessi receives
30 academic points.)
Do we trust her?
(So Min and Ji Hyo
trust their sister too.)
They decided to trust her.
I think my sisters will trust me.
The other two teams
trusted their sisters.
They showed their trust.
- Really? Who?
- Let's enter the room.
- Did you also?
- Not yet.
Are you going to enter the room?
(Nodding)
Let's do this.
(They don't hesitate
to choose to enter.)
(If Young Ji
is answering the question,)
(they'll lose all their points.)
(If she's filming
the audition tape,)
(they'll receive
all the academic points.)
(She was filming the audition tape!)
What did I tell you?
(She was busy
filming herself when...)
(She puts on a straight face.)
(I can't believe
you didn't trust me!)
I knew it.
Of course, I'm right.
- Young Ji!
- What did I tell you?
Why didn't you trust me?
- You're seriously asking that?
- We knew this would happen.
- Right? See.
- She was filming.
- See? She was filming a video.
- I knew it.
I thought you'd trust me.
I was wondering
whether you'd come in or not.
- I knew it.
- That's what I was wondering.
- We knew it.
- It's over now.
- Our team is done for.
- Nice!
There's no trust between us at all.
But I want to be an idol singer.
But you should study, Young Ji.
The essay question
should come first.
Let's barge in there.
I bet she's filming.
Shall we?
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook
decided to barge in too.)
(Will So Mi be filming
just as they suspect?)
See?
What did I tell you?
(She was filming just like
her days on "Produce 101".)
See? I knew it.
- Right?
- Good thinking.
So Mi, really?
- Right off the bat?
- Why did you come in?
I thought you'd at least study
in the first round.
Right? We made the right decision.
My brothers are like real parents.
I can't believe all their nagging.
(The first round
of Sister's Room is over.)
(Current points)
(Where the first game
awaits the members)
(Three chairs...)
(and six water balloons?)
Everyone,
I hope you're fond of your siblings.
- Sure.
- Yes, of course.
- We're the perfect family.
- I'm loving my siblings.
- I finally met my family.
- Me too.
What does that matter anyway?
Is there no bond?
Come on.
The first game...
will allow you to show
your brotherly and sisterly love...
by asking for phrases
you want to hear.
The game is Just Say Anything.
- I love it.
- Just Say Anything?
- Just Say Anything.
- Hold on a second.
Bo Pil, wait a second.
I bet you came up with this game...
- to make us lose.
- He's right.
- Be honest with us.
- It's because she lived abroad.
- Be honest with me.
- You're targeting her, aren't you?
You know that Jessi's bad
at games like this.
Of course, he does.
- It's why we're playing it.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Unbelievable.
- They'll have a lot of screen time.
- Okay.
- They'll steal the attention today.
Jae Suk, wait.
- Suk Jin's jealous.
- Why?
He's jealous of you
getting all the attention.
You can't speak Korean well, right?
- He's jealous?
- I don't speak Korean.
- Yes.
- No.
- You don't speak Korean?
- I don't speak Korean.
So the little sister...
will sit under the water balloons...
with a phrase on her forehead.
She must guess correctly
what her siblings describe.
- This will be fun.
- Every 10 seconds though,
someone from another team
will remove one of the sticks.
- What?
- Every 10 seconds?
Time is of the essence then.
You fail if the balloons all fall
before you answer correctly.
The remaining number of balloons
will be converted to points.
- I'm the one answering?
- That's right.
Let's do this.
- Let's see who goes first.
- What's this?
Why?
- What?
- Why?
- Jae Suk, are you kidding me?
- What?
We're going first?
I need to watch
other teams play first.
- But...
- Guys.
Guys, let's begin with a laugh.
(Guys, let's begin with a laugh.)
We know who'll come last.
Can I ask for a favor?
Since I'm going first,
let us do a practice run.
- No way.
- We'll just go ahead.
- No.
- How about an example?
Come on!
- Is it a difficult one to guess?
- No.
(They calm her down
in order to begin the game.)
Am I the one guessing the answer?
Is it difficult?
- It's super difficult.
- It's difficult.
Do I know these Korean words?
- Yes, of course.
- They wouldn't be that cruel.
- I know these words?
- Yes.
- We'll describe the situation.
- You know these words.
- Hold on.
- You have to do a good job.
Just do it already!
- Let's just begin the game.
- Begin the game!
(They protest
that they begin the game.)
Oh, my gosh!
Ready, set, go.
So this is said...
to immature...
- Brothers or sisters.
- Yes, brothers or sisters.
We say this to them.
- What would you say?
- When they act foolishly.
- "Gosh..."
"Gosh, you stupid cow."
"Gosh, you stupid cow"?
No, no one curses.
There are no curse words.
- Then...
- Jessi, listen up.
Hold on a second.
You need to make it easier for me.
Did you purposely pull the one
that would let a balloon fall?
- Darn you.
- No, of course not!
- That's not true.
- Jessi, don't swear.
- How could I...
- Jessi, come on.
- The clock is ticking.
- Calm down.
- Okay?
- Kwang Soo, pull out another one.
That's a lot of water
for just one balloon.
It's all right.
- He got it.
- Did you just poke at it?
(Video referee)
(Poke!)
- Did you just poke at it?
- Seriously?
- Hey!
- That wasn't my intention.
- I'm sorry, Jessi.
- You poked it.
- No, I didn't.
- Hey.
- You popped it.
- No, not on purpose.
- Time out.
- Jessi, I'm sorry.
He popped it deliberately.
- I can't believe him.
- I swear.
You're out.
- What did he do?
- Ji Hyo,
- you do it.
- Why would you play dirty?
- But...
- Ji Hyo, you can do it.
Sure thing.
Jessi?
Jessi, you need to
answer this quickly.
- Jessi.
- Calm down.
I'm 35, right?
Someone two years older than you...
is acting like a child.
What would you say
in that situation?
How would you mention
one's older age?
I don't know.
What do we do with food?
- With our mouths...
- That's right.
- Yes, keep going with that.
- Add on.
"Shut it!"
Why on earth
would that be the answer?
- Calm down.
- That's what you came up with?
Calm down. Come on, Jessi.
What do you call
the length of time we've existed?
- The length of time.
- That's right.
- What do you mean?
- What's the word for that?
Wordy?
We go from 1, 2, 3...
- What do you call that?
- Age!
- Yes, that's right.
- All right, good! So I'm...
- two years older than you.
- That's right.
- "Gosh, he's..."
- "Gosh, that..."
- "Age..."
- Yes?
- She's getting there.
- "Age..."
- What about it?
- Jessi, you're almost there.
- I'm almost out of sticks.
- I cleared most of them.
- Your time is almost up.
The answer is right in front of you.
The food...
- What do you do with it?
- What do you do?
- You eat it.
- Exactly!
- Age.
- Yes.
- Eat.
- Yes!
(You aged but didn't grow up)
(She's not going
in the right direction.)
Why are they saying
that she's on the right track?
- She's right.
- So the age...
- You're only confusing her.
- She's not on the right track.
- So what we eat...
- Tell me what comes next.
- Okay.
What do we call
the next location we go to?
- How do we say it?
- They'll all drop at once.
- The next location...
- They'll drop at once.
- I know.
- When we move locations...
Hold on a second.
- You're almost there.
- What comes next?
- What do we say...
when we need to
go to a new location?
"Go!"
"Grow up and leave."
No, that's not it.
- You're almost there.
- You are.
You almost got it.
When we're on the move...
- It's over for you guys.
- What do we say to the taxi driver?
- Just say anything.
- Shoot at random answers.
What's the relative pronoun we use?
(They're in their final moments.)
- Your older brother...
- "Where."
When he acts silly...
(Welcome to the water park!)
(The water balloons fall
like a stack of dominoes.)
Your older brother
is being immature!
What's the answer?
(What's the answer?)
"Age..." What?
You can't just read it!
She still doesn't know
what it means though.
"You aged but didn't grow up."
She doesn't know
what that phrase means.
- It's too difficult for Jessi.
- She doesn't know what it is.
I've never heard
of this phrase before.
It's too difficult for Jessi.
What's this about one's age?
What does it mean?
- I bet Solar will do well.
- Look.
(Next up is Team Solar.)
This is something many of us say.
- It could be easy.
- It's not a bad one.
- Ready, set, go.
- I didn't get mine.
(Don't you dare tell people
that we're related!)
If only this was our phrase.
You and your terrible memory.
Solar, keep watching.
Can't you at least
shower more often?
- "Dirty!"
- You embarrass me.
No, that's not it. My friends...
(Screaming)
(She flutters her arms
after getting splashed.)
What was that?
It was only a splash of water.
- What's up with you?
- It wasn't a bug, you know.
- I was completely shocked.
- It startled me.
What on earth was that?
- This is quite scary.
- It's all right.
It's not like the water's hot.
- Yong Sun, calm down.
- What's up with her?
How is that scary?
Let's try this again.
Watch me, okay? You...
- You...
- "What do you think you're doing?"
- "Do you have a death wish?"
- One's scolding the other.
- These days...
- "Don't you dare..."
(Screaming)
- What on earth...
- I'm only removing the sticks.
I'm not spraying the water on you.
All I'm doing
is removing the sticks.
It's just...
You're almost there.
"That we're sisters..."
- You're almost there.
- Stay put, Jessi.
- Do better when it's our turn.
- So Min...
(Startled)
(Every time, she responds
with a high-pitched scream.)
Look at her.
You and your reactions.
Please take your seat.
- She's hilarious.
- You're almost there.
- She's great.
- I love her reactions.
No wonder her online channel
is a hit.
- We should take notes.
- She's doing an amazing job.
- You...
- I know!
"How dare you talk back to me."
- No.
- But it's similar.
- You're almost there.
- It's similar.
(I know!)
Goodness.
(She smashes into
the case of water balloons.)
- Solar, stay calm.
- What's wrong with you?
Please stay seated.
"Don't you dare say
that we're related!"
It's similar. You're almost there.
- "Don't you dare..."
- You're younger, right?
"Don't you dare..." Hey!
(Screaming)
(Instead of the answer,
she lets out a high-pitched scream.)
- What's wrong with her?
- Hey.
- Why is Yong Sun...
- It's water, not a bug.
Oh, my. That's awesome.
- She's good at reacting.
- Indeed.
- Have a seat. Sit here.
- Yong Sun.
- I'm the younger sister.
- Use a different word for "say".
Yong Sun.
- So my older sister...
- Oh, I know.
"Don't you dare tell people
that I'm your sister."
- But I'm the younger sister, so...
- Correct.
We'll accept that
as a correct answer.
(Team Solar got the right answer
with three balloons left.)
- Great job, Yong Sun.
- Good job.
"Don't you dare tell people..."
- You did well.
- Yong Sun is good at reacting.
That was awesome.
I'm a fan of Yong Sun's as of today.
I'm a huge fan.
(Her funny reaction made him a fan.)
- Jae Suk.
- Yong Sun was...
Is it over?
Everyone, if one of the siblings
succeeds,
- the team wins additional points.
- We'll do it.
- Let's go for it.
- Of course, we'll do it.
- We'll do it.
- No matter what.
- Everyone, let's begin.
- Okay.
Look. Okay. Good.
- Right.
- I guess it's an easy one.
- No, no.
- That's also easy.
- Ready. Go.
- Oh, I see.
It's not hard, right?
- It's short, right?
- Okay.
- A short word?
- Let's explain it to him.
- Ready. Go.
- Is it a short word?
- Jae Suk.
- What is he doing?
- What?
- It's hard to pull out.
- It's true. It's hard to pull out.
- All right.
- "Horse"?
- Yes.
- "Hey, you..."
- "Listen to me."
- It's close.
- "How dare you talk..."
- Oh, no. I...
- What?
He said the exact word again.
- "How dare you..."
- "How dare you talk back?"
Good. But...
- What sound is this?
- "How dare you talk back to me..."
Yes! He got the right answer.
What sound is this?
(Jae Suk pulled out
the sticks powerfully.)
(What?)
- "How dare you..."
- Yes! He got the right answer.
"How dare you... How dare you..."
"How dare you talk back to me
every time I talk to you?"
(Correct)
(Jae Suk pulls out more sticks
pretending he didn't hear it.)
- You saw that, right?
- "How dare you..."
(He can't do that.)
- But Haha said, "talk".
- Yes, he did.
- True.
- He gave him a word.
It was a mistake.
Give us another chance.
- Try it again.
- Forget this round.
- It doesn't count.
- Exactly.
(They're asking to let us
start over?)
What are you talking about?
What's wrong?
- I said the word.
- He said, "talk".
(It was a little helpful, but...)
- Start over.
- Even my underwear is wet now.
- Kwang Soo, you did well.
- How about we deduct a point?
You did well, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo did a good job.
- He got the answer quickly.
- He did a great job.
(Team Young Ji got the right answer
with three balloons left.)
You thought of it
when you pulled it out, right?
It's okay.
- That was cool.
- It's So Min.
- So Min...
- Kwang Soo will do it, then.
Kwang Soo should do it for So Min.
- Enjoy it.
- Kwang Soo.
- It's showtime.
- It's okay.
If you think about
the previous questions...
(Kwang Soo.)
Look at him.
Oh, my.
Look at Kwang Soo.
(Everyone is
surprised by Kwang Soo?)
(He brought a whole bucket
of water balloons.)
- Turn around.
- Look at that.
I brought them for the next round.
(Lying)
- Seriously. He's so mean.
- I just...
- brought them for the next round.
- I'm so excited about this sitcom.
I'm so excited.
So Min, I'm sure you expected that.
- This is...
- I'm so excited about this.
Look at that.
(He's bringing drinking water.)
(He's stacking up materials
to do a bad thing.)
- My goodness. This is...
- Kwang Soo.
I'm looking forward to it.
This will be a great comedy skit.
(Sister, have you lost your mind?)
- That's easy.
- Ready. Go.
- It's too easy.
- "What is wrong with you?"
- "Who are you?"
"What is wrong with you?"
"Is something wrong with this?"
- "Hey."
- "Are you out of your mind?"
Yes! But...
What?
(Kwang Soo dropped
a lot of water balloons.)
What?
(Falling down)
I didn't...
(The new technique to pop balloons
without pulling a stick out)
- Listen. I didn't...
- What was that?
- I didn't do anything.
- He didn't do anything.
- He didn't even pull a stick out.
- I didn't do anything.
- He didn't do anything.
- I really didn't do anything.
- It's close, but...
- "You're out of your mind."
No. Who am I to you?
- Who am I to her?
- Sister.
- "Sister, are you insane?"
- That's close.
You know, the right mind...
(Kwang Soo won't stop
dropping water balloons.)
I didn't mean to...
- "Are you out of your mind?"
- No.
- When you...
- You're running out of time.
"Sister..."
(Hitting)
(So Min threw a water balloon
at him.)
I didn't mean to do that.
It wasn't my intention.
(Pouring water)
(Water balloon war)
- My goodness.
- "Sister..."
- Here they go again.
"Sister, are you out of your mind?"
"Are you in your right mind?"
It's close.
(He poured the whole bucket.)
(The audience is fully satisfied.)
- "Sister..."
- What is wrong with you two?
(They're too immature
for people with a younger sibling.)
- Pull another one out.
- What is wrong with you?
- Try a different verb.
- A verb?
Yes, a verb.
When you... How should I put it?
- "Have you lost your mind?"
- Correct.
- "Sister, have you lost your mind?"
- Yes!
Good job.
(Team Solar got the right answer.)
- She succeeded quickly.
- I expected it, but...
(The battlefield is
a complete mess.)
- Gosh. Although I expected that...
- I have a question.
Is the penalty worse than this?
- Or is this worse?
- My gosh.
They say this is worse than
the penalty.
The penalty is worse than this?
- No.
- This is worse than the penalty.
What is wrong with you guys?
So, this is it.
We tallied the points including
the ones from the additional rounds.
- Please.
- The first place team is...
(The first place team)
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Solar.
- The team gained 50 points.
- We did well.
- We did great.
- Team So Mi, 2nd place, 40 points.
- Team Young Ji, 3rd, 30 points.
- Okay.
- Why are we in last place again?
- Team Jessi gained 20 points.
- I thought we'd be in second place.
- I'm not happy with the result.
Now, we'll begin the second round
of Sister's Room.
- A lot of points are at stake.
- According to your scores,
you will also be given lunch.
Jessi, we're going to open the door.
- We'll open the door this time.
- We'll open the door.
- What will you do again?
Trust me.
- Will you take the test?
- Loyalty.
To get more points,
the only way is not opening the door
while you're taking the test.
- If you want to win.
- Okay. Then don't open it.
- Trust me.
- We won't.
- Because...
- 1, 2, 3. Go, Team!
- Go, Team!
- We won't open the door.
- Listen.
I really like our teamwork.
- Teamwork?
- We had great teamwork.
- We have great teamwork,
- Yes.
- and I want to eat a nice lunch.
- Okay.
Right. Let's eat this time.
- I'm serious.
- I know.
Yong Sun, let's eat lunch.
- Will you take the test?
- Let's eat.
- The first place team can eat.
The younger sisters,
please go to your rooms.
Young Ji, I trust you.
I think that I need to gain...
more academic points.
Since I got
almost no individual point,
I'm going to continue...
to write an answer to a question.
I have a feeling
that they will trust me.
I asked them to trust me, but...
Oh, no. The strap got stained.
I'm going to dance
because I'm upset.
(So Mi broke her promise
and chose to film audition tape...)
(because she got upset.)
All right. Let's go. Let's do this.
It's a little hard to decide.
My team is in last place, right?
We can't trust So Min,
but we must trust So Mi.
- Shall we trust her?
- Sorry?
Do you want to go in?
- We should give her a stamp, right?
- Yes, we should.
- We should give her a stamp.
- Shall I?
- Yes. Let's do that.
Okay. We trust her.
We trust So Mi.
We're leaving because we trust her.
Can we open the door now?
Yes, you can.
One.
(The two brothers are ambushing her
unlike the promise they made.)
(If Jessi is auditioning,
they'll gain academic points.)
(She is answering a question.)
Did you not trust me?
Oh, my gosh.
What happens now?
I think that you are not
compatible with us at all.
We keep choosing the opposite.
Gosh, Se Chan. I clearly told you.
- Come on. Get it together.
- We doubted you.
- Se Chan.
- I'm going to be bad now.
I think my team will be
in first place.
I'm worried because I think
we'll win too easily.
See? They won't come in.
(What?)
Guys.
(The two reliable sisters
showed up.)
Oh, no. We couldn't trust you.
- Because we have a high score...
- We have a high score.
Let's trust her.
Wait. Wait. Hold on.
She might be studying.
I have a feeling.
No? Are you sure?
(They're going into the room as
Kwang Soo is sure about it.)
Darn it. I told you so.
She's studying. I told you
she must be studying.
(Awkward)
- I said I'll go to the Ivy League.
- It's not like that.
I said we shouldn't come in.
Young Ji, listen.
- You'll see later.
- Okay.
- He insisted.
- Now, we've become a real family.
- He didn't trust you.
- We've become a real family.
I trusted you.
You see...
Oh, she was... She was writing
an answer to an essay question.
See? I told you she was studying.
Gosh.
- We should've trusted her.
- I'm going to be bad now.
- Hey, I trusted you.
- I'm going to be bad.
- I trusted you, but he didn't.
- You see,
we finally became a real family.
I trusted you.
- Forget it.
- My gosh.
- Listen.
- My brothers doubted me.
- Let's do it. Let's do it now.
- Young Ji, I trusted you.
As a result of the 2nd round of
Sister's Room, the 1st place team...
- Is it us?
- We were in first place.
- Yes, but it might've changed.
- Because we didn't trust her.
- The first place team is...
Ji Hyo, So Min, and Solar.
- We're still in first place.
- We're in last place?
- I think all the other teams...
- went into the rooms.
- Right.
- What?
- Why?
Gosh. She filmed the audition tape.
- Hey, you filmed...
- No, I studied.
- I studied.
- She filmed the audition tape.
I guess she filmed
the audition tape.
- No, I didn't.
- She was the only one I trusted.
Next.
2 teams came in joint 2nd place
in academic point.
Which teams?
Team Jessi and Team So Mi.
- Come on.
- Jessi.
- My gosh.
- Come on.
- Earlier, we...
- Good. We're in 2nd place.
- We're in 2nd place?
- Last place? We're in 2nd place.
- We're in 2nd place at least.
Are we in last place?
- So Mi...
- I asked you to trust me.
(Only if they trusted Young Ji...)
I knew it. We're not family.
- How could it be?
- Now, I have to stop her.
This is a disaster.
- I think we'll play a game...
- Like throwing balls.
where we throw balls.
This is the last mission
before the graduation...
- that requires teamwork.
- Okay.
It's Guard Your Sister,
a basketball game.
- So we have to guard her.
- Okay. You guys will guard me.
You will be given 10 minutes
in 1st and 2nd halves,
and the team that gets most balls
in the hoop...
that the other teams carry wins.
In the first half, the little sister
will carry the hoop,
- and one of her siblings will...
- Okay.
- carry it in the second half.
- Got it.
However, you must find balls
that are hidden in different places,
and write your sister's name on them
to score a goal.
Or else, it won't be
considered a goal.
- Oh, we have a rule like that.
- We must find the hidden balls.
In the order of the number of goals
scored by each team,
the teams will gain
50, 30, 20, and 10 points.
- This is our last chance.
- Okay. Got it.
- A chance to turn the game around.
- If we fail again this time,
- it's over.
- Okay, okay.
- A chance to turn the game around.
- Or you can be an idol singer.
- Okay.
- Become successful...
- Being an idol singer sounds great.
- Exactly.
- We want you to be successful.
- To study...
- Okay.
- But let's do our best in this.
Okay. Understood.
- The game will begin shortly.
- Let's do this!
- 3, 2, 1.
- We must find the balls first.
- The race begins now.
- Okay.
(First half started.)
Is there no ball in here?
There might be one.
- I don't think so.
- I'll take a look around.
I'll go check that room.
The trash can.
(Jessi has a hunch.)
- How does a ball look?
- My gosh. Gross.
(My gosh. Gross.)
- Why?
- The trash can was full of trash.
- Of course, it's full of trash.
- But...
But there might've been
something in it.
There's no ball in here.
- I think...
- We wasted our time.
We came down here
because you told us to.
- You're right. I'm sorry.
- I like how she points things out.
I'm sorry.
(Haha is searching for a ball too.)
Wait.
(He found something!)
There it is. I found one.
(Finally, he found a ball.)
"Lee Young Ji".
I wrote down her name. Let's go.
(Kwang Soo found a ball too.)
(He's heading somewhere
with the ball he found.)
Where are you going?
(He ran into Suk Jin,
who's not a threat.)
Wait.
(But!)
- Wait.
- What is it?
Just let me pass through.
- No.
- Just let me pass through.
- Give me that.
- Young Ji, run!
- Hey.
- Oh, gosh. Let me go.
- No, no.
- Did they see me?
- Where is it written?
- Hey, be careful.
(He's trying to throw the ball.)
Don't worry.
(Moving to the sides)
(Screaming)
(Lee Kwang Soo has been kicked out.)
- Bye.
- What?
- Why would this door...
- Let's go.
Wait! Wait.
Why did the door open?
Let's hurry.
- Hurry up and write it down.
- Haha!
They're coming.
- Hey, where is Kwang Soo?
- Be careful.
Hurry up and go. Kwang Soo.
(Jong Kook is rushing to Young Ji.)
(Lying on the floor)
Be careful.
(She's blocking the ball
with quick movements.)
(Unexpected breakdance)
Hey!
You're supposed to stop them!
(The 21st-century girl doesn't
feel intimidated by Jong Kook.)
No. Come on.
- No.
- You see...
- The net is turned inside out.
(While Jong Kook is confronting
Young Ji...)
Be careful!
Hey!
(Kwang Soo is fighting with So Mi
one on one.)
I failed.
(Bricked)
Haha.
(Haha showed up and succeeded
in scoring a goal.)
No, no. Run. Run.
- No, no.
- We already lost a point.
It's turned inside out.
We lost a point.
Gosh. Where have you been?
Where?
(So Min is waiting for
the right time for the attack.)
- Okay. Gosh. Give me that!
- So Min.
(Kwang Soo snatched her ball
while chasing after her.)
Give me that!
(Kwang Soo ran away from So Min.)
- So Min.
- He stole my ball.
I mean, this is...
There she is.
(Haha's target is...)
(the weakest, Solar.)
Kwang Soo, no.
(Solar barely blocked
the second shot.)
Kwang Soo, no.
Okay. It's done.
(Haha and Kwang Soo scored goals
against Team Solar.)
I stole the ball.
Haha, this is our chance.
- They have so many balls.
- Stop. Come back.
- Come on up.
- Hey!
Hurry up.
- Okay.
- Don't get involved in that.
You don't even have any balls.
- Hey.
- We have to find a ball.
I think there's one
in a trash can.
- I found one!
- Great.
- Did you find a ball?
- Jae Suk.
We should write down your name.
I told you it was in a trash can.
(Speechless)
I'm sorry,
but it wasn't in the trash can.
It was behind the trash can.
Hey, we... Oh, here it is.
Did you find another one?
- Come on. Wow.
- Wow.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Move it, move it.
Solar.
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- What's wrong with you?
- Watch out. So Mi is here too.
- Be careful.
- So Mi, be careful.
Come over here.
Kwang Soo, I really don't like you.
What... Wait. You don't like me?
- This is how the game is played.
- Hey.
- So Mi.
- What? Hey.
(Suk Jin is taken aback
as he lost it in an instant.)
- Darn it.
- Why did you let him take it?
- I'm sorry.
- Why did you do that?
- Let's go to Solar.
- No.
But we... Oh, no. Run. Hurry.
(Only Ji Hyo is guarding Solar.)
- He's coming.
- Goal!
(He scored a goal easily.)
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
I mean... Not again. Stop!
(Jong Kook goes on the offense.)
(Ji Hyo hit the ball
with her elbow.)
Hey, our net is full now.
Be careful with that.
Be careful.
- Hey!
- Jessi!
(Kwang Soo saw the ball bouncing out
and went crazy.)
(Let go of me.)
(They're punishing
Kwang Soo together.)
(While they're taking him down...)
It fell on the floor.
(Screaming)
Don't bite me.
Let go of me. Let me go!
I said, let go!
I said, let go. What are you doing?
- Gosh, my hair.
- Who is it?
(A piece of art on long paper
created by Ji Hyo)
- What are you doing?
- Gosh, my hair.
- Who is it?
- My hair.
(Finally, they're all calm.)
- Jessi.
- My gosh.
We should score a goal.
Jessi. Jessi.
- I'll be here.
- Jessi.
- Who is that?
- Oh, my gosh.
- What happened to your face?
- What happened?
- What's wrong?
What happened?
- It wasn't me.
- What color is it?
- Kwang Soo.
It's drawn in this color.
- It wasn't me.
- It was So Min.
- No.
- I think...
(However, Ji Hyo doesn't have
the lid of the marker.)
It's easy to move.
(I got you!)
(Kwang Soo is in a frenzy
with a revengeful spirit.)
Come here. Let's go.
(I don't want to be
dragged into that.)
(You are watching
a basketball game.)
Where is it? An orange ball.
(Ball, please come out.)
(Team Solar is also busy
looking for a ball.)
Where did they find so many balls?
- Did you find one, Ji Hyo?
- No.
I think...
(At that moment!)
No. Ji Hyo! No!
No. Go away. Go away.
- I got it.
- What was that?
(So Min blocked the shot.)
That was awesome.
- So Min.
- Let's get out of here.
Haha!
Solar, take this and run.
- Run.
- He lost the ball.
Wait.
Wait. No.
Close the door. Close it, Ji Hyo.
Close it. Close it now, Ji Hyo.
Close it. Close it.
I said, close it. Close it now.
Close it.
Where did my marker pen go?
- My marker pen...
- It's not here.
What do you mean it's not here?
- Here...
- I don't have it.
It's right here!
- Don't make me laugh.
- I'll take it out.
- Why...
- I'll take it out for you.
- Give it to me.
- I'll take it out.
- Stop pressing. I'll give you.
- How? How?
- What?
I'll take it out now.
Wait. You should give it to him.
What? When and who did this?
(What? When and who did this?)
Jessi, earlier... Calm down.
- Jae Suk!
- Calm down.
- When did this get in here?
- One ball is okay.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
That could happen to any team.
Wait.
Gosh. You can't keep it
under your shirt.
But we have only girls in our team.
I don't care. Kwang Soo.
Gosh. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Stop it. You can't do that.
Hey, what are you... Oh, gosh.
Stop it.
(The battle for revenge)
- What are you guys doing?
- Hey.
That's ridiculous.
(Biting)
Hey, you brat.
(A headlock)
You shouldn't do that to her.
(And new face painting)
That's bad.
(Kwang Soo is in trouble.)
Hey, stop it.
- Go. Good job.
- Stop it.
- What? What was that?
- Jessi.
- Help me.
(While everyone was
looking at Kwang Soo,)
(So Mi scored a goal too.)
Everyone, the first half is over.
- The first half is over.
- I put a ball in Young Ji's net.
- Did you?
- Yes.
Please go to your team's
starting place.
(Team Young Ji: 26, Team So Mi: 14,
Team Jessi: 8, Team Solar: minus 10)
There's no way we can...
We lost too many points.
I was so surprised.
They came at me like crazy.
It's no joke.
Which one of you will
carry the hoop?
- Ji Hyo, you do it.
- I'll do it.
She's better at dodging than me.
I don't know.
There's nothing we can do.
How about we forget about scoring
goals and beat Kwang Soo up?
(How about we forget about scoring
goals and beat Kwang Soo up?)
- I won't let it slide.
- I'm sure...
that Kwang Soo will carry the hoop
because he's tall.
- He's fast too.
- You're right.
I'm so annoyed.
(The big sister is still upset.)
I think Jae Suk
will cover for me better.
Who didn't cover for me earlier?
- What do you mean?
- Who didn't cover for me?
You? We both protected you.
- Jessi.
- Get the ball in whenever you can.
- I'm worried about this guy.
- Why?
- I just have a feeling.
- No.
Worry about yourself.
- Don't fight.
- We're not fighting.
I was complimenting her.
- Hey.
- I'll be there for you.
- Are you looking down on her?
- No.
- Never.
- The whole time, you're...
- No.
- Oh, my gosh.
- I was...
- Hey, do you watch NBA games?
- What? Yes, I do.
- You watch NBA games?
- Can you play basketball?
- I can.
I think I got a nosebleed.
- Is this the last game?
- Because you said that...
- Is this the last one?
- To be honest,
I'm happy I'm not
on Kwang Soo's team.
- It's best if you carry the net.
- Me?
If I do it, everyone will target me.
- Of course.
- Everyone will come at me.
- It's better if I defend.
- Yes, you should defend.
All right.
Who should carry the net?
Who should?
Do you want to play offense?
They were all coming at you, right?
I think...
(It shows
that everyone came at him.)
I'll play offense.
I'll attack.
Okay, I'll carry the net.
Let's start the second half.
- I'll get many balls in this time.
- Let's do this.
The race starts.
(The second half starts.)
There will be more nets this time.
Here he comes.
Kwang Soo has two balls.
- Gosh, that crazy punk.
- Here he comes.
- We have no balls?
- Where did he find them?
- He's running here.
- They...
They already have balls.
- What's with him?
- I found one.
Watch out!
- Watch out!
(He charges at So Mi.)
Fine, I'll leave.
I'll leave.
(He gets scared and runs away.)
Come here! Stop!
(Se Chan is confronted with So Min
while carrying a net.)
Hey!
(So Min swears...)
(and punches him.)
(He gets punched
in the left front side of his head.)
Hey!
How could you slap me?
(After the first half, Yong Sun's
sisters are getting mean.)
(Young Ji looking for balls
on the 2nd floor alone.)
This is insane.
(She finds a ball under the sink.)
You're good at this.
(The staff is impressed.)
(She hides the balls
inside her T-shirt.)
Run!
(There is a war going on.)
(Young Ji is hiding in the corner.)
Haha! Jae Suk!
(She lowers her body.)
(She gets a ball in.)
(She scores a goal
without anyone finding out.)
(Celebrating)
(Jong Kook hasn't noticed it.)
(Young Ji finds
another opportunity...)
(and takes action.)
Here she comes. Hey!
(Her second attack succeeds too.)
Hey, look at her.
Okay!
(The 21st-century girl challenges
the invincible Jong Kook.)
Here we go. Okay.
(The 20th-century singer
versus the 21st-century girl)
(The chase of the century)
(Screaming)
Young Ji, what happened? Young Ji!
- Young Ji.
- Young Ji!
(Everyone is shocked
at the unexpected situation.)
(When Jong Kook finds his target,
he never gives up.)
(In the end, Jong Kook
gets 2 balls in.)
What's with her face?
(Shocked)
(Even her face
intimidates everyone.)
- It's me.
- Young Ji!
(Even her face
intimidates everyone.)
(Young Ji looks
for her next target.)
(She suddenly takes her shoes off.)
(Her steps to the battleground
feel much lighter now.)
(Her feet move incredibly fast.)
Hey!
(No one dares attack Young Ji...)
(when she even took her shoes off.)
Young Ji is hilarious.
Young Ji, why did you
take your shoes off?
To run faster.
(Determined)
Young Ji.
- Do you have it or not?
- It's mine!
Give it to me!
Kwang Soo!
(She tries to defend
against Jae Suk...)
(but unfortunately fails.)
Hey, you're good at this.
Young Ji, I love your energy.
- Young Ji, you have so much energy.
- Young Ji, you're amazing.
Very good.
(I'm Lee Young Ji.)
- We have 30 seconds left.
- We got 30 seconds left.
(The second half ends
in 30 seconds.)
(Faking)
(His ball is so fast
that no one can see it.)
Give it to me.
Look at Kwang Soo.
Good. We can't see it.
What are you doing?
- This is hilarious.
- It's so fast I can't see it.
I can't see it.
Gosh, it's so fast.
(Jae Suk approaches Kwang Soo.)
(Jae Suk slaps him.)
(Kwang Soo's one-man show
is over.)
(What's with him?)
In the end,
it finishes in a silly way.
(They have 3 seconds.)
- Two!
- Gosh.
(Exhausted)
Game over.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
In first place...
(The results are announced.)
With 40 points,
Team Young Ji.
(With 40 points, Team Young Ji
finishes in 1st place.)
(Young Ji took her shoes off,
and Kwang Soo didn't spare himself.)
They got many balls in?
Our strategy paid off.
In second place,
with only one less ball in...
I hope we're in second place.
- With 37 points,
- Team Jong Kook.
Team So Mi.
- I knew it.
- I'm relieved.
(Satisfied)
- So am I.
- We're in second place.
- We won't be penalized.
With four less points...
(With 4 less points
than Team So Mi...)
- Team Jessi is in third place.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- And then...
Team Solar has...
minus nine points.
Minus nine points?
What is that?
They ended up with so many balls
that they carried in their bags.
- It's the last Sister's Room.
- We're at the bottom.
- We have to trust each other.
- Exactly.
- Trust me.
- Okay. Go to your room.
- We'll trust you.
- We shouldn't open her door.
- We shouldn't.
- No, you shouldn't.
- Gosh, what should I do?
- What do we do?
- I don't know what they'll do.
- Me neither.
(They go to their rooms.)
Is Jessi already in her room?
- What? What's with you?
- What are you going to do?
I don't know. What about you guys?
But from my experience...
Let's say you're working
on your computer.
They'd think you're doing this.
- Right?
- They want me to work on this.
Don't trust them.
Do whatever you want.
They can do whatever for the show.
I'm going to play you against them.
They've betrayed you, right?
They betray me all the time.
So should you.
But I don't want to.
I promised them...
5, 6 times.
I'm playing them against each other.
(I'm playing them
against each other.)
I'm going to dance this time too.
In my opinion...
I'm having an inner conflict
right now.
I'll give up on my Ivy League dream.
I need to set this up first
since I'll become an idol singer.
(Going back on her word,
Young Ji prepares for an audition.)
If they had won my trust
in the 1st and 2nd rounds,
I would be answering
essay questions now.
They should have trusted me.
It's not my fault.
Okay. I choose this.
I'll stick to this.
Oh, my gosh. What do I do?
Tell me what to do.
(Me?)
What do you think?
I'll trust them.
(She decides to trust
her teammates again.)
Jae Suk.
(All of them have made up
their minds.)
Young Ji, we trust you.
(All of them have made up
their minds.)
(Their siblings arrive.)
We should trust our little sister.
Let's trust her.
- Let's give her a stamp.
- Do it. Let's not think too much.
Rather than losing it...
- Let's trust our little sister.
- Let's do this.
- We should trust her.
- Come on.
Stop bragging and stamp it already.
Why are you bragging so much?
- I can't hear you.
- Okay.
Let's go.
(Thanks to their trust,
So Min wins audition points.)
Oh, my.
Did they leave?
(Solar wins a stamp of trust
from her sisters.)
(Thanks to Solar keeping her word,
her team wins academic points.)
All teams seem to trust
their little sisters.
We never know.
What if she is
filming an audition tape again?
She might.
(They're 100 percent sure
Jessi is filming an audition tape.)
They're betraying me.
They think
I'm filming an audition tape.
(They fail to trust her
and decide to open the door.)
Come on!
(Screaming)
(Jessi can't take it anymore.)
Come on!
You...
(I can't believe
you're my brothers!)
- Jessi.
- I'm not going to see you again.
- Jessi, I'm sorry.
- I told you.
Jessi, you're mistaken.
- Jessi.
I told you we should trust her.
- I wasn't sure.
- Jessi.
- Jessi, let us explain.
- You promised me!
- Calm down.
- Knock, knock.
Come on!
- Come on, Jessi.
- Jessi.
I wanted to give you a stamp,
but he insisted on opening the door.
(Team Jessi fails to win
academic points.)
I'm sorry, Jessi.
Jessi, come on.
I trusted you! Oh, my gosh.
- You...
- Oh, my gosh.
- Let's give her a stamp.
- I...
Let's trust her.
(They don't want to end up
like Team Jessi.)
- On the far right.
- Has it been three times?
(They give Young Ji a stamp so that
they don't end up like Team Jessi.)
Let's trust her.
(Kwang Soo isn't feeling good
about this.)
(And he has a good reason
for that.)
I feel a lot more guilty
than expected.
Thank you.
(Young Ji wins audition points.)
We're family.
The race for your little sisters'
graduation is over.
In the last round, all the teams
except Team Jessi...
decided to give stamps.
- It's touching.
- Let's see.
- Are we really family?
- You guys really are my brothers.
- You should trust your family.
- Let's see what happens.
It's touching. It's really touching.
- This is what family is all about.
- It's a happy ending.
You should trust your family
at crucial moments.
- We were at the bottom before this.
- What is this?
When Team Jessi opened the door,
she was answering essay questions.
- Oh, my.
- Too bad.
Solar, who was trusted
by her sisters,
was answering essay questions.
(Team Solar wins academic points.)
- Moving on.
- Team So Mi.
So Mi, who was trusted
by her brothers...
(Team So Mi trusted her.)
- was filming an audition tape.
- What?
(She was filming an audition tape.)
We beat them.
- We beat them.
- Yes!
- We'll move up then.
- We did it!
- We're in second place.
- I can't believe this girl.
- If she was answering questions...
I learned it from you.
I hope Team Young Ji beats them.
- Beat them.
- I trust Young Ji.
- Young Ji, who was trusted,
- They beat them.
was filming an audition tape.
(She fooled us.)
(She shows off her dance moves
she has been practicing.)
(He's swearing with his eyes.)
So the sister who came in
first place in the audition is...
(It's time to announce the sister
who came in 1st place.)
It's Jeon So Mi,
who got 100 points.
What?
I didn't come in first place?
Then we don't get the penalty.
- She got 100 points?
- No, it's just So Mi.
Only So Mi gets exempt
from the penalty.
The other two members
will get the penalty.
The sister in second place
who will get a prize is...
(The person who came in 2nd place
and gets a prize is...)
It's Lee Young Ji.
(The person who came in 2nd place
and gets a prize is Lee Young Ji.)
Goodness.
My gosh.
(Young Ji, who came in 2nd place,
will get a prize.)
- We just need to avoid the penalty.
- Right.
Only the teams in 3rd and 4th place
will get the penalty, right?
- It's time to announce the penalty.
- It's the penalty.
- The penalty...
- Let's just give up.
- I don't think it's going to be us.
- This is fun.
- We won't get the penalty.
- I can get the penalty,
- but...
- She's going to get it too.
I need to get the penalty with her.
- That's my goal.
- I will get the penalty with her.
The team that will graduate with
the highest academic points is...
(Today's race was filled with
mistrust and betrayal.)
(Despite that, the team that
protected their sibling love...)
(and came in 1st place is...)
It's Team Solar with 70 points.
(Team Solar graduated
with top marks.)
This is a good memory.
Girl power!
Solar!
Hey, Yong Sun!
- Our youngest sister, Yong Sun!
- Yong Sun is the best!
- Gosh, Yong Sun!
The second place team will avoid
the penalty too.
The team in second place.
- In second place...
- Tell us it's Jessi.
- Please hurry!
- I think we're in third place.
The point difference between the
2nd and 3rd place team is 10 points.
- Let's come in 2nd place.
- I think we might be in 3rd place.
Let's come in 2nd place.
- In 2nd place with 30 points...
- 2nd place.
(The team that came in 2nd place
with 10 more points...)
Let's come in second place.
(and gets to avoid
the penalty is...)
The team that will graduate
and avoid the penalty is...
Jeon So Mi.
- Yes!
- Thank goodness.
(2nd place, Team Jeon So Mi)
- Yes!
- Thank goodness.
She came in 1st place,
but her team also gets exempt.
Our little sister came in
first place, and we...
If only...
- Stop bragging.
- she studied hard in school...
- Did we lose again?
- And we got exempt too.
Why are you bragging so much?
Team Jessi came in 3rd place
with 20 points.
Team Young Ji came in 4th place
with 10 points.
- This is...
- We're in last place?
We came in last place?
- It's better to be in last place.
- We got everything we wanted.
Get your hand away from me.
(Their younger sister fulfilled
her dream to audition.)
Shall we bring in the prize?
- Are we in fourth place?
- What's the prize?
- No, we're in third place.
- Wow.
A sound bar.
The 1st and 2nd place winners
of the auditions,
Jeon So Mi and Lee Young Ji,
will each get one.
Congratulations on your debut.
- Thank you.
They came in 1st and 2nd place
on their 1st time on Running Man.
- 21st-century kids.
Congratulations to the 2 people
born in the 21st century.
Amazing.
We'll go straight into the penalty.
Each of you must stand behind
1, 2, and 3.
The 3 doors will open, and 2 of them
will have a flour bomb in them.
- Okay.
Okay. It's behind there.
- It's not us.
- It's behind there.
- Young Ji gets the penalty too.
- Right.
Because she's in second place.
- Thank goodness.
- Nice.
We came in 2nd place
because of them
- Right.
- Then I...
(Team Young Ji will start. Only one
of them can avoid the flour.)
- Are you in position?
- Will it reach here?
Does anyone want to switch spots?
(Kwang Soo and Young Ji
switch spots at the last moment.)
(1 of these 3 will be exempt
from the penalty.)
- Okay.
- One.
Two.
Three.
(Lucky Young Ji
avoided the penalty.)
(Are we in paradise?)
How is that possible?
She avoided it.
- Hold on.
- Why?
Who got hit with it?
How did the two of you get it?
(It's an overwhelming view.
They're covered in flour.)
(They gave it their all.)
- Young Ji is really lucky.
- You look handsome like that.
- I know.
- We changed spots too.
Wait. Hold on. Is it random?
Yes, it's random.
Seriously. Please.
- Door number two?
- I don't know.
It's either 2 or 3.
- Okay.
- Okay. Come on. Let's go.
Does anyone want to switch?
Do you want to switch?
I don't know.
I'm just standing here.
- Okay.
- Face the door.
- Jessi chose door number two.
- You don't want to switch?
You can't complain to us if you
get hit because you didn't switch.
My gosh. Be quiet, please.
Okay. One.
Two.
Three.
Oh, my gosh!
(What?)
(This is 100 percent real.
Jessi is chosen.)
(Why did it have to be Jessi?)
- Oh, my.
- Jessi, come on!
I'm so sorry, but I love you.
It's all a lie.
Oh, no. Jessi.
(The strong sister has been adorned
with white.)
Oh, no. Jessi.
- Jessi. Come on.
(The childish brothers are excited
about their sister's punishment.)
Jessi.
- Jessi.
- Oh, my gosh.
You didn't switch!
- You've become flour dough.
- Jessi.
Jessi.
Don't touch me!
Hey! Don't touch me!
Hey. You. "Nunu Nana".
Jessi.
Jessi. Come on.
No, I... I... Today...
- You look so scary right now.
- Don't speak.
- You look funnier when you speak.
- You look so scary right now.
- Oh, my.
- She looks like a ghost.
(Blowing)
- You spat on me!
- No, I didn't!
- He spat on me.
- I didn't!
- Why did you spit on her?
- I was blowing the flour off.
I was really blowing the flour off.
- Jessi.
- Can you tell us how you feel?
(He can't read the room.)
You want to know how I feel?
Jessi, come on.
- It was so funny today.
- Good job, everyone.
Good job, everyone!
(Iron gates are shut tightly here.)
(8 inmates are being held
inside a prison.)
- You must be the new guys.
- I'm here to get one of you.
(New inmate 2371, Kim Young Min.
New inmate 2370, Ha Do Kwon.)
I was a top executive...
(New inmate 2372, Ji Seung Hyun.
New inmate 2369, Kim Yong Ji.)
(The rules of Running Prison)
(The inmates here are connected
in pairs of 2?)
(However, nobody knows...)
(who they are connected with.)
(They must find their partner
without getting caught and escape.)
(Only those who escape can survive.)
(This was all planned by
a powerful boss and their member?)
(Who will be the first two people
to escape?)
(2 Person Prison Break Race,
My Unfamiliar Partner)