- Okay.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I heard Suk Jin has
very good news.
- I know.
- What news?
- I don't know what it is.
- You posted about our show...
on social media
even before it was aired.
That's right.
(Suk Jin spoiled the losers on
his social media before the show.)
- That's right.
- I saw that too.
How could he do that? My gosh.
I feel really bad, and I apologize
to the production crew.
We shot it a while ago,
so I thought it was already aired.
It's not like you're new
to variety shows.
- So Min and I...
- You're not supposed to say that.
You can't say that.
It's the spoiler.
No, it's not. The episode is aired,
so it doesn't matter.
Oh, really?
Will you pull yourself together? You
don't do things that you should do.
And you do what you're
not supposed to do.
- He never listens to others.
- Is he a green frog or what?
- Why did you do it?
- You know what?
I completely had no idea.
But about 30,000 people
read it immediately.
A lot of people read the post.
And they all said the same thing.
"Suk Jin, no!" "Spoiler alert."
- Please...
- They all said that.
"Suk Jin, no. Spoiler alert."
"Get it together, Suk Jin."
(Ji Suk Jin,
384,264 people like this post.)
What's funnier is
when I called him right away.
"Suk Jin." I said.
And he answered, "Hey, Chul Min."
"I just saw
your social media." I said.
"Did you? It's funny, isn't it?"
(Did you? It's funny, isn't it?)
Gosh, he's so tactless.
- He has no wit.
- My gosh.
(I thought he called me
because he liked my post.)
My gosh. So I deleted it right away.
(And there's a rising star
who's as popular as Suk Jin.)
Se Chan and Se Hyeong are
doing something together...
- On YouTube.
- on YouTube.
And it was categorized
as a kids' channel.
That's right. They think
it's a kids' channel.
- Really?
- Why?
- Why is that?
- Se Hyeong and you?
Is it a kids' channel?
Those who are in charge
watched their channel...
and thought it was for children.
- It's not like that.
- They looked like kids.
Their faces were automatically
recognized by the computer.
And it was categorized
as a kids' channel.
So you can't write comments
on their videos.
- Really?
- You can't. It's blocked.
- You can't leave comments?
- No.
(The video only has
childish mischief...)
(with a lot of screaming.)
(It's obviously a kids' channel.)
So we are classified as kids.
Isn't it good?
- Why?
- It's good. It sounds cute.
People say we look young.
They play pool in the video.
How would they look like kids?
(Kids who play pool
eating some jjajangmyeon?)
I mean, just one video.
You're right.
There's a vlog.
- That's right.
- I'm talking about the vlog.
It's cute though.
Before we start today's race,
I asked you to bring something
meaningful to give someone...
and something you couldn't throw out
but wouldn't mind...
- if someone else did.
- Yes.
Let's find out
what you brought first.
I brought something
that's really useful.
- Me too.
- I brought something good.
- What's that? It's too big.
- To be honest,
I wanted to bring a treadmill.
Gosh, what's this? It's so big.
- This is so...
- Gosh, what is this?
Is this what Ji Hyo brought?
- Is there a person in it?
- Is it a motorcycle?
- Isn't this a motorcycle?
- No.
Is it a bicycle or what?
Hey.
(He just can't
stop spoiling things.)
Can't you pretend not to know it?
What is this?
- Is it a bicycle?
- I don't know.
He spoiled it again.
He just did it again.
Is it a bicycle for kids?
- Spoiler alert.
- He did it again.
I like that character.
- There's only one.
- How did you bring a bicycle?
- Let's take a look.
- Okay.
- Please open it one by one.
- What is it? I want that one.
- Open the meaningful gift first.
- This is meaningful.
This is a meaningful gift.
I've given it a lot of thought.
I brought this
with one person in mind.
I have this in my restaurant.
- It's so...
- What is it?
(What is it that he has
in his restaurant?)
Let me tell you what it is.
(He brought it
thinking about one person.)
What is it?
(What's his meaningful gift?)
- This is it.
- I knew it.
I like to drink alone these days.
What is that?
That's...
I know what it is.
If you stick a bottle on it
and put a glass under it,
it pours you drinks.
(It's a drink dispenser
for those who drink alone.)
(This isn't PPL.)
It doesn't feel right
to pour yourself a drink, right?
But this makes it feel like
someone poured you one.
- That's right.
- I don't feel lonely.
I brought this...
- thinking about So Min.
- Me?
(Why did he bring
a drink dispenser for So Min?)
(Kwang Soo recited a poem
for So Min in Episode 471.)
(She has terrible drinking habits.)
(I saw you were rolling
your eyes drunk.)
(He revealed
her terrible drinking habits.)
No.
You got it wrong.
- I don't like to drink alone.
- I see.
(It's a lie.)
Shall we take a look
at the meaningless gift?
- What is it?
- Why is it so big?
- Isn't it a tent?
- No. This is...
something I treasured.
- I didn't want to get rid of this.
- You should...
pay money to throw out
something like this.
That's why I brought this.
- You need to pay to throw that out.
- You need a ticket.
- That's right.
- It's too big.
You're using our show to save money.
- To save 3 dollars?
- It's only 3 dollars.
- Gosh, Haha.
- Some people...
- might like it.
- What is it?
It's very meaningful.
- What's that?
- Gosh, what is this?
- It's Kim Jong Kook and Haha.
- There he goes again.
- It's our restaurant.
This is Jong Kook and this is me.
I just couldn't throw it away.
There he goes again.
- He's promoting the restaurant.
- This is PPL.
- Just throw it away.
- Hey, what's that?
This is the worst.
(He brought something
he wants to throw away.)
That's good.
Hey, it's nice.
It looks cute. It's cute.
- It's so cute.
- I know.
If you find it cute, scream.
(Screaming)
(His business partner is satisfied.)
- My gosh.
- It's cute.
- Is this Jong Kook?
- Yes, it's Jong Kook.
Jong Kook doesn't have
big eyes like this.
Are they big?
This needs to get changed.
Gosh, it's so cute.
That's ridiculous.
(Booing)
Just throw it away.
- People are dying to have this.
- Throw it away.
- It's so cute.
- Throw it out.
If you put it on the wall
and get an LED light,
- It's cute.
- It makes a good mood light.
That's true.
I brought something
that you would like.
- That's right.
- That sounds good.
Jae Suk brings something good
at a time like this.
This is also very meaningful
and easy to carry around.
It's not hard to take home.
All right.
You guys will love this.
This is popular these days.
(I see.)
(It's hot these days.)
(It's his album.)
It's called the Yu San Seul set.
(An assorted gift set
of Yu San Seul's goods)
We all are trying
to promote our business.
Why are you promoting
yourself on Running Man?
No. My parents would want this.
I can sign it for you.
Where's the bottle opener?
This isn't what you can buy.
- What did you say?
- I said a bottle opener.
- Where's the bottle opener?
- This isn't what you can buy.
What did you say?
(How dare you say that?)
Why are you being so sensitive?
A bottle opener.
(He's sensitive about Yu San Seul.)
I'm sorry.
Those are hard to get.
They are really popular.
All right, everyone.
I didn't bring anything useless...
- for what I want to get rid of.
- Really?
It's easy to carry around.
- Again?
- And...
I brought what you'd
find useful this season.
(A must-have item for this season)
What is this?
(A Halloween bucket)
- What?
- What's that?
(Unbelievable)
- What is that?
- Halloween is...
in October.
You just brought
what Ji Ho threw out.
What's that thing?
- Isn't it a chamber pot?
- No.
It's so insignificant.
Why would you say that?
- My gosh.
- I told you before.
There must be something else.
- There's nothing. That's it.
- Is that it?
- That's it.
- Unbelievable.
Isn't this nice?
You can use it when you paint.
To wash brushes.
(Laughing)
He's racking his brains.
And when you don't have much time...
and you don't need to buy much,
you can use this.
It's like a shopper bag.
You can use it as a shopper bag.
This isn't a shopper bag.
- It's plastic.
- Stay quiet.
What if Ji Ho wants it back?
- Does he know about this?
- To be honest,
Na Eun tried to take this back.
So I had to hide it.
- I had to give her something else.
- Seriously?
Yes.
I told Ji Ho about this.
He said he doesn't need it anymore.
- Ji Hyo.
- I'm curious about this. It's big.
- It's the biggest one.
- It looks like a motorcycle.
For a meaningful gift,
I brought this
thinking about So Min and Suk Jin.
Because Suk Jin is always...
- jealous of Jong Kook's thighs.
- Isn't this a motorcycle?
He was always jealous.
- And...
- It's really big.
- Wait. This is...
- Gosh, this is...
- It's a bicycle.
- This is nice. Are you sure?
(Suk Jin was right about that.)
- Is it a good one?
- It's really good.
Ji Hyo, I want this. Hey, Ji Hyo.
- This is really good.
- I want this.
This is mine.
- I wanted to buy a bicycle.
- This is expensive.
Why would you give this to us?
Ji Hyo, did you steal it?
It has a lock.
(It has a lock on it.)
Ji Hyo, I want this bicycle.
No, wait.
- I will ride it.
- Wait.
- It has her name on it.
- I'll take this.
This is new.
(Are you sure it's your bicycle?)
This is a road bike.
Gosh, this is good.
- Where are you going?
- He's so mischievous.
- Hey!
(The mischievous boy
steals the bicycle.)
He's so mischievous.
- Where are you going?
- Hey!
(He leaves the studio.)
- Jae Suk.
- This is...
You might get hurt.
It's perfect for your legs.
- Ji Hyo, when did you buy this?
- This?
Ji Hyo, what's this number?
You stole it. I'm sure she stole it.
Did she paint it?
- Does she still do that?
- She stole and painted it.
- You can't do that.
- This isn't right.
- Now, she even steals things.
- No.
- So did you paint it?
- I didn't steal it.
- Do you know the combination?
- No, I don't.
- What?
- What do you mean?
She stole it.
(It's my bicycle,
but I don't know the passcode.)
(She's turning herself in.)
- I don't know the combination.
- Why do you not know that?
After Ji Hyo turned 40,
- she started theft.
- No.
No, it's not like that.
- This is...
- Do you work two jobs?
- Ji Hyo, I just rode it.
- Yes.
It's not your size.
No. This is a pixie.
I guess her ex-boyfriend
was your height.
- Can you prove that it's yours?
- Try riding it.
- Ji Hyo, it's not your size.
- It's dangerous.
No. I'll show you.
Wait.
You can't even touch the ground.
Do you ride it like that?
(Levitating?)
Ji Hyo, this isn't right.
You're standing on your tiptoes.
I think she really stole it.
- I'm serious.
- No.
She couldn't just throw it away.
To be honest,
I gave this to Seong Mun.
- You just made that up.
- No, I'm serious.
I like that ad-libbing.
- That was nice.
- Well done.
If it was Seong Mun's
she would've said that sooner.
But she tried to ride it
as if it was hers.
I bought this for Seong Mun.
He uses public transportation.
- I felt bad so I bought him this.
- Okay. That's enough.
Let's move on.
(Okay. Let's move on.)
- Let's move on.
- All right.
- Let's say that.
- Okay.
- Just move on.
- Is Seong Mun okay about this?
Let's just move on.
I bought this for him,
- so it belongs to me.
- I feel bad for you.
No, listen to me.
She opened the door and took this.
No, I'm serious.
All right. What is the thing
you want to get rid of, Ji Hyo?
It's also big.
- It's a bicycle too.
- What? Is it a bicycle?
- She brought two bicycles.
- Why do you have so many bicycles?
What?
(Is she a bicycle thief or what?)
- She really stole it.
- What's this?
Gosh, what is this?
(A filthy bicycle)
She painted it.
It has a lot of dust on it.
- Hey.
- There are...
a lot of bicycles like this
in my neighborhood.
- No.
- Isn't this from "Um Bok Dong"?
No.
(Dirty)
(Um Bok Dong's old bicycle...)
(that he swept all cycling
competitions in the 1930s with.)
(Is this the bicycle?)
- He said Um Bok Dong.
- My gosh.
What is this?
- The tire is flat.
- This is horrible.
- I want to throw this away.
- This is for the trash.
It's so obvious
that she wants to get rid of it.
You should've at least
wiped it down. Look at the dust.
I received this as a present.
- When?
- It was a gift.
It's a bit...
- too small for me.
- It's too dirty.
(He was about to touch it
but stopped himself.)
He didn't touch it
because it looked dirty.
- It's too...
- He just pretended to touch it.
For some time, I rode this...
- from Ilsan to Gangnam.
- You must be good at riding it.
Mine are not objects.
I wanted to bring good presents.
- We had to bring meaningful ones.
- Right.
I couldn't sleep much
because I had to prepare this.
- I made a lunchbox.
- A lunchbox?
You're going to give these
to Se Chan.
(She's blatant.)
(Were they made for them?)
Look at that.
- I...
- She's very...
- She's very cute.
- They're not for me.
I've prepared this.
It's rice mixed
with butter and soy sauce.
- There are sausages and gimbap.
- They're heart-shaped.
- There's also jangjorim and eggs.
- This is amazing.
This is potato stir-fried with roe.
Seeing how there are cup noodles,
- it's not for me.
- It looks cute.
Look at this.
- Do you think this is for you?
- No.
Kwang Soo?
- She texted Se Chan this morning.
- What did she say?
She took a photo of this lunchbox.
She wrote, "This is enough, right?"
Wait. That means you two...
(Does that mean it's for him?)
What's going on?
There he goes again.
I asked him
if this would be good to bring.
- That's all.
- Why would you ask him?
You could've asked me.
What? It'd be weird to text
the rest of you in the morning.
- We were all up.
- It's...
(Laughing)
What's wrong with him?
(What's with him?)
(So Min and Se Chan
sitting in a tree)
What's wrong with you?
(Haha feels butterflies
in his stomach.)
Come on.
My heart is racing.
Why would yours race?
- I don't know, but it is.
- Come on.
This is an item
I want to get rid of.
Actually, I'd like
to apologize beforehand.
I can't really say it's something
I want to get rid of.
- It's... This is...
- Hey, what are you doing?
(It's a T-shirt of Jong Kook.)
- Why do you have that?
- Well...
- That's not it.
- Goodness.
Hear me out.
- Look.
- That's...
(Why does she have that?)
Why would you get rid of that?
- Just give it to me.
- Hear me out.
For Jong Kook's concert,
Se Chan wanted to make it special,
- so he made 10 of these.
- Right.
- He gave me one of them.
- He made it.
I really liked it,
so I took one home.
But when I wore it at home,
it felt like
there were just us two there.
(She felt like she was home alone
with him.)
(There was a certain man
in the room with her.)
- It really felt that way.
- I can understand.
- It seemed like we were together.
- Right.
When I laid this on the table,
it felt like he was watching me.
It was very frightening.
(It feels like
someone else is home.)
When I laid this on the table...
(It feels like
someone's watching me.)
Give it to me.
If you're mad at him,
you could pinch his nose.
Like this. Or...
you could do this.
(This is best for these weak two
who can't fight him.)
- That's hilarious.
- I like it.
- It's very meaningful.
- It's really cute.
- Next up is Suk Jin.
- Should I go?
After receiving the text,
I thought about the past 10 years.
- I...
- How about you take it out first?
(Jae Suk cuts him off.)
(Sure)
Gosh, that was refreshing.
- You wrapped it?
- I was happy...
to be able to give a present
to a fellow member.
- Did you buy that?
- So I went...
- to the department store.
- Seriously?
My wife came with me.
The moment I laid my eyes on it,
I was reminded of Kwang Soo.
Me? What is it?
My wife got it for him.
- Thank you.
- It was displayed,
- and she pointed at it.
- What is it?
- Thank you.
- We really bought this.
They couldn't wrap it,
- so my wife did.
- Really?
- She did it?
- We're so grateful.
Anyway, these are padded bottoms.
(Anyway, these are padded bottoms.)
He needs this.
It's...
- She got it just for you.
- It's real.
- Let me see.
- Suk Jin.
This won't do.
- It's enough.
- He needs more.
- Goodness.
- It's too thin.
- It's the best gift.
- How nice of her.
- That means she saw the movie.
- This is...
- Don't be ridiculous.
She watched it.
(She saw his bottom in that movie.)
(He'll be forever teased
for his nude scene.)
(Cheer up, Kwang Soo.)
- All right.
- We thought of each other.
Thank you...
Yes, thank you.
- Next up is...
- Something to get rid of.
For that category,
I brought an electronic device.
- Really?
- Does it still work?
I want it.
We used this when we rented a car
in the States over 10 years ago.
(This item holds memories
from 10 years ago.)
- Is that a navigation device?
- It's a navigation device.
(It's an American
navigation device.)
(Laughing)
Does it even work?
- We set this in our car.
- That's...
This is the device.
It looks very third rate.
- That's because...
- I can see it.
When can we use that?
You can use this in the States.
In the States and Canada.
- So who'll use that?
- It's for Americans.
It's for the States and Canada,
and it displays Korean too.
If you say Niagara Falls,
it'll take you there.
How can we go there from here?
You need to be there.
(How can we go
to the Niagara Falls from here?)
You need to be there.
- Right.
- But we got it here.
American rentals all have
navigation devices.
You can't use this here.
- It's for the States and Canada.
- It's useless.
It'd be insane to set that up
on Ji Hyo's bike.
- And ride it in the States?
- And ride it in the States.
You could visit the Niagara Falls.
(Turn the device on, ride the bike,
and go to the Niagara Falls.)
It's nice.
(He doesn't sound that excited.)
- You don't sound too excited.
- What?
What? It's nice.
I thought you were talking to me.
It's better
than your Halloween bucket.
(Suk Jin attacks him.)
(How dare you call it so?)
"Halloween bucket"?
- At least, his is useful.
- Come on, now.
How could you call this so?
It's so pretty.
This is an electronic device.
This will be very popular
when Halloween comes.
- This was expensive.
- He's so harsh.
You can fasten it like this.
Next up is Kwang Soo.
- This is something you need.
- Okay.
- That's important.
- I brought one.
This is...
(Impressed)
You rarely use this at home.
- This is more for restaurants.
- What is that?
- Jong Kook would like that.
- It's a blender.
- Isn't that a blender?
- Oh, it's a blender.
There are various utensils inside
such as knives.
- Those are good for athletes.
- You're right.
Wook Min would like it.
That's probably about 1,000 dollars.
- Really?
- You're right.
(This big blender
is worth around 1,000 dollars.)
- Am I right?
- Are you serious?
- I want it.
- It's expensive.
- It is.
- Seriously?
Let's start off by grinding
Suk Jin's navigation device.
(Let's find out how good it is.)
(You're going to do what
to my navigation device?)
It can easily grind it.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- You'll get brown-colored juice.
- Let's grind...
This is full of memories.
Let's grind it first.
This was very expensive.
And this is the item
I want to get rid of.
Jong Kook and I traveled
to the States before.
After having some drinks,
we became sentimental.
I bought this 300mm UGG boots then.
These are fur boots.
Those are the worst.
They look like
ancient Joseon footwear.
- I just couldn't wear them here.
- Why not?
- What?
- I wear them these days.
- But they're too big for me.
- Try them on.
We should give them to Han Gi Beom.
Suk Jin loves these boots.
I love them.
I brought something else.
I found this in my storage room.
What is that?
(They're curious.)
- What is that?
- That looks familiar.
- It's a Halloween item.
It looks familiar.
- What is that?
- What could it be?
- Nine years ago,
- Right?
Haha gifted this to me.
I knew it.
I remembered it.
Seriously?
How was I able to remember that?
- It's so dusty.
- We were at your house that day.
- It was before you got married.
- Right.
You told me...
to take whatever I needed
from your house.
I picked a hat, but you said
I couldn't have that.
Instead, you told me to take this.
(Take this instead of the hat.)
- You said this was a genuine gift.
- Seriously?
- What's it for?
- What do you do with that?
- I have no idea.
- What's that for?
- I remembered.
- I don't know what it's for.
- It looked so familiar.
- I think you lit a candle inside.
- You need to lit a candle inside.
- I see.
I tossed this in the storage room
nine years ago,
and I finally retrieved it today.
- It's the worst.
- I had forgotten about this.
Yes.
I feel bad for Haha but...
- How could you?
- This was in your closet.
That haunted house is full
of our memories!
That's why I couldn't throw it away.
- These could be a Halloween set.
- You're right.
- Right.
- Let's put them together.
We'll celebrate an early Halloween.
- Right.
- It's a Halloween set.
It didn't look that nice on its own,
but as a set,
- It looks nice, right?
- it looks nice.
- You can hang it here.
- They look nice.
All right.
I can totally remember that day.
- You're right.
- I'm feeling nostalgic.
- Who's up next?
- It's me.
It's Se Chan's turn.
He's So Min's future boyfriend.
(So Min's future boyfriend
will introduce his items.)
I'm talking in future tense.
He'll become her boyfriend.
I think all of you will want this.
Did you have
anyone specific in mind?
You wanted So Min to have yours.
- I'd also like her to have this.
- What is it?
They'd be a good collaboration.
- There are many items for her.
- All right.
- What is it?
- They'd be a good collaboration.
(What is this item that will
work well with Haha's?)
- All right.
- What is that?
It's a soda maker.
It's a soda maker. I'll give you
the can of carbon dioxide as well.
- It's a set.
- That's really nice.
Put a glass of water here...
- then press this.
- It turns into a carbonated drink.
- The carbon dioxide enters it.
- I know.
In what way
is sparkling water good for you?
It has a kick.
- The gas kicks your neck.
- So Min,
it'll give your heart a kick.
Love will surge from it.
Love will kick your heart.
Isn't this decent?
Yesterday, I asked Se Chan
to join me for shaved ice...
after church, but he just bolted.
- Right.
- He ran away again.
He always does.
What a cold idiot.
(What a cold idiot.)
(He's clueless
when it comes to love.)
Unbelievable.
- She gave him an opportunity.
- That idiot.
- Gosh.
- I had no other choice.
So Min officially made a move.
What's so hard about
joining her for shaved ice?
I was busy. All right then.
(He draws a line.)
Here's the item I wish to discard.
I received it as a gift recently,
and it's of a well-known brand.
However, I looked into it...
- and it was a fake.
- Really?
And it was a fake.
- Someone gave you an imitation?
- It was a fake?
That's why...
Hey!
- Why?
- You're throwing away our memory.
(The moment Kwang Soo sees it...)
(Kick!)
(You'll throw away our memory?)
- What is it?
- Is it a memory?
Kwang Soo must've
given it to Se Chan.
(It must be something
Kwang Soo gave him.)
- It is.
- Isn't that of...
- a famous brand?
- It is.
- It's a speaker.
- Isn't it a speaker?
- That's right.
- It's a speaker.
Who on earth would
give you an imitation?
- It's not.
- It is.
- But...
- You had no idea...
that this was an imitation
of a well-known brand.
I knew that, but...
- It was just adorable.
- I thought it'd suit him.
Still, how could you?
Once you hear how it sounds,
you'll understand
why I want to give it up.
- Give us a demonstration.
- Well...
(Unclear sounds)
(What's with the quality?)
Are we listening to a phone?
Are we hearing the speaker?
Yes, the speaker. The music
is coming from the speaker.
(Among the swaying flowers)
Did you turn on an LP record?
(The sound quality is worse
than the speaker on a phone.)
- This...
- Did you keep this underwater?
The bass sound should
be louder and clearer...
- Are the speakers wet?
- Who knows?
No way.
What's wrong with this?
- It has an LP record option.
- Beats me.
It makes recent songs
sound like oldies.
- You're right.
- Right.
It sounded like Jang Beom June
with a cold.
The speaker comes
with a stuffy nose option.
It sounded like Jang Beom June
with a cold.
(The speaker has an LP option
and a stuffy nose option.)
It'll sound incredible
if you turn on old songs.
- Really?
- Yes, old songs.
How much was this? Two dollars?
Still, someone might want it.
First, this is my meaningful gift.
I brought a massager.
What's this?
It soothes any soreness you have
and it can be used as a weapon.
For a second,
I thought he was
bringing out a weapon.
Your calves, thighs, and everywhere.
Even your backside.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
Don't you use a massage gun
powered by electricity?
(Anyone can tell
that a massage gun is better.)
But I use this too.
- I use this.
- The massage gun.
How could you?
- That's too loud though.
- It requires manual labor.
- That's too loud.
- You use a massage gun.
- But this is better.
- That feels good.
Unbelievable.
So what's the next gift?
I really want to throw this away.
- What is it?
- I don't know what to do with it.
I should've gotten rid of it
back then.
- But back then...
- Exactly.
How could you?
Are you kidding me?
Yes, this.
It's a life-size cutout of
Cristiano Ronaldo.
(A life-size cutout
of Cristiano Ronaldo)
- Hold on.
- Are you sure about this?
Can we air this on TV?
- Well...
- What can we do?
Please blur out his face.
He was supposed to visit my house
for "My Little Old Boy."
so I prepared this
to make the event memorable.
- That's right.
- But now...
- he's the most hated man.
- The whole nation hates him.
I don't want to leave it
in my house anymore.
I need to throw this away,
but I haven't had the chance.
I can understand your trouble.
That's something...
- I don't want it.
- I don't want that at all.
- On your way home...
- Gosh.
His and Haha's gifts are the worst.
Mine's perfectly fine.
(His and Haha's gifts
are the worst.)
(The two worst items)
It'll come with an autograph.
(Haha and Jong Kook's
cutout is way better.)
Jong Kook's second gift
is the worst of them all.
It's really something
he wishes to get rid of.
So you've all brought
your gifts today.
We asked you to bring them over...
to celebrate Suk Jin's birthday
and the release of So Min's book.
It's the Double Celebration Race.
(They celebrate Suk Jin's birthday
and the release of So Min's book.)
It's the Double Celebration Race.
Is it your birthday?
What about my birthday?
(He didn't understand it.)
It's your birthday.
Suk Jin, pull yourself together!
This must air around
the time of my birthday.
- Happy birthday.
- We asked you...
to prepare these gifts today...
so that we can celebrate
Suk Jin's birthday...
and So Min's debut as a writer.
Writer Jeon! Goodness.
This is amazing.
- Congratulations.
- Writer Jeon!
- It's embarrassing.
- Gosh.
- We also prepared a gift.
- Really?
- You guys prepared a gift?
Really? There's a gift?
- No way.
- What?
(Turbo's happy birthday song
is played.)
My gosh.
- Goodness.
- You're embarrassing us.
This embarrasses me, you know.
Gosh.
Stand in the center.
Look at this.
- Gosh.
- They used honorifics.
"Happy 55th birthday".
All right, Writer Jeon.
- "You Can Call Me..."
- "After a Drink".
I'm proud of her.
You heard that, right?
"You Can Call Me After a Drink".
A candle went out.
- Right.
- I guess I can call her.
(A candle went out.)
A candle went out.
It feels like my life
has just faded away.
Your life?
- What?
- It's a birthday cake.
A gush of wind blew, that's all.
- Wait, this went out too.
- The other one...
- What?
- It's back to normal again.
No!
(The other candle withered
like Suk Jin's feeble legs.)
(Happy 55th birthday)
(Say goodbye to his life)
What's happening?
(He identifies himself
as the candle flames.)
The wick dropped completely.
Like this?
- The wick...
- Just like his chin drops.
- I mean...
- I've never seen that happen.
- I'm perfectly fine, you know.
- Just look at it.
- All right.
- This is slightly embarrassing,
but thank you so much.
- Blow out the candles.
- Happy birthday.
- 1, 2, 3.
- So Min, go ahead.
(We wish So Min and Suk Jin
the best.)
Congratulations!
This seems out of the blue though.
Tell me about it.
You will compete in two teams today.
So Min and Suk Jin
will be team captains.
Through the games prepared today,
So Min and Suk Jin will win gifts
after each round.
You will compete in three rounds...
and the team to win two rounds first
will be the final winner.
The winning team captain...
will win a chance
to obtain all the meaningful gifts.
- That's nice.
- They're in for a treat.
Or, they will win a chance
to choose between two curtains...
where one conceals a dud
and the other one...
conceals a 100-inch TV
that's worth 8,000 dollars.
- A 100-inch TV?
- Really?
- That's worth 8,000 dollars?
- You can choose...
between two options.
A 100-inch TV
that's worth 8,000 dollars...
(Their eyes open wide.)
(If you choose the dud,
you will obtain one of the wastes.)
- A 100-inch TV?
- No way!
The wall in your house
isn't even 100 inches long.
It isn't.
If you don't want the TV,
you may swap it for
a gift certificate of 8,000 dollars.
- A gift certificate?
- My gosh.
- Then it's truly a gift.
- All right.
If you choose the gifts
that the members brought,
your teammates will
all receive a prize badge.
If you choose to gamble on the TV,
they will only win a prize badge...
if you successfully choose the TV.
- All our teammates.
- Hold on.
Isn't this the most expensive prize
we've been offered?
That's right.
However, there's only
a 50 percent chance.
You can easily choose the dud.
I really want to win today.
It'll be upsetting if the captain
doesn't choose our gifts though.
I know.
(The team captains could risk
their teammates' chances too.)
The member with
the fewest number of badges...
will receive a penalty at the end.
Before we begin the race,
you two will choose your teams.
- Okay.
- How will it be done?
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Good.
- You'll choose your teammates.
- We have to win for them.
It'll be their gifts
you'll be playing for.
But the TV is too good
not to gamble on.
- You'll have to win.
- Exactly.
It's impossible for me
to lose to Suk Jin.
Don't be ridiculous.
- Oh, please.
- Come on.
(So how will
the rock-paper-scissors go?)
Rock-paper-scissors!
(So Min wins.)
(He truly is the weakest
Running Man member.)
Hold on a second.
Which gift was the best?
If I had known,
I would've brought a better gift.
Exactly. If only we knew in advance.
- Right.
- Okay.
I choose the sparkling water maker.
(She first chooses
the sparkling water maker.)
(So Min first chooses Se Chan who
brought the sparkling water maker.)
- All right.
- Of course.
The two youngest
are on the same team again.
First of all...
It's the sparkling water I like,
not Se Chan.
- We get it!
- We hear you.
I really need it.
Okay, fine.
Can't you take the calendar instead?
I want
the sparkling water maker too.
(Suk Jin gets greedy.)
- Seriously?
- Suk Jin...
But I won. Wait, hold on.
- What is it?
- Is this gray hair?
(Is this gray hair?)
- What?
- Let me see.
He'll die if you pluck that out.
Won't he?
- It's not hair, is it? I'm glad.
- Suk Jin,
- is that a udumbara flower?
- I'm glad it's not hair.
- Udumbara?
- What's a udumbara?
- No way.
- I thought of a goat.
Anyway, they're the weakest links.
(Team So Min, Team Suk Jin)
I can't believe this.
The gifts are the worst too.
You never know though.
So you now have your teams.
You'll change clothes
and begin the race.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Today,
my teammates agreed
to be considered as the same age.
- Jong Kook, Kwang Soo...
- There's something...
called the Jeon So Min Rule.
- Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, Se Chan...
- What?
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
I love calling just your names.
Just like the members of AOA,
- we'll stick to just the names.
- Sounds good.
- Then can we...
- Can I call you Kook?
- Of course.
- Kook!
- Kook.
- Look at him.
- Just so you know,
friends get into fights
while growing up.
What?
So Min, say that
we can't argue or fight.
You see, it's mean to hit
someone younger than you,
but it's okay
to beat up your friends.
- Of course.
- That's how...
we grow up and build our friendship.
- I'm sure you're all hungry.
- Yes!
The first game
you'll be competing in...
is Name the Dish.
- Name the Dish?
- That's right.
You'll be given 100 minutes.
Among the dishes sold in Seoul,
find the dish with the longest name
to win.
What is this?
Only the actual name
on the menu counts.
If the other team finds a dish
that has a longer name than you did,
you'll get to try again
within the given time.
Does a set menu count?
- As long as it's on the menu.
- Of course.
Does "something and something"
count?
- That counts too.
- It does?
But you can only order...
one portion.
The member who eats the dish
wins a prize badge...
regardless of the result.
We have to compete
against each other.
- We compete against each other?
Only one member gets to eat.
Then it's a good thing
that we're all weak.
- It's a good thing.
- In that case,
- we're lucky.
- We have an advantage.
- It's not bad.
- I mean...
I have a chance.
You should have told us beforehand.
- You guys are so unlucky.
- It's war.
Hey.
- You picked the wrong guys.
- So Min is so unlucky.
If I had known...
I love my team.
We can just pick one randomly.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- All right.
You can decide
how you pick one member.
Please get on the cars now.
- Let's go!
(I think I picked the wrong team.)
- What should we have?
"A dish with a long name".
(They start searching the Internet
right away.)
It's an Italian restaurant.
"Red wine oxtail stew
and creamy barley risotto".
- That's perfect.
- Where is that place?
- Let's go there!
- Hold on.
- Let me see.
- Ji Hyo did it!
- I have to see where it is.
- How many letters are there?
"Red wine..."
It's in another country.
Gosh.
(What were we getting excited for?)
We can go there
as long as we have a GPS.
- Hey.
- Get a GPS.
There are many restaurants
like this in Itaewon.
- Hey, Suk Jin.
- What?
"Their dishes not only have
long names but also taste amazing".
"Woo Seul's restorative chicken..."
"with abalone, mitten crabs,
and small octopus".
- That's the place!
- Hold on.
- Let's go there.
- Where is that place?
- It's in Iksan. Gosh.
- That's too far.
That would have been perfect.
(Ji Hyo is counting something.)
- I found 16 letters.
- Where is it?
"Burgundy wine-marinated beef stew".
- Let's go there.
- Where is it?
- It's in Itaewon. Hold on.
- Let's go.
- There are even longer names.
- They have really long names.
"Roasted pork tenderloin
served with mustard sauce..."
"and grilled eggplants".
It has 22 letters.
- Unbelievable.
- Ji Hyo!
- It's not bad, right?
You did it!
Ji Hyo, good job.
We have two masters...
of Internet searching.
All right.
I'll try searching the Internet.
Hold on. 1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
- 11, 12, 13, 14... It's 17 letters.
- What?
- It's 17 letters.
- Can you find that?
- What is it called?
- Hey.
"Wings marinated in Analog Kitchen's
special soy sauce".
- Is that the name?
- That's the name.
- Is it in Itaewon?
- Yes, it is. It's not bad, right?
- I can't find anything.
- Should we look some more?
Let's look some more on our way.
Hey.
"The American mom's..."
"Beef meatballs and French fries
made by American mom".
- Unbelievable.
- Where is it?
- Where is that place?
- The "American mom"?
It says, the "American mom".
Not the Korean mom,
but the American mom?
- The "American mom"?
- That's right.
Where is the place? It sounds nice.
It's near Hongik University.
It's in Yeonnam-dong.
Guys, let me tell you
what we'll have.
It's 18 letters.
"Carbonara with rich cream sauce
that fills your mouth".
- That sounds good.
- I'm sure it tastes good too.
- Nice!
- I finally found something.
- Good job.
- You did a good job.
- Se Chan, you're the best.
While Kwang Soo was checking
his messages,
- I've been searching the Internet.
- I can't find anything.
I've been searching,
but I can't find anything.
I found something.
"Flavorful beef cream sauce risotto
served with ginkgo nuts,"
"bell peppers, and mushrooms
with a touch of lemon".
- How many letters is that?
- Kim Jong Kook!
- Where is it?
- It's in Itaewon.
- Can you call them? It's closer.
- It's even closer.
- Hey.
- Why couldn't you find this?
Hey, what are you doing?
- You're useless.
- I'm sorry.
Try calling them.
- Hold on.
- It has more than 20 letters.
- What?
It's closed on Mondays.
- Really?
Many restaurants in Itaewon
are closed on Mondays.
- Yang Se Chan!
- Yang...
- Seriously?
I can't believe this.
- Are they really closed?
- They're closed on every Monday.
Please go to the previous place.
Yes. Jong Kook!
(They're going to the place
Se Chan found in Yeonnam-dong.)
Okay.
That's so cute. "Okay".
- Okay.
- Jong Kook!
- "Okay. I admit it".
- Jong Kook, you're so cute.
- Jong Kook!
- Okay.
- You should work harder.
Try it. You're so cute.
- Okay.
That's so cute.
(Cute)
I love everything that's cute.
I respect everyone who's cute.
- What are you doing?
- He's so stubborn.
- I'm not good at it.
- Kwang Soo.
Are you okay with Se Chan
being rude to you?
Have you guys
ever been polite to me?
(Irritated)
Have you?
- They've never been polite.
- Kwang Soo.
Have you ever treated me
with respect?
- Don't be like that.
- Kwang Soo.
- Come on, you're good at this.
- Right.
- Do it just once.
He's so stubborn.
We've been begging him.
- Is it so hard to say, "Okay"?
- Why is it so hard?
Okay.
(Kwang Soo can be so cute
in front of Jong Kook.)
Good job.
We're Team Okay now.
We're Team Okay.
(Team Suk Jin is going to Itaewon,)
(while Team So Min is going
to Yeonnam-dong.)
I should take my wife
to places like this.
- He's lying.
- I know.
It's just something
he says on camera.
(He pretends to be a good husband
on camera.)
I'd tell her when and where
we should meet.
And she'd wonder what's going on.
He's lying.
We'd eat together.
We'd have steaks.
When Suk Jin says
he'd do something,
he never actually does it.
(Embarrassed)
I shouldn't have worn long johns.
- Did you think it'd be cold?
- I took mine off.
I never wear long johns.
You did the other day.
It was exceptionally cold that day.
Why would you lie?
I rarely wear them.
- I think we're here.
- We are?
Good that we're here.
Otherwise, Suk Jin would have
needed a special investigation.
(It looks like he is appearing
before the prosecution.)
Where is it?
- I think this is it.
- This is it.
Can we shoot here for a minute?
We're going to eat.
- Is that okay?
- It won't take long.
Can we see a menu, please?
We want the dish
with the longest name.
- The dish with the longest name.
- Here it is.
- Let's see.
- We came to the right place.
- Nice.
- It smells so good too.
- The food looks so good.
- This is nice.
- Hold on. This is even longer.
- What is it?
But it's sold out.
(Sold out)
It's already sold out?
- Truffle...
- It runs out fast.
It must be going well for you.
I'll come back with my wife later.
He's definitely not coming.
(Can you tell?)
Do you see that?
Suk Jin is embarrassed.
I can totally tell
what he's thinking.
Only the names on the menu count.
Can we order this?
"Roasted pork tenderloin
served with mustard sauce..."
"and grilled eggplants".
- Can we order this?
- Yes, you can.
- Is that all you need?
- Yes, please.
It has 22 letters.
"Roasted..." It has 22 letters.
Please decide who is going to eat.
- What should we do?
- Well...
(Thinking)
How about...
we ask someone passing by...
who should eat...
among us?
That's not okay. It's unfair.
You have an advantage over us.
They'll pick you.
How about this?
- We'll all be assigned a number.
- Right.
- Let's do that.
- That sounds good.
- Number 1, number 2...
- That should work, right?
- What number do you want?
- I want number one.
- No. I want number 2.
- Number 2? I want number 3.
- I'll be number 1.
- I'll be number 4.
Number three is nice.
We'll ask someone on the street.
- Just one person.
- Number 3 is nice.
- When there are 4 options,
- people would choose number 3.
- All Koreans choose number 3.
Each of the four is assigned...
a number between 1 and 4.
Can you choose a number
between 1 and 4?
(What number
will the passer-by choose?)
To be honest,
if we weren't shooting,
we could have come here
with some friends...
- That would be really nice.
- and eat together.
That sounds so nice.
(Suk Jin feels thirsty
and pours himself a glass of water.)
(Staring)
(Suk Jin, the oldest member,
fills his own glass first.)
That does sound nice.
Aren't you going
to fill our glasses?
(He puts the bottle
back on the table...)
(after filling his own glass.)
- I was watching him.
- Gosh.
- I knew it.
- Unbelievable.
I knew what he'd do.
I'm okay with him
filling his own glass first,
- but I thought he'd fill ours too.
- I thought the same.
I was watching him.
I couldn't believe what I saw.
- I'm sorry.
- He can fill his own glass first,
but he should fill
the others' glasses too.
(Disappointed)
- I couldn't believe it.
- You're the worst.
I'm disappointed.
I had no idea.
Here comes our food.
(Their food is served.)
- It looks delicious.
- What's this?
- It's pork tenderloin.
It looks fantastic.
Let me just try slicing it.
- Oh, my.
- Was this cooked sous-vide?
Let me explain.
It's cooked at low temperature...
- for longer than 10 hours.
- That's right.
Is that correct?
Is the result out yet?
Please tell us.
The person who gets to eat
the roasted pork tenderloin...
served with mustard sauce
and grilled eggplants is...
Please.
(Nervous)
- I'm nervous.
- I'm so nervous.
This is driving me crazy.
- Number 3.
- Number 2, please.
(Between 1 and 4, what number
did the passer-by choose?)
Congratulations, number one.
(Number 1 is Jae Suk.)
- Number one.
- Okay. Thank you.
No way.
(Devastated)
(Thank you for your time.)
I can't believe this. Number one?
(Jae Suk gets to eat
the roasted pork tenderloin.)
- No way.
- Unbelievable. Number one?
I'll try it.
(He tries a big piece.)
- Does it taste good?
- It tastes amazing.
- How does it taste?
- It tastes like a sausage, right?
Does it taste like a sausage?
- You know how it tastes?
- I do.
- It tastes amazing.
- I love it.
It's delicious.
- It looks so good.
- Are you going to eat all of that?
We'll play rock-paper-scissors.
Give one piece to the winner.
- Jae Suk.
- Just one piece.
Rock-paper-scissors is boring.
Do a talent show.
- A talent show?
- It tastes fantastic.
(What should I do?)
I'll improvise a song
about mashed potatoes.
That sounds good.
Let's eat mashed potatoes
Mashed, mashed potatoes
(Jae Suk doesn't look impressed.)
Tasty, soft mashed potatoes
It goes perfectly
with pork tenderloin
(The lyrics are
catchy and addictive.)
It's served with eggplants, mashed
potatoes, and pork tenderloin
Please give me a bite, ooh
(He ends the song
in a seductive way.)
That wasn't half bad.
Gosh, Suk Jin.
(Haha, you should just have a bite.)
Hey.
- You should just eat it.
- Hey.
- Does it taste good?
- You should just eat it.
- My goodness.
You should just eat it.
Jae Suk completed the dish,
so he gets a prize badge.
With 22 letters,
you currently hold the record.
- Currently?
- Yes.
Let's hit the road again.
That was tasty.
(They go to find a dish
with a longer name.)
- We are here.
- This is the place.
- Let's hurry up and eat.
- Let's go.
- All right. Let's go.
- Okay.
- It's a matter of who eats it.
Jong Kook, there is a dish
with a longer name.
Cream-Sauce Pasta with a Whole Crab
and Popping Flying Fish Roe.
- Paprika...
- This is legit.
- My goodness.
- How many letters are there?
- 19 letters.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 19...
(Why does 19 come after 16?)
- 17, 18, 19.
- 17.
(Se Chan, 17 comes after 16.)
What am I supposed to do with you
if you can't even count?
- You can't count.
- I got nervous.
- Which name is longer?
- Let's go in. There must be more.
- Hello. Would it be okay...
- Hello.
Would it be okay
if we have a shoot at a corner?
- It won't take long.
- Thank you.
- Let's go in.
- This is the place.
- Let's go.
There is a dish with a name
that contains 19 letters.
(My goodness!)
- 2, 4, 6, 8, 10...
- Cream Pasta...
- Hold on. 12, 14, 16, 18...
- Cream Pasta with Salted...
- 22, 24,
- My goodness.
26, 27!
(There is a dish with 27 letters.)
This is incredible.
We will surely win.
Please decide which member will eat.
Shall we point to and eliminate
one member?
Let's play Go Away.
- Okay.
- Go Away.
Go Away.
- Point to one member. 1, 2...
- 1, 2...
(Who will be eliminated first?)
- Three.
- Go away.
(Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and So Min
choose Jong Kook.)
What? Three.
(He gets all the votes.)
Jong Kook.
- When I wasn't looking...
- Jong Kook, I am sorry.
- No.
Why weren't you looking?
Okay.
(How did this happen?)
- Let's point to one member.
- Let's do that.
(Point to Jong Kook.)
Let's play Go Away.
(When Jong Kook was looking away)
(Tapping)
(Point to Jong Kook.)
- One person gets to eat, right?
- That's right.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
Let's play the game
Jong Kook suggests.
Okay. We will play the game
you suggest.
Do you know me?
Jong Kook.
(This is bad.)
- This is...
- You have nothing to do with me.
- This is the beginning.
- It's okay.
Suit yourself.
Jong Kook, this is the beginning.
Are you going to ignore us?
I am going to have my own show.
- I will hold the camera.
- No.
I am going to use Instagram Live.
- Jong Kook.
- It's okay. I am fine.
That was delicious.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
You found a dish with 22 letters
and only Jae Suk got a badge.
- Yes.
The other team is eating a dish
that's 27 letters long.
What?
How does it have 27 letters?
- How is it possible?
- Really? 27 letters?
- What happens now?
- You hit the road again.
- We need to find another dish.
- That's right.
Let's surf the Web again.
I don't think we will find
a longer name.
Why don't we draw lots?
Let's ask the owner to choose one.
When the dish gets served,
we won't say anything.
The person who is closest to it
gets eliminated.
- It's a good idea.
- What do you think?
The person who is closest to it
gets eliminated.
- Let me answer a call from Haha.
- You are getting a call.
- Haha.
- Which restaurant did you visit...
to find a dish with 27 letters?
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Hold on.
Hold on.
Hey.
(The one who is closest to the dish
will be eliminated.)
Se Chan.
(He puts it in front of Se Chan.)
(Se Chan, enjoy the dish.)
- Se Chan.
- Yes?
I hear you giggling
with your girlfriend.
I think...
- you need a scolding.
- Jae Suk.
Jae Suk, I am done.
You found a dish with 27 letters.
Do I know you?
(Anyang Loser
isn't through with them.)
Sit here.
I am sorry,
but I don't want to share a table
with a stranger.
There are other tables.
What?
Jong Kook is being the Anyang Loser.
This is suffocating.
You just sat next to me.
Okay. I am hanging up.
Okay, Jae Suk. See you later.
One person can eat, right?
- The one with a longer noodle...
- The one with a longer noodle wins.
Okay.
(So Min carefully picks a noodle.)
- You picked one. Lift it up.
- Okay.
- It's long.
- What? Is it buried underneath?
- What is going on?
It's pretty long.
- It's long.
- That's good.
- Kwang Soo, it's your turn.
I don't know what they are doing,
but it looks fun.
- Yes.
- It looks fun.
I used to have fun with them.
- You can't change once you pick.
- The noodles go deep.
- You know,
they are covered
with cheese and cream.
You can only pick one.
(After much deliberation,
he picks a noodle.)
You are done.
It's this one. Please let it short.
It's over if it breaks.
Please let it be short.
(What?)
(Is that it?)
(It's obvious that So Min won.)
Kwang Soo, come here.
Look at this. Yours is ridiculous.
You are done.
The dish is mine.
Come here.
(So Min gets Cream Pasta
with Salted Pollack Roe and Bacon.)
(Satisfied)
- So Min, do you taste...
- It looks delicious.
- all the ingredients...
in the name?
Yes. It's tasty, but there is a lot.
I wish I could share.
It contains
salted pollack roe, right?
- Yes, it does.
- Salted pollack roe and cream.
I see.
You know,
it's hard to find a dish
that's 28 letters long.
I can only find one
that's 25 letters long.
Why are they so good
at finding things?
This is bad.
- Jae Suk!
- Let's surf the Web.
- What?
- Jae Suk!
(Haha finds something
when they were about to give up.)
- Hold on.
- What?
- This one has 45 letters.
(45 letters?)
- 45 letters?
- Really?
Look.
It actually exists.
I can't believe it.
(My goodness.)
This is unbelievable.
- Let's go.
- It's bibim guksu.
- Bibim guksu has...
- Bibim naengmyeon.
- Let's go.
- This is unbelievable.
- This is...
- This is incredible.
- It actually exists.
I bet the production crew
didn't expect this.
You can't beat...
- 45 letters.
- Are they on the road again?
- I think she is done.
- That's good.
She ate with gusto.
- She ate everything.
- I know.
So Min's team succeeded
to clear a dish...
that's 27 letters long.
That's what matters.
We should hit the road again.
I don't think we should search
on the street.
- Jong Kook.
- What?
Sweet Melon, Parmesan,
Prosciutto That Has Been Cured...
- for 24 Months, and...
- And...
- Buffalo Mozzarella.
- Okay.
- 30... 31 letters.
- 31 letters.
Is that the name?
- Are you sure it's the name?
- Hold on.
- It's the name.
- This is the English name.
- What is this dish?
- A pizza?
- Are you sure it's the name?
It's on the menu.
Are you sure it's the name?
The English name is...
They translated it into Korean.
- You are right.
- This is driving me crazy.
It's the name.
- Where is the restaurant?
- Where is it?
It's in Hongdae.
- Hongdae?
- It's near.
- Let's go.
Shall we play rock-paper-scissors
this time?
So Min can choose...
a member to eliminate
just like she did the last time.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
That's funny because it wasn't me.
- It wasn't me.
- Listen.
- Even if someone else suggested it,
- That's right.
the team captain makes
the final decision.
- That's her responsibility.
- That's the weight of her position.
"One who wears the crown
must bear its weight."
That's her responsibility.
- I can tell that you are a writer.
- Stop it.
Stop it.
- I am sorry, but it's a saying.
- It's a saying.
- It's a famous saying.
Is it a saying?
"Must bear its weight."
Shall we play fair this time?
- Okay.
- Jong Kook isn't sullen anymore.
- That's good.
- Shall we start anew...
- with a round of applause?
- Okay.
Let's start anew
with a round of applause.
Let's start anew.
Let's clap the slate. 1, 2, 3.
This is good.
(It's hard to be the team captain.)
This is a familiar neighborhood.
We are in Hongdae.
We will get off
as soon as we turn left.
It just needs to be on the menu.
- That's right.
- It just needs to be on the menu.
Please stop here. This is the place.
(Is it Haha and Jong Kook's
barbecue restaurant?)
- The dish is...
- Hold on.
- It just needs to be on the menu.
- It's on the menu.
- A dish with 45 letters?
There is a dish with 45 letters.
- Hello.
Hello.
(As soon as they enter,
Haha's friend, Geun Sik, appears.)
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
You look familiar.
Let's sit down.
Sir, please give us the menu.
Please give us the menu.
Let me remind
that it needs to be on the menu.
- It's on the menu.
Why else would we be here?
I have been to this restaurant
many times,
- but I never saw such a thing.
- It's on the menu.
- It really exists.
- It came to be in 2020...
As an event.
Since it's a special dish,
it's at the back of the menu.
- It's at the back.
- It's on the wall too.
- Is it on the wall too?
- There it is.
(It counts if it has been sold
as a dish on the menu.)
(What's the dish?)
- There it is.
(Nino Maximus Keyser Soze Sonador
Sparta and Jack Sparrow's...)
- Nino Maximus Keyser Soze...
- Keyser Soze...
Sonador Sparta and Jack Sparrow's...
Beloved Lutartha Sparta
Kook's Lovely Bibim Naengmyeon.
- It actually exists.
- Let's see if it's on the menu.
- Here it is.
This is the menu, okay?
- It exists.
Look at this.
- It's obviously fake.
- Nino Maximus...
It doesn't even have a price
next to it.
(30 minutes ago)
(Geun Sik.)
(I'm doing Running Man right now.
Can you create a menu for me?)
(What do you mean?)
(Just make up a long name for
bibim naengmyeon on the menu.)
(Do it right away.
I'm heading over there now.)
(That's how the Nino Maximus Beloved
Bibim Naengmyeon got created.)
Nino Maximus Keyser Soze
Sonador Sparta...
and Jack Sparrow's Beloved...
- Lutartha Sparta Kook's Lovely...
- Bibim Naengmyeon.
How many letters is that?
It doesn't even have a price.
It shouldn't cost too much.
It's the same as any other
bibim naengmyeon.
Sir, how much is bibim naengmyeon?
- 5 dollars.
- It's all 5 dollars.
It's five dollars.
- That's cheap.
- You can just tell.
If this is different from
the regular dish, I'll accept.
(Show him that it's different
from the regular bibim naengmyeon.)
Regular bibim naengmyeon is...
Can you order
a regular bibim naengmyeon?
The egg is...
It's essentially the same thing.
(He comes out of nowhere.)
(He interrupts tactlessly.)
What?
- What did you say?
- It's half-and-half.
It's half-and-half.
The regular bibim naengmyeon...
- True.
- comes with a boiled egg...
- It's only a quarter.
- that's only a quarter.
This is the restaurant's...
- Right.
- special menu.
- That's cheap.
- You can just tell it's cheap.
Let me know
if this is too much for you.
My mouth is getting watery.
It's impossible to find a dish...
- It's impossible.
- that's over 40 letters long.
I'm done.
(She finishes eating
with 3 minutes left.)
- She's done.
- You have to approve.
Ji Hyo finished it,
so please take a prize badge.
(She gets a prize badge.)
They have no choice, right?
- What are they going to do?
- It's on the menu.
It's on the menu.
After some discussion,
we've decided to approve
Ji Hyo's prize badge.
(What about the mission?)
Mission failed.
(47 letters were disapproved.)
If we approve this,
the other team will try to
create a menu too.
- That's true.
- We did think far enough.
It doesn't matter if we win today.
We'll keep suffering.
We at least got a prize badge.
- That's at least comforting.
- Let's get going.
(They earn a prize badge
and conclude the first mission.)
Hey, weaklings.
- Here they are.
- Oh, dear.
- We heard.
Was it that difficult to find?
You were so short on letters.
So Team So Min won.
That was close.
Round one is now over.
Let's move onto round two.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Sit with your team.
Shall we?
Okay.
His name is Se Chan from now on.
- Sure.
- Se Chan.
Se Chan.
Sure, you can call it Se Chan.
Come here.
- Captain.
- I think...
So Min has a strategy now.
(He's trying to stir
something up again.)
- Oh, gosh.
- My Se Chan.
(She's trying to seduce Se Chan.)
- What are you doing?
- My Se Chan.
What is she doing?
This second mission is a quiz
related to memorable commercials.
Memorable commercials?
It's called Aged Commercials.
- This is ours to take.
- Good.
We're at a disadvantage.
The team that guesses more
out of the five commercials wins.
Okay!
After getting the answer right,
you will act out the commercial
and fill in the missing line.
- All right.
- The line.
There are so many old people...
It's a gathering of the old fossils.
- They have so many old people.
- They're the old fossils.
What are you saying?
The youngest is 40 something.
They're the aged ones.
- They're the old fossils.
- My gosh.
- We're all young.
- Excuse me.
- You should join us.
- Aren't you...
all old too?
(This is a controversy.)
We're not.
- You're not?
- I'm old,
- but they're not.
- They're old too.
- They're not.
- They definitely are.
You're all over 40.
- No.
- That's true.
There's 1 person who just turned 40.
- Still.
- I'm a newbie.
- I'm a new 40.
- Newbie.
- We're at a disadvantage.
- We're going to lose.
We're at a disadvantage.
We're going to win for sure.
- Let's do this.
- Whoever calls out,
"Let me answer,"
will get to go first.
Here's the first question
for Aged Commercials.
Play...
- I'm going to get this.
- the first commercial.
(It's a beverage commercial from
the 2000s with many catchphrases.)
(Zo In Sung and Jun Ji Hyun's
emotional acting is the key.)
I thought you were busy with work.
- Is dating part of work too?
- Don't jump to conclusions.
Why? Are you embarrassed of me?
Do I look pathetic?
- Be quiet.
- Are you sorry?
What's wrong with you?
Who are you to yell at me?
I thought you were busy with work.
What's this?
What's wrong with you?
Who are you to yell at me?
Have you ever bought me dinner
at a nice restaurant?
Have you ever dropped me off
with your car like other people?
(She got caught on a date with
somebody that's not her boyfriend.)
(Commercials back then had stories.)
- Was there a commercial like this?
- I've never seen it.
Is this a commercial?
I've never seen it.
Don't you have a sense of pride?
Get yourself together!
(Blank)
(This is the product.)
Liars...
Is love enough for love?
(The actors' enthusiasm
made this commercial shine.)
I don't remember the line,
but I remember seeing it.
- I don't know. I have no clue.
- This is so long.
Wait.
- We have to act this out?
- This existed?
We have to do this?
You just need to
make it sound similar.
This is for So Min and Se Chan.
- They have to do it.
- I'm looking forward to it.
- They need to act.
- I'm going to be Yang In Sung.
You'll become Yang In Sung.
Here comes Yang In Sung.
Personality controversy.
He said "personality controversy."
(It's a play on words.)
If I do this,
there'll be
a personality controversy.
I saw that a lot
when I was young.
- This...
- "Are you sorry?"
I don't remember.
The team that wants to go first
can start.
If we go first, they'll copy us.
- I think I know.
- They might copy us, so let's wait.
We can't get it on our first try.
- Right?
- Isn't this right?
- Go.
- "Get yourself together."
"I was never enough."
- That's right.
- Okay. Go.
- Let me answer.
- Go.
You can start.
- Please come up.
- Suk Jin wants to do it.
Go, Ji Hyo.
(Team Suk Jin's first attempt!)
- Jee In Sung.
- Jee In Sung?
Gosh, Jee In Sung.
He has to worry about
his personality.
His skin is oily.
Is he a Jee Rogue?
Jee In Sung.
- Go.
- Come this way.
Hey, you said you were busy at work,
but you were dating another guy.
You said you were busy at work,
(What?)
What are you doing?
That's not the commercial.
- This is horrible acting.
- Stop it.
- I can't do Zo In Sung.
- Just do the original.
- Copy the lines.
I thought you were busy with work.
Is dating part of work too?
Don't jump to conclusions.
Why? Are you embarrassed of me?
Do I look pathetic?
- He's yelling.
- Be quiet.
- Are you sorry?
- Have you ever bought me dinner...
at a nice restaurant?
Did you ever pour water for me?
Did you ever
open the car door for me?
You did nothing for me.
I guess you have a sense of pride.
Do you have a sense of pride?
Get yourself together.
(This is the blank part.)
This is the important part.
I was never enough.
Good!
(I was never enough!)
Does she remember?
Liars...
(Liars!)
I'll bury all of them.
- What?
- What was that?
- "I'll bury all of them?"
- I followed my instinct.
- You don't say that...
- in a commercial.
- You'll bury them?
- Why would you bury me?
- I stayed true to my emotions.
- When will you stop?
- Goodness.
Number 1 and 2 were both wrong.
- They were wrong.
- We were wrong?
Both?
- We're ready.
- What's number one?
(They're excited to see
who's up for Team So Min.)
- Jun Ji Min.
- I'm excited for them.
Jun Ji Min.
- Personality controversy.
- Yang In Sung.
Saeb In Sung.
- Please say, "ready, action."
- Ready, action.
I thought you were busy with work.
Is dating part of work too?
Don't jump to conclusions.
Why? Are you embarrassed of me?
Do I look pathetic?
Be quiet.
- Are you sorry?
- What's wrong with you?
Who are you to yell at me?
Have you ever bought me dinner
at a nice restaurant?
Have you ever dropped me off
with your car like other people?
Hey, does it drive you nuts that
I'm dating somebody else?
Does it make you mad
to see me like this?
Does it make you mad?
I guess you have a sense of pride.
Do you have a sense of pride?
(This couple acts well.)
Get yourself together.
Do you know what love is? Do you?
"Do you know what love is? Do you?"
"Do you know what love is?"
Liars...
don't get presents from Santa Claus.
(He summoned Santa Claus.)
You know that?
(Is this a Christmas commercial?)
Liars don't get presents...
- from Santa Claus!
- Your hair.
- Is number one wrong too?
- I think it's right.
- It's incorrect.
- Is it similar?
- It's wrong?
- Two?
I'll give you a hint for number one.
It starts with "Love is..."
"Love is amusing to you, right?"
- I'm right.
- What is it?
- Is it right?
- "Love is amusing to you, right?"
- Let's go.
- Go.
We'll give it a try.
I remembered.
- This is the answer.
- I think you're right.
- Let's do it.
- I thought you were busy with work.
Is dating part of work too?
- Get yourself together.
- Let's go!
(Get yourself together.)
Does love look like water to you?
(Does love look like water to you?)
- That's not right.
- Lairs...
Liars...
(Liars...)
have no right to love.
- For when you're 2 percent short.
(The performance is 2 percent short,
but the ending is perfect.)
Only the second one is correct.
I told you not to do it!
The tone was similar.
I told you not to do the second one.
They didn't know about that one.
Let me give you a hint.
This is a poor couple.
- The woman lied to this man.
- A poor couple.
Despite...
their financial difficulties,
they loved each other.
(Fiddling with his phone)
It makes no sense.
Jae Suk, you can't look it up.
- What are you doing?
- What is wrong with you?
- I didn't look it up.
- How could you be so shameless?
I didn't look it up.
- For goodness' sake.
- This is...
He got a text.
There is no way he got a text.
Who was it? Who told on me?
(He yells at the production crew
in embarrassment.)
This is something
the elders say often.
Give it a try.
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer. This is it.
- This is it. This is it.
- Let me answer.
- This is it.
- I don't think it's correct.
- It's correct.
- It's too old-school.
It's what the elders say.
You should try it.
- Okay.
- It's too old-school.
- Are you sure it's correct?
- It's correct!
Does it drive you nuts
that I am dating somebody else...
- and not working?
- It drives me nuts!
Does it make you mad
to see me like this?
- It makes me mad!
- Does it make you mad?
I guess you have a sense of pride.
Do you have a sense of pride?
- Yes, I do.
- Get yourself together.
Okay. Check it out.
(The second answer
has been revealed.)
- Love...
- You're right.
(If they get the first answer,
they will win.)
doesn't put food on the table.
- What?
- Is that the answer?
Liars...
- have no right to love.
- That sounds right.
(Team Suk Jin's answer
is correct.)
"Love doesn't put food
on the table."
We shouldn't have given away
the second answer.
I told you it's correct.
Gosh,
it's an expression old men use.
I guess you have a sense of pride.
Do you have a sense of pride?
Get yourself together.
Love doesn't put food on the table.
It's correct.
(Suk Jin really is an old man.)
Liars...
have no right to love.
Is love enough...
for love?
(We could have won.)
We revealed the second answer
too early on.
- Seriously.
- I remember the commercial now.
Their performance was incredible.
They filmed it hundreds of times.
How would you know?
That might not be the case.
- They are excellent actors.
- They filmed it for a day...
to get an okay from the director.
I had no idea
about the first answer.
Here comes
the second aged commercial...
- you barely remember.
- Okay.
We remember that period of time.
Let's go.
Here is the second question.
- Play.
- But I don't remember...
(It's a coffee commercial
from 2008.)
Da In, are you wearing makeup?
- She is wearing a skirt too!
- Go away!
I know this one.
I auditioned for it.
Really?
- She is wearing a skirt too!
- Go away!
She is wearing makeup!
(She is waiting for her crush.)
Sometimes,
lies are necessary for love.
Hey,
I think I have a fever.
Of course, you need wits
to fall for those lies.
I wish you luck.
- This is...
- Why...
It was a popular commercial.
It was incredibly popular.
I don't remember it.
- People parodied it.
- That's right.
I just remember the woman's line.
(Although I auditioned for it,
I don't remember the whole thing.)
"Hey, I think I have a fever."
Maybe this is the answer.
"Do you like me feverishly?"
- For goodness' sake.
(The comedian's ad-lib
makes them speechless.)
When the woman,
Ryu Hyun Jin, spoke,
the man laughed.
(Ryu Hyun Jin?)
Suk Jin, Ryu Hyun Jin
is a baseball player.
Her name is Da In.
- Suk Jin.
- Yoo Da In.
- The man's name is Lee Hyun Jin.
- He mixed up the names.
- Suk Jin, you are unbelievable.
- Lee Hyun Jin.
Don't you remember the man's line?
- I don't remember it.
- You auditioned for it.
- "Are you in a lot of pain?"
- Let's try it.
Let's see what we come up with.
Ji Hyo, try it.
"Hey, I think I have a fever."
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo get ready.)
- This is...
- Is this university for the elders?
Is this university for the elders?
- The university...
- The university for the elders.
(Team Suk Jin gives it a go!)
Go.
- Hey.
- Yes?
- What...
- That was so late.
How could you address the principle
that way?
- You should bow to him.
- The president of the university.
(Suk Jin failed to graduate
and became the principle.)
- I can't do this.
- How many years did he move down?
I can't get immersed in it.
I have no idea
what kind of commercial this is.
Let's do this one by one.
(A forbidden romance between
the principle and a student?)
"Hey, I think I have a fever."
"Hot water is pouring out!"
That's how
this commercial should go.
Take my hand.
Hey, I think I have a fever.
You are burning up.
That could be the answer.
- That was the worst.
- That could be the answer.
- What was that?
- Let me answer.
- We have an idea.
- It's our turn.
- Aren't you going to go?
- Let me answer. We have an idea.
- Sit down.
- Do this.
What a scary underclassman!
(Kim Jong Kook, the queen
of the PE Department)
That's cute.
(I should have gone out the back.)
- Hey, I think I have a fever.
- Put his hand on your forehead.
(Please spare me.)
What are you doing?
(I think I have a fever, okay?)
I think my hand is warmer.
- What? Is it incorrect?
- Is it incorrect?
- Was it close?
- It's correct.
- It's incorrect.
- No, it's correct.
Come on. It's incorrect.
- Let me answer.
- Try it with Jae Suk.
(Did they figure it out?)
- Here we go.
- Ready, set, go.
- Hey.
- Yes?
- I think I have a fever.
- How hot!
Your forehead is boiling up!
- What was that?
- "Your forehead is boiling up"?
- That sounds ridiculous.
- How hot!
- What was that?
- This isn't it.
- Your forehead is boiling up!
- Did you turn on the boiler?
- Come on.
Is it incorrect?
Come on, it's not a
commercial for a boiler.
Give me a break.
- "Your forehead is boiling up"?
- "Hey, I think I have a fever."
I will give you
the first thing the man says.
"Hey, I think I have a fever."
"Being sick..."
Let me answer.
"Being sick is the sign of youth."
(The upperclassman's
warm consolation)
Where did that come from?
"Being sick..."
"Makes you prettier."
"Being sick makes you prettier."
Let's go.
- Give it a go. Let me answer.
- Let me answer.
Hey,
I think I have a fever.
Being sick...
makes you prettier.
(Being sick makes you prettier.)
Is it correct?
I think it's correct.
(Will they succeed to get
two questions right in a row?)
- It's correct.
- I think it's correct.
"Being sick
makes you look prettier."
- We did it.
- My goodness.
- Our answer was very close.
(Team Suk Jin's answer is correct.)
That's good.
(The answer)
Hey,
I think I have a fever.
Of course, you need wits
to fall for those lies.
Being sick makes you look prettier.
I wish you luck.
That makes my heart flutter.
If we get one more question right,
we win.
- So Min, we are nearly there.
- We need to do this.
(Then Team So Min gets
2 questions right in a row!)
I am Dongwon.
- This is the final round.
- The final round.
We barely managed to catch up.
Let's go. We came this far.
- Let's get this right.
- I had nearly given up.
- This is the last question.
- We will win.
- Here it comes.
- This is the last question.
(Jang Na Ra, 18 years ago)
We're just friends.
I...
never loved you.
- I know this commercial!
- This is...
- Kim Jae Won.
- Jae Won.
I'm going to break you.
Oh, my.
Love is not...
(Love is not...)
"Love is not..."
"It's..."
That's the catchphrase.
Gosh, my memory is blurred.
Love is not a joke.
That's a song title.
- Love is not a joke
(Smiling)
Love is not furniture.
- It's science.
(They are ridiculous.)
It's a commercial
for a green plum drink.
You have the right approach.
- The drink is called Green Plum.
- Yes. Green Plum.
"Love is not green"?
Love is green.
Love is not yellow, it's green.
Love is not red, it's green.
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer. This is it.
They might get it right.
We're... We're just friends.
I never loved you.
I'm going to break you.
Okay.
That was good.
Love...
is not pink. It's green.
What?
(Love is not pink. It's green?)
Pink? Where did pink come from?
Try it.
The two of you should try it.
I think this is it.
- I think this is it.
- They might get it right.
- But...
- We're just friends.
I never loved you.
(Coldhearted)
(Splashing cold water)
(I am so upset!)
That's so cold. That's so cold.
I am sorry.
I shouldn't have messed with you.
I am sorry. You must be upset.
That's a comment
that would really anger So Min.
I'm going to break you.
- Narration.
- Female voice.
Love is...
not green.
It's a green plum.
(A green plum?)
No?
- My bad.
- It's okay.
(What's the answer?)
"Love is not green.
It's a green plum..."
sounds kind of immature.
This is it. This is it!
- Go for it.
- Let me answer.
- You be the woman.
- Be the woman.
- Go for it.
Go.
We're just friends.
I never loved you.
I'm going to break you.
(Flicking)
(Glancing)
(Why is he looking around?)
He's unbelievable. He looked at
himself after splashing the water.
(He's in the middle of an act,
but he still loves himself.)
(He splashes the water...)
(and scans himself.)
Did you see him?
He splashed the water.
He obviously splashed it on her,
- but he looked at himself.
- In case he got water on it.
That's sharp.
- I got goosebumps.
- My bad.
You're the worst.
I always think this is the worst
moment, and he surprises me.
(He's breaking his own record
for the worst moment for 10 years.)
Love is not a fantasy.
It's reality.
(Is he making a confession?)
- What was that?
- Wasn't that it?
That's when you sign divorce papers.
We thought of
"Love doesn't feed you."
Here's a hint.
Haha and Ji Hyo's first try...
- was very close.
- See?
I said so.
- Let me answer.
- Let's go.
We'll go.
(Get it right.)
- Do it.
- We'll go.
(He spots the water bottle.)
Okay.
I'll be Jang Na Ra.
What are you talking about?
- Why?
- What?
You're Jang Na Ra.
I mean... Am I?
I'm the woman.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins
and takes Jang Na Ra's part.)
He was late.
(Drinking)
Hurry up.
He has water in his mouth.
Are you going to do this?
(In a low voice)
This is not the last game.
We're just friends.
I never loved you.
(2 water strikes)
You got your face washed.
I'm going to break you.
Love is not pink.
It's green.
- It's wrong.
- Let me answer.
- No.
- Let's go for it.
I'm going to break you.
(Team Suk Jin's turn)
Pink is not the color of love.
- It's green.
- That's the answer.
(Are pink and green colors correct?)
- You were 99 percent correct.
- What?
Let me answer!
What is it?
(He's certain.)
This is the last time,
- so Jong Kook and I'll go.
- Okay.
Jong Kook.
(Are you going to challenge me?)
Good.
(He gets a new water bottle.)
Use the old water, punk!
(This country has a water shortage.)
I drank from it.
This is the last time.
- Is it me?
- Yes.
(This is the last question,
so I might as well...)
(Hold on.)
He loaded his gun.
Let's go. Ready, action.
(Water Sniper Kwang Soo is
fully loaded.)
(He's speechless.)
We're just friends.
I never loved you.
(This is a water bomb.)
(It turns into a trashy drama.)
(The water slap follows
the kimchi slap.)
This is improbable. Good ad-lib.
This is ad-lib.
(The male lead is mad
because this is improbable.)
(The female lead is unafraid
because this is the last question.)
What are you going to do now?
I understand why he's mad.
- I'll hit the other person.
- I understand.
- Me too.
Pink is not the color of love.
It's green.
- That's exactly what we said.
- That's what we said.
What was that? Let me answer.
- What was that?
- Isn't that what we said?
He's in deep trouble.
- Here's a hint.
- What was that?
"Love is not the pink..."
- Let me answer.
(We missed our chance.)
- Go, Jong Kook.
- Can we go?
What's he going to do?
- How many bullets do you need?
- Give me all of them.
What do you mean?
- The answer is important.
- Okay, good.
- You might forget the lines.
- Fine.
Let's go.
You'll get water on the cameras.
Move back.
Something will happen.
(He doesn't know where to look.)
Say your line.
(He's petrified.)
We're just friends.
(Trembling)
- Next.
- I...
(He predicted his fate.)
(It's a super muscle mist for
moisturizing the aged skin.)
I never... I never loved...
(Kwang Soo is becoming moisturized.)
I never loved... I never loved you.
(He's dripping tears or water.)
I'm going to break you.
Love is not the pink hue.
It's the green hue.
(Correct)
Good job.
- Good job.
- Okay!
I didn't think
my underwear would get wet.
We did it.
My underwear got wet.
(Answer video)
Love is no the pink hue.
It's the green hue.
Our team is amazing.
- That was too bad.
- We turned it around.
That was a drama without a script.
We have the final scores, but
there are 1 to 2 funny commercials.
- Let's watch them.
- Would you like to?
I'll give a prize badge
to the winning team.
That's good.
Queen, would you like to dance?
I remember this.
(Shim Eun Ha and Han Seok Kyu were
young stars 20 years ago.)
"Hello, I'm Han Seok Kyu."
If I'm a queen,
what are you?
I'm...
(Blank)
It's long.
That was so long.
It's so long. Why is it so long?
"I'm Dr. Romantic."
("I'm Dr. Romantic.")
"I'm Dr. Romantic 2."
Who's number two?
- Who's number 2?
- I'm number 3.
If I'm a queen, who are you?
I'm accompanying the queen
right now.
All right.
- "Accompanying"?
- We were right.
Haha got the answer,
so he gets a prize badge.
(Current Number of Prize Badges)
(Team So Min, Team Suk Jin)
As I promised,
So Min can choose a gift.
Really?
You can choose the meaningful gifts
brought by your team members...
or take a chance to win
a 100-inch TV...
that's worth 8,000 dollars.
Can I decide now?
(Will she choose the heartfelt gifts
from her team members?)
(Or will she be greedy
and go for the 100-inch TV?)
(What is So Min's decision?)
I'll try for the 8,000-dollar TV.
- Think about it.
- So Min.
- What are you doing?
- We have nice gifts.
There's nothing here
worth 8,000 dollars.
- I wouldn't hesitate.
- Why?
You might get a dud.
That's possible.
You'll get nothing.
- Rather than getting those,
- Is a dud better?
- I'd rather go for the TV.
- Go for it.
That's your style. I agree with you.
If I take this,
will you install it at my house?
(She's cute.)
(He's flustered.)
You don't need to install anything.
You just leave it there.
- You leave it.
- "Will you install it at my house?"
- So Min, please choose.
- Gosh, So Min.
I choose the TV.
Then switch spots with Ji Hyo.
Look towards it.
She might finish it.
I should have won!
If she wins the 100-inch TV,
everybody on this team
gets a prize badge.
- Everybody? All of us?
- Yes.
If she wins the TV,
you all get a prize badge.
I have a question.
What if both are duds?
- Jong Kook, can you check then?
- Okay.
You know what?
If I were you,
I would have done the same.
All right.
- Good.
- Jong Kook checked.
If I win the TV and cash it in...
(She's here to make a deal.)
She's trying to make a deal with me.
I'll give you 5,000 dollars.
5,000 for you, and 3,000 for me.
Go back immediately.
Everybody, let's vote.
Line up on either side.
Do I get something?
If I win the gift card,
- I will...
- Will you give us some?
It's 8,000 dollars, right?
I'll share 3,000 dollars.
Through a lottery.
That's if I win.
Please line up on either side.
I'm sure it's this one.
It's difficult when it's 3 on 3.
(She thinks hard.)
I...
You're giving us 3,000 dollars.
(Contemplating)
will go with my team's choice
and pick number one.
- Okay.
- They're too blue.
- So Min chose...
- Is she stupid?
number one.
I wish you luck.
- I think it's this side.
- Let me have some of it.
- Is this her final decision?
- This is her final decision.
One...
What will happen to the 100-inch TV?
(Instead of choosing
the members' gifts,)
One,
(she chose the TV.)
two,
(What's the result?)
three.
- What's that?
- Hey!
(Dud!)
Three.
- What's that?
- Hey!
What was that? What's wrong with me?
Did you not switch it around?
Did you not switch it?
- Did you not switch it?
- Jong Kook checked.
- Really?
- Was it like this earlier too?
And So Min,
we're the unlucky ones.
I was going to choose this side,
but they were all blue,
so I went for my team.
It's too early to give up
because you have to choose...
- the useless gifts.
- Take Ronaldo!
My billboard is pretty.
1, 2, 3.
- Suk Jin.
- The navigation device.
Use it when you go to the States.
You should use it
when you go to the States.
- This one.
- The navigation device.
Navigation of my life
I guess I'm unlucky this year.
Actually,
there was something...
that Suk Jin and So Min didn't
know about today's race.
(Something we didn't know?)
(Before the shooting)
- Hello.
Is this a show in a show?
- Se Chan, come over here.
- Hello.
So Min isn't here.
As you know,
two of the members aren't here.
Right.
Suk Jin isn't here too.
- Hey, why would you say that?
- I'm sorry.
- I didn't know.
- Right. Suk Jin isn't here.
We didn't know.
Today, we will have...
Double Celebration Race
to celebrate...
Suk Jin's birth
and So Min's book.
(Double Celebration Race)
But there's a secret
that the two captains don't know.
There will be no 100-inch TV
to win in the first place.
- I knew it.
- My gosh.
- I saw this coming.
- Really?
There's no TV?
All the choices are duds.
But if the captains
press their luck too hard,
whether they win games or not,
they won't get any prizes today.
That's good.
Actually, they both are greedy.
That's true.
If they don't choose
the gifts we prepared...
They will get nothing.
(If they don't choose the gifts from
the members, they will get nothing.)
(And So Min doesn't know
anything about it.)
(I want TV worth 8,000 dollars.)
(And the crew members switched
the prizes accordingly.)
(Jong Kook was in on it
with the crew too.)
We kept switching the places
behind the curtains.
Jeong Mi kept going
back and forth there.
Did you plan the whole thing?
So Min and Suk Jin were
the captains of today's race.
If they pressed their luck too hard,
their team members wouldn't
get any prizes.
And the members knew about it.
What?
Why did you not tell me about it?
We kept telling you to pick this.
I told you to pick this.
- I said that too.
- Right.
I...
You were blinded by 8,000 dollars.
I knew it when I saw her eyes.
She wouldn't listen to me anyway.
She seemed so greedy.
She would never listen to us.
We should've given up sooner.
Her eyes were full of greed.
You should've told...
What about you?
If you were me, you would've
made the same choice.
I would've been worse.
I'm so resentful
that I didn't get to open it.
Guys, I'm so sorry.
I'll be a nice person.
Let me announce the result
of today's race.
Those who didn't
win a single badge...
are Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
and Kwang Soo.
I didn't win a single badge.
They didn't lose the game,
but they didn't get a badge.
Can you let one of us
off the hook?
- I'll do that.
- Since it's my birthday.
- Let's make it 2 people.
- 2 people.
Okay.
The one who picks So Min's name
will be excluded.
All right.
Open it as I count to three.
(Who's the lucky one
to get excluded?)
(Kwang Soo and Suk Jin
will get the penalty.)
- My gosh.
- I picked it.
Gosh, Jong Kook picked her name.
- I got excluded.
- You picked it.
- My gosh.
- You're so lucky.
I didn't expect this.
You just got me a cake
to celebrate my birthday.
(He got a birthday cake
and the penalty.)
Let's do this.
1, 2, and 3.
My goodness.
(A salute to celebrate his birthday)
It's so red.
It's red today.
Kwang Soo got it just right.
Gosh, it looks so good.
You look cute.
It's so cute.
(Crowded and alienated)
Say something to Suk Jin.
Suk Jin doesn't look funny.
(Suk Jin doesn't look funny.)
(Funny and not funny)
Bye, Suk Jin.
My gosh.
Things are not going well in 2020.
(Good things will come
your way, Suk Jin.)
- You have no luck.
- I'm so unlucky.
- You don't look funny.
- It's not funny at all.
(Contestants of
Running Man Dance Challenge)
(Creaking dance, Kang Han Na)
(A humorous dancer, Heo Kyeong Hwan)
(The ambiance suddenly turns cold.)
(The clock is ticking differently
in their phones.)
(They should feed, lodge, and clothe
themselves in the circle of time.)
(Time is fair.)
(Time is unfair.)
(The same events repeat
for everyone.)
(Bad timing)
(The locked door of time)
(If you want to survive,)
(find the room of time
and steal time.)
(Success and failure will be
decided only in 10 minutes.)
(Join hands with someone
you can trust.)
(However...)
(There are time controllers
in yellow who are watching you.)
Is it over?
(Who's the one to get away
from the time circle?)
(Running Countdown)