(It is a sunny summer day.)
(There are 8 parking spots
with numbers.)
Kwang Soo's car has just arrived.
It's in number five.
Is it Kwang Soo's car?
Yes. It just pulled in.
Haha's car is coming in.
It's Haha's car.
(The members start to arrive
in their cars one by one.)
(Kwang Soo is the first one
to get off the car.)
(Looking around)
(As things feel a little different
than usual, he steps outside.)
Just a moment.
- Do you hear me?
- Put the microphone on him.
Okay.
- Has it started?
- Yes.
Has it started already?
Yes.
(It's still early, but I'm putting
on the microphone already?)
You will move
with this blindfold on.
Please put it on.
(Am I putting on the blindfold
as well as the microphone?)
- Just put it on.
- But...
Let's move now.
- Where...
- Follow me.
(Let's move now. Follow me.)
Some of the members
haven't arrived yet.
Let's move.
(Se Chan walks out of his car next.)
(Where is he going?)
Come here.
Where is he going? What's going on?
I know this place.
There's a coffee shop.
(Where is he heading
with the blindfold on?)
(Groaning)
Hang on.
I just broke my arm.
It's broken.
(Beeping)
It's an elevator, right?
(Did he hear some sound
from the elevator?)
I need to go to the restroom.
(Se Chan is being
taken away while whining.)
(So Min gets off her car too.)
(She also heads to somewhere
with a blindfold on.)
Are you being taken to somewhere?
- Hello, Haha.
- Where are you going?
I don't know. I'm being taken away.
Where are you taking her?
(All the members are taken somewhere
with a blindfold on...)
(as soon as they get off
from their cars.)
Where on earth are we going?
- What?
- What's the number?
Hang on. I'm getting in an elevator.
What's happening?
Kwang Soo.
(He gets in an elevator
without knowing why.)
Do you want me to get off?
(Kwang Soo reaches
the 5th floor alone.)
What?
It's the seventh floor.
What's going on?
(Se Chan is on the 6th floor.)
I guess we are on different floors.
(1st, 2nd, 3rd, 4th, 5th,
6th, 7th, and 8th floors)
(All the members have gotten
off at different floors.)
(Is there anyone around here?)
(So Min heads out to the stairs.)
Excuse me!
So Min?
Hey, Se Chan!
(- So Min?
- Hey, Se Chan!)
- Se Chan.
- What?
Which floor are you on?
Where are you?
Se Chan?
So Min recognizes
Se Chan's voice immediately.
I didn't even know who it was.
- Se Chan!
- Yes?
I'm wearing a skirt today.
What?
Okay. Good for you.
I look pretty today.
- What?
- I said I look pretty today.
(Laughing)
She says she's pretty.
Stop yelling if nothing's going on.
Pull yourselves together.
(Pull yourselves together.)
There might be people
like scarecrows again.
(1st, 2nd, 3rd, 4th, 5th,
6th, 7th, and 8th floors)
What's going on?
(Why are they waiting on different
floors without knowing the reason?)
Ji Hyo, you're on the eighth floor.
Please push the down button.
- I'm getting in.
- Okay.
(Ji Hyo pushes
the button carefully.)
- Take a look inside.
- My gosh.
What's that?
(There's something in the elevator.)
- Take a look inside.
- My gosh.
What's that?
"There are 80 R coins. Put as many
coins as you want in your bag."
(There are 80 R coins. Put as many
coins as you want in your bag.)
(The number of coins you take
will not be revealed.)
I can take as many coins as I want?
(It's Running Man Platform
from the movie, "The Platform")
Going down.
(The 8 members get 80 coins.)
(Each member will get as many coins
as they want from the top.)
(The fate of the members
on lower floors...)
(depends on the greed
of the members on higher floors.)
(I can take as many
as I want among the 80 coins?)
I should take them all then.
I should bring them all.
Why? Is there something?
(Ji Hyo wonders
what's behind it for a while.)
(Then she takes
as many coins as she wants.)
The doors are closing. Going down.
(The elevator goes down
to the 7th floor.)
(7th floor)
What's that?
What's all this? Shall I get in?
- Going down.
- Gosh, what is this?
"There are 80 R coins. Put as many
coins as you want in your bag."
There were 80 coins?
Does it go to the first floor?
There were 80 coins,
but this is all we have left?
9 and 10. Who was that?
Who took 60 coins?
Who's above there?
(Ji Hyo took 60 coins.)
Okay. I will take a bundle.
I'm being conscientious.
Seriously, I'm being
very conscientious with this.
The person on the eighth floor...
Okay. Good.
(Now it's Se Chan's turn
on the 6th floor.)
Shall we begin?
(He sounds determined.)
What?
What does it say?
How many coins
did they take from up there?
My gosh, they are so mean.
- Oh, dear.
- Going down.
(Ji Hyo is the first one
to arrive at the opening place.)
- Ji Hyo.
- It's So Min in a skirt.
Ji Hyo.
(Are you the one
from the 8th floor?)
Gosh, I can't believe this.
- What? Why?
- I mean...
They say a fair face
may hide a foul heart.
- You bragged about your skirt.
- Ji Hyo.
You were on the eighth floor, right?
- Me?
- You are from the eighth floor.
How can you be so sure
that there was no ninth floor?
There was no 9th floor.
You took 60 coins, didn't you?
60 coins?
Someone took 60 coins.
Were there 80 coins?
That's what the cue-card said.
It said 80 coins.
I didn't see it.
(The girl from the 8th floor
is unbelievable.)
I think Ji Hyo took the coins
without reading the card...
as soon as the door opened.
Hey, guys.
You should make things fun.
- Ji Hyo.
- You guys are so mean.
You should've left at least
20 coins to make things fun.
Se Chan, So Min says
she's wearing a skirt today.
Okay.
(Mindless)
She looks pretty today.
Okay.
(Are you still not interested?)
She says she looks pretty today.
- Hey.
- No.
You look pretty
only when you do something nice.
So Min says she's pretty today. See?
They don't look like flowers to me.
They look like R coins.
It shows the number
of R coins you took.
The number of R coins you have...
Just have me. You can have me.
Put me in your bag.
(She's bold.)
What are you doing
so early in the morning?
Gosh. They look like
R coins to me, So Min.
I don't know who's on the first
floor, but he will have a hard time.
- On the first floor?
- Yes.
What's that?
(Kwang Soo is on the 5th floor.)
Were there 80 coins?
There are only 5 left.
(He picks them up first.)
(Kwang Soo takes
all the 5 coins that are left.)
What's that?
"Put as many coins as you want
in your bag?" My gosh.
So Min was yelling earlier.
I'm sure So Min took them all.
Going down.
Darn it.
- Going down.
- There's nothing left.
What do you mean,
there are 80 R coins?
There's nothing here.
Why was I on the fifth floor?
Darn it.
It was decided
by our managers, right?
- Really?
- Isn't it the order we arrived?
- No.
- That's not it.
- Where the cars were parked...
- There were numbers.
On the ground?
The parking spots had numbers.
- Really?
(How was it decided
who goes to which floor?)
(This is where they parked
their cars this morning.)
(Each parking spot had a number.)
(Kwang Soo parked
in spot number five,)
(so he was sent to Floor 5.)
(Each member was placed
depending on their parking spot.)
Where's Chan Ho? Why did he park
the park in spot number seven?
- Where is he?
- It's a lucky number.
- That's right.
- You parked in spot number eight.
I shouldn't have thought much.
- I thought too much.
- Gosh.
Ji Hyo always benefits
from not thinking.
Here comes number 2.
He's from the 2nd floor
I guess Suk Jin is
on the first floor.
You're broke, right?
Did number seven take all the coins?
- No.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
- There were a few left.
This guy took everything.
Ji Hyo...
- No. Ji Hyo took about 20.
- What?
- Ji Hyo took 20.
- I think she took half of them.
They took 20 and 30 each,
and Se Chan...
left about five.
And Kwang Soo took five.
(Se Chan left about 5,
and Kwang Soo took 5.)
(100 percent correct)
That's accurate.
- Were you watching us?
- Jae Suk.
- Were you hiding in the elevator?
- Were you?
- Were you watching us?
- Right?
- I knew it.
- That was accurate.
I'm sure there were about five left.
Where's our old man, by the way?
There's nothing left for him anyway.
What if he collapsed on his way up?
Because he's exhausted?
"There are 80 R coins. Put as many
coins as you want in your bag."
"The number of coins you take
will not be revealed."
My goodness.
I'm getting greedy.
So where are the 80 R coins?
Where are they?
They used to be on the tray.
They've all been taken?
What should I do then?
I can't take anything?
(He finally understands.)
- Gosh.
- Gosh, I was so disappointed.
- Look at that.
- What's taking Suk Jin so long?
Did he get in a fight with
with a cameraman or something?
He might have grabbed the cameraman
by the collar.
- "Give me my coins!"
- Is he getting beaten up?
- He'd never hit anyone.
- But he'd get hit.
He might come out
with tissue in his nose.
"Hi, guys."
- That'd be hilarious.
- Did he get in a fight?
If he got in a fight...
I must be late.
What if the opening is over?
- Hi, Suk Jin.
- Hi.
He's alive.
- How could you take everything?
- That's not true.
Did you take everything?
Say the words clearly.
I considered parking
in spot number seven.
But I thought it was strange
that no one had taken it.
We have some good news.
("Yoo Jae Suk Wins
the Best Variety Performer Award")
("Lee Kwang Soo Wins
the Best Supporting Actor Award")
(Jae Suk and Kwang Soo won
awards from Baeksang Arts Awards.)
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Kwang Soo and Jae Suk.
- Did you two meet?
We sat next to each other,
but we were a little apart.
I'm sorry to say this,
but Kwang Soo...
Actually, the other nominees...
- were all amazing actors.
- Really?
- Who were they?
- The one from "Parasite"...
- You mean Choi Woo Shik?
- That's right.
They were all great actors.
After I received the award,
Jae Suk said, "Congratulations."
"But this might make people talk."
(The national host
made a careful prediction.)
He advised me to stay away
from my phone for a while.
(He advised me to stay away
from my phone for a while.)
You didn't expect Kwang Soo to win?
- I was hoping he would,
- Of course.
but when he actually did,
I was a bit surprised.
I looked at Jae Suk right away,
and he completely froze.
He wouldn't even look at me.
The other nominees were
all amazing actors too.
But Kwang Soo did a good job.
- He did. He did well.
- Of course.
Thank you.
He's always been a great actor.
He's never been bad.
- I saw that.
- Me too.
What is that?
- It's what Jong Kook posted.
- Gosh.
It's an indirect advertisement.
"I fell asleep after
a minute and 20 seconds."
When I saw his reaction...
As soon as I saw his fake reaction,
I dropped my phone.
You fell asleep?
- You dozed off.
- I'd watched for about a minute.
About a minute and 25 seconds.
Something I really want to achieve
this year is...
to finish watching
one of Suk Jin's videos.
Without falling asleep
or dropping my phone.
I never get to charge my phone
during the night.
That's so funny.
Are you satisfied with
the number of coins you have?
- I have nothing.
- What are you talking about?
We did a simple mission
before we start the race.
In today's race, you'll be sent to
different floors after each mission.
It's called Sharing Playbook.
After each mission, starting with
the person on the eighth floor,
you'll take as many coins
as you want.
Today, anyone can be penalized.
(Today, anyone can be penalized.)
Whoever fails to buy
an exemption card using the coins...
will be penalized
after the final race.
It must be expensive.
Let me show you the items
you can buy using your coins.
I'll buy it right away if I can.
I've always wanted a massage gun.
- It's really nice.
- The price will be revealed later.
You can buy
a penalty transfer card too?
- There's a transfer card.
- Really?
- I want a penalty transfer card.
- That sounds nice.
With it, you can transfer
your penalty within three months.
That sounds so tempting.
That's a good thing then.
- It's already started.
- We need many coins.
It's important to have
many coins today.
Each item's price will be
revealed after the final race.
Think carefully before distributing
coins among yourselves.
Please change and
go to the next mission spot.
- Okay.
- I don't have any coins.
It's possible that no one
gets penalized, right?
(Current Number of Coins)
What are those cardboard cutouts
doing here?
What's with the sandbag?
Jong Kook, there's a sandbag.
We probably have to choose a number.
What is this?
It looks like we'll have to
hang from the sandbag.
No, we'll use it
to break those boards.
We'll swing it to break
those boards.
- I think we'll hang from it.
- We'll swing it.
- We have to push it?
- Yes.
Don't you see
those Styrofoam boards?
Gosh, let's see who's right.
By the way,
how many is Suk Jin fighting with?
- He's like Sirasoni.
- He's...
"Bring it on!"
- It's okay.
- Seriously.
I feel alive
when people criticize me.
You can keep criticizing me.
This mission is all about
reading the others' minds.
It's called
Where is Running Man? Here.
- Here.
- It's Jong Kook's game.
- It's Kim Jong Kook Game.
- Here.
- It's cute.
You'll divide into 4 teams of 2.
The three defending teams...
will stand behind
one of the four doors.
Each member will wear a helmet...
worth 10, 20, 30, 40, 50,
and 100 points,
which will determine
the attacking team's score.
Also, behind
one of the four doors...
Do you see those cutouts?
Why do they have minus points?
You can place a cutout
worth minus 30 points.
So you brought them here
to smash them?
To throw them away?
They're hard to dispose of.
They look ridiculous.
- What did you do with your neck?
- What?
What did you do with your neck?
(Jae Suk can't understand.)
What did you do?
I just did this.
It's something he does all the time.
Each member of the attacking team...
will break a door
by swinging the sandbag.
The team's score will be
determined by the points...
on the members' helmets
or the cutout behind the door.
Each team's score will determine
its ranking,
and the one with a higher score
within each team...
goes to a higher floor.
- Okay.
- I'll take all the coins this time.
- Me too.
- You're all broke.
- I won't go easy this time.
- You have nothing.
- I won't go easy.
- We have to decide the teams?
- Yellow?
- Yellow.
- Green.
- Good.
Ji Hyo, we have to win first place.
- You're worth 10 points?
- I'm worth 10 points.
I'm worth 20 points.
I don't want to give them points.
I really don't want to.
In the first round,
we should all stand
behind the same door.
In the first round,
it's hard to guess.
- The chances are low.
- The chances...
- Right.
- Let's stick together.
Which one? Number one?
(As Suk Jin says, they will all
stand behind the same door.)
- Hurry up!
- We'll stand behind door three.
Let's place the cutout first.
In the worst case,
we'll choose the cutout.
Let's go for something
that you don't choose.
Okay.
- Something you don't choose.
- Okay.
(The cutout pops up.)
(Is that a mistake?)
(They're trying to confuse them.)
You know Ji Hyo doesn't
fall for such a trick, right?
- Forget about it.
- She's already made up her mind.
(Their strategy fails,
and they become flustered.)
(What do we do now?)
Let me tell you
where the cutout is.
(Again?)
- Here's the cutout.
(Kwang Soo pops up.)
Here's the cutout.
The cutout is behind
door number three.
That's not a cutout.
(The cutout is shocked.)
Okay.
(The real cutout is behind
door number 1.)
(They're deciding where to stand.)
Time's up.
Everything is ready.
You can't move anymore.
Please swing the sandbag now.
Just avoid the cutout.
You can go beyond the line.
Okay. Ji Hyo.
- One...
- Just a second.
- Number two.
- Hold on.
- You choose number 2?
- I choose number 2.
(That means Ji Hyo will
go for another number.)
Is Kwang Soo here?
(Panicking)
- Here?
- Good.
Throw it hard.
You choose number two?
Which number do you choose?
Number four?
(Ji Hyo chooses number 4.)
- Should I stand in front of it?
- Yes.
Yes, like that.
(No!)
(Haha covers his mouth.)
(If she breaks door number 4,
she gets 250 points.)
(It hits between the doors.)
(That was close.)
(Ji Hyo missed her target.)
- Ji Hyo!
- It's heavy.
You must have scared them.
It's so hard.
Which one are you aiming for?
- Number 3.
- 3?
(She switches over
to door number 3.)
(What a relief.)
Oh, gosh.
(Between 3 and 4)
- Where are you aiming at?
- Sorry.
- Ji Hyo, please.
- My aim is off.
(The board gets thumped
right in front of them.)
(It sheds years
off their life expectancy.)
(She would've got them if
her aim had been a little more off.)
You should swing it
from here instead.
Why is this so darn hard?
Ji Hyo, I want to
see them surprised.
(Which door will she
aim for this time?)
2, 3.
- Oh, no.
- Nice!
- Yes!
(No one's there.)
- You were behind number four?
- I thought so.
What did I tell you?
- I thought we were busted.
- That was so close.
Was the cutout
behind door number two?
- No, number one.
- You startled all of us.
- We should've chosen number four.
- Gosh.
- That was so close.
- Was that an option?
I chose door number four,
but it bounced off.
The aim was off,
and it went to number three.
Your bad aim
actually made us more anxious.
(It sent chills down their spine.)
You can't stand behind
door number three anymore.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
I'm not going to stall.
- Figure out where the cutout is.
- Sure.
I won't hesitate. Just watch.
(It's Jae Suk's turn
to fling the sandbag.)
(The cutout is placed
behind door 1 again.)
(Jae Suk suddenly goes somewhere.)
(Where is he going?)
(He tries to climb the set.)
(He's hoping to take a peek.)
(Peek-a-boo!)
(The director fails
to keep in his laughter.)
(Why is he suddenly laughing?)
(Haha senses
that something is wrong.)
Jae Suk.
(What are you doing?)
(His plan fails.)
- What?
Seriously?
- Jae Suk.
- What now?
- Seriously?
- As if I'd really take a peek.
- What's wrong with you?
- I was only joking.
You cheeky monkey.
Did you climb up there?
(The man of mischief
is hard to contain.)
I thought of that too, you know.
Hurry up then.
Unbelievable.
(It almost succeeded.)
How about number four?
(Like last time)
(They decide
to stand together again.)
Just follow your heart.
But I always make the wrong choice.
- Except that one.
- Right.
It could be number four again.
Four?
That could be their choice.
Let's play
rock-paper-scissors for it.
Which one?
(Which one will Kwang Soo choose?)
(Kwang Soo chooses number 1.)
(They'll stand behind door 1,
and the cutout will be behind 2.)
Four?
Choose one except four then.
- Okay.
- Choose one except door four.
- Except for door number four?
- Yes, because that's your choice.
- One out of the two then.
- Right.
(They'll choose between
door 1 and door 2.)
The choice has been made.
- But I'm feeling door number four.
- No.
(He has terrible hunches.)
(They try not to laugh.)
You saw what happened.
The cutout was close
to the door you chose.
Then I'll choose either
door 1 or door 2.
(Please choose door number 2.)
Door number two?
(He's the worst at choosing things.)
(The cutout is behind
door number 2.)
(Please choose door 2.)
Door number four?
- Door number 2.
- 2?
But door number two
doesn't feel right.
- Then door number one.
- Okay.
(Ji Hyo's hunches are always right.)
We'll stay away from the one
that I chose.
I'll choose number one
as Ji Hyo suggested.
Wait. Didn't you hear something?
When I said "number one,"
someone gasped.
Hold on a second.
I definitely heard it.
- I think we're right.
- It must be number one.
Someone definitely gasped.
I'm sure of it.
Could I have imagined that?
Let me do this then.
I'll go for door number one.
(Bingo!)
What?
My gosh.
- Goodness.
- What?
Who on earth gasped?
Who made the noise?
Who gasped earlier?
Who gasped?
I can't believe it.
- No way.
- That was incredible.
You were close
to choosing four though.
I wanted to choose four
more than anything.
- You win 250 points.
- How can you exclude number 4?
250 points?
- If it weren't for Ji Hyo...
- Unbelievable.
- How annoying.
- This is incredible.
Excluding what Jae Suk chose...
- worked.
- Exactly.
What a good guess.
(The Golden Hand is back.)
That was hilarious.
Why don't we stand
separately this time?
Right, sounds good.
We can't let them score
in the first round.
- We'll stand together first.
- Yes, in the first round.
We'll stand separately
in the next round.
Otherwise, we can't stop them
from coming out on top.
We need to stand together
in the first round.
I hope you make the right choice.
(Kwang Soo heads somewhere.)
(He goes up to the curtain...)
(and walks behind it.)
Where should I put the cutout?
You can tell us.
- The cutout?
- I'll put it where you want.
Where should I put the cutout?
Well...
(Movement)
I'll put it where you want.
Where should I put the cutout?
Who's that over there?
(Busted!)
Who's where?
It's one of the cameramen.
(Se Chan plays dumb.)
(She attacks the cameraman.)
- You...
- Get over here.
Get out.
- What are you trying to do?
- Why is he always like this?
How did you find out?
- Must you play dirty?
- What's wrong with you?
- He always messes things up.
- I almost saw it.
(I almost got a peek.)
(The cutout is placed
behind door number 2.)
They might see the shadow.
United we stand and divided we fall.
(Snap)
That came from door number two.
(She tries to throw them off.)
(That came from door number 2.)
Then I'm never choosing number two.
(I won't be fooled.)
That was either Suk Jin or Haha.
You have 10 seconds.
Are you done?
(Everyone playing defense
chooses number 3.)
Have you made up your minds?
Which one?
(Which number will
Kwang Soo choose?)
- Number 3. We choose number 3.
- Number 3.
(Number 3!)
(My gosh.)
Number three. Are you sure?
(They signal the staff.)
(Number 2?)
(Number 3?)
(They're trying to read the staff.)
(They want a hint from the staff.)
- Got it. So that's where you are.
- All right!
One...
(Instead of door number 3
where they all are,)
(he swings the sandbag
into the cutout.)
The cutout!
(His eyes widen.)
It was the cutout.
(Changing his choice
was the wrong move.)
Kwang Soo hit himself.
Are you kidding me?
You hit the cutout
of yourself instead.
You chose the wrong door.
I can't believe this happened.
- Do we get another chance?
- Okay.
Darn it.
You used Kwang Soo's cutout,
so only So Min's cutout is left.
- Can we still place one?
- Yes.
Yes, So Min's cutout.
Door number two
isn't an option now.
- Door 2 is out.
- It's either door 1, 3, or 4.
You're in last place
with minus 30 points.
Let's think about this.
(The cutout is placed
behind door 3 first.)
Guys, make your choices.
(You stand behind number 1.)
You can only choose between
door 1, 3, or 4.
(Only Jae Suk stands
behind door number 4.)
Your choice is final.
(They made their choices.)
- Which one?
- The cutout was behind door two.
They'll never guess that
we'd choose door two again.
- We can't.
- Number two isn't an option.
How stupid are you?
Did you just call me stupid?
You're no better than your cutout.
That's how idiotic you sounded.
Here we go. One,
two...
I bet you're nervous.
(They'll receive 150 points
if they choose door number 1.)
Here we go!
(They'll receive 100 points
if they choose door number 4.)
Let's do this!
(The sandbag knocks
the cutout of So Min.)
Let's do this!
- What?
- It was the cutout.
The cutout?
- You managed to find both.
- It was the cutout again.
It was the cutout again.
- Really?
- It was the cutout again.
See for yourself.
How can you choose it
twice in a row?
- Unbelievable.
- What are the odds?
You guys are incredible.
I'm amazed, guys.
- My gosh.
- How can this be?
- Do we have minus 60 points then?
- That's right.
So the results are out.
Jae Suk and Ji Hyo won the game.
Jae Suk who received 250 points
will head to the 8th floor.
(Jae Suk will be on the 8th floor.)
Ji Hyo gets to be on the seventh.
So Min will be on the sixth floor,
and Suk Jin will be on the fifth.
You'll now head
to your designated floors.
Unbelievable.
If only I was on the seventh floor.
- So Min.
- Yes?
- Can you leave me some?
- Have faith in me.
- I mean it.
- You can trust me.
The way we're positioned
leaves me no hope.
(He sees no hope.)
- Only a fool would be hopeful.
- Well, I am.
For the second time around,
you'll be sharing the coins.
Like last time,
there are a total of 80 coins.
The belt will travel
from the eighth floor...
and stop in front of you
for about 10 seconds.
I'm somewhat glad
that Ji Hyo's next.
I won't get greedy this time.
Leave me some!
Sure. I won't get greedy.
There's nothing here.
(Jae Suk received zero coins during
the first round of coin sharing.)
There's nothing here.
(No one knows
the exact price of the prizes.)
(Jae Suk is in a dilemma
over the coins.)
If Jae Suk only takes 10,
we'll follow suit.
- The belt will start moving now.
- Sure.
(Pondering)
Gosh.
(How many will he take?)
Jae Suk's not the selfish type.
Of course he isn't.
Which floor was he on
during the first round?
The second floor.
Is Jae Suk done already?
Already?
(Next up is Ji Hyo
on the 7th floor.)
(She flashes a smile
with mixed emotions.)
Didn't I leave you a decent amount?
Yes, you did.
- You already have a lot.
- Okay.
I won't get greedy this time.
I won't be greedy.
- My bag is already opened.
- Think long-term.
At least leave me a few.
Okay.
My bag is already opened.
Jae Suk, you're too much.
(Jae Suk, you're too much.)
(Jae Suk took 50.)
Ji Hyo, you are...
- Let's all live.
- Jae Suk.
You're too much. I will...
- Let's all live.
- Just know...
Just know today
will be full of twists.
- So Min.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
- Gosh, this is too much.
You and I were on the same team.
Goodness.
(She sweeps it in
without thinking about it.)
My goodness.
Seriously.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Hey, So Min.
(She leaves 5 according to
the number of remaining people.)
Jeon So Min, you are seriously...
Jae Suk, are you trying
to place the blame on me?
I was so surprised when I saw
how many were left.
How many did you take?
- Be conscientious, okay?
- My goodness.
- Be conscientious.
- Jeon So Min, you are seriously...
- Jae Suk.
I've opened up my bag.
(I wonder how many are left.)
I was surprised too.
I just took enough for me.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
- This is too much.
- Should I anticipate something?
(Peeking)
Is it Haha's turn now?
(I was a fool...)
(for anticipating something.)
I honestly believe I left enough
for everyone.
It doesn't even stop for me.
(The conveyor belt
doesn't even stop for me.)
My gosh.
(Drive-thru)
Goodness. So Min, I didn't think
you'd do that.
Why would it stop?
There's nothing there.
Just end it here.
Why are you making us see it?
Why would it stop
if there's nothing there?
You never know.
There's nothing to collect,
why would it stop?
(As expected.)
- Forget it.
- Why are we like this?
- Goodness.
- The second coin division is over.
- We'll move on to the next mission.
- Yes.
(Let's move on to the next mission.)
I'm not good at this game.
You have to choose the right seat.
Is this a team game?
They're balloons.
They must have different meanings
since they are in different colors.
This is hard. This is really hard.
If you don't acknowledge
the truth about you,
the balloon above your head
will get thinner.
This game is called
I Saw Running Man.
"I Saw Running Man"?
It's a play on the movie,
"I Saw The Devil".
A few weeks ago,
we asked our viewers...
to share stories if they saw,
encountered,
or heard of the Running Man members.
- Right, it was aired.
- I saw it too.
We received a lot of stories
through emails...
- and Instagram DMs.
- Did you receive a lot?
- Yes.
Is it okay to do that
without confirming if it's true?
You will be confirming if it's true
through this segment.
- Can we can deny it if it's false?
- Okay.
(There were thousands of stories
that were submitted.)
(Among them, 99 percent were
moving stories about the members.)
(We have swallowed our tears
and taken them out.)
We've also taken out the ones
that can't be aired.
Don't watch today's episode!
This is... Hold on. How can...
I'm sure you've taken out
all the moving stories.
There were so many moving stories
that we've taken them out.
- Right. I was sure you did.
- You should've kept them in.
- You have to include them.
- I'm sure I have a lot.
I'm an expert of moving stories.
In comparison to what I do, there
aren't many moving stories about me.
Who had the least amount of
moving stories?
- Who had the most negative stories?
- Who didn't have moving stories?
Yang Se Chan and Haha had the least
number of moving stories.
Goodness.
They are good at keeping secrets.
- You're all loyal.
- Like "The King with Donkey Ears".
They're all loyal.
- I have a lot of moving stories.
- I have a lot too.
So we are...
going to give each member the files
containing the members' stories...
excluding their own.
You can choose whichever story
you'd like about Jae Suk.
- Okay.
- After they read it,
according to the number of stories
you can't admit to,
the layers of the balloon will be
removed.
- Goodness.
- After everyone has gone,
the layers will be removed,
and the person...
whose balloon pops first
will come in last place.
- If you deny it, you lose a layer.
- You can admit to everything then.
You can admit it.
- But they could be false.
- That's right.
You can admit it
despite it being false.
You have to clarify
the false ones though.
(Looking)
(Fiddling)
Suk Jin seems really nervous.
- Why are you fiddling?
- Suk Jin seems really nervous.
(Suk Jin seems very nervous
about this corner.)
- He keeps playing with his hands.
- He seems very nervous.
- Goodness.
- Once you take a look,
you'll find that some of them
are very old.
- Really?
- So they may be false.
You can hand out the files...
- to everyone.
- Honestly,
we don't know if it's true or false.
- We might not be aware of it.
- Right.
We might not remember.
- Gosh, this is...
- There are a lot.
- Jae Suk's...
- Goodness.
- There are some about dating.
You can't deny this.
Aren't Jae Suk's stories
too detailed?
Why?
- Why?
- Oh, my gosh!
Is it okay to start it like this?
You said you filtered them,
but you didn't filter this one?
Yoo Jae Suk, out!
(Jae Suk's stories
are interesting.)
Jae Suk,
your stories are incredible.
- Kyung Eun!
- Why?
Don't watch today's episode!
Gosh, this is... Hold on.
- This is really intense.
- Should I read it?
- It was during high school.
- Reading this,
I'm worried about our stories.
- I know. This is quite intense.
- Gosh, this is...
Okay, everyone.
Take a look at Jae Suk's file,
and whoever wants to start
can read one of them aloud.
- Goodness.
- This is really intense.
These are really detailed.
- Stop exclaiming and read one.
- They're really detailed.
I will read one aloud.
"Hello. I'm Park Hyung Man,
and I live in Washington D.C."
Do you know someone by the name of
Park Hyung Man?
- Hyung Man is my close friend.
- Do you know him?
- Really?
- This one is true!
- This is undeniable!
- The real deal is here!
- Hyung Man is my friend.
This is true?
(Does that mean this is true?)
"I'm sure Jae Suk will know
who I am after hearing my name."
- Yes.
- He knows who you are.
He was a good friend of mine
when we were in high school.
"The story I will share with you..."
- "is about..."
- Please continue.
"where Jae Suk had his first kiss."
(This story is about where
Yoo Jae Suk had his first kiss.)
- My first kiss?
- I've never heard this story.
- How does he know?
- Oh, my.
Jae Suk needs to take his family
out for dinner this weekend.
- "It was..."
- It's really detailed.
"sometime between the spring
and summer of our senior year."
- Right.
- Keep that in mind.
"The location was..."
"on a secluded overpass
in Sadang-dong."
Do you remember?
Please continue.
On a secluded overpass
in Sadang-dong.
Please continue.
- He must've gone there often.
- But...
He wasn't there. How does he know?
He must've been hiding
and watching you.
"I remember how he told us
at the school store the next day."
(I remember how he told us
at the school store the next day.)
Goodness, this is fun.
(Goodness, this is fun.)
(His robotic reactions are in full
swing at his friend's disclosure.)
He told his friends about
his first kiss.
He has lost his mind.
He has gone insane.
Are you really my friend?
It's really his friend.
- "One more thing."
- Okay.
"In high school, after breaking up
with his girlfriend."
"He gave me the photographs, gifts,
and letters he received from her..."
"and asked me..."
(He gave me the photographs, gifts,
and letters he received from her.)
"to get rid of them for him."
I did?
- Jae Suk did that?
- How lame.
How lame.
He asked him to get rid of them.
I don't remember the latter half
of the story.
"For your information,
this girl was not his first kiss."
(For your information,
this girl was not his first kiss.)
- This is a lie.
- He's a player.
- This is true.
- Did he date that many girls?
- What?
- This sounds like a lie.
He was a good friend of mine.
- Goodness.
- He also said this.
"I enjoy your show and have watched
every episode while in the US."
"I hope you continue to make
a fun and original..."
Are you kidding me?
"I hope that you continue to give
joy to viewers like me,"
"who are abroad and wait for your
show every week, for a long time."
Goodness. Hyung Man.
Hyung Man.
Let's give him a round of applause.
Thank you, Hyung Man.
Hyung Man is a good friend of mine.
It is true I had my first kiss
on an overpass.
- Really?
All the details aren't correct,
but the kiss is true.
- How cool.
- I admit it.
- Can I read this one?
- Which one?
- Go ahead.
- Is it okay?
- I will read this one.
- Okay.
Okay. Gosh, this is...
"Confident Yoo Jae Suk,
Whom I Met at a Sauna".
(Title: "Confident Yoo Jae Suk,
Whom I Met at a Sauna")
(The title is already interesting.)
I will read this while standing.
"Confident Yoo Jae Suk,
Whom I Met at a Sauna".
- I'm dumbfounded.
- Let's find out if this is true.
- I don't know who it is, but...
- The title is funny.
"About a year ago, I was hanging out
at the R Hotel sauna in Sinsa-dong."
That's where Jae Suk goes.
"There was a commotion inside
the sauna, so I went in."
"I saw that
Jae Suk and Suk Jin..."
That's right. I went with Suk Jin.
- We went together.
- "came to the sauna."
It's true. I went with Suk Jin.
"Despite the many eyes looking
at them,"
"they calmly undressed
and entered the sauna."
"Their preferences
were the exact opposite."
("Their preferences
were the exact opposite.")
This is the truth.
This is the funny part.
"Suk Jin seemed a bit embarrassed
and covered himself with a towel..."
"and entered with his bottom
sticking out."
"Whereas, Jae Suk did not cover up
and entered confidently."
Okay.
- "Furthermore..."
- That's all a lie!
- "Furthermore,"
- What are you saying?
"he wore his glasses,
so everyone could recognize him."
Everyone could tell
he was Yoo Jae Suk.
"I respect your confidence,
Jae Suk."
- Thank you.
- Is this true?
(Yoo Jae Suk, the man who
is confident in the sauna.)
Thank you. Although
I don't know you personally.
- We went there.
- I remember.
I went with Suk Jin.
- We went to the R Hotel once.
- Right.
It's right next to Suk Jin's home.
- Yes. Suk Jin wanted to go.
- It's right next door.
Is this true? Do you admit it?
- I admit this.
- Do you?
- I went there about a year ago.
- Really?
- I went with Suk Jin.
- Yes.
- It's true?
- It's right next to my home.
Next,
we'll read Kwang Soo's stories.
- Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- He has a lot of stories.
Should we read Kim Ju Hyun's story?
- Kim Ju Yeon?
- Kim Ju Hyun.
"Hello. I am studying to become an
anchor at B Academy in Sinsa-dong."
"On March 23 at around 6 p.m.,"
"I got on the elevator after class."
"Surprisingly, Kwang Soo was inside
the elevator."
Goodness.
"He's a superstar, so I couldn't
say hello to him and got in."
- Goodness.
- "At that time,"
"Kwang Soo had hurt his leg, so I
thought he was there for a checkup."
- It wasn't too long ago.
- It was when you hurt your leg.
"But there is only a plastic surgeon
and a hair loss clinic there."
(But there is only a plastic surgeon
and a hair loss clinic there.)
(Kwang Soo went to a plastic surgeon
or a hair loss clinic.)
Where did Kwang Soo go that day?
He must be losing a lot of hair
these days.
Is it plastic surgery or hair loss?
- What is this?
- Plastic surgery or hair loss?
- It's neither.
- Where is it?
- What is this?
You can go to those places.
- I can go, but I didn't.
- You can go.
I don't have hair loss.
- You can go, if needed.
- At some point,
he got thick and luxuriant hair...
- on the back of his head.
- He got more hair.
Are you saying I got a lot
of back hair after a treatment?
So I thought he had
some back hair implanted.
Why would I do that?
You usually implant back hair
on the top of your head.
I thought he implanted the top hair
on the back of his head.
- I guess this is what happened.
- What?
Maybe that's when I went
to Jong Myung's clinic.
- My brother's clinic?
- Yes.
I got treatment for this.
That's true. The building of
Jong Myung's clinic...
has an announcer academy.
- That's true.
- That's what it is.
Okay. I admit it.
That's where I went.
There's a hair loss clinic too.
- So Ju Hyun told us the truth.
- That's right.
- It's true.
- It is true.
- This is really funny.
- Go ahead and read it.
"I worked at the A club
in Sinsa-dong..."
"as a server of the VIP Zone
a few years ago."
- Don't be nervous, Kwang Soo.
- It's so detailed.
- Kwang Soo, don't worry.
- That's not true.
I don't know what it is,
but it's not true.
- Kwang Soo, don't be nervous.
- It's a detailed story.
- What does he know about me?
- No. It's okay, Kwang Soo.
This is really fun.
Kwang Soo, we don't have anything
that can't be aired on TV.
- Don't worry.
- Are you sure?
- Just listen.
- It will be okay.
"Kwang Soo came
to the club by himself."
To the club?
- Really?
- To a club?
- Flex.
- He went to a club alone?
"I was in charge of his table,
so I was waiting for him to order."
"Then he suddenly asked..."
- "how old I was."
- What? That's so rude.
- Did I...
- He suddenly asked it.
"I was a little flustered,
but I told him that I was 29."
"Kwang Soo said, 'I see.'"
"Then he started to dance around
all by himself."
- That's ridiculous.
- Why?
- It doesn't make sense.
- What was that?
- "How old are you?"
- Go ahead and dance.
What's that?
- What were you doing?
- Can you believe that?
- What were you up to?
- It doesn't make sense.
Why did you ask him about his age
and started to dance?
Did you not go there alone?
Who did you go with?
I once went to a club with you.
- And I went there with Haha.
- When did I do that?
You were...
- When did I go?
- What is he talking about?
- I didn't go to a club with you.
- Look at Suk Jin.
Why are you feeling nervous?
He seems very nervous.
Why did Suk Jin get nervous
after you brought it up?
(Suk Jin is feeling ill at ease.)
- What did you do?
- That's not true.
- Do you not admit it?
- I don't.
Okay.
It will get thinner then.
This one sounds arrogant.
Let me read this story.
She went to Hongdae
when she was the sixth grader.
And she saw
a tall guy in a red cap...
- walking towards her.
- He does wear a red cap a lot.
- That's what he often wears.
- It must be a true story.
"I wondered who it was,
and it was Kwang Soo."
"As he walked past me, I said this."
"Gosh, it's Lee Kwang Soo."
"Then he looked at me..."
- "and winked at me."
- How could you...
You're just ridiculous.
- He thinks he's a big celebrity.
- Hey.
- He's so sick.
- You're unbelievable.
I admit the previous one,
and I don't admit this one.
- This isn't true.
- Why did he wink at her?
Only huge stars wink at fans.
- I rarely wink at all.
- He winked?
- I saw him wink.
- Why would you wink?
- I saw him wink before.
- He does.
He was eating at Haha's restaurant.
When some customers
recognized him, he suddenly...
(He winked at the customers.)
- I don't usually wink.
- I saw that too.
We were shooting Running Man.
We've done a lot of stuff with mud
at mudflats.
After he took a shower,
he looked into a mirror.
And he...
- What are you talking about?
- I was so shocked.
That's absurd.
I don't usually wink at all.
I winked at an elementary
school kid on the street?
- You'd do that.
- You're really...
I thought it was true
when I heard about a red cap,
but I don't admit it.
Gosh, I'm so upset.
Shall we move on to Jong Kook?
- Gosh, this is...
- Read it for us.
A lot of stories about Jong Kook...
- are from L.A.
- They all are from L.A.
Stories from L.A.?
There are a lot
of stories about L.A.
Hang on.
- My gosh.
- Isn't that true?
Let's hear it.
Can I read this story from L.A.?
"I'm a college student
who lives in L.A., California. "
"One day, I went downtown
and saw Jong Kook there."
"He was wearing black pants, a black
shirt, black mask, and black cap."
- "His whole body was covered,"
- I don't dress like that in L.A.
- "but I could tell it was him."
- I will hear it anyway.
"I was excited to see a Korean
celebrity in a foreign country,"
"so I went to get his autograph."
"But there was a woman
who looked like a Korean American."
"She was coming out of a cafe
with some coffee."
- Listen.
- What are you talking about?
- All right.
- Okay.
- Go ahead and read it.
- He has a girl in L.A.
- "Jong Kook got..."
- Okay.
- "a coffee from her casually."
- And?
"Then he went his way with her."
"So I couldn't talk to him."
"The woman who looked fabulous."
"She's your girlfriend, isn't she?"
- This one is good.
- We have to check the fact.
- She looked like a Korean American.
- I'm telling you the truth.
There are a lot
of photos of you in L.A.
You see?
- Are there photos?
- Photos?
- There are a lot.
- We have photos.
- Are there photos?
- We have to reveal the truth.
Did you walk around the streets
dressed like this?
This is a long time ago.
I was a member of Turbo.
I guess there were times
when I traveled around with women.
I won't deny it.
- Did you get a coffee from a woman?
- But it's not like...
I was alone
with a Korean American woman.
Did you ever get a coffee
from a woman or not?
- From a beautiful woman.
- A Korean American.
There must've been a time
when I got coffee from a woman.
That's not what I'm talking about.
That's enough!
- Just admit it.
- Do you admit it or not?
Are you from the National
Intelligence Service or what?
- Just tell us.
- What?
I might have gotten some coffee.
- You can't say that.
- That's not right.
What more do you want?
- I don't admit it's true.
- Just tell us the truth.
I don't admit it.
Is your girlfriend
a Korean American or not?
Do you have
a girlfriend in L.A. or not?
I can have
some acquaintances in L.A.
Okay. I admit it.
- It's done.
- It doesn't matter.
There's another story about L.A.
We have a lot of stories from L.A.
"I'm a college
student living in L.A."
There are a lot of college students.
"I miss you, Dad."
Is she his daughter?
- Do you admit it or not?
- What?
Do you admit it or not?
Is my child a college student?
- When did I get married?
- Do you admit it?
- "Dad."
"I miss you, Dad." It says.
Why do you miss me?
We met last week.
- Do you admit it?
- I went there last year.
Listen, Jong Kook.
I'm 100 percent sure this story
about Jong Kook is true.
- What?
- This is...
- What is it now?
- This is how he talks. Listen.
"I'm from Anyang. I've heard a lot
about Jong Kook since I was a kid."
"In 2006, my friend walked by and
saw Jong Kook shooting a TV show."
"He got excited and said,
'What? There's Kim Jong Kook.'"
"And Jong Kook said this."
"Am I your friend or something?"
(Jong Kook said,
"Am I your friend or something?")
- I'm sure it's true.
- You have to admit it.
- It's true, isn't it?
- It must be true.
- It's true, right?
- I'm sure.
- It sounds just like you.
- That's the way he talks.
- Is it true?
- If a young kid...
- Do you admit?
- said such a thing to me...
- in 2006,
- It must be true.
- it must be true.
- You see?
"Am I your friend or something?"
While we talk about Jong Kook,
I read stories about So Min.
- All the stories are about men.
- Really?
- So Min's stories are unbelievable.
- What do they say?
- So Min is...
They all say that she was with men.
Let me read one.
What? That can't be true.
So Min is...
I see. I have a lot of male friends.
- I know.
- I have many friends.
"So Min Doesn't Seem
Like a Celebrity".
- That's the title.
- Let's hear it.
"I saw So Min at a cafe
in Yongridan-gil last winter."
"She was with a guy."
(She was with a guy.)
"When a female celebrity is
out with a guy,"
- "she would wear a mask."
- Last winter?
"But So Min revealed her face..."
"while the guy covered his face."
(Now she covers her face.)
- Who was he?
- Gosh, this is...
- Gosh, So Min.
- I can feel...
the temperature difference already.
So who was the guy
who was covering with his face?
- I can feel the difference already.
- I know.
- Who was he?
- It was last winter. Who was he?
I guess it was
one of my male friends.
All right, then.
Do you go to a cafe a lot
with a male friend?
- I admit it.
- Do you?
- Yes, I admit it.
- She admits it.
Can I read this one?
- Go ahead, Ji Hyo.
- This is...
The story was about Yongsan.
- It says about Yongsan again.
- Is it Yongsan again?
"Two years ago,"
"I saw So Min
at a corner of a street..."
- "behind an apartment in Yongsan."
- This is crazy.
- "She was wearing a cap..."
- I'm so nervous.
"pulled down low,
so I didn't recognize her at first."
"But she was talking loudly on the
phone, so I recognized her voice."
- "And she sounded quite serious."
- What happened?
"I'm not sure,"
"but I guess she was fighting
with her boyfriend."
"That's what she sounded like."
- "Unlike her serious voice..."
- Hang on.
Hang on.
I will...
admit it without hearing the story.
(I will admit it
without hearing the story.)
(I can tell it's my story
without hearing it.)
We have to finish the story.
- No.
- So Min, this is...
- So Min, just listen.
- Let's hear it.
- You should hear it.
- No.
- I don't have to. I admit it.
- Ji Hyo, continue.
Read it calmly.
"Unlike her serious voice,"
"it was just a childish
lover's quarrel."
- It's no big deal.
- And she heard it.
"'Who should I hang out with then?'"
"'I want you to hang out with me.'
That's what she said."
- It sounds like So Min.
- "Who should I hang out with then?"
"I just walked by
trying to keep a straight face."
- "Are you still seeing him?"
- Who is it?
- So Min.
- But So Min's story is...
I broke up with the guy
two years ago.
- Really?
- We broke up two years ago.
I admit it. He was my boyfriend.
- Okay.
- "In 2013."
Haha.
Is there more?
"I went to watch a musical one day."
Do you admit it?
I won't read it anymore.
I dated all of them secretly.
How did they see me?
This is crazy.
You were sitting next to her.
(She's Love Frog from Yongsan
who can't hide her love.)
- Everyone knows it except you.
- She saw you there.
(There are a lot
of detailed stories.)
How many of my old boyfriends
are they going to mention?
There have been three already.
It was 2014. Do you admit it?
It was a musical.
A musical.
I'll admit it
without hearing the story.
(She admits it without
hearing the story again.)
You should read it.
Let's move on to Haha.
"I live in the same apartment
complex as Haha."
(A report from someone who lives
in Haha's apartment complex)
"Late at night, I saw Haha
get carried on his friend's back..."
"in a drunken state."
Admit it. Admit it.
"The next morning, I saw Haha
send Dream off to the kindergarten."
"Byul must have scolded him since
he couldn't stand next to her."
"He trailed behind her
like a puppy in the rain."
I have seen him like that.
- This is a beautiful story.
- I have seen him like that.
That's right.
(I am sorry.)
Do you admit it or not?
I admit it.
- Let's move on to Suk Jin.
- Okay.
I will read this one.
It seems like a good one.
"This happened at a duty-free shop."
"The Running Man members
were going abroad that day."
"'It's Yun Jae Suk!
I have never seen him before!'"
"The crowd went wild."
"I also took photos of Jae Suk
with my phone."
"But when I studied
the photos later, I realized..."
"that the man next to Jae Suk
wasn't a manager but Suk Jin."
"He cleared the way for Jae Suk.
I want to apologize."
Did you clear the way for Jae Suk?
- I cleared the way?
- Yes.
I cleared the way for Jae Suk?
It's belated, but thank you.
- I never did that!
- This is a heartwarming story.
Thank you, Jae Suk.
I simply went my way.
You should admit it...
because we saw this happen
many times.
- I cleared the way for Jae Suk?
- Of course. Don't you know?
- You...
- I simply went my way.
You always do this.
- You do this.
- That's how you clear the way.
Suk Jin, you walk like this.
- Admit it.
- Hey!
- Don't be ridiculous.
- There are so many photos.
I don't do that. I walk confidently.
Suk Jin, you should hold
your head up high.
What are you talking about?
I don't admit it.
- It makes Jae Suk uncomfortable.
- What are you talking about?
- I don't do that.
- Stop making him uncomfortable.
I don't admit it.
- Shall we read a report on Se Chan?
- Okay.
Se Chan's story.
- "I saw Se Chan at the dentist's."
- This one. That's it.
"Se Chan exited the dentist's
by saying, 'See you next time.'"
"But the dentist's I go to
specializes in teeth straightening."
"I couldn't ask the dentist, but..."
"Se Chan, are you getting
your teeth straightened?"
"Your teeth make me wonder
if I should find another dentist."
He got his teeth straightened.
Did you get your teeth straightened?
- But...
- I got my teeth straightened.
We should send this person
a present.
- Goodness.
- He got his teeth straightened.
- It's so funny.
- It's a fact.
- I was so surprised to find out.
- It's so funny.
He got his teeth straightened.
Did you look like a woodpecker
at first?
- No, I didn't.
- What happened?
My teeth used to protrude more.
- Really?
- I get this person's concern.
That dentist's office
specializes in teeth straightening.
I recommend you to go there.
- You didn't get it done, did you?
- What do you mean?
- Teeth straightening.
- No, I didn't.
Who gets his teeth straightened
like this?
Who gets his front teeth twisted
If he had gotten
his teeth straightened,
I wouldn't have let that dentist be.
- I would've exploded.
- Who gets...
his front teeth twisted like this?
- I would have destroyed him.
- I guess your teeth are straight.
- You got them straightened.
- Yes.
- I will read a short account.
- Okay.
"I am a member
of an amateur soccer team."
"One day, the team had a match
against Jong Kook's team."
"The match started at 10 p.m."
"When I arrived early
and went to the restroom,"
"Se Chan was talking on the phone."
"I couldn't help but overhear
what he was saying."
"I guess he had agreed to drink
with his friend..."
"because he said he will leave
after the first half."
Hold it right there!
(He said he will leave
after the first half.)
(Did he try to escape
after the first half?)
Who sent that account?
That's not true. I never did that.
Jong Kook, when did I ever leave
after the first half?
I always play soccer
until the very end...
and go home at 1 a.m.
- You did leave early once.
- I never did it in order to drink.
Never. This person is absurd!
I never said that on the phone.
It's a blatant lie.
- I don't admit it.
- But it happened.
- No.
- You did leave early once.
I never did that.
It's a misunderstanding.
- I don't admit it.
- It's Ji Hyo's turn.
- You should admit it.
- I don't admit it.
Let's read an account on Ji Hyo.
"I am Ji Hyo's fan
who lives in Yeosu,"
"Kim Kwang Seong."
- Do you know him?
- Yes, I do.
- You know him.
- Yes.
- Really?
"I always attend
Ji Hyo's fan-signing event."
"Ji Hyo always recognizes me
and greets me warmly."
"She would ask,
'Did you come from Wando?'"
"Then I would say,
'No, I came from Yeosu.'"
(No, I came from Yeosu.)
(It's definitely a true story.)
It suits her.
- That's so funny.
- She is unbelievable.
(She can't dispute it.)
- "At the next fan-signing event,"
- She is unbelievable.
"she recognized me and greeted me."
"Did you come from Geoje Island?"
- She is unbelievable.
- "I told her again..."
- "that I came from Yeosu."
- She is unbelievable.
"At the next fan-signing event,"
"she asked me if I came from Jindo."
At least she knows Jindo.
- The places are near Yeosu.
- Seriously.
She shocked me
at a fan-signing event in Hong Kong.
She said, "I love Malaysia!"
She didn't know where she was...
- or what she was doing.
- That's right.
That's right.
It's an account that suits Ji Hyo.
Do you admit it?
Yes, I do.
That's so funny.
I will read one. The title is,
"Ji Hyo Doesn't Call Back".
It's a well-known fact.
"A few years ago,
I worked as a staff member..."
"for a movie Ji Hyo starred in."
"Ji Hyo and a few staff members
were drinking..."
"when her phone rang."
"It vibrated for a while,
but Ji Hyo didn't answer..."
"and I glanced over at the screen."
"The caller was Suk Jin."
(The phone vibrated for a while.)
(Ji Hyo's secret is revealed.)
Hey!
You...
- It was purposeful.
- That's too mean.
How could you screen my call
like that?
Seriously.
"She didn't answer until the end.
Did Ji Hyo call him back that day?"
She hasn't called him back yet.
She hasn't called me back yet.
There are a lot of funny accounts.
I must have done that
because I was having fun...
and wanted
to call Suk Jin back later.
You mean Suk Jin isn't
as interesting as drinking.
- It's not like that.
- It is like that.
- I mean...
- You didn't want to talk to him.
It's not like that.
I don't think I have ever done that.
Do you admit it or not?
I admit it.
It's understandable.
In accordance
with the number of "I don't admit",
we will subtract from 10 layers...
and hang up the balloons.
Hang up the balloons.
- I admitted to every account.
- I didn't expect...
Hyung Man to send an account.
We will start from So Min and go
in Haha's direction.
My order is the best.
Jong Kook's order is the best.
All right. I will do it lightly.
I am bad at this.
- I will do it lightly.
- So Min is bold.
(What will be the result
of So Min's bold touch?)
So Min is bold.
(It bursts in one go!)
- You poked it with too much force.
- That startled me.
Didn't you do better the last time?
What was that?
- You made it burst in one go.
- You dug in the blade.
I slashed it gently.
I slashed it very gently.
- So Min, you take the eighth place.
- You dug in the blade.
- I hope everyone's balloon bursts.
- I know.
I slashed it very gently.
I think the layers are thin.
The surface is very tight.
Are you sure there are 10 layers?
What are you doing in the air?
(The layers come off instantly.)
He survived.
- He survived.
- One more layer.
(One more layer
comes off belatedly!)
One more layer.
(It's nerve-wracking.)
It's barely hanging.
It will burst the next time.
Suk Jin.
Burst. Burst.
- Burst.
- Bye.
That's too gentle.
- Gosh, this is...
- There should be a time limit.
(It bursts!)
See?
You should have stopped
after the first scratch.
- You went further.
- Seriously.
This is cutthroat.
- It's so scary.
- It dropped here.
- Next.
- Here I go.
I got completely wet.
This is nerve-wracking.
The surface is taut.
It's very taut.
Is the blade touching?
The blade isn't doing anything.
You should slash it like a man.
(Slashing)
- Okay!
- What was that?
- He removed 1 layer.
- 1 layer.
- How did you do so well?
- Okay.
- Did he remove one layer?
- How did he do so well?
I got the hang of it.
You need to use the tip.
(Ji Hyo gives it a go
after a tip from Se Chan.)
That's right. Use the tip.
I thought she would make it burst
in one go.
I am scared.
Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- You are slashing the air.
I am scratching it.
(It shows no sign of tearing.)
What was that?
Did it work?
(Coming off)
- What was that?
- It worked.
- How did she do that?
- Is someone controlling it?
- What did you do?
- Was it magic?
- One layer suddenly came off.
- Seriously.
It suddenly came off.
- I did it.
- You must have done it delicately.
- Jae Suk.
- Go ahead.
(Jae Suk gives it a try.)
- This isn't easy.
- This really isn't easy.
Jae Suk wouldn't be able
to succeed.
I am really bad at things like this.
Jae Suk, I will give you
two coins...
- if you let me slash it.
- There you go.
Why does his mouth do that
when he concentrates?
Look at his mouth.
He looks like
he is kissing on the overpass.
(He looks like
he is kissing on the underpass.)
Come on.
- The first kiss?
- For goodness' sake.
Don't bring that up.
(He slashes the balloon carefully.)
That's...
I can't do it.
I am too scared.
I bet he had
his first kiss like that.
(I bet he had
his first kiss like that.)
- "I am too scared."
He would have pulled back.
"What should I do?"
"I am too scared."
I don't want to think about that.
What are you doing?
"I can't do it."
(Look into that memory and do it.)
- 5, 4, 3...
- Jae Suk.
Do it confidently.
You are a confident man.
- Okay.
- You are a confident man.
(He confidently makes
the balloon burst.)
- My goodness.
- That was cool.
For goodness' sake.
That was good.
- It isn't easy.
- It's so hard.
It's not something I can do.
Three people are out.
Okay, okay.
Slash it, Kwang Soo.
You have done it before.
- Let's see how he does it.
- He will make it burst.
Let's see how he does it.
Okay!
(He cleanly peels off one layer.)
- What is up with him?
- Seriously.
- What happened?
- I just put the blade on it,
and a layer came off.
- Really?
- What happened?
I bet Jong Kook is good
at something like this.
- No, no.
- Your brother is a plastic surgeon.
- That has nothing to do with me.
- Seriously.
(He must have doctor's genes.)
- What was that?
- He did a good job.
He did it gently.
- Haha.
- Is it my turn?
I should move out of the way.
- Hey.
- That won't work.
Put some strength into it.
Don't do it like that.
- For goodness' sake.
- Look back on what you did.
- He is practically patting it.
- Just do it like this.
Just do it like this.
(Kwang Soo gets a splash of water!)
He's out.
(Dumbfounded)
(Flustered)
What are you doing?
He got completely wet.
(Jae Suk can't stop being
mischievous.)
Kwang Soo, I am sorry.
- What?
- You are out.
He said, "I am sorry."
Is that all you can say?
It burst on its own, right?
- What?
- It burst on its own, right?
(Swearing)
- "It burst on its own."
- Kwang Soo.
You should have stopped him.
- I am sorry.
- What?
That's...
- Okay.
- I knew that would happen.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Okay! Let's take first place!
Ji Hyo, go ahead.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
I put a hole in it!
- Ji Hyo is good at slashing it.
- Gently.
It shows
that she has used a knife...
- ever since she was little.
- I know.
(The importance of early education)
- The knife...
- It shows that she's experienced.
- It's coming off.
- There is a hole.
- I am seeing a different color.
(What?)
- What?
- Does it count or not?
- What is that?
- She needs to slash the upper part.
- Does it count or not?
- It doesn't count yet.
- It hasn't peeled off.
- Ji Hyo, it doesn't count yet.
- It needs to peel off completely.
Slash this part.
You should slash the red part.
(You should slash the red part.)
Haha, be quiet.
Do you think I am a fool?
Then why are you reaching
for the blue part?
(Ji Hyo reaches for the blue part.)
Just take that part off.
- It will be hard to do that.
- This is...
Just slash the blue part.
For goodness' sake.
(There are 3 people remaining
including Ji Hyo.)
- Three?
- What?
For goodness' sake.
(She suddenly self-destructs!)
- What?
- Why did you do that?
- It's so frustrating!
- Are you serious?
- She is weird.
Did you give up
because you have many R coins?
- Why did you do that?
- Ji Hyo is scary!
It's so frustrating
that I can't do it.
What is wrong with her personality?
- You are scary.
- Listen.
It didn't come off cleanly,
but I couldn't do it again.
- I understand.
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
- I think it will burst.
It would be better
for Jong Kook to take first place.
I think he will fail.
No, no.
(What?)
(The balloon falls to the ground.)
- He is still in.
- The balloon didn't burst.
(Thankfully,
the balloon didn't burst.)
The balloon didn't burst.
(What?)
Hey, hey.
Pick it up!
- Pick it up!
- Hey!
(Popping)
- For goodness' sake.
- Pick it up!
- Hey!
- You should have picked it up.
- What?
- Couldn't you have picked it up?
What happened?
(Kwang Soo stayed true
to his character.)
- I tried...
- What was that?
I tried to pick it up.
- It can't be helped.
- Jong Kook is out.
- Thank you so much.
- Okay!
- Thank you.
- For goodness' sake.
- I tried to pick it up.
- You shouldn't have done that.
Se Chan took first place.
It can't be helped.
After this,
you have one more chance...
to get more coins after the race.
For goodness' sake.
I will listen to my conscience.
We will start the conveyor belt.
Can I start taking the coins?
- Yes.
- Se Chan, stop it already.
You are making yourself look bad.
I am serious.
I did it conscientiously.
- Jong Kook.
- We will need to give up.
You will be impressed.
(The conveyor belt reaches
Jong Kook on the 7th floor.)
(My goodness.)
Who knew I would end up
on the first floor?
The number isn't half bad.
You are right. Seriously, Se Chan.
- Yes?
- I have no expectations.
I have no expectations either.
I will leave some behind...
- for Haha.
- That's right.
(What?)
Haha needs some coins.
I mean...
Don't take so many.
(Why did Se Chan laugh?)
Ji Hyo, don't take so many.
You have a lot already.
- Okay, okay.
- Promise me.
I promise.
Let me see how many coins there are.
(Clean)
(There aren't any coins to see.)
I left a lot of coins.
How did... How did this happen?
(The tray moves on
without taking a client.)
For goodness' sake.
What?
Gosh, this is...
What's the point of making it stop?
I shouldn't have had
any expectations.
It's time for the final race.
You will choose the last order
in which you take the coins...
through the Running for 10 Years.
It's the tail-catching
name tag elimination.
(The tail-catching
name tag elimination)
The person below your number
will be your target.
- My goodness.
- 8's target is 7.
- 7's target is 6.
- Hold on.
1's target is 8.
For goodness' sake.
- This determines the last ranking.
- Yes.
However,
you can purchase items
during the race.
(You can purchase items
during the race.)
Adding a target costs five coins.
Putting a bell on a member
also costs five coins.
If you pay five coins,
you can have another target
who isn't right below your number.
Okay.
It's important to have five coins.
Suk Jin doesn't have any coins.
Then you can get the target
who is right below your number.
Otherwise, you can beg
and ask for mercy.
- Is begging an option?
- Yes.
- My goodness.
- Please move to your spot.
- Okay.
- Get ready to beg.
This hurts my pride.
You are having a hard time today.
I have a plan.
I will lick Se Chan's shoes.
(I will lick Se Chan's shoes.)
(He made up his mind to beg.)
That's my plan.
What should I do?
Whom should I choose as my target?
It's meaningless to hold on
to these five coins.
Se Chan will try to take off
my name tag.
When it's me against Jong Kook...
after he takes off
everyone's name tag,
I will take off his name tag
and become a hero.
All right. The race will start.
My heart is beating fast...
even though I have done this
for 10 years.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
The race starts.
(The race starts.)
(Se Chan, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Haha,)
(Kwang Soo, Jae Suk,
Suk Jin, and So Min)
(Picking up)
The race starts.
Here are 10 coins.
- Put two bells on Jong Kook.
- Okay.
I'll put them on him from the
start. That'll make me feel at ease.
Where is Ji Hyo?
Jong Kook, someone put bells on you.
For goodness' sake.
It must be Ji Hyo.
The wealthy Ji Hyo did it.
I will need to take off
her name tag soon.
Let's see where she is.
(With the bells, Jong Kook shows off
his sense of presence.)
I will first watch a performance
of "Heungbo Is Dumbfounded".
(Before the race began)
(I don't have any coins.)
(Beg when the camera is running.)
Sing this part. "Where do you want
your little brother to go?"
(Show me a performance
of "Heungbo Is Dumbfounded".)
(Satisfy me!)
(They agreed to be clowns
for 5 coins.)
Se Chan.
Wait.
(Haha begins to warm up.)
All right. Let's see it.
All right
(All right)
(Here I come)
- Here I come
- There you go.
(This beggar let go of his pride.)
(He is doing great.)
Heungbo is dumbfounded
(Heungbo is dumbfounded)
(He gives a passionate show
for 5 coins.)
That's life.
There is no such thing as seniority
before capitalism.
That's life.
(He sang the entire song
to get some coins.)
Please give me some coins.
That was perfect. Here you go.
- I will give you five coins.
- Se Chan.
I am giving you these coins
so that we can be allies.
That's right. Se Chan.
(The beggar gives a gala show
in happiness.)
I will take off
So Min's name tag first.
Gosh, Jae Suk will come after me
with all his might.
So Min is over there.
Jae Suk and So Min are over there.
I need to avoid Suk Jin.
I can take Suk Jin out.
Then I will be bait.
I'll be bait.
I'll make Suk Jin come to me.
Jae Suk is protecting So Min.
(Suk Jin is watching everything.)
(Jae Suk is hiding.)
(He finds something.)
- Hey, Suk Jin is watching you.
- I know.
To be honest,
our eyes met,
and it's so awkward
to pretend I have no idea.
(It's too awkward.)
- Our eyes definitely met.
- Suk Jin thinks...
he is...
in "Mission: Impossible".
He thinks he is Tom Cruise.
Look at that.
Wearing a yellow cap...
How can he think
we can't see him?
How long are we supposed to
pretend we have no idea?
If I approach her right now,
she'll call Jae Suk,
and Jae Suk will run to her.
Then it'll be 2 to 1.
(What is she doing?)
I'm letting Suk Jin know
where I am.
I'm letting him know.
(Lying down)
So Min is right there.
Jae Suk is coming upstairs.
Don't you think she's looking at me?
(The middle-aged man
can be slow.)
(Jong Kook is figuring out
what's going on.)
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
You have to put on two more bells.
(This is driving me crazy.)
(He has to wear so many bells.)
Just a second.
This is not okay.
How many bells do I have to wear?
What's the use of R coins?
(Ji Hyo invests her R coins
in bells.)
I'll cover Jong Kook's legs
with bells.
He's wearing two bells,
and I can't hear him?
(He's wearing as many bells
as a shaman does.)
There she is.
(So Min and Se Chan
run into each other.)
- What about me?
- What about her?
Suk Jin can eliminate her, right?
Yes. I'm running away from him.
I'm not going to eliminate you.
- Are you So Min's target?
- Yes.
- Pay five coins then.
- What?
(Se Chan can eliminate So Min
if he pays 5 coins.)
I should pay coins?
Bye. Thanks for today.
What?
- I'll eliminate you.
- Why are you doing this?
You can't do this.
- Don't do that.
- Are you going to cry?
(She is about to cry.)
- This is how you play.
- Why are you crying?
- She shouldn't be like this.
This is how you play.
- I'll pay you. Eliminate Se Chan.
- What?
- How much?
- Take it, and we'll eliminate you.
I'll pay you.
(So Min's offer
makes Kwang Soo's eyes shake.)
- Look at Kwang Soo's face.
- I'll give you one coin.
Let's see what he does.
Why don't you make an offer to me?
Fine.
- All right.
- Hey.
(Haha takes it back.)
I get it.
(So Min suddenly attacks Kwang Soo.)
(So Min's target is Se Chan.
Why is she attacking Kwang Soo?)
Target Kwang Soo.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Eliminate Kwang Soo first.
- Okay.
Okay.
- I'll target Kwang Soo.
- Okay.
(So Min paid 5 coins
to be able to target Kwang Soo.)
(She attacked him
while he was distracted.)
- Gosh, this is annoying.
- What happened?
- This is annoying.
- What's wrong?
- Did she pay to attack me?
- What happened?
Haha, hold Kwang Soo.
- No!
- Pay me.
- Hold him!
- Okay.
(I can't believe you.)
Hold him.
- Stop it!
- Hold him!
Hold him! Hurry!
What did I do so wrong?
I don't even have coins!
Listen, I don't even have coins.
- Look at his face.
- I don't even have coins.
- He looks genuinely frustrated.
- This is so unfair.
I don't even have coins.
Look at his face.
He looks so desperate.
Eliminate him!
(In the end, they use force.)
(Suk Jin pops out of nowhere.)
(So Min's name tag is ripped off.)
(So Min is eliminated by Suk Jin,
whom she looked down on.)
What happened?
(This is
the older generation's skill.)
(Kwang Soo's name tag is
ripped off.)
- Give it to me.
- Kwang Soo is out.
(So Min and Kwang Soo
are out.)
- Who is my next target?
Am I your next target?
Suk Jin, am I your target?
Hold on.
(Se Chan backs off.)
Haha, hold Suk Jin.
- Those who are out...
- Hurry up and pay.
(The beggar is back.)
- This is not okay.
I'll target Suk Jin.
(Se Chan can now attack Suk Jin.)
Did you two team up?
- Rip it off.
- Hey!
Suk Jin.
This is...
(Suk Jin is out.)
(Even though he has never been
this quick in 10 years...)
- I can attack Jae Suk now.
- Those who are out should move.
(Suk Jin is eliminated by
the beggar alliance.)
We'll be penalized.
This keeps you cool.
This cools you off.
- Oh, this...
This keeps you really cool.
This is really effective.
I feel so much cooler now.
Se Chan has been so arrogant today.
It's annoying.
It is annoying.
Gosh.
He can't win first place anyway.
- Jong Kook will win.
- Jong Kook will win for sure.
It feels like he's older than me.
Just imagine he's older than you.
(Jong Kook is stronger
than Suk Jin.)
Gosh, what should I do?
I can attack you now.
Okay.
But let's eliminate Jong Kook first.
Then promise me.
- We'll be top two,
- Okay.
- and we'll share the coins.
- That sounds good.
- Whether I win or you win...
- Okay, it's a deal.
- I promise.
- Promise me.
- I can attack you now.
- Okay.
Let's eliminate Jong Kook first.
Let's go.
(Jingling)
Here he comes.
(Jong Kook appears
with the jingle of the bells.)
Gosh, this is frustrating.
(He appears right away.)
Gosh.
Here comes Jong Kook.
I'll eliminate Ji Hyo.
She has too many coins.
(Staring)
What's with your face?
- You...
- You want to attack me?
That's not it.
- I want to attack Jae Suk.
- Hold on.
(Is he paying to attack Jae Suk?)
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Calm down.
- I want to attack Se Chan.
Wait.
- There's no point in attacking me.
- Calm down.
I'll eliminate Ji Hyo.
She has too many coins.
But if you eliminate Ji Hyo,
I'll be in danger.
I'll be Jong Kook's next target.
Then you two can team up
and eliminate me.
Do you think that'll work?
- I wish we could do that.
- I wish it was that simple.
Then should we keep Ji Hyo alive...
and try to eliminate
each other here?
Gosh.
Do you want me
to eliminate her first...
or should we start right now?
- Why do you have to scare us?
- I mean...
- Why...
- We can start right now.
Eliminate Ji Hyo first,
and we'll decide later.
- You can eliminate her now, right?
- I can do that.
- Then do that.
- I'll eliminate her.
She's survived long enough.
(He sets out to get Ji Hyo.)
I have to find Jae Suk.
(Meanwhile,
Ji Hyo is looking for Jae Suk.)
(She finds him.)
(However)
Ji Hyo.
(Jong Kook appears in front of her.)
- What are you doing here?
- Jong Kook.
You've survived long enough.
- I get it.
- You've survived long enough.
- We need to talk.
- No.
Ji Hyo is here.
They're going up.
- They're going up.
- What happened?
Why doesn't he eliminate her
right away?
- Why are they being lovey-dovey?
- What are they doing?
That's how a couple fights
in an elevator.
(Romance, seen from a distance,
but action, seen up close)
- Why isn't he ripping it off?
- I know.
Hey! The bells...
The bells are no use.
- The bells...
- Stop it!
You've survived long enough.
You have a lot of coins.
Darn it.
Why did you have to show up there?
- Ji Hyo is out.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk.
- Hey.
(Wait for me. I'll be right there.)
Like we said before...
We should both attack him...
whether you win or I win.
- We have no choice.
- Okay.
Please don't betray me.
Why would I?
You really shouldn't betray me.
- We'll eliminate him together...
- Okay.
- and share...
- equally...
- If we...
- Let's finish it the right way.
- If we don't do this right,
one of us will be out.
- Right.
- Okay.
Let's eliminate Jong Kook.
(Will they be able to get
the innocent serial eliminator?)
(How will the final fight end?)
You two...
have some money.
- Yes.
- You to have a bit of money.
So we should talk.
- Did you pay to attack us?
- What?
I'm your target, right?
(Jong Kook's target is Jae Suk.)
He's your target,
and you're my target.
I'm your target?
That came out wrong.
(What did you just say?)
- I mean we're not a team.
- Hold on.
- That's what I meant.
- I'm your target?
I'm supposed to attack you.
Are you angry?
By the way, don't you want to
finish in second place?
(Glancing)
Or...
do you want to finish in
first place? I'll make you king.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
(What's going on here?)
Just let me finish in second place.
- Hold on.
- That sounds great.
- Don't you want to win?
- What do you say?
- Call me a kingmaker.
- Hold on.
- A kingmaker.
- Just a second.
- Se Chan.
- I know you two are close, but...
- Don't be so desperate.
- He says he'll make me win.
- Come here.
- Let's get it over with.
- I'll make you king.
- Hold on.
Wait.
- Let's not waste time.
- Don't waste time.
- I mean...
- Come here.
- Hold on.
Rip it off.
Okay!
This is...
- This is unfair.
- Go away.
Go away.
- Third place is good enough.
- Okay.
- How many coins do you have?
- What?
- How many do you have?
- Jong Kook.
- How many coins do you have?
- What?
- How many do you have?
- Jong Kook.
How many do you have?
Do you want me to open your bag?
Why...
What are you talking about?
Just tell me roughly.
- You sound so scary.
- Just tell me roughly.
Fine, how many are you
going to take later?
- Promise me.
- Do I have to tell you...
(What?)
- If you were going to be...
- I'll make you king.
Can't you do that much?
I'll take half.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
I always keep my promise.
I'll make you king.
Say thank you.
What are you talking about?
- Say thank you.
- Can I film this?
- Just say it.
- Is it really necessary?
Say thank you.
- The game is over now.
- No one will know.
- Only Se Chan will hear it.
- Still,
thank you.
Still, thank you.
- Okay. Promise me.
- Thank you.
If you break your promise today,
it'll affect the next episode too.
(And he has to pay interest.)
Seriously.
If you were going to be
stressed out...
I mean...
Just answer me.
Just say yes or no.
Just rip off my name tag!
(I can't stand it anymore.)
(The puppet king loses his temper.)
- I can't handle this stress.
- That's enough.
- I will make you king.
- What are you saying?
- Let's split it.
- Just rip it off.
Don't do it then.
(An outbreak of a coup d'etat)
Rip it off! Just rip it off.
If I have to live like this,
I'd rather you rip it off.
Okay!
(The unfortunate king
who was dethroned in 5 minutes)
- The race is over.
- Gosh, I'm dumbfounded.
If you were
going to die like this...
- No, this is...
- Let's go.
Gosh. I'm dumbfounded.
I will be conscientious
and leave you some.
I will keep it a secret
that you died so miserably.
I will be conscientious.
(Jae Suk's words ended up becoming
an ornament for Jong Kook.)
- Seriously.
- Jae Suk got ripped off.
- Okay, everyone.
- Yes.
Before we start dividing up
the coins for the last time,
- I will tell you the prices...
- I don't have any coins.
- of the prizes you all wanted.
- I hope they cost 100 coins.
The penalty exemption card...
I just need to avoid
getting the penalty.
- is 40 coins.
- 40 coins.
(Penalty exemption is 40,
Penalty transfer is 50)
(Massage gun is 30, A box of masks
and hand sanitizer is 20)
50 coins?
You have to spend 50 coins then.
I wouldn't have wasted my coins
if I knew.
- Gosh, this is...
- They're affordable.
Today, as you can see,
a total of 320 coins
have been given out.
- Right.
- If you divided it up evenly,
no one would've ended up
with a penalty.
I know.
But you all squandered it
and kept each other in check,
- I'm embarrassed of myself.
- No.
We could've avoided
the penalty today.
- Right.
Goodness.
(The moments of greed
cross their mind.)
- The condition is the penalty, yes?
- If you can't buy the exemption,
you'll get the penalty.
Hold on. If I use 40 for today...
Hey, Jong Kook.
If you aren't greedy...
It's not too late.
- The conveyor belt...
- How much do we need?
- will start.
- Just start already.
This isn't a competition.
We can all survive.
- Okay, go.
- Hold on.
Hey!
- What are you doing?
- Hold on!
What are you doing?
How many are you taking?
Hold on.
What are you doing?
Why did you take so much?
My gosh. Hold on.
Is this what it's like? Hold on.
- He took so many.
- How many are left, Se Chan?
(He picks up as many as he needs.)
- I have just enough.
- You have enough, right?
- Really?
- Got it.
(The last 2 will go to Ji Hyo,
who's on the 5th floor.)
Jong Kook took so many.
No, Jae Suk.
(He has only seen
an empty tray all day.)
There weren't that many
to start with.
- You're a fool to expect otherwise.
- There's nothing there.
(As expected, there are no coins
left for the lower floors.)
You're a fool to expect otherwise.
(The final coin division is over.)
(The results of
the final coin division)
(Jong Kook 56, Jae Suk 52,
Ji Hyo 52, Se Chan 40, So Min 24)
(Haha 10, Kwang Soo 6, Suk Jin 0)
What's the penalty for today?
The penalty
will be revealed shortly.
I'm considering buying the massage
gun and just getting the penalty.
- Seriously?
- I really needed one.
I just need 20.
Will anyone give me 20 coins?
- No one will do so, right?
- How many do you have?
I have 24 coins.
I've decided to get
the massage gun.
Are you going to give them to me?
- What?
- You're going to get the penalty?
I...
You're going to get the penalty
and buy a massage gun?
Are you serious?
You can get an exemption card today.
I'm going to buy the massage gun.
- Why are you obsessing over it?
- I could...
I could just go home
after the penalty.
- Why?
- Here, have 20 coins.
Why are you doing this?
I don't need it.
What will I do with 20 coins?
He's just giving it to her?
I want to get a massage gun now
because of him.
I want a massage gun because
Jae Suk keeps talking about it.
There's a limited supply.
There are only three.
I want a massage gun
because there's a limited supply.
- You're sure, right?
- Haha.
- What's going on?
There aren't many left.
- Haha.
- Hurry up and buy it.
- There's one left?
It's better to buy this
and get the penalty.
- Hurry up and pay him.
- Here. I'll buy the massage gun.
I'll purchase an exemption card.
We have one more.
There's one more. I'll get it.
I'll buy the massage gun.
- Okay. Masks and hand sanitizer.
- We're so warm-hearted.
(Kwang Soo got
the mask and hand sanitizer set.)
We're so warm-hearted.
Am I the only one
who doesn't get anything?
- Yes.
- It's okay.
- Six people will get the penalty.
- Right.
The penalty that you all feared...
- What is it?
- I'll reveal it now. Come in.
- "Come in"?
- What is it?
(What is the penalty...)
(that they exchanged
for the massage gun?)
- Is it a gourd?
- What is that?
- We have to break the gourd.
- Is that it?
(The mysterious gourds come in.)
- Are we breaking gourds?
- To end the day...
with your warm loyalty, we will do
Break the Gourd with Loyalty.
This is really...
However the winner feels like?
It will be in order
until the last one is broken.
- I told you.
- Jae Suk.
- Thank you.
- What did I tell you?
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
- I also...
(Jae Suk goes first.)
- I'll start.
- Okay.
Nice shot.
(With the power of the massage gun,
he breaks the gourd satisfyingly.)
- Jae Suk broke it.
- One more.
The gourd is hard too.
- One more!
- Okay, one more!
You're so cool!
- This one is hard.
- This one is...
(An unexpected dull sound)
Jae Suk, think of...
Think of the massage gun.
This one is... Gosh.
This one sounds different.
- Goodness.
- Look at that.
Gosh, this is...
- Goodness.
- Look at that.
(It's more like he's breaking
his head with a gourd.)
It didn't break even though
he threw it on the ground.
It has a crack in it now.
- It is cracked.
- It has a crack in it now..
It will break now.
(He had some difficulty, but he
successfully breaks 2 gourds.)
The gourds are breaking!
Can't you wear a hat?
- It won't break?
- It should break now.
That's why it's a penalty.
You got it. One more.
That's right.
- Good job.
We are loyal.
It's so heartwarming.
I will pass it on
to the next person.
(I will pass it on
to the next person.)
Gosh. As soon as he said that.
- He's the worst.
- I'll pass it on.
It's not that. I just...
I'm sorry.
- He passed it on.
You can do it.
You should do it.
- He won't do it.
- You should.
I already went.
What?
(He already broke some
in his imagination.)
And then I returned to my spot.
- What are you saying?
- What?
- You didn't even touch it.
- You have to touch it.
Who said?
Then I'll break one.
- Okay.
- Okay. Break one.
- It's not that bad.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- Okay. Good job.
Finish up the last three.
Se Chan does this all the time.
(Hitting)
Okay!
(This is the pride of a comedian.)
He's so cool!
Yang Gourd.
- Gosh, Yang Se Chan.
- Good job!
Good job, Yang Gourd.
(The members enter
a mysterious room.)
I really wanted to do this.
(A mysterious liquid
is in front of them.)
(You are...)
(a person with a superpower.)
(With new students,
Kang Han Na and Lee Sang Yeob)
(The legendary superpower race
has returned.)
What is this?
(They have returned with strong
superpowers.)
(The ultimate superpower war)
(They don't know
each other's superpowers,)
(but they must become
the last man standing.)
(It's an end game of superpowers
unseen anywhere else.)
(The final war among superpowers
to change destiny will unfold.)
(Superpower School Race,
War of Superpowers: The End Game)