(This was filmed before the practice
of social distancing step 2.)
Hello, hello.
- Hello.
- Our spots are marked.
Ji Hyo sent me black raspberries.
Did you send them to everyone?
- Yes.
- You think I sent them selectively?
- You didn't send any last time.
- To whom?
- To me.
- What do you mean?
Remember gwamegi?
- Suk Jin.
- I sent it to you.
- You sent him black raspberries?
- Why?
They won't be any use to him.
(You sent him black raspberries?
They won't be any use to him.)
Goodness.
What is he saying?
Jong Kook, you were waiting
for the right moment to say it.
Suk Jin can use them
to make kimchi.
- To make kimchi?
- Yes.
He can enjoy them
because they're sweet.
They're sweet.
What do you know?
- Why are you blushing?
- I am not.
You lose if you blush.
- He lost.
- I'm not blushing.
It's because it's hilarious.
I expected it,
but why is it so funny?
(It's the effect
of black raspberries.)
I heard that Ji Hyo has been
generous these days.
- Why?
- About what?
She sent coffee to everyone.
She sent it to Solar.
- That's right.
- Yes.
Why are you doing this
all of a sudden?
Are you out of your mind?
- "Out of your mind"?
- I wanted to be generous.
She makes an effort
to maintain her relationships.
- Now...
- She got rid of her walls.
- Ji Hyo broke down her walls.
- Now?
She's opening up to the world.
- At the age of 40?
- She was in a cave before.
She's 40, and now she's opening up.
- That's impressive.
- That's great.
Ji Hyo, what happened to you?
It's nothing.
Will you be making a sudden,
- important announcement?
- No.
- Are you getting...
- Is it all for your wedding?
(Is that why
she's giving out presents?)
- Are you getting...
- Is that why?
There's a rumor
about So Min's relationship.
- What's going on with you?
- What's with you?
("Rumors about Oh Dong Min
and Jeon So Min's Relationship")
("They Deny Their Relationship",
"They're Just Close Friends")
I have many male friends.
Now they're blocking my way.
Why would you go to an escape room?
Isn't that where you go
with your boyfriend?
- Did you go camping with him?
- By the way...
- Camping?
- No.
We didn't go camping,
but these days...
- That's impressive.
- No.
- Did you even go camping with him?
- That's not true.
Now that I think about it,
she was friendlier than usual...
to Se Chan in the waiting room
today.
Exactly. Suddenly,
she told me to come...
- and offered me a seat.
- She told him to come next to her.
They talked while sitting on a sofa.
You're the only one for me.
(You're the only one for me.)
She's setting up a shield.
My goodness.
I'm an easy target as her shield.
- You know...
- Se Chan must be confused.
She's pretending to be close
to everyone including Oh Dong Min.
Se Chan is acting as her smoke bomb.
Since two days ago, Se Chan
didn't respond to my messages.
- After the news about Dong Min...
- Are you upset?
- That's right.
- Just pay attention to him.
No, he's just a friend.
His name is Oh Dong Min.
You mispronounced his name.
It's Oh Dong Min.
What you said is
a song by Choi Heon.
- You understood what I mean.
- Right.
Today, you're students
at Brahms Music School.
- A music school?
- You'll be showing off...
your music skills.
What's Brahms?
- It's an instrument.
- An instrument?
It's one of the instruments
in an orchestra.
(Johannes Brahms, a composer known
for "The Hungarian Dances")
Four students at the same school
are waiting for you.
- Really?
- Please come out.
Please come out.
- My goodness.
- Gosh.
- Hello.
- What's going on?
- My goodness.
- Ji Hyun
- Gosh.
- Eun Bin.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you.
(Park Eun Bin, a popular actress
appearing on "Hot Stove League",)
("Hur Jun, The Original Story",
and "Hello, My Twenties!")
It's Ji Hyun. Wow.
(Park Ji Hyun in "Gonjiam: Haunted
Asylum", and "Rookie Historian...")
("Goo Hae Ryung"
and Running Man Episode 475)
It's Min Jae.
(Kim Min Jae appeared in
"Dr. Romantic", "Goblin",)
("Flower Crew: Joseon Marriage
Agency" and "Love, Sling".)
All right.
(Kim Sung Cheol appeared
in "Prison Playbook",)
("Kim Ji-young Born 1982",
and "The Wind Blows".)
(The four actors are the cast
in "Do You Like Brahms?")
(The drama tells a story
of dreams and love.)
All right.
What do you think when you look
at the four of them?
- They're in a new drama.
- Are they promoting it?
- Promoting?
- It must be an SBS drama.
Look, Eun Bin seems embarrassed.
- Don't be embarrassed.
- Okay.
Promoting isn't bad.
- In that case...
- What kind of drama is it?
Is it about youth?
That's right. We're here
to promote it anyway.
- Please do.
- Okay.
It's a Mon-Tues SBS drama called
"Do You Like Brahms?"
- It's at a music school.
- That's why today's theme...
- is a music school.
- Yes.
- It takes place at a music school.
- It's a youthful...
melodrama that's full of emotions
based on classical music.
- Is that so?
- The roles that we play...
are 29 years old.
- What?
- It's about questioning...
dreams and love
at the end of their 20's.
- Love?
- That's what...
- it's about.
- Are you guys couples then?
Is it a love triangle?
Isn't that right?
Should it be a secret for now?
- Of course.
- I see.
I bet there's a couple
and one of them interferes.
You're the one interfering.
My goodness.
- That's what makes it fun.
- Let them promote.
Normally, the way
Eun Bin promotes is...
that she hopes
that people enjoy the drama.
She's discreet about it.
Now, she said the entire synopsis.
(Now, she said the entire synopsis.)
I think she memorized it.
- The first episode is on August 31.
- Like a machine.
- It's tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
That's right.
Please be sure to watch it.
We have these four guests today.
What's the theme today?
All 12 of you are students
at a music school.
You'll take a simple music test...
and be assigned to your grade
from 1 to 4.
- I hope I'm in a higher grade.
- Are questions related to music?
- Yes, they are.
- That's a relief.
It's a total of 10 questions.
The top three enter fourth grade.
The next top three
enter third grade,
second, and first in order.
It's better...
to lie about your score and grade.
- I'll tell you why later.
- Is that so?
- I'm good at that.
- The higher your grade, the better.
I wonder what the questions are.
- We'll bring in desks and chairs.
- Okay.
(What kind of music test is it?)
Please open the test.
(They open the test.)
Okay, do we start?
- Gosh, isn't it that one?
- I can do it.
My goodness.
Why are we taking a test?
- Do we start?
- Now?
- "Listen to the classical piece."
- Do we write it down?
It's a listening question.
Do I write down the answers
with the pen?
Open up the PDF file.
- Take out your pen.
- With the pen?
Write down the answers
and send them.
Do we start?
Here's number one.
(Listen to the piece
and write down the title.)
- What's this piece?
- I definitely know it.
(What's this?)
- It played at Western restaurants.
- Right.
- When you order a course meal.
- Yes.
Either pork cutlet or hamburg steak.
I definitely know it.
(Listen to the piece
and write down the title.)
- What is it?
- Brahms?
- What?
- Isn't it by Brahms?
It's by Brahms?
Isn't it by Brahms?
- This?
- What?
It's 3 syllables plus 2 syllables.
I thought it was something else.
Isn't it what I think it is?
I can't remember the last word.
Here's the second question.
Play music for the second question.
Number one.
(Next are the titles of songs
by Jang Beom June.)
(Listen to the four songs
and list the titles in order.)
(Each is worth 2.5 points.)
(Glancing)
Number two.
(He spots her trying to cheat.)
These are Beom June's songs
that I'm not familiar with.
Number three.
(These are the hit songs
that everyone knows.)
I have no idea.
(They sound all the same.)
I have no idea either.
Number four.
(They all sound familiar.)
(4 similar yet different songs
by Jang Beom June)
What was it?
I don't recognize this one.
Next is a short answer question.
You get an advantage
if you submit first.
Option number three...
and four. Aren't they the same
person with different wigs?
They're definitely different.
I'm just writing down names
that I know.
Did you write "Sam Hammington"?
No way.
These two are confusing.
- Aren't they the father and mother?
- Right.
- What is this?
- Father and mother?
Which one is the father?
But they're both men.
Why are they father and mother?
Father of music and mother of music.
- Is it Vincent van Gogh?
- My goodness.
- Gogh was a painter.
- He was a painter.
Was he?
"Amor Fati"?
I knew it before.
Amor party
(The answer is "love your fate".)
(She tries to cheat again.)
Come on.
(Looking around)
Eun Bin, you can't cheat.
- She's cheating a lot.
- No.
I didn't know she was like this.
"Just imagining it feels like
my heart is about to burst".
my heart is about to burst"?
Based on "I might cry",
it's a recent song.
I might cry
- Cry, cry
- What?
- Amor fati
(Amor fati!)
(They sing along
in the middle of the test.)
That's right.
Is SEVENTEEN a group of 13?
Were there six in god?
How many were in H.O.T?
There were 23.
(It's a very wrong answer.)
If you can get two right,
you'll get the top score.
(They write down their answers.)
I'm finished.
Please send it.
- Is it better to send it quickly?
- I'm done...
If your scores tie, the person
who sent earlier wins.
"Message", "Search PDF".
(It's time to submit the answers.)
Five.
- I sent it.
- I should just write what I know.
(The bad students always
submit their test last.)
(The test is over.)
While we check your answers,
we'll give you the answers.
Number one is "Love's Greeting"
by Edward Elgar.
I wrote "Love's Conversation".
(Continuous wrong answers
that are just extraordinary)
Isn't it called "Our Love"?
Min Jae and Haha wrote "Our Love".
- "Our Love".
(They're happy to hear it.)
Question number two.
Number one.
"It's Hard to Face You".
("It's Hard to Face You")
Number two.
"Yeosu Night Sea".
("Yeosu Night Sea")
- Number three.
- "Love, At First".
("Love, At First")
- Number four.
- "If You Really Love Me".
("If You Really Love Me")
Question number three.
The first is Beethoven.
That's obvious.
The second is Mozart.
- I got it wrong.
- I should've written it.
- The third is Handel.
- Okay.
The fourth is Bach.
That's right. It wasn't van Gogh.
If you wrote Bach,
can you get three points?
- That's amazing.
- I remember them.
- You do?
- I learned it when I was young.
I remember it clearly.
In general,
students with bad grades
are the loudest.
(They're just all talk.)
I'm getting so many correct.
Ji Hyo will definitely
be in first grade.
Instead of listening,
she's watching a video.
She's not curious about the answers.
It's because I did well on the test.
I don't need to check my answers.
Here's question number five.
You'll recognize when you hear it.
Number five?
It was right.
It's "What is Love?" by TWICE.
(The three who cheated
got the same wrong answer.)
It was TWICE as I said.
The lyrics seemed like
TWICE's songs.
Please remember...
that it's not helpful to say
what you got wrong.
- Right.
- It's better to act.
I got everything right.
The questions were so easy.
- I've been lucky thus far.
- These are so easy.
Eun Bin, did you do a terrible job?
I did very well.
- Really?
- Yes.
I was the first to submit
the answers.
- Really?
- Yes.
Question number 10.
The answer is number three.
That's right!
If you don't know, it's always
number three. Awesome.
I should be one of the top students.
Gosh, I got one wrong. I'm doomed.
You got one wrong?
You mean you got one right.
- You mean you got one right.
- How can I...
- Kwang Soo.
- get one wrong?
What's wrong, Kwang Soo?
I got one wrong by mistake.
It might as well as be zero points.
(They're doing everything
that they couldn't do in school.)
Here are the results.
Check your own score.
I'll scold you if you're
in a lower grade than me.
- I...
- We graded you fairly.
We won't receive any inquiries
about the test result.
(The scores make them speechless.)
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
Everyone.
No way.
Goodness.
(They're assigned to a grade
based on their score.)
Was I this smart?
We have to decide on the team
for the first mission.
- We have four guests.
- Yes.
Three of you will pick
your members...
by playing rock-paper-scissors.
(Results for Team Ji Hyun,
Team Min Jae, and Team Eun Bin)
- Everyone?
- Yes.
This is the first period
at your musical school.
During this period, you can improve
your music skills.
It's called Dreaming
of Being Gifted in Music.
We're dreaming of being gifted.
Each team
will pick a penalty sign...
and sit next to it.
You'll hear four remixed songs
of different periods.
Answer as soon as you recognize it.
When you answer correctly,
you win one point.
Okay.
If you get a finger flick
from Se Chan or Jong Kook,
you'll die.
Is the weapon for hitting
or getting hit?
I'll explain.
At this time...
You embarrassed him.
- You're so cold to an aged man.
- Come on.
We have guests too.
Why did you scold him?
It's all right.
Suk Jin is close to being 60.
I was the one who interrupted
when you were talking.
- Right.
- It's okay.
- Don't think like that.
- It's all right.
- Come on.
I stopped Bo Pil from talking.
It's okay, Bo Pil.
That's how he acts
when he's furious.
Every time you answer correctly,
you get a point.
Each team has three members.
A member from three teams
will take a seat.
(1 person from 3 teams)
The one who answers correctly...
performs the penalty
on 1 of the 2...
from the other team.
- After answering?
- You do it?
These six are sitting
in the finger flick zone.
These six are in
the toy hammer zone.
You should sit
in the finger flick zone.
- Can we choose?
- Yes.
In terms of pain, who's
on your team is important.
If Jong Kook and I are
on the same team,
everyone will be doomed.
- You can use different flicks.
- Is this possible?
It's your choice.
This can't be possible.
Please stand up.
Starting with those in blue vest,
pick your seat.
- Okay.
- Each person?
The one who can answer...
Since there are four songs,
I can do it.
Where should I go?
Jong Kook should go
to the finger flick zone.
- I'll sit here.
- Okay.
Only one person from each team
can sit in the zone.
(He sits next to So Min.)
Go away, Jae Suk.
Don't come here.
Come here, Ji Hyo.
Go.
- Is the team with Ji Hyo full?
- Yes.
- We can be at ease.
- Right.
Be at ease.
- Who's sitting here?
- This is...
Sit here.
- You should sit here.
- No.
No, no.
- I don't hit everyone so hard.
- Okay.
Really?
(There's only one seat
where you can avoid Jong Kook.)
(Approaching at the same time)
Where will you sit, Min Jae?
Hold on.
(They get into a fight.)
Se Chan.
(They struggle to avoid Jong Kook.)
- I can't sit there.
- Why would you sit there?
- You sit there.
- Where are you going to sit?
- Send Kwang Soo here.
- No, no.
- Okay.
- No. Where will you sit? Wait.
(Kwang Soo is taken aback.)
- Nice.
- Where will you sit?
- It's perfect.
- Please sit there.
- Is he really going to sit there?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Why should we?
- Come over here already.
Come here, you punk.
Darn it.
I've been sitting next to him
for 10 years in a row.
I sit next to him whenever
the penalty is finger flick.
- I could've been in trouble.
- When it comes to finger flick...
(Left: finger flick,
right: toy hammer)
(They all found their seats.)
We'll play 4 songs at the same time.
You can just get 1 song right.
- Just the song title, right?
- Four songs at the same time?
You have to tell us both the singer
and the song title.
Okay. Let's go.
Here's the first question.
(Try to guess what songs they are.)
(Four different songs are
being played at the same time.)
- Let me answer.
(Sung Cheol was faster.)
Sung Cheol, go ahead.
Hwasa's...
- What was it? "Maria".
- Oh, you just...
- Let me answer.
- Hwasa's "Twit".
- Correct.
- Okay.
- Oh, right. "Twit".
(Oh, I'm such a twit.)
You may hit one of them.
Se Chan, come on.
(They forgot the power
the winner has for a moment.)
You got the right answer
because of me.
- What?
- You knew it because of me.
Right. My team member
practically gave you a hint.
I gave you a hint.
- I choose Min Jae.
- Gosh.
(Min Jae will be hit.)
I'll hit Min Jae.
Oh, gosh. I...
- He's really good at it.
- It stings.
You'll be surprised when you wash
your face tomorrow morning.
(The reason why Kwang Soo was
surprised while washing his face...)
(Hitting)
(The painful finger flick
made him miss her mother.)
- It really hurts.
- At least, he has a fringe.
With the fringe down?
(He spoke casually to him
because he's scared.)
- Part his fringe.
- I'll do that.
- That would be better. Good.
- Like this.
- Yes, that's good.
- He'll be surprised.
Oh, my gosh.
Don't worry.
It will be over quickly.
- Hey, Min Jae.
- It will be over quickly.
- You can get a chance to hit him.
- It'll be over quickly.
It'll sting a little.
Think of it as getting a shot.
- You can get a chance to hit him.
- Stay still. Here we go.
- I can't watch that.
- Me neither.
(A shot of finger flick
was fired.)
My goodness.
(My goodness.)
(It hurts more than
he thought it would.)
All right. Let's continue.
Min Jae, don't forget this.
- Look at him. He's angry.
- Okay.
Let's get fired up.
- Let's continue.
- He's so cute.
(Three songs are left now.)
(Everyone became more focused
after Min Jae got the penalty.)
All I can hear is "Twit".
Let me answer.
"Sorry, Sorry" by Super Junior.
- Wrong.
- Was "Sorry, Sorry" played too?
(The time for finger flick
came again sooner than expected.)
He's so good at this game.
- How did he know that?
- Should I go with the same person?
You should give Sung Cheol
a chance as well.
Give it a try. It's worth it.
You shouldn't make too many enemies.
Should I go with the same person?
- Of course.
- Yes, you should do that.
- Why would you make more enemies?
- Hold on a second.
- Hang on.
- Exactly.
Don't give Min Jae a hard time.
Why are you meddling in this?
Let him choose.
- They're on the same team.
- Let them both try it.
- Exactly.
- Let him get a taste of it.
Let him get a taste of it.
- He should get a taste of it.
- Of course.
You know what it feels like
only when you try it.
It's worth the pain.
Right. He must be so curious.
- Here we go.
- It will sting.
(He got a taste of it.)
- Exactly.
- Gosh.
(Shocked)
(It looks so painful
that everyone is surprised again.)
(Well...)
(Clenching his teeth)
- That won't be good enough.
- Don't get me wrong.
(Oh, is it not good enough?)
Don't be mad. It's just a game.
- Okay.
- Get the right answer to hit him.
- Let's go!
- I want to get the right answer.
They can endure it
because they're actors.
Now, we'll continue playing
the music.
(He looks bloodthirsty.)
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
Is it "I Really Like You"
by Lee Ji Hye?
- Lee Ji Hye?
- Lee Ji Hye's "I Really Like You"?
I'm sorry.
(They're listening
to the songs again.)
- Let me answer.
Jewelry's "I Really Like You".
(Correct)
Eun Bin almost got the right answer.
She almost got the right answer.
I heard Ji Hye's version
of the song.
I'm sorry.
(Sit down, Jae Suk.)
- Jae Suk, cover your mouth.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
- To prevent it from popping out.
- If you're going to hit him hard...
- Hit me.
- Shouldn't he take off his glasses?
Go ahead and hit me.
Just wait and see what I'll do next.
- His front teeth will be revealed.
- Go ahead.
- Hit me.
- His front teeth will be revealed.
Hit me.
(His mouth looks like
it's sticking out more.)
(The hit on the back of his head
caused it to stick out more.)
- That wasn't weak at all.
- Exactly.
- Fine. All right.
- This is war.
- That was good.
- Good job.
- Wait until I get the right answer.
- That felt so good.
- Get the right answer.
Only one song is left.
- Darn. I can't hear any songs.
- Right? Isn't it frustrating?
- Isn't it frustrating?
- Play the music.
(The music is played again.)
I can only hear the songs
that we already got right.
(He's on his knees
with determination.)
What was it?
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
"First Love" by Clon.
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
"Holding onto
the End of the Night"...
- by Solid.
- I think it's Clon's song.
- Let me answer.
- Go ahead.
"My Only Friend" by Solid.
- Let me answer.
Clon's "Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah".
Okay.
(Their faces turned pale
in an instant.)
Oh, it was "Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah".
(It's time to check the answer.)
(Se Chan is dancing to the song
to celebrate.)
(But the 2 of them can't smile
as 1 of them will get hit.)
(When you feel blue and frustrated)
(Min Jae is feeling blue
and frustrated.)
- Which one...
- He should choose one of them.
They're looking at me
with a pitiful look.
Don't worry.
(The thought of the finger flick
makes them tear up.)
- Let them play rock-paper-scissors.
- That's a good idea.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- I'll get hit.
- That'll be better.
- Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- You see...
- Oh, yes.
- I said I'd get hit.
(After the desperate struggle,)
(Sung Cheol's forehead
showed up again.)
His finger flick is blunt.
I'm going to get hit later anyway.
(Hitting hard)
He hit him really hard.
(Exclaiming)
- He hit him even harder.
- He hit him so hard.
That was amazing.
(He had an out-of-body experience.)
- Sung Cheol.
- That was amazing.
Sung Cheol, you're having
a nosebleed.
(Really?)
Sung Cheol.
- He endured it well.
- Right?
We'll move on to the next question.
(So Min and Haha switched
their seats.)
- The beginning part is important.
- Okay.
- So Min, let's do well this time.
- Play the music.
(Try to guess what songs they are.)
(Everyone is listening closely.)
- Let me answer.
"December" by Turbo.
- Okay. Nice.
- Good job.
(As soon as Jong Kook got
the right answer,)
(Kwang Soo's face turned pale
as if his stomach got upset.)
Good job.
Good job, Jong Kook.
- But Eun Bin...
- Is it Turbo's song?
- Stay still.
- might want to experience it.
- Why would she?
- Stay still.
- That's scary.
- Just let me hit you.
- Eun Bin...
It'll be over quickly.
You saw them earlier.
(The most powerful finger flick)
(She closed her eyes.)
(He's having dry heaves.)
Good job.
I think he got a dent
on his forehead.
(It hurts, right?)
Play the music.
(Three songs are left.)
- Let me answer.
- But it hasn't...
"10 Minutes" by Lee Hyo Lee.
No, that's not one of them.
- Let me answer.
- Yes.
"I'm Your Girl" by S.E.S.
Let me answer.
"More and More" by TWICE.
(Correct)
(Nice!)
- Eun Bin, how did you know?
- I heard the song many times.
Which one will you hit?
I am going to hit Kwang Soo.
Me? I just got hit.
I just got hit. Why me?
It's better to hit the one
who just got hit.
- He's dazed right now anyway.
- Well, I don't mind...
- I can't hit hard.
- It would be better.
Here we go.
(Hitting lightly)
That was cute. That was really cute.
He seems happy. Kwang Soo liked it.
That's not the reason.
I'm sure none of you knows,
but she hit my nose with the palm
instead of flicking her finger.
(She pretended she would
flick her finger,)
(but she hit his nose.)
- With the bone here on the palm.
- I know.
- It's hard.
- You always do that to me.
How hard did she want to hit me?
Eun Bin seems to like cheating.
Two songs are left.
Play the music.
Let me answer.
"Eternal Love" by Fin.K.L.
(Correct)
(Good job.)
(He finally got a chance
to hit somebody else.)
Which one is it?
(Which one will he hit?)
(He chose Eun Bin right away.)
Did you choose her?
- You'll hit her?
- How could he choose her?
Let me explain.
Rather than fighting
against Jong Kook...
Good. Change your direction.
- He has a point.
- I thought I should...
- make a wise decision.
- You're right.
But Kwang Soo, you know
that Jong Kook will attack you...
if he gets a chance, right?
I can't believe him. Suk Jin,
check the color of your vest.
(What is wrong with him?)
- Check the color.
- Oh, I'm on your team.
(Oh, I'm on your team.)
- I forgot that.
- You see,
- we always join the team...
- Exactly.
that's the rival
of Jong Kook's team.
- Check the color of your vest.
- We're on the same team.
- I should check it often.
- Yes.
Can I hit my team member
when I get the right answer?
(No, you can't do that.)
Can we volunteer to get hit
instead of her?
- Yes, you can.
- Sung Cheol.
(Me?)
- Me?
- He's good at reacting.
Continue the momentum.
You were hit already.
You can do it.
- You should do it for her.
- You're a man.
Sung Cheol is contemplating.
- I'll get hit.
- Okay.
I didn't hit you
hard earlier, right?
By the way, Eun Bin,
do you have a shoot tomorrow?
- Yes, I do.
- Eun Bin, do you have a shoot?
I have a shoot tomorrow.
I'll hit her on the head,
not the forehead.
- On the head?
- It won't be visible.
- That's a good idea.
- Here.
- I'll hit on the side of the head.
- On the side?
- I can't hit hard either.
- Right?
- Kwang Soo can't hit hard.
- It's just a game.
Hey, how could you...
(He hit the side of her head.)
(Oh, boy.)
- Goodness.
- Eun Bin.
- Hey.
- Are you a human?
- How could you do that?
- Are you insane?
- No...
- You call yourself a human?
I didn't know how to do it.
Eun Bin. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. Are you okay?
- Eun Bin. Are you okay?
- You should check.
- Eun Bin. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
How do you call yourself a human?
Can I go home?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
- It's okay.
- She must be startled.
She has a good reaction.
I think I can answer
the questions better now.
Right. You can do it.
- Let's go.
- Are you okay? You can do it.
Okay.
- Go, Team Green.
- Play the music.
(I'll get it for sure.)
Let me answer.
"Love and Remember" by god.
(Correct)
Really?
- We need to improve.
- How did you know?
We better improve.
I really can't hear anything.
Who?
Wait. Who should I pick?
Make them play rock-paper-scissors.
Right. Play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Honestly, I want to hit So Min.
- She won.
Ji Hyo. Did you win?
- Yes, I won.
- Okay.
- But I won.
- You won.
I won.
Jae Suk wanted to hit Ji Hyo
from the beginning.
Maybe he was thinking he will
hit the winner in his head.
Right. I wished you'd lose.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
I'd already made up my mind.
- Okay.
- Okay, Ji Hyo.
Then now...
Okay.
- That sounded refreshing.
- Right.
(Current Points)
This is the third question.
Play the music.
Let me answer.
(As Min Jae shouts out,)
(Se Chan looks nervous.)
- Min Jae. You should answer it.
- Five,
4, 3...
(His forehead still hurts
from the flick.)
(He finally got a chance
to revenge.)
- Don't be nervous. Answer it.
- Okay. It's Haha's...
"Nino Maximus Keyser Soze".
(Incorrect)
(Sneering)
- Let me answer.
- Oh, please.
(Oh, please.)
"Story of a Little Kid" by Haha.
("Story of a Little Kid" by Haha)
(Correct)
(Screaming)
- Hey.
- Oh, please.
- I forgot.
- You didn't know the title.
- Gosh.
- Oh, thank you.
- That was...
- You didn't know the title.
You didn't know the title.
Why do you keep giving it away?
- I know. Why?
- I...
I forgot the title.
Who are you going to hit?
Why aren't you taking it off?
Take it off.
(He already chose the target
in his mind.)
Here?
Okay. Just hit anywhere. Hurry up!
Hit me already. I need to answer
questions. Hurry up.
Gosh.
(Delayed spike)
(He got a strong one
for acting tough.)
Good shot.
(He got a strong one
for acting tough.)
- I'm so angry.
- You have three songs left.
Play the music.
(Wait. This song is...)
- Let me answer.
"Aing" by Orange Caramel.
- Yes.
- Two...
- It's ZE:A's
- "After Effect".
(Correct)
Okay.
- Pardon?
- Why do you look sad?
Why do you look sad?
How about hitting the back
of Kwang Soo's head instead?
- Why...
- Hit Kwang Soo?
Sure. I won't hit his forehead.
The back of your head doesn't hurt.
Me?
The back of my head doesn't hurt?
- It doesn't hurt.
- You want me to hit you with this?
No.
Hey. The top of the head
doesn't hurt.
- Wait.
- It doesn't hurt at all.
I...
(Cracking)
(His head is split in half.)
(Swearing)
(Shocked)
(Screaming)
That was really loud.
That was loud.
(It feels good to hit
the top of the head.)
Hey. The top of the head
doesn't hurt.
Everything looks green.
Don't lie.
- I'm serious. Everything is green.
- I said stop lying.
That was amazing.
I think that was the loudest.
That sounded like
a watermelon though.
That was strong.
You have two songs left.
You can't get up and discuss.
- Let's do this!
- Play the music.
(Music plays again
to find 2 hidden songs.)
(Let me answer.)
Let me answer.
It's Park Hyo Shin's...
(Sung Cheol got flicked twice.)
(He finally got a chance
to revenge.)
Let me answer.
(Will he be able to take his revenge
on Se Chan?)
5, 4...
(It's Park Hyo Shin's...)
- "Memories Resemble Love".
- Let me answer.
(He lost his chance.)
"Snow Flower" by Park Hyo Shin.
(Correct)
"Snow Flower" by Park Hyo Shin. Yes!
(Oh, right. "Snow Flower".)
Come on.
You're out of control.
(My Jong Kook.)
(Happy ceremony)
(Jong Kook is excited.)
Calm down.
That's scary.
- Hey.
- That was scary.
- Yes!
- Anyway, I'm happy.
- I'm happy.
- That was good.
- Good.
- That was close.
- Was it correct?
- Good.
Was it correct?
(His legs feel weak. He staggers.)
That was insane, Jong Kook.
Look at Kwang Soo.
He doesn't want to get hit.
He's sitting politely
to avoid the hit.
The back of the head wouldn't hurt.
I already hit the forehead
and the top of the head.
Hit me in the back.
- Here?
- That's...
- How about here?
- Honestly,
I can't hear well since the last
hit. I can't answer the questions.
Then you tell me.
- In the back.
- I'll stroke. You tell me.
I'll stroke. Tell me to stop.
- Stop.
- Here?
Okay. Is this okay?
We'll get to see Kwang Soo bowing.
- Thank you.
- Wait.
Kwang Soo. It's all right.
This doesn't hurt at all.
Did you hit in the back of the head?
Happy New Year.
(Happy New Year.)
Give them a bow.
Good.
It's okay, isn't it?
It doesn't hurt in the back.
(It's already been 8 months,
but still, Happy New Year.)
- Good job.
- It doesn't hurt, does it?
Okay. Okay.
(It's a lie that the back of
the head doesn't feel pain.)
It's the last question.
Play the music.
(They can only hear the songs
they answered already.)
Let me answer.
- All I can think of is her
- No.
Let me answer.
(Jae Suk from Jong Kook's team
gives it a try.)
It's Hong Kyung Min's...
- 5, 4...
- It's...
"Broken Love".
- Let me answer!
(Let me answer!)
Let me answer.
- It was Sung Cheol.
- Let me answer.
Sung Cheol was fast.
"Broken Friendship"
by Hong Kyung Min.
Okay. Let's do this.
- Let's do this.
- Why couldn't I remember it?
- Why didn't you remember?
- My flicks aren't strong.
I feel sorry for Kyung Min.
Sung Cheol. Make it good.
I can't do it.
- You have to do it.
- Hit this for practice.
Practice on this.
(It's pretty strong.)
- That was pretty strong.
- Right. That's what you do.
That's what you should do.
He's strong.
I've never done it before.
Right here...
You should practice on this.
That's right. That was good.
You got it.
(He can't help but smile
at the thought of flicking Se Chan.)
Okay. Remember this.
- If you...
- No. I don't know anything.
- I'm going to be a gangster now.
- Okay. Sure.
- He's going to be a gangster.
- I sure will.
- I need a support.
- Put your hand. That's right.
Put your hand on the protruding...
(Hitting)
(Eyes opening wide)
(Unimaginable power)
You did it.
He has the talent.
- You have the talent.
- Good job.
(He found an unexpected talent.)
(That's how it feels.)
You have the talent for it.
- Good job.
- Well done.
- Was that good?
- Yes.
- That was really strong.
- Okay.
No. Now I have a reason
to become a gangster.
Good. Okay. Let's do this.
All gangsters have a reason.
They didn't just become a gangster.
That hurts.
It's the last question. Play...
(Team Green answered "SOLO"
and "Because You're My Woman".)
the music.
(They look for the third song.)
- Let me answer.
Gosh.
"Bingo" by Turtles.
- Let me answer.
- No.
You should play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's do it. Let's go.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(If Team Green answers
this question, they win.)
Now, now. Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
- Nice job, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
So Min.
Kwang Soo. We need to take revenge.
This is the last one.
If we win, it's over.
(Two proud geniuses)
(The result of the first game
depends on the rock-paper-scissors.)
Rock-paper-scissors. Okay!
"Airplane" by Turtles.
Okay!
(Correct)
(That was close.)
That was good.
That was close.
Now, Team Green won.
Why... I don't get to hit someone?
Go ahead.
(Hitting means more to Kwang Soo
than his team winning.)
- Wait.
- He didn't hit me right.
(He ruined it
from straining too much.)
- It's over.
- No.
- You hit me. It's over.
- It doesn't count.
- It's over.
- No.
- You flicked already. It's over.
- No, it doesn't count.
- It's over.
(He finally hit Jong Kook right.)
I'm sorry.
(He's acting cute
with all his body.)
He just hit me.
I'm sorry.
Okay, okay.
He's generous.
(The first mission ends
with Jong Kook's tolerance.)
I'll announce the result
of the first mission.
- Ji Hyun's Team Green placed first.
- That was close.
- I'll tell you the benefit.
- You tried hard.
It's the first Promotion Time
where you can guess...
each other's grade
and earn the Promotion Badge.
You can ask one person
from each team their grade...
in front of everyone.
(They can ask 1 person's grade
from Team Blue and Orange.)
After guessing the grade,
we'll pick 1 person randomly
among you 4.
That person will place
three people in each group.
Then the person
with the highest grade...
will receive the Promotion Badge.
So, if Sung Cheol's the highest,
he receives one badge.
(The person in the highest grade
will get the Promotion Badge.)
They'll be able to place them.
So based on the results, we have
to guess one another's grades.
But what's important here is...
If there are two people
who are in the same grade,
they will be eliminated, and
the next highest grade will get it.
Really?
- Either you win or get eliminated.
- Overlapping is the worst.
- Really?
- First,
Team Green must decide
which person they want to ask...
from each team.
- Should we gather up in our teams?
- Yes.
We can ask two people.
Yes, we can ask two people.
Should we ask
who's in the lowest grade...
- or who's in the highest grade?
- The lowest grade.
- The lowest?
- That way,
when we place each person,
we can write them down.
We have to ask about
Jong Kook or Jae Suk...
because at the end
during the race...
- we can calculate our moves.
- It will help us.
Should we ask about Jong Kook first?
We've decided. We want to know
about Haha from Team Blue...
and...
- Jong Kook from Team Orange.
Haha...
- is in second grade.
- Goodness.
(This child who cried out
when he got one wrong...)
(barely got 25 points
and was placed in 2nd grade.)
Haha...
- is in second grade.
- Goodness.
Kim Jong Kook is also
in second grade.
(Jong Kook is also in 2nd grade.)
- Goodness.
- Now,
the four of you must come
to a consensus,
and the person that is chosen
will go inside the booth.
We don't know
who will go inside the booth, right?
Right. We'll choose that person
in three minutes
Then what grade are you in?
Are we not allowed to tell?
We need to know that...
- We need to know. Let's reveal it.
- to place them together.
I'm in fourth grade.
- It's true.
- I'm sorry, but...
If you're in fourth grade,
it's over because I...
I'll be honest, I'm in third grade.
- I'm in third grade.
- I will...
bet everything I have on the fact
that you're in first grade.
No. That's not true.
- He's a kid.
- I...
(He's a young kid.)
I'll choose the person now.
(They will start the random draw
to choose the representative.)
The person
who will place everyone...
- is Song Ji Hyo.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Did you understand the rules?
- Song Ji Hyo will...
- Ji Hyo...
- To be exact,
do you know what she said earlier?
I told her we needed to place them,
and she asked me what a badge was.
It's "place", not "badge".
You should go.
You can go in now.
You can't explain it to her.
- She needs to go right in.
- I have high hopes.
- Yes, me too.
- Ji Hyo...
I have high expectations.
I hope Ji Hyo makes a complete mess
of things.
- I am expectant.
- You know what we mean, right?
- I understand.
- We'll show you the placement,
and then we will announce who won.
You can make your guesses with that.
So you have to go in there
no matter what.
You can betray your team
from in there.
Ji Hyo will place them so that
she benefits from it.
(Ji Hyo contemplates for a long time
with a vacant look on her face.)
(She places herself
in the fourth box.)
(She places Haha and Jong Jook
who overlap in 2nd grade with her.)
(Surprisingly, she understood
the rules well.)
(If she's not in 2nd grade,
she gets the badge.)
You know what you're doing, right?
(Ji Hyo understands the rules
very well today.)
I expect something nice, Ji Hyo.
- I'll show you the placement.
- Okay.
This is how Ji Hyo placed everyone.
Okay.
- Ji Hyo...
- Okay.
- In the first room...
- understood the rules.
- The person to get the badge...
- This is hard.
in the first room is...
Park Ji Hyun.
Ji Hyun is in a higher grade.
In the second room,
it's Kim Sung Cheol.
(Promotion)
In the third room, it's Jeon So Min.
In the fourth room,
it's Song Ji Hyo.
(Promotion)
- Hold on.
- We were fooled.
(Ji Hyun, Sung Cheol, So Min,
and Ji Hyo get promoted.)
- They are in a higher grade?
- Hold on.
We don't know if they're
in a higher grade.
There could've been eliminations
because they overlapped.
That's possible too.
- Hold on. Wait a minute.
- Ji Hyun is in a high grade.
You will use the badges
during the race.
It doesn't change your grade
right now.
Please put it on.
I guess So Min got a lot right.
I can't believe this happened.
I got bad grades
when I was a student.
- We'll move on to the next mission.
- Okay.
I think our guests definitely got
better scores than us.
Did you guys cook here?
They must've cooked.
- What is this?
- Soy sauce marinated crabs.
- It looks delicious.
- This looks amazing.
- It's acorn jelly.
- I love acorn jelly.
- Are you letting us just eat it?
- This looks delicious.
- Can we just eat it?
Why? What did we do to deserve it?
Do you just like us?
Are you just giving it to us?
- They must be taking dishes away.
- Before the final race,
this is the final mission.
We're in second period.
We're going to test your sense of
beat and rhythm for a chance to eat.
We're going to play
Break Up Strawberries.
- Break Up Strawberries?
What are we breaking up this time?
Using the word "Strawberry",
you're going to break it up
according to the beat.
- St-raw-ber-ry
- For one, it's...
- For two, it's...
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- For three, it's...
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
For four,
it's "Strawberry-strawberry
strawberry-strawberry".
- St-raw-ber-ry
- Strawberry-strawberry
(Song Ji Hyo, a student at the music
school, lacks a sense of rhythm)
St-raw-ber-ry
(Guys...)
Show me.
(Ji Hyo's hopeless.)
- St-raw... Strawberry.
- Someone who's good should show us.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Everyone.
Every time you get one wrong,
you must give up one dish.
- What?
- You must return it when you lose.
Gosh, Jae Suk is bad at this.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- We'll start with Suk Jin.
- I'll start.
- Let's go! Let's do this!
- We'll start with Suk Jin.
- Let's cheer before we start.
- Do three no matter what.
Let's cheer before we start. One...
- 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
Let's go!
We should go after Ji Hyo.
Okay. I understand.
Right? That member is bad, right?
- Suk Jin too.
- Get ready.
- Suk Jin.
- We're starting.
- Jae Suk.
- Let's go!
- Ready, set, go.
- Let's cheer before we start.
Let's cheer before we start.
(Team Green is giving Ji Hyo
a last-minute lesson.)
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Strawberry-strawberry, It's three.
- Get ready.
- We're starting.
- Ready,
- Attack.
set, go.
- Break up strawberries
Sung Cheol, three.
(Happy)
(Sung Cheol fell victim to
Team Orange's plan.)
- Sung Cheol.
- This is really hard.
Please return one
of your side dishes.
- The soy sauce.
The soy sauce.
- Where should I put it?
- I'll do it.
Let's go!
(Kwang Soo ran over
to help them return the side dish.)
I'll do it.
Let's go!
Our referees will collect it.
(He got up, but the referee came,
so he wasn't helpful.)
Kwang Soo, you shouldn't wander
around during a shoot.
Do I start now?
(At a loss for words)
(He is always waiting for a chance
to attack Kwang Soo.)
- Team Blue will start.
- Okay.
- Break up strawberries
- Kwang Soo, four.
- Strawberry-strawberry-...
strawberry-strawberry
Jae Suk, three.
(His fist lost track
of the rhythm already.)
Break up strawberries
(Flustered)
(He was flustered and suddenly
sang about strawberries.)
Hey!
Focus.
If it's Kwang Soo's turn, he's bound
to go after you.
It's either you or me.
- Try not to go after Jae Suk.
- My gosh.
- Jae Suk is...
- Gosh, I feel refreshed.
I feel refreshed!
Well done. Nice shot!
Let's take out the soy sauce.
- Take out the soy sauce.
Take it.
We're going to go after Jae Suk,
so take out the acorn jelly too.
Look.
- St-raw-ber-ry
- I got it.
- What comes after?
Strawberry-strawberry-strawberry-
strawberry. This is four.
Strawberry-strawberry-
strawberry-strawberry
- Strawberry-strawberry
- Is Suk Jin teaching him?
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Try three.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- That's right. He's good now.
- I got it now.
Set, go.
- Break up strawberries
- Kwang Soo, three.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- So Min, four.
- Strawberry-strawberry-...
strawberry-strawberry
- Ji Hyo, one.
- St-raw-ber-ry
- So Min, two.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
(Straw-berry-straw-berry)
- What was that?
- She did a good job.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- I did it right.
- No, you didn't!
- What was that?
- It was right.
No.
That sounded more like three.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Hold on.
- I'm happy because this happened...
- after she acted like she was good.
- You made a fool of yourself!
How much more exact
did I have to be?
Straw-berry-straw-berry
- See? It's right.
- What kind of game are you playing?
- You made a fool of yourself.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Take one out. What will it be?
(Staring)
I'm so sorry.
Don't you feel sorry to us?
Take one out. What will it be?
We'll take out the ssamjang.
You can't remove just that one.
(This whole thing is a set.)
- You can't remove just that one.
- It's a set.
- Eun Bin plays dirty too.
- Eun Bin...
She's also a bit...
- She doesn't play nicely.
- She doesn't.
- Let's take this one out.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
So Min, be strategical.
Okay.
- Hey.
- I'm going to get it this time.
- Break up strawberries
Jae Suk, three.
(She calls on
Jae Suk strategically.)
- I'm going to get it this time.
- Break up strawberries
(Nervous)
Jae Suk, three.
Strawberry-strawberry-
strawberry-strawberry
(It's 3, but he did 4.)
Strawberry, strawberry,
strawberry, strawberry
(Yoo Jae Suk, Bad at strawberry
games, Gets it wrong every time)
Why is he so bad at games
involving strawberries?
- He's bad at strawberry games.
- Don't be so nervous.
- This is driving me crazy.
He's nervous.
If I get it wrong again,
just beat me up.
Take out the acorn jelly.
- Take it out. We won't eat it.
- How many times is this?
- Hold on.
- We won't have the acorn jelly.
- Try three again.
- You should've given the lettuce.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Good.
That's right. I'm good at practices.
- You'd be good if you were calm.
- He's too nervous.
Are you afraid of strawberries?
- This is how I was as a rookie.
- Prepare yourself at every round.
- You will be chosen every round.
- Okay.
I'll go. Ready, start.
- Break up strawberries
- Ji Hyun, two.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
Strawberry, four.
- What was that?
(She got it right,)
(but she failed to attack.)
- What was that?
- She did such a good job too.
- You need to attack.
Ji Hyun, who's Strawberry Four?
- What did she say?
- She couldn't attack.
What did she say?
She just said Strawberry, four.
Who is that?
- What's she saying?
- Is someone named Strawberry?
- Who's Strawberry?
Does anyone have the nickname
Strawberry?
- Strawberry, four.
- Strawberry.
Do we have a spy today?
I kept thinking about
saying strawberry.
She kept thinking about strawberry.
- Just think about Jae Suk, two.
- Okay.
- If you do that, it's over.
- Isn't this wrong?
- They have to take something out.
- They do.
- Let's take out the acorn jelly.
- Let's do that.
Since we took out the soy sauce,
we'll take out the acorn jelly.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- We have the main dishes.
- What is it? Strawberry-strawberry
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- St-raw-ber-ry
- Strawberry, for 2 and 3,
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
I got it down perfectly this time.
- I will do it perfectly this time.
- Ready, go!
- Break up strawberries
Eun Bin, three.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Jae Suk, two.
- Strawberry-strawberry
(Strawberry-strawberry)
(His hands were resting after
his turn.)
(He got it wrong right away.)
(Get over here.)
It was like he was attacked.
- Hear me out.
- Grab him.
Get him.
Kick him.
- I mean...
- Just watch.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
Isn't this right?
Why can't you do that
during the game then?
Here. Take one of his legs.
- Actually, lay him on the floor.
- Hey.
- You need to be taught a lesson.
- Hold on.
(Trembling)
Let go of him.
Get a grip on yourself!
(The split wakes him up good.)
Get a grip on yourself.
- Why...
- He must've dreaded his turn.
- Unbelievable.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- I got it now.
- Exactly.
- Don't tense up.
- I won't.
Always think that it's your turn.
I was like this in my rookie days.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Let's practice.
Jae Suk, three.
Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(His gesture is wrong too.)
- Jae Suk, three.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(He failed to tap his thighs.)
- Right?
- Tap your thighs first.
- Tap here.
- Hold on.
Tap... Hold on.
Tap here.
(His thighs get smashed.)
Tap your thighs first.
Got it?
(The terrorizing Jong Kook
gives a lesson he'll never forget.)
- Tap your thighs first.
- Got it.
- I will.
- Tap your thighs first.
- I got it.
- Unbelievable.
Okay, I won't forget that.
That'll help you
stay within the beat.
Let's practice once more.
- Jae Suk, four.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
(He chanted the 3-beat
instead of the 4-beat.)
You need to say "strawberry"
four times.
- Okay, got it.
- What's with your fingers though?
- What's this?
- Don't you dare chime in.
- What are you trying to say?
- Don't you dare speak.
Is it a white flag or a blue flag?
- Like and dislike.
- What?
Like and dislike.
Unbelievable.
- Let's give up the lettuce.
- Sure thing. It's useless.
What about the dried laver?
Okay, that could go next.
The doenjang stew is cold now, so...
- I'm sorry, but...
- Sounds good.
Did you taste the food?
- Who ate the food?
- What on earth?
- What...
- You actually ate it?
- Eun Bin, really?
- What do you think you're doing?
Here.
(She takes a bite.)
Is it good?
I don't get it though because
no one knows that we ate it.
(She shares how she cheats
as if it's a clever skill.)
I'm sorry,
but did you taste the food?
- Who ate the food?
- What on earth?
- What...
- You actually ate it?
- Eun Bin, really?
- What do you think you're doing?
You should give one up.
I get why So Min did it, but
I didn't expect this from Eun Bin.
- What?
- You corrupted her.
I'm regretting liking you
in "Hot Stove League".
Let's go again.
- All right.
- Let's do this.
Ready, set, go.
- Break up strawberries
Se Chan, four.
Strawberry-strawberry-
strawberry-strawberry
- Jae Suk, two.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Se Chan, three.
- Strawberry-strawberry... Gosh.
Nice!
Strawberry-strawberry... Gosh.
(Jae Suk manages to score
for the first time.)
All right!
- See?
- Nicely done.
- You can do it, you know.
- What did I tell you?
He's actually gotten better.
- I had no idea he'd manage this.
- He's actually gotten better.
- Sometimes, a beating is required.
- That was nice.
I have a feeling
that Jae Suk will be able...
to return my attack.
- You...
- You can be sharper.
Think more about
how you'll manage his attack.
I can't believe
it's Ji Hyo saying this.
She's not bad at this, that's why.
Se Chan can take it once,
but not twice.
- Not twice.
- Yes, I can see that.
Please give up a dish.
- Let's give this up.
- Jae Suk's back in the game.
I know.
- I can do this game perfectly now.
- As irony would have it...
The chemistry...
(Se Chan's on the offensive next.)
- Attack Jae Suk again.
- St-raw-ber-ry
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
- Let's go again.
- Strawberry...
- I'll go with Jae Suk first.
- Break up strawberries
- Jae Suk, three.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Se Chan, four.
- Strawberry-strawberry-...
strawberry-strawberry
Jae Suk, two.
Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Se Chan, four.
- Strawberry-strawberry-...
strawberry-strawberry
Haha, two.
Strawberry-strawberry
(The blitz attack
makes him say it on beat.)
Jae Suk, that was a long battle.
- What a long battle.
- Nice!
- We did it.
- What a long battle.
Nice!
- That was awesome.
- Jae Suk,
that was a long battle.
- Strawberry-strawberry
- It went back and forth.
- Okay.
- Why make it sound so cute though?
- Please hand in a dish.
- Okay, got it.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Go, go.
- A beating from Jong Kook...
- It wakes you up, doesn't it?
- Jae Suk.
- It woke you up.
- You're way better now.
I'm someone who needs a beating.
- You're perfect at this now.
- I know.
Beatings work for those old.
Is it my turn then?
- Ji Hyo will go first.
- Right.
- Break up strawberries
- Jae Suk, two.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- Ji Hyun, three.
- Straw-berry-strawberry-strawberry
- Min Jae, one.
- St-raw-ber-ry
- He's so good at that.
- Ji Hyun, one.
St-raw-ber-ry
- Suk Jin, two.
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
(His hands weren't on point.)
(He creates a new beat
by being off-beat.)
Did you see that?
- What was that?
- I mean...
Didn't it remind you
of this catchphrase?
- This.
- Hold on.
You were off to a good start.
- The beat was just wrong.
- What on earth was that?
- Straw-berry...
- Straw-berry-straw-berry
- What on earth was that?
- What's with the tongue?
What was the reason for that?
(Thanks to Suk Jin,
Team Green earns another point.)
That's too bad.
I know I could've won this round.
Once again,
Team Green is the winner.
They keep winning.
We'll warm up the food for you.
That's too bad.
It really was a close game.
- We could've won.
- I know.
- Two?
- Yes.
You can ask one from each team.
Why don't we ask this person?
Eun Bin and Jae Suk.
Right, Jae Suk.
We'll ask Eun Bin from Team Blue...
and Jae Suk from Team Orange.
(They'll check the grades
of Jae Suk and Eun Bin.)
This will probably reveal
the answer. Let's write it down.
Eun Bin is...
- in fourth grade.
- Okay.
- Really?
(Running Man Music Test)
(Eun Bin received a high score
which put her in 4th grade.)
(Eun Bin's in 4th grade?)
(Ji Hyun was promoted because
Suk Jin is also in 4th grade.)
- Then Suk Jin is in fourth grade.
- Right.
(Running Man Music Test)
(Suk Jin's in 4th grade
with 37.5 points.)
And Jae Suk...
(Jae Suk...)
- He's in first grade.
- What?
- That kid!
- Hold on.
- Really?
- Are you kidding me?
You're in first grade?
I'll probably be top of the class.
(Jae Suk bragged
about getting a high score.)
(But in reality, he only scored 15.)
- Seriously?
- You were bluffing!
You got most of
the questions wrong.
You told me that
you had a high score.
First grade?
- You said you scored higher.
- Oh, dear.
First grade?
- He...
- Consider yourself dead.
First grade?
Our grades have
mostly been revealed.
(1st grade, 4th grade, 2nd grade)
- And Eun Bin's in 4th grade.
- Mine's been revealed too.
Gosh, that's awesome.
(Eun Bin received the top score
with 57.5 points.)
This time,
Kwang Soo will decide the groups.
- Okay!
- Kwang Soo...
He only thinks of himself, you know.
(It's the last opportunity
for a promotion.)
(How will Kwang Soo
sort out the groups?)
What matters the most
is my promotion.
How the others do
is none of my business.
In order to figure out
their grades though...
(He places himself
with Jae Suk and Haha.)
- Kwang Soo?
- Yes, I'm done.
Just like last time,
the ones at the top...
will receive the Promotion Badge.
- Hold on.
- What happened?
No way.
Kwang Soo got promoted?
- Out of those three...
- Kwang Soo?
He's in third grade then.
- He's in 3rd grade then.
- Yes, 3rd grade.
- Kwang Soo's in third grade then.
- You're right.
- He's in third grade then.
- We figured it out.
We figured out his grade.
Kwang Soo's in third grade.
(1st grade, 2nd grade, 3rd grade)
(Promoted)
Then So Min's in 4th grade.
- I'm sure of it.
- Kwang Soo's in third grade.
(2nd grade)
(Promoted)
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyun,
Eun Bin, Sung Cheol,
- you all get a badge.
- Got it.
Can we eat now?
We'll get together after we eat.
Thank you for the meal.
I can't believe
my grade was revealed.
- It's now time for the final race.
- Right.
This is The Sole Winner,
the chance to be the sole winner
at Brahms Music School.
(The Sole Winner)
The Name Tag Elimination
will take place for 30 minutes.
Out of those who survive,
the one with the highest grade
will win.
(The one person
with the highest grade will win.)
(Two or more with the same grade
will not be eligible to win.)
You're eliminated for good...
when your name tag gets ripped off
as a first grader.
- If I lose it as a 3rd grader...
- You'll become a 2nd grader.
- That means Jae Suk...
- Then we have an extra life.
- I mean...
- Then if Jae Suk...
- loses his name tag...
- How can first graders survive?
Jae Suk is mine.
(Jae Suk is mine.)
You can only take off the name tag
of a person...
in the same grade as you
or in a lower grade.
The person who took off a name tag
gets to be promoted,
and the person who lost a name tag
gets demoted to a lower grade.
But if you remove the name tag of
someone in a higher grade than you,
you get demoted to a lower grade.
Oh, we get demoted?
However, you can form an alliance
with others.
If you hold hands together,
your grades will be tallied.
You can eliminate others
in the same or lower grades.
What's important is that only
the person who removed a name tag...
can move up to a higher grade.
Likewise, if you ally with someone
else and remove the name tag...
of a person in a higher grade,
only you will be demoted.
Even if you formed an alliance.
Then some of us will probably
attack others as a group,
and then attack their allies too.
- That's possible.
- Can I...
drag my partner around?
(Can I drag my partner around?)
Can I drag him around
in a lying position?
Yes, you can.
- There won't be a problem, right?
- If I drag him around...
What does the Promotion Badge do?
You will move up to higher grade
according to the number...
of the badges you have
before we begin the race.
- I see.
- Ji Hyun has two.
(Ji Hyun moves up from 3rd
to 5th grade as she has 2 badges.)
Also, there are Up and Down Rooms
here and there, which open randomly.
Only the first one to find it
can use it.
- Oh, I see.
- They will open randomly.
Right. Those are our last hope.
Do you think we can enter
any of the Up and Down Rooms?
- You think we have enough time?
- I know.
- No one will pair up with Jae Suk.
- This is frustrating.
- He must be lonely.
- You'll be alone.
- It'll be a lonely fight.
- This is driving me insane.
Please move to your starting place.
Jae Suk is mine, everyone.
(The result of the music test
will be revealed.)
The result came out.
We'll reveal the result to you.
Don't share it with others.
(Suk Jin in 4th grade, Eun Bin
in 5th grade, So Min in 5th grade)
We graded you fairly.
We won't receive any inquiries
about the test result.
That's great.
- My gosh. Today is my lucky day.
- Oh, gosh.
- I can't believe this.
- Nice.
(1st: Jae Suk, Min Jae, 2nd:
Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Haha, Se Chan)
(4th: Kwang Soo, Suk Jin)
(5th: Ji Hyun, Sung Cheol,
Eun Bin, So Min)
You're in second grade now, right?
I'm in third grade, you brat.
- You moved up?
- Of course.
(They're lying to each other
from the beginning.)
Did you say you're in 4th grade?
You're in 3rd grade now.
- I'm in 5th grade.
- Oh, I see.
- I'm not asking for a high-five.
- You're in 3rd grade now.
(She gave him a high-five
as he revealed his grade.)
What can we do when we can't
even communicate with each other?
Why did you hit my hand?
Hey, then were you
a fourth grader?
Yes, I was. How many times
should I tell you?
(Brazen)
That can't be right
as far as I know.
You'll see.
I wrote down what I found out.
I'm in 5th grade.
So Min is in 5th grade.
I can stay in the race
until I lose my name tag five times.
(Jeon So Min, fifth grade)
Sung Cheol is in 5th grade.
Ji Hyun is in 5th grade.
I'm going to attack...
(Kim Sung Cheol, fifth grade)
whomever I run into.
I'm a fifth grader.
(She looks relaxed.)
Suk Jin is in fourth grade.
Kwang Soo is in fourth grade.
I'm planning to let Jae Suk
tag along with me as my assistant.
Petty Gang is back.
He'll be my right-hand man.
- You'll ally with him?
- Yes, I'll ally with him.
From the moment she gave me
a high-five,
I only thought of sending her
to jail so she can rest.
You're unusually confident today.
It's because...
(Lee Kwang Soo, fourth grade)
As I told you earlier,
I studied music as a little boy.
I learned to play the piano
and other types of...
musical instrument
including the violin.
Jong Kook is in second grade.
Rather than forming an alliance,
I should eliminate them...
and use their power to...
Se Chan is in second grade.
And don't ally with So Min.
- She'll definitely betray you.
- I understand.
So Min and Kwang Soo
are dangerous.
Ji Hyo is in second grade.
You know that the Up and Down Rooms
will open later, right?
I know the rules.
Up and Down Rooms?
I missed that part.
You can worry about it
when you enter it.
Haha is in second grade.
It will be pointless
to ally with lower graders.
That's what only Petty Gang
would do.
The only way I can survive is...
to ally with a person
in a higher grade.
Because I'm in first grade,
I have no confidence.
But I will show you how I go up
from the last to the first place.
Now, the race will begin.
I really hope
I can make that happen.
"The race starts."
The race starts.
Oh, gosh.
(Jae Suk starts looking for
someone to ally with.)
(He found Eun Bin,
the fifth grader.)
- Eun Bin.
- Shall I come to you?
- You're in first grade, right?
- Eun Bin, I think...
- Oh, no.
(At that moment,
Kwang Soo showed up!)
(If those small fish join forces,
things will get complicated.)
(Kwang Soo said he would
hunt for small fish.)
(He started running
when he saw Jae Suk.)
(The small fish hunting has begun!)
(Jae Suk will be out
if he loses his name tag.)
Hey. Wait.
Wait. Hold on.
(Jae Suk allied with
Se Chan and So Min.)
- Hey.
- What's going on?
Se Chan.
- Kwang Soo, take off his name tag.
- Kwang Soo, hold him.
(Kwang Soo makes
a strategic retreat.)
So Min, let's go and help Jae Suk.
Hurry up.
(They start chasing Kwang Soo
right away.)
Go back. Too many are
coming down here.
- Too many are coming down.
- Let's go.
(Urgent)
- Come join us.
- Let's form an alliance.
- The three of us?
- We'll be invincible.
- Really?
- We'll be...
- in 15th grade.
- Now, we're in 15th grade.
- Let's say it. We're in 15th grade.
- We're in 15th grade.
- Okay.
- Let's go downstairs.
Let's get them all.
(The 15th graders
got into action right away!)
Take off his name tag. Come on.
- I'm holding your hand.
- Take that off.
- Wait. Let me think.
- Take it off.
They're in 4th, 5th, 1st,
and 2nd grade. Take it off.
Someone is coming.
(Haha heard the commotion
and came.)
- He's in first grade. Take it off.
- Let's join forces.
- Eun Bin, hold my hand.
- Hurry up.
- Hold my hand.
(We shouldn't ally with them.)
- Take off his name tag.
- Haha.
- What are you doing?
- What?
(The unexpected peace treaty)
- Why did you hold Kwang Soo's hand?
- I'm stuck.
I didn't mean to...
I'm stuck here.
- But...
- Eun Bin... Wait. No, wait.
- Why are you...
- Jae Suk.
No, don't let go.
- Let go.
- Hold on.
- Jae Suk.
Hey, Jae Suk is...
(Taking off the name tag)
Gosh.
(His name tag was removed!)
- Gosh.
- I removed his name tag.
- I removed 1 of his name tags.
- Kwang Soo took 1.
(As the 4th grader, Kwang Soo
eliminated the 2nd grader Haha.)
Kwang Soo gets promoted,
and Haha gets demoted.
- Wait.
- Can we remove their name tags now?
- Yes, you can.
- Stop. Don't do that.
- Don't take it off.
- I should avoid them.
I need to find
the Up and Down Rooms first.
But there are too many people
up there.
Seriously...
The Up and Down Rooms are open now.
(The Up and Down Rooms where they
can get promoted are open now.)
Where are the Up and Down Rooms?
We have to find
the Up and Down Rooms.
Is there an Up and Down Room there?
This is crazy. I really need to
find an Up and Down Room.
Oh, gosh. What is it?
(He must find it
before the others do.)
I found an Up and Down Room.
(He found an Up and Down Room!)
(The first grader Kim Min Jae
got into the booth.)
Where is it? Okay.
(He's checking the mission
that he has to do in the booth.)
Next. There.
First, choose one person
you want to promote or demote.
Next, write down your name
and someone else's on three balls,
and put the balls in the Up Box
or the Down Box.
You will pick one ball by yourself,
which will decide the person
to be promoted or demoted.
For example, if you want to
get promoted,
(If you pick your name,
you'll be promoted.)
Write down someone else's name
on 1 of the 3 balls,
and write down your name
on the rest 2 balls.
Next, put the balls in the Up Box.
If you pick a ball with your name
on it, you'll get promoted.
(Promoted to 2nd grade)
I can write down my name
on two balls, right?
I'll write down Eun Bin's name
on one ball.
I'll write my name on another ball.
So there's a better chance
that I'll pick my name.
Now, I'm putting the balls
in the Up Box.
(Min Jae is mixing the balls
unlike the cast of Running Man.)
Please let me get promoted.
Okay.
(2 balls with his name on them
and 1 with Eun Bin's name on it)
(Which one of them
will be promoted?)
Okay.
(He picked one ball.)
How could I pick this one?
(Eun Bin)
How could this happen?
(Eun Bin?)
(I'm done for.)
Does that mean
this person will be promoted?
Gosh, seriously.
(Eun Bin is promoted
thanks to him.)
Let's go together.
We're invincible.
Let's go inside.
Okay. Let's go.
This is crazy.
How dare you?
(Glancing)
Why? I wasn't doing anything.
- I won't take off your name tag.
- She's holding...
- I won't take it off.
- Hey.
- I'm just checking.
- Let go of my hand.
- Haha.
- We're holding hands together.
Haha, let go of my hand
just for a moment. I'm hot.
- It's too hot. That's all.
- Let's abandon him.
(Se Chan got caught.)
So Min, you're
a fifth grader now, right?
10th grade...
And you're in 1st grade, right?
(He got the message.)
- No.
- What do you mean?
- No. Don't betray me.
- Haha.
- No.
- Why?
- Don't do that.
- What? I wasn't doing anything.
- Don't let go of my hand.
- Haha, let go.
- Let go of Eun Bin.
- No!
- So Min.
- You're so mean.
I came on a variety show
after a long time.
- I know.
- You'll be on another show.
One show wouldn't be a problem.
- No.
- One show wouldn't be a problem.
Hold on. I...
- Let me catch my breath.
- Okay.
- Before I stand up...
- Wait. How could you...
(They changed the target!)
Eun Bin, get up.
- Come on. Get up.
- I... I got him.
Hey, don't...
(He lost his name tag in a blink.)
- Eun Bin, get up.
- Hey!
Can I just get up?
- I am out.
- Let's summarize.
(Wasn't Haha a 1st grader?)
- I am out.
- Don't lie.
- I was a first grader.
I was a first grader.
Haha is out.
- My goodness.
- Haha is out.
(Haha's name tag got removed
in 1st grade, so he is out.)
- Se Chan,
- Did I move up a grade?
you moved up a grade.
- Let's go, Eun Bin.
- What?
That little...
(Haha was discarded in cold blood.)
Gosh, I am so annoyed.
How did this happen?
Give me that.
(Even an eliminated student
gets a mission.)
It's an important mission.
(An important mission?)
Let's go.
Hold on!
- Who is that?
(Haha reappears
with an important mission!)
- Hold on.
- What's going on?
Haha.
- Were you given a role?
- Was it the Up and Down Room?
- You are very curious, right?
- Yes.
- What's your role?
- Take a look at this.
- What is it?
(Which important mission
did he take on?)
(The status board
of the current members?)
"The number of members per grade"?
I see.
- The sixth grade.
- You managed to survive.
Who are the first graders?
One of them must be Jae Suk.
Who is the other one?
- Min Jae. Where is Min Jae?
- Min Jae.
You are right. Where is Min Jae?
- I haven't seen him around.
- He must be hiding.
- What is he doing?
- Shall we go and take him out?
Shall we go and find Min Jae?
- Let's go and find Min Jae.
- Okay.
Someone's name tag got ripped off.
(He is having a lonely fight.)
Is Haha out?
- Are you a fourth grader?
- Yes.
Then our combined grade is 10.
- 10.
- I am in the middle.
If one of you...
You know the Electricity Game,
right?
- If one of you...
- I will stand in the middle...
- so that it doesn't happen.
- Hold on.
If one of you squeezes my hand
to send me a sign,
I can attack right away.
There is no reason for us
to turn against each other.
Let's not do that.
(So Min feels the squeeze
as soon as they finish talking.)
Kwang Soo.
Give me your hand.
(It's like the calm
before the storm.)
- Come on. Don't be like that.
- So Min.
What's the use of ripping
each other's name tag?
What's the use of moving up
a grade?
Hold on.
(They talk of trusting each other,
but uncomfortable silence ensues.)
This is driving me crazy.
Come here.
Let's go someplace quiet.
(They move to someplace quiet
to take someone out.)
This is like...
the Mafia Game.
- We are close...
- I am feeling the squeeze.
- to having a ruckus break out.
- Seriously.
In order to survive,
- you can either stay still...
- Yes.
or rip off someone's name tag.
All right.
Did everyone send a signal?
This is my signal.
All right.
(Squeezing)
By the way,
both of you are giving me a squeeze.
Hey.
(The signals of betrayal are
all over the place.)
Hey. I thought you gave me a signal.
Stop sending him a signal.
All right.
1, 2,
(They try
the Electricity Game again.)
three. Let go.
(They twist Se Chan's arms
so that he wouldn't run away.)
- No.
- They are coming!
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyun, and Min Jae
appear!)
Hold on. Hold on.
We can't win against them.
- Hold on.
- We can't win against them.
I got him.
Kwang Soo, cut ties with them.
Cut ties with them.
- Do it.
- No, no.
- No.
- Cut ties with them.
We won't survive without you.
You were struggling before.
(Should I cut ties or not?)
Hold on.
Why are you doing this to me?
(Jong Kook goes after Se Chan.)
Rip off Se Chan's name tag.
Okay.
(He removed Se Chan's name tag!)
(The moment
his name tag got ripped off,)
(Kwang Soo let go
of Se Chan's hand!)
- Let's summarize.
- Their grades are too high.
- My grade isn't that high.
Jong Kook's grade is too high.
- Their grades are too high.
- No, my grade isn't that high.
Please put this back on.
(This is ridiculous.)
Why do you guys betray each other?
- Don't hang out with Kwang Soo.
- No, no.
- I didn't start this.
- Se Chan, don't...
- Really?
- They are just like me.
- The three of you should scatter.
- Let's scatter.
We are in a pretty good place.
Our combined grade is 10.
That this rate,
Jong Kook will win again.
- We shouldn't fight.
- Let's not do that.
- We lost because we fought.
I won't do it.
Let's not betray each other.
Okay. Keep your promise.
- Okay.
- 20 minutes remain.
There is a time limit too.
(Se Chan sends So Min a signal.)
I didn't do anything!
You little...
(A war breaks out.)
Stop it.
So Min. So Min.
I am sorry.
(A betrayal after a betrayal)
- So Min.
- I am holding his hand.
- You two, make up.
(The trio can't trust each other.)
Let's hold hands again.
My arms are about to fall off!
Let's just...
I am sorry, but please get us
a small room.
We will put an end to this.
It won't end.
All right. We're done.
I need to survive no matter what.
I will show you.
If I enter the Up and Down Room
and become a second grader,
anything could happen.
(I will move up a grade
no matter what!)
- All right.
- You know,
a 6th grader doesn't need to stay
a 6th grader.
We could rip off
a sixth grader's name tag.
- That's right.
- We could do that.
Do you want to see the status board?
- Yes!
- Yes, we do.
- Do you want to see it?
- Yes!
(Haha appears
with the status board.)
Let's see it.
The fifth grade is...
The fifth grader will win
at this rate.
(Only 1 person is in 5th grade.)
Hold on. Hold on.
To be honest...
Hold on. Please listen to me.
Shall we take them on?
(Provoking)
- Let's do that.
- Right now?
- Hold on.
- So Min.
- It's not a good idea.
- Is our combined grade higher?
- Yes, it is.
Then Kwang Soo should attack.
- Okay. Let's do it.
- Kwang Soo.
Hold on. Stay still.
It's okay even if your name tag
gets ripped off.
- Our combined grade is higher.
- It's okay even if it happens.
- You are right.
It's okay even if your name tag
gets ripped off.
(Certain that their combined grade
is higher, the 6 members attack.)
So Min, why did you hold her hand?
(At that moment,)
(So Min suddenly betrays her group.)
- We can still win.
- No, no.
- Can we attack?
- We aren't sure.
- Hold on.
- Should we go ahead and attack?
(Sung Cheol goes ahead and attacks.)
- No, no.
- Should we go ahead and attack?
- Should we try it?
- Hold hands.
- No, no.
(He can't finish the attack
because he is unsure.)
- Should we try it?
- Their combined grade is lower.
- I think we can win.
- No, no.
- We need to attack now.
- Really?
- You...
- Okay.
- Hold on.
- Where are you going?
- I am staying here.
Let go of my hand, you fool.
(His voice shakes terribly.)
- What is up with you?
- Why are you so excited?
Suk Jin must be in first grade.
- Me? Think that I am in 1st grade.
- He isn't in 1st grade.
Should I rip off
Suk Jin's name tag?
Sung Cheol and Eun Bin's grade
is too high.
Their combined grade alone is 12.
- Is it 12?
- Hold on.
- Shall we scatter?
- Shall we do that?
- Let's do the calculations first.
- Let's scatter.
- There are too many people.
- Go.
- Isn't our combined grade higher?
- I don't think so.
- No.
Sung Cheol and Eun Bin's grade
is too high.
- I am sorry.
- They are coming!
(At that moment)
Hold on.
It's okay.
They held hands.
They held hands again.
This won't do.
(Suk Jin attacks Se Chan.)
I did it.
(He succeeded to rip off
the name tag.)
- I did it.
- Wait.
- The result...
- My name tag got ripped off.
Kwang Soo didn't let go.
He didn't let go.
Suk Jin, you moved up a grade.
Really?
(Suk Jin becomes a 4th grader,
and Se Chan becomes a 1st grader.)
- Is his grade higher?
- Okay. I will put it back on.
We can attack them
as a group again, right?
- In that case...
- I am going to leave.
Can we rip their name tag off?
- Here...
- Let's resume right away.
Se Chan left. Se Chan left.
- Se Chan left. Se Chan left.
- Let's rip off Min Jae's name tag.
Let's rip off Min Jae's name tag.
- Hold on!
- Let's rip off Min Jae's name tag.
- I don't want to get eliminated.
- Don't do it.
Hold on. Hold on. Let's talk.
- Hold on.
- Hold on. Hold on. Let's talk.
Listen to what I have to say.
- I...
- What is it?
What is it?
(His name tag gets ripped off!)
(HIs name tag got ripped off
before Kwang Soo held his hand.)
- That's good.
- His name tag got ripped off.
- Is he out?
- Sung Cheol ripped it, right?
- I was a 1st grader.
- Were you a 1st grader?
- Really?
- Does that mean you are out?
- I was a first grader.
- I told you not to do it.
- I told you to listen to me.
- I didn't know.
Why did you have to rip off
my name tag?
For goodness' sake.
Now...
- We will leave.
- Go ahead.
- What's your grade?
- 5... 4th grade.
- Are you in fourth grade?
- Yes.
- You are in third grade, right?
- Yes, I am.
If I rip off your name tag,
I will be a fifth grader.
(Kwang Soo attacks her.)
You can't rip off my name tag.
(If Ji Hyun is in 4th grade
and Kwang Soo is in 3rd grade,)
(Kwang Soo will move down a grade
upon ripping off her name tag.)
Is it okay for you to do that?
Aren't you in third grade?
(Why did he rip off her name tag
if he is in 3rd grade?)
I guess he isn't in third grade.
Kwang Soo.
(Isn't Kwang Soo in 3rd grade?)
You moved up a grade.
I am sorry, Ji Hyun.
Let's go.
(Ji Hyun moves down a grade.)
I am sorry, Ji Hyun.
(He means it.)
Where is the Up and Down Room?
I don't think this will end
anytime soon.
(So Min spots Haha
with the status board.)
It will take some time.
(She uses her cell phone
to zoom in on the status board.)
It's Haha.
It will take some time.
Two sixth graders,
two fourth graders,
and two first graders.
(Upon checking the status board)
- It's So Min.
- Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
(Please team up with me.)
Hey, forget it.
You are a betrayer. Come here.
Hold on!
- Hold on.
- Done.
(He removed her name tag
without hesitation.)
(Jong Kook becomes a 6th grader
and So Min becomes a 1st grader.)
You are so mean.
- Okay, okay.
- You are so mean.
So Min, come here.
(He is an expert
in teaching people a lesson.)
What am I going to do?
I need to run away.
This became a game of wits.
What's your grade?
I will give you a consultation.
- You are in 5th grade, right?
- 6th grade.
- 6th grade?
- Yes.
You moved up too much.
Right? Right?
In order to make you win...
- Third graders have no chance.
- No? Why not?
It's most likely
that a fourth grader will win.
You should rip off
these two members' name tag.
(It's an on-point lesson.)
It's crystal clear.
The status changed.
Let's think of a way.
Sixth grade?
- That changed fast.
- No one is in fifth grade.
This is it. This is the way.
You should get betrayed.
So I should get my name tag
ripped off.
Get your name tag ripped off
and hide.
That's right!
(This customer is touched.)
- Good luck.
- Okay.
(Haha doubles as a counselor.)
Why are you alone?
(Sung Cheol and Ji Hyun show up.)
What's your grade?
Are you in sixth grade?
- Which grade are you in?
- Second grade.
- Take him out.
- It doesn't seem that way.
You can't avoid it. Fight him!
Fight him! Get a good shot!
(Jong Kook is planning to be
the final winner.)
Fight him! Fight him!
Ji Hyun, watch your hair.
(Jong Kook let Ji Hyun rip off
his name tag.)
Jong Kook, you moved down a grade.
(He moves down to the 5th grade
as he has planned.)
- This is driving me crazy.
- Ji Hyun, you moved up a grade.
Let's scatter.
(The timid 1st grader,
Jae Suk is hiding.)
(He runs away
upon hearing someone's footsteps.)
Jae Suk!
I won't rip off your name tag.
I don't need to do that.
- Really?
- Yes.
I don't need to do that.
There is only one fifth grader,
and it's Jong Kook.
- Which grade are you in?
- 4th grade. No, 3rd grade.
There are so many fourth graders.
I saw you walk around
while holding someone's hand.
I had teamed up with Ji Hyun.
I ripped off her name tag once.
You shouldn't do that
when you have a girlfriend.
What are you saying?
My girlfriend has nothing to do
with this.
I don't understand
what you are saying.
Hold on.
You shouldn't do that.
What are you saying?
- You were alone with Ji Hyun.
- Someone is coming.
Hey.
Kwang Soo.
(They move downstairs
upon hearing someone approach.)
The situation keeps changing.
- It's Se Chan.
- Jae Suk.
- Which grade are you in?
- First grade.
How about you?
I am in third grade.
Things became complicated.
It's a ruckus upstairs.
Se Chan, you moved up a grade
due to the Up and Down Room.
Me?
- You are in second grade.
- Hold on.
- Then Jae Suk is the only one.
(So Min picked Se Chan's ball
in the Up and Down Room.)
The status board is here.
- Min Jae.
- Min Jae, come here.
Min Jae, come here.
So many things changed.
There are two people in every grade.
This is giving me a headache.
(The number of members per grade)
You said you are in third grade,
but you aren't.
Why is no one in third grade?
(He got caught lying.)
- What happened?
- What is the meaning of this?
- Are you a ghost?
- What are you?
- Let's hold hands and talk.
- Are you a ghost?
No one is in third grade.
What happened?
(Tell me honestly.)
I don't know.
(He stops thinking.)
(He can't think of an excuse.)
- I mean...
- I forgot about my grade.
- Which grade are you in?
- My name tag got ripped off a lot.
This is...
I am in second grade.
- You are in second grade?
- Yes.
Hold on. Hold my hand. Listen.
Things will be interesting
if we team up.
If we rip off Jae Suk's name tag...
- What are you saying?
- I mean...
- It was just a discussion.
- Don't be like that.
There is no reason
for the three of us to argue.
- Let's move.
- I will keep updating the board.
Hold on. It looks like...
I am in the highest grade. Let go.
- What?
- Let go.
Are you in the highest grade?
Which grade are you in?
- He is in 2nd grade.
- I am in 2nd grade.
- He is in second grade too.
- If we team up,
our combined grade is higher.
I was joking around.
Don't joke around like that.
- Let's hold hands for a while.
- Seriously.
Okay.
This is driving me crazy.
(They move
with their hands held tight.)
I can't act rashly.
(Glancing over)
(Jae Suk tries to attack.)
Hey.
(Annoyed by the betrayal,
Kwang Soo strikes back.)
Hold on. Hold on.
(They grab each other's name tag
at the same time.)
(Se Chan is holding
Jae Suk's hand.)
Hold on.
(Jae Suk ripped off
Kwang Soo's name tag first!)
All right.
(Kwang Soo said he is in 2nd grade.)
(Then Jae Suk and Se Chan's
combined grade is higher.)
- Jae Suk, you are out.
- Why?
(Is Jae Suk out?)
- Jae Suk, you are out.
- We were holding hands.
- That's right.
- So?
Which grade are you in?
I didn't lie.
Kwang Soo, which grade are you in?
Don't ask, you punk.
He must be in sixth grade.
Are you in fifth grade?
(We were fooled again.)
I can't believe him.
Okay. Let's stay together for now.
I really am in fifth grade!
(It's nearly the end of the race.)
Come on.
Three...
What?
- We are doing you a favor.
- Why?
- What?
Either a 4th grader
or a 5th grader will win.
- Promise to share the prize.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Make sure you win.
- Let me change the status.
- Come on.
- You are so mean.
Sung Cheol, you are so mean.
- No! Don't do it!
- Come on.
- No!
- Hold her hand.
(The status changes rapidly
towards the end of the race.)
All right.
(The status changes rapidly
towards the end of the race.)
The race ends.
Please gather around.
As I explained earlier,
the only member
of the highest grade will win.
Sung Cheol is in sixth grade.
(He will win if there are
no other 6th graders.)
Eun Bin is in sixth grade.
My goodness.
Suk Jin is...
- in fifth grade.
- Okay.
- Why did you become a fifth grader?
- Seriously.
Jong Kook is in fifth grade.
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is...
- in fourth grade.
- I knew it.
- Yes!
- Kwang Soo will win.
Ji Hyo and Ji Hyun are
in third grade.
- Kwang Soo is the winner.
- Yes!
I can't believe it.
(Kwang Soo's strategy for victory)
I should get my name tag ripped off.
That's right.
Who will do it?
Who are they?
- Let's go.
Hold on. He wants
to get his name tag ripped off.
- Let go.
- Let go for a second.
Let go for a second.
What? What is up with him?
Let's go.
(He succeeded to move down
to 4th grade.)
- Which grade are you in?
- I am in second grade.
(Kwang Soo lied and said
that he is in 2nd grade.)
- Are you in second grade?
- Yes.
(He didn't want to move up
to 5th grade,)
(so he made Jae Suk rip off
his name tag!)
(It was Kwang Soo's strategy
to become the sole 4th grader.)
- Thank you, Suk Jin and Jae Suk.
- How did he keep it that way?
- How strange!
- Like I always say,
it's a good idea to take him out
in the beginning of the race.
- We shouldn't leave him behind.
Please bring in the prize
for the best student...
- from the music school.
- What is it?
Please let it be a xylophone.
A triangle.
- Please let it be a xylophone.
- I haven't won a prize in a while.
Please let it be a xylophone
or a recorder.
A pipe.
That's incredible.
Really?
- He will receive a turntable.
- It's nice.
- It's a good prize. It's pretty.
- It's really nice.
It's pretty.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's an antique.
The four members who were eliminated
will get a penalty.
- Bring in the penalty.
- I forgot about the penalty.
- There is a penalty.
Out of 4 sponges, 2 contain ink...
- and two contain water.
- Oh, no.
- Please.
- It's pretty visible.
- You can't change your choice.
- I choose this one.
- Number four.
(Haha picks the 4th one.)
So Min picked number two.
Min Jae.
- I pick number four.
- I can't tell.
You can't tell by looking.
2 sponges have water
and 2 sponges have...
- One,
- That's right. Hold it up.
two,
- three.
- Stamp your face.
Rub your face.
Get your face in there.
Keep going. There you go.
(Haha gets a sponge with water.)
(Min Jae gets
a sponge with water too.)
(In that case)
Keep going. There you go.
(So Min and Jae Suk get ink
on their faces.)
(How did the two of them get
those sponges?)
(It's a shocking look.)
My goodness.
- I can't believe it.
- This is the best.
The drama will start airing
tomorrow.
Please watch "Do You Like Brahms?".
- Thank you.
(Please Watch
"Do You Like Brahms?".)
We did it!
(Running Man Thief Race ended
with the thieves' victory.)
(Jae Suk, Haha, and Ji Hyo's
joint birthday party)
(Is there a copycat criminal?)
(They set out to catch a thief
who is aiming to steal a jewel.)
(Profiler, detective)
(Who are watching them?)
What?
(The real ones are here.)
I heard about the crime.
(The 1st profiler in Korea,
Pyo Chang Won)
I have experiences.
(The model of "The Outlaws",
Detective Yoon Seok Ho)
(The experts...)
(will catch the 2 thieves!)
(They will analyze...)
(and dig deep
for the interrogation!)
So here they are. There are so many.
(The moment you let your guard down,
the photos will remain.)
(A match of deductions will keep you
on your toes!)
(What will become of the thieves
who are aiming for the jewel?)
(Running Man Thief Race 2,
The Copycat Criminals)