(A theme park in Yongin,
full of spring)
- Hello.
- The weather suddenly became cold.
It's warm in here.
Kwang Soo's
life-sized figure is here.
- He's acting cool.
- My gosh.
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo.
- The life-sized figure...
You mean the figure, right?
- I did.
- It's his life-sized figure.
- Look at the figure of Kwang Soo.
- Gosh.
Look at the life-sized
figure of Kwang Soo.
- Suk Jin.
- What?
I like your outfit.
You're all dressed up today.
It looks very fancy.
Why do you have
tattoos on your arms?
What's wrong with your clothes?
- Why?
- What's with your clothes?
Mind your own business.
- Why?
- He's dressed up today.
He dressed carefully.
He really did.
He slurred the end of his sentence.
- What's wrong with my clothes?
- You should wear something...
that's age-appropriate for you.
What's wrong about this?
- Don't be intimidated.
- What's wrong about this?
(He shakes his fingers
feeling nervous.)
It looks very fancy.
- Look at him.
- Jae Suk.
You know this is
Park Saeroyi's hair.
- Gosh, no.
- Yang Saeroyi.
- Stop it.
Don't do that.
Is that the hair?
- My goodness.
- Yang Saeroyi.
Really?
What? What did he say?
- A character from "Itaewon Class".
- I see.
- Yang Saeroyi.
- Don't do that.
Is that the hair?
No, it's not like that.
My hair has always been like this.
And he had the same hair.
So it's "Dongducheon Class".
Stop it. Don't say that.
It's similar though. There are
a lot of foreigners in Dongducheon.
- My gosh.
- Why?
- You look nothing like him.
- Not even close.
Your face looks
totally different from his.
You should change it
a little next week.
- Yang Saeroyi.
- You should get a haircut.
Did So Min and Se Chan shoot
a TV commercial?
Really?
Yes.
- Congratulations.
- Buy us a meal.
- Of course I will.
Why did you not tell me?
I'm disappointed you didn't tell me.
What was the commercial about?
It's for the parcel service
of a convenience store.
Can I say this?
- A parcel service.
- Yes.
Even people in advertising know
that they are flirting.
Sure.
- They acknowledge it.
- Right.
- They admit it.
- It means they know that.
I can't say they accept it,
but they are interested.
That's right.
- It's a good thing.
- It felt strange...
as I took pictures with So Min.
Actually I think...
So what are we doing today?
We should be careful
with outdoor activities these days.
A lot of people feel bored
spending time at home.
That's true.
So today, we'd like to show
how to have fun at home.
It's called
Running Man Has Plans Race.
We should have plans.
We have two guests to join us today.
I asked the two guests
to bring something they can play...
with the members of Running Man.
So is this the guests' idea?
Please come on out.
What are we doing today?
Who are they?
My gosh. Look who are here.
Hello.
(Actor Jo Byeong Gyu,
Actress Im Soo Hyang)
There they are.
Soo Hyang.
(Jo Byeong Gyu played an immature
character in "Stove League".)
(He's in Running Man
for the first time.)
(All the dramas she appears in
become a huge success.)
(Rising actress Im Soo Hyang)
(She's active
even in variety shows.)
(She's the 9th member
of Running Man.)
(She's the next generation
multi-entertainer, Im Soo Hyang.)
(Jo Byeong Gyu and Im Soo Hyang
are in Running Man.)
Soo Hyang.
It's good to see you.
- Byeong Gyu.
- Hello.
All right.
Come here. We go to the same gym.
Byeong Gyu.
Have you been doing well?
- Hello.
- Soo Hyang.
My gosh.
Gosh, this is so nice.
Byeong Gyu, what is that thing
on your back?
I heard this is a retreat.
Is it for today? I see.
Puffed corn.
We just talked about this.
We will never go out today.
We will stay indoors.
I brought some games...
- we can play indoors.
- Really?
I brought some eggs.
What are the eggs for?
We can strike them on the head.
- It's a random game.
- Kwang Soo's not here today.
And I brought
some nutrition supplements.
- What are they for?
- Why?
- You can eat it when you're hungry.
- That's a good idea.
- When we're hungry?
- We can eat them.
I have bellflower root juice
and noni juice.
I like noni juice.
It's good for joints.
He brought all kinds of juice.
Did you have them at home?
Yes. These are what I have
at home. There's milk thistle.
- What?
- Does...
- your family...
- Medicine.
I've been suffering from
nightmares these days.
So I take these.
I'm sorry, but you've never been to
a retreat before, right?
Is this what do people do
at retreats?
- What kind of retreat is this?
- This is my first time.
- So I'm excited.
- He's excited. I know how he feels.
Byeong Gyu, you've never been
to retreats before.
I took some time off from school,
so I didn't go to school.
I got expelled a few days ago.
- You got expelled?
- You talked about it before.
My school asked me...
if I wanted to be expelled or
drop out, so I chose to drop out.
I didn't want to drop out
because it hurts my pride.
- So did you get expelled?
- Yes.
Why would it hurt your pride?
Your pride has
never been hurt, right?
(He doesn't know
the sweets and bitters of life.)
- He doesn't know anything.
- He knows nothing.
He doesn't know the time of day.
(Byeong Gyu embodies the immature
character in "Stove League".)
Byeong Gyu looked
just like this in the drama.
Right. It's a cheerful character.
He's a guy from a rich family.
He joins the company
through the connection,
but he takes
the employment exam again.
- That sounds great.
- He's handsome.
- You look sophisticated.
- You think?
Haha likes sophisticated people.
Look at Se Chan and him.
They look totally different.
Why would you compare us?
He's good-looking.
- Thank you.
- Byeong Gyu is very...
He's perfect for a guy
from a rich family.
Se Chan would never play
a character like that.
Me? It's impossible.
But in fact, there are...
a lot of rich guys
who look like this.
Jong Kook!
(There are a lot of rich guys
who look like this.)
(A rich guy in reality)
Jong Kook, my goodness.
- Hang on.
- That's true.
There's someone
who looks just like him.
- It's true.
- Wait.
I'm serious.
I think I've seen someone like him.
It's really...
Rich guys in reality
don't look like him.
- Most of them look like this.
- That's true.
- This is the reality.
- Exactly.
And we have Ji Hyo here.
She's called Cavewoman Ji Hyo
these days.
She lives under a rock.
Did you watch "Stove League"?
I watched only three episodes.
("Stove League" is the best
drama guaranteed by Ji Hyo.)
- You watched it anyway.
- You know what?
If Ji Hyo watched three episodes,
it means everyone watched it.
I'm serious.
I watched three episodes,
so I was very excited
to see him earlier.
It's amazing
that she recognized you.
Ji Hyo, did you watch
"Graceful Family"?
(Did she watch Soo Hyang's drama,
"Graceful Family" too?)
I will watch it.
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo is
the Great Wall of dramas.)
- My gosh.
- See?
Like I said, if Ji Hyo
watched three episodes,
It means
the whole nation watched it.
it means everyone watched it.
Ji Hyo, what is the movie
that you watched recently?
- Or VOD.
- "Number Three"?
What's the latest movie you watched?
"Green Fish".
- Just anything.
- What did you watch?
- "Christmas in August"?
- Nothing.
Isn't it "Harry Potter"?
Ji Hyo, please tell us.
- I watched it yesterday.
- Did you watch it yesterday?
On OCN.
(A cable movie channel)
You watched it on OCN?
It's surprising that Ji Hyo
watched OCN yesterday.
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo starts
to communicate with the world.)
- She's improved.
- Right.
I didn't watch it though.
It was on TV when I woke up from
my nap, and I fell asleep again.
- You fell asleep.
- Ji Hyo is always...
Whenever I ask her what she
did at home, she says she slept.
I had a sound sleep yesterday.
You did?
He goes to the same gym with me.
- Really?
- Yes.
We go to the same gym.
Were you a soccer player
in middle school?
I was a soccer player.
Really?
- You were?
- So I brought a ball.
When did you quit?
I played soccer until
the third grade of middle school.
Jong Kook wants to cast him again.
He's always like that.
I saw him at the gym.
I heard that a lot
from people around me.
If I join Jong Kook's soccer team,
I'll be dead.
(If I join Jong Kook's soccer team,
I'll be dead.)
No, you won't die.
- That's correct.
- You won't die.
- He knows something.
- You won't be dead.
(That's not true.)
We go to the same gym.
But I've been avoiding him...
because I was afraid
he'd want to play soccer with me.
Why did he not tell me that?
Be honest.
What did you hear
about Jong Kook's soccer team?
If I play soccer in the team,
I might throw up during a break.
(Throw up?)
They all have plastic bags
around their necks.
I was told to go there
on an empty stomach.
People take a break
while playing soccer.
But our team gets a rest like that,
I tell them this.
"If you want to chat,
you should go to a cafe."
- I know that.
- "Keep moving."
(They have to keep moving
in order to survive.)
So we talked to Byeong Gyu.
- And we have Soo Hyang here.
- Soo Hyang.
Soo Hyang.
Our Soo Hyang.
When I was in college,
we went on a trip for three days.
And there was a girl who stayed for
one day. She was dressed like this.
She left early.
She just has fun and leaves early.
- Have fun.
- She stays for a short time.
- And she's cool.
- Right.
She just stops by and says...
"I have a plan tomorrow.
You guys have fun."
She always has sunglasses
on her head.
Like I always say,
- Soo Hyang is very cheerful.
- Really?
- Once she gets carried away...
- No one can deal with her.
Do you have any
connections with So Min?
We drank with Kwang Soo
the other day.
(We drank with Kwang Soo
the other day.)
Oh, that was...
She doesn't remember it.
- I ran away.
- Why?
Gosh, she was unbelievable.
- She kept playing games.
She kept playing games
and made me drink.
- She's a professional gamer.
- I ran away.
- Once she drinks...
- So Min.
Whenever you drink with people,
- they have a hard time...
- What made me like this...
is this show, Running Man.
I ran away at around 3 or 4 a.m.
I understand why you left.
So Min stays there until the end
even if it's 5 or 6 a.m.
If it was 3 or 4 in the morning,
it's just that she went home.
We can say she ran away.
I ran away.
That's unbelievable.
I have connections with Soo Hyang.
- What connections?
- Really?
- She went to my high school.
I found it out when I got here.
When I was in high school,
she visited...
our school play.
- She went there as a celebrity.
- Right.
- I was a sophomore in high school.
- Really? So?
I asked her to take a picture
with me in the playground.
- What did she say?
- Did she take a picture?
She said she was busy,
so she had to leave.
(The celebrity ran away.)
- She didn't take a picture.
- He got her a blow.
You should say that I did.
- Keep going.
- You should say I took a picture.
He's getting her a blow.
I think she took a picture with me.
(That's right.
That's what you should say.)
This is membership training,
but we don't know anything about it.
This is Running Man Has Plans Race.
You should plan three things
you'll do with your friends...
and have fun.
But there's one condition
we ask for.
All the members
start with 10 R coins.
The top three members...
with the most R coins
at the last moment will get a prize.
The one with the least number
of coins will get a penalty.
(The one with the least number
of coins will get a penalty.)
You will write down the three things
you want to do and present them.
After the presentation, the rest
of the members will give marks.
The one with the highest marks
will be the host today.
And you will stick to the schedule
that the host planned.
- It will be fun.
- We should plan three things.
That's right.
The host will get...
10 R coins when each event is over.
I should come up with something
that people will like.
- I need something that people like.
- Something interesting.
After one event is over,
if you want to change
to another person's event,
you can always change it
through your votes.
- Here's the evaluation sheet.
- Okay.
So we have the evaluation sheet
for the plans.
As you can see, the sheet says
items like screen time,
realistic possibility, completeness,
- and attitude.
- We should give scores, right?
Yes. Five points for each item.
You can give a presentation...
- either in the digital way...
- What?
- or in the analog way.
- What's digital and analog?
I'm more comfortable
with an analog way.
- Me too.
- I will do it digitally.
I prefer analog.
I want to do it digitally.
I'll do it in the digital way.
- What?
- Sir.
(He turns out to be
an early adapter.)
- Sir. Wait.
- What?
Will you do this digitally?
- Sure. I can use a pointer.
- All you can do is...
search on a price comparison site.
That's good enough.
Suk Jin will do it
in the digital way then.
(Digital: Suk Jin, So Min,
Se Chan, Byeong Gyu)
(Analog: Jae Suk, Jong Kook,
Haha, Ji Hyo, Soo Hyang)
- We should move the table.
- Will you move it?
Okay.
(A laptop for digital)
They will use PowerPoint.
- This one?
- Yes.
(Is Suk Jin going to be okay?)
As you can see, the digital team...
can use the laptop here.
Do we get bonus points
if we make it look pretty?
(They can get more points
for completeness.)
Do we?
You see PowerPoint there.
What's that?
(Byeong Gyu runs the program
as soon as he hears it.)
I will show you an example.
You can use the program.
(I can barely see it.
What's PowerPoint?)
(He doesn't even know
how to use it.)
- What's that?
- I wonder...
Suk Jin.
Does he even know what it is?
Why did you go there?
Is PowerPoint...
It's Excel.
like sending text messages?
Suk Jin, do you not go
to the school for the elderly?
- What did you say?
- The school for the elderly.
(He's learning late in life.)
(What am I supposed to do?)
And we have tools
for the analog team.
What's that? This is too much.
I can't believe this.
That belongs to Suk Jin.
(What's the analog tool
that shocks everyone?)
- What's this?
- This isn't right.
(Inkstone?)
It's calligraphy,
the analog tool of Korea.
You should make it look good
in the same way.
- This is better.
- He needs one.
This reminds me of the time
when I learned calligraphy.
Actually,
- it's harder to do it digitally.
- I know. This is better.
This is better.
"Enter a subject."
(He says digital is better,
but he doesn't know what to do.)
There should be a time limit.
It's 15 minutes.
We have to finish it by 10:15.
If you don't finish it in time, you
will give a presentation like that.
Gosh. I did this when I was
in elementary school.
I liked to grind an ink stick
on an inkstone.
I like the sound.
You know what?
Calligraphy is all about sincerity.
I should forget all worldly cares
grinding an ink stick.
- As I grind an ink stick...
- I grind them all.
I melt the people
I want to grind on here.
(I melt the people
I want to grind on here.)
It kills my urge.
- As I grind this.
- Guys.
- All worldly cares in your mind...
- That's right.
(So Min already finished
producing the template.)
Can you do this?
I've never done this before.
(The senior member is
a two-fingered typist.)
All he can do is search
on a price comparison site.
Retreat... Hang on.
Wait. What do I do?
This is...
Suk Jin, you have a mouse
next to you.
- What?
- There's a mouse.
I have a mouse.
(He has a mouse that works fine.)
He just grabbed a camera
instead of the mouse.
(An up-to-date mouse?)
He just grabbed a camera
instead of the mouse.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- How would he do this digitally?
You fool. Don't be silly.
Hang on. This is page one.
Should I create page two?
New slide.
Gosh, I did it.
I think I created the next page.
How did you make the next page?
Can't you do that?
I don't know how to do it.
I know how to make page two.
You can press Enter.
(His bragging ended in 3 seconds.)
I can just press Enter?
- Yes. You can just press this once.
- My gosh.
(It's created immediately.)
- This is amazing.
- Just press Enter.
- Suk Jin is...
- It came up as I pressed Enter.
That's Shift. Press this key.
(He keeps pressing Shift.)
(Frustrated)
What's with him?
(He pressed the laughter key
instead of the Enter key.)
Thank you.
It looks like a grandson teaches
his grandpa how to use a computer.
It's like he's doing volunteer work.
An old man is here to learn.
Byeong Gyu looks like a college
student doing his homework.
And So Min looks like a girl
who's here for Byeong Gyu.
(She's obsessed with the guy
doing his homework.)
She doesn't have anything
in her laptop.
She just came here
to see Byeong Gyu.
That's right. I came with him.
Gosh, I still have
the calligraphy skills.
- You're good.
- I know.
I learned calligraphy
when I was in elementary school.
I should write down
the program for the first class.
The first class.
I should feed them
in the first class.
I thought about what to eat...
All right. It's ramyeon.
But what matters is...
what kind of ramyeon we are eating.
- Is it jjapaguri?
- What?
(What is he? He's scary.)
I guess that's what it is.
Jjapaguri.
Gosh, this is...
I want to add a picture of pillows,
but I don't know what to do.
Wait.
You can type pillow.
Then you can copy the picture.
His way of talking is so funny.
"You can type pillow."
(He was afraid
if Suk Jin might not hear him.)
Pillow...
Does anyone know
how to spell pillow?
- Pillow?
- It's pillow.
- P-i-l?
- P-i-l-l-o-w.
Pillow.
P-e-l.
- What are you talking about?
- It's p-e-l.
It's p-i-l-l-o-w.
- Isn't it p-e-l?
- It's p-i-l.
It's p-i-l-l-o-w.
Of course.
It's 11:08am now.
It ends at 11:15.
(They pick up the pace
to finish it in time.)
Save the image.
Where's Save?
Jae Suk, Suk Jin is
about to swear now.
How do I save this image?
It's so annoying.
- Do you know how to save an image?
- Yes.
How do you know?
Save it in my heart.
Wait.
Watch this.
Look at the image and say,
"Save it in my heart."
- Then the image is saved?
- Sure.
If you want to save it
inside your eyes, do this.
Goodness.
- Press Ctrl, Alt, and Delete.
- What?
- Ctrl.
Ctrl, Alt...
(He follows Se Chan's instructions.)
(He closes the program.)
What is it?
Everything's gone!
(That's the shortcut
for closing down a window.)
You have 15 minutes.
- I'm serious. We changed teams.
- Where is it?
So we're going to be strict.
Okay, okay.
Let's see.
You have three minutes.
Three? Hold on.
It's on my wallpaper.
I have a wallpaper of a pillow.
(He has a pillow wallpaper?)
(He's currently struggling
by himself.)
This is driving me crazy.
- You need to start it again.
- Wait.
(One can always learn new things.)
Goodness.
It's been 14 minutes now.
- We have a minute left?
- Hold on.
(They only have 1 minute left.)
In the past, we used to wait
until everyone was done.
But we won't do that anymore.
- Suk Jin, please stop.
- Okay.
Gosh.
(He's not finished yet,
but they're taking his computer.)
You're taking it?
They're taking our computers.
(What are their programs?)
Who should start first?
- Should I?
- Sure.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
- His looks so simple.
- I know.
Most retreats are full...
of games.
I'm sure you all have
various programs planned out.
But I believe having no set program
is the best.
That's what I believe.
(Eat ramyeon, With Kwang Soo,
Shouting in the silence)
- That's the most convenient.
- So...
I've simplified my program.
You're explaining everything.
- You are.
- Yes.
I refrained from taking up
too much of your time...
because I want you all...
to go home early.
That's lovely.
My program is very simplified,
and you can eat quickly.
The game won't take too long,
and you'll go home early.
- That's how my program will be.
- That's wonderful.
We'll be spending about six hours.
- That's how long it'll take.
- Six hours?
Wait, how long are we having
ramyeon for?
- Wait.
- Six hours?
- I thought it'd be simple.
- It is.
Will that program
even last that long?
Of course.
- Because...
- I think it'll take two hours.
Come on. We'll be chatting.
- Still, that's impossible.
- No.
We should let Byeong Gyu talk.
Right.
- Soo Hyang as well.
- That's nice.
- Don't you know me?
- What do you mean?
I'm a veteran host.
(You all know that.)
(His skills are acknowledged.)
- Right.
- That's it.
- I'll give you a high score.
- Okay. Thank you.
Right.
That was nice.
- I like it too.
- "Yoo Jae Suk".
Hold on.
"Attitude, one point".
(He's merciless.)
Now that I know
what you've given me,
you better watch out.
"He chats a lot,"
"but his material
isn't that detailed."
(He mainly focuses on chatting.)
- "Seven points".
- "Yoo Jae Suk".
He deserved five points
for "realistic possibility".
Next up is Jong Kook.
Your handwriting looks nice.
- All right.
- He's dexterous.
- Jong Kook.
- He wrote well.
(Random trashcan basketball,
A talk with Writer Jeon,)
(With Trainer Kook)
- That's wonderful.
- "Writer Jeon"?
What is that?
- What is that?
- "Writer Jeon"?
- I'm going to give you zero points.
- What is that?
Listen.
Who's "Writer Jeon"?
It's her.
I've published a book.
(It's me.)
He asked who Writer Jeon was.
(Giggling)
- You published a book?
- Yes.
We'll start off by staying loyal
to our show...
and playing a game.
You need to throw objects
into a trashcan.
- Random objects? That's nice.
- They'll be random.
Yes. It'll be entertaining
for our viewers to watch.
- It'll be a light game.
- That's nice.
After that, we'll eat...
and talk with Writer Jeon.
What if we don't have anything
to talk about?
We'll read her book.
- Her book?
- You'll open it...
to a random page
and have a chat with her about it.
Here's the last one.
People are very interested...
in watching workout videos
these days.
- I'm not sure about that.
- So...
- I'll teach you some moves.
- I don't like that.
They'll help you lose weight.
I'm against that.
I saw how your manager almost died.
We'll be working out together.
- We'll work out together.
- Hold on.
I'm not sure about that.
You don't seem interested.
I'm interested in all of them.
- What's wrong?
- You've lost points...
since I don't like to read.
Come on.
I've given you a high score.
I love "A talk with Writer Jeon".
- Should I go next?
- Okay.
Okay. Haha.
You have nice handwriting.
"A Noisy Retreat Mission"!
(A Noisy Retreat Mission)
I don't like that.
- I don't like that.
- Why not?
- Try it.
- Let's hear him out first.
Here's the first program.
"Crazy Ping-Pong Match"!
I don't like that attitude.
I'll give you one point.
- I don't like that.
- I really don't.
Now comes the second program.
"Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo,
Hilarious Lunch Time"!
- We'll be having random ramyeon.
- Gosh.
- "Hilarious"?
- Ping-pong will be random as well.
This will be random as well.
- I'm going to give you one point.
- Don't you think it'll be fun?
"A Noisy Retreat Mission"!
- Sit down.
- It overlaps with his.
Sit down, you betrayer.
(He wants him to stop.)
- His attitude annoys me.
- Next up is Ji Hyo.
I look forward to her program.
- Ji Hyo.
- This is mine.
Is it a ghost leg.
It'll be very simple.
- What is that?
- "Nap for now"?
- "Nap..."
- We'll be taking a nap first.
(Nap for now)
(She wants to take a nap wherever.)
(It suits her.)
- And then?
- We'll eat.
- And then, we'll nap again.
(They'll nap, eat, and nap again.)
What about our show?
- Come on, Ji Hyo.
- Hey.
Come on.
We'll shoot our show
while lying down.
"Screen time, zero points".
You're determined
not to shoot anything.
Byeong Gyu said he's been having
nightmares these days.
Have you actually seen anyone
have nightmares?
- No.
- Today, you'll be able to.
That's nice.
- Have those nightmares.
- What?
You may.
(She urges him to have nightmares.)
- This suddenly sounds fun.
- That's screen time right there.
That sounds fun.
Have your nightmares.
She's convincing.
- It's nice.
- Think about it.
Have you ever witnessed someone
having nightmares on the spot?
- No.
- This is your chance.
Byeong Gyu,
do you get nightmares often?
- Yes, I'll be having them today.
- He's been having them often.
What's "free time"?
You can take a walk.
- "A walk"?
- Yes.
That's original.
Where's the fun in taking a walk?
I'm curious.
Where is it?
- You need to meet a wild animal.
- Really?
You'll fight off the animal.
(Thanks to Jong Kook,
her program sounds more fun.)
She's won some points.
I think this episode...
- will be fun.
- Really.
I've given you at least four points.
Mine rose from 0 to 2 points.
Your score...
is higher than Jae Suk's.
- Me too.
- Really?
- Is it higher?
- She almost got a full score.
- Exactly.
- Hers is the best.
That's why she got a full score.
Goodness.
- Gosh.
- Soo Hyang is next.
(Next up is Soo Hyang.)
Why is she carrying a bag?
- It's the girl who left early.
- Why is she carrying a bag?
It's not her, is it?
- It's the girl who left early.
- She looks similar.
- Hi, guys.
- Hello.
Hello.
Don't you have plans
in Gangnam later?
I'm running out of time,
- so I'll be quick.
- Right.
It's her.
"Welcome. This Must Be
Your First Retreat."
("Welcome. This Must Be
Your First Retreat.)
- I like her attitude.
- Me too.
Which segment during a retreat
encourages cooperation...
and is the most important?
- It's the games.
- Right.
- We need to play games.
- We'll get to know each other.
- She's good.
- That's why I chose family arcade.
In that segment,
there's Cry in Silence...
and Speak with Your Actions.
Soo Hyang,
unlike your outer appearance,
your games are a bit outdated.
She's old-fashioned.
There's even the mafia game.
(Soo Hyang is old-fashioned.)
(Speechless)
She's flustered.
- This is retro style.
- I see.
- This is the trend.
- Having plain ramyeon is boring,
- That's tasty.
so I'll cook kimchi fried rice.
- You'll be cooking?
Are you good?
Have you cooked it before?
She's good.
I'm good at making it.
I've had her dish before.
She's good.
This is a snack.
(She pulls out some jjondeugi.)
- Do you want some?
- This program sounds nice.
- Don't you?
- Yes.
You can try some right now.
- Okay.
- If you pick me,
- I'll let you have more.
- What's the reason?
Goodness.
I'll give you all of these.
- Our lunch will be...
- We'll...
- What are those?
- Gosh.
- You threw them.
(She pulls out packets of jjondeugi
from her bag.)
This is jjondeugi flex.
- You're right.
- This is jjondeugi flex.
Your score is rising.
- My gosh.
- Okay.
- I've given her the highest score.
- Me too.
- Let's move onto the digital ones.
- Yes.
- Suk Jin.
- All right.
(Suk Jin goes first.)
It'll be harder than you think.
Let me introduce my program.
- Please look here.
- Okay.
Look here, please.
"If you want to have fun,
follow me!"
I hate it. "Attitude, zero points".
This is the title.
- We'll have some fun.
- Let's hear him out first.
It'll be fun. Let's move on.
Clap.
(Clapping)
- All right. Pillow fight.
- What is that?
- We'll be doing this.
- What?
- We don't have any pillows.
- What is that?
- This is...
- Pillow fight.
Where are the pillows, you ask?
It's here.
Here.
It took me eight minutes
to find this image.
- What's with him?
- Please do understand.
We could play "Find the pillow".
(No one knew he worked so hard
to find that image.)
I didn't notice it.
- I didn't notice it.
- Me neither.
Right.
Please understand
the effort I've put into this.
All right, next.
(Happy lunch time. Let's have)
Why didn't you finish the sentence?
You see...
This was when the staff
took my laptop.
What were you going to write?
- "Let's have a tasty meal."
- "Let's have..."
- Goodness.
- I had so much more to write.
I'm not kidding.
I can only give him a point.
Anyway, please be generous
with your points.
It was entertaining though.
Byeong Gyu is next.
- He did a good job.
- He worked hard on his.
Is Byeong Gyu good at these things?
- Yes.
- His looked really good.
Well, I am the youngest here.
Let's take a look then.
Sure.
(His presentation material
looks different right off the bat.)
- Nice.
- It looks good.
As you can see,
I laid the letters on the photo.
This isn't easy to accomplish.
- Really?
- But you don't have a computer...
- at home.
- Well, I was able to...
figure out the functions.
- He's the type to show off.
- Right.
Okay, Mr. Show-off. Noted.
I'm deducting two points for that.
- I'm deducting one.
- So he's arrogant.
I'll write down "arrogant."
- He likes to show off.
- That's right.
Anyway, let's move on.
- What?
- Wait, what's that?
Didn't it appear
from Kwang Soo's nose?
The letters came from his nose.
- How? Let's see that again.
- What was that?
If this was something
to brag about...
Can you do that again?
I didn't get to see it.
Gosh, look at that.
No way.
I did it myself.
I found this feature.
- He's showing off again.
- What?
He can't help himself.
You like to brag, aren't you?
You get what
I'm capable of now, right?
Okay, let's move on.
- First class...
- Beat Jong Kook.
That's right.
Why did you space out
his name like that?
So his grammar isn't that good.
- The spacing is odd.
- Byeong Gyu,
your grammar isn't that good.
"Bad grammar and a show-off."
(Bad grammar and a show-off)
A show-off.
Right. And next?
- Lunch.
- Lunch time.
I laid the letters...
- in front of the photo.
- Stop mentioning that.
You've said it enough.
"Annoyingly boastful."
I wanted my visual aid
to score me at least five points.
- Right.
- That you get.
- Five points.
- Of course.
However, your attitude sucks.
You're scoring zero points
as a presenter.
Still, I gave you five points
in terms of visual aid.
- Me too.
- That's right.
- Thank you.
All right.
It's "Rich, Poor, and Fun Retreat"!
What on earth is that?
To the next page, please.
First class, Cry in Silence.
- I had the same idea.
- It's not original at all.
How boring!
Third class,
Three Smartphone Games.
All right, fine. We get it.
What do you mean?
You've received the lowest score.
- Unbelievable.
- Well,
- photos and...
- This isn't enough to air.
This would've been funnier
with a photo.
I give you 1 to 2 points
for feasibility.
- So Min is the last one up.
- Sure.
Hello,
- I'm Jeon So Min.
- This is a nice start.
I'm sorry, but what is that?
- Why that photo?
- You're the face of Running Man.
- She's right.
- I see.
Let's move on to the next page.
Two,
Yum-yum Time!
- Yum-yum?
- At 50?
- Mamma mia!
- Unbelievable.
Let's all enjoy a cooking session.
- Here.
- That I don't want to see.
This is bad.
- Three.
- It started off all right, but...
- Next up is...
- I'm already over this one.
It's the third activity.
- You typed in a lot.
- Right.
Earlier, I saw that
"saand" was available.
- "Saand"?
- With two As?
(They spot a typo.)
She got the spelling wrong.
Saand?
- Am I wrong?
- You got the spelling wrong.
- That's not how you write it.
- Seriously?
"She reminds me of Byeong Gyu."
I only got the spacing wrong though.
"She's like Byeong Gyu."
Let's go treasure hunting.
- Next.
- Its feasibility...
- Saand...
- "Saand"?
(Saand)
It wasn't just a typo.
Writer Jeon?
- You...
- What a huge disappointment.
It's an honest mistake.
You had me fooled all these years.
For 30 years, you knew that
as the spelling of "sand"?
I had to type at a fast speed, guys.
You say you were in a rush,
but you typed them all
with two As.
- Exactly.
- Guys,
doesn't it sound like fun?
(She quickly wraps it up
with a cute gesture.)
You get one point for presentation
because of that annoying tone.
- Writer Jeon...
- Just so you know,
you startled me
with the spelling of sand.
- Gosh, I'm embarrassed.
- Stick to books from now on.
Soo Hyang has the highest score...
- while So Min has the lowest.
- Just stick to books.
- Really?
- I gave Jong Kook...
the highest score.
- I...
- Jong Kook...
- Right.
- His plan got good points too.
- Let me now read...
- All right.
- some of your comments.
- Sure thing.
Right.
Ji Hyo, why did you
give everyone the same score?
- Everyone?
- Mine too?
- Couldn't you be bothered?
- You couldn't be bothered.
- That's not it.
It's my way of saying
that I'm fine with all the options.
Look. She gave me 4, 4, 4,
and 5 points, and it's 7 in total,
which is what she
also gave Jong Kook.
The same goes for Haha.
4, 4, 4?
Are you telling us to drop dead?
She wrote jjondeugi for Soo Hyang
and Yang Se Chan for Se Chan.
Are you kidding me?
Well...
- Was she writing in her diary?
- Were you scribbling?
What on earth is this?
- I wrote what was memorable.
- You were scribbling.
- Those were memorable.
- Goodness. Cavewoman Ji Hyo.
So let me read what Soo Hyang wrote.
Jae Suk.
"I almost fell for his words."
(This is how Soo Hyang
evaluated Jae Suk's program.)
"His eloquent presentation
grabbed my attention,"
"but he lacked sincerity."
- You finally came to your senses.
- Next is So Min's program.
"Doesn't sound like fun."
(Doesn't sound like fun.)
I bet that hurts.
- Hold on.
- She thinks it'll be boring.
But my program is the bomb!
I'm glad she didn't go harsher
than that.
Next up is Jong Kook's evaluation.
He wrote that
Se Chan's program is boring...
while Suk Jin's is no fun.
(Jong Kook's evaluation sheet)
Boring and no fun?
- What about So Min's?
- He wrote that Byeong Gyu...
bragged too much.
It's the same
as writing hate comments!
What? Hate comments?
Starting with Se Chan's,
what you wrote were hate comments.
- Yes, from mine...
- Gosh,
it really hurts to hear that.
Next up is Haha's.
Jae Suk...
"The Grand Award winner of 2019..."
(The Grand Award winner of 2019...)
This is what Haha wrote.
"The Grand Award winner of 2019."
"I still believe in Jae Suk..."
Who are you kissing up to?
- Unbelievable.
- Seriously?
"We have the same ideas."
Yes, that's why I wrote it.
- Gosh.
- He wrote that Suk Jin...
should only focus
on staying healthy.
(From Haha to Suk Jin)
(The words Haha
never got the chance to say?)
Are we writing letters instead?
"Only focus on staying healthy".
- Gosh.
- Anyway, that's all.
The points have been added.
- Who's in first place?
- Who won?
The programs in 1st and 2nd place...
only were a point apart.
So the winner by a point is...
(Who won by receiving 1 more point?)
- It's Jong Kook.
- Goodness!
All right!
Now I feel burdened.
Soo Hyang's program
is in second place.
So the first game you play...
will be Random Trashcan Basketball.
- Okay.
- Good.
Everyone will receive
10 regular coins...
and Jong Kook will receive
extra 10 coins for being a host.
You'll all change...
and play the game
suggested by Jong Kook.
Let's go!
(The retreat begins!)
We'll now begin
the first item in today's program.
Random Trashcan Basketball?
- We...
- It won't be easy.
What happens to the 10 coins
the host Jong Kook has?
Must he hand them over
to the next host?
The host will receive 10 coins
every session.
- Every session?
- Really?
Jong Kook can use those coins
however he sees fit.
One more thing.
The props needed
can be bought from the next room.
So they're sold?
We prepared props
needed for fun games...
as well as snacks
and food ingredients.
We can buy them?
I explained the rules earlier.
- Yes, perfectly.
- We all know the rules.
You will compete in two teams.
- Two teams?
- Yes.
One from each team will come out...
and choose a card with
various objects written on them.
Your objective is
to throw them into the trashcan.
The winning team...
will receive five coins
from the staff.
Simple, right?
Nice.
- How simple and clear was that?
- Sounds like fun.
- I can't wait.
- It sounds exciting.
- The winning team...
- Let's get on his good side.
(They kiss up to him silently.)
I will also hand out
the coins I have...
to those who deserve it.
- All right.
- Nice!
(They keep kissing up to him.)
Those bootlickers.
- Let's decide the teams first.
- Right.
How many people are there?
- 9 people.
- 9.
Right, nine.
How about 3 teams of 3?
3 teams of 3? Nice one!
- No. 1 in place.
- No. 2 in place.
I'm in place.
(They immediately join Jong Kook.)
- Unbelievable.
- Look at them.
- Those bootlickers.
- Those suck-ups.
Well, I guess we already
have one team then.
(The host calls it.)
(Team Jong Kook has been decided.)
Nice!
- Oh, yes.
- Oh, yes!
(Nice!)
So that's your team?
- Yes.
- This is absurd.
- This isn't right.
- I'm not one...
to make things complicated.
They came to me in a natural way.
He's the best host.
Then let's form a team ourselves.
- Okay, good.
- Us three.
We're a team of three too.
Are we good to go?
- Yes, I like this team.
- It seems fun.
- Nice.
- The ladies.
- Nice one.
- Byeong Gyu, it's too bad.
- Are we a team then?
- Yes.
Good.
I'm not sure
I'm okay with this team.
Get over here.
We're not that bad.
(You'll grow to like us.)
It's as if he's being
bullied by his uncles.
Byeong Gyu, shut it.
I feel like I'm being punished.
(They have their 3 teams.)
Please pick up the objects first.
- All right. Se Chan...
- Se Chan, let's go.
- and Haha, get going.
- Yes, sir!
(Dashing)
Unbelievable.
Make sure they'll give us
a good laugh.
Those bootlickers.
- Those suck-ups.
Wait. Oh, the trashcan.
I see the props.
Must we pay for these?
The staff came well-prepared today.
Tell me about it.
Must we pay for this too?
Yes.
- Wait.
- Out of our own pockets?
- Yes.
- No way.
(Dashing)
- There's an issue.
- Jong Kook!
We must pay for the props.
- What? You have to pay?
- Yes.
- With coins.
- How much is it?
It seems like
you'll have to collect, sir.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
There are a variety
of props back there.
But none of them are for free.
Unbelievable.
What are you two doing?
I'll never do...
- Jong Kook's games again.
- At first...
I've had it with these two.
I'm looking for volunteers
who'll offer their coins...
for our show today.
I'll give you a prize.
Jong Kook, then...
- let's play Race of Wits.
- What?
Make the losers pay.
Hold him.
(How dare you?)
Kneel!
How dare you...
How dare you say that?
You need a lesson.
How dare you?
- Our host was talking.
- Be quiet!
Be quiet!
- Okay.
- I'll take care of him.
Okay, good.
How could you
just stand by and watch?
Byeong Gyu, how could you?
You deserved it.
Please volunteer.
Show me how enthusiastic
you are about the first round.
Wait.
Shouldn't the host pay
for the game tools?
That's right. You should.
That's how it works.
What are you talking about, kid?
Take care of him!
How dare you?
Okay, good.
- Gosh, you guys...
- This is not okay.
- My team is too weak.
- We'll bring some tools,
and the losing team will pay
for them. What do you say?
- That sounds great.
- Thank you.
(I'm getting hot.)
Jong Kook, Jae Suk is
getting ready to fight.
(Ready for combat?)
He's getting ready to fight!
I'll let you fight.
Do you want to do it?
- Do you want to do it?
- Okay!
- I was getting hot.
I was getting hot,
so I wanted to change.
Isn't it too white?
- It's too white.
- You look so weak.
- I was getting hot.
- You were getting hot?
- He's getting ready to fight.
- Okay.
- Pay participation fees.
- You have to.
Each team will pay one coin.
Each team will pay one coin?
Each team gets to decide how to pay.
If I like a team's method,
- They'll win a point.
- I'll remember it.
We'll fight.
I love that.
Byeong Gyu.
- He thinks his teammates are weak.
- Byeong Gyu.
Be quiet, will you?
He's very brave.
I love it.
- That's definitely my style.
- Good job.
I think the youngest member
should pay.
(Soo Hyang is the youngest.)
Ji Hyo, you're okay with it, right?
Running Man is scary.
They just steal your money.
- We'll play Race of Wits.
That sounds good.
The three of you will play.
- Okay.
- Ready.
Can you say, "Start"?
- Start.
- 1.
- 2.
(The game only took 3 seconds.)
Give it to us.
(Jae Suk is a fan of Race of Wits,
but he is not good at it.)
- Pay.
- Is that it?
- Of course.
You didn't even sit
all the way down.
That's not true.
- Our team...
- Yes.
I'll pay.
(Touched)
I was going to say, "I'll pay."
- But you...
- My hand was in my pocket.
- What should we do?
- Okay.
I'll just remember you did this.
You both pay
and give me my coin back.
Stay out of this!
- I can't believe them.
- All right, good.
I'll volunteer to pay first.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Okay.
- First of all...
- I'll go.
- She's taking the initiative.
- You want to take the initiative?
- Yes, I'll go.
- She's taking the initiative.
- 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2...
- My goodness.
- So Min, I'll remember you.
- She's taking the initiative.
Taking the initiative
on a variety show?
Taking the initiative?
It's my style. You know it.
- Unbelievable.
- Take the initiative.
It's frustrating.
The game hasn't even started,
and we're already having fun.
Is this really a retreat?
Are you sure this is not training?
What is this?
It's boot camp training.
It's a variety show
boot camp training.
- Why don't we do a talent show?
- That sounds good.
Byeong Gyu is...
- good at impersonations.
- I'd love to hear it.
- What should I do?
- Try Lee Sun Kyun. You're good.
- He does sound a little like him.
- He does.
"Hello, I'm Actor Lee Sun Kyun."
(Impressed)
"Are you the only doctor?"
"I'm a doctor too!"
- That was amazing.
- He took the initiative.
- I love it.
- "I'm a doctor too."
Your score is very high right now.
I'm looking for the MVP
of each team.
Byeong Gyu is never shy.
I bought two items.
Hold on.
Hey, you have to get a trashcan too.
- I have to?
- Of course.
Do we have to buy a trashcan?
- Did you use all the coins?
- She must have pocketed some.
I bet she pocketed some money.
Come here.
- What are you talking about?
- Come here.
So Min, we know
how much those items cost.
- Exactly.
- What do you mean?
This costs 1 coin,
and that costs 2 coins.
- Come to your senses, okay?
- This costs one coin.
Did you forget about
taking the initiative?
I knew she might do that,
but I didn't know
she'd really do that.
- We knew she'd do that.
- It's no surprise.
You guys are being ridiculous.
I'll go buy a trashcan, okay?
Fine, I'll buy it.
She had many thoughts
in such a short time.
It's over for So Min.
You've finally come to your senses.
- That's more like it.
- Right.
How much money did she pocket?
Seriously...
All this costs 3 coins,
and she got only 2 items earlier?
I didn't know you could buy a set.
I love this. Okay!
- Are you ready to choose a tool?
- Yes.
We have to win this.
- Draw one.
- Everyone draws one?
This will decide your tool.
- Okay.
- Draw one.
- Hold on. If it's decided...
- You took two.
I'm the host.
Why are you crossing the line?
(Jae Suk is caught
trying to be the host.)
Hold on.
Haven't you learned your lesson?
You want to be the host
all the time.
Only do what I tell you to do.
- Stand over there.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
Hand out the cards.
(Jae Suk does as Jong Kook says.)
- Here you go.
- Okay, good.
- This is...
- Okay.
a random selection.
- One for Soo Hyang.
- Are you sure it's random?
I got duct tape.
- That's good.
- That's not bad.
- It's pretty heavy.
- It's good. It's heavy.
You always brag about
your basketball skills.
- Show us.
- He's a point guard.
- Point guard Haha.
- Shoot a three-pointer.
You shouldn't throw it
like a basketball.
It won't get in. Never.
If you get it in,
I'll give you one of my coins.
- Do you promise?
- Yes.
But if you fail,
you'll give me one of your coins.
- What is that?
- What?
- Then I'll give you two.
- Okay.
- It's 2 to 1.
- Deal.
I think he'll get it in.
- Never.
- I think he will.
It doesn't get in if you throw it
like a basketball.
Throw it like a basketball.
(Suk Jin is sure
his investment will pay off.)
(Haha is sure it'll get in.)
(What's the result
of this reckless bet?)
It won't get in.
(It goes right in.)
(Suk Jin's investment fails.)
- Oh, my.
- Okay!
- Did you see that?
- Why did you make such a bet?
Wasn't that cool?
- That was incredible.
- Take just one coin.
Give me two.
- It got in.
- Keep your promise.
Gosh.
Give me two.
- I'll give you some later.
- Suk Jin hasn't changed a bit.
Suk Jin is way behind now.
I was sure it wouldn't get in.
(Haha wins 2 coins.)
- The 3 beautiful ladies.
- I'm the youngest member.
- What did you get?
I got a rubber ball.
A rubber ball.
- It's okay. You can do this.
- I can do this.
You can't bounce the ball.
Show us.
It didn't get in.
- That was close.
(The small investor,)
(Suk Jin, fails too.)
- It flies.
- Fail.
Next up is
Yang Saeroyi from our team.
- I'm in trouble.
- Yang Saeroyi.
A tissue?
- You could crumple it.
- Crumple it.
Crumple it into a ball.
Do you want to make a bet?
- He wants to make a bet again.
- Suk Jin loves making a bet.
Why would you make a bet?
- I can't believe you.
- It's 2 to 1.
It's 2 to 1.
- It's 2 to 1?
- It's 2 to 1.
- Deal.
- Deal? Okay.
I hope it'll get in.
- I hope it'll get in.
- So do I.
I can crumple it into a ball, right?
- Yes, you can.
Crumple it as hard as you can.
But don't crumple it too hard.
- That's not okay.
- It'll get in.
- Here's a new tissue.
- What's the point?
This is not okay.
You crumpled it too hard.
But a tissue won't get so far
if you don't crumple it.
I mean...
- This is ridiculous!
- This is not okay.
- It's too easy now.
- No, it isn't.
Hold on.
- Why is it not okay?
- It's not okay.
Why is it not okay?
- It's okay to crumple it.
- You're on their side now?
- She's on their side now.
- This is...
It's not okay.
I think it's okay to crumple it.
If you crumple it,
it'll definitely get in.
All right, everyone.
- Let's take a vote.
- Let's do that.
Raise your hand if you think
it's okay to crumple the tissue.
(Byeong Gyu too?)
Raise your hand.
(Byeong Gyu raises his hand
right away.)
- Good.
- Byeong Gyu.
Byeong Gyu, how could you...
- I can't believe you.
- Good job.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Wait and see.
Byeong Gyu, I can't believe you.
I just changed my mind.
Byeong Gyu, how could you...
It's 2 to 1.
Se Chan, please get this in.
You can easily get it in.
The host is on our team.
"Dongducheon Class" can
pull this off. Yang Saeroyi.
(Se Chan finally throws the tissue.)
(Suk Jin and Yang Saeroyi
made a bet on this throw.)
(It's in.)
(Oh, no.)
Okay!
(The investor is frustrated
at his loss.)
Give me your coins.
- I'll give you just 1.
- Give me 2.
It was 2 to 1.
It was 2 to 1. Give me 2.
We need Kwang Soo...
- to stand up to them.
- Give me two.
- Without Kwang Soo...
- Okay!
(There's no one to stop
Jong Kook's tyranny.)
(In Jong Kook's world,
coins mean power.)
What is Suk Jin doing,
sitting here?
Of course, Se Chan got it in.
Listen, guys.
Since we became a team,
you were exempt
from participation fees,
which saved each of you
one coin,
and then you won more coins
by winning the game.
You guys...
- The perfect host!
Okay, good.
You're being ridiculous.
- Yang Saeroyi, sit down.
- Yes!
- Haha, sit down.
- Are you his pet?
- Yes!
- Are you?
- You want to be too,
- don't you?
- I do.
- She wants to join us.
- Let me in.
(Team Jong Kook is 2 points ahead.)
(Jae Suk succeeds
with a backscratcher.)
(The oldest beautiful lady fails.)
(Team Jae Suk 1, Team Ji Hyo 0,
Team Jong Kook 2)
Fail.
- Byeong Gyu, it's your turn.
- Okay.
- A shuttlecock.
- Use this.
Can I crumple this into a ball?
No, it needs to fly.
You can't crumple a shuttlecock
into a ball.
You have to throw it as it is.
- Yes, you can.
- You can only crumple a tissue.
- It should retain its shape.
- That won't do.
- The viewers would be curious.
Then you should have used tissue
in its original form.
I am talking.
You shouldn't have done that.
(He changes his stance.)
For goodness' sake.
- Hey.
- You are the absolute worst.
Byeong Gyu.
He is like a treacherous subject.
He is like us.
Byeong Gyu is like us.
(Satisfied)
- I will throw it as it is.
- Of course.
- That's the way to go.
- Here I go.
Okay.
Get ready.
(Where will
Byeong Gyu's shuttlecock go?)
(Byeong Gyu fails.)
(It was close!)
(It could have been disastrous.)
It should have gone in.
It was close.
I am the last one to go.
- What are we going to do?
- I didn't peek inside.
- Okay, Jong Kook.
- I will open it now.
- 1, 2, 3.
- The last person to go.
- What?
- What is it?
Toy hammer.
You can do it.
Toy hammer. All right.
Give him a round of applause.
(Give him a round of applause!)
Let's give him a round of applause.
- Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
- Kim Jong Kook!
(Jae Suk throws a rubber ball
in annoyance.)
- He threw something.
- What did you throw?
Something hit me.
- How could you be so base?
- What?
Even if I have nothing,
I won't live that way.
For goodness' sake.
Even if I have nothing,
I won't live that way.
(He throws a headband in fury.)
What is your problem?
For those who clap for me,
I will have another draw.
- Kim Jong Kook! Kim Jong Kook!
- Kim Jong Kook!
For goodness' sake.
Where did you learn to host a show?
For those who clap for me,
I will have another draw.
Hold on.
I think someone is passing gas
little by little.
(The talk of gas
makes everyone look at Suk Jin.)
Suk Jin, don't pass gas.
- Hold on.
- Is it you?
Do you smell it?
- All right.
- That means gas is leaking out.
- Gas is leaking out.
- If you...
If you tell us honestly,
I will give you an R coin.
(Jong Kook makes an offer.)
I did it!
(I farted!)
I did it.
Give me an R coin.
- I did it.
- I did it, you jerk.
- My goodness.
- Who did it?
- I did it.
I passed a bit of gas three times.
(He comes clean.)
(He reveals
how many times he did it.)
(I did it.)
- I admit it.
- This is ridiculous.
- All right.
- Give me an R coin.
Give me an R coin.
- Are you sure you did it?
- Yes, I am.
When you feel it coming,
let me hear it.
The sound of passing gas?
I will let you smell it.
I need to check.
- Give me an R coin later.
- Stop passing gas.
Didn't we win?
No one asked you to do it.
- What?
- Don't be like that, Jae Suk.
I am sorry.
Why are you sorry?
What's the current score?
Didn't we win?
- You won.
- I don't know.
- Is it over?
- This is bad.
- You won.
- We won.
- Then I won't do it.
- It was a clean win.
- Let's sit down.
- All right.
- Please congratulate Jong Kook.
- That's right.
Let's receive the coins.
Retrieve the coins
for the winning team.
Yes, Jong Kook.
Now...
Aren't you going to use
the 10 R coins?
- Which ones?
- The ones you received as the host.
I will use them. I will use them.
- Thank you, Jong Kook.
- Thank you for your hard work.
You hosted the game without a hitch.
Good job, everyone.
- I sided with you earlier.
- Hold on.
That orange hat is inching close.
That orange hat is inching close...
like a slow-witted fool.
Firstly, I will award those...
who helped me by my side,
Se Chan and Haha.
- Se Chan. Okay.
- Thank you.
Haha.
- Thank you, Jong Kook.
- All right.
Now...
This is really annoying.
(Would you give me one?)
Jong Kook.
Hold on.
- This is...
- What is it?
You will be able to hear
the sound of passing gas.
(Does he finally feel it coming?)
Come here. Hurry up.
(Suk Jin was gathering his energy
at a corner.)
- Hold on.
- Be quiet.
- Did you do it?
- It went back in.
(The gas went back in shyly
because everyone was watching.)
You might end up pooping.
- Didn't you hear something?
- No.
This is a new kind of show.
- You can try anytime...
- Okay.
when it comes to passing gas.
Jong Kook, let's play the game
for three R coins.
Let's do that.
I will bet two R coins instead.
- I will give you a chance.
- Okay.
- Whoever succeeds first wins.
- That's right.
(At that moment)
Are you ready?
Be quiet.
- Be quiet.
(Passing gas)
(What?)
(He passed gas for real.)
(Suk Jin's action
causes a commotion.)
For goodness' sake.
What do you think you are doing?
- He is the worst.
- What was that?
I hate it.
We should check his underwear.
For goodness' sake.
(Jong Kook is highly satisfied.)
What is your problem?
I won't do this.
- Thank you.
- I am all for a new kind of show.
It wasn't a bit of gas.
He passed a lot of gas.
- Suk Jin, I think you pooped.
- I lost too many R coins earlier.
I think you pooped.
- It's my turn.
- All right.
It's my turn, right?
It doesn't smell.
How many coins will the winner get?
The winner will get three coins.
I will throw it lightly.
(Will Suk Jin be able to succeed?)
- That was hilarious.
- Be careful.
(Suk Jin fails.)
- That was close.
- He could have been the champion.
Seriously.
May I pass gas and try again?
Why would you get R coins
with your bowel condition?
I can pass gas.
It was close, right?
Aim for the middle.
Let's go.
Aim for the camera, So Min.
- The camera?
- That's right.
(Se Chan advises So Min
to aim for the camera.)
(What will be the result?)
That's right.
You did it.
So Min, I told you.
- That's right.
- You did it.
(The ball hits the camera
and goes in.)
- It went in...
- How many R coins does she have?
because you aimed for the camera.
How many R coins does she have?
Se Chan!
(What? She is so forward.)
- What are you doing?
- What was that?
Se Chan gave me...
- a tip.
- That's right.
What is that on your left chest?
Is that So Min's name tag?
(Is that So Min's name tag
on his left chest?)
What? What is this?
- My goodness.
- What is this?
- Hey.
- Do you like Se Chan that much?
What is this?
When did you put this on me?
- How did you put it on him?
- How did it happen?
Was it on your bag?
How did it happen?
(Be mine)
(Jae Suk is at it again.)
Jae Suk is the worst.
- Good job, orange hat.
- Was it okay?
All right.
So Min.
(The woman of the left chest,
So Min wins 2 coins.)
So Min is the winner.
- Seriously.
- She has everything.
So Min is the winner.
The first class came to an end.
Will you do the same thing
for the second class?
If four members agree,
you can change the program.
- We must change it.
- Let's change it.
We need to eat ramyeon.
- Okay.
- Let's change it.
- You turned on me right away.
- Let's eat ramyeon.
- Ramyeon.
(Whose lunch will be picked?)
What should we do?
Let's eat something. I am hungry.
How about Yum-yum Time?
We can go with this one.
But the ingredients
will be chosen at random.
Kimchi fried rice sounds nice.
Soo Hyang's Ramyeon
and Kimchi Fried Rice sounds nice.
- I like Soo Hyang's class.
- Me too.
We will be able
to eat kimchi fried rice, right?
- Let's go with Soo Hyang's class.
- Okay.
(Ramyeon and Kimchi Fried Rice)
- Okay. Kimchi fried rice.
- Does that mean...
- You are the host.
- Am I the host?
That's right.
Since Soo Hyang is the host,
she will receive 10 R coins...
to lead everyone well.
(She received 10 R coins.)
Those give you power.
Those 10 R coins give you power.
- Gas gives you power.
- Gas.
- That was hilarious.
- Thank you.
I will return the badge.
We need a lot of money to buy
a pot and such.
- How much...
- We need a pot.
Let's check how much we need.
- One ramyeon.
- I will go since I will cook.
Hey.
This is the place.
(Soo Hyang shops.)
I need more than three rice.
If we have eggs,
fried eggs are good.
Eggs. Let's make fried eggs
and eat with it.
You brought eggs, right?
Byeong Gyu brought these, right?
Yes.
Give me one coin,
and I'll give you all of these.
- This is for everybody.
- Hey.
Wait. Isn't this boiled egg?
No, it's raw.
- Really?
- Yes, I'm sure.
If you don't trust me,
I won't sell them.
- I'll have them for myself.
- Isn't this the only raw egg?
No.
- She's back.
- She's here.
- Let's help her.
- There's a lot.
She bought a lot of pork.
If you obey...
- my orders,
- Yes, ma'am.
- I'll give you some coins.
- Sure.
There's so much to do.
Please obey my orders.
Please give us orders.
We have to do it
even if you don't give us coins.
Sure thing.
- Of course.
- I like that attitude.
We have to do it regardless.
- I like that.
- Is that right?
- Can you do this?
- What should I do?
- Do this.
I'll do it.
I have to work for the money. Okay!
I can make ramyeon very well.
- Ramyeon chef.
- We can make it well.
Please take care of the ramyeon.
Sure.
Are you not going to add eggs
in ramyeon?
These are boiled eggs.
No, these are raw.
This is not fair. These are raw.
What are you doing?
He's trying to sell me eggs.
- Can you wash this?
- Oh, gosh.
Give me one.
- Here.
- He's getting an egg.
This is raw, right?
Here's ramyeon.
He brought eggs.
(He brought eggs.)
What? Hey.
Why did you get eggs?
- Eggs for that.
- Hey.
- What's wrong?
Take it back.
- No.
- Take it back.
I can't do that.
- I can't do that.
- It was so cheap.
How much was it?
- How many did you buy?
- Nine.
- What? How much was it?
- One coin.
- Really?
- It was 10...
- 10.
for one coin.
(It was 1 coin for 10 eggs.)
(Come here, Byeong Gyu.)
1 coin for 10 eggs.
Come here.
- Take it back.
- They're good.
I didn't know about this.
- Give it back.
- No.
- These are better.
- This is from Seoul.
- Hey.
- From Seoul.
- Give it back.
- This is from Seoul.
You already bought it from me.
Oh, gosh.
These are not boiled eggs.
I have raw eggs.
If you give me one coin,
I'll add it.
- In the ramyeon.
- These are actually...
all boiled eggs.
(Interrupting)
- Really?
- Except one.
(Cracking)
- Give it back.
- What a swindler.
(Give it back.)
Come here.
- No.
- Come here, Byeong Gyu.
Listen.
Kwang Soo is gone,
but he's the new swindler.
That little guy.
We checked them together.
You said they weren't boiled eggs.
They're boiled.
Are these all boiled?
They're all boiled except for one.
They're boiled...
(It breaks this time.)
- This is the raw egg.
- This is it.
(This is the raw egg.)
- Oh, my gosh.
- Why?
- Oh, gosh.
Put it in here, So Min.
What were you doing?
Gosh, So Min.
Is this my fault?
- It was raw, right?
- I thought it was his fault.
Oh, gosh.
It was raw.
Ramyeon is ready. We can eat.
(Ramyeon is
the highlight of retreats.)
This looks great.
Give us some too.
Put it in a bowl.
There are many ingredients.
This kimchi is good.
- This is so good.
- Kimchi is good.
- This is good.
- It's so good.
My gosh.
(Slurping)
Ramyeon is great during retreats.
We only need to eat ramyeon.
Ramyeon is good...
when you eat together.
Aren't you happy you bought
the eggs? You can taste it.
Gosh, Byeong Gyu.
I grew up poor.
What does that have to do with this?
You look like a rich boy.
- No.
- No?
People used to say about me.
You look like you were born
during a war.
(You look like you were born
during a war.)
(A flower
that bloomed during the war)
War Diary.
My gosh.
(Ji Hyo is busy eating
while helping Soo Hyang.)
Ji Hyo.
- I'm doing good, right?
- She's helping me.
Did you see me?
(Take this.)
- Soo Hyang.
- Take it.
You can't give it to her
like it's pocket money.
(It's a secret!)
When will the fried rice be ready?
I'm looking forward to it.
- It smells good.
- It's almost ready.
Soo Hyang, this looks good.
It looks really good.
I hope nobody is adding rice...
to the ramyeon.
- No way.
- I hope not.
I hope nobody is adding rice...
(He feels guilty.)
(He doesn't know where to look.)
You have to try this.
They must be shameless.
- That person must be...
- The worst.
- You can't do that.
- They're not even human.
They are not.
She took so long to make it.
What are you doing, Ji Hyo?
Are you making pork belly?
- Yes, I'm making pork belly.
- Amazing.
I have to make pork belly.
- It's so hard being a host.
- This is good.
I'm sweating right now.
You're the mother bird.
Soo Hyang is the best leader.
I have to get paid.
You should get paid.
- This is so good.
- I should pay myself.
Ji Hyo.
Thank you for the food.
- One for you.
- Thank you for the food.
(We worked hard, so let's have them.
Thanks, Soo Hyang.)
Thanks, Soo Hyang.
- Ji Hyo deserves it.
- You should give her one.
- We also...
- You're giving us more?
- What an angel.
- You're an angel.
- Angel.
What hospital was it?
They removed your wings
without leaving any marks.
(What hospital was it?
They removed your wings.)
(It's an angel plastic surgeon
who specializes in removing wings.)
This is amazing.
Good one.
I like it.
You like that?
Soo Hyang is the best leader.
Let's wrap up.
You have to wrap up
the second program.
- I'm still the MC.
- Will you change the third program?
Or will you keep Soo Hyang's?
- I'm the best captain.
- What was it?
- I'm a good captain.
- Mafia Game?
There's Cry in Silence.
Cry in Silence is good.
Hold on. Jae Suk has it too.
- I have it too.
- Soo Hyang has it too.
Me too. Se Chan's...
Kwang Soo will select teams for us.
- Really?
- Me too.
- You have it too.
- I do.
Let's go with Se Chan's.
Kwang Soo will select teams.
We'll call him.
Let's do Se Chan's.
I can call Kwang Soo.
- You didn't write it down.
- You can't.
Why are you trying to steal his?
- Why are you trying to steal 10?
- It's still Cry in Silence.
I can call Kwang Soo.
- Of course.
- Right?
- Can we split 10?
I'll split.
He's going to split 10.
This is good news.
Are you going to split right away?
- We can split too.
- Let's hear him out.
- I'll split too. I told you.
- What?
Once I get 10 coins,
- Right away.
- I won't keep any of them.
- He'll split all.
- I will...
- use them for a good cause.
- He'll use them all.
- Se Chan!
You can talk.
Look. What's a good cause?
They might split it
among themselves.
- I'll give them to you guys.
- That's not true.
- What about us?
- No way.
- Give us some too.
- How many of us?
Up to her.
- Okay!
- We will...
include up to him.
What about me?
- Come here.
- Look.
As the number of people increase,
you get less coins.
- I'll include up to her.
- I'll come.
- Up to her?
Yes. Okay.
- Don't do that.
- Are you guys good?
Sure.
- Keep your words.
- It's my...
Cry in Silence.
Keep your words.
Jae Suk.
- Keep your words.
- We trusted you.
- He's a good host.
- Here's 10.
- Don't worry.
- You're a good host.
This guy is good.
Don't worry.
- He's good in recreation games.
- Give me one.
This is finally
the springtime for the host.
How warm.
- Is this springtime?
- I feel at ease.
- How warm.
- I'm Springtime MC Yu.
- Springtime MC. I know you.
- Springtime MC Yu.
I was waiting for this moment.
I'll distribute the coins
equally later,
- so don't worry.
- Wait.
- Give us one each.
- Sure.
- You have to give us 1.
- Give 1 each.
- One each then.
- He's revealing his true colors.
As I have said...
You need to bring the headsets.
We also have to divide the teams.
We have to buy them.
We have to split teams.
I'll call Kwang Soo.
Sure.
- For teams?
- Ask him to split the teams.
- Let's talk to him first.
- Sure.
He's more relaxed now.
He used to pick up right away.
- I know.
- When he was just injured,
he picked up right away.
He must be crawling around.
- "He must be crawling around."
- He's not crawling.
He won't pick up.
I had the same injury before.
Maybe he's not picking up
because it's you, Jae Suk.
- No way.
- I hope you don't get hurt.
You never know.
- Suk Jin, don't get hurt.
- You never know.
He won't pick up
even if you call him 100 times.
- Oh, gosh.
- He might not like you.
It would be so funny
if he picked up your call.
You might not have his number.
- He didn't...
- "This number is out of service."
He didn't pick up my call.
Will he answer Suk Jin's call?
That cannot happen.
I agree.
- This is a loyalty game now.
- I hope his call gets rejected.
- This is a game.
- We called, and he didn't pick up.
Who will he call back first?
Let's bet one coin for that.
- You sound confident.
- We should call him too.
He must be sleeping.
Suk Jin, let's bet one coin each.
Let's do one each.
That's not bad.
- One each.
- Whoever gets the call first.
The one who doesn't get called
will give up a coin.
- Let's split the teams.
- Let's do that.
- Let's do it.
- We'll do it.
Let's split these three.
It doesn't matter.
- Split these three.
- We'll try our best no matter what.
We have to split you guys,
so let's send the chief that way.
- I'm not the chief.
- Boss.
- You're the boss.
- Should I go that way?
- Leader.
- Should I move?
- What about me?
- You should go twice.
- Good idea.
- Do that.
- Go twice.
Look back.
(Jae Suk will participate
in both teams.)
Does the winning team get five?
Seven.
- 7?
- 7.
- Do we split seven among ourselves?
- Right.
What happens to Jae Suk then?
Does he win no matter what?
(Jae Suk returns
with the game props.)
- Jae Suk.
- What was that?
We have a problem.
- What is it?
- Because...
- Oh, dear.
- the winning team gets seven coins.
Do you not get any?
I have to get some.
You'll win regardless of
which team wins.
- It's unfair.
- But I am the host.
- I should have that perk.
- No way.
I have an idea.
You should hand over three coins.
The winning team has 5 members,
so each member can take 2 coins.
- It's the perfect solution.
- He is right.
- Hand over three coins.
- You are the host.
- Why would I hand over three coins?
- You said earlier...
that you will share all the coins.
- Seriously.
- You changed your words.
Excuse me. Answer this question.
You have no intention...
of sharing the coins
you received, right?
If you continue to be this way,
I can't share them.
- See?
- Hold on. What did you say?
- What are you going to do?
- He changed his mind.
What are you going to do?
We can take those coins from you
with a bit of force.
- My goodness.
- A bit of force.
Guys, count me in.
Don't involve yourself
in this matter.
- Will you steal my coins?
- Listen.
Would you lose everything
or hand over three coins?
- Answer me.
- That's right.
- That's good.
- Hand over three coins.
That's good. That's perfect.
All right. From the MC coins,
- I will hand over three coins.
- That's a good idea.
That's only fair.
- That's right.
- You only used 10 percent.
You only used 10 percent.
Which team should go first?
- Go to the production crew.
- Hold on.
It's an incoming call.
Hand over a coin.
(Is it Kwang Soo?)
If it's Kwang Soo,
you need to hand over a coin.
It's Kwang Soo.
(As everyone but Suk Jin expected,
Kwang Soo called Jae Suk first.)
- Kwang Soo.
- Hey, Jae Suk.
Why didn't you answer
the phone earlier?
I didn't know. I missed it.
Suk Jin called you too.
Yes, Suk Jin called me too.
- Why did he call Jae Suk first?
- Why did you call me first?
I did it without thinking.
(The priority is ingrained
in his subconscious.)
(Opening his pouch)
Give it to me.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes, Jae Suk?
Kwang Soo, do you want to have
a video call?
How is your current appearance?
It's very bad.
(The current appearance is
very bad.)
Kwang Soo, rest up.
- Call Suk Jin too.
- Okay.
Forget it. This is good enough.
(He refuses to be pitied.)
It's okay.
It would be a hassle to call me.
I have nothing to say.
- I have nothing to say.
- Forget it.
- Forget it. There is no need.
- He is cool.
- He is calling me.
- Kwang Soo is calling you.
- Forget it.
Why didn't you answer it?
- Forget it. There is no need.
- Are you sullen?
No, I am not.
Have you ever seen me sullen?
- I am never sullen.
- Are you sure?
I am never sullen.
- Why didn't you answer the phone?
- It's okay. Let's keep shooting.
Let's keep shooting.
- He is sullen.
- I am not sullen.
- Why would I be sullen?
- This is hilarious.
Hold on.
The time limit is 100 seconds.
- 100 seconds.
- Yes.
Read the lips. Read the lips.
- What?
- Copy the lips.
Copy the lips.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- Let's go. Get ready.
(Team Haha starts first!)
This four-character idiom
is well-known.
- Washinsangdam.
- Wa...
- Washin...
- Sangdam.
(It's too easy.)
Washinsara?
Washinsang...
Washinsarang.
For goodness' sake.
(Jae Suk smacks his forehead
in frustration.)
Washinsarang.
- Wa...
- Sarang.
(It's as if there is a wall
between them.)
- Washinsangdam.
- Wa...
- What am I going to do with him?
- Washinsaram.
- Washinsarang.
- He says it with confidence!
Washinsarang.
For goodness' sake.
Hey!
(I delivered it perfectly!)
Washinsarang.
My goodness.
(Ji Hyo passes it on
without a hint of doubt.)
- Washinsarang.
- I don't get it.
Shouldn't they know the idiom
that starts with "Washin"?
Washinsaya.
- What?
- Go.
- Washinsaya.
- What even is "Washinsaya"?
Gwashinsarang.
(Incorrect)
(The game continues to be funny
even after 10 years.)
This is too easy.
- This is too easy.
- They should know this one.
- They should know this one?
- Is it easy?
Gyeolchoboeun.
- It's easy.
- It's too easy.
- Gyeolchoboeun.
- Come on.
Gyeolchoboeun.
(It's the four-character idiom
I had used the last time.)
Gyeolchoboeun.
Keep going.
(They will succeed at this rate.)
Did they get it right?
Endangered...
What?
(Where did "Endangered" come from?)
What? Say it again.
- Thank goodness.
- Endangered sign.
Soo Hyang is ridiculous.
Endangered sign.
"Endangered sign"?
Byeoljubuin?
(Incorrect)
(Amazed)
This one is easy too. Seriously.
(Ileonbangu)
- Seriously.
- Here.
Ileonbangu.
- Yieon.
- Ileon.
- Ileonmangu.
- Ileonbangu.
(His veins pop up.)
Hey!
(He resorts to violence in the end.)
Ileonmangu.
- I am so annoyed.
- Ileon... Ileon...
- Ileonmangu.
- I can't believe him.
- I am so frustrated.
- Ileonmangu.
I can't believe him.
This mandu.
"This mandu"?
How did she get "This mandu"?
This...
What are you saying?
I can't hear you.
- Let me read your lips.
- Haha, your face...
(He is fascinated by the sight.)
This is driving me crazy.
This mandu.
Is this allowed?
Go. Say it.
- Say it.
- Deli Manjoo.
This is driving me crazy.
- Hey!
- Is this allowed?
- You only got the easy ones.
- What?
It was "Ileonbangu."
Ileonbangu. Gyeolchoboeun.
- Ileonbangu.
- How did it become "This mandu"?
- Washinsangdam.
- When did we have "Gyeolchoboeun"?
Where did you get Deli Manjoo?
I heard "Manjoo."
Then I naturally thought
of Deli Manjoo.
For goodness' sake.
Wasn't it "This mandu"?
So Min.
Get ready.
(Jirimyeolryeol)
- My goodness.
- All right.
Jirimyeolryeol.
Jiinbyeolgyeo?
- Jiri.
- Yi.
- Ji...
- Yiyibyeolgyo?
(They will fail too.)
Yirimyeolryeol?
Jirimyeolryeol!
Jirimyeolryeol. Jirimyeolryeol.
Jirimyeolryeol.
- Byul.
- Myeol.
- Ryeol.
- Byulli?
(What is he doing?)
(He leaves it up to Jong Kook.)
Yiyibyeolli.
Ours is too hard.
- Yiyi...
- byeolli.
- Byeol... Yibyeol?
- Yibyeol. Yi...
- Yiyi...
- byeolli.
- Byeolli.
- Yiyi...
(You are watching them play
Cry in Silence.)
- Byeolli.
- Byeol.
- Why are there three characters?
- Yiyi...
- Yibyeolli.
- Byeolli.
(It looks like they will fail.)
They will fail.
- Byeolli.
Yiyibyeolli.
(Incorrect)
(Nangjungjichu)
- I don't know.
Nangjujichu.
(What?)
Dangjuksilsu?
Nangjujichu.
(It's "Nangjungjichu.")
Nang... Nang...
This is a mess.
He forgot the four-character idiom.
Nangwujicho.
- What? What is up with him?
- "Nangwujicho"?
(He is doing whatever he wants.)
Jichu?
What is it?
Give it a try. Give it a try.
Nangdokjihyo?
- Dangyuji...
- Ji...
Dangukjisu.
- What?
- My goodness.
- Dangukjisu.
- No way.
- What is that?
(It doesn't go well.)
He must have gotten it wrong.
Dangyujichu.
- Furniture building.
- Furniture.
- Furniture mistake.
Hurry up.
Furniture mistake.
(Incorrect)
Time's up.
- How many did we get?
- I think we got one right.
- It was hard to read lips.
- You got all of them wrong.
(Both teams fail to win coins
and the last program ends.)
All programs
of Running Man Has Plans ended.
I will announce
1st, 2nd, and 3rd place winners.
(Who are
1st, 2nd, and 3rd place winners?)
- Jong Kook is 1st with 17 coins.
- Okay.
Soo Hyang has 16 coins
and So Min has 15 coins.
The three of them will win prizes.
At the very bottom is...
(Who will receive
an embarrassing penalty?)
At the very bottom is
Suk Jin with 10 coins.
Okay.
It's because I lost in games.
- Suk Jin made too many deals.
- I know.
I didn't win once.
The prizes will be revealed first.
Bring them in.
Are there prizes?
I can't believe I will get a prize.
Will Soo Hyang get one too?
You will have a draw...
- and receive a prize.
- Really?
Yes, you will really receive
a prize.
The prizes range
from a luxury massage chair...
- to the members' autographs.
- Really?
(There is a variety of prizes.)
(1st, 2nd, and 3rd place winners
will have a draw for these prizes.)
I want this one.
- I want this one.
- The prizes are nice.
So Min, you should get a speaker.
- I want it.
- This speaker is nice.
This speaker is nice.
Are these AirPods?
Are there AirPods?
(There is a pair
of the latest Bluetooth earphones.)
AirPods.
Is the massage chair
the most expensive prize?
What is this?
- What are these autographs?
- Autographs?
- What are these?
- We were asked to sign name tags.
- It's my face.
Will we have a draw?
This is me.
- My goodness.
- This is you, Suk Jin.
- Is this a prize as well?
- It's a prize.
How is a cardboard cutout
of Kwang Soo a prize?
- Why would anyone want it?
- I can't believe it's a prize.
It's trash.
(They react strongly
to a shabby prize.)
"It's trash."
(My goodness.)
It would be hard to throw it away.
I will explain the rules.
This will give you
the joy of winning a draw.
It's the lucky prize draw.
1st, 2nd, and 3rd place winners...
can take the 30 prize name tags...
- and arrange them...
- Right.
from 1 to 50 in random order.
You can take
whatever number you pick.
(You can take the prize
that's allocated to the number.)
- Arrange the prizes.
- These?
- Yes.
- Arrange them.
We put these in random order.
- Whatever you pick.
- You've all tried this before.
This is Wolmido Island.
Right.
Then...
Jong Kook, go first.
Sure.
- Is this how I do it?
- Yes.
- If you pick eight,
- Yu San Seul's CD.
you take 3.75g of gold.
- I see.
- Sounds good.
I'm going to cluster them
into lower numbers.
- Low numbers?
- Yes.
I'm going to cluster them
into lower numbers.
First place will arrange them,
and three remaining people
will pick.
Go first, Jong Kook.
I'll win something
as long as it's under 30.
Jong Kook.
- As long as it's under 30.
- This is nerve-racking.
Jong Kook might win gold.
Okay!
- All right. He picked.
- I picked.
- So...
- Silence!
(Silence!)
(Guy with the orange cap hollers.)
Silence.
- What did I do?
- You sounded like a senior.
- You're a senior.
- Be quiet.
- Good job.
- First place is picking.
- I'm first place.
- My gosh.
First place.
- Low number.
- If he gets 30, it's nothing.
- He's okay up to 30.
- Yes, up to 30.
- Wait.
- Why?
- Low, right? Wait.
You're good up to 30.
First digit shouldn't be high.
Why are you taking so long?
Can he take this long?
- I saw the first digit.
- Tell us what it is.
(You saw it?)
No, I didn't win anything!
1st digit is 3!
(He shudders because he's so sad.)
- What number is it?
- 34.
- Oh, dear. It's a dud.
- It's a dud.
(34 is a dud!)
- Good!
- It's you now.
- Second place.
- Keep going.
- Soo Hyang.
- Should I keep it?
- I think it's good.
Change whatever you want.
It doesn't matter.
- I want this the most.
- I agree.
- I want wireless earbuds the most.
- That's the best.
All right. Soo Hyang is next.
- Please pick one.
- I'm nervous.
A dud is better than
something mediocre.
She might win a massage chair
or wireless earbuds.
(Let's see.)
- She's taking a long time.
- She is.
- Why?
- Did you get it?
It must be something big.
- What number is it?
- 20.
(20!)
16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
(Sincerely autographed name tags
of Running Man members)
Autographed name tags of
Running Man members.
(She's ecstatic.)
- What's wrong?
- Why?
This is amazing.
People fight for these.
- This is a legend.
- Kids love these.
- This is awesome.
- This?
Kids love these as holiday presents.
There's Jong Kook, me,
and everybody else.
I came here, and you made me cook!
(She throws them
because she's so deeply moved.)
Take these.
- So Min.
- Kids love these as presents.
Fine. We'll address it to you.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
This looks interesting.
- Okay.
So Min.
I really want to win something.
- You don't need to be first place.
- Take the massage chair.
- Air fryer.
- This is nice.
- It's nice.
- This is useful.
- Right?
- I need an air fryer.
- What's this?
- Okay.
- All right.
So Min.
What number?
I got...
- What's this?
- Did you win?
What number is this?
27.
(27 is...)
- Is it 27?
- Yes.
Air fryer.
Air fryer!
(That's amazing.)
- I wanted this.
- Air fryer.
Jae Suk.
So Min.
- I wanted this.
- It's real.
They really give it to you.
So Min, you win the air fryer.
Congratulations.
(You get your prize right away.)
Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.
There's a penalty as well.
Last place will be treated as
noise cancellation.
Suk Jin, during tomorrow's intro,
- you will not have a microphone.
- Good.
Excellent.
(His audio will be missing.)
- That's excellent.
- Great.
- Just the intro?
- That's a great penalty.
Suk Jin is the most energetic
during the intro.
What will he do?
Byeong Gyu and Soo Hyang
joined us today.
- What did you think?
- They were the best.
It was great seeing you.
- I missed a teaser like him.
- I agree.
I didn't mean to do it,
but I think I teased you too much.
I would like to apologize.
- All of a sudden?
- Now? Pretending to be nice?
You have to keep going. You have to.
- Personalities like you are rare.
- It's rare.
I'm so happy
to see teasers like him.
What about you, Soo Hyang?
I was so happy to be here again,
but am I taking these home
after working really hard?
- People really like these.
- For sure.
- Can I sell these?
- People like them.
- Sure.
- For fan meetings abroad...
- See you later!
(Cruel exile has begun.)
(He's the poor man without audio.)
(They're surprised
to hear this music.)
(The return of Kwang Soo
makes Suk Jin get up.)
(Kwang Soo is back.)
Isn't it "Kwang" for crazy
and "Soo" for water?
(Kwang Soo was looking forward
to coming back, and he turns crazy.)
This finally feels like Running Man.
(Lee Il Hwa is waiting
for her kids.)
(So are Park Mi Sun...)
(and Hwang Young Hee.)
(Kang Daniel is here
to find his mom.)
(In order to become
the moms' kids,)
(they try desperately.)
(I'll rip name tags.)
(Son, you can cut rice cakes.)
(It's a serious war among the moms.)
(Back slapping)
(Tearing name tags)
(Who will protect their mom?)
(Protect Your Mom:
Another Rice Cake to the Ugly Child)