(One March day
at a restaurant in Mapo-gu)
(Haha is the first one to arrive.)
- Is this your first time here?
- Yes.
- Hello.
(Things are somewhat different
than usual for the opening.)
- Hello.
- I know it.
I pretend to know everyone's name.
Namkoong is a unique name.
- Can I go in?
- Yes, please.
(He goes into the filming room.)
(Surprised)
What is this?
(It's an empty room
with no one around.)
What's going on? Why is no one here?
These are seats for the guests.
(There's not even a crew member.)
Why am I alone?
(A sense of anxiety comes over him.)
What's going on?
Hey, why are you here so early?
- I was asked to come early.
- You got a mission, didn't you?
- Not at all.
- I'm sure you did.
(He's misunderstood
just because he came early.)
- Gosh, this is...
- Just tell me the truth.
- Haha.
- This is crazy.
- I'm serious.
- Hello.
- Haha.
- Will you lie to us?
- Hello.
- He was sitting here alone.
- He's a spy.
- It doesn't make sense.
- I was on the fourth floor.
- This is strange.
- What? Are we eating?
- Hello.
- I guess we're eating.
- I think Haha got a mission.
- He came early.
- He was sitting here alone.
What about Haha?
- He was waiting for us.
- What's going on?
- What?
- He was here waiting.
- He's being suspicious.
- We get a bag like this...
all the time.
What?
Since when did we have cameras
that moved like this?
This is amazing.
The camera is moving.
- So Min.
- Don't be silly.
Is this your first time seeing that?
So Min dyed her hair.
Oh, right.
Doesn't she look Russian?
So Min, can you show us?
- Eastern Europe.
- Right. Eastern Europe.
(Tetris dance)
She looks like a woman
from Eastern Europe.
I agree.
- Press it.
- Do we have R coins already?
What?
What? When did we get this?
Hey, if someone picks these up...
- So Min.
- Jae Suk.
We haven't started yet.
You can't do this.
Give me that. Hey.
- Give it back to me.
- This is mine.
- Give it here, punk.
- It's mine.
- So Min, your hair...
- Don't lie to me.
- That's not true.
- You can count them.
How many do you have?
Last time,
- I got gum.
- That's terrible.
- It's the worst.
- Seriously, this is mine.
- Hang on.
- Guys, please help me.
What's wrong with her?
I didn't take your coins.
- What's wrong?
- I didn't take your coins.
You can check my bag.
- Jae Suk hid his.
- Why?
- Stand up.
- We should be a team.
I can't trust you.
- I'm 36 years old now.
- I saw that.
(What really happened?)
(While Ji Hyo looked away,)
(he stole 2 coins.)
(As he tried to put them
in his bag,)
(she gets a glimpse.)
(Give me that.)
(Ji Hyo ended up losing 1 coin.)
It's not over yet.
- It's not started yet.
- We should wait.
Did you watch their commercial?
- They did a commercial together.
- Did you watch it?
I have 18 coins and he has 21.
- Give it to her. Let me count mine.
- We're talking at the same time.
(Tired)
You have 21 coins while we have 20.
I guess we're doing something here.
Let me see.
- You should watch it.
- This is open at the bottom.
(After chatting for a while...)
Why are we doing this?
I was asked not to eat
before I come.
- This is a little awkward.
- What?
- I had a big meal earlier.
- I didn't eat.
(Two women are approaching.)
- Excuse me.
- Gosh.
(Today's guests)
(Comediennes Hong Hyun Hee
and Kim Ji Min)
(Welcome)
- Ji Min.
- You've lost a lot of weight.
- She looks different.
- Hello.
- She's become so prettier.
I haven't changed that much.
- Have a seat.
- You've lost a lot of weight.
You look so much better.
Your face is so small.
You look healthy.
- I like your hair. It looks good.
- Now that I lost weight,
- the wave looks better.
- You look pretty.
You look perfect.
She has a pretty face.
You're so pretty. You look cute.
My features?
Why did you lose weight?
They don't even care about me.
(She's upset that Hyun Hee gets
all the attention.)
- Ji Min.
- So this is how it feels.
- It feels so good.
- We will talk to you too.
- We should talk to Ji Min.
Ji Min's wearing snakeskin.
Right. That's what I'm wearing.
It looks unique.
Is it a jacket?
I just got goosebumps
as I looked to the right.
I just saw Se Chan's face.
After I lost weight,
I gained confidence.
So my husband and I tried this app
where you can switch faces.
And my face was
switched to Se Chan's.
Really?
- Seriously?
- Because I have a protruding mouth.
- They look alike.
- She kept getting Se Chan's face.
- I think they look alike.
- See? I look just like him.
Gosh, look at this.
- This is Se Chan.
- Se Chan!
- This is Se Chan's face.
- Se Chan.
- It's unbelievable.
- My gosh.
(Se Chan is even more surprised.)
Hyun Hee.
If you keep using this app,
you'll get more photos of Se Chan.
This is scary.
- I guess my gene...
- Se Chan.
- My gene is very strong.
- It's really strong.
To be honest, Se Chan
has become ugly these days.
Why?
- He just looks ugly.
- I feel offended.
Why would you feel offended?
- Never mind.
- She didn't mean you.
She didn't say that to you.
You don't have to be mad.
- No.
- She wasn't talking to you.
- You look good these days.
- I feel offended.
I got mad as she said
Se Chan is ugly.
You two look good together though.
- Hello.
- We should place an order.
Thank you.
- Are we eating here?
- Yes.
- What are we doing?
- Are we eating here?
Is this it?
- This is the beginning.
- There must be something.
- I'm sure something's going on.
- We're here to eat.
- Hey, are we teams like this?
- That will be fine.
(Something doesn't feel right.)
I guess we're a team.
- Really?
- Two teams like this?
Let's just eat.
- Hang on.
- Wait. Why is he...
Why are you trying to lead us?
- Did you get a mission?
- He's being strange.
Haha is being strange.
He was sitting here alone
waiting for us.
- I just came early.
- He usually doesn't come early.
I just got here early.
(What is going on?)
- I'll have hairtail.
- Me too.
- I'll have grilled hairtail.
- Grilled hairtail.
Two grilled hairtails, please.
It feels like we're
having a get-together.
Give us some soju and beer.
We're not having a party.
Beer and soju, please.
It's so loud when we're together.
It's not like we're having a party.
What are we doing here?
This is nice though.
- It's very nice to eat together.
- This is our first time.
- There's no trash can in here.
- What?
- I can't throw this way.
- Give me that.
I will...
(Jae Suk goes out
to throw away the garbage.)
Can we get some water, please?
(He keeps asking for something,)
Could you get us some water?
(but it's quiet.)
(Something's strange.)
What is going on?
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
- Give us five coins.
- Why?
Today is a Race of Wits.
We will get five coins from members
who leave the room in an hour.
(Those who leave the room
will hand in 5 coins.)
- My gosh.
- Since you're out,
- you need to give us five coins.
- I'm just here to get some water.
It will be advantageous to you
if you let other members leave.
This is ridiculous.
You left the room without focusing
on the shoot. Give us the coins.
I just came out to throw out
some garbage and get some water.
Everyone's thirsty.
We'd like you to focus
more on the shoot.
(Frustrated)
All right. So this is
how it's going to be.
Five coins.
(He just spilled R coins
feeling frustrated.)
Gosh, I'm so upset.
I can't believe this.
(They all are chatting away
without knowing anything.)
- You mean Jason could do better.
- That's what I thought at first.
(He sits down quietly.)
(He taps Kwang Soo quietly
with his leg.)
(What?)
(Check outside, Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo sensed something.)
(And he leaves quietly.)
(What is it? I guess
something's going on.)
Jae Suk told me to come out.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- You've failed your mission.
- What?
We'd like you
to hand in five R coins.
Why?
Because you didn't
focus on the shoot.
So you need to hand in five coins.
Jae Suk tapped me with his leg
and told me to leave.
You left the room
without focusing on the shoot.
That's not true.
You may go back now.
(Kwang Soo lost 5 coins.)
- I talked to them.
- Why aren't they giving us water?
- Suk Jin.
- What?
The garbage.
The garbage?
- Give me that.
- There's a trash can out there.
Go throw it away.
Thank you.
(He suddenly gives it to Ji Hyo.)
- Here, I'll go.
- Ji Hyo.
Let Suk Jin throw it away.
- Why?
- Ji Hyo does it a lot.
- You should do this.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Suk Jin wins.)
You should do it.
You do it.
Ji Hyo does it all the time.
(Jae Suk just kicks him out.)
(Suk Jin is forced out.)
Where can I throw this away?
- This is crazy.
- There's something here.
- What?
- My gosh.
- What's going on?
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
- You've failed your mission.
We'd like you
to hand in five R coins.
We'll take five coins.
This is ridiculous.
I should tell them to come out then.
I knew it was strange.
- Where did you go?
- What?
(He smiles after fooling him.)
- Where did you go, Kwang Soo?
- He got his mission.
Where is Suk Jin?
- Is he on a mission?
- He's out to throw away garbage.
And why did you go out?
- I went to ask for water.
- I see.
(I should fool Se Chan this time.)
- Se Chan, go ask for water.
- Okay.
- I asked earlier, but...
- I know.
Why are you taking that with you?
Hey, why are you taking the bag?
You'd steal my coins.
I can't let that happen.
I have to keep my coins.
(Kwang Soo tries to fool Jong Kook.)
(You should go out.)
(Okay.)
You can just ring the bell.
Why would you go out?
This is strange.
Why are they all leaving?
- What's going on?
- I just...
need to go to the bathroom.
(Are we supposed to leave the room?)
Kwang Soo just went out
with his injured leg.
- Why are they leaving?
- Why did you do that?
If you're curious,
you should go out.
- So Min.
- What's going on?
(You should go out.)
(Should I go out?)
(Standing up)
(As Suk Jin sends a signal,)
(Ji Hyo gets up too.)
(They feel like they shouldn't be
the last one to leave.)
(Haha gets up too.)
Why are they leaving?
(They just can't hide their smiles.)
- Is something going on?
- What?
What's going on?
Is this a prank?
(Snorting)
(While Jae Suk gives
a snort in joy...)
Se Chan and Jong Kook.
You've failed your mission.
Hand in five R coins.
- What?
- Jae Suk came out, so...
Because he came out.
When Jae Suk came back,
I thought he didn't look happy.
Hand in five coins.
(So Min and Ji Hyo lose
5 coins too.)
Haha, you've failed your mission.
Give us five R coins.
(He hears the bad news
as soon as he gets out.)
I can't believe this.
I'll get them later.
- We have one person left.
- So all the members left the room?
- Yes.
- What? Why?
(He smacks Kwang Soo in anger.)
One more person needs to go out.
(Why are you clapping?
You're the same.)
Why did you do that to us?
Come here.
- I can't believe this.
- Gosh.
What?
(What's going on?)
- What?
- I had no idea.
- Go ask for water.
- Okay, I'll go get some water.
Where do I go?
I was surprised
when I went out there.
You all are unbelievable.
- I know.
- Nice.
- So it's reset.
- I'm so disappointed.
- You are evil.
- You're so mean.
If one of us leaves...
- You're the worst.
- It could happen.
- I shouldn't have left.
- You left because it was strange.
We did it out of greed.
We wanted to get something.
We should've stayed here.
(There's one more victim.)
- Welcome back.
- Hyun Hee. Did you order water?
- So we're starting over again.
- See?
I shouldn't have left.
It was so funny. When I came back,
I just tapped Kwang Soo
with a foot without saying anything.
(And he fell for it right away.)
His face seemed serious.
I had to believe him.
You thought he was
only talking to you.
(Jae Suk's face phishing is
scarier than voice phishing.)
You thought he was
only talking to you.
So I was very moved.
I was deeply touched.
(He was moved as he thought
Jae Suk was being nice to him.)
I'm cautious about what I do.
What would be next?
If we go out of the room again,
do we have to pay again?
- I don't know.
- I'm not sure about that.
If you leave again,
something good might happen.
It might be something good.
I should go out then.
- I will.
- Hey.
(As Jae Suk tries to leave...)
(Kwang Soo sprints out.)
- That was quick.
- Is his leg okay?
Is his leg okay?
- Why is he so fast?
- He's just like before he got hurt.
He walks fine.
(He's like Keyser Soze
from "The Usual Suspects.")
(Keyser Kwang Soo)
(He hurries his steps as if
he needs to go to the bathroom.)
Kwang Soo, you are out again.
Since you didn't focus on the shoot,
I'll get another
five coins from you.
Give me your coins.
You did it before.
(He has come all the way here
with his injured leg.)
Are you serious?
(Wasn't it a good thing?)
He's back. Look at his face.
Okay? He said okay.
You lost another five coins, right?
No.
Let me tell you one thing.
- It's begun.
- We don't have much time.
- It's done.
- There's not much time.
- Just have a seat.
- Okay.
As he came back in...
I'm curious though.
Because...
- it might be a double fake.
- That's right.
- That's what I'm afraid of.
- A double fake.
There might be something good.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors
and let the loser go out.
(He fails to hold himself back
and gets up.)
What if we get 10 R coins?
What if they give 20 R coins?
Is that it?
We might get all the coins
they collected earlier.
- What?
- They got five coins from us each.
I'm telling you this because
I can't go out again anyway.
I can't go out again.
But there aren't many chances left.
No.
Wait, Suk Jin.
- Wait.
- Let me go.
The unlucky ones are moving now.
It means it's not good.
I'm serious.
I'm only saying this because
I can't go out again.
The unlucky ones are moving now.
I pushed him out.
(He forces Suk Jin out.)
It was your plan.
- I let Suk Jin out.
- You pushed him out.
Good job.
It was like when you pretend
to throw a ball...
and your dog would fall for it.
- He looked just like that.
- He fooled Suk Jin.
Is it a good thing or not?
Just be honest with us.
It's not good.
- It's a good thing.
- Is it good?
You'll see it on Suk Jin's face.
We should wait and see
how Suk Jin reacts.
Since you didn't focus again,
I'll get another five coins.
(No, it's not good.)
(His blood pressure is going up.)
Please stay focused.
(Sad)
This is a war of wits.
I know.
It's like "believe it or not."
It's not a good thing.
He smiled as soon as he got in.
He's bitter.
He's smiling because
it's something absurd.
- He's mad.
- How can I put this?
(Everybody is looking at him.)
- Is nobody else going?
- No.
- That's not it.
- Let's just see what happens.
- Are you going again?
- Are you seriously not going?
Leave him.
- Are you going again?
- Are you seriously not going?
(No, we're not going.)
- We're not going.
- He just said...
- he can't go more than twice.
- He did.
Why are you trying to...
- aggravate us?
- Are you really not going?
- I'm serious.
- You said you can't go again.
- Go ahead.
Why are you going again?
He has the door open. Go.
- Stop it.
- Why are you doing this?
- Are you not going?
- Hey, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
- Move.
- What?
But...
- He got tricked.
- Sit down.
Just sit.
(It sounds like he's acting.)
That makes me actually want to sit.
What was that for?
What's wrong with you?
I was about to go out.
I was about to go,
but I sat down because of Suk Jin.
"Just sit."
He never shares anything good.
I'm relieved.
(I almost had them.)
Focus. Why do you keep
going back and forth?
- That's why you're losing coins.
- Focus!
- That was too obvious.
- Sit.
- Are you sure? Okay.
- We're not going.
(He goes out for the 3rd time.)
What's going on?
- He's trying to trick us.
- It's a race.
- It's something good.
- He said he can't go out again.
He would have gone
back and forth already then.
- It doesn't make sense.
- You can't go more than twice.
Jae Suk is so gullible.
Do you want to go?
Are you sure about this?
I'm not sure.
Move over. I can't resist.
- Throw out one of them.
- I can't resist.
Are they both going?
(Kwang Soo came out first.)
Kwang Soo...
Since you didn't focus on filming
for the third time,
so you must pay five coins.
So you must pay five coins.
(Kwang Soo slaps his cheek in fury.)
- Does this keep going?
- When will you focus?
Focus? I'm focusing.
I'm focusing on the mission.
Please focus on the conversation.
(He pays 5 more coins
for a total of 15 coins.)
(He looks lonely from the back.)
I couldn't resist.
(2 more guests come.)
Since you didn't focus on filming
again, you must pay five coins.
- I thought we'd get something good.
- It's not.
Please focus.
Why did you push me?
My gosh.
(They take out 5 coins to pay.)
(Dropping)
(A coin drops from Ji Hyo's bag.)
(He picks it up quickly...)
(and pays as if it was his.)
(Thanks, Ji Hyo.)
Why do I only have eight?
That's weird.
(While Cavewoman Ji Hyo
is confused,)
(Jae Suk returns disappointed.)
This time...
Your front teeth are protruded.
- He's dejected.
- Let's watch.
He doesn't look happy.
I'll tell you that
there aren't that many spots left.
I believe that.
Jong Kook,
I'll go and decide for myself.
(Se Chan gets up.)
- Our food is here. Let's eat first.
- What's that?
Let's eat.
(Current Number of Coins)
There must be a mission about food.
That's possible,
but what could it be?
Shouldn't we just enjoy our food?
Maybe you're not supposed to talk
with food on the table.
That's possible.
No talking while eating.
No, that's the wrong etiquette.
You have to laugh while you eat
for good digestion.
- We can enjoy our food, right?
- Thank you.
(Let's worry about the mission
after the food.)
- I want to go out so badly.
- This grilled hairtail is huge.
It's so good.
It's delicious.
It's good.
- This is delicious.
- It's good.
- Thank you.
- It's amazing.
It's good.
(They forget about the mission
and gobble down the food.)
This is good.
It's delicious.
- Didn't you order grilled fish?
- I know.
Kwang Soo and I ordered
the braised fish.
Let's share.
Share?
(He says "share"
when he steals other people's food.)
What language was that?
People who went already are
eating quietly.
I don't know about Jae Suk.
- I'm curious. This drives me nuts.
- Me too.
I don't think I can digest my food.
It makes me think.
- Ask Ji Hyo.
- Should I go?
Listen to her voice.
She sounds different.
(Try this, Se Chan.)
(He rejects her.)
It's nothing.
- I'm just giving it to you.
- I don't want it.
It's not a mission.
She gave me her yellow corvina.
What am I supposed to do?
Do I need to eat it?
(I thought something else
for a moment.)
That was great.
- I didn't eat from the bowl.
- I'll take it then.
- That was good.
- That was delicious.
(At that moment,
the producer comes up to the door.)
The hairtail was good.
(I see somebody moving.)
Do you have any white radish left?
Can you give me one?
(Jae Suk approaches the door
carefully.)
Jae Suk, don't look too serious.
- Come out, Jae Suk.
- Why?
- He's calling you.
- You finished eating first.
- Why is he calling you?
- You put down your spoon first.
He made eye contact
with the producer.
Because we can't go out.
If the person in front of you is
still eating,
- it's bad table manners to leave.
- You know what, Kwang Soo?
He got up.
I understand up to two times.
(There are many speculations
as Jae Suk leaves the room.)
Why? I didn't do anything wrong
this time.
- It's not me this time.
- Jae Suk.
(Why did he call me?)
(After a while)
Can I have some more?
Sure. The head?
- He looks happy.
- My gosh.
Jae Suk, you got up
when we didn't finish.
(They think he lost more coins.)
Come out, Suk Jin,
- Sure.
- Why?
What's going on?
Do you get more coins
if you go out early?
I think so.
I think you're right.
(He walks to the producer
nervously.)
- Suk Jin.
- Yes.
(What happened to
Suk Jin and Jae Suk?)
Maybe not.
I think something happened.
- I think these two are done.
- What is it?
Who?
Come out, Jong Kook.
- Who?
- Who was that?
- He called Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
That was so random.
- Me?
- What is it? The water?
He didn't finish his food.
- He didn't go out.
- What is it?
(What could it be?)
Are we not supposed to
have leftovers?
I think so.
(They can't tell
from these two's faces.)
(He's very intrigued.)
- Jong Kook.
- What is it? Yes.
For a smooth resumption of filming,
three people who finished eating
first will receive R coins.
You got third place.
(That's what it was.)
(They were eating
just 5 minutes ago.)
(He's done eating.)
(His plate is clean.)
(Jae Suk finished eating first.)
(After Jae Suk,)
(Suk Jin put down his spoon.)
(Jong Kook was next.)
(His plates are clean.)
(They received 10 R coins each!)
This is becoming...
- What is it?
- Why? Did you lose some?
What did he do again?
He doesn't look happy.
I know. He used his chopsticks
incorrectly.
My chopstick skills are by the book.
It's by the book. I'm so good.
- You're actually good.
- Anyhow.
I don't know what it is.
Picky eaters.
Picky eaters?
Was it people who were picky eaters?
- I ate everything that was here.
- Me too.
I did.
I'm full.
- I'm full.
I'm full too.
I don't think this is it.
- What is it?
Look at his face.
We can't help it.
It has to do with coins.
They look like people
who lost coins.
Can we only go out if we get called?
(Touching)
You ate as much as you wanted to.
(Jae Suk, is this a sign?)
He kicked him.
(Of course, Kwang Soo.)
You can't just go.
How many times has he gone out?
(He received Jae Suk's sign,
so he excitedly goes to the staff.)
Why did you come?
Your name wasn't called.
- Sorry?
- I didn't call you.
Jae Suk sent me a sign.
No?
He tricked you.
Jae Suk, he asked me why I came
when he didn't call me.
Why did you send me a sign?
It doesn't work that way.
(It's fun making fun of Kwang Soo.)
I know now.
You can't go even if you get called.
We're not done eating.
(That's not it.)
I got goosebumps.
Haha. Wasn't that observant?
- I finished eating.
- The person next to you.
- They're here.
- What?
- What's going on?
- Is it over?
- It's over. It's done.
Like Se Chan said.
We weren't supposed to
go out, right?
What am I supposed to do?
You met up in this restaurant
and had breakfast...
while the staff conducted
a hidden Game of Wits.
The first mission was...
to focus on your peers
during filming...
and not to leave the room.
People who left got coins deducted
according to the number of times.
Kwang Soo must be broke.
Did you pay?
- But then...
- That's insane.
He said "this time," so I thought
it would be different next time.
- Why did he do that?
- That's awful.
- What was the 2nd one?
- The 2nd mission was...
for a smooth resumption of filming,
three people who finished
eating first...
- All right!
- received R coins.
(That's what it was.)
People who finished eating first?
There were also people who finished
late and delayed filming.
So Min and Ji Hyo
will have to pay five coins each.
(So Min and Ji Hyo have to pay
5 coins each.)
They were slow.
(While the staff was coming in,)
(Ji Hyo and So Min were
still eating.)
Why did you eat so slowly?
I always eat slow.
- I eat slow.
- They were nibbling on their food.
There were hints in this room
regarding the missions.
- Here?
- Where?
There were inside napkins
and so on, but we'll tell you later.
- We used all the napkins.
- Really?
I have the napkins.
Why do you have them?
There's something written here.
What does it say?
"Within this hour,
it's more beneficial for you..."
- "if other members leave."
- I see it.
Is it written on it?
- They printed this on the napkins?
- Nobody looked.
- You should've shared these.
- Seriously?
I took them
because I have a runny nose.
(Haha was first to arrive.)
Gosh, I'm starving.
Why is this here?
(Why is this here?)
(He pushed away the napkins
that contained clues.)
(Ji Hyo took the napkins
that Haha pushed away.)
(She wiped her nose with the clues.)
(Then she kept them all to herself.)
- But...
- We need to inspect our pockets.
- The napkins...
- She took them all.
She stashed them for herself.
We should check
our pockets from now on.
- The napkins...
- On the napkins?
- Unbelievable.
- Just like you experienced,
you will be rewarded today
depending on how witty you are.
The race is called
Hey, You Can Find Out Too!
The missions will pop up randomly.
Depending on your actions,
you will either lose or gain coins.
The two with
the most amount of coins...
will be given a chance
to pick an ungraded prize.
An upgraded prize?
You'll now change outfits
and then head to the next location.
- Got it.
- Sure thing.
Let's get on the bus.
- Understand?
- Many were tested.
- Yes.
- What a twist.
- Hold on.
- Don't you agree?
What's this?
(Who's waiting for the members?)
(Assistant Director Son
is holding up his hand.)
(What would you do if you saw him?)
(His hands have been sanitized.)
(Kwang Soo runs forward...)
(and slaps his hand.)
- Wait.
- What's this?
I think we need to high-five him.
(Slap)
I walked right past him.
- I was first.
- I was third.
(Whatever the mission is...)
I was second.
(Does the order matter?)
(Suk Jin also slaps his hand.)
Just get on the bus.
(Hyun Hee gives him a hug.)
(Goodness)
Wait, what now?
(Peck)
(Hyun Hee slaps his hand
after doing everything else.)
(Ji Min gives him a hug
but doesn't slap his hand.)
Shouldn't we bump his hand
with our elbow?
- Really?
- Of course not.
(So Min lets out scissors.)
(It could be a game
of rock-paper-scissors.)
Just get on the bus.
(She then slaps his hand.)
(And then she hugs him.)
Have you been here all this time?
This seems like
another hidden mission.
Everything feels like a mission.
I swear!
(Was he in the Boy Scouts?)
Okay.
Please buckle in.
Actually, this bus seems new.
(What was the mission?)
I think I was able to get it right.
I think he's about to tell us.
- The high-five...
- Is that what we should've done?
No, you shouldn't have.
- I was first.
- You see...
Let me reveal the result
of the third Game of Wits.
- Was there another one?
- We shouldn't have done anything.
Some of you high-fived
Assistant Director Son.
- That's right.
- I wasn't going to,
but Kwang Soo
made me question my decision.
- It could be a good thing.
- I shouldn't have.
Ji Min, Jong Kook,
and Ji Hyo didn't slap his hand.
(Ji Min, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo
didn't high-five him.)
We value how you didn't
kiss up to the staff...
and that wins you two R coins each.
- What?
- Nice!
Okay!
Are you kidding me?
How is a high-five
considered as kissing up to someone?
(He can't believe it.)
(Kwang Soo ran over
even with his injured leg.)
(The other 7 members
kissed up to the staff.)
We're friends,
so a high-five meant nothing!
I can't believe
you'd put it that way.
We didn't give him a high-five
to kiss up to him.
I only high-fived him
so that he wouldn't feel awkward.
So everything
is linked to a mission.
You can't keep punishing those
who are willing to take action.
I hate how you put it
as "kissing up" to him.
- Exactly.
- That's hardly the case.
- He's right.
- Besides,
why would we kiss up to Soo Yong?
- Tell me about it.
- Why would we?
(He suffers a loss for some reason.)
Anyway, you shouldn't do anything
that has nothing to do...
with the show.
- Okay.
- I hope we get going.
Let's go!
(Let's go!)
- There's more.
- We commend...
Se Chan's active participation
of yelling "Let's go"...
and reward him with five R coins.
(Se Chan receives 5 R coins.)
- What on earth?
- Let's go!
Nice!
- Are you kidding me?
- Five coins?
- This is too random!
- Let's go.
- Let's begin filming!
- You're too late.
- We're already filming,
- so why would you say that?
- We're already filming.
Sir, please drive safely.
That's you kissing up to him.
The director is...
giving out random missions
whenever he feels like it.
- That's not the case.
- The rules are set.
We already set the rules
and have filmed that separately.
They're not random.
There's no way
he'd do things on the fly.
- Unbelievable.
- Be wittier, Kwang Soo.
- My gosh.
- So now...
Se Chan, for some reason,
you look like a sardine today.
A sardine? What's that?
- Don't you know what it is?
- Isn't that bait?
- Sardines.
- The kind that you pickle?
Don't you know what is it?
It's the fish you feed dolphins.
- As bait.
- Bait?
No, it's food.
- It's bait used to catch big fish.
- Yes, it's used as bait.
But still...
(He suddenly bursts into laughter.)
- What's going on?
- I'm actively reacting.
I doubt that's one of the missions.
You never know. It could've been.
(He desperately tries
to win R coins.)
You never know, right?
Gosh, what a bummer.
My gosh.
I'd like to receive some R coins.
There's no way to know
what the missions are.
- I'm completely broke.
- I don't have many either.
Ji Hyo, are you broke?
Yes.
Then forfeit the game.
Jae Suk, don't be ridiculous.
Unbelievable.
You guys...
Look at you all
trying to win R coins.
What I said made sure...
that Ji Hyo and I
didn't get edited out.
Also, did you check out my reaction?
- Isn't that worth R coins?
- You did well.
- There you go.
- He commended you.
- Congratulations.
- Just a compliment?
- Good job.
- It's as if he's teasing us.
How do we get him
to pay us R coins?
- Why would you put it like that?
- We're not in Sangam-dong yet.
We're going somewhere else.
Something must be up.
Get ready for the next mission.
Sir, we're not in Sangam-dong!
You're going the wrong way.
- Unbelievable.
- I know what it is.
We're taking the wrong path.
Let's not be silly.
- What was that?
- What did you say?
- Wasn't that it?
- Kwang Soo...
You sounded like
a translation device.
I'll drive!
- We're all taking action.
- I'll drive.
It's all right, sir.
Drive as safely as you want.
(They've never been
this proactive before.)
- It's all right.
- Go, sir!
- This is great.
- Everyone makes mistakes.
Why don't we sing songs
just like we do on picnics?
(In the spring breeze)
(They sing along in hopes
of winning R coins.)
(Jong Kook is most proactive.)
(The R Coin Effect)
- It is spring for sure.
- It's nice to be with you all.
Can we hear Yu San Seul's song?
(Hyun Hee makes a request.)
(All of it)
- Hold on.
- Just redevelop it
I bet this isn't
just for the R coins.
(The R coins bring out
their party DNA.)
Any more requests?
We're all doing our best
to earn a few coins.
I mean, just take
a look at Jong Kook!
- He's on a roll.
- What's gotten into him?
(The R Coin Effect continues.)
- What's next?
- I'm happier
(He was furious about being told
that he kissed up to someone.)
Suk Jin makes it sound
like an oldie though.
(Suk Jin makes it sound
like an oldie though.)
(You're mine, ha!)
- Gosh.
- It sounds so old-fashioned.
I love it when songs
are changed up that way.
We'll soon arrive at
the broadcasting station.
We're almost there.
Where are we heading then?
- So we're almost there.
- We have arrived!
You will get off the bus
with the person you trust the most.
- Please team up.
- A team of two?
- Yes, a team of two.
- So Min,
Kwang Soo, and...
- Jae Suk too.
- Yes, him.
- You included.
- As you know, I'm trustworthy.
Ji Min, how would
you describe yourself?
I'm quite witty.
- Then I choose Ji Min.
- Sure.
How about we team up?
- Jong Kook, what do you say?
- Ji Min and I.
- I'd love to team up with Se Chan.
- I choose Jong Kook too.
Of course,
I'd choose my comfort doll.
I'll team up with whoever wants me.
- And I...
- Me!
I...
- Kwang Soo...
- I promise.
- Should I take it back?
- You'll be with Kwang Soo?
Yes, Kwang Soo.
Gosh, I'm grateful.
I'm teaming up with Ji Min.
- Suk Jin, you and me?
- Sure thing.
I'll team up with Ji Hyo.
- I...
- Who else?
Your name hasn't come up yet,
so stay put.
- Jae Suk...
- Jae Suk,
I'll team up with you
for one R coin.
I have no intention of doing that.
Let's hurry then.
Jong Kook and Se Chan
can leave first.
All right.
Get ready for Kook and Chan.
Kook and Chan, here we come!
(What mission awaits them?)
Kook and Chan!
(SBS Prism Tower, Sangam-dong)
They're filming from a distance,
so let's say hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Among the flowers
(Their energy runs too high
because of today's mission.)
There's another camera
filming from afar.
I wonder what they have
in store for us.
- I'm curious.
- I'm excited.
- My heart's pounding.
- Mine too.
(Kook and Chan
couldn't be more excited.)
I wonder what game
we'll be playing.
- I'd love to get to work.
- Where are we headed?
I can't wait to start filming.
I can't wait.
Third floor. Here we are.
- Where are we supposed to go?
- This way. What now?
- We need to start filming already.
- I know.
I wonder what's going on.
Don't forget the hand sanitizer.
- Once more?
- Of course.
(Is using the hand sanitizer
their mission?)
- Does it work?
- Yes, a lot comes out.
Okay. Let's go.
- Se Chan.
- What is it?
- I see R coins.
- What?
(R coins are dropped on the floor.)
- Didn't you see it?
- I didn't.
- This...
- Hold on.
(This must be a mission!)
- Se Chan.
- I didn't see it.
Are we supposed to split these?
Say we're filming.
These are props
used by our show only.
- Let's say someone dropped them.
- Right.
- So taking them...
- Okay.
would be a bad move.
- Still...
- Yes?
They could be here...
for us to take though.
As a reward for paying attention?
There is more than one coin, right?
So if we split them...
- No, wait.
- We shouldn't take them?
To me,
these look like...
they were dropped.
Someone dropped them by mistake?
It doesn't say anywhere
that we should take them.
- Right.
- We shouldn't do anything...
that the staff
doesn't want us to do.
You're right.
- What do you say?
- You're right today.
What Director Choi...
doesn't tell us to do...
Why are you brimming
with energy today?
- We shouldn't take them.
- Right.
We came here to shoot,
and they said, "Please go up."
So we came up here. Wait.
There are coins on the floor.
Is there anything written here?
Did our producer leave a note? No.
- Should we just go?
- We should leave them here.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
I think you got it perfectly right.
All right.
- Here come good citizens.
- Yes.
- Only do what you're told to do.
- We're good citizens.
- Jong Kook to the Assembly!
- Yes!
Don't stab me in the back.
No way.
Don't stab me in the back,
seriously.
You can't stab me in the back,
but I can stab you in the back,
so be careful.
You know I'm smart, right?
Right?
I'm pretty smart.
Don't even think of
stabbing me in the back.
(Welcome)
- These days...
- What's that?
- What is it?
- Oh, my.
(Whatever it is, I'll pick it up.)
- What's that?
- Unbelievable.
What's that?
I can't believe this.
(Suk Jin sounds excited.)
We're not supposed to take it,
are we?
- We should just leave it here.
- Right?
You shouldn't take something
that doesn't belong to you.
- I shouldn't...
- It doesn't belong to you.
- I don't think I should take this.
- No.
Right?
I don't believe in...
- unexpected good luck.
- But...
I don't know what to do.
I'm slow-witted.
I hate these things.
It bothers me.
- There are 30 coins.
- Gosh.
With these,
you'll move up to the first place.
- Let's split them 50-50.
- Okay.
It's no big deal
if they take them away.
(They fail to let go of
their greed.)
- Hi.
Did you take something
that isn't yours or not?
- Who says it's not ours?
- Who knows if it's just good luck?
Who knows if it's
unexpected good luck?
The staff...
- never told us to take them.
- It shows your personality.
We should trust each other.
Why would we not trust each other?
- Right? Always trust each other.
- Definitely.
Can I...
(Haha steps on the coins.)
(Haha finally notices the coins.)
Gosh, that's bad luck.
You dropped your coins?
(Ji Min thinks
Haha dropped his coins.)
Gosh, why did I drop them?
What happened?
(Smiling)
(Haha pretends
the coins belong to him.)
You and... Who is it?
- Ji Min? What did you do?
- What did you do?
- What do you mean?
Did you find anything on the floor?
(Be quiet.)
- Did you find them?
- What did you do?
- We know you did.
We all found them.
Ji Min, did you pick anything up
from the floor?
Did you pick?
- I didn't...
- What happened?
(What happened between these two?)
You took them
without telling Ji Min?
I thought they dropped
from your bag.
They did.
- Gosh.
- Unbelievable.
- You're so mean.
- I...
- They dropped from my bag.
- We're supposed to take them.
They told us to team up
with a trustworthy person.
- We're supposed to take them.
- That makes sense.
- Even if you pick them up first...
I mean...
They dropped from my bag.
(Ji Min is betrayed
by her partner..)
- Trust me.
- Hey.
So Min, you have to trust me today.
- We have to trust each other.
- Okay.
- Wait. What is that?
- What is that?
Well...
I guess they're for us.
- They're for us?
- Yes.
We're probably doing something
with these.
It's a test.
Let's return them to the staff.
They were on the floor.
- They don't belong to us.
- We should return them.
- Let's find out who they belong to.
- We should do the right thing.
We want to find out
who these belong to.
(They look for the owner
of the coins in the empty hallway.)
- Why is no one answering?
- But there are so many.
Should we take just one?
Hey, you shouldn't do this.
They won't even be able to tell.
Let's just take one each.
Hey, we shouldn't do this.
- There are so many.
- No way.
- You're being ridiculous.
- You don't have so many coins.
- How many do you have?
- Still, we shouldn't take these.
I know that, but...
- no one will know if we take one.
- We can't.
You're being dishonest.
It won't even show.
What are you talking about?
Let's just count how many there are.
I knew it.
- Let's just count them.
- You want to take them, don't you?
- You want to. Be honest.
- I'm just counting them.
So Min is persuading Ji Hyo.
She's persuading Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is getting sneaky
these days too.
- Don't take anything secretly.
- I won't.
Don't take anything.
I'm good at these tests.
I never cheat on tests.
We just found them on the floor.
They don't belong to us.
We should go in here.
- They're finally here.
- Those two...
We decided to return these
to the staff.
- Yes, we're returning them.
- We just picked them up.
We're returning these.
- You're returning them?
- Yes, we'd like to return them.
(The last pair appears.)
Why is no one here?
For this game,
we have to trust each other.
- We should rely on each other...
- Exactly.
and help each other out.
(As soon as he sees the coins,)
(he picks them up and runs away.)
(Until 3 seconds ago,
they were talking about trust.)
We should trust...
Give them to me.
(When Hyun Hee picked Kwang Soo,
everyone expected this to happen.)
- Wait.
- It's started.
Seriously.
- He took everything?
- Is this a comedy show?
- He took everything.
- Give them to me.
(Kwang Soo loses control again.)
Did you two fight?
- Yes, a little.
- Did you pick those up?
You said we're a team.
We are.
What's going on?
- On your way here,
- Yes.
- did you all see the coins?
This mission was about...
sharing happiness together
without suspecting each other.
- Okay.
- You can keep the coins.
- Okay!
The one who took the coins...
- "Okay"?
- Don't worry.
What are you talking about?
Give them to me right now.
Seriously, don't worry.
I mean...
If you pick up something
on the street,
you're supposed to return it
to its owner.
We returned them to you.
Shouldn't we get at least one?
You're too nice.
At least show me.
I didn't even see them.
I'm glad I didn't pick
Kwang Soo or Haha.
Gosh, we're a team.
(Hyun Hee and Kwang Soo
finish the game...)
(looking silly.)
Should I carry them for you?
You can win more R coins
in this mission.
- It's called Break the Basket.
- What's that?
The winning team can win R coins...
from the box of wits.
One member of each team...
will sit under the team's basket.
Two members of each team will put on
gloves and put a gym ball...
under their shirts
and deliver bean pouches...
to the members under the baskets.
They can push others outside
the lines with their bellies.
When you're pushed out,
you have to pause for 10 seconds.
Each basket contains
100 ping pong balls,
which will be exchanged with coins.
The number of the ping pong balls
you catch from the basket...
plus 25 will be the number of coins
you can receive.
Divide into teams.
(They divide into teams.)
(Team White: Ji Min, Jae Suk,
Haha, So Min, and Se Chan)
(Team Blue: Hyun Hee, Suk Jin,
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo)
Are you allowed to punch others?
He's intimidating us.
(Do you have a problem?)
He's glaring at us.
Se Chan, you can beat Jong Kook.
(He has no chance.)
I like it.
- Go!
- Let's start.
- Let's do this!
- You can do this!
- Ready.
- Knock him down.
They're targeting you.
(Jong Kook pushes 2 people at once.)
Push Suk Jin!
- What are you doing?
- What's going on?
Get the bean pouches!
(Se Chan tries to deliver
bean pouches to Haha.)
(He gets blocked by Jong Kook.)
Get the bean pouches!
I can't pick them up.
(All you have to do is
toss bean pouches.)
(But it turns into wrestling.)
Wait. I have to toss it like this?
- Like this?
- Hurry up.
- Suk Jin, bring me bean pouches!
- No!
Jong Kook has to defend.
Why can't I pick them up?
Suk Jin!
Either defend
or bring me bean pouches!
- Come on!
- Push him out!
- Hey!
- He's out.
(He gets pushed out
without doing anything.)
- Suk Jin is out!
- Now!
(Frustrated)
Goodness, Suk Jin!
Why are you on our team?
(In the end, Jong Kook uses force.)
Se Chan is out.
Let's finish him off.
(With Suk Jin out, Jong Kook
successfully delivers bean pouches.)
Aim higher, Kwang Soo!
(He misses the basket.)
(Team Jong Kook's hope
is thrown away.)
(Kwang Soo turns out to be
a bigger problem than Suk Jin.)
I figured it out.
(Even though Haha doesn't have
many bean pouches,)
(he hits the basket every time.)
- Hang in there!
- Haha.
You're almost there.
(All his 3 bean pouches
hit the basket.)
You're almost there. Keep going.
- It's starting to break.
- It's breaking.
(The basket finally breaks.)
(His team can win as many coins
as the ping pong balls he catches.)
(How many ping pong balls
will Haha catch?)
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
- Okay!
- Haha!
- What did you do?
- You should have caught them.
- How many did you catch?
- You should have caught them!
What did you do?
What's with you?
I mean...
I was so focused
on breaking the basket.
The losing team also has
a chance to win coins.
What's that?
- What's that?
- Is it like drawing lots?
We get to select a number.
(6 boxes of wits are brought in.)
- "Take coins from the other team"?
- Yes!
The rules are simple.
The losing team will distribute
the balls the winning team caught...
among the six boxes of wits
in secret.
Each member of the winning team
will choose a box...
and get to keep the coins
in the box.
The coins in the remaining box
will go to the losing team.
Okay.
There are 31 ping pong balls
in total.
The losing team will distribute them
now. Please turn around.
- Okay.
- Turn around. Go away.
Put at least one ball in each box.
- Put 1 ball in each box first.
- Put 1 in each.
Put one in each.
- Do it quietly.
- You can't hear anything.
- Suk Jin, I'd like to ask a favor.
- Keep calm.
- Please don't say anything.
- Right.
- Don't even touch the balls.
- I can't say anything?
I can't say anything?
- Don't say anything.
- When they choose boxes,
can you step out for a moment?
- Please.
- I can't do that.
How about putting all of them
in one box?
- Seriously?
- In one box?
- Should we...
- Or in two boxes?
- Let's put them in two boxes.
- That'd be better.
Or one?
(How will the losing team distribute
the ping pong balls?)
You didn't put all of them
in one box, did you?
- What?
- We can't tell you.
- I think they did.
- You put all of them in one box?
- Each box has at least one ball.
- I know.
- The rest would be in one box.
- Exactly.
- We didn't discriminate.
- One box has all the balls.
If you look inside, you will suffer
dismemberment.
- Let me... What?
- What? Dismemberment?
Do you even know
what dismemberment means?
Isn't it some kind of harassment?
(He has no idea.)
- It involves cutting off the limbs.
- Is it that bad?
- Yes.
- I was so startled.
- Your limbs get pulled off.
It was a punishment for treason
back in the days.
I lack the vocabulary.
I choose...
number two.
Number two. Please pick a box each.
I need to figure out
what they are thinking.
I bet...
Jong Kook made the decision.
(He pretends to be sharp.)
I bet the four of them
blindly followed his decision.
How did you know?
Did you take a peek?
- All right.
- Did you hear us talk?
All right. I choose number five.
(Jae Suk chooses number 5.)
- Haha.
- Number four.
(Haha chooses number 4.)
I choose number six.
Number 6? Then you are number 1.
I don't have a choice.
- Open the boxes from number one.
- Shall we do that?
- Number one.
- Yes.
1, 2, 3.
(How many balls are inside?)
How many balls are there?
There are a lot.
(Full of balls)
- Are there many?
- 5, 6, 7, 8,
- 9, 10, 11.
- There are many.
They put all the balls in there.
Yes. They put all the balls
in there.
- Number 2.
(Se Chan chose number 2.)
(He opens the box!)
There is one.
(Jae Suk opens box number 5!)
(It's a jackpot.)
- There are a lot.
- Number five has a lot.
- How many balls are there?
- In my box?
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
- 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16.
- There are a lot.
- 15, 16.
- We will check.
You got a lot of balls.
- I got 1 ball.
- Shall we open number 3?
Number 3 has 1 ball.
(1 ball that was in box number 3
goes to the other team.)
Okay.
We should have put the balls
in different boxes.
I suggested the boxes in the middle.
I told you that we should choose
boxes number 3 and 4.
Why didn't they choose
the middle one?
Who will take the ball
in box number three?
(Kwang Soo's arm is
in box number 3.)
Kwang Soo is taking the ball.
Suk Jin should have it.
(What is Ji Hyo doing?)
The ball in box number three
is ours, right?
It's yours.
Where did it go?
- Ji Hyo has it.
- Here. Play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Who doesn't have a ball?
- Just take it. It's only one.
- Okay.
- What are you doing?
Change it.
He is asking the staff
to change it to an R coin.
Ji Hyo.
I am sorry,
but he already made the exchange.
- What? When?
- I am sorry.
I am sorry,
but Ji Hyo stole my ball.
(Me?)
She put her hand inside
and took a ball.
Is it yours?
Did Kwang Soo take the ball?
Ji Hyo must have thought
it was ours.
This is mine.
Give me the R coin.
How could you allow this?
- Didn't you give her the ball?
- Why would I do that?
She took my ball.
Would it be okay if I take
other people's ball?
Put it back.
Jae Suk must be in the first place.
I am not in the first place yet.
Race of Wits. One.
- 2.
Three.
The 2 of you should pay up
2 coins each.
What is your problem?
Are you keep going to stress us out
this way?
Why did you yell "Two"?
Why did you?
I wanted to win coins.
- I did it without thinking.
- I wanted to win coins.
- Let's play it one more time.
- Does it count...
as a game?
- I am annoyed it's in the script.
- I know.
Is it really in the script?
We will now play a game
that is popular...
among university students.
It's the Projector Game.
What is that?
You make the shape
of the projector...
- with your arms first.
- Okay.
Then you pick a person.
"Jae Suk, 'The Face Reader'."
Then in five seconds,
Jae Suk needs to say a line
or act out a scene.
- "Do I have the face of a king?"
- That's right.
- Projector.
- Yes.
Who wants to go first?
- Should I go first?
- Yes.
All right. Let's begin.
- Projector
Se Chan,
"E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial".
(The signature pose of E.T.)
- Projector
Suk Jin, I can't believe you.
Why did you start the game
with "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"?
- What?
- Seriously.
Why do you keep making the game
so boring?
- What?
- It's an ancient movie.
I gave him the hard one.
"E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial"
was too much.
- Projector
- Did this count as an answer?
Jae Suk, "RoboCop".
(Is it "RoboCop" this time?)
"RoboCop" came out ages ago.
- Don't you know any modern movies?
- It's an ancient movie.
Name a modern movie.
"RoboCop" is an easy one.
(Whirring)
This is getting boring.
Let me start first.
- Which movie isn't boring?
- I knew the answer,
but I didn't want to do this.
- This is so frustrating.
- I can't think of anything.
Let's begin.
- Projector
Se Chan, "Veteran".
- "This is unbelievable."
- That's right.
- Projector
Haha, "Exit".
(You can imitate a motion
in the movie.)
- That's good.
- Projector
Se Chan, "Extreme Job".
"Why is the business going so well?"
- Projector
Suk Jin,
"Young Gu and Daeng Chil".
(Young Gu's signature sound)
(Suk Jin knows the old works
the best.)
- Projector
So Min, "The Wailing".
"What's the most important?"
- Projector
Ji Min, "A Violent Prosecutor".
"I..."
She watched the movie.
It's in the movie.
- "The accused..."
- That's right.
"Your Honor."
That's right. That's right.
- Projector
Jae Suk, "Joker".
What is that?
(It looks more like
the Korean mask dance.)
- That wasn't "Joker".
- That was an executioner.
- What was that?
All right. All right.
- I will pay up.
- An executioner!
- I haven't watched the movie.
Okay.
- I should have a movie in mind.
- Let's go. Let's begin.
- Projector
Hyun Hee, "Alien".
That has to be correct.
- Correct.
- That has to be correct.
Correct.
(That was perfect.)
- Projector
Ji Hyo, "Miracle in Cell No. Seven".
(It isn't a difficult one.)
This one is really easy.
I gave you an easy one.
Think of the daughter's name.
- I didn't watch the movie.
- What?
- 10 million people watched it.
- 10 million people.
- "I didn't watch the movie."
- What do you do for fun?
Ji Hyo, pay up.
Every Korean watched that movie.
Let's begin.
- Projector
- Jae Suk, "Train to Busan".
- "Train to Busan".
(Groaning)
My goodness.
(That was a good performance.)
- Good job. Good job.
- That was perfect.
- Projector
Suk Jin,
"E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial".
- What is he doing?
- "E.T."
He sounds perfect.
That's the sound of E.T.
He is a fossil.
- Projector
Hyun Hee, "Armageddon".
(Screeching again)
- What are you doing?
- Incorrect.
She is on some kind of a planet.
- There aren't aliens.
- There aren't monsters.
There aren't aliens
in "Armageddon".
- There aren't aliens.
- It's a Bruce Willis movie.
- Really?
- Yes.
- It's about saving the earth.
- I didn't watch it.
I didn't watch the movie.
Let's keep going.
- Projector
Suk Jin, "Riverbank Legends".
What?
"I went to great lengths
to build this riverbank."
- Suk Jin.
- It's "Riverbank Legends".
- It's not that kind of a movie.
"Legends", not "Construction".
- "Riverbank Legends".
- My goodness.
- Construction.
I have never heard of the movie.
- I almost cried.
- Suk Jin.
- Projector
Suk Jin, "A T. Rex Claw".
(It's a comedy movie
Suk Jin starred in as an extra...)
(about dinosaurs and primitive men.)
- There is no such scene.
- Suk Jin, that's wrong.
- You played a primitive man.
- Hold on.
- You played a dead man.
Suk Jin. Hold on.
There is no such scene.
What? I am imitating a dinosaur.
I played the 16th primitive man.
(He's imitating
one of these characters.)
- Okay.
- There are dinosaurs.
- Projector
Se Chan, "Ratatouille."
"Ratatouille"?
"Rata, Rata, Ratatouille!"
Nice job.
(He makes one up.)
- What? "Rata, Rata,"
- That's not it.
"Ratatouille!" What's wrong?
- It did come out!
Check the movie!
- The 44-minute mark!
- No.
"Rata..." No one knows.
- That didn't come out.
- "Rata, Rata, Ratatouille!"
- That's wrong.
- "Rata, Rata..."
- But...
- It's a movie about cooking.
It's about a mouse that cooks.
- I see.
- That's what it's about.
- He's so cute.
- Let's wrap it up.
Suk Jin's construction skit
was hilarious.
One.
- 1.
- 2.
(Suddenly, another game is played.)
Two.
- 3!
- 4.
Five.
- This was a game of 3, 6, 9.
- What?
- It was a game of 3, 6, 9.
(It wasn't a Race of Wits?)
- Really?
- That was round two.
(Loser of 3, 6, 9 loses 2 coins.)
- This is hilarious.
- I like how...
- that was sudden.
- That was funny.
- That was hilarious.
- Goodness.
- That was humiliating.
- I wrote it down.
This is interesting.
- Give it to me.
- How dare you humiliate me?
- How many coins?
- Two.
- Poor thing.
- He just had to say three.
- I thought it was a Race of Wits.
- Poor him.
I'll announce the results.
Okay.
The couple that lost the most
will be able to hide theirs in here.
It was Jae Suk and Suk Jin.
(They will hide the coins.)
- It's us?
- Yes.
- You two will hide...
- Gosh.
all 66 coins,
and the rest will pick.
- There are 66 coins?
- Yes.
- Goodness.
- We could win.
- Let's turn the tables.
- "Turn the tables"?
- Let's put in one each.
- Okay.
You're good with things like this.
You should do it.
(They come up with a plan.)
- Hold on.
- I put them in.
Let's not divide them.
- Let's put them all in one box.
- Okay.
How about the middle one?
Weren't they in here before?
We shouldn't put them in there.
How about here?
(They're in a dilemma
between number 3 and 4.)
- Let's put it in here.
- Okay.
- All right.
- I don't care anymore.
(They pick number 4.)
I don't care anymore.
Please turn around.
- So Min.
- Turn around.
- Okay.
- We're putting them in right now.
- We are.
(If they're smart,
they can obtain all the coins.)
(Which box will they pick?)
Gather, please.
Let's go.
We need to pick the right one.
The couple with the most money
will go first.
Haha and Ji Min will go first.
Pick.
Okay.
- We pick number two.
- Okay.
- Please!
- 1, 2...
- I'm sorry.
- Why?
- There are none.
- None?
- There's one.
- 1?
- 1.
If you're sorry, then I'll take it.
I'm not that sorry.
We've lost two competitors.
Next.
- We pick number 1.
- Kwang Soo picked number 1.
Come on. Let's go.
(They only find 1 coin.)
- There's 1 coin.
- Just 1?
Open it.
- There's 1 coin. What a bummer.
- Just 1?
(Box number 5 has 1 coin.)
- There's 1 coin. What a bummer.
- Just 1?
Are they all in one box?
1 of these 2 boxes is a jackpot.
So Min, I feel hopeful.
- That was a smart move.
- Seriously?
(These 2
are the only remaining boxes.)
- We pick number four.
- Next up...
is So Min and Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo.
- 1, 2, 3.
(1 of the boxes have 62 coins.)
(They could turn the tables.)
- Look at it first.
- Will they get it?
What? There's just one.
(There's just 1 coin.)
I said it was number three.
- No way.
- They were so lucky.
- They're in first place.
- We should've picked the other one.
Right?
- Right?
- Whose idea was this?
- No way.
- It was the middle box.
You must've been surprised
when I wanted to pick number three.
Yes, we were shocked.
- We did it.
- This is unbelievable.
Lucky you.
Go, Suk Jin.
Let's get rid of these.
This too. Where's the "laptop"?
- It's here.
- Right.
- It'll be number 38.
- Number 19.
Let's put "Massage from Jong Kook"
down here.
- And...
- You'll probably get that one.
Pick.
The staff is determined
to give us gifts.
Give me the "laptop."
- They're all good prizes.
- I hope it's a dud.
Let's see.
Dud, dud, dud
- Number 45.
(Suk Jin picks number 45.)
(What?)
"Massage from Jong Kook".
He picked that one?
- All right.
- No way!
- I can't believe he picked it.
- This feels surreal.
- I'll give you a hip massage.
- "Hip massage"?
- Lie down.
- I'll give you a hip massage.
- Massage my shoulders instead.
No.
- Just do my shoulders.
- That's a nice prize.
- This is a rare opportunity.
- Lie sideways.
- What is this?
- This will make you healthier.
- Right. I'm good at this.
- What is this?
- It'll loosen up your muscles.
- It's good for your hips.
- Okay? I'll start now.
- Okay.
- How many seconds?
- Ready, set, go.
(He presses down.)
My gosh.
He dodged.
Gosh, seriously!
Jong Kook, aren't you supposed
to be massaging him.
- I did.
- This is his prize.
- You need to loosen them.
- It's acupressure.
- How is it?
- It's so painful.
- I bet it is.
- How was it?
Not bad.
- "Not bad"?
- Yes.
- I hope you get it.
- I'm cheering for him.
Number 41.
- It's a dud.
(He gets a dud.)
(He's still not lucky enough.)
- Okay!
- Dud
- Dud, dud
- This is great!
- Jae Suk.
- I can't believe this.
This was the only empty one.
- He wasted his luck on this!
- I can't believe it.
You're so unlucky.
(It's springtime,
and the flowers greet us.)
Hello, everyone. Good morning.
It's been a while since you started
the race by yourself.
You're right. Here I am once again.
- Hello.
- This is simple.
Hello.
What are we doing today?
Before you arrive
at the opening venue,
you must pick an angel
and a devil...
among the members
while excluding yourself.
- An angel and a devil?
- Yes.
The devil may face
disadvantages in the upcoming race,
so please pick wisely.
This is hard.
Judging by their appearances,
don't Se Chan and Kwang Soo
look like a devil?
I'll give up.
(He thinks back
on the things he's done.)
I can't. An angel and a devil?
I need to pick a devil?
(She listens to the rules
and gets in the car.)
Hello, sir.
- Hello.
An angel and a devil?
An angel?
Once the filming is over,
they're all angels.
But during the filming,
all the angels disappear.
Hello, Mr. Angel.
(An angel appears.)
Hello, Angel Jee.
(Laughing)
Let's pick each other as the angel.
- Shall we?
- We can do that.
We can just pick each other.
Then pick me.
- Okay.
- Because...
I can't think of anyone to pick.
- Exactly.
- Right.
I can't think of anyone either,
so let's just pick each other...
- Okay.
- and not get humiliated.
Let's do that.
- Okay.
- Bye.
(They promise to pick each other
and hang up.)
I could use this strategy.
This will help me become an angel.
Angel Lee.
- Angel Lee.
- Hi.
You do know
that no one will pick you, right?
I do.
So let's just pick each other.
We can do that.
I will change your name
saved on my phone...
as Angel Jee.
As Angel Jee.
(Hold on.)
What did you say?
- Hey.
- Don't get me wrong.
Isn't that an antidiarrheal?
- That's not what I meant.
- It's an antidiarrheal.
I will pick you no matter what.
Okay. I'll pick you too, Angel Lee.
Let's do that then.
Gosh, there are no angels among us.
There really aren't any.
Jong Kook is calling.
(He receives a call from Jong Kook.)
Why, hello, Angel Kim.
- Hello, Angel Jee.
- You know what?
- My lovely.
- I was just about to call you.
I'm serious. What a coincidence.
Hey, what about we just pick
each other?
- I'll pick you.
- That's a promise.
Yes, I promise.
- Hello, Angel Song.
- Hello, Angel Jee.
I'm going to pick the person
who deserves it. And who is that?
It's you, Angel Song.
Why have you become so kind?
It's nothing. I just decided to be
a better person from this week on.
- I'll pick you.
- Okay.
You should pick me too.
Angel Ha.
Hello, my role model.
My guardian angel.
- Hey.
- Yes?
How about we pick each other?
Are you going to betray me?
- You'll only hurt me.
- I won't.
Life is all about getting betrayed.
Even my stocks have betrayed me.
Hey, life is all about betrayals.
Hey.
You can't always have it easy.
His stocks have betrayed him.
I feel so bad for you.
I'll pick you.
- All right.
- Okay.
Let's just pick each other.
Okay.
Gosh, I think he's really
going to pick me.
Am I just naive?
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk calls someone.)
Is this Angel Yu?
Goodness, it is you.
Gosh, where are you?
I'm on my way.
I truly think you're an angel.
- I really do.
- Why?
- Because...
- Yes?
Let's see. It's because...
What? You're disqualified!
- No, hear me out.
- You're disqualified.
You're done.
You had no plans to pick me.
To be honest,
you're a devil candidate.
Please, Jae Suk.
I need to be an angel.
- Please remember that.
- All right.
- I'll pick you then.
- Okay?
You truly are an angel.
All right. Goodbye.
Bye.
It feels awkward to say it.
It feels awkward saying,
"I am an angel."
(It's time to decide on
the angel and the devil.)
I am torn. This is driving me crazy.
The angel is my angel.
My angel is...
(Se Chan's angel is...)
I will pick Jong Kook.
Jong Kook is my angel.
I did promise him earlier.
Besides,
he isn't much of a threat to me.
I will choose Suk Jin.
(Jong Kook chooses Suk Jin
as the angel.)
The angel is Ji Hyo.
The devil is...
Jae Suk.
Would Suk Jin pick me as the angel?
I highly doubt that.
That's why he is the devil.
The devil is...
Jong Kook or Jae Suk?
Suk Jin.
Today,
(The rules are explained.)
you will need to identify
the devil among the members...
though the Devil's Whisper Race.
Depending on the results
of the first vote,
you will either gain
or lose ballots...
from the five
you were originally given.
So there are more angels.
Let's say you received
three angel votes...
and one devil vote.
Then you will receive
two more ballots...
and come to have
seven ballots in total.
I will attach something
to your head.
Make sure you don't see it.
(The current number of votes
is attached to the head.)
Should I turn around?
I can see my reflection.
Shall we go here?
Isn't this an angelic deed?
- So that I wouldn't see it...
- Okay.
So that I wouldn't see
the reflection, I turned around.
I could have seen it.
But only a devil would do that.
- Please turn around.
- Okay.
- I will face the wall.
This puts me at ease.
This puts my mind at ease.
I don't know why.
I was like this since childhood.
I was like this since birth.
If you come this way,
I will put it on your head.
(He wears a hat
with the result of the 1st vote.)
(0 angel votes and 0 devil votes)
Don't look at the reflection.
(1 angel vote and 5 devil votes)
(5 devil votes?)
(5 out of 8 people voted him
for the devil.)
- The devil is Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk.
- The result is on your head.
- Okay.
Will you accept...
the original result
or the reversed result?
(The original result: 1 ballot
The reversed: 9 ballots)
Why would you do
something like this?
(The original result: 1 ballot
The reversed: 9 ballots)
(Is there a reflection?)
Maybe I can see it.
This is...
I should go
with my gut feeling, right?
There is no way
I got the angel votes.
Why would they do that?
They wouldn't do that.
I bet I have many angel votes.
I will go with the original result.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Tell me.)
(He is fishing for information.)
What are you doing?
What?
- What?
- Hurry up and pick one.
What?
Not many people would pick me
as a devil.
I am sure the devil votes
went to a select few people.
I doubt I have many devil votes.
Please make a decision.
(He is a strong devil candidate
without any deducting skills.)
(What will be his decision?)
O.
What does that mean?
- I choose the original result.
- The original result.
- That's your choice, right?
- Yes.
Please check the result now.
(It's time for Jae Suk
to face reality.)
My goodness.
(What is this?)
This is the worst.
Did I really get five devil votes?
I should have gone
with the reversed result.
Do I get zero ballots?
No. Since you had 5 ballots,
we will give you 1.
For goodness' sake.
(I can't believe them.)
I bet I have more devil votes.
I will go with the reversed result.
- The reversed result?
- Yes.
There is no way
people picked me as the angel.
I will check the result.
1, 2, 3.
(Gosh!)
Who picked me as the angel?
Who did that?
I just came back
from a two-week hiatus.
(He diligently make deductions.)
So I doubt they picked me
as a devil.
- The original result.
- The original result?
No. Hold on.
I bet I received some devil votes.
Someone must have voted for me.
(Since no one gave him a vote,)
(the result will stay the same
either way.)
- The reversed result.
- The reversed result?
(He worries and changes his mind
in a meaningless fashion.)
The original result.
I won't change my mind again.
- The original result.
- Yes.
(Then he checks the result.)
The original result
was the way to go, right?
It's the same either way.
(I see.)
There is no change.
I got zero votes.
This is upsetting.
(He has no sense of presence.)
Today, I will show you
what a true devil is.
I shouldn't have expected much.
They are too much.
Now, you can make the final vote
using the ballots you have acquired.
There are ballot boxes
with the members' names.
Write down the name
other than your own...
and put it
in that member's ballot box.
Use the white side
to vote for someone as the angel.
Use the side that's black...
to vote for someone as the devil.
What am I going to do
with a single vote?
We have a pouch for the ballots,
but since you have only one...
Give it to me.
(He takes everything he can.)
This is so annoying.
- Do I go and vote now?
- Ballot boxes are here and there.
They are here and there?
- Jong Kook.
- Suk Jin.
Your angel vote came from me.
Didn't you get an angel vote?
- I did.
- It came from me.
Really?
- Our deal worked out.
- I know.
- I voted for you.
That was me. Thank you.
- Don't be. I only kept my promise.
- Seriously.
(Actually,)
(Se Chan gave Jong Kook
an angel vote.)
(The angel is Ji Hyo.)
I knew you would need
one angel vote.
Thank you. I mean it.
Ji Suk Jin World.
- My mind is at ease...
- Right?
- to be in the Ji Suk Jin World.
- That's right.
This is great.
Hey.
Let's vote for each other.
- I will write your name.
- As the angel?
- Yes.
- I will do the same.
I have many ballots.
- I have many ballots.
That's right. I can use one for you.
- Kim Jong Kook. I wrote it.
- Okay.
- Your handwriting is nice.
- I know.
Here.
- Ji Suk Jin.
- We can use one for each other.
- Of course. Where is yours?
- Go.
- It's over there.
- Why is it in a corner?
My goodness.
Why is it in a corner?
- "Corner Suk Jin" is my nickname.
- You are right.
- Corner Suk Jin.
- Yes?
I will cast this vote.
Okay, okay.
(Ji Suk Jin)
All right.
He stayed loyal since the beginning,
so I will use a ballot for him.
(Meanwhile)
(Hesitant)
Let's save it for now.
I will hide it.
Who is that? Suk Jin!
- Suk Jin.
- Hey.
What happened?
- You had one angel vote, right?
- What?
You had one angel vote, right?
- Did it come from you?
- That's right.
Didn't you vote for me?
I voted for you.
That didn't sound too convincing.
- Right? That's how it is.
- Yes.
In that case,
how about this?
Let's start with a ballot.
- For whom?
- You.
Please give me an angel vote.
- You should vote for me too.
- Okay.
You have a ballot, right?
For goodness' sake.
- What are you talking about?
- You have a ballot, right?
- You have a ballot.
- Of course.
I have many ballots.
I will write your name.
Thank you so much.
- Write my name.
- I will write your name.
I will write your name.
- Let's vote for each other.
- Okay.
- I wrote your name.
- I wrote your name too. Okay.
My ballot box is there.
- Where?
- Over there.
Put it in there.
I will go and find your ballot box.
- Make sure you put it in there.
- Of course.
For goodness' sake.
Ballots keep coming back
to my pouch.
This is the second one.
(The ballots keep coming back
into Suk Jin's pouch.)
- Okay.
- Jong Kook, how was the result?
- It was good.
- It was heartwarming, right?
(Se Chan bows to him.)
Okay.
My guardian angel.
You are my angel.
- My guardian angel.
- You saw the result, right?
It was from me.
You saw the result, right?
I am serious.
- Move out of the way.
- My angel.
- I will keep it short.
- Did you receive my vote?
There is no way
you didn't get any angel votes.
He had more than one angel votes.
He had more than one angel votes
because I voted for him.
- Stop lying.
- I am not lying.
Watch the episode when it airs!
- Stop lying.
- Please.
Jae Suk.
The result was nice, right?
- My goodness.
- You are here.
We have someone impressive here.
- Jae Suk.
- He is impressive.
- I think...
- Excuse me.
Do you even have ballots?
I bet he doesn't have any.
- Of course, I have ballots.
- Really?
- I have ballots.
Of course.
Do you know...
what's happening right now?
- We are headed that way.
- Why?
(What's there?)
(Yoo Jae Suk)
- Why are you headed that way?
- Is everyone here?
- Let's go.
(Jae Suk's ballot box
is wildly popular.)
Let's go.
(Walking over)
- You can't vote for yourself.
- Is everyone here?
- Hold on.
- I have already been there.
- Kwang Soo.
- You can't vote for yourself.
- Where are you going?
- I'm standing in line.
Why would you go there?
This is the red carpet.
- Put one in there.
- Jae Suk, hold on.
- Hold on.
Apparently, you can vote
for the same person again.
- Really?
- What...
- My goodness.
Why would you vote for me?
Apparently, you can vote
for the same person again.
I will go all in.
- I didn't know.
- I don't want to go anywhere else.
- Will you give me an angel vote?
- Jae Suk.
You can vote
for the same person again.
- Please put this in the ballot box.
- Really?
Why do you have so many?
It doesn't look like you're voting.
- Have you run out of ballots?
- I'm going to vote.
- Do you have some?
- Of course.
- You do have some.
- You do.
He has one.
I have a couple.
Jae Suk, if you run,
you'll win for sure.
Fine.
I'll vote for you.
- Is Jae Suk popular?
- Are you lining up?
- We're lining up.
- Is this the trend?
- Yes.
- Voting for him.
Excuse me.
Why are you butting the line?
- Why are you butting the line?
- My bad.
- You cut in very naturally.
- Is this the devil's den?
- Go back.
- It's popular.
- It is.
I set up a tent
and slept here last night.
I stayed 3 days and 2 nights.
People fight here a lot...
because they butt the line.
He only has one left.
Leave him be.
(The voters are unperturbed.)
I don't have ballots,
so this is unfortunate.
Right. You reap what you sow.
He's an angel behind the cameras,
but this is Running Man,
so you can't help it.
- There was 1 person.
- I think there was 1 ballot.
(Haha gives 2 devil votes
to Jae Suk.)
If I get one vote, I won't do it.
It's full inside.
I'm sorry,
- but this is sold out.
- Why?
- No!
- The ballot box is full.
- I lined up for days.
- It's totally full.
- What?
- I want to go in.
- There's no more space.
- It's totally full.
- Can you open it back up?
Is this break time? Can you open it?
(He's uncomfortable
with his own popularity.)
Can I buy some ballots?
I wish I could get around nine.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
I think...
(Sneaky Suk Jin is done
analyzing the market.)
you're the devil.
They are...
(They're lining up to vote.)
They're lining up.
It's a popular place.
Do you have one?
Hey.
- Be quiet.
- You have one.
- I made the wrong decision.
- Why?
I should have went the opposite way.
You should have.
- I would have had nine then.
- Right.
You should have went
the opposite way.
Didn't you know?
Didn't you have a feeling?
Hey, couldn't you tell?
You have no intuition.
My gosh.
(When did I stoop down
to his level?)
I'll see you later.
Where is he?
Do you want to check out
this new and upcoming place?
- What is it?
- It's up here.
This is like Gyeongridan-gil.
It's Kwangridan-gil.
- It's called Kwangridan-gil.
- No.
- It's not this way.
- Let's go to Kwangridan-gil.
- What are you talking about?
Is this Kwangridan-gil?
- Yes.
- Let's go!
- Let's go to Kwangridan-gil.
- Everybody,
- this is Kwangridan-gil.
- No.
It's a popular spot.
- You must be a tour guide.
- I am. Follow me.
This place is very popular.
- Is it?
- Yes, it's Kwangridan-gil.
This is pretty.
Jong Kook,
Kwangridan-gil is so nice.
- This is nice. There's a lamp.
- This is not Kwangridan-gil.
There are flowers too.
This is so nice.
This is nice.
- This is it.
- This is Se Chan district.
- It's Se Chan district.
- Please keep going.
- Isn't the air good? It's spacious.
- Please pass by Se Chan district.
(A crowd gathers.)
Jong Kook.
- This is nice.
- It's great.
- Here it is.
- This is great.
- There's the sun too.
- Everybody.
(By topography, Kwang Soo's
ballot box is in an excellent area.)
This is a new tour.
- I'll check it out first.
- Welcome, everybody.
- You went in already.
- Yes.
- Of course.
- You were fast.
I'm going to vote for you.
I have many ballots.
(Will So Min give Kwang Soo
an angel or a devil vote?)
Kwang Soo,
I can't believe
you think of me that way. Look.
So Min, you're an angel.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you?
So Min.
(This world is still
a good place to live.)
(Scratching)
Hey, I heard you crossing it out.
(She erases his name
and turns it into a devil vote.)
- Hey.
- Even I heard it.
I heard it too.
- That was so loud.
- That was too loud, So Min.
What was that?
Is there a microphone on the pen?
You just need to erase one letter.
Why were you crossing it out
so hard?
That was too loud.
I thought there was a fly.
What was that sound?
- She crossed it out too hard.
- I can't trust her.
Do you have one?
That was tasty.
That was delicious.
- Did you enjoy?
- That was delicious.
(So Min had a devil set menu
at Kwang Soo's restaurant.)
That was amazing, everybody.
That was the best restaurant
I've tried.
Where's Jeonridan-gil?
I want to go there all of a sudden.
- Jeonridan-gil does not exist.
- Jeonridan-gil.
- You have three minutes left.
- Where is Jeonridan-gil?
You lose the ballots you don't use.
- Really?
- I have one ballot left.
Tell me where Jeonridan-gil is.
I'm going to Haha's.
- He's a weasel.
- Wait.
He repeatedly said
I was his role model.
Haha.
(Jeonridan-gil is very popular.)
There's a lot.
Where's Jong Kook's?
Excuse me.
Do you know where Kook Francisco is?
- Where?
- Kook Francisco.
- It's over here.
- Where?
- Over here.
- I see.
(He asked around for
Kook Francisco.)
(Kwang Soo casts a vote.)
- Se Chan.
- You're confirmed.
- I'm done.
- You're the devil.
Okay, this is what I think.
Even if I had many ballots,
I would have become a devil.
- I'm certain.
- Okay.
Is he voting for Jong Kook?
For devils,
it's better to vote for Jong Kook.
Be quiet. Let me enjoy spring.
Hey.
Who cares
how many votes Jong Kook has?
Se Chan.
Jae Suk,
don't try to look composed.
- He's shaking right now.
- Se Chan.
Enjoy life.
(This is the bluff of a devil.)
Jae Suk.
This is a perfect day
to be a devil.
(The polls close
for angels and devils.)
I would like to tell those
who will become devils.
- If you...
- Excuse me.
He went to the bathroom.
He'll be back soon.
The devil is not here yet.
- He's not here yet.
- Right.
- Here comes the devil.
- Here he is.
Jae Suk,
he's announcing who the devils are.
There's an announcement.
- Devil.
- Relax, relax.
He told me to enjoy spring.
He's going to make
an announcement about the devils.
Relax.
- He's announcing the winners.
- Relax.
Let me tell you
who will become devils.
Even if your identity is revealed,
you should protect other devils.
(It's more beneficial to protect
the identities of other devils.)
We need to hide our identities.
I see.
- We know already.
- We know.
- Jae Suk.
- His place was sold out.
- This is meaningless.
There were more angel votes
than expected.
- Really?
- That was unexpected.
- There were angel votes?
- See?
- This is warm.
- Right. You never know.
- It's spring.
I used one angel vote.
- He's getting started again.
- I'm serious.
He even shaved.
- He'll pay for it.
Did you shave?
- Did you?
- That's why you looked weird.
- It looks weird.
- He looks so ugly.
Your face looks really weird.
- His beard made him look good.
- Did somebody hit you?
Hey, I told you before
you look weird without a beard.
After I shaved, I went home,
and my son is like,
"What's wrong with your face, Dad?"
What's wrong with your face?
He was not used to it.
I'm embarrassed.
He looks weird.
We all know who the devils are.
There might be a lot of angel votes.
You never know
how this will turn out.
- No.
- Don't say something weird.
Shut your mouth.
Shut your mouth. What do you know?
- He's a devil. He sounds like one.
- He's a devil.
He flipped.
He must be nervous right now.
Look at his hands.
- He's a devil.
- Kid's hands.
- He's mad.
- When kids get mad.
"What do you..."
"What do you know?"
We'll distribute the envelopes.
Read the content on your own.
- Okay.
- Jae Suk.
- Stop acting.
- What are you doing?
- It's him.
Please take the envelope
with your name on it.
Devils, it's beneficial for you
to act like you are angels.
Look.
The cherry blossoms have bloomed.
- We know.
- On a good day like this...
My gosh.
(Jae Suk is...)
(a devil.)
(No surprise there.)
It's your fault.
(Jae Suk is a devil.
Who are the remaining 2?)
Is this "The Voice of Korea"?
(The Voice of Running Man
with angels and devils)
(Is this a blind audition...)
(where you only compete
with your voice?)
(The members are surprised to see
these four popular actors!)
(Ahn Bo Hyun, Ji Eui Soo)
(Song Jin Woo, Lee Joo Young)
There's a devil on our team.
(The race between
angels and devils starts now.)
You got it.
(A desperate struggle to escape
the branding as a devil)
(The devils have been
decided already.)
(Meanwhile, the devils' advocate
for themselves.)
(When the devils are on the move,)
(they can destroy a team?)
(It's a close tug-of-war...)
(between the angels
and the invisible devils.)
(Which angels will protect
their team from the 3 devils?)
I won't stay still.
(I Saw the Angels and Devils:
The Devils' Advocates)