(This was filmed before the practice
of social distancing step 2.)
(Someone arrives 40 minutes before
the beginning of the shoot.)
Hello.
(So Min arrives early again.)
I didn't mean to,
but I got here early again.
I'm the first one here.
No one's here, right?
- Good job today.
- Well done.
You will get to choose
a role tomorrow morning.
Really? Should we
arrive early again?
Yes. We will start at 8 a.m.
Whoever comes first will pick first.
- Are we choosing a role again?
- We should come early.
(Is it something like the Thief Race
where we get to pick an occupation?)
Hello.
Get her a microphone.
I'm Jeon So Min who got here first.
You told us to come early.
Do you know what time it is now?
The crew members are
complaining a lot.
I woke up at 4 a.m.
I'm really tired. We need to hurry.
(She turns on a light for herself.)
There's no lighting.
Hello. Can I get my microphone?
When I came in and asked
why things weren't ready,
I heard a crew member say...
it's my fault that I came too early.
(They exchange words of blessing
from early morning.)
Please take a look around.
I didn't see this.
"Jae Suk, Haha, and Ji Hyo's
joint birthday party".
(Are we having
a birthday party today?)
Are we having
a birthday party today?
(Then she finds
something on the table.)
This is nice. I like it.
There's a new occupation.
(There are several occupations
like the Thief Race episode.)
Why did you put these separately?
(A profiler and detective
are put aside.)
They are for the guests.
(A profiler and detective are
for today's guests.)
I guess this one is useless.
It has no power.
Honestly, I find
this one attractive.
I want to pick this one.
Why did So Min come here so early?
- Hey.
- Se Chan is here.
Why are you here so early?
- Se Chan's here.
- Hello.
Why did you come so early?
Just tell me.
My house is only 15 minutes
away from here.
You're the one who's being weird.
I always come early.
- Did you pick one already?
- Not yet.
Are we supposed to wait?
- I need...
- You can pick one if you want.
I need to do some thinking.
What is a headhunter?
Is it about blowing a head off?
(What is a headhunter?
Is it about blowing a head off?)
Gosh, no. It's like finding someone
who meets the qualifications.
Like employees.
(He thought it was like
hunting people.)
I think this one suits you well.
- Audio engineer?
- Yes.
I'll pick this. Audio engineer.
Audio engineer?
It's right up your street.
What should I pick?
A photographer or a hacker?
(She's stuck between
a photographer and a hacker.)
I think Haha will make
a good photographer today.
- I'll pick hacker then.
- It's settled.
- He's here.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- Haha.
- She came here really early.
- Again?
- Yes.
Hang on. You're crazy
about see-through shirts.
- Just stay quiet.
- Take a look at this, Haha.
We need to talk about this.
He's crazy. He's wearing it again.
- What's wrong with you?
- Why are you being like this?
- What?
- You need to pick one.
- Just pick one.
- I want to be a hacker.
Pick something else.
You can't pick this one.
I think this one sounds cool.
Haha, do you know
what a headhunter is?
- What is a headhunter?
- Do you know what a headhunter is?
It means a boss, you silly.
- What?
- It means...
(He sounds so confident
giving a wrong answer.)
(Se Chan didn't know it,
but he laughs at Haha.)
- Why?
- Are you saying...
- a headhunter is a boss?
- Sure.
- Like a head?
- Yes.
- Why are you laughing?
- I mean,
I didn't know too.
You can't pick these two.
I think this one suits you.
I think Photographer suits you best.
It sounds like an insurance agent.
You're here.
- Hello.
- Hang on.
I came early
because I live in Hapjeong.
Why do you wear a see-through shirt
so often these days?
We talked about that earlier.
- I think he's an exhibitionist.
- What's his problem?
- You should choose.
- Should I choose one of these?
- Then I'll pick this.
- Which one?
A photographer? Good choice.
That suits you.
- You should be a headhunter.
- Jae Suk.
- These two won't be helpful.
- Why?
- Think about the last time.
- They had no power.
But a prosecutor is different.
- Let him do as he wants.
- A prosecutor can...
- investigate the case.
- I think...
his hunch is...
He seems to want to have
a powerful job today.
- Let him do as he wants.
- Let's trust his hunch.
- I'll be a prosecutor today.
- Okay.
Gosh. You shouldn't be late.
I'm not late, Jae Suk.
You're late.
I have no idea
what the interior expert does.
I'll be the security guard.
Just as you predicted,
today, we're going to have...
- Running Man Thief Race 2.
- I see.
(Do you remember
the Running Man Thief Race?)
(The thieves, Kwang Soo and Se Chan,
aimed to steal gold bars...)
(at CEO Big Nose's party.)
(They arrived early and chose to be
the judge and detective.)
(Se Chan moved the gold bars
instead of stealing them,)
(which made it difficult
to investigate the case.)
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo
worked together...)
(and successfully confused
the others.)
(The thieves won as Se Chan survived
at the final trial!)
(Today's race is
Running Man Thief Race 2.)
While you were choosing your roles,
our two guests were watching you.
- What?
- Why were they watching us?
They were here?
(Who are the guests who saw them
arriving and choosing their roles?)
(This is the monitor
that the guests watched.)
Because they are not
actual criminals...
(The two guests will play the roles
of a profiler and detective...)
(that were already assigned
to them.)
Profiler and Detective,
please come out.
- They were here?
- Where were they watching us?
What? Who are they?
- What?
- Isn't he a real detective?
- They are...
- What?
- real detective and profiler.
- Really?
- Hey, Seok Ho.
- No way.
- They're really here.
- How...
(The real ones are here!)
- They're really here.
- How...
- My gosh.
- He's a friend of mine.
- Hello.
- The real ones are here.
(Lieutenant Yoon Seok Ho,
Profiler Pyo Chang Won)
(Lieutenant Yoon Seok Ho was
the model...)
(of Ma Dong Seok's character
in "The Outlaws".)
(He was on the front line of
the gang mop-up operation in 2004.)
(He's here to catch thieves
with his keen eye.)
(Lieutenant Yoon Seok Ho, the master
of investigation and interrogation)
(A former professor at Korean
National Police University)
(The criminal psychologist who can
see through criminals' minds)
(The current director of
Pyo Institute of Crime Science)
(Pyo Chang Won,
the master of psychological fight)
- How have you been?
- Hello.
- They never come on a variety show.
- I can't believe this.
They never appear
on a variety show, right?
- What do you expect us to do?
- Hello.
The real detective and profiler
are here.
Why would you take this game
so seriously?
My goodness.
The real ones are here.
- This is unbelievable.
- Actually,
we heard that a crime
happened here.
- Here?
- Yes.
We received a report
and came here.
- But...
- He's already into his character.
- My gosh. This is unbelievable.
- We must not...
- make any mistakes today.
- First of all,
Director Pyo Chang Won is...
- the first profiler in Korea.
- That's right.
He studied overseas.
Didn't he appear
on Running Man once?
- We played some kind of mind game.
- Exactly.
- He lost to me.
- Yes, he lost to you.
- He lost.
(Chang Won appeared in Episode 257
as the reasoning master.)
(He played the Catch the Thief
Card Game with Suk Jin.)
(He ended up with the Thief Card.)
(He lost to Suk Jin because he
couldn't hide his emotions.)
As a matter of fact,
I realized that he was very smart.
- I was just lucky.
- That's not true.
A few years ago,
you played rock-paper-scissors
with Haha and lost on another show.
- He was lucky.
- True.
I had no strategy.
I didn't think of anything.
- I'm embarrassed.
- Today...
I'm determined to win today.
Director Pyo is here with us today.
It's not that surprising to see him
on this show if you think about it.
Detective, what are you doing here?
- He's a real detective.
- Why did you come here?
To be honest, it was hard for me
to decide to come here.
- And?
- Because I'm not good with words.
(Everyone is listening to
Detective Yoon closely.)
Now that I'm here,
it's really hard.
You can relax.
- He seems nervous.
- You're too nervous.
- You know Suk Jin personally.
- He and I...
Yes, we first met about 10 years ago
through our mutual acquaintance.
He may seem very gentle,
- but he's scary to a criminal.
- Of course.
- It's true.
- Did you see that?
- Pardon?
I heard about it.
Didn't you watch "The Outlaws"?
Ma Dong Seok's character was
modeled after him.
- He's the model of that character.
- You've never seen him...
catching a criminal before.
Why do you act like you know?
Everyone, we gathered here today
for the joint birthday party...
of Jae Suk, Haha, and Ji Hyo
who were born in August.
We prepared jewels for the guests
as a gift.
(The guests will receive
jewels as a gift.)
However, among you, there are
two thieves who aren't invited.
They're after your jewels,
so you should catch them.
The 10 of you are suspects of theft.
You'll receive a prize if you
succeed in catching the thieves,
but if you fail to catch them,
you'll receive a penalty.
There are three steps in arresting
the thieves like the last time.
At the 1st trial, you can find out
if any of 2 suspects is the thief.
You will arrest 1 thief
at the 2nd and final trials.
(They will arrest the thieves
through three trials.)
Just like the last time,
you will have three chances
to search rooms before the mission.
Each of you will have 70 seconds.
(2 members search each room
for 70 seconds.)
This time, you will partner up with
someone else to search the rooms.
(Each team of two people will go to
the rooms where the jewels are.)
And each of the two people
will go into a different room.
(They will go into two rooms
separately.)
But only one of the rooms
has real jewels.
In the other room, there are bags
full of fake jewels.
(Only one room has real jewels!)
In the bags of the eight of you
who are not the thieves,
there are 100 pieces of real jewel.
In the thieves' bags,
there are 100 pieces of fake jewel.
(There are real jewels
only in the civilians' bags.)
In the room with fake jewels,
there are 100 pieces of fake jewel
in all the 10 bags.
(There are fake jewels
in all the 10 bags.)
(There are more fake jewels
here and there in both rooms.)
(The two thieves must go into
the room with real jewels,)
(and steal more than 100 pieces
of real jewels.)
(The thieves know the combination
for the locks of all the bags.)
(The civilians must find ballots
and the trail of the thieves.)
(However, the civilians don't know
the combination for the bags.)
In each round, the thieves...
will be informed which room has
real jewels,
and search the rooms knowing
the combination for all the bags.
(Only the thieves know
the combination.)
Just like the last time,
additional ballots are hidden.
You can use it whenever you want.
There's only one thing
different from the last time.
The videos were revealed last time,
but this time, photos will be taken
at a set time.
(The photos of the last two places
will be revealed after the mission.)
(Room A, Room B)
(Photos will be taken at 10th and
20th seconds during the search.)
Some photos will be revealed
according to the mission result.
(The photos to show will be chosen
according to the mission result.)
Since we have two experts,
the thieves will be caught.
- But they might be the thieves.
- Could they be...
- the thieves as well?
- One of them...
- must be a thief.
- We never know.
- Maybe they wanted the roles.
- Right.
- They never get a chance to do it.
- Exactly.
First, I'll announce the benefits
of different roles.
Please come in.
(What could be
the upgraded benefits?)
- He can interrogate someone alone?
- Oh, gosh.
- "Before the third trial..."
- We get great benefits this time.
Being the prosecutor isn't
very helpful.
(The Power of Each Role)
First, Lieutenant Yoon Seok Ho,
who plays the detective,
can call one person who he thinks
is the most suspicious...
- for an interrogation.
- That's scary.
(The 1-on-1 interrogation
with an active detective)
- Really?
- Should we put on a helmet too?
- For an interrogation.
- That's scary.
Should we put on a helmet too?
Like a real interrogation?
- We made the interrogation room.
- It's like the Room of Truth.
It'll be a whole new experience.
(Detective Yoon can interrogate
1 person before the 1st trial.)
Next, Profiler Pyo Chang Won...
can watch everyone
going in and out of the rooms...
and hear what they say.
- He can hear us too?
- Yes.
(Profiler Pyo can watch and hear
everyone as they go into the rooms.)
We should be careful with our words.
- What did you just say?
- Hold on a second.
- I meant the thieves.
- Be careful with our words?
- The thieves must be careful.
- Okay.
Is that so?
You know what Jong Kook does
when he suspects someone, right?
- You're done for.
- The security guard caught you.
You won't be able to do anything.
As for the interior expert...
In each round, he can decide...
which room should have real jewels.
- I thought of choosing that role.
- That's great.
(Kwang Soo will decide which room
has real jewels in each round.)
The headhunter will decide...
- the team members and the order.
- He got a great benefit too.
You will maintain the teams
during the missions as well.
That's great.
(Ji Suk Jin, the headhunter)
(He will organize teams and decide
the orders for search and missions.)
The prosecutor has
the final decision...
for choosing 2 suspects
for the 1st trial.
That's amazing.
- The prosecutor is powerful.
- Indeed.
The hacker will receive the passcode
of one person's bag...
before the second Room Search.
You can open it as many times
as you want.
- Can I open it?
- Yes.
You got a good benefit.
(Jeon So Min, the hacker)
- You got a good benefit.
- Then you can check...
- if the jewels are gone.
- Then...
do I get to open it
only before the second search?
That's when you will be given
the passcode,
and you can open the bag
as many times as you want.
- I can open it just once?
- You can open it more than once.
- She's asking too many questions.
- Exactly.
- I mean, the first search.
- She asked unnecessary questions.
- You didn't see her, did you?
- He's suspecting her.
- Her eyes looked like this.
- We're all acting like a detective.
- She could've waited.
- Exactly.
- She can ask him privately later.
- That was unnecessary.
That was unnecessary.
- But she didn't wait.
- I can't ask him privately.
That was unnecessary.
The security guard...
can check the photos of the person
of his choice.
Oh, is that so?
(Jong Kook can check the photos of
1 person before the 3rd trial.)
The photographer will decide
the time to take...
the third photos of everyone...
following the 10th and 20th
seconds during Room Search.
- Good. Okay.
- That'd be helpful.
(Haha will decide the time for
taking photos during Room Search.)
The judge will receive two
additional ballots from the start.
You can use them anytime
at the 2nd or 3rd trial.
(Ji Hyo has two additional ballots
that she can use anytime she wants.)
The audio engineer can put a mask
on one person of his choice...
to make that person stay silent
for three minutes in each round.
- What's that?
- For a talkative person.
- That won't be useful at all.
- It's like a penalty.
- It won't be useful.
(Se Chan can make 1 person
stay silent for 3 minutes.)
(Hacker, Interior Expert, Audio
Engineer, Headhunter, Detective)
(Photographer, Security Guard,
Prosecutor, Judge, Profiler)
Actually, the two guests were
watching you come in here.
Really?
We were watching you.
- On a monitor.
- They might have noticed something.
(The two guests were watching
the members on a monitor.)
There was no camera
when I got here.
So you've been watching them.
Given what you saw,
- Was anyone acting strange?
- is there anyone suspicious?
Of course,
they could be thieves too.
- They can give professional advice.
- We need an expert opinion.
- Please tell us.
- What do you think?
You go first, Detective Yoon.
They should know about
the members of Running Man.
Who was being strange?
(It's hard to tell because they've
never met the members before.)
Since you guys aren't
real criminals...
I guess there's a difference.
So it's hard to tell.
- Just tell us your hunch.
- You can't pick out the thieves.
What does your hunch say?
To be honest, I guess
she's the thief.
- So Min?
Why is that?
Because she was the first to arrive.
- She was the first to arrive.
- I got here first.
She's suspicious because
she was the first to arrive.
But she's too enthusiastic
in everything.
- She also came early the last time.
- She was the same the last time.
- I just came early...
- But she's being strange today.
- You think?
- She's making a strange face now.
Who do you think is a thief
considering their looks?
- What?
- Considering their physiognomy.
Their physiognomy?
He's not a physiognomist.
Why would you ask that?
That's ridiculous.
Detectives can tell.
It's not like he's a fortune teller.
Hey, detectives know
stuff like that.
I get that you're trying
to get your friend to talk.
- It's not like that.
- But he's a forensic expert.
Why would you make him
talk about his hunch?
Director Pyo, who do you think
is being suspicious now?
Like what Detective Yoon said,
So Min got here way too early.
What's wrong about coming early?
We just don't know
what you're like at other times.
I came an hour early last time.
So I came only 30 minutes
early this time.
Really?
She doesn't need
to make an excuse like that.
- Anyway...
- This is just the beginning.
- But she keeps making excuses.
- Do you think I'm the thief?
- Go ahead and say it.
- I knew it.
- I thought she was being strange.
- Just say it. Is it me?
- From the beginning.
- That's enough.
- She didn't think it was strange.
- Okay. I get it.
- All right. Fine.
- So she's flustered now.
- But the thing is...
- I want to secure my part here.
Listen.
Hang on. Are you doing this
to make a strong impression?
This is what we can see in a movie.
What are you talking about?
- Is he the thief?
- He might be the thief.
I don't even know what I'm like.
- We don't know him well.
- I don't know what I usually do.
- Actually, Director Pyo would...
- That was spontaneous.
- make a good thief.
- I know.
It would be fun that way.
- He can be a thief anytime.
- Who knows? He might be the thief.
Before you get changed,
we need the interior expert.
(Kwang Soo is an interior expert.)
We need you to mark the rooms
without showing it to others.
- Now?
- Yes.
And keep it to yourself.
According to his choice,
we will mark the rooms...
Room A and Room B.
And only one of them will have
the bags with real jewels.
(Once Kwang Soo makes his choice,)
(the bags will move accordingly
in each round.)
(Room A, Room B)
(He's not supposed to talk about
what he chose before the search.)
(Kwang Soo's choice will be shared
with the thieves in secret.)
Please go get changed then.
- All right.
- Let's go.
(Now they need to catch the thieves
who are here to steal the jewels.)
Just relax.
Are you sure you're
dressed as a headhunter?
Yes. I'm a headhunter.
Aren't you a waiter?
I'm not a waiter.
I'm a headhunter.
You look like a waiter
at a nightclub I used to frequent,
who went by the name Dandelion.
I almost shouted for a waiter.
I do look like Dandelion,
a famous waiter back in the days.
You should've gotten me
a decent outfit.
- Look at him.
- This is really lame.
- Isn't he a fisherman?
- I'm an interior expert,
- Isn't he a clerk at a supermarket?
- but I don't look like one.
- He looks like a fisherman.
- What?
I got one.
What's with Kwang Soo's outfit?
Before we start the mission,
you will do the first Room Search.
You'll get 70 seconds.
You will search in pairs
as the headhunter says.
You can talk with your partner...
and decide which room
you will enter.
The thieves already know
about the rooms.
Those who are not the thieves
can lift the bags to weigh them.
If someone moved the bags,
they might be different in weight.
Or you can look for ballots.
Now we want the headhunter
to decide the order.
Let me tell you one thing. I know
it's different in a variety shows.
But I tried to sort out
the occupations.
- That's great.
- Nice.
He's a real profiler.
If you were a thief, you'd pick an
occupation that makes stealing easy.
Or you'd pick something that
helps you to hide your identity.
An occupation that makes it
easy to conceal your identity.
And lastly, you'd pick an occupation
that can confuse the ruling.
Exactly.
If the two thieves
planned this together,
- they would've divided the jobs.
- I know.
And they would come early
to pick a good occupation.
This is what we should do
when we solve a case.
But we only talk about our facial
expressions and tones of voice.
It's just a mess.
I'm sure the thieves will
get caught today.
This is what we need to do.
(Now the headhunter needs
to pair them up.)
I don't think the order is important
in the beginning.
I just need to pair them up, right?
- You have to split up the thieves.
- Based on my hunch.
It's better
to let them work in a pair.
You think?
All right. So Min, who was
considered a suspect, will go first.
- I like that.
- And...
Ji Hyo is going with you.
- With Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo is your partner.
- Really?
- You two are a team.
It's not like he has
some special plan.
Did you pick them randomly?
- I have a plan.
- You do?
We have a detective
and a profiler here.
You should ask them
before making any decisions.
- He's right.
- I don't want to.
You should ask them for advice.
I have my own plans.
Why are you being so stubborn?
In the restroom, I heard you say,
"Seok Ho, just trust and follow me."
- What do you think you're doing?
- "Trust and follow me."
Seok Ho.
Who do you think are the thieves?
You don't think it's me, do you?
- No.
- Okay.
- He sounds tired.
- That doesn't sound sincere.
- He's right about that.
- He's tired of Suk Jin.
See? He's the best detective.
He just said it half-heartedly.
You two should go first. There are
two people who look relaxed today.
Who are they?
Se Chan and Jae Suk.
- You two will go together.
- Okay.
You two are a team. Seok Ho,
I'll get you an underling.
- Haha is going with you.
- Okay.
All right. So Min
and Ji Hyo will go first.
You should remember...
that Director Pyo will be
watching you search the room.
Is he watching the whole thing?
- Why don't you start?
- Go.
Please start.
Director Pyo, please go
to the monitoring room.
(The profiler is going
to the monitoring room.)
(He will be watching all the actions
and communications in real-time.)
This way.
(He will be watching all the actions
and communications in real-time.)
So Min, you were
the first one to come, so...
(The thieves and the interior expert
know the room with real jewels.)
I don't even care
about what they say now.
I just came early
to pick a good one.
And it wasn't even that early.
It was just 30 minutes early.
- Where should we go?
- These are Room A and Room B.
(They are standing
in front of the two rooms.)
- You...
- Either one will be fine.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors
to pick a room.)
I want Room B.
(So Min picks Room B.)
- Room B?
- Do you want to change?
You seem quite confident.
Room B?
I'll do as you say.
- It doesn't matter.
- No. You won.
- You go in there.
- Okay.
I don't know anything about this.
Hang on. Does it start
as soon as I step in?
It starts as you step into the room.
We should hurry.
(They get only 70 seconds.)
(They have to find ballots
or steal jewels in the given time.)
There's nothing.
(They leave the rooms.)
Did you lift the bags?
No. I was looking for the ballots.
Did you find anything?
Is there only one ballot?
I found only one.
- Me too.
- I just touched it.
They're back.
The rooms have the same structure.
- What?
- That's right.
So Min, you have a weird look
on your face.
So Min, you're being
really strange today.
Director Pyo is watching you.
- You should remember that.
- Me?
- Next is me and the audio engineer.
- Is he watching me?
- Look at her smiling.
- Me and...
She's forcing a smile.
She's been like that the whole time.
- Really?
- This is what I'm talking about.
She's smiling.
Can he hear us talk
as we go into the room?
(Se Chan and Jae Suk
are next to go.)
You can choose the room you want.
- It doesn't matter for me.
- Either one will be fine.
I don't care either.
Okay. You passed my test.
Even if I was the thief,
I wouldn't have picked one.
- It's an amateur thing to do.
- That's what an amateur would do.
I want to choose Room A.
- You?
- Yes.
Okay. I'll go into Room A then.
- You are suspicious of me.
- Right.
- Then I'll go to Room B.
- Okay.
I'll go to Room B then.
- I'll choose Room A then.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay. I choose Room A.
Okay.
I'll go to Room B then.
(Se Chan searches Room A,
and Jae Suk searches Room B.)
There are bags.
There's nothing.
Did you find anything?
I knew it. I didn't find anything.
I found this.
Where do you want to go?
- Well, I...
- Whatever you want.
I'm fine with anything.
Just pick what you want.
Either one will be fine for me.
- Are you sure?
- Yes. Do as you like.
All right then.
- I'll search Room A.
- Room A?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Please go ahead.
I guess the thief will choose
the room with real jewels.
- I think so.
- Okay.
All right.
I should find ballots.
(Haha and Detective Yoon
are done searching the rooms.)
Which one?
We should check the bags first.
Room A and B.
(Kwang Soo knows which one
is the room with real jewels.)
You can pick the room you want.
I'll go into Room A.
Room A has real jewels.
Actually, it doesn't matter
which room I go into.
We should do this for the cause.
- You're not the thief.
- I'm not the thief,
so I don't need to go
into the room with real jewels.
The ballots are hidden
in both rooms anyway.
All right.
Kwang Soo.
(Room B: So Min, Jae Suk,
Jong Kook, Haha, and Suk Jin)
(Room A: Ji Hyo, Se Chan,
Chang Won, Seok Ho, Kwang Soo)
Se Chan who had been quiet
turned out to be a thief last time.
- Yes, he was so quiet.
- And you know that, right?
Also, when Jong Kook takes you
under his wing, you'd be so happy.
The moment he picks you
as his partner, the game is over.
You wouldn't have to do anything.
That's why Jong Kook would
never get caught...
- if he were a thief.
- I would never get caught.
It was the same for Suk Jin.
He stayed right by my side,
- acting as my right-hand man.
- It was so great.
- I'm sitting too far...
- away from him.
- Hurry up and sit next to him.
I sat too far away from him.
This is so annoying.
So Min, go back to your seat.
You see,
criminals tend to sit at the end.
But listen, Jong Kook.
- Whenever we gather around,
- For a psychological reason,
- I sit around the end.
- they don't sit in the center.
- So Min, it's you today.
- But you've never sat at the end.
(Swearing)
The detective got surprised.
- Detective Yoon is shocked.
- My gosh.
(The quick-tempered So Min surprised
even a violent crimes detective.)
- Almost everyone is here now.
- Do you know how I felt?
- You brat.
- I'm so frustrated.
Director Pyo wrote down
so many things.
- I've been observing all of you.
- Our behaviors?
I'll give you some tips.
Let me organize my thoughts first.
- He's amazing.
- That's good.
- He's a real profiler.
- Exactly.
We need to know which room
has the real jewels.
- That's the biggest issue we have.
- That's right.
- And the thieves know.
- Yes.
- So they probably...
- I also know which room has.
- tried to pick the right room.
- Absolutely.
So Min and Ji Hyo said
they didn't care...
about which room they'd go into,
but they played rock-paper-scissors.
- So Min won and picked Room B.
- Yes.
(The scientific investigation based
on facts is used on Running Man.)
- Please remember this. And third...
- Okay.
As for Kwang Soo and Suk Jin...
They fought to go into Room A.
Both of them wanted to enter Room A?
- Did they fight?
- Yes.
In the end, Kwang Soo
went into Room A,
and Suk Jin entered Room B.
- It seems that Room A...
- I will...
I will give you an important hint.
Okay. Go ahead.
Who was suspected the most
in the beginning?
- It was So Min, right?
- So Min.
- So Min is not the thief.
- Why?
- Kwang Soo decided on the rooms.
- Yes.
So he knew which room had
the real jewels.
And he wanted to go into Room A.
- But I didn't have to...
- Then why did she pick Room B...
when she won the game?
- Maybe it was to confuse us.
- Exactly.
- I think...
- Because she was cornered.
Suk Jin is trying to help So Min...
be freed from suspicion.
- But that wasn't so convincing.
- Are you defending her?
It just doesn't make any sense.
If you were a thief, wouldn't you
want to go into the real room?
You know which room is the real one.
- Since there are two thieves,
- To be honest...
maybe she let the other thief
search the real room.
- That's right.
- That's what Kwang Soo did.
Right. She must've been flustered
because she was suspected.
It would be the scariest...
- if Director Pyo is a thief,
- Indeed.
or if Detective Yoon
who has been quiet is a thief.
If the interior expert is a thief,
- that would cause great confusion.
- Exactly.
He must've picked the wrong room
on purpose.
Gosh. I really don't know
who are the thieves now.
It's hard.
I have no idea except for So Min.
(Not again.)
Gosh, you. Haha, stop it.
I think we should get rid of So Min
since we all think she's a thief.
- I'm the prosecutor, right?
- Yes.
I'll put her on the first trial
no matter what.
(I'm the prosecutor, right?
I'll put her on the first trial.)
- I'm the thief. Put me on trial.
- I mean it.
I'm the thief. Put me on trial.
- All right. Go back to your seat.
- Put me on trial.
So Min seems excited although
she's acting like she's upset.
She's enjoying this situation.
- I don't think she's a thief.
- She likes getting attention.
Detective Yoon, would you like to
share your opinion?
He has a keen eye.
Usually, thieves... You know...
Listen to his voice.
(Usually, thieves... Well...)
(He gives off his charisma
as a detective.)
- The tone of his voice...
- It's so scary.
- I'm so scared.
- It makes it feel realistic.
- I'm scared.
I peed my pants.
Exactly.
- Please continue.
- The thieves might just confess.
I bet the thieves are
shuddering now.
Before national holidays
or before they steal from houses,
"Before they steal"?
thieves go around
in a residential area.
They check if there are any CCTVs,
- and where they are,
- Really?
and if the lights are on or off
for a few days in a row.
- After checking everything,
- Yes.
they start making their moves.
- So the two of them...
- Kwang Soo and Jong Kook?
One of them could've been hired
as insiders.
I see.
- You see... How should I put it?
- Because of their occupations.
- His job is useful for theft.
- That's true.
- The interior expert.
- But as you all know,
the thieves know which room
has the real jewels.
If I were a thief,
I wouldn't have chosen to be
the interior expert...
- You're trying to avoid suspicion.
- That also...
- makes sense.
- Okay. I'll cover his mouth.
(I will cover his mouth!)
- Hey, wait.
- No.
- Hear me out.
Wait. You should...
- Hear me out, please.
- That vile mouth of his.
- I'll cover it with this mask.
- No, wait. Hear me out.
- All right. Good.
- I don't want to hear him anymore.
- Good job.
- I'm glad you did that.
- Good job, Se Chan.
Fisherman, please be quiet
for the meantime.
Secondly, what if...
A thief should not get caught
after stealing jewels.
- Yes.
- To avoid getting caught...
In my opinion, the hacker...
She can find out the passcode
of a suspicious person's bag.
And she can see if that person is
the thief or not right away.
- That's right.
- So she couldn't let anyone...
- get her job.
- Absolutely.
We can ask the hacker
to check if a suspicious person...
- is the thief or not.
- That's right.
I can't stop thinking about
what Jae Suk said earlier.
Did you arrive earlier
than Jae Suk?
(Did you arrive earlier
than Jae Suk?)
- He can't speak right now.
- Oh, right.
- Three minutes haven't passed yet.
- But he can nod instead.
- He can use body language.
- I put the mask on him.
Tell us.
Out of all the great jobs...
I can't forget
what Jae Suk said.
Why did you pick the interior expert
out of all the great jobs?
You could've chosen the headhunter
or the security guard.
- You chose it first.
- Did I?
- He didn't know what it is.
- Really?
(I didn't know
what headhunter does.)
- Good. You can interpret for us.
- Okay.
Great. Now, we have an interpreter.
He didn't know what it is?
That's right. He thought...
a headhunter meant a hairdresser.
- He thought it was a hairdresser.
- Because it has the word "head"?
- Cutting hair.
- I get it now.
- Okay. Thanks.
- Okay.
- That's so funny.
- He thought it was a hairdresser.
Before we begin the first mission,
the photographer can decide
which time can be revealed.
We took photos of you in the rooms
at every second.
- I see.
- As for the last place team,
the photos that were taken
at the 10th, 20th seconds,
and the time
chosen by the photographer.
As for the 3rd place team, only
the 1st 2 photos will be revealed.
Photographer, please tell us
the time you want now.
- The photos of a suspicious person.
- When would be the best?
- Please tell us.
- They must've been more active...
at a later time after pretending
to search at first.
But if the photographer
can decide the time,
he can avoid doing
a certain action at the time.
You have a point.
Because he knew he'd decide it.
- Okay. That's true.
- He could've avoided the time.
Hold on a second.
(Hold on a second!)
One of the strangest things
I've seen today is...
- Go ahead. Tell us.
- I was the fourth to arrive.
- Okay.
- He looks at me while speaking.
But no one had picked
the prosecutor and the judge.
- That's weird.
- That's right.
- What?
- No one had chosen those roles.
It would have been only natural...
if the two roles had been chosen.
That means 1 of the 3 people
who arrived before me...
- is one of the thieves.
- That's possible.
- I agree.
- Okay.
- I won't argue with that either.
- Who arrived before you did?
But I'll tell you what we said
before you came.
As Detective Yoon and Director Pyo
must've heard us,
we said, "The prosecutor and judge
won't be helpful."
We didn't want to be
the prosecutor or the judge.
We thought the roles
wouldn't have much power.
- We decided not to choose them.
- Yes, we did.
- Se Chan said it first.
- It's because last time...
If you think that way, everyone is
suspicious... What are you doing?
(What are you doing?)
- That's great.
- He wants you to shut your mouth.
I want you to shut your mouth.
Just shut it.
- When I was an insurance agent,
- Jae Suk.
my superior used to
harass me like this,
- so I hated my job.
- You know what you put me through.
It's so strange
that the photographer...
Please make your decision now.
Kwang Soo, your time's up.
(Please make your decision now.
Kwang Soo, your time's up.)
This is so fun.
Let's do this more often.
- Who could be the thieves?
- I feel like I became ill.
I felt so frustrated. I hadn't
felt that way in a long time.
I bet he was dying to speak again.
What time will you choose?
I think you should pick
a later time.
I'll pick...
- the 45th second.
- The 45th second?
Let's think about
the time again later.
According to the result
of the mission we'll begin now...
You'll pair up with the same person
for the mission.
Three photos of the members
of the last place team...
- will be revealed to everyone.
- All right.
- The last place team.
- And two photos of the members...
of the fourth place team
will be revealed to everyone.
- Okay.
Here's your first mission.
You have to find someone on set
with a composite sketch you draw.
It's Composite Sketch Operation.
What's that?
You'll play the game
with the same partner.
One has to complete
a composite sketch...
through an interview
with a staff member.
The other has to find the person
using the composite sketch...
wearing headphones
once the sketch is done.
2 photos of the 4th place team...
and 3 photos of the 5th place team
will be revealed.
- Okay.
- This is a very important mission.
Please sit with your partner,
and decide who will draw the sketch
in the first round.
- Okay. Detective Yoon, please come.
- Please come here, Prosecutor Yu.
Take turns to ask questions to me.
Each team has two questions.
Starting with a question
about the gender.
You can't ask about the gender. I'll
only tell you about the appearance.
- Okay.
- It's one of the people here?
Correct. And the photo was taken...
- this morning.
- This morning?
- But they're all wearing a mask.
- All of them?
They will pull down the mask
when you approach them.
- Just for a moment.
- I see. Okay.
I'm very good at drawing
this kind of drawing.
- Jae Suk's team is done for.
- We can do this.
He's lousy at drawing.
Starting with So Min,
you may start asking questions.
What fruit would you compare
to this person's face shape?
(A fruit shape?)
- Please compare it to a fruit.
- That's a weird question.
Compare the face shape to a fruit?
She could've just asked,
"Please describe the face shape."
Whether it's long or round.
- But if it's compared to a fruit,
- Or if it's a square face.
If it's compared to a fruit,
it will be more accurate.
A wide and flat mango.
- A wide and flat mango?
- A wide mango.
- Okay. See? It's more accurate.
- I don't know how a mango looks.
- Hold on. A wide mango?
- A wide and flat mango.
The question was wrong.
- I'll draw it just as I heard.
- A wide and flat mango?
- Okay.
- A wide and flat mango.
A wide and flat mango?
How big are the eyes?
Somewhat large.
Somewhat large?
(Face: A wide and flat mango,
Eyes: Somewhat large)
A wide and flat mango?
Wide and flat?
(Who can it be?)
A wide and flat mango.
Next question, please.
Please describe the eyebrows.
The eyebrows...
They're quite bushy.
- Bushy.
- Bushy eyebrows.
- A little bushy.
- Bushy?
- Let me ask an important one.
- Large eyes.
Does this person wear glasses?
No, no glasses.
(Kwang Soo's composite sketch)
- I'll ask an important one.
- Sure.
Does this person have on makeup?
- Makeup? A little, I think.
- Okay.
- That indicates a woman.
- It must be a woman.
Hold on. That changes everything.
So Min, you're up.
This is called the top zone,
the middle zone,
and the bottom zone.
Is this person's bottom zone
on the longer side?
What's the bottom zone?
Is the mouth situated
toward the center or the chin?
What kind of question is that?
You call that a question?
You already asked.
- The mouth is close to the chin.
- I mean...
What kind of question is that?
She must desperately want
to be suspected as the thief.
Why not ask about the nose instead?
- Let's move on.
- Jae Suk?
- Tell us about the hair.
- What was her question?
The hair...
This person has bangs,
and the hair is shoulder-length.
Jong Kook?
Tell us about the nose.
How about the nostrils?
The nose bridge is high.
It's on the higher side?
Is the mouth big or small?
- I think it's small.
- I did a good job then.
- Small?
- A small mouth?
To me, it is.
Is it closer to
the center of the face or not?
Why is she so bad
at asking these questions?
- Some are closer to the nose.
- So Min is...
the thief which is why...
She's making it seem too obvious.
How else can I sketch properly?
We need to know...
- if this person has a long chin.
- Haha?
- Is there a mole on the face?
- Yes.
- A mole on the face?
- That's what I said.
I know that there's a mole,
- but where exactly?
- You have five seconds.
- Where is the mole?
- 5, 4,
- 3, 2, 1.
- I think I know who it is.
Put this sticker on that person.
- Go ahead.
- I don't know where the mole is.
- Hurry.
- Hurry. You need to get going.
- How is this supposed to be done?
- Take the sticker.
- Come on.
- Who on earth is this?
Here's the sticker.
Are you okay?
- Hold on.
- Over here.
There's a mole.
- Wait.
- Hold on.
(Jae Suk's composite sketch)
(She looks like the sketch.)
Is it you? Okay, hold on.
Here.
Is it Yoo Ri?
It looks just like her!
This person has big eyes.
(Does she look like the sketch?)
She looks like it.
- See?
- What's this?
- What on earth is this?
- I found her.
Min Hee?
- I think you're right.
- Right?
Perfect, right?
- You're right.
- It's Min Hee.
- He's right.
I drew Min Hee, didn't I?
That staff member though...
- Right.
- See?
- She looks like the sketch too.
- A wide and flat mango.
I didn't think that a face
that had the shape...
of a wide and flat mango made sense,
but that's all I could see.
- Guys...
- She has a mole there.
Let me reveal the answer.
Someone got it right.
- What?
- Really?
The answer is...
Just know that I kept it
as objective as possible.
The answer is...
(Who was he describing?)
Min Hee.
This is amazing!
- Hey...
- This is what I had to go on.
- I mean...
- Based on this...
- How did you figure it out?
- Jae Suk,
- she immediately came into my view.
- Jae Suk.
- How did you know?
- Look at my sketch.
It looks exactly the same.
Yours looks just like her.
- It looks just like you.
- It looks like Min Hee.
Mine too.
(Kwang Soo's sketch?
She refuses to agree.)
A wide and flat mango.
That was a perfect description.
Anyone can tell
that this is Min Hee.
- You have great teamwork.
- Nice.
I have received the photo
of the next staff member.
We'll start with Ji Hyo.
Tell us about the shape of the face.
It's on the slimmer side.
(Face: On the slimmer side)
- Okay.
- Is it my turn then?
Does this person
have double eyelids?
Yes.
- Double eyelids?
- Yes.
(Face: On the slimmer side,
Eyes: Double eyelids)
- Go ahead and draw.
- Does this person have long hair?
- Go ahead.
- How long is it?
- The hair...
- It's on the shorter side.
- The shorter side?
- This person has short hair.
- Short hair?
- It's on the shorter side.
- Then it's a guy.
- Is the mouth big or small?
I'd say average.
Does this person have a long nose?
It's not short,
but it's also not long.
This is someone's foot, not a nose.
Does this person have big eyes?
There are double eyelids, so yes.
But they're not huge.
Everything about this person
is average.
- Does this person wear glasses?
- No.
All right.
- 5, 4...
- Do we get going?
- 3, 2...
- Is that it?
- Who on earth is this?
- One.
How am I supposed to find
anyone with this?
(Detective Yoon's
mediocre drawing skills)
- Can you believe it?
- What on earth is this?
- How is this a good enough sketch?
- This isn't enough.
No one that looks like this exists.
- We should hurry.
- This can't be a person.
Where is a guy that looks like this?
(I've never seen a person
with this face before.)
Does this person even exist?
- I mean...
- Jae Suk, use your sharp eyes.
Yes, he looks like the drawing.
(Jong Kook already
brought someone over.)
This hair can be called short.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo...)
(He spots someone.)
This guy... What?
It's like his photo.
I have his photo!
(He looks exactly like the drawing.)
I didn't think this person exists,
but this was a photo of him!
(Beware: It's not a photo.)
(The drawing looks
exactly like him.)
Can you believe it?
(Cho Sung Oh, cameraman)
I can't believe you took
a photo of him.
- It's you.
- No, this one looks like you.
- He was here.
- You were here all along.
Look at this!
(He has the face
that fits all composite sketches.)
- This looks like you too.
- I found you!
- I must be gifted in this field.
- I can't find one.
But he doesn't have double eyelids.
- He does.
- He has them.
Can it be one of us?
It can be anyone in this auditorium.
- It could be Detective Yoon.
- You're right.
Kwang Soo found
the perfect person though.
Can you believe it?
They look the same!
I thought it was him at first too.
- Guys...
- Did someone get it right?
Yes, someone got it right.
- What?
- Really?
It must be Detective Yoon.
The answer is...
(Detective Yoon?)
(Or the cameraman
who had his photo taken?)
It's Na Dong Geun.
(Chang Won and Jong Kook
got it right.)
I knew it.
- What did I tell you?
- But...
I had to give up though.
(That's too bad.)
I said it was him.
How can one find
the right person with this?
I knew it almost immediately.
He was right there.
(Chang Won and Jong Kook
score a point.)
- Shall we begin?
- Yes, ask away.
Please describe the face again...
in the shape of a fruit.
That turned out...
- to be a smart question.
- Right?
- It gives you the shape.
- The shape of the face?
- All the way up to the head.
- Well,
it's like...
a rotten zucchini.
(Hesitant)
A rotten zucchini?
Come on.
We'll feel bad about
guessing who it is.
A rotten zucchini?
It's not completely rotten,
- but...
- Only a bit?
- A wilted zucchini.
- Something like this?
One that's about 15 days
past its expiration date.
- Is that a radish?
- What about the hair?
Near shoulder-length.
Near shoulder-length?
- Next?
- Are there bangs?
Kwang Soo?
(Jae Suk's, Kwang Soo's,
Chang Won's)
Are the eyes small or big?
They're on the bigger side.
- Haha?
- A rotten zucchini?
The eyes are big and...
- What about the eyelids?
- Tell us about the nose.
The bridge is high...
and on the long side.
- Really?
- Yes.
(So Min's, Chang Won's)
- Jae Suk?
- What about the mouth?
Is it large?
The mouth...
I guess it's not small.
- This one's difficult.
- Director Pyo?
- I'm clueless right now.
- Does this person have makeup on?
Yes, a bit.
The nose is long.
If there's a mole,
tell us where it is.
There seems to be a mole,
but I can't tell from the photo.
So it's not a big mole.
No big ones.
5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
Does a person like this exist?
What now?
Hold on.
Go and look for this person.
- Unbelievable.
- Me?
- Wait.
- Is this even human?
I think I saw this character
in a film.
Look and you'll find.
- Who can this be?
- Look and you'll find.
("Rotten Zucchini" by Lee Kwang Soo)
This actually looks like her!
- It does.
- This is you.
- I think it's you.
- Me too.
Wait, you resemble
this drawing the most.
The detective already
put a sticker on me.
- It's you.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- I can't believe it.
- You will find the right person.
There's no one here
that looks like this.
Why does she look like the drawing?
She does, right?
Why does it look like her?
I can't find anyone.
- Just bring over anyone.
- I can't find anyone.
Go ahead
and compare it to the photo.
Honestly,
this has to be Kwang Soo.
- It's him.
- No way. That's insane.
- You're right.
- How is this not him?
I drew exactly what I heard.
- Are the eyes big?
- That's you.
Someone found...
- Really?
- the right person.
- Seriously?
- I knew it!
From the start though,
Detective Yoon came to me...
searching for a rotten zucchini.
(A rotten zucchini)
- Who said that?
- Detective Yoon!
- Really?
- For real?
He then twisted my arm
to bring me over.
- Really?
- Yes!
I'm amazed that
there's a right answer here.
The answer to Round Three is...
(Who has the right answer?)
Interior Expert Lee Kwang Soo.
Nice!
- See what I mean?
- I knew it wasn't you.
- Just look at this.
- It's Kwang Soo.
The 2 teams
who failed all 3 rounds...
are in 4th and 5th place.
Since Suk Jin and Kwang Soo
couldn't submit the final answer,
they'll be in 5th place.
So Min and Ji Hyo are in 4th place.
We'll get to see their photos then.
You'll be able to see...
their photos
at the 10-second mark...
- and the 20-second mark.
- It's okay.
And with Suk Jin and Kwang Soo,
you'll see their photos
at the 10, 20,
and 45-second mark.
Please bring them in.
There's nothing to see in my case.
(The photos will help them
catch the thief.)
There really can't be anything.
(Thief Investigation Log:
Room Search 1)
Before you look at the photos,
I will reveal how many jewels were
stolen during the first room search.
So they're going to reveal this.
The number of jewels that
the thieves stole...
is a total of...
(The number of jewels that
the thieves stole is...)
zero jewels.
- Right.
- Really?
(The thieves weren't active.)
- They didn't do anything.
- It's hard in the beginning.
They didn't go into that room.
Take a look at the pictures
and talk among yourselves.
Afterward, the detective will choose
one person and interrogate them.
Which room is the real room?
Jeon So Min is making it...
a point to not go near the bag.
- I went near it.
- Is it because I'm suspicious?
She's not here or there.
- It's not that...
- So Min.
Look. This is what I did.
I went in and looked around.
(So Min claims the photo was taken
after she looked at the bag.)
I noticed the bag and touched it.
Then I went to look over here.
When you look at Kwang Soo's angle,
doesn't it look like he's opening
something? He's tall.
This angle is of him
opening something.
I think he's just checking.
Is he checking to see
if it's right or wrong?
- He checked it.
- I didn't open it.
- So were you checking it?
- I was checking to see...
if there was one where
the passcode was moved a lot.
I'm sorry, but Suk Jin's angle
also looks like he's opening it.
- Me?
- Kwang Soo...
- At 20 seconds.
- This one?
- We need to choose one person.
- Do you think it's them?
At this angle?
I think Suk Jin is the one
who is pairing up with someone.
No, not that.
We can choose this person now,
and then...
- Detective Yoon and Director Pyo...
- Oh, their role?
are deep in conversation.
- They're so serious.
- I think it's because of this.
It's like a documentary over here.
- Kwang Soo, why did you...
- It's meaningless.
put all the bags on top?
I didn't put them up.
They were already up.
It was already like this.
You went into Room B.
- Kwang Soo went into Room A.
- I went into Room A.
- Who went into Room A?
- Right.
- Someone touched the evidence.
- Did you go in there?
(Did Kwang Soo
turn all the bags up?)
First, based on these pictures,
Kwang Soo is the only one
who is acting suspiciously.
- Why?
- All the bags were lying down.
(Every bag was lying down, but in
Kwang Soo's turn, they weren't.)
So why were they all up
when Kwang Soo entered the room?
I can tell you why.
I didn't turn them up.
- Really?
- When I went in,
- the bags were already like that.
- Were they?
Yes. Then Detective Yoon...
(Kwang Soo claims that someone else
moved the bags.)
- Among the two of us?
- Yes.
I turned them up.
(What?)
You did?
(After everyone suspected Kwang Soo,
Detective Yoon came forward.)
- Director Pyo...
- You did?
- Why did you do that?
- Why?
Why didn't you say anything before?
- Why didn't you say anything?
- You touched the evidence.
I thought I wasn't allowed
to say anything.
But everyone was blaming
Kwang Soo for it.
I wanted to feel how heavy
they were, so I picked them up.
Why didn't you say anything when
everyone was blaming Kwang Soo?
My gosh. Jong Kook acts like this
to a detective too.
He does this to a detective too.
Why are you interrogating
a detective?
Detective Yoon. You can choose one
person you think is suspicious...
and interrogate him or her.
Whom do you choose?
Isn't Detective Yoon the person
whom everyone is suspecting?
He should bring a mirror in
with him.
I want Detective Yoon to
take Jong Kook in and say,
"You need to keep your mouth shut."
(It's a place to threaten others
to keep his identity a secret.)
- "You're dead meat."
- I feel like he'll call me in...
and ask about something
completely different.
Right.
Detective Yoon,
who will you interrogate?
I will...
(Who will Lieutenant Yoon Seok Ho
call in for interrogation?)
I choose Se Chan.
- Me?
- I choose Se Chan.
Me?
Se Chan?
- Se Chan?
The two of you will move to...
- the interrogation room.
- Okay.
(Detective Yoon and Se Chan will
move to the interrogation room.)
- Se Chan?
- We found something suspicious.
- Go to the Room of Truth.
- He found something he can't say.
Yes, we caught something suspicious.
I can't tell you because it's
confidential, but...
You should tell me
why you brought me here.
It looks like this?
(This space looks like
a real interrogation room.)
(There is even an interrogation log
with everyone's information on it.)
It looks like this?
(He is nervous as he
feels pressured for some reason.)
This is intimidating.
- May I take a seat?
- Yes, you may.
You can interrogate me like
you would do in real life.
- Okay.
(Sighing)
(Flinching)
- What is your name?
- It's Yang Se Chan.
What's your ID number?
You want me to tell you
my ID number?
You told me to do
as I would in real life.
It's 861208.
- Are we being filmed?
- Yes.
Don't worry about it.
Just pretend we're not.
(He forgot and focused on
doing his job.)
It's okay. It's fine.
What time did you get here?
They told us to come by 8 a.m.,
but I came 30 minutes early.
- I was watching everyone,
- Yes.
but there was something
I didn't understand.
(Swallowing)
- When you were choosing your roles,
- Right, when we were choosing them?
- Yes.
- I chose the audio engineer first.
Right. You chose it.
Do you want to know why I chose it
when there were better roles?
No, it's not that.
- You told the other members...
- Yes?
which role they should play.
- I suggested roles to them.
- Yes, you did.
I told them which roles
I'd like them to play.
I don't understand why.
(During the opening)
(I think Jong Kook will go
well with a security guard.)
(Se Chan suggested a role
to each member.)
It's similar to the insurance agent.
(At the same time,
in the monitoring room,)
(Detective Yoon found this behavior
to be suspicious.)
If you're the thief, it could be
how you kept your composure.
That's the composure of
a criminal.
That's the composure of a criminal?
Yes, that's right.
I'm not really composed.
Why did you move the bags?
(He asked him a question
out of nowhere.)
I had to try picking them up,
but I didn't have much time.
- When it's sitting upright...
- Right.
(Detective Yoon fell for Se Chan's
change in subject.)
How can you do it?
You need to pick it up like this.
But I couldn't put it back
in its place.
- Because you didn't have time.
- Yes, I didn't have enough time.
Ji Hyo is suspicious of someone.
- I'm suspicious of someone.
- Tell us who it is.
- Me?
- Jong Kook?
She's always suspicious of me.
You might just be looking around,
but you're watching everyone's
movements as you talk.
- Your eyes are.
- That's necessary.
- Look at that.
- I need to watch.
- He is glaring at everyone.
- Look at his eyes.
- He has daggers...
- Fists are coming out of his eyes.
- He keeps shooting lasers.
- In the beginning...
- I must do that.
In the beginning, Jong Kook tried
to make everyone think it's So Min.
- He did, right?
- What is it?
- The criminal...
What kind of fish
can you catch around here?
- Pardon?
- What kind of fish can you catch?
(He asks about fishing
to the fisherman.)
He's sitting next to me
when he asked...
what kind of fish one can catch
around here.
Does he want to figure out
who the thief is?
What do you think?
- What can you catch here?
- How would I know?
(While Prosecutor Yoo interrogates
the fisherman,)
(Detective Yoon finishes
interrogating Se Chan.)
- Did you get something?
- Did you...
- get anything?
- Give us a hint.
Why did you suspect him
in the first place?
The reason why I suspected him is...
Before I knew anything,
I said it was So Min,
- Was that a fake?
- but honestly...
- Right, and I kept watching.
- He was pretending.
I don't have enough evidence yet.
Because the thieves
haven't done anything yet.
I had a thought.
I thought these two...
- teamed up again.
- That's possible.
- Right. That's possible.
- Just like how Suk Jin...
played the role of
the boss of Petty Gang...
- for two weeks in a row.
- Right.
That's possible.
You're quite talkative today.
- You're talkative today.
- Me?
- Sit down.
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
My gosh. Just because he's
playing the role of a prosecutor...
It's time to start the first trial.
The prosecutor, Jae Suk, must
choose two people to go to trial.
Is it finally my turn?
Gosh, the prosecutor is up.
How can we put him...
Settle down.
- Focus on your fishing cork.
- This is really important.
- Fishing cork?
- Look over there.
What about the headhunter?
- What gave me chills was...
- This is insane.
- Then you can tell us later.
- Okay.
(Okay, I understand.)
Gosh, I got chills.
If you have chills,
you need to take a break.
- After they settle down.
- When you have chills,
you may say something
you didn't intend to say.
- Right?
- Right.
What about you, Director Pyo?
I believe that the combination
of the interior expert and hacker...
is ideal to commit a crime.
I recommend those two people.
What do you think, Fisherman?
Right.
- To be honest, I...
- How many fish did you catch?
- I caught five.
- You caught five?
How big was the biggest fish?
- It was 30cm big.
- 30cm?
- I need to put two people to trial.
- Right.
Just choose the two people
you think are guilty.
- Should I?
- Yes.
(Who will Prosecutor Yu
put to trial?)
The first person I choose is
the photographer.
(The photographer!)
- Okay.
- Right.
- That's not a bad idea.
- I accept that.
It's not a bad choice.
It's because I'm angry.
What if they all come out now?
- That's possible.
- They won't tell us how many.
- They'll say if there is or isn't.
- Only if there is or isn't.
Just choose someone
who's suspicious.
- Jeon So Min. Come up.
- Just one. Right.
- Right.
- Get it out of the way.
- It's not me.
- To be honest,
- You can get rid of suspicions.
- in the beginning,
- Let's find out.
- most people suspected her.
- Right.
- It's not me.
One more thing.
If they tell us there is a thief,
we must figure out if it's one
of them or both of them.
It would be like last time.
That's why everyone suspected me.
Right. That's right.
Telling us that there isn't one
is good too.
Okay. The prosecutor,
Yoo Jae Suk, chose...
the suspects, Jeon So Min and Haha.
Among them, there is...
(Among the two suspects...)
a thief.
(One or more thieves exist!)
- I am not a thief!
- I knew it!
I am not a thief. I am not a thief.
- I am not a thief.
I am not a thief.
I am telling you I am not a thief.
- Jae Suk.
- I got goosebumps.
I was wrong.
I am not a thief.
- That was unbelievable.
- Good job.
I swear I am not a thief.
(Both of them claim
that they aren't a thief.)
- Things became complicated.
- I swear I am not a thief.
It's like the last race.
- Listen.
- This is driving me crazy.
You saw.
The other thief
will keep a distance now.
- This is driving me crazy.
- It's bound to happen.
It's time
for the second Room Search.
- Headhunter Suk Jin.
- Yes?
Please decide on
the order and teams.
Okay. I will separate
the two of them.
- The hacker and photographer.
- Okay.
(The two thief candidates
will be separated.)
The thieves will steal
no matter what this time, right?
- That's right.
- In that case,
make So Min and Haha enter Room B.
You should team up with So Min
and enter Room A.
- I will do that.
- All right.
Do you know which room is real?
All right! Now,
(Jong Kook cuts Kwang Soo off.)
people who are suspicious...
- Listen.
- That's right.
The rooms keep changing.
Do rooms keep changing?
- The rooms keep changing.
- Then Kwang Soo should tell us.
- Only the bags move.
- In that case,
- Kwang Soo...
- Listen.
should give
that information to those...
(But I am the one
who decides on the order.)
Kwang Soo should give
that information to those...
- Hold on.
- He is the headhunter.
- Sit down.
- Is Jong Kook the headhunter?
This is exactly what I am saying.
He does everything!
- Seriously.
- Sit down.
- He doubles as the headhunter.
- You are the prosecutor...
and headhunter.
- Headhunter, judge,
- Hey!
thug, delinquent...
He does everything.
Kwang Soo, give the information
to those who team up...
with So Min and Haha.
(I have had enough.)
- Jong Kook.
- Okay?
- That's it.
- I will cover Jong Kook's mouth.
Cover his mouth. Good job.
- He is so annoying.
- I refuse to listen to him further.
Are you in the race alone?
Everyone has a role to play, okay?
- I am the headhunter!
- Good job.
- Cover his mouth.
- All right.
- Good job.
- It's finally quiet now.
Seriously.
- Let's go.
- All right.
It's nice that
Jong Kook's mouth is covered.
(Jae Suk and Kwang Soo set off!)
(Director Pyo enters
the monitoring room.)
Which room do you want to go to?
Take your pick.
Director Pyo is watching us.
(Kwang Soo enters Room A,
and Jae Suk enters Room B.)
(So Min enters Room A,
and Jong Kook enters Room B.)
Did you find anything?
- I did.
- I opened it.
What did you open? A bag?
I am the hacker.
You can open the bag. What happened?
(So Min claims that she opened a bag
using her ability as a hacker.)
Do real and fake jewels
look different?
Can you tell by looking?
The colors are the same,
but I don't know...
if they are real or fake.
You don't know?
(Seok Ho enters Room A,
and Haha enters Room B.)
(Seok Ho and Haha finish
the search.)
The jewels got robbed.
- Where?
- Room A.
What?
My bag became a bit heavy.
(My bag became a bit heavy.)
(Detective Yoon suddenly says
that his bag became heavy.)
What?
My bag became a bit heavy.
- It's strange.
- Why?
- Why are you tilting your head?
- What is it?
- Is something off?
- Why are you tilting your head?
- Something must be off.
- What is it?
Detective Yoon, is something off?
(What is up with him?)
This is getting interesting.
(This is getting interesting.)
(Detective Yoon makes
a mysterious comment.)
I got goosebumps.
Okay. We need to figure out
who went before us.
(The 2nd Room Search)
I lifted all the bags.
Everyone else's bag is light,
but Seok Ho's bag is...
- noticeably heavy.
- What?
It became heavier.
Maybe it's So Min's doing.
Maybe So Min put jewels in my bag
and made it heavier.
- She went before you.
- Maybe...
one of them put jewels...
- in my bag.
- Was it Jae Suk?
Another possibility is
that you did it yourself.
- That's one possibility.
- That's right.
(Who put jewels
in Detective Yoon's bag?)
Photographer Haha, decide on
the time to check.
- Make it 30 seconds.
- 30 seconds should be good.
I choose the 31-second mark.
- That's his pride.
- That's my pride.
He has his pride.
All right.
I will reveal the number of jewels
the thieves stole...
during the second Room Search.
(The total number of stolen jewels
will be revealed.)
- How many did they steal?
- I bet they stole a lot.
The total number of jewels
the thieves stole is...
Did they steal the jewels?
(How many jewels
did the thieves steal?)
- 100.
- What?
(100 jewels!)
The thieves poured in the jewels.
They opened the bags
and poured in the jewels.
That must have happened.
(Who stole so many jewels
in such a short amount of time?)
But Detective Yoon's bag
became heavy.
It's not just his bag.
Director Pyo's bag...
also became heavy.
- They poured in the jewels.
- There must be jewels inside.
- Their bags aren't empty.
- Thieves...
completed their mission
by stealing 100 jewels.
They will win
if they aren't arrested.
Let's catch them.
(The thieves could either stay low
to avoid arrest...)
(or steal more jewels
to win a bigger prize.)
I will bring in the photos.
You already met the goal.
I didn't do it.
Look at Haha's shameless face.
(As per the result
of the second mission)
Two photos
of Chang Won and Ji Hyo...
will be revealed.
(Photos of the 2nd Room Search,
Chang Won and Ji Hyo)
Three photos of Jong Kook and So Min
will be revealed...
since they placed fifth.
(Photos of the 2nd Room Search,
Jong Kook and So Min)
It looks like So Min is opening...
- She is holding up the bag.
- That's right.
- She opened it.
- She held it up.
So Min said she opened a bag.
- Why?
- Why did she say it?
She didn't need to say it.
She probably knew
that she would get caught.
The posture makes me wonder
if she is studying the bag.
Director Pyo seems to be studying
the bag too.
Right? He is studying the bag.
Ji Hyo's outfit...
(Watching intently)
That's the case with Ji Hyo.
Detective Yoon is looking
at the details.
I think he is opening it.
Do you think he is opening it?
(I think he is opening it.)
I think he is opening it.
- Did he open it?
- That's right. Look at his pose.
Detective Yoon, don't be like that.
Hold on. Are you serious?
- What?
- I got goosebumps.
Could he be a thief?
Seok Ho singled out Chang Won
for the first time.
If he gets arrested...
Detective Yoon, don't be like that.
Wake up.
I can't believe you.
He turned red.
Why is your face so red?
Your face is about to burst.
- Even his neck is red.
- I mean...
- Even his ears are red.
- I am really flustered.
You turned so red.
I am really flustered.
- Let's see.
- You want some water, right?
- My goodness.
No, no.
Even before I entered the room,
Detective Yoon's bag was...
already heavy.
- That's right.
- I didn't do it.
Why is Detective Yoon framing me?
It's hard to tell from the photos.
(Could one of them be a thief?)
We were narrowing down
the candidates...
when he suddenly clouded the issue.
It gives the thieves an advantage.
The two of them are the thieves.
- We are open to all possibilities.
- Who?
The hacker and the spoiler.
Oh, that came out wrong.
- Spoiler!
- The hacker and the spoiler.
(Spoiler?)
Spoiler! Spoiler?
No spoilers are allowed.
- Hold on.
- No spoilers are allowed.
Spoiler?
- It's the worst thing.
- He is a profiler.
(Profiler!)
Profiler.
That was funny. That was funny.
That made everyone laugh.
- Spoiler.
- Detective Yoon.
We are colleagues.
You should know my title.
- I am sorry, but...
- The interrogation will begin.
(He suddenly becomes interrogative.)
In the photos,
you...
(Detective Yoon finds him
suspicious.)
He is making a move, right?
No matter how I look at it,
he isn't simply holding the bag.
- He is making a move, right?
- Yes.
They are going back and forth.
I am really flustered.
It would make the perfect story.
It's time to start the second trial.
For the second trial,
use your ballots as you want.
The person with the most number
of votes will be arrested.
We will give you one ballot each.
Whom should we vote for?
The one we know?
That's right.
We should do that this time.
Let's write down the name.
- Write down So Min's name.
- We should do that.
- We need to know.
- Listen.
If So Min isn't a thief...
- Then Haha is.
- Haha.
That's right.
(Haha enters the ballot box first.)
(He casts his ballot quickly.)
(He comes out.)
We should do that this time.
Haha entered and came out too fast.
I guess that makes sense
since he is a thief.
This is driving me crazy.
All right.
Let's do this fast and move on.
(Jong Kook casts his ballot
as well.)
Our decisions
won't be revealed, right?
They won't know, right?
(Thinking)
Here is the problem.
We need to figure out
if only one of them is a thief.
- That's right.
- If So Min turns out to be a thief,
we won't know if Haha is a thief.
- That's right.
- Haha.
- We must cast our ballots for Haha.
If Haha isn't a thief,
- we will know that So Min is.
- Shall we do that?
- Let's go with Haha.
- That's right.
- We must cast our ballots for Haha.
- Why?
- If Haha isn't a thief...
Let's find out if he isn't.
I don't think
both of them are thieves.
It makes sense to write
Haha's name.
It doesn't matter
as long as it's one of them.
Just cast your vote.
One of them is a thief.
(All of them cast their votes.)
- I will announce the results.
- Okay.
The member who received
the most number of votes is...
(Who received
the most number of votes?)
(Is it So Min, the member
who was highly suspected?)
(Did they cast their votes for Haha
as Chang Won asked?)
(Is it Chang Won, the member
who behaved in a suspicious way?)
(Is it Seok Ho, the member
who cornered Chang Won?)
The member who received
the most number of votes is...
- So Min.
- All right.
(So Min received
the most number of votes.)
- Please come forward.
- Go up the stand.
So Min.
All right.
Many people wrote down her name
in the beginning.
They did that
before Chang Won voiced his opinion.
I should have written down
Haha's name.
This is driving me crazy.
You keep...
(A strong thief candidate,
So Min goes up the judgment stand.)
Since So Min has been put on trial,
I will reveal her identity.
(It's time to check
So Min's identity.)
So Min is...
- She is a thief. Of course she is.
- So Min...
(Is So Min really a thief
as everyone expected?)
So Min is...
She is a thief.
A thief.
(So Min is a thief!)
I knew it.
I was certain of it.
(Thief 1 was So Min.)
All right.
She is still acting. Come on down.
Thief, sit down.
(So Min's secret)
(She chose to be a hacker to prevent
other members from seeing her bag.)
(During the 2nd Room Search)
(She opened Jong Kook's bag...)
(and succeeded to transfer
the jewels to her bag.)
(Thus, So Min acquired 100 jewels.)
Thief, sit down.
(She couldn't shake off
people's suspicion.)
There is a problem.
- We didn't clear Haha's name.
- That's right.
You can vote for me the next time.
- No. It will be our last chance.
- We can't do that.
- That's right.
- We have one chance left.
You can put 1 person
on the 3rd trial.
Now comes the last round.
- The last Room Search begins now.
- This is really hard.
All right. Now,
we need to keep So Min
from entering the real room.
So Min will steal
without hiding now.
I need to enter the real room.
Headhunter, decide on the order.
Me?
- In that case...
- You should go last.
Kwang Soo can't tell us
which room is real in advance,
so send him and So Min together.
That's the only way.
- Go with her.
What if she enters the real room?
Tie her. You are strong.
- Should I use force?
- Yes.
For fairness,
you can decide through discussion
or rock-paper-scissors.
We will get going then.
(The order of the 3rd Room Search)
Go. Go ahead.
We must catch the other thief.
- Why?
- We must.
- Which room did you go to?
- The real room or the fake room?
Did you send her to the fake room?
Did she go to the real room?
- Who went to the real room?
- Did you send her to the real room?
I didn't send her.
We played rock-paper-scissors.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- For goodness' sake.
Rules are rules.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The winner gets to choose.
- Okay. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay. Thanks, Kwang Soo.
Look forward to it.
(After winning, So Min the thief
entered the real room.)
That throws off our deductions.
Why did you do that?
- Kwang Soo is suspicious.
- We can't make deductions.
- He really is.
My hands are shaking.
- I wanted to go to Room A.
- Okay.
But it really doesn't matter
which room I enter.
I am curious about this room.
I have never entered it.
Let's see.
(My goodness.)
- It's a mess.
- What happened?
Jae Suk's bag is empty.
- Really?
- Was it open?
Kwang Soo's bag is empty too.
And...
(I can't believe her.)
Ji Hyo's bag is open,
but filled with jewels.
- Thieves didn't have enough time.
- It seems that way.
The jewels are all over the place.
They didn't have enough time.
- And...
- It was like that before.
Detective Yoon's bag is still heavy.
- Right?
- Is it still heavy?
- It's still heavy.
Chang Won's bag...
is as light as ours.
- Really?
- Yes.
That came out of nowhere.
- How did that happen?
- I guess jewels got taken out.
I guess so.
- I will go.
- In that case...
I will go.
- Se Chan, go.
- Detective Yoon.
Detective Yoon is suspicious.
(Whispering)
Jong Kook, So Min said,
"That punk is a shaman."
I am serious.
She said, "All of this happened
because of that punk."
She said she will give me
50 percent of the prize...
if I let her go into the real room.
(So Min tried to strike a deal.)
(Se Chan and Detective Yoon
come back.)
- How was it? Was your bag heavy?
- Well,
it was exactly as Suk Jin said.
- It's a big mess, right?
- Yes.
Hold on. So are there
still a lot of jewels in your bag?
Yes. My bag is still heavy.
If we were to focus on the fact,
the person
whose bag is the heaviest...
with jewels is you.
Right?
Haha, you are quite chatty today.
I have always been chatty.
No. You are acting differently
today.
Do you think Haha is a thief
as well?
- He is suspicious.
- This is driving me crazy.
Photographer, decide on the time
one last time.
- 25 seconds.
- Bring in the photos.
- I will say it as the photographer.
- 25 seconds.
Everyone.
I will reveal the number of jewels
the thieves stole...
- during the last Room Search.
- Okay.
The total number of jewels
the thieves stole is...
(Although So Min has been arrested,
her accomplice is still hidden.)
(How many jewels
did they steal today?)
- 352.
- What?
(352 jewels)
So Min let go
and stole all the jewels.
Simply put, there are
352 red jewels...
inside the thieves' bags right now.
Shouldn't we add Detective Yoon...
to the list of thief candidates?
When you think about it,
he is right.
So Min stole
as many jewels as she could.
- Then Suk Jin entered Room A next.
- Yes.
You saw the room in a disarray.
I left it as it was.
And Detective Yoon's bag was
as heavy as it was before.
Yes, it was.
Did you lift up So Min's bag?
I didn't pay attention to it.
I lifted up everyone's bag,
but no bag was particularly heavy.
Only Detective Yoon
could have stolen more jewels.
- You are right.
- No one else could have done it.
But a total of 350 jewels
got stolen.
So Min stole as many as she could,
but another person
must have taken part.
Then Detective Yoon is the only one
who could have done it.
Your deduction is wrong.
(Chiming in)
A few bags were heavier
than the others.
About two bags were heavier.
Whose bags?
I don't remember the names.
If we study the fact,
- he has the most number of jewels.
- That's right.
Let's sit down.
What should we do?
This is so hard.
- Director Pyo.
- Yes?
I get that you are helping us
as a profiler,
but you never explained why
you aren't a thief.
- Me?
- Yes.
I can't be a thief.
- Why is that?
From the start, I said So Min is
a strong thief candidate.
Isn't that right?
If I were an accomplice,
I wouldn't have put her in danger.
We do that sometimes.
(We do that sometimes.)
We do that on purpose.
That's right. We do that a lot.
It could be a ploy
to avoid suspicion.
We use such a tactic a lot.
The other thief had no reason
to enter Room A.
- That's right.
- So Min did all the work.
So Min was the only thief
who entered Room A.
It must be one of the people
who entered Room B.
Who entered Room B?
Room B. Haha entered Room B.
- I entered Room B.
- Room B.
- Who else? Room B.
- I entered Room B.
(Ji Hyo, Haha, Se Chan,
Jong Kook, and Kwnag Soo)
The security guard can check...
three photos of a member.
Jong Kook, pick a member.
Whose photos should I look at?
Give me recommendations.
How about Director Pyo?
I recommend Director Pyo too.
Why...
do I want to see
Haha's photos like crazy?
Look at Haha's photos.
Jong Kook has suspected Haha
from a while ago.
- Jong Kook has a hunch.
- This is driving me crazy.
But it would be meaningless
to look at Haha's photos.
I say that...
because he probably did nothing
in Room B.
- So it would be meaningless.
- Don't do it.
I should look at So Min's photos.
(I should look at So Min's photos.)
- Again?
- I should see how she moved them.
That's right.
- That's right.
- How she moved the jewels.
- I should do that.
- That's a good idea.
It would be better to see
where she put the jewels.
That will give us the answer.
- That's right.
- You are like a profiler.
So Min is the only one...
- whose action can give us clues.
- That's right.
Will you look at So Min's photos?
- Yes.
- He is smart.
(So Min's photos will be provided
as soon as they are ready.)
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are
at fourth place,
and Jae Suk and Chang Won are
at fifth place.
- The third Room Search.
- Look at the last ones.
- Here.
- The last ones.
Let's look at the last ones.
Is Ji Hyo lifting up the bag?
I lifted up the bag.
I did it with every bag.
(Photos of the 3rd Room Search)
(Ji Hyo seems to be straightening
the bag.)
Jae Suk is shaking it.
- Jae Suk is checking.
- I checked.
(Jae Suk seems to be checking
the bags in the photos.)
It looks like he is opening it.
- He is opening it.
- It looks like he is opening it.
(Director Pyo seems to be opening
the bag in the photos.)
(Chang Won, Room B, 10 seconds,
Chang Won, Room B, 20 seconds)
(Chang Won, Room B, 25 seconds)
Why is he picking it up like that?
Don't you usually do this?
This is right. You have to
pick it up like Jae Suk.
Or when you shake it.
- This is...
- This is... Look.
It looks like he's opening it,
not shaking it.
(What is the truth behind
the suspicions?)
Suk Jin.
What is this bag that's open?
- The ones that were open are...
- This one was open.
Kwang Soo's bag...
and your bag.
(He gave a clear testimony that
the bag was open and it had jewels.)
(He got excited and told everyone
that the bags were open.)
You said that two of the bags
were open.
Kwang Soo's and yours.
- But it's not open here.
- It's not open.
It's closed here.
(The bags are all closed?)
(Come to think, all of the bags...)
(are closed in Suk Jin's photos.)
- They're all closed.
- I opened them later.
- What?
- Later.
- Later? How?
- Later?
- I was touching them, and...
- You opened them?
Suk Jin.
- You clearly said...
- This is driving me crazy.
- I did this.
- that two were open.
I shook the bags, and they opened.
I shook them, and they opened.
You said my bag was on the floor.
- He said it was open.
- You said it was open, right?
- None of them are open.
- Two of them were open.
Gosh. This is driving me crazy.
- We caught him.
- It was Suk Jin?
(Could Suk Jin be the thief?)
Jong Kook.
You can't share this with anyone.
You must look at it alone.
(So Min's fellow thief's identity
will depend on her movements.)
First, she opened it.
She opened it and...
(So Min touched the fourth bag on
the right as soon as she started.)
(So Min, Room A, 10 seconds)
(So Min, Room A, 20 seconds)
(So Min, Room A, 25 seconds)
(Nervous)
(What did Jong Kook find out?)
Guys, come here.
Tell me if you know what it is
after you listen to me. Hold on.
- This is...
- After So Min went in.
- after So Min went in, right?
- Yes.
Whose bag is this? This one.
Does anyone know?
Whose bag did you say it was again?
- This one.
- I don't know.
(Jong Kook believes that this bag
belongs to her fellow thief.)
- So Min took out the first bag...
- Hey.
Isn't the middle bag Haha's bag?
(Does the bag belong to Haha?)
(If so, is Haha a thief?)
(The thief, So Min's decisive
evidence has been revealed.)
This is driving me crazy.
I have no idea.
I really have no idea today.
The suspect list keeps changing.
(It's almost time to do
the last vote.)
- Se Chan is suspicious too.
- This means...
Isn't So Min's partner
always Se Chan?
- It's clear that...
- No. It's not that simple.
(He takes a look at
all the pictures they've collected.)
Jae Suk...
Director Pyo's suspect list is...
Hold on.
Let me ask one last question.
Who entered Room B
during the second search?
Yes, please stand up.
Who entered Room B
during the second search?
(After finding out who went into
Room B during the second search,)
- The people who went into Room B.
- During the second search?
Room B during the second search.
Who went into Room B
during the third search?
(he asks who went into Room B
during the third search.)
I went into Room B
during the third search.
Haha is the only one who kept
going into Room B.
- Right.
- And Ji Hyo.
After the first trial where
we determined that...
Haha and So Min might be thieves,
they might've divided up their roles
and agreed to go into one room,
- so he kept going into Room B.
- But I...
(Haha is suspicious because
he never went into Room A.)
But I... You can suspect me,
but I never chose
which room I wanted to go in.
From the beginning,
I can't stop suspecting Haha.
If you look here, there aren't
any photographs of Haha.
Right.
(Haha isn't in any of the evidence.)
(Thief Investigation Log)
(Haha's whereabouts haven't been
revealed in the slightest.)
I'm wondering if he purposely
tried to keep himself hidden.
I didn't do anything.
- I think I have to go with my gut.
- Right.
I don't have a choice.
(Potential Thief 1,
Pyo Chang Won, Profiler)
(Powerful authority as a profiler,
Looked like he was opening a bag,)
(Seemed flustered
and his face turned red)
(Potential Thief 2,
Yoon Seok Ho, Detective)
(Bag got heavier,
Last one to enter Room A)
(Potential Thief 3,
Haha, Photographer)
(Came early and chose photographer,
Went into Room B all three times,)
(Doesn't have picture evidence,
Quite talkative)
(Potential Thief 4,
Ji Suk Jin, Headhunter)
(The photo contradicts
his testimony.)
(Possibility of another
Petty Gang crime)
We'll start the vote quickly.
You can use all of your ballots.
Shouldn't we put Lieutenant Yoon
on the list too?
He has the most jewels.
(Are you?)
- I'm not. I'm really not.
- They went to Room A then Room B.
If it's you, I'm really going to...
- It's not me.
- Right.
If it's you, then...
- It must be Haha.
- Haha?
- Write it down.
- I don't think it's you.
- It's not Suk Jin.
- Because you...
didn't go in at the end.
I'm really happy right now.
The thief must not be
one of the people we mentioned.
We're done voting.
- We're done counting the ballots.
- Please.
Show your determination.
The final person to go
to the third trial is...
(They'll reveal the person who got
the most votes...)
(and will go to the third trial.)
(The person to go to
the 3rd trial is...)
- Haha.
- Okay.
(The person to go to
the 3rd trial is Haha)
(Haha got 46.7 percent of the votes
and will go on the Judgment Stand.)
I don't know why it's me.
That's right.
We lost.
- I don't think it's him.
- I don't know why you chose me.
- I have no idea who it is.
- Why did you choose me?
I didn't even consider Haha because
there's no way we chose...
both thieves during the first trial.
That's what I thought too.
It's fine.
If Haha is a thief,
- Team Thieves will lose.
- Right.
If not, the civilians will lose.
I don't know who it is,
but you're a great actor.
- It's not Haha.
- You're great.
I acknowledge you.
Haha's identity is...
(Haha was suspected from the start
and was uncomfortable all day.)
He is...
(What is Haha's identity?)
- Please.
- He's not.
He's not.
He is a thief. The civilians win.
(Haha was a thief.)
(The civilians win.)
- Seriously?
- Didn't I tell you?
- Kim Jong Kook!
- We found...
- We found them at the beginning.
- What did I tell you?
I told you he was, right?
He is a thief. The civilians win.
- We found them at the beginning.
- What did I tell you?
(Kim Jong Kook!)
(I know how you feel.)
I can't believe it.
I'm so annoyed.
- Jae Suk.
- I told you it was him, right?
We wouldn't have gotten it right
if it weren't for you.
- The two of you...
(The second thief duo was
Jeon So Min and Haha.)
The two of you will
become thieves...
Thieves?
and get your revenge.
I'm not confident.
I can't do this.
I already have
a bad feeling about this.
- Is it jewels this time?
- Depending on how many you steal,
we'll give you a gift accordingly.
Then our first pick is photographer.
The photographer
is really important.
Hacker and photographer?
(They followed their plan,
came early,)
(and became the hacker
and the photographer.)
(Everyone was suspicious because
So Min came really early.)
(Their plan failed because
they came really early...)
(and made artificial choices.)
(They altered the weight of
the bags in each room.)
(So Min used the fake jewels
to make the bags heavier.)
(Detective Yoon and
Director Pyo's bags became heavier.)
(Haha, who was in the fake room,)
(also altered the weight of the bags
to cause confusion.)
(They briefly mentioned that
Room B was manipulated,)
(but Jong Kook's senses kicked in
and said it might be fake.)
(Their plan failed because nobody
focused on Room B...)
(because they believed that Room A
was the real room.)
I'll say that it's you.
What if we get caught in
the 1st or 2nd trial?
That won't happen.
There's no way.
(As everyone suspects So Min,
Haha cut her off as planned.)
(Are you already cutting me off?)
(However, Jae Suk caught Haha.)
(The results were humiliating as
they were both put on trial.)
(Haha saved himself.
So Min got caught,)
(so she stole while Haha
didn't do anything suspicious.)
(Exhaling)
(However, Jae Suk figured him out.)
(That tenacious...)
(Have Jong Kook on our side.)
(The criminals...)
(tend to sit on the edges.)
(They were sitting with Jong Kook
between them...)
(when they got flustered.)
(These two people kept bothering
the thieves from the beginning.)
(They were Jae Suk and Jong Kook
who have good intuition.)
(This resulted in the failure
of the two thieves.)
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook's
splendid achievement.)
- Jae Suk.
- I was right, wasn't I?
(This is how dangerous it is
for them to be on the same team.)
(These two suffered a lot today.)
Let's not have them guess based on
how they speak.
His hands were like this all day.
He kept moving them.
(The theory of profiling doesn't
work in this universe.)
Jong Kook is amazing too.
I know.
(You tenacious people.)
I could tell.
They had no evidence whatsoever.
The two civilians
who will receive the prize are...
Detective Yoon, please enjoy.
Goodness. Thank you.
Director Pyo and Detective Yoon,
- please say goodbye.
- Right.
We had so much fun today.
Thank you so much for inviting us.
It was delightful and fun today.
- Come in.
- Thank you.
- The two of you made it more fun.
- I agree.
- Seriously. We had so much fun.
- Let's thank them again.
- Thank you.
Your penalty will be combined...
- with the next one.
- Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Good job everyone.
(1st place, 37g of gold)
(37g of pure gold
is waiting for them.)
(Among them, the luck of
winning the lotto...)
(will go to 1 lucky person only?)
(A desperate struggle
to become that 1 person)
(The 8 hobbies of 8 people
will start.)
(1st period, Teamwork is important
when dancing the Samba.)
(She's the only who's
overly passionate.)
(Passionate newlywed couple...)
(versus two people
who are about to fight)
(This is Hawaii.)
(2nd period, Your expression is
important when dancing the Hula.)
(Expressing love, happiness,
and gratitude with his body)
(The winner is the person
who enjoys this stage.)
(They try singing in a capella,)
(but they fail.)
(Their attempt at hobbies doesn't
seem easy. Will they succeed?)
(8 People, 8 Colors Preference Race,
Lucky Hobbies)