(Member's Week on Running Man)
(Fourth)
(Who is the fourth participant?)
Today's rule is if the participant wins, the prize will be doubled.
Say a few words to the members.
Are you fully prepared?
I won't go easy on you.
I won't feel bad.
My plan is to get rid of them all at once.
(Please look forward to my great accomplishment.)
(Running Man, Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals)
(Gary was the winner of the 1st and the 2nd Ultimate Battle.)
(Haha was the winner of the 3rd Ultimate Battle.)
(Jae Seok was the winner of the 4th Ultimate Battle.)
(Haha was the winner of the 5th Ultimate Battle.)
I am Agent Jae Seok.
(Agent Jae Seok)
I am Black Widow Ji Hyo.
(Black Widow Ji Hyo)
(Avatar Kwang Soo)
I am Thor.
(Thor Jong Kook)
In front of your eyes...
(Detective Seok Jin)
I am the Time Controller.
(Time Controller Haha)
(Who will be the final winner?)
(Magic energy surrounds Sangam-dong.)
(R Headquarters have an unapproachable aura.)
(It's the shrine of the best supernaturals.)
(Jae Seok appears first in R Headquarters.)
The fourth Member's Week is Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals.
You are to prevent the host of the fourth Member's Week from winning...
and to become the ultimate winner.
I understand.
- You are Agent Jae Seok. - That's right.
Water gun is a symbol of me.
(The first supernatural is Agent Jae Seok.)
(He approaches quietly and eliminates his target at once.)
Your special ability is to snipe at the name tags.
- What is that? - If you shoot the name tags...
with your water gun,
you can eliminate the corresponding member.
Everyone is on their toes about my water gun.
(Agent Jae Seok has to shoot their name tags with the water gun.)
Haha, you are Time Controller.
I can travel the time.
I am Time Controller Haha.
(The second supernatural is Time Controller Haha.)
(He has a superhuman ability that stops the time from passing by.)
Your mission will determine the level of your special ability.
Your mission is to deactivate bombs.
Did you say I have to deactivate bombs?
You have to solve the hints in order to deactivate each bomb.
The level of the ability will depend on how many bombs you deactivate.
Will it explode here?
I have to succeed this mission then.
I am Time Controller.
(Time Controller Haha's mission is to deactivate bombs.)
You are Black Widow Ji Hyo.
Your special ability is your looks.
With a particular motion and spell, your ability will be put in action.
It will help you defend yourself and is divided into three stages.
Your mission is to make the coin stand.
If you can make the coin stand for three seconds, it's a success.
(Black Widow Ji Hyo's mission is to make the coin stand.)
I am Detective Seok Jin.
It's the unfortunate character.
(Unfortunate Detective Seok Jin is stepping up.)
You have to spot the differences to complete the mission.
- Spot the differences? - Yes.
Take a good look at the scriptwriter in front of you.
I have to figure out what has changed.
(He has to find 7 differences to get the highest level.)
In 10 seconds?
(Detective Seok Jin's mission is to spot the differences.)
You are Thor Jong Kook.
Your special ability can enlarge the name tags.
When you hit the ground with the hammer,
the chosen member's name tag will be enlarged.
In 30 seconds, you have to hammer the nails stuck on the wood.
You clear the mission if you hammer them properly at the first try.
The ability level will be determined by the number of nails you hammer.
(Thor Jong Kook's mission is to hammer the nails at once.)
You are Avatar Kwang Soo.
You have the ability to control other supernaturals' abilities.
You can control one of the members' abilities that you want.
- So I can absorb their abilities? - Yes.
You can absorb them. The mission for you is...
to make bonds with people as an Avatar.
Put on an Avatar make-up and meet citizens...
What? Hey.
(You are joking, right?)
It's not difficult. Go meet the citizens...
and say the certain spell out loud.
- Then bond your hair with others'. - What?
Did I do something wrong? Is this a penalty?
- What? Spell? - Yes, that's your mission.
Hold out your hair after then.
If the citizens say those words and hold out their hair in return,
you accomplish the mission.
It's easy, right?
I give up.
What is this?
(Perfect urination system)
We prepared so well.
Thank you so much.
(Avatar Kwang Soo's mission is to bond with people.)
(We can sometimes find the Na'vi people in Sangam-dong.)
(We hear that a new Avatar has been born.)
(Earth, are you ready to meet the new Avatar?)
(Kwang Soo's waiting room)
Why?
(I see you.)
I give up.
You can't give up.
I'll rather accept the penalty.
You remember the spell, right?
(Avatar Kwang Soo heads out to the outside world.)
(Walking on eggshells)
Hello.
- Are you an Avatar? - Yes.
- You are Kwang Soo, right? - Yes, hello.
- You can't recognize easily, right? - I can know because of your height.
You can recognize with me with my height.
I'd rather be nude.
(He finds people in the elevator.)
(Embarrassed)
(Please leave the elevator. I want to be left alone.)
(It's hard to even look at him with his hideous aura.)
(Are there anyone who will join me in my mission?)
(The area is full of people today.)
I really can't go outside like this. What should I do?
He's over there.
What's that Avatar doing there?
(Strong impression)
Avatar Kwang Soo.
Hello. Wait a second.
Why do you look so normal?
What are you doing?
(Why are you dressed like that?)
Kwang Soo...
(I was tricked.)
That scumbag.
(Do you think I'm easy?)
(Jae Seok's mission is to shoot as many name tags as possible.)
(Avatar Kwang Soo is occupied with the director.)
What is this?
(He approaches slowly and shoots quietly.)
That's not what you told me.
Why are you dressed like that?
(Agent Jae Seok succeeded in shooting one person.)
What are we doing today?
(He hides the evidence quickly after he's done.)
Hey, why are you...
Why are you dressed like this?
Did they tell you that everyone's doing the same?
(I need to do something with that director.)
By the way, what is this? Are you a servant or something?
What are you talking about?
I have to go now. See you later.
You are doing something, right? What are we doing today?
I don't know. What's she doing over there?
She's not wearing any costumes.
(Black Widow Ji Hyo is absorbed in her mission.)
Don't come near me.
- What are you doing? - Oh, my. What is that?
(It's a shocking visual.)
(Silently approaching)
What are you doing?
(Ji Hyo is absorbed in her mission.)
How did you get this to stand up?
Don't come near me.
(In that case,)
(shall I do my mission?)
- How did you make this stand up? - Leave me alone.
- Kwang Soo. - How?
(Shooting)
(Agent Jae Seok succeeded in shooting 2 people.)
Don't come near me.
(He shot at a single chance with his confusion tactics.)
How did you do it?
- It's easy with one-cent coin. - It's so cool.
(Ji Hyo doesn't know anything.)
- Is that your mission? - Leave me alone.
(Going this way and that)
Go away.
(He's hiding the name tag in case Kwang Soo notices.)
Where is Seok Jin and Haha?
Ten seconds left.
Ten seconds? She must have a deadline.
Do you have a mission?
(Wait a minute. Why does the paint stain look so familiar?)
Wait a minute.
(Did you see it?)
(Please keep quiet.)
I didn't do it to yours.
(It might feel suspicious but I didn't shoot at yours.)
- You didn't do mine? - I didn't do yours.
(What is happening?)
I couldn't do yours.
(Anyway, I caught you.)
- Be quiet. - Everything is up to me now.
You know that you can't finish your mission if everyone knows, right?
- I'm begging you. - In that case,
- I'll give you a final chance. - Okay.
(Avatar spell)
- Think carefully. - What is that?
You need to make a bond with me. Using the hair.
Yes, I remember.
(Give and take)
This is your final chance.
(It's okay to commune in exchange for keeping quiet.)
- It's your final chance. - What is that?
I told you to concentrate.
It's your final chance.
I told you that it's your final chance.
- Okay. - I can tell...
I get it.
(Running away)
Hey.
(Sorry, Kwang Soo. I can't do this.)
I'm telling you.
Jae Seok, wait!
What are you doing?
(Be careful of that blue giant.)
- Be aware of Kwang Soo. - What is it?
(I only need a strand of hair.)
- Wait. - He looks really like an Avatar.
He's scary.
(Jae Seok runs away leaving the cameraman.)
Please do the mission with me.
What am I supposed to do?
You know how they make a bond, right?
Jae Seok, wait. Do this for me.
(Jae Seok runs towards Thor Jong Kook without a cameraman.)
(Shooting)
(Agent Jae Seok succeeded in shooting 3 people.)
(He hammers in anger without knowing anything.)
The time is up.
I can't do this.
Jong Kook, you couldn't hammer even a single nail.
- Oh, my. - Your ability will be level one.
You get a cotton hammer and an Exchange Card.
(Filming is not important. Kwang Soo is in a rush.)
You have to do this.
Please.
(Avatar spell)
(What would the first captured human do?)
(Shy)
Thank you.
(Kwang Soo succeeds in communing with one person.)
Thank you! You're the best.
(He's the best cameraman.)
(Thank you, kind human.)
Thank you.
Where is Seok Jin?
(After shooting at Jong Kook's name tag, Jae Seok looks for Seok Jin.)
(Detective Seok Jin is trying to find the differences.)
The glasses.
- Where is Seok Jin? - Here.
- I'm really good at this. - He's here? Okay.
(After a quick interrogation, he finds where Seok Jin is.)
Do we have to tear out name tags today?
It's not finished yet.
(He hides the water gun before going inside.)
- What are you doing? - Oh, hey.
- I'm doing my mission now. - What is it?
It's important. You can't see.
- I can. - No, you can't.
Why not?
I shouldn't let you know what my ability is.
What is your power?
(What would his deadly shot be like?)
This cigarette box looks suspicious.
(Shooting)
(One shot, one kill)
You can't see this. Go away.
This cigarette box...
(Seok Jin couldn't have noticed, right?)
- This isn't your week, is it? - Go away.
(This detective is very naive.)
He's acting weirdly.
(Then I'll get going.)
(Agent Jae Seok succeeded in shooting 4 people.)
Their knowing my mission doesn't matter, right?
(If he shoots Haha's name tag, his ability becomes the highest level.)
Where is Haha?
(The six members are busy doing their missions.)
(Kwang Soo has a long way to go.)
What should I do?
I mean, they seem scared of me.
I should go ask them.
(He finds the target to make a bond.)
- Hi. - What are you shooting?
(They seem curious. It's a nice start.)
- Aren't you cold? - Yes.
I got a hot pack for you.
- Thank you. - I only have one.
- He's so kind. - I'm not finished.
(Don't just go after receiving my hot pack.)
I have a mission.
Look at me and listen carefully.
- We're busy. - I'll be quick.
(Avatar spell)
(Desperate)
What is he talking about?
(Can you feel my telepathy?)
I want to bond with you.
I really like your hair.
(Avatar Kwang Soo fails to make a bond.)
Thank you.
(Please stop following us.)
(He now feels even colder without his hot pack.)
I'm sorry but can you get my hot pack back?
Can you get my hot pack back?
(Everyone is looking.)
What should I do?
(He wants to hide as everyone's looking at him.)
You can't see me, right?
I am of the same color.
(He's proud of his protective color tactics.)
I feel like a chameleon.
(I should keep looking for the color blue.)
It's the perfect color.
(We still can see you.)
Hello.
(Some people approach him.)
- Have you seen the movie "Avatar"? - Yes.
Do you know how they bond each other?
- Yes. - You know?
Do you want to make a bond?
(I found the perfect partner.)
Can you look at my actions and do what comes into your mind?
- Is that okay? - Yes.
- You do it. - Well...
(Avatar spell)
(It's the same scene from the movie.)
(Just connect your shiny hair to mine.)
Don't they do like this?
(Shrieking)
(What is this?)
What is wrong with you?
Wait a second.
(She must have thought of an archaeopteryx.)
I couldn't find it on the internet when I searched.
Do we do the same thing?
(That's correct.)
(He tries one more time.)
(He says the word.)
(Will she help Avatar Kwang Soo clear the mission?)
(She repeats after him.)
(The mission is cleared.)
- Mission accomplished. - Yes!
Thank you so much.
(Kwang Soo reaches level two.)
Of course. Thank you.
(They take a photo together.)
(Avatar Kwang Soo, The Legend of the Blue Sea)
Where's Haha?
Which floor is he on?
I have no idea.
(Agent Jae Seok's last target is Haha.)
What does this mean?
Who's Grakkus?
"What's the color of the lightsaber blade in 'Star Wars'"?
Is it red or blue?
(He chooses blue.)
Was that wrong?
(He fails the first bomb.)
Wait, what's Wright and Grimm?
(They refer to brothers.)
Is it the Wright brothers?
(Which number do the words refer to?)
(He picks the second.)
It was right.
"Which color do the blank letters refer to?"
(The answer is red.)
(If he's correct, he reaches level two.)
(Will Haha cut the red cord?)
(He chooses black.)
What happened?
(He only reaches level one.)
You answered one correctly.
Let's go to the third floor.
(At that time)
(Agent Jae Seok's last target is Haha.)
(Run quickly and send Haha away.)
What are you doing?
(Haha spots Jae Seok.)
- What are you doing? - What's this?
What was this?
Who's Grakkus?
- What are you looking at? - You didn't do well.
- I'm wandering about. - Don't come near me.
- Don't come near me. - What's wrong?
You have a water gun.
I was only scratching myself.
Goodness, what's this?
Why do you keep coming here? Go away.
I was only passing by.
Are you trying to do something to me?
Where's Seok Jin?
Have you seen Seok Jin?
No.
Where's Seok Jin?
(Jae Seok seems suspicious.)
He's too suspicious.
(He waits for another chance.)
This is my superpower.
(He's ready to say the word.)
Let's go back in time.
(Haha gets the superpower to turn back 10 seconds.)
He's still there.
It's better to attack Haha after his mission.
(Haha, you're terribly mistaken if you think it's over.)
What's going on?
Gosh, he's done.
Turn off the lights.
(It's time to charge.)
(Agent Jae Seok goes back to where Haha came from.)
Can I go this way?
(He goes to the waiting room.)
(Jae Seok follows him in secret.)
(He waits to attack when Haha is off guard.)
(Haha enters the waiting room.)
It's not over yet.
(He's fully prepared to reach level three.)
(It's his last chance.)
(Haha's waiting room)
(Agent Jae Seok arrives at Haha's hideout.)
(It's not over until it is.)
It's not over yet.
(Will Agent Jae Seok successfully attack his last target?)
Come on, you can't do this.
What do you mean?
You can't do this.
(Haha is completely defenseless.)
- I'm not even fully dressed. - What?
Come on.
- What's wrong? - I know you'll attack me,
but what are you hiding behind?
- What? - You're hiding something.
(Here's Agent Jae Seok's item.)
(It's a water gun.)
(He shoots.)
(Haha is angry.)
Okay, I'm leaving.
You jerk.
(What an annoying sniper.)
You're such a jerk.
- See you. - Stop filming!
(Agent Jae Seok reaches level three.)
Mission cleared.
Let's break up.
(Good job, everyone.)
(The final battle begins for the supernaturals.)
(Agent Jae Seok, level three)
(Black Widow Ji Hyo, level one)
(Avatar Kwang Soo, level two)
(Thor Jong Kook, level one)
(Detective Seok Jin, level two)
(Time Controller Haha, level one)
(Who will have the last laugh?)
(Prism Tower in Sangam)
(Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals equipped with superpowers)
(Who's the first supernatural?)
I'm Detective Seok Jin.
(He's the most observant.)
(It's Detective Seok Jin who hasn't reached his dream yet.)
It's Agent Jae Seok.
(He's the best spy despite his green outfit.)
Here's Agent Jae Seok.
(Agent Jae Seok has a fake employment for 7 years.)
Is that your gun?
(He's invincible.)
Look at him.
(He moves like a robot.)
(It's Thor Jong Kook, the strongest of all.)
What kind of hammer is that?
(The hammer is smaller than his fist.)
Look at you.
- What's that? - Did you hear it break?
Do you want me to break you?
He looks so cute.
What's that?
Who's that?
Hello, I'm the hare from "The Tortoise and the Hare".
Are you a cartoon character?
I'm the time controller,
the rabbit from "Alice in Wonderland".
(It's Time Controller Haha, an idol for children.)
Did you open up a new bar?
(How dare you?)
- You look like a bartender. - His mission was terrible.
- Who's that? - Who's that?
Does that run?
(They're jealous of her toy car.)
- What are you doing? - Who are you?
Who are you?
- I'm Black Widow Ji Hyo. - Black Widow Ji Hyo?
(She's the beautiful Black Widow Ji Hyo.)
I'll go and park it.
It's valet parking.
(Jae Seok is kind.)
Reverse.
- I can't reverse it. - You can't fit in the space?
Come on.
(He's all over the place.)
Look at him.
- You're too playful. - What are you doing?
(He finally parks the car.)
I did it.
(What is this sound?)
(Kwang Soo says the word.)
(His superpower matches his outfit.)
(It's Avatar Kwang Soo who just arrived from Hollywood.)
- You went through a lot. - Why do you all look normal?
- He deserves Top Excellence Award. - That's not it.
He deserves the Grand Award.
Why is everyone else normal?
This suits you better. You're not an actor.
- What? - Don't even try.
(He's annoyed.)
Welcome, everyone.
Welcome to Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals.
Each of you reached a certain level by clearing missions.
We'll give you a chance to obtain additional superpowers.
Depending on the result, you'll win Superpower Exchange Cards.
Superpower level is based on how many cards you win.
It's best to win as many cards as possible.
- Here is the group mission. - What is it?
It's "Group Jump Rope" which all members will participate.
- Gosh. - I like that.
If you jump 10 times, you get 5. If you jump 20, you get 7.
The number of jumps determines the number of cards.
- Do we get one chance? - Yes.
(They only get one chance in "Group Jump Rope".)
- Let's determine the order. - Jae Seok goes first.
- I'll go first. - Does it start when we all jump?
- Let's hurry then. - Get ready.
- Please do well. - I'll start.
- Let's go. - We can do it.
- In 1, 2, 3, challenge. - Challenge!
We're good at this.
("Group Jump Rope" starts.)
All right, go.
Go next.
(The first and second are off to a good start.)
(Avatar Kwang Soo hesitates.)
(He joins without a problem.)
(Even Seok Jin joins safely.)
- I'm next. - Go.
- Wait. - Go.
- Hurry up. - Go now.
(You can do it.)
(Ji Hyo joins safely.)
(If Haha joins safely, they can start counting.)
Do we get one chance?
(All members jump the rope.)
- Six, seven, eight. - Turn the rope faster.
(Kwang Soo looks like an alien.)
(They win 5 Superpower Exchange Cards.)
(If they continue at this pace...)
(Someone trips.)
What happened?
We could have done 100.
You jumped 15 times.
We will...
(Kwang Soo takes it away.)
(It's too loud.)
That was my hammer.
What did you do?
- That was mine. - I'm sorry, but I'm too sensitive.
- Give it back to me. - My hearing is sensitive.
Give back my hammer.
Take out the batteries.
It needs to make sounds.
You jumped 15 times.
We'll give you five cards.
We only get five?
- We could have jumped more. - 30 jumps were possible.
- How do we share them? - How?
- Who tripped on the rope? - Check the camera recording.
To be honest, I shouldn't say this but...
("To be honest"?)
(Who tripped on the rope?)
I don't think Seok Jin skipped the rope at the end.
- I agree. - I'm being honest.
- He's right. - I'm being honest.
Am I not right?
- Right? - I agree.
- It wasn't me. - Let's be honest.
Don't replay the camera but...
it wasn't me.
(He's not convincing enough.)
- It's because... - Excuse me.
- It's because... - Be honest.
- Be honest. - It wasn't me.
You were the only one on this side. Everybody else jumped over.
- Give me one. - That was too obvious.
- Let's be honest. - Come on.
Weren't you behind me?
- I was. - See?
- It was you, then. - It wasn't.
- It wasn't me. - Fine. Give it to me.
- Let's do a lottery pick. - Okay.
- We had an even number. - Let's give him a chance.
- We'll let it go if you admit it. - Admit what?
We'll give you another chance if you admit your mistake.
- Admit it. - Well...
To be honest,
the rope got caught on my left foot.
Give it to me.
(Seok Jin is out.)
- It's definite. - It was my mistake but...
- He admitted it. - He even lied.
- You can't do that. - He even lied.
- Let it go. - You made me confess.
I understand your point of view,
- but let's do a lottery pick. - We're one.
Hey.
(He collapses.)
- That's cheating. - His legs gave out.
His legs gave out.
(The elderly deserves some credit.)
- How does this sound? - What?
We'll ask the staff to place these cards in the rooms we were in.
- We'll pick which rooms to go in. - That works.
- That sounds fair, right? - That sounds fun.
If you open the door...
and there's no card, you don't get one.
It sounds like it's better to go first.
It's better to go at random...
- or go first. - I agree.
But if the first person goes and there's nothing, it's done.
Let's do rock, paper, scissors. Rock, paper, scissors.
(They do rock, paper, scissors.)
(Kwang Soo and Jae Seok win.)
Yes!
(The unlucky ones meet again.)
(Who will be the ultimate winner?)
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
(Avatar Kwang Soo wins.)
Yes!
(I'm going to pick the right one.)
(His unlucky DNA has been with him for 7 years.)
(Would be become the lucky icon of 2017?)
- It'll be crazy if he loses. - That would be.
Imagine having no card and looking like this.
- He'll look like a loser. - That'll be the best.
I pick R5!
(Avatar Kwang Soo chooses R5.)
- That's 5. - He chooses 5.
Okay. I think there'll be one.
I think so too.
There's a high possibility.
It's 5 out of 6.
(Opening)
(R5 has opened.)
(They get nervous.)
(Is there an Exchange Card or not?)
(What?)
There's none.
(What? Why is there none?)
- There's none. - Really?
There's nothing.
There's none.
- There's none. - Really?
There's nothing.
- There's none. - How's this even possible?
- Hey. - I'll help you.
- There's actually nothing. - Hey.
- I pick three. - Let's look in the other ones.
- There's really nothing? - There's one here.
- There's one here. - Same here.
- There is. - My goodness.
- This is insane. - Kwang Soo.
Should I turn time back for you?
- How's this possible? - Do you want me to turn time back?
- How could this be? - My gosh.
This is insane.
- How could this be? - This is impossible.
I can't be as unlucky as him.
You're unbelievable.
You shouldn't do anything this year.
What? What do you mean I shouldn't do anything?
Just appear on variety shows.
The next game is "One on One Match".
("One on One Match")
You'll be given keywords related to the game you'll be playing.
You can then choose the person you'll be playing against...
and conduct a one on one match.
However, you must bet your Superpower Exchange Card.
If you win, you get two times the numbers of cards you bet.
If you lose, they'll be taken away.
Go ahead and pick.
- Who would like to go first? - I'll go.
Sure. Go ahead, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Let's keep going like this.
- Blue ball. - All right.
They're all blue.
(Whose name is written in the first ball?)
- Jee Seok Jin. - Jee Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin's name is written on the ball.)
- Do I go first? - Seok Jin has to pick.
We're not facing each other?
You're not.
- Seok Jin goes first. - I'm the first to go, right?
- Go Seok Jin. - Okay.
The first keyword is...
- "vision". - He has bad vision.
- If you take your glasses off... - Do I have to take them off?
No, you wouldn't look good if you took them off.
Why wouldn't we look good?
- What are you talking out? - What's the point, then?
What do you mean we wouldn't look good?
We should all take them off.
My goodness.
Who has bad vision here?
Kwang Soo's pretty bad but he's wearing contact lenses.
- Right. - Choose whom you'll be playing.
Song Ji Hyo.
(He chooses Black Widow Ji Hyo.)
We've played it many times.
I pick Ji Hyo.
(Black Widow Ji Hyo vs Detective Seok Jin)
Bring in the game.
(What kind of "vision game" could this be?)
(There's a steel container.)
("Steel Container Game")
- I'm an expert in this. - That's right.
I am.
He used to do this on "Achieve the Goal Saturday".
(It makes use of Agent Jae Seok's agility.)
(Any agent should be able to do this.)
You can only see this if you try hard enough.
If you stay still, you won't be able to find out.
(Detective Seok Jin bets 2 cards.)
(Black Widow Ji Hyo bets 1.)
Ready.
(The game starts.)
(Lifting)
(Their gazes are fixed on it.)
(He does his tricks.)
- He's so fast. - There's nothing.
How silly.
How many are there?
- It's behind. - It must be on top.
Hey, I can't see anything.
(Peekaboo)
I saw it.
(They spot something.)
You can see it, right?
A pill.
(Black Widow Ji Hyo makes a guess.)
Incorrect.
Listen. The container is faced this way so you need to come here.
Why would you stay there?
(The steel container is tightly secured.)
You need to come here. That's right.
You can only see this if you work hard for it.
I open it like this.
(Is the door open?)
Look.
(The other members are curious too.)
He's so bold.
Is this some kind of trick?
- Is that what this is? - Look.
(Turning)
(They can't stand it anymore.)
Can we go up?
You can't be so far away.
Not too close, though. That's good.
I'm opening it.
I keep opening like this. See? Look.
- Look. - He's doing it in a new way.
- See? - Hey.
(For goodness' sake!)
- My gosh. - What's wrong?
What are you doing?
You have to leave it open until we can see it.
I'm so mad.
- I saw it a few times. - What am I doing?
You have to keep following me.
(They take a breather.)
I'll reveal it this time. Here I go, Ji Hyo.
(He takes the lid off.)
(As soon as you see it first, you'll win.)
(What?)
(His spins are becoming fancier.)
(You have eyes so why can't you see it?)
- I can't see any of it. - Me neither.
(He adds more tricks.)
(He must have learned a lot from the agent academy.)
(Spinning)
(Up, down, up, up, down)
(You little...)
(Game on?)
What is he doing?
(Back and forth)
(Have you heard of the tornado skill?)
(Once you take the punch, you're done for good.)
(He's the best master out there.)
(It's an honor to meet you, Master.)
- What was that? - He looks so cool.
What are you doing?
(Martial arts should have been his superpower.)
(His wrist snaps are getting better and better.)
- What's this? - What's this?
I think you two need to see a doctor.
Bubble gum. It's bubble gum.
(He repeatedly flips it over.)
(You have to get it this time.)
(If you win, you get double the number of cards you bet.)
- Pebbles. - What?
(The answer is "pebbles".)
You saw that?
- I knew it from the beginning. - They're pebbles.
- They're pebbles. - I knew it from the beginning.
- I thought it was a hair tie. - I thought it was an eraser.
It was so obvious.
I thought it was a colorful hair tie.
- I saw the color. - You have to focus to see it.
(Ji Hyo gets 2 cards and Seok Jin loses 2.)
- The second game... - I'll pick.
Seok Jin.
(Hitting)
- You can't do that. - What did I do?
(Ta-da)
That looks fun.
Lee Kwang Soo.
(Next person to play is Avatar Kwang Soo.)
Keyword for the next game...
What is it?
(Next keyword is "senses".)
- What is it? - Senses.
I think I know this.
- I hate this game. - You have to stick your hand in.
I know this one.
- You have to stick your hand in. - Haha.
No, don't. Go with Jae Seok.
(I choose you.)
- Please. - No.
I pick you.
It has to be you.
(Time Controller Haha vs Avatar Kwang Soo)
(Avatar Kwang Soo bets 1 Superpower Exchange Card.)
(Haha bets 1 as well.)
This game is called "Cheek to Cheek".
There'll be an object placed between your cheeks.
You must only use your sense of touch to guess what it is.
Whoever guesses it correctly wins that round.
The one who wins twice first will be the winner.
- Okay, shall we... - Are you ready?
Why did you pick me?
Because you're bad at this.
(What will be the first item?)
(Gosh)
(Why?)
I'm so disappointed.
(The first shocking item is here.)
Oh, my.
- This is not okay. - This is too...
(Here we go.)
(Yu Jae Seok?)
This is not okay.
(They have to feel Jae Seok with their cheeks.)
- This is too much. - It is.
- This is not okay. - This is too much.
(Nervous)
- This kind of thing... - I'm not going to be fooled.
I'm not going to be fooled, but it's still annoying.
(Feel Jae Seok between your cheeks.)
- We mean it. - Let me tell you.
When you find out the answer, you'll be so annoyed.
- I'm not sure they can do it. - I know.
- We should win twice first? - Are you ready?
Let's go.
Gosh, I'm scared.
Is it here.
(Will they get it right?)
Please tell me when you touch it.
It's coming now.
Tell me beforehand.
(Touching)
(What are you guys doing?)
(It's forbidden love that goes beyond gender and race.)
(They start feeling each other's cheeks.)
What are you doing?
Someone licked my nose.
(Someone licked my nose.)
(Hilarious)
I mean...
I felt some hair.
There's hair.
(Haha's mustache felt like a hairy monster.)
That's strange.
(Kwang Soo's lips felt like a monster's tentacles.)
Gosh.
I mean...
(Here it really comes.)
Start. It's there.
Where is it? I can't find it.
(Kiss)
(He escapes.)
(It rekindles the forbidden love.)
- Wait. - Where is it?
Where is it?
(Gosh, it's disgusting.)
- Here it comes. - Here it comes.
Is this the thing?
It's there.
(Kwang Soo sticks out his tongue.)
(It's the sweetest kiss in the world.)
(Jae Seok is blushing.)
- Don't stick out your tongue. - I know the answer.
(Did Haha already figure out that it's Jae Seok?)
- Pig skin. - It's wrong.
(It felt like pig skin.)
I thought it was something else.
(Does my skin feel like food?)
Ready.
Let's go.
(Jae Seok gets hurt many times today.)
Here it comes.
What is this?
I felt some hair.
(After kissing the microphone, Kwang Soo is shocked.)
There's hair.
(What kind of mammal did I just kiss?)
I told you you'd be annoyed.
You'll be really annoyed.
Here it comes.
I know the answer.
- I know the answer. - What is it?
- Was that it? - What's your guess?
(Will he get it right this time?)
Yu Jae Seok.
(Correct)
Is it right?
(He feels disgusted.)
- Was it you? - Hey.
Why did you feel my face with your tongue?
- It was... - I thought it was food.
The second item will be ready soon.
- Broccoli. - Correct.
(Kwang Soo wins the second round.)
Here we go.
(What's the last item?)
(Watch how they react.)
- This is too... - This is too much.
- It's alive, I swear. - Did you hear how Ji Hyo reacted?
(What are you?)
This is too...
(Abalone)
(It's too alive.)
(Here comes fresh abalone.)
- Is it here? - Yes.
It's cold.
(Why is it moist?)
Don't get too close too fast.
You'll hurt your face.
(Gosh)
I can't tell if it's your tongue or the item.
I didn't stick out my tongue.
- Don't stick out your tongue. - I didn't.
Hey, you sucked my eye earlier.
- I didn't suck it. - I did?
- Hey. - That's not true.
Your tongue touched my eyes.
There was some hair.
(They try again.)
Change the direction a little.
What?
(Biting)
(It's love beyond race again.)
What's this?
Look at him.
Kwang Soo.
(Biting)
- Stop it. - Is he eating it?
(Stop eating it.)
(I haven't had enough.)
(I need to take a big bite.)
Is he eating it?
(Licking)
(He's tasting Haha.)
Stop licking.
I know the answer.
(Did he figure it out?)
- Abalone. - Correct.
(Correct)
(Kwang Soo beats Haha 2 to 1.)
Gosh.
(We thank Kwang Soo's tongue, the abalone, and Jae Seok.)
- Gosh. - You're disgusting.
(Kwang Soo has 3 Superpower Exchange Cards now.)
- It's time for the last game. - Let's go.
- Is it between Jong Kook and me? - They're the only ones left.
- It'll be only one round. - What is it?
Face each other...
and take turns putting clothespins on each other's faces.
The one who screams first loses.
Decide who will go first by rock, paper, scissors.
This is Jae Seok's hobby.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
The winner goes first.
- I'll bet one. - I'll do the same.
No. I'll bet two.
You're determined to win.
Someone might have broken my record by now,
I have a Guinness World Record...
for putting 28 clothespins on my face.
You could scream then.
Yes, I was screaming.
Eyelids will hurt.
Start.
(Where will Jong Kook's first clothespin end up?)
- Do I go first? - Yes.
- Look at him. - Are you starting there?
- He's... - From the beginning?
(There?)
(Jong Kook is confident.)
(It's on his eyelid.)
He's standing it.
- Jae Seok. - He's thinking.
Don't think too much.
Don't hesitate.
(Coughing)
What's the point?
The nest one will go to your right eyelid.
(Jong Kook is nervous.)
Can you really stand it?
How much does it hurt?
(Jae Seok attacks this time.)
- I don't think that will hurt. - Oh, my.
(He's not good at attacking.)
All right.
Please.
- He's a devil. - This is too much.
How could he start from there?
Oh, my.
It's barely hanging there.
- Just give up. - Please.
(Someone's squeezing my eyes.)
My stomach hurts.
He looks like a cartoon character.
(He's dancing to "TT".)
They look like tears.
Just scream and get it over with.
(It's too much.)
They're dangling.
Can you see anything?
I can't see anything.
(Gosh, I can't see anything.)
(She's cracking up.)
Take revenge.
(Here I go.)
That won't hurt. You should get back at him.
That should hurt.
(He's so bad at attacking.)
- It's over now. - Are you sure?
(Where will the next clothespin go?)
There again?
(It's the eyelid again.)
Oh, my. That's not okay.
(It's a new year, but I can't see anything.)
(Soon, a kid will be hanging from his eyelid.)
That's not okay.
Drink some water.
Drink water.
Gosh.
(Jae Seok gives up.)
Take them off.
(Screaming)
(Jong Kook now has four Superpower Exchange Cards.)
You can exchange the Superpower Exchange Cards you have now...
with supernatural powers.
In the armory are three different kinds of boxes.
What you can have is determined by the number of your cards.
Each box has a different supernatural power.
You'll choose one randomly...
and use it in the final round.
(Jae Seok goes in first.)
I only have three.
(Jae Seok has three Superpower Exchange Cards.)
(He needs to make a rational decision.)
(Should I get one of each?)
I'll choose a gold box.
(Gold boxes are the strongest. What will he get?)
It's a Death Note Card.
(Death Note Card)
I guess 1 gold box will be better than 1 silver and 1 bronze.
(Ji Hyo chooses a gold box as well.)
(What is the additional superpower Ji Hyo has picked?)
You can choose one.
(Seok Jin has only one Superpower Exchange Card.)
(He has obtained this superpower with the bronze box.)
It's GPS Card.
(GPS Card reveals the location of a member via walkie-talkie.)
(Haha has only one Superpower Exchange Card.)
This is nice.
(He has obtained Blinding Card.)
I have three cards.
(He owns 3 Superpower Exchange Cards.)
I have to use them all here, right?
(Avatar Kwang Soo chooses the gold box.)
(What is the extra superpower that surprised Avatar Kwang Soo?)
(Exchanging superpowers is over. Who will win this Ultimate Battle?)
The final war of the Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals will start.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Agent Jae Seok's ability is level 3 and he uses a big water gun.)
(Black Widow Ji Hyo's level of superpower is 1.)
(She can pause a member for 1 minute and run away.)
Does this look weirder without it?
(Avatar Kwang Soo's level of superpower is 2.)
(Thor Jong Kook's superpower level is 1.)
(He can double the size of a name tag.)
I will disappear in front of you.
(Detective Seok Jin's superpower level is 2.)
(Time Controller Haha's superpower level is 1.)
(He can rewind 10 seconds.)
(The final war starts.)
In the final war of the Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals,
the last member, who survives after everyone is eliminated, will win.
But if this week's participant wins, the prize will be doubled.
The rest of you will face a punishment.
I have to eliminate the participant for this week's episode.
In addition, a special room has been prepared.
You can either strengthen...
or lose your superpower in this room.
(Finding Reinforcement Room, which will appear randomly, is crucial.)
It's like a secret room.
(It's more crucial for supernaturals with lower levels.)
I should find the Reinforcement Room and improve my power.
(Haha is also wandering around to look for the Reinforcement Room.)
Will it be here?
I have to find that room,
but I may lose my power.
(Agent Jae Seok walks quietly.)
(People are talking.)
(Shall I start wetting them with my water gun?)
The rest of the members don't have to...
(Jae Seok targets Seok Jin who is usually clueless.)
(Approaching)
You startled me. Hey!
You can't start shooting now.
You won't shoot me, right?
What's your superpower?
- My superpower? - Yes.
- I shouldn't tell you that, right? - No, you shouldn't.
Then why do you ask?
- Why were you about to answer? - Well...
- You're not the participant, right? - No, I am not.
- It's not my week. - It's not.
I think it's Kwang Soo's.
- Symbol of power. - There's Haha.
(Haha appears.)
Cross!
- Power. - Speed.
- Cross! - Cross!
(He retreats instinctively.)
I shouldn't provoke them first.
(It's better to avoid members who play dirty.)
My goodness.
If I shoot, it will be the end of me.
I'm certain there will be someone who controls time.
I can't use it until then.
What should I do?
(Agent Jae Seok is contemplating.)
(At the same time,)
(Avatar Kwang Soo is still looking for Reinforcement Room.)
(I have to strengthen my power quickly.)
(He spots Thor Jong Kook from a distance.)
- Hey. Kwang Soo. - Yes, Jong Kook?
- Kwang Soo. - Come here, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
It's Jong Kook. It's him.
(Alert for Thor Jong Kook is issued.)
Let's stop the participant from winning first.
Who do you think came up with this theme?
- Jae Seok. - It's Jae Seok.
- I think so, too. - Didn't I predict accurately?
- Jae Seok thinks it's Kwang Soo. - No, it's not him.
Compared to our missions, his mission was too easy.
(He strolled around Sangam-dong, butting in their missions.)
(After eliminating everyone, he put his superpower in the 3rd level.)
(His mission did seem noticeably easy.)
I predict it's Jae Seok's week. I am not certain, though.
(At the same time, he's filming a spy movie all by himself.)
Before he is eliminated,
we shouldn't be separated.
- We have to avoid the punishment. - Let's not leave each other.
- I agree. - I heard it's terrible.
Haha, why are you doing that?
(Talking)
(He stops.)
(Turning back)
I can't shoot when they're all together.
(I should be extra careful today.)
That will be the end of me.
What I hate the most is...
I have to compete against you with just my superpower.
Can you stop this?
Give it back.
This is the best part of it. This is what's keeping me happy.
We are talking about something important.
(This is my hammer.)
That's bothering me.
(Hammering)
It doesn't do anything. It's really nothing.
Stop it.
It's the only fun part about this.
- It does something, right? - All right.
It doesn't do anything.
- I will break this. - I swear. It doesn't do anything.
- Let's find the room, Ji Hyo. - Let's find that first.
- Okay. Let's do that. - Let's find the Reinforcement Room.
(He's being careful.)
(I think they are coming this way.)
(Seok Jin spots Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok.
- It's your week, right? - What?
It's not my week.
You are in danger.
I will tell you something as your old friend.
I heard you encourage others to eliminate me first.
(I know I am in danger.)
I didn't say that.
You said it right there.
Stop lying.
I heard it. That's why I was leaving.
- Did you hear it? - Yes.
(He talked with Jong Kook minutes ago.)
- I had my week. - It's not me as well. Shouldn't...
Shouldn't we eliminate Jae Seok first?
(Listening)
Seok Jin just said I should be eliminated first.
- When did you hear it? - You said I must be removed first.
You said that to Jong Kook.
You are so funny.
- You were listening? - Yes.
I don't know if you believe me, but it's not me.
(To communicate with the room, he wanders around.)
(There's an object that looks like a room.)
(No one's here, right?)
(Avatar Kwang Soo finds Reinforcement Room.)
(If he's successful, he can upgrade his 2nd level to the 3rd level.)
(However, if he fails, he will lose the superpower he has now.)
(Should I do it or not?)
(Haha gets close to the Reinforcement Room.)
(Here comes Haha.)
- Did you succeed? - Yes, I did.
(How brazen.)
- Don't lie. - I'm not lying.
- You are not? - I am not.
- Did you upgrade your power? - Yes.
- Is it closed? - It's not closed.
Come on.
(I knew it.)
- Why do you lie? - You know I was here first.
- I came in first. - What is wrong with you?
- I was here first. - You...
If you fail, let me try.
I found it first.
- Then why don't you try it? - Let me make a call first.
What is he doing? He's not doing it.
- Yes, Kwang Soo. - Ji Hyo.
- What? - Where are you?
I am in the main building.
I found the Reinforcement Room. Do you want to come?
Why would you want me there?
- What? - What are you doing?
Don't come, Ji Hyo.
You must come.
Why would I go there? Where are you?
Ji Hyo, you can strengthen your superpower.
(I'm wondering if I can take your superpower.)
(Kwang Soo acquired the ability to control Ji Hyo's superpower.)
(Ji Hyo's superpower is Kwang Soo's superpower.)
Where are you?
Come to the annex on the fourth floor.
- If he fails... - Okay.
(Ji Hyo, you will come to see me, right?)
(You will also successfully improve your superpower, right?)
- What? - It's there.
What is it?
It's the Reinforcement Room. I didn't use it yet.
You can strengthen your power.
(Why is he being so helpful today?)
(It looks suspicious, but can't you just reinforce your power?)
You should use it.
- What? - You should use this room.
It's pointless for me.
Why is it pointless for you?
- My level of superpower is three. - What?
- My power is in the 3rd level. - Really?
I'm fine without it.
(But I am not fine with that.)
I don't think so.
Why?
Can I try?
- You can try. - No, you can't.
He said I can't.
Why are they clustered there?
What is it?
You startled me.
- It's the room. - Something's fishy about him.
He keeps telling me to go in, but Seok Jin can't.
If one of you wants to come in...
(Shall I give you a massage with my hammer?)
- Why are you guarding it? - That's exactly my point.
- He's acting strangely. - I didn't...
- It's just... - Shall I get rid of his name tag?
Let's do it so that we can be comfortable.
Do I make you uncomfortable?
I mean...
How can you say such things? You're making me sad.
Look at my clothes.
- I will remove your name tag. - Jong Kook.
- All you want is for me to go in? - You can go in...
and it might be better if you can strengthen your superpower.
(You are falling for my trap.)
But why does it have to be her?
- You don't make sense. - Maybe he can exchange...
- his power with yours. - It's doesn't add up.
- I can't understand this. - This is good for you, Ji Hyo.
It's good for you. So stop talking and go in already.
- I'll just go in. - Fine. I will go in first.
Okay. I will go in.
Ji Hyo. Practice. Practice before you try it.
Practice. Adjust your power when you spin it.
This is so funny.
Practice until you get the hang of it.
I'll start.
You know what to do with this. You turn it.
(If she fails, Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo both lose their superpowers.)
(Will it be an upgrade or a co-destruction?)
(Black Widow Ji Hyo fails.)
(I failed. What should I do?)
Don't even think about it.
Come here. What happened?
I lost everything because of you.
(Are you serious?)
- Ji Hyo. - You lost everything?
- Ji Hyo. - Did you lose everything too?
- You scumbag. - Let's just...
Did you say scumbag?
You scumbag. It's because of you...
that I lost everything.
What are you talking about.
You shouldn't only think about yourself.
(The unluckiness is infectious.)
(Jae Seok hears some noise.)
They are still there.
(In that case...)
(Crouching)
Hide.
(He lowers his body and tells the cameraman to stay behind.)
(Now that everything is in place, he is ready.)
(Pressing)
(He leaves the cameraman and takes the elevator alone.)
(Where are you going without me?)
(Cameraman Kwon Ryeol and the staff are retreating for the moment.)
- Let's go for now. - We can't even start.
It's relaxing to be with people that don't want your name tag.
Sure.
- Where should we go next? - That way?
Let's go down the stairs.
I think there's someone here.
(Aren't you Kwon Ryeol?)
- Jae Seok is here somewhere... - Where?
because Kwon Ryeol is here.
(I'm sorry, Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok is here.
He's here.
(Passing by)
(Where are you going so suspiciously?)
- Hey. - What?
(He is keeping quiet while pressing the close button.)
- Hey. - Why?
He's here? He's here.
(Jae Seok, why won't you open the door?)
(She presses the button.)
(I should move downstairs to be safe.)
- So he went down. - He went down.
- He went down. - He went with Kwon Ryeol.
Kwon Ryeol was here.
He went down with Kwon Ryeol.
He's here. Come here, Haha.
- Have you seen Jae Seok? - I followed him up the stairs.
He went downstairs on the elevator.
Without the cameraman?
Is Kwon Ryeol following him?
- Let's go. - Let's follow Kwon Ryeol.
Let's run!
- I have to do something. - Be quick.
- Kwang Soo. - Let's have a talk.
(Where there is Kwon Ryeol, there is Agent Jae Seok.)
Is this the third floor?
(Jae Seok arrives downstairs without knowing anything.)
(Sorry, Kwon Ryeol. I'm here.)
(I see you, Agent Jae Seok.)
Is this the third floor?
(This is one hectic, wild goose chase!)
(He's running away while trying to take Kwon Ryeol with him.)
(Is this the end?)
Hey. Hey.
(The Kwon Ryeol followers have arrived.)
Listen to me.
It's not me. It's really not me.
- It's you or Haha. - Kwang Soo.
It's you or Haha.
- What's this water gun? - It's not me.
This isn't anything. Someone's setting me up.
In my perspective, it's either you or Haha.
Think carefully.
If I made this up,
I would choose a smaller one.
I'm spilling water everywhere.
Look at this. I wouldn't have chosen this one.
I'm not that dumb.
- Seok Jin is out. - What?
(Why is he out all of a sudden?)
We were all here.
Out?
(What is this?)
(Few minutes ago, when everyone was focused on chasing Jae Seok,)
(Detective Seok Jin quietly left the group.)
You'll be out now.
(His level 2 power is pretending to be out. One false alarm is allowed.)
I'll disappear in front of your eyes.
(He used his superpower.)
No one has done it. He just outed himself.
He's Sherlock. He's trying to do something while faking his death.
(That's right.)
Anyway, it's not me.
Kwon Ryeol, why are you pretending to be on their side?
- You have to be where I am. - I'm sorry.
We're not here for this.
I told you. I'm not that person.
(He escapes amidst suspicion.)
Is it you?
(Staring)
You know that Jong Kook is staring at you, right?
Yes, but I don't know why.
(Chuckling)
He's staring at you.
I mean...
I don't know if he's giving me a sign or if he's suspicious of me.
He is suspicious of you.
Really?
It's pretty obvious.
I think he knows something.
Kwang Soo.
(Do you want to know what he knows?)
What is this?
You should do something, right?
Is it me? Wait.
- You can turn back the time. - Not now.
- You'll turn it anyway. - Not now.
- You'll turn it anyway. - Not now. Wait.
- What is this. - You should do something.
Wait. Is it me?
(Agent Jae Seok begins his mission.)
- Why me? - Someone has to...
- Someone has to give himself in. - Wait.
Wait.
You can do it after you're out.
(His target is Thor Jong Kook.)
- Okay. - Why me?
(Thor Jong Kook doesn't have his guard up at the moment.)
(Agent Jae Seok's gun is fully loaded.)
(He commences.)
(Can Jong Kook be outed first for the first time in history?)
Wait. The time controller!
The time controller!
I'm not supposed to use it like this.
(Agent Jae Seok has succeeded.)
(Thor Jong Kook is out.)
He called the time controller.
You shot me after that.
We'll go back to 10 seconds ago.
- What is this? - Oh boy.
Okay, I got it. You're a dead man now.
This can't be happening.
This was the perfect timing.
- You're a dead man now. - Goodness, I'm dead.
The time controller!
(Time Controller Haha turns time back to 10 seconds ago.)
You can't do this to me.
What did I do to you?
Five, four,
- We'll talk later. - three,
- It's over. - two, one.
- Start. - Run!
(They are closing up to the likely suspect, Jae Seok.)
(It's a door! He heads straight to the emergency exit.)
What is this?
(Thor Jong Kook aims for the target.)
(He rips Jae Seok's name tag.)
(However, the main character tag that everyone expected isn't there.)
We were wrong.
(The main character wasn't Agent Jae Seok.)
Does he have another power?
(I said it wasn't me.)
(Jae Seok is out.)
(Jae Seok wasn't the main character. They're in an emergency meeting.)
It looks pitiful.
(History will remember the good hero under false accusations.)
It looks like blood, too.
(Meanwhile, if Jae Seok isn't the main character,)
(it's one of these two.)
Let's not count the people who have already done Member's Week.
All right. We're safe.
(They're talking out loud on purpose, right?)
Should we scatter first?
Okay. Let's do that first.
(To isolate the suspects, they part ways.)
They will plan something if they are together.
We should take all the name tags.
Let us live.
So it's you.
If it isn't Jae Seok, it's you.
Tell me the truth.
- I'd tell you if it were the truth. - The viewers are watching...
- and blaming you. - It's not me.
You know, right?
- It's not me. - You know, right?
If we add up all the times that...
I was betrayed by him, I am nothing compared to him.
Let's take Haha first...
and then Kwang Soo.
You are really good at acting.
You are doing all the acting you should be doing in dramas.
What did you say?
Don't squeeze too hard. I know you are feeling guilty.
You need me if you want to take Jong Kook's name tag.
Trust me.
- What did you say? - Why is he still here?
You told me we'd cooperate, Haha.
Let's take Kwang Soo's name tag.
I'm telling you. It isn't me.
I'm not the one. I swear.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
It isn't me. I promise you.
It isn't me.
(This is a dilemma.)
Isn't it like this?
What is that?
- What is that? - They're clones.
(Clones?)
(All of a sudden, there are unidentified men in the hall.)
(Who are they?)
Hold on!
Wait.
(The unidentified men pounce on Kwang Soo.)
(Who summoned the clones?)
Come here. It's not time yet.
What?
Gary?
(It's Gary?)
- It's not time yet. Come here. - It's Gary?
- It's Gary? - Isn't it his voice?
- Yes. - Wasn't it Gary?
(They all panic.)
- What? What's going on? - What's going on?
(What did I just see?)
That was Gary's voice.
This is Gary's week.
(Avatar Kwang Soo is pale because he's in shock.)
For real?
(He doesn't understand what's going on.)
(The four clones appeared out of nowhere.)
(There could only be one person behind it.)
(It's Gary, the 1st and 2nd winner of Battle of Supernaturals.)
(What happened?)
(Two hours before filming)
(One man awaits for the beginning of Battle of Supernaturals.)
The invitation came in a rush...
but thank you for having me here.
(Gary is the fourth participant of the Member's Week.)
(He's the man of the Battle of Supernaturals.)
(Your abilities are useless in the face of his clones.)
(There's no Battle of Supernaturals without him.)
We called you in a hurry to invite you.
Thank you.
It's been a while since I've met them...
but I'll never...
go easy...
or be soft-hearted.
I will be...
the winner.
(He plays a game to earn his superpower.)
(He earns 4 clones which is the 3rd level of superpower.)
(Gary is the man of Battle of Supernaturals.)
(He transforms into Ga Wukong.)
(30 minutes before start of the race)
They're going to try to eliminate me for certain.
Jong Kook will hold on to two of you.
Let me go in the middle.
(Gary is back.)
Haha, you wanted to work together.
(They were being suspicious over whose special this was.)
(Here comes Ga Wukong.)
Should I eliminate Seok Jin?
- Who's that? - Go after Kwang Soo.
Hold on.
(The surprise attack shocked everybody.)
Who is it?
Let go.
Come back. It's not time yet.
(His first target has gone pale.)
That's enough.
You just have to scare them.
It's Gary. That was his voice.
(They didn't expect to see Gary.)
(That was Gary for certain.)
(The real battle starts now.)
- I'm getting goosebumps. - I was shocked.
- That was Gary. - Are they all dead, then?
They're all dead.
(That was totally unexpected.)
His clones are too strong. He has the best superpower.
- That's right. - I thought...
he quit.
Why does he keep coming back?
We start forgetting about him and he comes back.
How does that work for us?
(We said our farewells and wished each other the best.)
We try to move on but he comes back every time.
Ji Hyo has to cry again today.
I'm sick of this.
Tell him to just show himself.
We should bring all the Avengers together.
Jae Seok and...
Time Controller Haha.
Thor Jong Kook.
The big, blue...
(He's a blue man in vacation clothing.)
- I have no power. - Black Widow Ji Hyo.
We'll protect the Earth.
We will.
(We are here to protect the Earth.)
(Rummaging)
Time Controller.
Blue long hair.
(We'll protect the Earth by ourselves.)
I don't know how else to introduce myself.
Pervert.
(Call the police to report indecent behaviors.)
(I want to be something cool.)
First person should be Haha...
or Jong Kook.
I can eliminate Gary.
- You can? - Yes. Should I?
- Yes. - Now?
- Can you just do it? - Yes.
- Are you going to use it? - I have my superpower.
(A few hours earlier at the Superpower Exchange Card Room)
"Stick any member's name tag on yourself to eliminate them."
(Jong Kook earned an extra name tag.)
(He just needs a copy of Gary's name tag.)
(Should I do it?)
Keep going forward.
(What are those four planning?)
Somebody's coming.
- Somebody's coming. - What's the announcement?
Jong Kook is out.
- Jong Kook, you've been eliminated. - What?
Why?
(Grinning)
(Whose special do you think this is?)
(He was sure it was Jae Seok.)
(Throughout the race, Jong Kook was questioning Jae Seok.)
(I'm in trouble.)
I might...
get eliminated with no chance.
(Jong Kook is Jae Seok's biggest obstacle.)
Okay. Give it to me.
Give me the Death Note Card.
- Would you like to use it? - Yes.
I'll write his name down just to be safe.
(He wrote Jong Kook's name down so that he can't eliminate him.)
(If I get eliminated, Jong Kook will also be out 10 minutes later.)
(He got no chance to negotiate.)
(Fine. Let's die together.)
(Jae Seok got eliminated without doing anything.)
(10 minutes has passed.)
Jong Kook is out.
(Jong Kook is out.)
I've thought it over but I have no choice.
If I get eliminated,
you're out as well.
I'm sorry.
(Thor Jong Kook is eliminated because of Jae Seok.)
I have such a good superpower.
(He's mad.)
(Did you think I'll let it go?)
- This is too funny. - You should have kept him alive.
- Why? - Jae Seok.
There's Gary.
- What? - It's Gary's special.
- What? - Gary's here.
- Gary's here? - He's here with his clones.
It's Gary's special.
- I told you it wasn't me. - It's your fault.
It's not me, you fool.
I was trying to bring you back alive.
Forward.
Stop.
- What's that? - Hurry.
(Without Jong Kook,)
(Gary has nothing to be scared of.)
It's Gary. His clones are with him.
Get Haha. Haha.
Let's get far away.
He's coming.
(Just run.)
Get Haha.
(Dashing)
You guys are too fast.
These clones have upgraded.
What if I die, guys?
What's going on?
(Black Widow Ji Hyo sprints away.)
(Gasping)
This is insane.
Is Haha not here?
He went downstairs?
(Gary and his clones are closing in.)
Gary... That was unexpected.
That was totally unexpected.
(Gary is the real champion of the Battle of Supernaturals.)
(Would he remain as the ultimate winner?)
(The members are scattered everywhere.)
(Frightened)
Fetch Haha. It's Haha.
(The clones are faster and more powerful than before.)
It's me? Hold on.
Gary. Hey.
(We'll deliver you to him without hurting you.)
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
(He waits for an opportunity to attack.)
Hey, let's change plans.
Gary.
(It's a surprise attack.)
(Bye, Haha.)
Blinding Card.
(Blinding Card)
(Gary is blinded for 1 minute.)
What's this?
(He runs away.)
Is he gone?
(The camera has been filming his back all day.)
How does this work?
What I'm hoping is that Haha...
(They discuss how they'll be revived.)
- He can turn back time. - That's one possible way.
If we get revived,
I'll kill Gary right away.
- That's a good plan. - I'll do it right away.
We have to avoid the penalty.
There might be something else.
If Gary wins, we'll all be penalized.
Do you have no superpower at all?
I have none.
Haha. Kwang Soo.
Be quiet.
- If we don't work together, - Right.
- Gary will win. - Right.
He has his clones so there's nothing we can do.
And Gary is still affectionate about you...
so can you eliminate him?
That's not the problem. He has his clones so I can't even get close.
They'll grab me.
Why do his clones follow him all the time?
Come with me and grab on to the clones.
Okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
(Am I supposed to come, too?)
(Gary and Ji Hyo haven't met for a while on Mondays.)
- Since when have you been here? - Are you with them?
Ji Hyo.
Hold both of his hands.
I can't eliminate her.
(He gets soft-hearted.)
- Let's shake hands at least. - Sure.
- It's great to see you. - You, too.
(They're happy to see each other.)
- Aren't they happy to see me? - Come on, Gary.
Don't plot something against me.
- Of course not. - Don't say that.
Are you going to turn back the time?
Turn back to when?
To seven years ago.
(Please turn the time to 7 years ago.)
Let's go back to July, seven years ago.
It's good to see you.
- Are you the main member today? - Give me a high five.
Are you the main member of this week?
- I love you, Gary. - Me?
I'm not sure about that.
If you aren't, it's one of these two.
(Does Ji Hyo trust Gary and suspect these two?)
(Gary summons Haha.)
(He orders his clones to capture Haha.)
- I summon Haha. - Wait.
(Kwang Soo runs away.)
Wait a minute. Kwang Soo.
(Ji Hyo starts to attack.)
- Don't push me. - Hurry up, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, please. - There you go.
Haha is out.
(Time Controller Haha is eliminated.)
(Kwang Soo has the superpower to betray.)
Haha, who eliminated you?
Gary and the clones.
Why didn't you eliminate Gary?
- It wasn't possible. - Actually, I'm not out yet.
(Seok Jin is still alive.)
(His superpower was to pretend as if he's eliminated.)
(He's happy to disappear.)
(Detective Seok Jin pretended to be out and waited for his chance.)
Actually, I'm not out yet.
- Seriously? - Yes.
- Gary doesn't know. - What's going on over there?
- Is Ji Hyo eliminated? - Eliminate Gary.
Just go.
Okay, I'll go and improvise.
(Everyone's hope, Detective Seok Jin, is back.)
(He's surprised.)
Kwang Soo, I'll tell you the truth.
I seem eliminated, right?
- Everyone forgot about you. - I know.
As soon as he sees me, he'll wonder.
We should team up.
- Gary is too strong. - Isn't he?
Let's go to Ji Hyo.
Gary is coming.
Get Kwang Soo.
Hurry, we must catch him this time.
Gary is coming.
We must catch him.
(They run after Kwang Soo.)
(Seok Jin hides behind the door to chase after Gary.)
(He's after Gary.)
(Gary doesn't notice Seok Jin.)
(What?)
Hey.
(They stop.)
Clones, hurry and catch him!
Stop it.
(Tearing)
No way.
He startled me.
Seok Jin is out.
You surprised me.
This is what I heard when I turned.
(It's the sound of Seok Jin running.)
It's the sound of your footsteps.
- It's obvious. - It could have been amazing.
(Detective Seok Jin tried his best.)
I was so close.
I definitely heard that you were eliminated.
- Seok Jin is really eliminated. - Is it real this time?
Clones! Clones!
He held my arms!
Gary is out.
I'm out?
Am I eliminated?
(How did he get eliminated?)
(This is what happened during the superpower exchange.)
Death Note Card?
(Ji Hyo obtained the Death Note Card like Agent Jae Seok.)
(She wrote on it beforehand to defend herself.)
(Whoever holds both of her arms will be eliminated.)
(Gary was happy after eliminating Seok Jin.)
- Gary. - Seok Jin.
You startled me.
(Black Widow Ji Hyo hid behind and waited for her chance.)
(It was when Gary was relieved.)
(She gave both of her arms while pretending to attack him.)
(He's flustered.)
(Gary holds both of her arms.)
The person to hold both of my arms is eliminated.
Am I really eliminated?
Right?
(Today's main member, Gary, is eliminated.)
(The other members are exempted from punishment.)
Ji Hyo.
You must win.
Kwang Soo still remains.
I can't help you.
I completely failed.
(He fails.)
I couldn't defeat Ji Hyo.
(It's too difficult to defeat Ji Hyo.)
What do I do?
(It's a match between Avatar Kwang Soo and Black Widow Ji Hyo.)
I can't eliminate him because he's too strong.
(He's too strong to defeat. Is the strategy the only answer?)
(Tall and blue Kwang Soo appears.)
There he is.
(She hides to attack him from behind.)
(Kwang Soo is within her radar.)
Go away. Don't film me.
(He stops filming.)
(Avatar Kwang Soo slowly approaches Ji Hyo.)
(She's fully alert.)
(Ji Hyo is only 10m away from Kwang Soo.)
(She runs up quickly.)
(She approaches him.)
(Black Widow Ji Hyo silently follows Kwang Soo from behind.)
(She just needs to remove his name tag.)
(Now is the time.)
(Tearing)
(She takes off his name tag.)
(She stops.)
I knew you would do that.
(Ji Hyo isn't happy, and Kwang Soo is smiling.)
(Something is written under Kwang Soo's name tag.)
(He has a Reflecting Card.)
(Kwang Soo chose a gold box.)
(Luckily, he got a Reflecting Card.)
I'm blue with long hair.
(He relieves everyone by acting foolishly.)
Only you and Ji Hyo remain.
(That means...)
(it's time to use the hidden card.)
(While Ji Hyo is hiding, Kwang Soo spots her.)
(He smiles a little.)
(He turns back and exposes his name tag.)
(Black Widow Ji Hyo falls for Kwang Soo's acting.)
(Goodbye, Ji Hyo.)
(He shouts joyfully.)
With his Reflecting Card, Ji Hyo is out.
(Black Widow Ji Hyo is out.)
Why did I even believe you?
(She's completely fooled.)
(He unbuttons himself.)
(He shows off his blue muscles.)
(The winner of Ultimate Battle of Supernaturals is Avatar Kwang Soo.)
He let her rip his name tag on purpose.
I didn't expect Gary to appear.
I had no idea, either.
I follow Gary on social media.
- He's been in China. - Right.
- I posted more photos on purpose... - Really?
after receiving the invitation.
- He was in China. - I was surprised.
- My appearance was perfect. - You stayed in China for long.
How you showed up was perfect.
- I was so surprised. - I had no idea.
I was very surprised.
Why don't you come back?
- Just come back. - Come on, Gary.
- I'll return once in a while... - You should.
after I travel abroad.
Today's winner is Avatar Kwang Soo.
(Avatar Kwang Soo wins.)
That was impressive.
- The trophy looks better. - It's all gold.
We're together again after a long time.
We're together again.
I still have the pen at my studio.
(The members can't let go of Gary, and he can't leave.)
Gary joined us for Lunar New Year.
It was a pleasant surprise.
The Running Man family is together.
I'm happy that all seven of us can wish Happy New Year to the viewers.
- Everyone, Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
(We'll work hard again this year. Everyone, Happy New Year.)
This is Running Man, Member's Week.
(It's the 5th main member.)
(Haha)
Haha!
It's because I trust you.
(Haha can't decide while the members are at risk.)
I'm about to lose my mind.
Haha, please save me.
(The members' fates depend on Haha.)
(It's the moment of decision. Haha must choose only one.)
(Whom will he choose to save?)
(The Fifth Member's Week, Haha's Choice)