(This is Running Man's global project of 2017.)
(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by bloggers)
(Shark cage, USA)
(Cage of Death, Australia)
(Fly Toledo, Spain)
(Active volcano in Mount Bromo and Mount Ijen, Indonesia)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan)
(Nevis Swing, New Zealand)
(Insano water slide, Brazil)
(Three Tour Stickers will earn them a trip to the tourist attraction.)
(Starting with Se Chan and Haha,)
(a cutthroat war of Tour Stickers breaks out.)
(In the midst of this brutal war, Se Chan takes the lead.)
- Se Chan will get the Tour Sticker. - Se Chan, you are in the lead.
(Part 3 of the global race continues.)
(It is Running Marble with Hyorin.)
(The team that obtains two of the same colored areas wins,)
(and the member with the least amount of money gets the sticker.)
(Who will receive the Tour Sticker today?)
(Team So Min will try the mission for Thailand.)
- By the way, So Min. - Yes?
Did you mean any of it or were you just saying it?
For example, before you threw the dice,
you said you could throw the number you want just by saying it.
(A while ago when she rolled the die for the first time...)
- She said she has a special power. - What is it?
If she picks a number,
- she can get that number. - Then So Min,
- why don't you pick a number? - Choose one.
- I will pick number 5. - Number 5?
- She called it out. - She really said it.
(The result was...)
(4, not 5.)
(Gosh, that was so close.)
I meant it.
- You did? - Yes.
- You really must be crazy. - No.
(He respects the crazy girl.)
Look. 5 and 4 were very close.
If I could've put more energy into it, I could've gotten it.
(She really believes in her power.)
- I have a special power too. - What is it?
- Everyone has their own power. - Okay.
We are the only ones who are aware of this.
I can turn back time.
(Haha the Time Traveler)
I have a death note.
You are talking rubbish. I have one too.
(You have it too?)
- What? - I have one at home.
- Do you really have one? - I really do have it.
- Mine really exists. - Really? Please tell us more.
There are a lot. I used to write on that notebook since primary school.
- Are you serious? - How do you write on that notebook?
- You've been writing for 20 years? - Yes.
I write down the name, date of birth, and blood type.
I also write down when and what happened.
(He gets goosebumps.)
I am serious.
(She is truly crazy.)
- Of course. - Three.
We need 5 or 6. We don't need anything else.
- Where? What do you want? - I want...
- to go to the Philippines. - How about you?
I want Greece. I want to go there quickly.
Let's aim for Greece and Sweden. All right.
Greece! Here we go.
(Their target is either Greece or Sweden.)
Please be 5 or 6. Be 5 or 6.
(The result is...)
- It's 5! - It's 5!
(They get Greece.)
- Jae Seok! - We are off to a good start.
- We will go to Greece. - It's Greece.
Please give us the board.
- What are some Greek dishes? - Hey, there's one with olive oil...
- What about Greek yogurt? - Right, Greek yogurt.
- We can search them online. - Let's search and go.
- Jae Seok, there's one in Hongdae. - What is it?
There's a Greek and Turkish restaurant at Hapjeong Station.
But people don't usually look up Greek dishes and try them.
Now that I think of it, I've never had Greek food before.
"Moussaka".
- What is moussaka? - What is that?
It's a Greek eggplant dish with ground beef...
- in bechamel sauce. - Eggplant?
(Hesitant)
- Eggplant? - Well... Eggplant?
- Eggplant... - It sounded unappealing with that.
- I was taken aback with that too. - I liked the ground beef part.
- And... - Are there other dishes?
- Tzatziki. - Tzatziki?
It's mixed with yogurt, cucumber, and garlic.
It's a traditional Greek dish.
- Cucumber and garlic? - It can be an appetizer or sauce.
- Cucumber and garlic? - There are a lot of dishes.
We can order three dishes from Athens.
Let's order a course meal.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
- Hi, this is all very sudden. - Yes, it is.
We happened to come to a Greek restaurant.
- Can we film while we eat? - Thank you.
- Sure. Have a meal too. - Thank you.
- We're here to taste Greek food. - You are?
Winning is important, but we should enjoy our meal.
- That's my point too. - Give me the menu. I'll order.
Is the water from Greece?
No way. Can it be from Athens?
You didn't bring this water from Athens?
- No, we didn't. - I see.
I thought this could be from there.
- Gosh, it's expensive. - Why? How much is it?
- "Lamb steak"... - Do you want to try moussaka?
Gosh, it's 14 dollars.
(The member with the least amount of money will get the Tour Sticker.)
- Sir. - What is souvlaki?
Souvlaki in Greek means "skewer".
I see. It means flower?
(Gosh, people from the Mediterranean country sure are romantic.)
- It means flower? - No, it means skewer.
- It's skewer. - Oh, it means "skewer".
- It's like a chicken skewer. - I thought it meant flower.
- Please give me one. - You'd like this one.
- Chicken souvlaki and spaghetti. - And this one too.
- All right. - Thank you.
But now, I'm curious to taste them.
We never had sea bream spaghetti.
I've never had it before.
If we need more, let's order some more.
Let's see first.
(Souvlaki is being grilled nicely.)
We will see.
(This Greek-style sea bream pasta has a unique flavor.)
- The food is here. - It's here.
- Gosh, they look so delicious. - This is amazing.
Here are your souvlaki and gyros.
- What is this? - This is the souvlaki.
Take the meat out from the skewer, dip it in the sauce,
- and eat it with the bread. - This is my first time trying this.
- First of all... - This is my first Greek dish.
- I should dip it in the sauce... - And the bread...
- and make a wrap with the bread. - Eat it with the bread.
- This smells good. - Jae Seok.
- Is it like yogurt? - It tastes similar to it.
(She takes a bite.)
The sauce tastes like yogurt.
Souvlaki tastes so good.
- What is this? - That's sea bream pasta.
- Gosh. - This looks great too.
- Is this sea bream? - Yes.
Are the pasta noodles made of squid ink?
- Don't you think? - Are they buckwheat noodles?
Do Greeks cook with buckwheat noodles?
(It looks similar.)
- At least I made sense. - Se Chan.
- Did I go too far? - You went too far.
This is a bit sour too.
(The pasta noodles are delicious.)
- This is a bit sour. - Doesn't it taste unique?
Excuse me. I think the pasta noodles are more slippery...
- than the noodles we usually eat. - The pasta noodles are slippery.
It's because we put in a lot of extra virgin olive oil.
I see. Extra... That oil is quite tasty.
It would have been more delicious for my taste if you put in more.
- More what? - Extra...
That oil is nice. I see. That's what he put in this dish.
No wonder it's slippery.
Se Chan.
(I don't know what it is, but I do know.)
- What? - Yang Se Chan.
I went too far.
(In an instant, they are done eating Greek food.)
- This was a nice meal. - It was delicious.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
- I'm glad. - We really enjoyed the food.
(Team Ji Hyo acquires Greece.)
- Hyorin, eat as much as you want. - Yes?
- Can I eat as much as I want? - Yes, eat.
Of course. Do you know what kind of a man is the easiest to pick up?
What kind?
- Why? - He's the easiest.
- Why? - I am kind of...
- I always say this. - He's really easy.
Say that I wasn't interested in this girl,
but if she says she's interested in me,
I become interested in her too.
(His heart easily pounds.)
- I'm sort of like that. - But that's everyone.
- No, men like to make a move first. - We are similar in that sense.
I don't like someone first.
- When someone likes you first... - Someone has to...
like me first for me to like him back.
That's how I figure out if someone likes me. If not,
- I don't pay attention to him. - They are so similar.
What do you want to drink?
- I heard Thai milk iced tea's good. - Okay.
- Isn't that expensive though? - But I want soda.
What do you want to eat? Choose one.
(Both Hyorin and Jong Kook get Coca Cola.)
How are they so similar?
Jong Kook really likes Coke.
I am getting Diet Coke.
- Are you getting plain Coke? - Really? Diet Coke...
contains more sugar.
I like the taste. Coke tastes too sweet.
- Isn't Diet Coke sweeter? - No, it isn't.
(He feels nervous.)
You have such similar tastes in food and other things...
that you look like you grew up in the same place.
Seriously. Are you from the same town?
I am from Anyang while she is from Incheon.
I know.
(It's fun mealtime among colleagues.)
It will be really hard for you...
to become a couple.
(They are good colleagues.)
(Team Hyorin acquires Thailand.)
We have to pay 20 dollars?
(Team So Min pays 20 dollars to pass through Thailand.)
Do we have to pay?
- Let's play rock, paper, scissors. - Let us.
We decide who pays 10, 7, or 3 dollars.
- Okay? - Sure.
- First place pays three dollars. - Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors.
- Yes! - This is insane.
What is going on with you today?
(Why is he so lucky today?)
Haha.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
(So Min will pay seven dollars.)
- 7 dollars. - Haha, 10 dollars.
It's a relief.
So Min wrote 50 cents.
How can you call yourself human?
(They betrayed each other from the start.)
Kwang Soo wrote...
- 50 cents. - For goodness' sake. Let's stop.
(Kwang Soo and So Min were like twins.)
Did you give me 50 cents?
(I should have realized back then.)
(Between these traitors...)
You are very thorough.
(I will only be a victim.)
- Haha, 10 dollars. - It's a relief.
I think you will go to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
(What will be the fate of Haha, the king of tricks?)
Wait a minute.
So Min has talent.
When she rolls the die or does other things,
what she shouts out loud comes true.
She is serious.
She told us that in the car.
- 1. - 1.
(So Min chooses 1.)
(Will she get one as she has predicted?)
What she shouts out loud comes true.
- We are desperate. - One.
One.
- I will count it on the floor. - Okay.
(She gets 6.)
Perhaps, she wasn't desperate enough.
She didn't say, "Challenge!"
- She didn't say, "Challenge!" - Say, "Challenge!"
Move out of the way.
(Don't go near the die.)
Should I go away?
- Switzerland. - Switzerland.
Hurry up and spin the wheel.
I will give it a go.
(What will be Team So Min's mission regarding Switzerland?)
(Please let it be something easy that involves eating food.)
(Please let it be something like eating Swiss dishes.)
- This is bad. - Buy a "Made in Switzerland".
(They need to buy a Swiss product.)
Buy a "Made in Switzerland".
This is bad. What should we get?
This is a disaster.
I have never seen anything that was made there.
Wait a minute. Gosh, I am so annoyed.
Who spun the wheel?
Please let me get one.
- Please let me get one. - Please.
Please give me one.
- Please give me 1. - 1.
(Team Ji Hyo will win if they occupy Sweden.)
(Will the spirit of die answer?)
- That's good. - We got a Golden Key.
(They advance two spaces and acquire a Golden Key.)
- It's not bad. - Golden Key.
Jae Seok, it's okay.
Pick one.
Pick the one that gives you a good feeling.
I picked one.
(They don't know what's written inside.)
Let's take a look.
All right. Please.
Lottery ticket will be nice.
- I'm feeling good. - Me too.
Swapping Card?
(Swapping Card?)
(Why does it have to be Swapping Card?)
Swapping Card?
"Swap countries."
(Swap countries with another team.)
You don't swap places. You only swap countries.
You only swap countries.
Countries?
Shall we swap Greece with Thailand?
That would be the best choice. We need to keep Japan.
We need to go quickly and get the country next to it.
Wouldn't you agree?
I agree.
Yes.
I should have picked a better one.
(The sinner lowers his head.)
You know,
I am aware that we have many unlucky members,
but this is too much.
I can't believe I got Swapping Card.
There were a lot of lottery tickets.
- Let's do this. - I will make the swap.
You will swap Greece with Thailand.
(Meanwhile, Team So Min is on the Switzerland mission.)
(Will there be anything at the convenience store?)
This is Belgium?
Czech Republic.
(This isn't it.)
Made in Switzerland?
(That one isn't it either.)
How can we find one?
Switzerland...
(Where are you?)
Hey, hey.
- What products do they have? - Hey, hey.
What is it?
- Switzerland. - Where?
My goodness.
This is unbelievable.
- It's from Switzerland. - It says Switzerland right here.
It's from Switzerland.
(It's a precious item that came from a faraway country.)
(Swiss candy is their savior.)
It's made in Switzerland.
(They complete the mission with a 2-dollar Swiss candy.)
Let's pray.
Roll the die and move to the next location.
This is interesting.
(To which destination will the dice guide them?)
Wait a minute.
(They get 1.)
- Germany. - We got one.
- We got 1. - 1.
(They move one space from Switzerland.)
(Team So Min will win if they occupy Germany.)
Let's get this country no matter what.
Let's get a food-related mission and eat German food.
Let's buy something that is made in Germany.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Please let it be an easy mission.)
Please. Please.
Let's get a food-related mission and eat German food.
Let's buy something that is made in Germany.
Please. Please.
(Which mission will they get on the wheel?)
(Meet a famous person related to the country.)
(How will they meet a famous person who is related to Germany?)
It's one mission we didn't want.
Seriously.
(Haha is acting strange.)
I don't know if this will work. Wait a minute.
- Whom should we meet? - Wait a minute.
- Whom should we meet? - Come here.
Germany...
It has to be someone famous, right?
- Yes. We must know them. - Someone who is related to Germany.
- All of us must know the person. - That's right.
That person doesn't have to be German.
- Someone who is related to Germany. - I will go...
- and do what we discussed earlier. - Okay.
Order something tasty.
He is leaving to cast the person.
- Go on. - We will part ways.
- I will get going. - Let's meet up later.
(What are they thinking?)
Where can we find him?
How will we find a German in the middle of Itaewon?
Seriously. It's not an easy country.
Hello.
(They hear a voice from behind.)
- Hello. - What brings you here?
Hello.
What brings you here?
My goodness.
- What brings you here? - Wait a minute.
- Are you Haha? - Yes, I am. Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- You know who he is, right? - Hello.
He is famous in Germany.
Good morning.
He was born in Germany.
- Type his name online. - He was born in Germany.
It says right there that I was born in Germany.
- You completed the mission. - Yes!
(Their plan worked.)
However...
(However...)
About three minutes ago,
Team Jae Seok claimed Switzerland as their own.
(They swapped their country with Switzerland.)
(It happened 3 minutes before they met the famous person.)
We got a Golden Key again. Roll the die again.
We got it again.
I can't believe...
we got another Golden Key.
We always get bad cards.
(What did they pick this time?)
Swapping Card.
That's good. Let's get Switzerland.
(They stopped Team So Min from winning.)
Pay 20 dollars for Germany.
- Then we will move... - We have to pay again.
to the next destination.
Let's pay.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors. If you play the same hand, you pay.
- If you don't, you are exempt. - Then you are exempt.
(The person who plays a different hand will be exempt.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
(What are you guys planning?)
- It's impossible to plan ahead. - Don't lie.
- It's impossible. - I saw you exchange looks.
- It's impossible to plan ahead. - I saw you exchange looks.
Think about it. It's impossible to plan ahead.
- I saw you exchange looks. - We must play different hands.
The one with a different hand wins.
I saw you exchange looks.
You fool, think about it. We can't come up with a plan.
- No. - How will we do that?
I can't believe you.
You are mistaken. I swear.
I saw you formulate a plan with your eyes.
It will be good for you if we play the same hand.
- She has issues. - I swear.
- I swear. - She needs treatment.
The one who plays a different hand will be exempt.
Is it even possible for us to win at this point?
That's not what's important.
- I don't care about the result. - This is a matter of pride.
It's a battle between us.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
(They play rock, paper, scissors with suspicion.)
- Yes! - This is annoying.
(Kwang Soo is exempt from paying.)
(I am spending a lot of money today.)
This is upsetting.
- Ji Hyo, this is the only way. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
We can swap countries.
- This is our best chance. - We can swap countries.
We can swap these two countries.
- Right. - Then we will be done.
(Get 4 on the die and acquire a Golden Key.)
(Get a Swapping Card.)
(Swap Germany with Thailand to win with Germany and Switzerland.)
It's our only chance.
Please show us four.
- It's our only chance. - Please show us four.
(The die is cast.)
(Will she get a four?)
- What? - Hey.
(She really got a four.)
- Hey. - Did you see that?
- We have it. - Did you see that?
- Ji Hyo, you are insane. - Did you see that?
- You are insane. - You saw that, right?
This is crazy. You are the best.
You are insane.
- Ji Hyo. - It's too early to give up.
What will become of Running Man?
- Let's read the signs. - You are insane.
She should be a fortune teller.
What do the signs say?
You are insane. You are insane.
Give us a Golden Key.
Give us one. Ji Hyo, you are the best.
(They succeed in getting a Golden Key.)
It will be game over if we get Swapping Card.
It will be over right here.
I can't believe Haha used such a cheap trick.
He's not that famous.
- He isn't good enough yet. - He has to be famous in Germany.
- It'd be insane if you pick it. - You can be psychic.
The probability is too low.
If you draw a Swapping Card, I'll be very happy.
However, I'll be scared of you after this.
Seriously.
It's a 1 out of 14 chance.
This is too difficult.
Please throw the die again.
If we land in Spain, don't we win?
(They win if they purchase Spain.)
We're doomed if we have to find something related to Luxembourg.
It's hard to find things related to Iceland or Madagascar.
- Don't land in the South Pole. - We'll be doomed.
My fingers went limp.
- One is the best. - Throw a low number.
(She already threw the die.)
(Please let it be one.)
- Throw a low number. - One is the best.
(She throws a 1.)
(We're proud of you, Hyorin.)
I told you that you'd make it.
- This is turning the tables. - It depends on your will.
- Wait a minute. - This is turning the tables.
(Will they get an easy mission?)
- It's "Cultural Experience". - Is that it?
- It's not bad. - It isn't.
- It's "Cultural Experience". - That's right.
Here are the rules.
Siesta is a part of Spanish culture.
Here are the rules for "Cultural Experience".
Like siesta in Spain, you must take a nap for 10 minutes.
You must take a nap for 10 minutes.
You fail if you open your eyes before 10 minutes pass.
Really?
- Keep your eyes closed. - Let's keep our eyes closed.
Let's talk with our eyes closed.
- 10 minutes is long. - Don't open them.
Imagine that we're sleeping.
I want to open my eyes.
Can we eliminate 1 by 1?
- You may do that. - Is that okay?
- We'll pick the ones to eliminate. - We have unlucky hands.
- Gosh. - Look at that.
- I pick this one. - Turn it over.
It's desert island.
We increased our chance. We only have 12 cards left.
- Let's keep eliminating them. - We're unlucky after all.
Look at this.
(The unlucky men increase Ji Hyo's chances.)
(He hesitates.)
Turn it over once you touch it.
- Otherwise, she'll be confused. - There we go.
You'll get it, Ji Hyo. Please.
- Ji Hyo. - Please.
It's one of these.
(They need Ji Hyo to be lucky again.)
- We win with a Swapping Card. - We win.
It's game over then.
You'll get it, Ji Hyo. Please.
- Please. - It's one of these.
(Team Hyorin sleeps while dreaming of turning the tables.)
(Will they clear the mission first or will she pick Swapping Card?)
Don't look yet.
(She grabs it.)
(Ji Hyo picks a card.)
(What does her Golden Key say?)
Look at this!
(She screams in joy.)
(They all scream.)
(Ji Hyo gets lucky again.)
(They successfully draw a Swapping Card.)
- What's the mission? - I don't want to play anymore.
We picked a Swapping Card.
(They pick a Swapping Card.)
This is amazing.
You swapped Germany with Thailand.
Yes.
The winner of Running Marble is Team Jae Seok.
(They win Running Marble Part Two.)
(It's a result of great teamwork.)
I'm so happy.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
- You made our day, Ji Hyo. - Seriously.
(Team Ji Hyo wins Running Marble.)
It's Running Marble, a backpacking trip in the neighborhood.
The team that came in last must take a Tour Sticker.
The one with the least amount of money will take it.
- Please count how much... - Goodness.
you have left.
- I might be the one. - Do you have two?
(Haha started with 50 cents.)
(He was betrayed by So Min and Kwang Soo.)
(As his team members continued to betray him,)
(he had to spend his money little by little.)
(He was doomed from the start to the end.)
I'm in trouble.
I'm hopeless.
(Hyoin, order as much as you want.)
(He kept spending his money to win her heart.)
(He had to pay many penalty fees.)
(He may go bankrupt soon.)
I need to count every last penny.
I have 18 dollars.
(Jong Kook's remaining amount)
(He has 18 dollars.)
I have 18 dollars and 30 cents.
(Haha needs more than that.)
I have...
- I have 18 dollars. - What?
(Haha also has 18 dollars.)
(Who will lose?)
How could he not know?
- I have three coins. - He has a lot.
- He has 18 dollars and 30 cents. - He has the same amount.
(Does he have the same amount?)
I have a 50-cent coin.
(Is one of them a 50-cent coin?)
(He has 70 cents total.)
I have 18 dollars and 70 cents.
- You have the least. - It's 18 dollars and 70 cents.
Put a Tour Sticker on Jong Kook's name.
Jong Kook gets a Tour Sticker.
He finally got it.
(Jong Kook gets a Tour Sticker for this round.)
(As the end of a beautiful spring draws near,)
(what type of mission will the members get?)
Hello, hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Where's Se Chan?
- Right. Where is he? - Why isn't he here?
- Se Chan isn't here. - Where is he?
I guess he isn't coming.
- Really? Already? - That's true.
- I didn't see him in the car. - What happened to him?
Give him one more chance.
He is... No, he was sweet.
(Where could Se Chan be?)
- May is a familial month. - Yes.
For you to get to know the new members like your own family,
you'll visit Se Chan's house.
Are we visiting his house?
Se Chan thinks the shoot is in two hours, and he's getting ready.
That's why he isn't here.
This also happened to Kwang Soo.
- He was brushing his teeth. - I remember that.
(He can't forget how shocked he was.)
This is scary.
We can't visit his house empty-handed.
Right.
Here are the rules...
- for Dangerous Gifts. - What are they?
Each of you must buy an item that he needs,
but it must be something that he doesn't have at home.
- Goodness. - A necessary item he doesn't have?
- It's difficult. - Something that he doesn't have?
(It's a dangerous, house-warming party.)
You lose a point if you buy an item he already has.
If all seven members buy an item that he doesn't have,
Se Chan will lose one point.
We're sensitive about clearing each mission...
because a Tour Sticker is the penalty.
- It's a harsh price to pay. - It'll determine our next week.
This is how to make it fun. Some should get many Tour Stickers.
(Get many Tour Stickers.)
- One member should get many. - That's impossible.
That would be strange.
- Obvious members got them. - That's true.
Why is there so much more space for this round?
- Why? - That's true.
(There's a lot of space in the chart.)
(Is there a hidden intention?)
(One member is selected for a Dangerous Tour.)
- There must be several stickers. - What's the reason?
There must be 2 or 3.
- There are several today. - That's true.
In that case...
After you purchase a gift each, we'll drive to Se Chan's place.
Okay.
What should I buy?
This is very difficult.
- Would he have this? - What?
(She whispers to Ji Hyo.)
Why don't you share your idea with us?
Come on, you're so silly.
(She thinks as she walks.)
(So Min, you're the best.)
(What kind of gift will So Min buy?)
Can I buy it?
Will they consider me dirty if I buy it?
I know many male friends who use it.
It's over there.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Do you have an enema?
(Did she say enema?)
(Her embarrassment disappears.)
May I just get one?
Just 1? It's 40 cents.
It's very cheap.
Please give me 40 cents.
(She begs for 40 cents from the staff.)
Is this okay to be aired?
(Will you be okay with it?)
Thank you.
I'm so smart.
I think I'm so smart.
(Se Chan won't have this at home.)
Something just hit me and...
It was just a fly.
- What's the idea? - Come on, Jae Seok.
- It was a fly that hit you. - It's not what I meant.
Something came up in my head.
- My goodness. - Kwang Soo.
- I know you were joking. - Think carefully.
How about a lottery ticket?
(A lottery ticket)
(Kwang Soo finally comes up with a brilliant idea.)
Do you still think I lack ideas?
Do you still think...
(They fight to buy a lottery ticket first.)
Kwang Soo.
- That's such a great idea. - He won't have it at home.
A lottery ticket is perfect.
Do you sell lottery tickets?
(Are you going to buy it first?)
Seriously, not many people have lottery tickets at home.
I want to come up with something really unexpected.
Should I get foot care products?
I saw them earlier.
- Do you have this at home? - Everyone does.
- Do you have this? - You do, right?
You don't, right? Do you have one of these?
- No, right? - Something like this.
(Ji Hyo gets something unfamiliar.)
Thank you.
He can't have one of these at home.
If a male celebrity has one of these,
he'd be a super, ultra celebrity.
If he has lottery tickets at home, I'll accept my fate.
(Jae Seok is looking for toys.)
What should I get?
- Kwon Ryeol. - Yes?
We're doomed.
(I'm sorry I've dragged you into this.)
I can't find toys.
How far are we going?
All I see are restaurants.
Could there be one in Sangam?
Perhaps a robot... He probably doesn't have a hamburger.
I'm sure he definitely doesn't have this.
He can't have diapers. Red beans... Stamps...
He can't have tuna at home, right?
Keys... He might have chocolate.
Candles? Tacks... Leads...
He might have a tape measure.
He might have all these things.
(He's wandering anxiously around Sangam.)
(He's back where he started.)
I could have come here in the beginning.
It's right here.
My goodness.
Hello.
He can't have one of these.
(Jae Seok buys his gift.)
They must be waiting for me.
- Gosh. - What happened?
- What happened? - Where did you go?
- What happened? - What happened?
I wanted to get toys, but I couldn't find a store.
- You spent an hour for this? - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's hurry.
All right.
(They visit the unsuspecting man.)
(His neighborhood is filled with the beauty of spring.)
We're here.
- We're here. - Let's go.
(Se Chan, here we come.)
- Well... - He lives in Building 125.
- There's the gate. - Let's go in when it opens.
Se Chan's manager is here.
- Hi. - Hello.
- He knows the passcode. - Does he really have no idea?
- Really? - No, he has no idea.
- Se Chan has no idea. - It's exciting.
Let's be quiet.
(Raid Se Chan's place.)
(Se Hyung is not home.)
- Hey. - Where is his place?
Here?
- He really doesn't know? - No.
He doesn't.
(They're at his door.)
(When the door opens,)
(we'll barge in.)
(We're all set.)
(Let's go.)
(The manager rings the doorbell.)
He might see you.
(The cameramen are hiding too.)
(The door opens.)
(What is this?)
- What is this? - Look at him.
Let's go in.
(Surprise!)
Oh, my. He's not wearing a shirt.
- Hey! - Let's go in.
- He's not wearing a shirt. - Stay that way.
- Stop it. - Stay topless.
- Stay topless. - No!
- He's not wearing a shirt. - It's okay.
- Se Chan. - Stay that way.
Stop it.
Put the shirt on.
You have a nice place.
What is this? What were you watching?
I wasn't watching it.
What is this?
(Lingerie channel?)
Why were you watching it with your shirt off?
- What were you doing? - Why weren't you wearing a shirt?
- What's with you? - Why were you watching that?
- Why were you topless? - What were you doing?
- What is this? - Were you watching this?
- Why are you changing the channel? - You were watching something weird.
- Look at that. - Why did you change the channel?
You should have told me in advance.
Why weren't you wearing a shirt?
- What's so wrong about it? - I mean,
- I was at least wearing pants. - you were expecting your manager.
Hey! I was going to put on a shirt. Why didn't you tell me in advance?
He wasn't supposed to tell you.
(Satisfied)
You were at least wearing pants.
- Of course. - My goodness.
What are you eating?
They're chips.
- Feel free to eat anything. - Can we?
- Can we look in your fridge? - Go ahead.
- Feel free. - We showed up unannounced.
It's chaos. Se Chan.
We brought all the equipment.
- We have to install that. - They're going to install that.
- You have a lovely place. - I'm just renting it.
- Let's sit down. - Take a seat.
He has a nice place.
Se Chan, thank you for letting us come in.
Letting you come in, my foot. You just barged in.
We can't say that he let us come in. He was half-naked.
He didn't let us come in.
Seok Jin, you keep shedding something.
It's from his knees.
- Hey. - It's not only his hair that sheds.
His pants shed too.
(Hesitant)
Is it just me or does someone's feet smell bad?
- Why do you ask Kwang Soo? - It's not me.
Why do you pick on me?
You're the only one who's not wearing socks.
- It's not me. Smell my feet. - It's your feet.
Smell mine.
(I'm innocent.)
- Who is it? - So Min.
- You're not wearing socks. - So Min.
- She's not wearing socks. - You're the only one.
- I think it's him. - No, it's not.
- Gosh. - My feet don't smell.
- Stop it. - My feet don't smell.
Your feet are closest to you.
Gosh, it's you.
- It's really you. - That's not true.
- Smell them. - Stop it.
Stop it.
So Min, I'll write about this in my report on you.
My feet never smell.
Did you touch your nose after touching your feet?
That's why.
(It's from your hands.)
- That's why. - Some people do that.
(She should compete with Do Yeon sometime.)
The one with the lowest score...
will get a Tour Sticker at the end.
With one more sticker, Se Chan will be sent on the trip.
- He will. - You're almost there.
Now, you'll give Se Chan the gifts you've bought.
If he already has the same thing at home,
the present-giver will lose one point.
If he has none of the things the members got,
he will lose one point.
I will? Comedians have all kinds of stuff.
- That's right. - I have all kinds of props.
- He might have what I got. - What is it?
- What is it? - I'm serious.
- Is it expensive? - It's...
You definitely have one of these.
- It's a beauty product. - A beauty product?
- It's a pack. - I have packs.
- You do? - Let me see.
- What kind of pack is it? - It's a foot pack.
A foot pack?
(Is there such a thing as a foot pack?)
- That's awesome. - Are you serious?
- Is this real life? - Is it?
- Is it? - Is this a foot pack?
This is the least strange thing we have.
It removes hardened dead skin cells.
Jong Kook is so petty.
A foot pack? Give me a second.
- Do you have one? - See if you have one.
- I mean, - You might have one.
he might have gotten one from his fans.
- That's possible. - Se Hyung might have one.
(His fridge is full of packs.)
I've never seen a foot pack before.
I've never seen it before.
I think he might have one.
- What if he has one? - I think he has one.
- No way. - A foot pack...
These are all the packs I have.
I've never gone through all these.
- You have so many. - I'm getting nervous.
(One of them might be a foot pack.)
- He has a lot. - Wait.
- Aren't they all face packs? - Gosh.
- This one is for the face. - This one is for the face too.
- I hope I have one. - It's for the face.
- They're usually for the face. - They're all for the face.
How did you think of a foot pack?
(Se Chan is new to foot packs,)
(but his brother, Se Hyung, might be familiar with them.)
- There isn't? - There isn't.
That's a relief.
He has no foot packs.
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
This is a very useful gift.
Can I put it away?
I'm worried I'll use it on my face while drunk.
Don't be absurd.
- It might happen. - That's absurd.
- Seriously. - That's absurd.
Let's give the foot pack to So Min.
Why are you doing this to me?
Stop wriggling your toes.
Hey, don't blame me.
The smell is not too bad.
- It's not too bad. - I have my socks here.
- Don't take them out. - But they're skin-color.
- Why are you showing them to us? - They're skin-color.
(She takes her socks out.)
I took them off because the color is embarrassing.
Do you touch your face after touching them?
- They don't smell. - So Min.
- Put them back in. - They don't smell.
- What are you doing? - They don't smell.
- Put them in. - Put them in.
- Fine, we get it. - They're clean.
- Fine. - Viewers,
- this is not fair. - Put them in.
(She pleads to the viewers.)
- Put them in. - Gosh.
It's you.
No, it's not.
They don't...
What are you doing?
(Seok Jin is knocked out.)
- Hold on. - Why did you rub your fingers?
- Stop it. - What is she doing?
- It makes the smell worse. - I know.
- What did you do? - Why did you do that?
Now, it's Ji Hyo's turn.
I got something both Se Chan and Se Hyung can use.
I got chewable toothbrushes.
- I got chewable toothbrushes. - Do you have it?
What's that?
That's ridiculous.
(Ji Hyo succeeds.)
You might have something that has the same function.
- He must have one. - What is this?
It's hair removal cream.
- It's for waxing. - It's wax.
Wax?
You don't have it, do you?
Haha succeeded.
What's that?
- It's an enema. - It's an enema.
An enema?
(Why is she giving me this?)
- I don't have this. - That's funny.
- I'm... - Show us your present.
- Mine? - Yes.
(What will be his gift?)
- What is that? - All right. I...
got you a double eyelid tape.
- A double eyelid tape? - It's to make double eyelids.
- A double eyelid tape? - Yes.
If he has this at home...
(Let's see.)
- Wait a second. - You have it?
- If you have this at home... - Wait a second.
But you have double eyelids. Are you trying to double what you have?
- Do you really have it? - "Wait a second" is funny.
- He's looking around to find it. - No way.
- He can't have it. - Okay.
(Will Se Chan really have the tape?)
There we go.
- He can't have the tape. - Who uses...
Who uses tapes anyway?
- He doesn't have much at home. - He can't find it.
- Jae Seok, what did you bring? - Yes?
- Double eyelid tape. - Double eyelid tape.
I'm not sure if this is the right one.
(If he has it at home, Jae Seok will be the first to fail the mission.)
- Let me see. - Please check.
- This is right. - Okay!
(He indeed had it at home!)
- My gosh! - Why does he have this at home?
Why do you have this at home?
- Why... - Hey.
- It's understandable. - He used almost all of them.
- Yes! - Why do you have them?
I'm not sure. I was trying to take out what was in my pocket and...
I think it was there.
- Make yourself clear. - It doesn't make sense.
- In your pocket? - It was in your pocket?
- You were mumbling just now. - It doesn't make sense.
It just happened to be here?
Why do you have used up tapes at home?
Tell me. Whose is this?
- Well... - Be honest.
- Wait. - Why are you blushing?
- Tell us this instant. - Whose is this?
- Why is it here? - Why?
- If it's hard to say... - Why do you have it?
My acquaintance...
- Your acquaintance? Who? - Well, my friend...
Then did your friend...
sleep over for... 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 days?
(Is this a dormitory or something?)
- Your friend stayed for five days. - I mean...
- My eyelids aren't the same. - They don't have the same shape.
- Don't you lie. - That can't be the reason.
- Do it yourself then. - Right. Do it.
- Let him do it himself. - Let's see if you're used to this.
- Don't help him out. - Do it.
Girls would notice right away.
Sorry, but are you a detective?
- Are you from the police? - I'm a sheriff.
He's a Mapo sheriff.
- He's investigating now. - Let's see.
- If you're not good at it... - Do it.
- You have to do it at once. - How can he have this at home?
- He's good. - He's actually doing it.
- He's good at it. - He's really doing it.
- It looks natural. - He's right.
- He's good at it. - He's right.
- It's his. - This side of my eyelid...
- All right. I admit. - Okay.
(They're still suspicious, but they admit that it's Se Chan's.)
- It's Seok Jin's turn. - All right.
- He can't have this at home. - Se Chan has...
- unusual things at home. - I'm sure of this.
(Seok Jin even confirmed it to the staff before buying.)
(It's deodorant.)
I won't say a word if you have it.
You won't say a word? All right. Wait a second.
(All right, wait a second.)
- "Wait a second." - Then it'll be mine.
I'm sure he doesn't have it.
Bring it in front of me. Then I'll admit.
Bring it.
I mean...
This is right.
It clearly says so.
(It says deodorant.)
- Bring it. - It says so.
- Don't be so sure. - Bring it!
- I got it. - Isn't that hair spray?
It says deodorant.
- It's hair spray. - No.
It's not.
(He really didn't want to admit that it's deodorant.)
- It's deodorant. - No way.
- It's hair spray. - You spray it on your armpits.
It's for your armpits. Okay, who's next?
I have almost everything at home.
- It's Kwang Soo's turn. - Okay.
- I got a lottery ticket. - That's tricky.
- It's a lottery ticket. - Lottery ticket?
- That's tricky. - It's a lottery ticket.
- Lottery ticket? - I don't think he has it.
- Do you have it? - Hold on a second.
Hold on.
Is any kind of lottery ticket acceptable?
- Right. - Sure.
(Well, then.)
- Wait a second. - Do you have a lottery ticket?
- Do you really have it? - Let me check first.
(I shall bring the item to you if you give me some time.)
- "Wait a second." - Wait a second.
- This is crazy. - Wait a second.
- Hold on. - This is now getting scary.
(People usually throw it away when it's a dud.)
There you go.
- His reaction is too funny. - Does he really have it at home?
- Don't lose hope yet. - You don't keep a dud at home.
- This won't make sense. - No way.
(Is he really...)
(returning with a lottery ticket?)
(He's now going to meet the members.)
- No, right? - It's not a scratcher.
But this is also a lottery ticket, right?
- That's right. - That sure is a lottery ticket.
- My gosh! - He sure has one.
(He's taken aback to see him have one.)
- It's right. - The one with six numbers.
My gosh.
- So you have it at home. - It was a dud.
He bought it on September, 2016.
And he still has it at home?
- This is crazy. - But it's the lottery ticket.
Let's scratch it while we're at it.
Is it his or yours? Decide on that.
- Why all of a sudden? - It's mine.
- Is it yours? - I lose a point, but it's mine.
- But you have to give it to him. - Wasn't that a gift for me?
Wait. Did you buy it with your money or the staff's?
- This will turn the tables. - Right.
I borrowed money from them.
I plan to pay them back.
- No, make it clear. - Just in case you win.
- How much was it? - It's Se Chan's.
- It was a dollar. - It's the gift after all.
I'll pay two dollars.
- 2 dollars? - I'll pay 3 dollars.
Three dollars.
- I'll pay 5 dollars for it. - 5 dollars?
- All right, let him have it. - It's done.
(They close the deal right away.)
(All of a sudden?)
- Five dollars are reasonable. - I did that once.
Give him five dollars.
(A 1-dollar ticket turned into a 5-dollar one.)
You hustlers.
Give a dollar each for Se Chan and the staff, and you take the rest.
(Jae Seok and Haha did a great job on fooling Seok Jin again.)
- Give him five dollars. - That was a nice decoy.
If I win some money, it'll all be mine.
(He's scratching the ticket with much excitement.)
- How much is the prize money? - It's 500,000 dollars.
- Look for a 4. - Okay, the lucky number is 4.
If there's a 4, then I gain 500,000 dollars.
If there's a 4, I gain 500,000 dollars.
- You just need a four? - Yes.
Please. Let me give them a lesson.
(Once there's a 4, you'll all be regretting.)
Look.
It's 3, 4... I got 3, 5, 6, 7, and 8.
- Only four is missing. - I see.
(He has only one number remaining. He's got a good feeling about this.)
It's one.
- What is this? - It's a dud.
- Is this all? - Yes.
(He was scratching without even knowing the rule.)
- Kwang Soo gets minus one point. - All right.
Here's the results of Dangerous Gifts.
Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and Seok Jin get minus one point each.
- Oh, dear. - Stop with that teasing.
Here, take these Whale Badges.
It's for those who got a deduction in points.
(They're given mysterious Whale Badges.)
- What is this? - It's small.
What is this for?
(Does today's mission have something to do with whales?)
Here's today's real mission.
It's the fourth part of Global Project.
It's called Dangerous Choices.
Dangerous Choices?
If every one of the members clears a mission,
today's race and the shooting will end right away.
But if at least one of you fails to clear the mission,
one person will be given a Tour Sticker.
- There will be many Stickers. - This is horrible.
Also, you will each have to earn scores throughout the race.
- You got a deduction just now. - Right.
You'll be given a Whale Badge according to a certain standard.
In the end, the person with the most number of badges...
will ride a whale-watching ferry...
- which departs at 5am... - Whale-watching ferry!
in Ulsan tomorrow.
(One of them will have to ride the whale-watching ferry.)
What time?
Did you say 5am?
Then you have to depart at 1am at least.
- We have to leave immediately. - One person?
- This is no joke. - My gosh.
The one with the most number of Whale Badges...
- will pick one member to go with. - My gosh!
The two will go together to watch the whales, the symbol for luck.
On their trip,
if they get to see a whale,
- they won't get a Tour Sticker. - I see.
- If they don't get to see one... - See whales?
Did you say whales?
I've never seen a whale in my entire life.
- Are you serious? - At 5am?
(They'll be given Whale Badges according to hidden rules.)
(The Whale Badges will decide who will go on the trip.)
(Those who figure out the hidden rule will be safe from the penalty.)
(Will the members be able to guess?)
- Is there something hidden? - Is there?
So we have to find out why we are given the Whale Badges.
Right.
First mission you need to clear together is called...
- Dangerous Household Items. - What is that?
Among the household items in this house,
- grab one item with you. - So it depends on your luck.
By any chance, did you assume that I'd give permission to all of this?
- What if I reject... - That's what I'm saying.
- What if he says no? - I know.
Please put your socks in, So Min.
- Gosh. - It stinks.
- Can I have some socks? - Seriously.
I hear sticky noises whenever you walk around.
- It's not true. - Sticky noises.
- Household items? - Household items.
(They start looking.)
So there are hidden rules which only the staff members know.
- What should we pick? - Should it be something long?
What should I pick?
(They're being careful.)
I'll just take this and not think further about it.
(After searching through Se Chan's house,)
(they pick kitchen scissors,)
(a cleaning roller,)
Okay.
(and even a cologne bottle.)
- A cologne. - Kwang Soo!
Yes, I'm done.
(They're done choosing the items without knowing the mission.)
Are you done picking?
- Yes. - Yes.
From now on, you will take turns...
to put up a tower with the items you've brought.
With this?
- Where did you find that anyway? - But...
you must put these cubes between each item.
(They must put up a tower with the items and the cubes.)
- We have a table. - How do we...
We can use this table when we pile the items up.
(We need to focus!)
(Deep in thought)
How about we flip the table...
and put this bottle underneath?
It's too small to balance.
Who brought this cologne?
- Unbelievable. - Kwang Soo, seriously.
Do you want me to take it back?
That cologne ruined everything.
Who brought this?
- Why would you bring this? - Why did you bring it?
Asks the person who brought a useless stick.
(Both of them are just as useless.)
- Jae Seok, you're about to ruin it. - This isn't just a stick!
- What kind of stick did I bring? - I bet you will lose today.
If I am chosen, I will choose you to come with me.
(Kwang Soo is chosen.)
I'll choose you to come with me.
I think this side is slanted.
- It's because of the cologne. - What is this hair doing here?
(Is this hair?)
(Shaking)
- Don't touch it! - What are you doing?
(Flinching)
That hair isn't that important.
- I'll pull all of your hair out. - Hey.
Jong Kook, try your best, but his stick...
I will do it.
- I will do it. - He said he will do it.
- You're noisy. Go outside. - This one should be...
Jae Seok, be quiet!
Hear me out. At the end, I will balance this on the tower.
- At the end, with his stick, - It will stand.
let him take all the blame.
(This is the big picture in mind.)
Let him take all the blame.
Hey, I shouldn't be the one. Kwang Soo should be responsible.
- Don't touch it. - Leave it alone.
That one is a hard one too. Who brought the feather duster?
I brought it.
You did?
That's understandable.
(He's intimidated.)
Balance them for me.
- This is leaning toward this side. - You must feel frustrated now.
- The staff must feel frustrated. - Jong Kook, move it to this side.
- Don't you? - It has to go this way.
- We are almost done. - Why isn't this working?
(Crashing down)
(Oh, no. We were so close to finishing it.)
- It's all because of the cologne. - You have failed.
- I didn't even get to try mine. - Kwang Soo.
- This should have been on top. - Why did you bring the cologne?
- All right. - To finish that...
- All of you have failed. - Yes, we have.
One of you will receive the Whale Badge.
(Who will be the recipient of 1 Whale Badge?)
It will be Jae Seok.
- Why? - Yes!
(Jae Seok is the recipient.)
(Why is it me?)
- Why do I have to get one? - Okay!
(Why is he getting it?)
- Why did he get one? - We have to figure that out.
It must be that!
- Okay! - What is it?
- Can I tell them? - I figured it out.
We have to find the reason why.
It's because he brought the longest item.
- No, that's incorrect. - It's incorrect?
Move your feet.
- It could be the penalty. - What is it? Why?
- Did he get it? - Okay. Haha told me his answer.
(He's known to be quick-witted.)
(Did he really find out the hidden rule?)
(Haha's answer is...)
"It's because Jae Seok is ugly."
(Haha's answer is because Jae Seok is ugly.)
(Somehow, it sounds convincing. Is that why?)
- What are you trying to do here? - What?
- That's my opinion, Jae Seok. - Goodness.
All right. Why don't you mark only one piece of paper for us?
- Mark it a dud. - Okay.
- Whoever gets it is chosen? - Yes.
(Whoever gets the marked paper is chosen.)
To be honest, regarding this game,
I believe Jae Seok should receive one.
- Why? - It's because...
Let me be blunt. Seok Jin and my items...
They pile up in a stable manner. I can even show you now.
- Show us. - Will they still work?
Look. They are stable.
- Mine works too. - I agree with Haha.
- Ours work too. - If they do, I will let you off.
They'll work.
- I can balance it. Look. - Will it really work?
If yours work too, I will accept it.
It has to last five seconds after you put it on.
- Gosh! - In 5, 4,
- 3, 2, 1. - It's not a problem at all.
- This isn't a problem at all. - Kwang Soo is helping.
You all saw this, right?
That's not it. The thing is, you two made a mistake.
Didn't you make it or not?
He looks like a magistrate. He turned into a magistrate.
(He's the strictest magistrate.)
- Hey, think about it. - Hey.
Can you talk to this magistrate for me?
And say what?
- This doesn't make sense. - I can't do this.
- Tell him it's a variety show. - How can we add this on the pile?
Everyone, everyone.
Not getting the Tour Sticker is crucial,
but I will keep getting the Badges and choose...
one of you to come with me.
- Oh, he's right. I forgot about it. - I mean it.
All right. Let's go with eight pieces of paper.
- All right. I agree. - Okay, Jae Seok.
- Let the papers decide. - Jae Seok, I agree with you.
- Let's go with these papers. - I want Kwang Soo to get picked.
Or you can come with me to watch the whales.
I guess you want to watch the whales with me.
(I have forgotten about Jong Kook.)
- It's a twist within a twist. - All right then.
- All right then. - It's a twist within a twist.
Why don't the seven of us pick the paper?
(He retreats.)
(In front of Jong Kook, Jae Seok feels small.)
- We should make him distribute. - Okay.
Whoever gets the dud will be ruined.
(The chosen one's chance will increase.)
- Please. - If I'm chosen, I am finished.
- Don't unfold it yet. - How does this make sense?
I am too nervous to open it.
I hope someone before me gets it.
- I hope someone gets the dud. - Let it be the dud.
(Ji Hyo is exempted.)
So Min is usually lucky.
No, I bet she will get the dud.
In 1, 2, 3.
(So Min is exempted.)
- So Min, come here. Come to me. - Hey, move aside.
(We are lucky. We survived!)
- We are safe. - He's the new unlucky member.
- Is it my turn? - Why don't you go last?
If he gets it, he will go on the trip right away.
- Right. - That's right.
- I should open mine... - You should open yours.
- since I am not that unlucky. - You two don't have any Stickers.
There's no way.
In 1, 2, 3.
(He spoke too soon.)
(Seok Jin gets one Tour Sticker.)
(He said he's not that unlucky.)
- Gosh. - You have one, right?
- This is unbelievable. - Let's check ours too.
- We are all exempted. - All right.
- Let's keep them. Use them later. - This is amazing.
- I am relieved. - Seok Jin got it.
The first round of Dangerous Choices wasn't successful.
Before we start the second round,
- it's lunchtime. - Yes, it is.
We will order the food you'd like to have.
- What is this? - This is nice.
- He might be up to something. - There might be a hidden agenda.
Hey, if you order something special,
- there might be something. - I agree.
You might have to face a penalty.
Hold on, this could be a mission where we have to unify our choices.
- Or they have to be all different. - No, I don't think so.
Or maybe there's a budget limit.
- No way. - They won't be that petty.
- They should feed us properly. - Let's not overlap.
All right, let's do that.
- Se Chan, what do you want? - I want...
I'd like to have ganjjajang.
I'd like to have tangjjamyeon.
Hey, we are going to order tangsuyuk separately.
- No, we're not. - We are not?
I guess we're not.
- Let's order one. - All right.
- Order large tangsuyuk. - Large tangsuyuk.
I want jjamjjamyeon.
I want beef brisket jjamppong.
- Hey. - I want stir-fried jjamppong.
Kwang Soo chose white broth jjamppong.
Haha chose beef brisket jjamppong, right?
Yes, but may I switch to jaengban jjajang?
- You'd like to change? - Yes.
I think something must be up. They wouldn't give us the menu.
They would just ask us.
- I think this might be a mission. - It's seven dollars.
We have ordered now.
The second round is Dangerous Orders.
(The 2nd round of Dangerous Choices is Dangerous Orders.)
- You said this wasn't the mission. - No way.
Since you didn't unify your choices,
- you have failed. - Hold on.
(They have failed.)
Everyone, sit down!
Wait.
What did I tell you?
Didn't I tell you we should unify our choices?
He became a thug.
- Didn't I tell you or not? - He looks like a thug now.
- You did tell us. - Didn't I tell you?
- Se Chan is teasing you a lot. - Didn't I tell you or not?
- You did tell us. - He's teasing you.
- I told you so, didn't I? - We have different tastes in food.
- I believed you. - All right, the Whale Badge...
This is driving me crazy.
- Se Chan, take the Badge. - What?
(Since you failed, Se Chan, take the Badge.)
- Is it me? Is it really me? - What's going on?
- What is it? - I know! I know!
- Why? - Me?
What did you order?
- Only you ordered jjajangmyeon. - I did.
- I ordered jaengban jjajang. - What is it?
- Why is it me? - I know!
(Ji Hyo seems to have figured it out.)
(It's because Se Chan was the only one who ordered jjajangmyeon.)
Why is it me?
(Wait. This is only the 2nd round.)
I ordered jaengban jjajang.
(Did she figure it out already?)
- That's incorrect. - I guess it's not correct.
- Ji Hyo, what did you tell him? - What was your answer?
I said it's because he ordered jjajangmyeon.
Is it the same reason from the first round?
I told you we should unify our choices. Goodness.
- Haha. - We...
(He has a mysterious look.)
Is it correct?
(Did Haha tell him the correct answer?)
He said, "It depends on your mood."
What? "It depends on your mood"?
(Wasn't that funny?)
- Haha. - I thought he was about to curse.
(Haha's guess is obviously incorrect.)
It's about me. I should get it.
(It's all right as long as it's funny.)
Se Chan, what did you do when you were standing here?
Do what you were doing. Try to remember.
- I massaged his shoulders. - What is the reason?
- I massaged his shoulders. - Then what did you do?
Are you certain it's not because they are ugly?
Is it not because we're ugly?
- I figured it out. - It's the reason for every mission?
Aren't I right?
You are giving the Badge to the ugliest member first.
Kwang Soo will be next.
- What are you talking about? - Kwang Soo is next.
- It's not me. - Isn't he next?
- Why was I picked? - Wait!
To be honest, I know the answer.
I know the answer. Can I tell you? I won't try to be funny.
- Yes. - Okay.
- You just gave me a chance. - Sure.
(He looks pretty confident of his answer.)
- I didn't do anything. - Don't pretend you are sharp.
The first person who spoke after you said we failed the mission.
- Goodness. - Hold on.
(What is that look?)
(Did he really figure it out?)
That's incorrect, but his answer was very close.
- What did you say? - What is it?
(Can you tell us what it is?)
- Is that so? - What is it?
(All right. I got it now.)
Consequently,
you failed the second round,
- but your food will arrive. - Right.
The owner of the dish...
that the delivery man puts down first will receive a Tour Sticker.
(Whoever gets their dish first will get a Sticker.)
There are two orders of stir-fried jjamppong.
- We have to settle between us. - You have to settle between you.
If he puts down tangsuyuk first, we are off the hook?
(What about the dish for all of us?)
Since Se Chan suggested ordering it,
you have both tangsuyuk and ganjjajang.
(Tangsuyuk and ganjjajang will count as Se Chan's.)
Let's order large tangsuyuk.
(He ordered tangsuyuk because he felt sorry for Seok Jin.)
He will be in the lead.
- Se Chan, just give up already. - Se Chan.
- You are done. - It's over.
- It's game over. - Just go.
(Se Chan is a rising, unlucky member.)
We ordered your dishes.
Here's the third mission.
We invited a special guest.
What?
(Who is the special guest?)
- Who is it? - Is it Se Hyung?
(Is Se Hyung here to check on his younger brother?)
- He's here again. - It's the massage therapist.
(Why is he here again?)
Come on.
I'll explain again for the new members.
He's a masseur and Running Man's mascot.
(It's Masseur Kim Hyung Joon.)
(Your body is in pain every time you see him.)
The rule is the same.
You clear the mission if none of you make a sound for 10 seconds.
Everyone has to get a massage, right?
- It's impossible to stay silent. - I know.
- It's impossible. - So Min should try it.
- So Min should go. - Get a hand massage.
It feels refreshing.
Just don't make any sounds.
Shouldn't it be her shoulders?
- Get ready. - Please relax.
- You have to endure it. - Relax.
(Did he feel my tension?)
- Endure it. - It's shorter than you think.
- Start. - It will be short.
(She moans.)
Come on, why did you cry?
- It hurts. - You should endure it.
- She should go last. - It hurts.
- You should go last. - That's okay.
Come here, So Min. It's okay.
- He's so strong. - You did a good job.
- We haven't started the mission. - No, not yet.
- It was a test. - That's right.
- Ji Hyo is good at enduring pain. - That's true.
- She endured it last time. - Get a shoulder massage.
Try the shoulders. Have a seat.
- She will endure it. - Have a seat.
- Do you want a chair? - No, it's okay.
- Get ready, set, go. - It's Ji Hyo's turn.
(She squirms.)
- She's enduring it. - Endure it.
(She's determined to endure the pain.)
- You're a champion. - She's impressive.
- You're done halfway. - Endure it.
(She grimaces.)
- She'll make it. - You're doing well today.
- Stop. - She made it.
(Ji Hyo succeeds.)
(She endures the pain by making an ugly face.)
She's so impressive.
- You looked the ugliest. - Seriously, Ji Hyo.
(This is what he says after all she went through.)
- She looked the ugliest ever? - I'm serious.
- I've never seen her that ugly. - Jae Seok.
- Let's see how you do it. - Goodness.
Sir, that was so painful.
I wanted to draw a runny nose on her.
- To make her more ugly? - It really hurt.
Now that Ji Hyo finished,
there's no one else who can endure it.
(The rest are scaredy-cats.)
- This part hurts the most. - Haha endured it before.
- That's right. - It's Haha's turn.
Can you massage this part?
(Haha is forced to go.)
- His outfit isn't right for this. - Get ready.
- Hold on a minute. - Haha is impressive too.
Can you give me something I can bite on?
I don't want your foot.
You can bite this stuffed dog.
- Get ready. - Isn't this your dog's toy?
- Set. - Didn't your dog play with it?
That's right.
(He stuffs his mouth with it.)
- It belongs to his dog. - Start.
Endure the pain.
(He feels the pain.)
Just don't make any sounds.
5 seconds have passed. You have 5 seconds left.
(He expresses pain through his body.)
Everyone should endure it.
(Please stop. I can't do it anymore.)
- He's impressive. - It's a success.
(Haha succeeds.)
(Haha endures the pain.)
It's our turn, so move out of the way.
- Haha. - Get out of the way.
Go to the back.
(Enjoy the pain in the back.)
- How many more do we have? - I feel bad for them.
What if we fail after what they've been through?
(The rest are hopeless.)
Only the weak members remain.
Haha, are you okay?
(Do I look okay?)
- What's wrong? - Is he okay?
You shouldn't lie down during a shoot.
(He disapproves of Haha.)
- You should get up. - Get up, Haha.
You shouldn't lie down during the shoot.
- Look at Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
It's really painful.
- Kwang Soo is next. - He can endure it.
- He's good. - He'll endure it.
(He exhales.)
Sorry, but may I be anesthetized before we start?
Bite the stuffed dog.
(He can only depend on the dog.)
- Get ready. - Poor dog.
Wait a minute.
- Start. - We can get off early if we pass.
Wait a minute, sir.
(He calls for a break as soon as it starts.)
- I feel strange. - What's wrong?
I can't endure it.
(He whispers.)
- You can do it. - Let's go, Kwang Soo.
- You'll be fine. - I really can't.
- Make him pass out for a while. - You can endure it.
Get ready.
Set, go.
(He snorts.)
(Jong Kook covers his mouth completely.)
(He asks for help with his toes.)
You're almost done!
(Let me breathe.)
Look at the masseur.
You're almost done.
(Haha is shocked by the masseur.)
It's a success.
- Did you see him? - Did you see the masseur?
He pressed while using his foot as a support.
That's how he pressed.
(He's about to cry.)
(It's more like a combat.)
I thought he was doing martial arts.
(Gripping)
He blocked me from escaping.
I had nowhere to go.
Gosh, that was impressive.
- It was very impressive. - Jae Seok.
- We're in trouble. - It's your turn, Jae Seok.
He will be fine since he exercises a lot.
(It's another scaredy-cat.)
He lied down.
It's obvious he won't make it.
(They can already predict the outcome.)
(Failure is written on his face.)
- I can endure it. - Get ready.
Bite the stuffed dog.
- Bite it. - It won't work.
Set, go.
(He snorts.)
There he goes.
(He makes a fuss.)
(He flaps his legs helplessly.)
(We will take care of your legs.)
(He grunts loudly.)
(Jae Seok fails.)
- It's a failure. - It must be painful.
- Come on, Jae Seok. - I knew it.
(Once he makes a fuss, he will always make a fuss.)
Gosh.
- I knew it'd happen. - It's so painful.
Not all the members cleared the mission.
Gosh, Jae Seok.
- It's too hard. - Who gets a Whale Badge?
Shouldn't the person who failed get a Whale Badge?
He might not get it.
- Isn't it obvious? - It could be Kwang Soo.
I bet it's Jae Seok.
It's hard to endure the pain.
(Will Jae Seok get a Whale Badge?)
- All right. - Who could it be?
- Is it... - Jae Seok.
See?
- Why me? - It's you.
Why do I get it?
(Haha knows the reason.)
There goes Haha.
Haha is so quick-witted.
- Why is it me? - You made a sound.
- That can't be the reason. - The one who said the last thing...
(Haha's answer was close last time.)
(Has he found out the hidden rule?)
It's very close but wrong.
Come on.
Is the rule the same as before?
It is. Here's another hint.
Look at the people around you.
(What does he mean by that?)
(Does one of them have a secret?)
(This was when Se Chan got a Whale Badge.)
(So Min deliberately stopped Jong Kook.)
(Se Chan got a Whale Badge.)
(This is when Jae Seok got a Whale Badge.)
(Jong Kook called on Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok got a Whale Badge.)
(This all began this morning.)
(This was the Sangam SBS parking lot this morning.)
Hello.
(So Min had a private meeting with the producer.)
I'll give you a secret mission.
(Is there a secret mission?)
You won't be alone in it. He'll join you.
I'll give it to both of you.
Do we do it together?
(She has a partner.)
- So Min. - What's going on?
(Her partner for the secret mission is Jong Kook.)
It's the presidential election two days after the show is aired.
- Is that so? - I see.
Today's secret mission is called Kook-Min's Pick.
It's Kook from Jong Kook and Min from So Min.
(Thus, the name of the mission.)
Kook-Min?
(That's why they're chosen.)
A member will get a Whale Badge when all members fail to pass.
- Whale Badge? - Someone will get it.
The two of you will decide who gets it.
- I see. - Here's how.
As soon as I announce that they failed to clear the mission,
you need to touch each other and call out the name...
of the person who will get it within a minute.
(They must touch and call out his name in 1 minute.)
The one to notice and tell me what the hidden mission is...
will be exempted from penalties for today.
If more than three members notice it,
you'll be sent to the whale tour.
(They're punished if more than 3 notice it.)
Don't get playful and do something strange.
Don't do anything strange. Act natural, okay?
Honestly, I'm not good at hiding secrets.
Can you do it?
(They start their secret mission.)
- We can do it. - We can do it.
(This is how the hidden mission started.)
(Shall I give a Badge to Se Chan?)
(She pulled on Jong Kook.)
(She called out Se Chan's name.)
(How about Jae Seok this time?)
(Jong Kook hinted while pretending to look at Se Chan.)
(He called out Jae Seok while touching So Min's arm.)
(They've been acting naturally so far.)
Look at the people around you.
(Look at the people around me?)
(Grabbing)
- What? - I knew it was you.
Why me?
- Me? Why me? - You're the spy, right?
- It's not me. - It's him.
- Why me? Why? - I don't know what but it's him.
- What? - I'm sure it's him.
We don't know what it is but it's him.
It's Se Chan.
Pick a person who'll get a Tour Sticker.
It's Jae Seok.
- It's Jae Seok. - It's Jae Seok.
Why me?
- It has to be him. - Stop acting...
Stop acting like you're flustered. You're so shameless.
- I'm so flustered. - You screamed so it's over.
- I'm so flustered. - Anyhow, you...
- Let me say this. - It's your fault.
One of you will come with me.
I think it's kind of unfair for him.
- That's right. - This is my true opinion.
I agree.
Three people agreed it was unfair for me.
- Seok Jin... - I'm being honest.
I think it's unfair.
1 of us 3 will take the Sticker.
- That's a great idea. - Great.
(The penalty goes to the Unlucky Trio.)
One of us will take it.
- I agree. - We'll play Incorrect Times Table.
- All right. - The loser gets the sticker.
- You know the rules, right? - Yes.
The 10s have to be correct but the 1s have to be wrong.
3 times 9 is 24. Is this correct?
- Okay, I got it. - Okay.
- Set... - We'll give you the question.
- Incorrect Times Table - Incorrect Times Table
- 6 times 9 is? - 45
What?
- Hold on. - It has to be 50 something.
(That was wrong.)
You should have said 52.
- Is he done? - No way.
He's done.
He has to go.
(Seok Jin climbs to the top of the list within a day.)
- That was wrong. - It has to be after 50.
He's right after Se Chan.
- That's good. - This is great.
This is so unpredictable.
We don't know about Seok Jin.
- We have to conclude this today. - That's right.
(If you get 3 Stickers, you will be chosen to go.)
- Do you have to leave right away? - You must.
This can't be!
(Which member will go on the Dangerous Tour?)
Your delivery food is on the first floor.
- It's here? - Yes.
It's the dish the delivery man puts down first as soon as he comes in.
Okay.
(The owner of the first dish...)
(to be served gets a Sticker.)
- He's here. - Your food is here.
He'll come inside and put the food down.
There's not a lot of space so two of you can come forward.
We'll look.
He's here.
Please come in.
(They just hope it's not theirs.)
Here he comes.
He's here.
- It's a red steel box. - You can take them out here.
What if it's tangsuyuk?
It's coming. He opened the lid.
(If it's Se Chan or Seok Jin's food, they'll go on the tour right away.)
(Which dish will come out first?)
He opened the lid.
It's jaengban jjajang.
- Jaengban jjajang is number one. - It's Kwang Soo's.
(Kwang Soo is chosen.)
It's jaengban jjajang.
- It's jaengban jjajang. - Jaengban jjajang is number one.
(I think that was mine.)
- Stir-fried jjamppong is next. - That's second.
- Thank you. - Why isn't it tangsuyuk?
- Thank you, sir. - Excuse me.
- Don't you put it on the bottom? - Here comes jaengban jjajang.
Wait.
It's Kwang Soo!
Don't you usually put jaengban jjajang on the bottom?
(Kwang Soo is back to his unlucky self again.)
- It's Kwang Soo. - Jaengban jjajang is number one.
Don't you usually put it on the bottom?
I'm so happy with it.
- Thank you, sir. - Doesn't it go on the bottom?
(Kwang Soo accumulates another Tour Sticker.)
Jaengban jjajang, it is.
You must receive a text message within 3 minutes...
that's longer than 10 syllables.
- That's the mission. - I got it.
- I got it too. - I got it from Ryu Hyun Jin.
- I got it from Hwang Je Seong. - I got so many.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Kwang Soo are the losers.
- Are you serious? - You got nothing?
You think this is unfair?
Give me the roulette. There's something more important than this.
The Tour Sticker...
I can't lose, right?
If we get Kwang Soo, he'll surpass me again.
I hope it's 1 of you 2.
It usually lands on Kwang Soo.
No, that's not true. I didn't get the ice shower.
- Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok. - Kwang Soo.
- I have to write your name again. - That's not fair.
It can't be helped.
(This wasn't intentional.)
- There should be a pass. - I did it in order.
How can my name be on there twice in a row?
Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok. Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok.
- Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok. - It could have been flipped.
Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok. Then it's you again.
So it's Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and Jae Seok?
Make it a dud.
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and Jae Seok?
- Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok. - You have a chance.
Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok. And then...
Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and Jae Seok.
(So it's Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and Jae Seok.)
(Why are you doing this to me?)
It's Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo, Seok Jin then Jae Seok.
It's Kwang Soo, Seok Jin then Jae Seok.
We can't do anything about it.
Fine. Let's do this then.
- There are six people. - Right.
This is different, right?
(He fills Kwang Soo's name in 2 spaces.)
- Hold on. - Right?
- Okay. - Are you happy?
- Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok. - Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok.
(They explain the logic to Kwang Soo again.)
- Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok. - Kwang Soo!
(It's a big Kwang Soo.)
- Are you happy? - It's good.
- It's fine. - Let's go.
- You'll get lucky. - I'll overcome it.
What if he gets picked?
I'll do it. I'll overcome it.
- Should I spin it? - Okay.
- Go ahead. - Okay.
- He's good to go. - Here I come.
- He's neutral. - If it's Seok Jin, he leaves.
- Please. - Jong Kook.
If it's Seok Jin, he leaves right away?
If it's Jae Seok, he'll have two Tour Stickers.
- No! - I'll overcome it.
(The dangerous roulette has spun.)
It's Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, Jae Seok.
(If it lands on Seok Jin, he'll be the first person to go on the tour.)
(What will be their fates?)
It's Seok Jin.
(It lands on Seok Jin.)
- Really? It's over now. - Is it?
(Seok Jin is the 1st.)
(He's the biggest coward.)
All of this in a day?
(Seok Jin collapses.)
(Raging)
This can't be!
I think...
Is this possible?
- How is this possible? - Really?
This is not possible.
(He has three Tour Stickers.)
(2017 Running Man's Global Project)
(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by bloggers)
How is this possible?
This is impossible.
(Seok Jin is the first to go.)
This mission is called Dangerous Spoon.
Each member will flick the spoon...
one at a time and try to get it...
in the cup. That's the mission.
I'll go first.
- If you get it in, you're our hero. - Challenge.
(I'm the hero.)
(Flicking)
Okay. I failed.
So...
all of you fail.
- How is this possible? - This is really hard.
Is this even possible?
- The mission should be reasonable. - It's difficult.
- You're next. - This is impossible.
- No way. - It's you.
- It's you or Jae Seok. - Does it have to go in?
(So Min, pick Jae Seok or Kwang Soo.)
Jae Seok?
(She says it right in front of him.)
- I think... - Jae Seok?
I think the chance of him going...
Why are you looking at me?
How is this even possible?
(That was too obvious, So Min.)
All right. The Whale Badge...
- goes to Jae Seok. - It's Kwang Soo.
Really?
- Why is it him? I'm curious. - It's you?
Why is it you? Do you have a clue?
(Jae Seok gets a Whale Badge.)
This...
(They told me to look around,)
(and what I just saw was a bit strange.)
Do you know what you did?
- Try to think. - I think...
- I know. - Hold on. A little while ago...
I keep...
- I'm not sure if I'm right. - It can't be correct, right?
He can't get the No Tour Card.
I'm going to drink some water.
(What now?)
(Jae Seok seems to have caught on. Is this the end of Kook-Min's Pick?)
Are you asking for a favor?
- All right. - No, I...
As I have mentioned earlier,
if you find out the hidden rule,
- you're free from all penalties. - All of them?
- What about your Tour Stickers? - Not those, right?
- Not your Tour Stickers. - Not them?
It doesn't matter for you.
I won't get the Whale Badge.
(Did Jae Seok guess the hidden rule?)
- Jae Seok is correct. - Really?
(Jae Seok is correct.)
I'm right?
Jong Kook and So Min...
are working on a mission together.
She said my name, and I got picked.
(He guessed the rule correctly.)
- Jae Seok is correct. - Really?
(Really?)
I'm right? Okay!
(Roaring)
It was you two, right?
(He calls them out.)
(What did he just say?)
(Did he just disclose everything?)
If three or more guess it right, you'll get the penalty.
- No way. - We can't.
Just be natural. Play the games.
It was you two, right?
- What is he doing? - It was them two.
(He's spoiling it for everybody.)
(What is he doing?)
- What are you doing? - What is he doing?
What are you doing?
- What is he doing? - What's wrong with you?
(The staff members panic.)
- What is it? - You see...
I don't know what he's talking about.
Wait.
When missions are done,
Jong Kook and So Min...
(Haha finally catches on.)
- Haha is correct. - Okay.
Why did you ruin everything?
- I had no idea. - What?
He has to go on the tour.
He ruined everything.
What is it? I don't get it.
- He has to go. - I had no idea.
Was he accurate? Even the details?
He was very detailed.
- Jong Kook and So Min. - Even the details?
He doesn't know.
Jong Kook and So Min are the spies.
- They're the spies. - I had no idea.
- I had no idea. - Let me do this.
Jae Seok is correct.
Haha was 70 to 80 percent correct. He was close,
- so I'll give him that. - Okay!
- These two got it correct. - Really?
The rest of you have no clue,
so only those two will be exempted.
- Okay. - What is it?
(Jong Kook and So Min won't get Whale Badges either.)
The four of us got the mission correct.
So for now, Ji Hyo has no Whale Badge,
- and we each have one. - It'll be 2 out of 3.
The person without the Whale Badge can go.
- Because... - So this is how it is.
- Ji Hyo, you have no Whale Badge. - Right.
- Come forward. - Why?
- You can't do that. - You can't do that.
I said the person with the most number of Whale Badges is the loser.
- I know it's right but... - Right.
Let go.
- Let go and talk. - "Let go."
- She can pick the person, right? - She can.
- She won't get the penalty. - She can pick one...
- but we have to pick the loser. - Wait.
I'm sick of picking.
I won't pick this time.
- He's intimidated. - One of us doesn't...
- Everyone stand back. - have to pick.
One of us doesn't have to go, right?
Don't touch it. Just pick one.
The person who'll go on the whale-watching ferry tomorrow...
Do rock, paper, scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
(They're betting their lives on it.)
- Okay. - Yes!
- Make sure you open it. - I got this.
- In one... We have no time. - I'm going crazy.
- Don't. Give me time. - One.
Whales, here I come.
In 12 hours,
(It takes 5 hours to get there. There isn't much time left.)
- Let's go catch a whale - One.
- Bye, Kwang Soo. - No!
- 1, 2... - Please, Kwang Soo.
Please let it be him.
(Please don't get unlucky again.)
(Would Kwang Soo avoid the whales?)
- Kwang Soo. - Three.
Yes!
(There's no Whale Badge?)
- Goodness. - Yes!
(Kwang Soo survives.)
Se Chan is next.
You're next.
- He's the rising icon of bad luck. - Yes.
He's the super rookie bad luck.
(This is a big match between new and old unlucky members.)
You can open it together.
Seok Jin, you can open it right after Se Chan.
- I'll pick this one. - All right.
If Kwang Soo gets picked to tag along...
(He'll be going to Ulsan if he gets picked to tag along.)
(Why would you mention that now?)
Get ready.
You know how it goes.
- Ready. - 1, 2...
(In 12 hours, 1 person will be standing by the sea in Ulsan.)
(This is a close match between the unluckiest members.)
(Who's the unluckiest one between them?)
Three.
(It's Seok Jin.)
(He's impossible to beat.)
I got lucky.
(He got 3 Tour Stickers, and he gets to go on whale-watching ferry.)
- This is insane. - He's going on the tour too.
- He's going on the tour... - He's definitely...
- and the whale-watching ferry. - excited today.
(This is his unluckiest day of all.)
Seok Jin...
can take one person out of Kwang Soo, Se Chan and Ji Hyo.
Seok Jin will give the Whale Badge to one person.
Why aren't you looking at him,
- Kwang Soo? - Pardon?
- It's not me. - Why aren't you looking at me?
I feel bad for Se Chan. You even got your house taken away.
- I gave everything I have. - Gosh.
(Hold on. Who shall I go with?)
(Should I pick Se Chan because he annoyed me all day?)
(He was being annoying.)
(Or should I pick Ji Hyo because she was being curt?)
(Can you let go of my hand?)
(Or should I pick Kwang Soo because he's always nasty?)
(Stop bothering me.)
(He always talks so much whenever I'm being made fun of.)
- I gave everything I have. - Gosh.
I'm going on the tour for sure, right?
- Yes. - You are.
You're going to Japan and the whale-watching ferry.
(There's nothing to be confused about.)
What did you say?
(Do you want to go too?)
Seok Jin.
He didn't clip it on yet.
- He didn't clip it on yet. - He's not supposed to do it.
(Kissing)
(I'll only take your kindness.)
Rip your shirt.
- If he clips it on, it's over. - Seok Jin.
(Are you being serious?)
(He didn't filter out his choice of words.)
It's Kwang Soo.
(He gets the badge.)
It's Kwang Soo and Seok Jin.
They'll be heading to the seas of Ulsan.
- Go! - Go!
You would have picked me too.
This concludes today's missions.
Seok Jin and Kwang Soo will be going on the whale-watching ferry.
- That's the final decision. - This is our day.
(He's going out of his mind.)
- Feel-Chok cross! - Feel-Chok cross!
I get to on the tour and watch the whales as well.
If you don't see the whales, Kwang Soo gets a Tour Sticker.
- Wait. If we don't see the whales? - Okay. Please.
Hide, whales.
- I've never seen whales in my life. - Hide, whales.
Is it possible to see them?
I said it before. There's 20 percent chance.
- Have you seen whales before? - No.
Are there whales in Korea?
- This is our king. - It's the king.
- Let's worship him. - Let's worship him.
- Let's worship Kwang Soo. - Let's worship him.
I'll be trapped inside for three hours, and if I don't see a whale,
I'll be dropped from the sky or get haunted by a ghost?
- This is a true story. - This is a true story.
I'm going to make sure I see it.
(Would they be able to avoid the tour?)
(Next day 5am in Jangsaengpo, Ulsan)
Good morning.
(He's exhausted.)
I can't stop laughing.
What time is it right now?
It's 5am.
(It took five hours from Seoul to get here.)
Hurry up.
(Kwang Soo looks annoyed.)
Hello. Hi.
Kwang Soo didn't do anything wrong.
I dragged you here.
Seok Jin, you have three Tour Stickers...
and Kwang Soo, you have two.
If you think about it,
- I'm here because of you... - I'm sorry.
and if I don't see the whales, I might go on the tour because of you.
You ruined my life.
Hey, we have to see the whales.
- Did you hear? - What?
You can see them 2 out of 10 times.
I've never seen any whales since I've watched "Free Willy" as a kid.
Drink it.
Let's go. Let's see it.
- I hope we can see it. - I really want to see it.
- Hello. - Hello.
If you go out to the sea, do you usually see them?
We don't actually see them too often.
You need luck.
(We need luck?)
We have no luck.
How recent was the last time you saw one?
- She saw one. - It was April 12.
- On April 12? - Yes.
- They remember the exact date... - Hey.
because it's precious to them.
They sail out every day...
- but it's meaningful to them too. - Why would you say that?
- Let's get on. - My gosh.
- Whales... - This is so big.
- Isn't this like a movie? - It's huge.
- There's an observatory here. - Second floor is nice too.
Imagine seeing a whale.
- It'll be right in front of us. - It'll be here.
They'll be here right in front of us.
- It'll be no joke. - It feels so unrealistic.
Whales, please...
(I'm quite serious today, whales.)
We have to see one today.
(The ferry takes three hours. It heads out to see the whales.)
- You haven't had breakfast, right? - No.
- Would you like some noodles? - Give us some food.
- Really? - They taste great on ferries.
They taste great.
- Can I have one? - I was hoping for one.
I did think about it earlier.
- It tastes the best. - It tastes great on ferries.
(They gobble it down.)
(It's amazing.)
It's so good.
(They're happy with just noodles.)
This will be a happy ending only if we see the whales.
Then,
if we see a large 20m whale,
can you take a Tour Sticker from us?
You can do that.
- Of course you can. - How many people do you think...
- saw a 20m whale in Korea? - You can see it every few years.
It'll be a miracle.
- It's impossible. - If you see a 20m whale,
it's still 3 and 2.
(That's the producer's answer.)
What about 50m?
If it's 50m, we'll take it off.
It can also be three 20m whales.
(Why does it feel like this negotiation is a fail?)
It's the size of this ferry?
- 3 of them. - 3 of them.
- What about a 10m whale jumps... - Your Tour Stickers...
and makes a heart with its fins?
- Like this? - Yes, like this.
Let's do this. We'll divide it up.
If we see a 50m whale, we'll take Seok Jin's sticker away.
If we see 3 20m whales, we'll take Kwang Soo's away.
- You're going to divide it up. - Yes.
Do you know how rare the chances are? Why would you divide it up?
- You should just give it to us. - You're so cruel.
Is this necessary?
- Did you see him giggle? - Do you think they can do this?
- Come on. - Is that even possible?
There's a chance we'll see a 50m whale. Who wants to take that one?
- Me. Please. - I'll take it.
I got dragged here.
- Me. - I suggested it. I'll take it.
Please put your hands down.
Who wants to take the 50m whale?
- Me. - Me. I was faster.
- Me. He didn't say anything. - I stood up.
- Sir. - It's Kwang Soo.
- Okay. 50m whale? - What's your standard?
He was faster.
- I stood up. - Kwang Soo gets the 50m whale.
- It's three 20m whales for me? - I'll give you that.
- You'll take away a Tour Sticker? - I will.
(They're going beyond Guinness World Records.)
I'll show you.
(30 minutes later)
(An hour later)
(An hour and a half later)
(They must sail back in 30 minutes.)
I have a bad feeling about this.
Gosh.
(If they don't see whales, they'll see sharks,)
(ghosts or crocodiles.)
What if we can't see them?
(Where are you, whales?)
This...
This is an announcement.
There's a pod of whales on in the front of the ferry.
Where?
(There's a pod of whales?)
- Let me repeat. - Where?
- Where? - Where?
Do you see the fishing boat? They are near that boat.
I see them.
There they are!
(There's a whale in front of them.)
It's a whale!
- It's jumping. - It's jumping.
- It's coming here. - I see it.
- I see it. This is awesome. - It's coming.
- Over there. - You see it, right?
Sir.
- There are about 500 of them. - Look at that.
No!
There are 6,000 of them.
No. Look at that!
Hey!
(Thrilled)
- Guys! - Move ship backward!
- Look! - Move ship backward!
- They're whales. - This is unbelievable.
- Look at that. - Guys.
(They can't believe what's in front of their eyes.)
My camera can't capture them.
(The scene is breathtaking.)
Look at that.
- This is crazy. - I can't believe this.
(They approach the ship.)
Look at that.
- Please stop the ship! - The whales are here.
- This is amazing. - This is not computer graphics.
This is not computer graphics.
This is unbelievable. Look at that.
(They're awed by the nature.)
- They're so close. - This is amazing.
- This might seem unreal... - The whales are dancing.
You have to film them.
- Film the whales. - You don't have to film me.
If I jump off the ship now, I'd land on a whale's back.
They're that close.
- Where are they? - Guys.
- They're right here. - Where?
(They can't contain the excitement.)
- The whales are following us. - They're following us.
- This is so exciting. - Guys.
I'll go to the other side of the ship.
Guys.
(Kwang Soo bumps into a chair.)
(He was blinded by the excitement.)
I'm okay.
Don't film me, film the whales.
(He's giving up the camera for the whales.)
Don't film me. I'm okay.
(Leave me here.)
Look at that!
(They're excited at the whale's dance.)
This is a breathtaking scene.
This is real.
We have to go back to the port now.
We're turning the ship.
- What are you talking about? - What?
(Are we going back?)
We can't!
(They have to say goodbye to the whales.)
I was a whale in my past life.
Leave me here. My family is here.
- Calm down. - My family is here.
- Calm down. - I can't.
(Kwang Soo, we're waiting for you.)
- Everyone. - Are your knees okay?
(I'm a whale.)
My jacket has the whale color.
(He's sending ultrasonic waves to his family.)
(My family and friends,)
(can you hear me?)
Kwang Soo, calm down.
- Well... - Yes.
Seok Jin and Kwang Soo...
succeeded in spotting whales, which happens only 20 percent of the time.
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin completed the whale-watching mission.)
- Thank you, Kwang Soo. - My pleasure.
- Whale! - Whale!
(We love you, whales.)
- You'll be given a No Tour Card... - Give us five dollars.
and...
(The whale mission is not over yet.)
(This is only the beginning.)
(Next week)
(Another mission is given.)
(What is the secret behind the whale-watching tour?)
(And)
(Dangerous Tourist Attractions)
(Global Race)
(Who will be sent to the Dangerous Tourist Attraction?)
(The final competition to avoid the dangerous trip)
(Avoid the dangerous trip if you can.)
(It's unpredictable.)
(The result is unexpected.)
(Soon)
(The destination will be determined.)
(Running Man's Global Project coming soon)