(2017 Running Man's Second Global Project)
People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent.
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(The member with 3 I Go Stickers will go to a place for 1 percent...)
(with a member they choose to go with.)
(As a result of the first race, the die chose...)
(Haha and So Min to receive a Sticker each.)
(As a result of the second race, Seok Jin got a Sticker.)
(Currently, Seok Jin, Haha, and So Min have 1 I Go Sticker each.)
(And the mysterious people arrive.)
- It's Tae Hwan. - It's Jin Young!
(Lee Tae Hwan, Hong Jin Young)
(Son Yeo Eun, Na Eun, Ha Young)
(Famous celebrities join Running Man as guests.)
(She shows off her dance in Gyeongju...)
(which has brought huge attention online.)
(It's Son Na Eun with an unexpected charm.)
(And this man falls straight in love with her.)
(He's shy, but he'll take courage to take a step closer to her.)
(He has found his love in Gyeongju.)
(Stay tuned to find out if his love will come true.)
That was amazing.
- She's attractive. - She became even more charming.
It's hard to dance in high heels.
She looked very charming when she did this.
Can you do it again?
- Do you mean this? - Yes. Move the side.
- That's great. - That's great.
Isn't that a dance for Deux's "Look Back at Me"?
(Is it a dance for "Look Back at Me"?)
Gosh, he is old.
- Look back at yourself. - Psy must've liked...
the dance for "Look Back at Me".
What is wrong with your makeup?
What do you mean?
For goodness' sake.
I look the same whether I wear makeup or not.
Come to Jin Young.
- Jin Young can fix your makeup. - That's right.
Why are you so chatty today?
She is a strong woman.
- Step back. - I mean...
Okay.
- She is good. - She is a strong woman.
She is a strong woman.
- Please keep Jong Kook in check. - We have things in order.
We have things in order.
- That was nice. - I knew it.
Jin Young is the only one who can do that.
Jin Young and Moon Sook.
They are male and female gangsters.
- I was only making an example. - Kwang Soo.
I meant that the two of you are like a couple.
Don't say that.
Jong Kook is a male gangster.
(He goes over the fact.)
- What are you talking about? - It is true.
Don't be ridiculous.
Haha.
Should I button or unbutton my shirt?
- Unbutton it. - Does that look better?
(Fiddling)
- He is driving me crazy. - Why?
"Should I button or unbutton my shirt?"
You should take off your shirt.
- No. - Why don't you take it off?
Here is what I think.
I don't know if it's possible, but it would look best...
if you can button the shirt and remove your body.
(The shirt isn't the problem.)
This shirt is pretty.
This shirt is very pretty.
- I am serious. - The atmosphere is nice today.
(The atmosphere is nice today.)
You are laughing hard at the smallest things.
- I am happy. - I know.
The opening is going smoothly today.
I was very tired because I couldn't sleep last night.
You still feel happy.
I don't care about the ratings for this episode.
I am very happy.
(Ratings fade with time, )
(but our memories will be forever.)
Your happiness and the bad ratings will cancel the program.
(A program with bad ratings is bound to be canceled.)
- Why would you say that? - We still need good ratings.
- Let's go. - For goodness' sake.
- That's how happy I am. - Okay.
Pull yourself together and commit to the shoot.
- Your words scared me. - Let's not get too excited.
After Na Eun...
is the youngest member of Apink,
- Ha Young. - Ha Young.
Oh Ha Young.
Ha Young, this is...
- your first visit to Running Man. - This is my first visit.
That's right.
We recently went to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
- I heard that you went there. - Really?
- I went there alone. - What?
(How did she go there alone?)
Did you go there alone?
(Ha Young, you and I have a similarity.)
Kwang Soo, come back here.
I went alone, too.
People who went alone share a connection.
Shaking hands is not allowed...
- before you partner up. - Don't do it.
It's foul play.
- You know, - You need to stop.
I don't think I deserve a punch for a handshake.
He punched me in the face.
Jong Kook, take him to the back.
- I mean... - Teach him a lesson.
- I mean... - What do you think you are doing?
Wasn't it scary to be alone at Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear?
- You went with a cameraman. - Right.
I held a camera and went inside by myself.
Didn't you scream?
I screamed,
but it wasn't very scary because I knew they were people.
That's incredible. She is brave.
We knew they were people, too.
How long did it take for you to come out?
It took me about 30 minutes.
- She only spent 30 minutes. - That's fast.
It's annoying to see her brag.
What does that make us?
I don't know if you knew,
- but Ha Young can read minds. - Can she read minds?
- She has talent in mind reading. - Yes, I do.
- Can you read minds? - Yes, I can.
That's scary.
That's a bit scary.
Would you read a member's mind?
What is Se Chan thinking?
(Ha Young, can you read my mind?)
(Let's see.)
He is very nervous right now.
- Why? - Why?
It's because he saw us women.
(Thinking hard)
- Okay. - Who is making him nervous?
- We can guess that much. - Who wouldn't be able to do that?
Wait a minute.
In that case, would you read a staff member's mind?
His legs are hurting.
He is sitting down.
Do your legs hurt?
No.
(No)
They will hurt.
Is she cursing him?
- He says his legs don't hurt. - Are you cursing him?
You said that his legs will hurt.
- It's not like that. - Okay.
Anyway,
since she is on the show for the first time,
we hope she will enjoy her time with us.
It's good to have her here.
We have another celebrity who is the talk of the town.
Lee Sun Bin.
(Lee Sun Bin)
(It's Sun Bin.)
Sun Bin,
you said that Kwang Soo was your ideal type.
Kwang Soo actually paid you a visit.
(Last fall, Kwang Soo verified her claim.)
("My ideal type really is Lee Kwang Soo.")
(Yes, it's the truth.)
(The truth was revealed.)
(False)
(Sun Bin's claim only left a scar in Kwang Soo's heart.)
I know.
I felt so dejected that day...
that I couldn't sleep.
All right.
Do you still have feelings for Kwang Soo?
(Does she still have feelings for him?)
- Of course. - Really?
Yes.
(Is Sun Bin's ideal type still Kwang Soo?)
Please give me the lie detector.
Do we have it? Did you bring it?
Did you bring it?
It's pretty accurate.
(A lie detector appears.)
(Flustered)
I tried to hold back that time, but I felt like I was dying.
- You tried to hold back? - Yes.
I hope it goes well.
I am serious.
Me, too.
If she is serious, you won't have to look elsewhere.
(Sun Bin, tell me how you feel.)
Please answer when I ask you a question.
- Kwang Soo has feelings for her. - Right.
"I am still interested in Kwang Soo."
Yes.
(To Kwang Soo, who has always sought after love, )
(Sun Bin expresses her interest.)
- That's cool. - I hope it's true.
(Is her answer true?)
(True)
- It's true. - Really?
(My goodness, it's true.)
Fine. Take this away.
(I don't like this lie detector.)
Jae Seok, how can you finish it that way?
How can you finish it that way?
- Kwang Soo should go. - Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo should go. - For goodness' sake.
- Kwang Soo should go. - I am confident.
- He means his words. - That's right.
He has feelings for her.
Let's go.
- I will ask you one question. - Okay.
- Look her in the face. - Answer the question.
- All right. - Look at Sun Bin.
(It's his chance to show her his heart.)
(Sun Bin, I will show you my heart.)
"Today,."
"I like my outfit."
(Today, I like my outfit.)
Answer the question.
- Answer the question. - Go ahead.
- There is one question. - Yes.
Let's see if it's true.
It's true.
Is that it? Is that it?
That's it.
Why would you be curious about that?
I like my outfit, okay?
All right.
Both of them spoke the truth.
- They like each other. - Congratulations.
Congratulations.
(Will it really end this way?)
The next guest is...
Son Yeo Eun.
(Son Yeo Eun)
Also known as Ha Eun's mom.
The thing is,
she resembles So Min.
Do people tell you that often?
Yes, they do. So Min is always present...
- among the related keywords. - I see.
Son Na Eun is also there since her name is similar.
- I see. - Jeon So Min, too,
- Yeo Eun has a specialty. - What is it?
She has the perfect pitch.
(Does she have the perfect pitch?)
(I said that, didn't I?)
She is a bit like So Min.
I think she will get it wrong.
She majored in piano.
(She majored in piano at a university.)
Then she would know.
Even if she doesn't have the perfect pitch,
piano majors get tested on the musical notes.
She can play the piano very well.
- She can probably play it. - You can play it, right?
- Yes. - Please play something.
I haven't played the melodica in a long time.
She can move her fingers very quickly.
Hold the melodica.
- What is there to play? - You can play anything...
- you are comfortable with. - My mind is blank.
"The School Bell".
(Is she asking a piano major to play "The School Bell"?)
What is she talking about?
Who doesn't know how to play it?
So Min, even I can play "The School Bell".
Can you play Chopin?
(Yeo Eun begins to play "Nocturne Op. 9 No. 2".)
It's Chopin.
- It's Chopin. - She is really playing Chopin.
(Breathing)
She has shortness of breath.
She doesn't have a big lung capacity.
(She ends the impromptu performance with a reddened face.)
Chopin!
She is good.
Does she have the perfect pitch?
It's finally the time to introduce Hong Jin Young.
She is...
the queen of events.
- She is the queen of trot. - That's right.
Hong Jin Young!
- I love her. - She makes you happy.
- You composed "Ring Ring". - That's right.
The version you sang with Young Chul...
became a hit.
We are receiving a lot of love.
- That's right. - The reaction is nice.
Is there another song you composed?
Yes, there is.
- What is it? - I originally intended...
to give "Ring Ring" to Heo Kyung Hwan.
He missed his opportunity.
- I wrote another song for him. - You wrote another song.
Why do you write songs for Kyung Hwan?
Is there something between you and him?
(They act like they aren't, but they're curious in fact.)
Well, I promised to give him a song,
but he missed the song due to the voting result.
In a sense, he kicked his luck away himself, right?
So the song title is "I Kicked My Luck Away".
(It's called "I Kicked My Luck Away".)
(That was such a natural way to introduce the song.)
- "I Kicked My Luck Away". - I see.
- Can you sing a little for us? - Sing us the melody of it.
(I kicked my luck away)
(Bouncing to the rhythm)
You can dance right to it.
(That sounds so familiar.)
(They're speechless.)
You're helpless.
It feels a bit like Jo Hye Ryun too.
(It's very familiar.)
- Exactly. - Jo Hye Ryun.
It's exactly like her.
- Not long ago... - I kicked my luck away.
Not long ago, my aunt...
danced exactly the same at her 60th birthday party.
I'm being serious.
- It's exactly the same. - She's a girl of different colors.
I'm serious.
(They begin the race with these charming girls.)
People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent.
The 3rd race is called Number 1 Couple Race.
(Number 1 Couple Race)
The mission money will be crucial in winning this race today as well.
It's about I Go Stickers, right?
Right, it's about I Go Stickers.
- I almost forgot. - Me too.
A couple who has the most amount of money at the end will win the race.
They'll be exempted from receiving a Sticker,
and they'll get to throw the die.
Also, a guest in the winning team...
will receive a pair of golden rings.
(A guest who wins the race will earn a pair of golden rings.)
(Motivated)
All right. Now, before we move onto the race,
you'll first decide your partner in this mission.
Each of the seven girls have told us...
a keyword of the competition in which they're the best.
Male members will decide their partners...
only by looking at these keywords...
and choosing one of them.
After you find your partners,
the girls will compete to prove their keywords.
If they do win first place in the competition they mentioned,
corresponding couples will earn...
extra 10 dollars for their mission money.
Let's be on our toes.
- Can I go wash my face? - Let's do this.
(They have only one chance in deciding their partners.)
Let's see the keywords.
"Best Hands", "Best Cuteness", "Best Eyes",
"Best Waist", "Best Magnet",
and "Best Dance".
I should say, Best Magnet is...
Best Waist"?
Who could Best Punch be? Is it Jin Young?
(Is Jin Young's keyword "Best Punch"?)
- Who could be Best Waist? - Best Waist.
- They all have small waists. - I know.
I see several of what I should avoid.
What are they?
(It's better to partner up with someone new.)
You can go ahead and choose your partners now.
I'll go with Best Hands.
- Why are you... - Goodness.
Best Hands.
If you're done choosing,
hide and reveal them one by one.
It caught my eyes, so I chose this.
I think it's either of the two.
Who are the two?
I assume it's either Sun Bin...
or Na Eun. That's what I think.
I'll reveal my choice now.
I chose Best Dance.
- Who is it? - It must be So Min.
A girl whose keyword is Best Dance is...
Please come on out!
It's Yeo Eun!
(Yeo Eun comes out unexpectedly.)
(It's me.)
- It's you? - Really?
- It's you? - Well...
- This is unexpected. - Is she really good at dancing?
Are you really good at dancing?
You told this keyword yourself, right?
Well... I...
I learned how to do modern dance in the past.
Then we should check it out.
- We can't miss out. - She was hiding her charm.
It's your turn, Haha.
I thought of choosing this right away when I saw this keyword.
I too was going to choose it, but then...
I could sense whose keyword it was. It sounds so absurd, you see.
(Who's behind this absurd keyword?)
Whose keyword is Best Magnet?
Please come on out.
(Who's Best Magnet?)
(It's So Min.)
Hey, what's wrong? Why aren't you happy?
Why aren't you happy?
(Yes, my partner is Haha!)
It's So Min.
(Surprised and disappointed)
All right, Haha and So Min are a couple.
We'll check on her keyword later.
I'm just being curious,
but aren't you going to switch your choices?
(Aren't you going to switch your choices?)
Do you want us to?
- I mean... - Well...
- Is something wrong? - I'm not sure who it is,
- but she doesn't like her partner. - It must be Best Eyes, right?
This has never happened before.
Why did you ask this suddenly?
Why?
I was just wondering.
You're being very straightforward.
It's usually hard to be this straightforward.
Not many people express like this.
Maybe she really hates her partner.
It's not what I meant. I'm just wondering...
I don't know who it will be, but that person must be very upset.
She'd rather go to the Labyrinth alone.
She thinks he's scarier than ghosts.
I think it's you, Se Chan.
- It's you. - Is it me?
Whom do you want to change his choice?
(Can you be a little more specific?)
(They're all nervous.)
I'd like Seok Jin to change his choice.
(Seok Jin, please change your choice.)
- I'm with this until the end. - You're doomed.
- Don't even think about it. - You're completely doomed.
- It's hilarious. - It's funny.
I was going to change my choice, but now, I'll never do it.
We're not sure whose keyword it is yet.
- We're not sure yet. - Right, it's not me.
- Tell me about it. - We'll find out later.
Next is...
- Se Chan. - Let's see the end of it today.
All of you look very depressed to find out what my choice is.
It's not a penalty, you see.
If what you said is true, the one with the most depressed face is...
Na Eun among them.
Na Eun is grinding her teeth now.
- She's... - She doesn't look very happy.
If it's really Na Eun, play the song for her.
If it turns out she really is his partner,
- please play "New Face" for her. - Sounds good.
- All right. - It can't be.
Whose keyword is Best Waist? Please come on out!
(She confidently volunteered to be the Best Waist.)
- Whose keyword is Best Waist? - Please.
- Please come on out! - No way.
Why isn't anyone coming out?
(Who is the one with this keyword?)
- Who... - Wait!
(It's really Na Eun.)
(He's excited to find out it's Na Eun.)
Let's dance together.
(He's so excited that his dance becomes gross.)
(Se Chan and Na Eun are a couple.)
Yes! It's great!
This is it!
I guess Gyeongju goes so well with me.
- Hey, it's only you who faced her. - What?
- Na Eun was facing over there. - She didn't look at me?
You didn't?
- All right, please come this way. - Goodness.
- It's amazing. - What if they measure...
and it turns out she isn't first place?
What will happen then?
They won't receive the extra money.
- But they're still a couple. - Yes.
- It won't be changed? - It's set.
Do we stay with one partner until the end?
(She's desperate.)
Ha Young, stop it.
- I'm sorry, - Stop it already.
But we're not here to be actual couples.
We're here to play games as teams.
(Endure for 8 hours, and it'll be done.)
We don't do love relationships these days.
(Will she be able to go against her fate?)
- All right, Se Chan. - Yes.
- I'm so happy. - I see.
- Hello? - Hello?
Is it true that Na Eun's next to you?
It's a fact.
- Really? - It's true.
I'm going to be a romantic guy today.
I'll be in love in Gyeongju today.
- It's a fact. - It's for certain.
It's great.
Next up is Jong Kook.
- Let's see who's his partner. - Who will it be?
It's Best Cuteness.
- Best Cuteness. - "You."
Jong Kook, you!
- You! - Goodness.
I'm going to you!
It's you?
(He's given up now.)
It's the end? Is it really her?
Just like this?
- Smile. - Okay.
- It's the end. - Really?
- She told me to smile. - Yes, smile.
- She told me to. - Next up is Tae Hwan.
- Yes. - Which keyword did you choose?
I chose Best Hands.
- Best Hands! - We can easily guess...
- who it is right away. - Of course.
- That's why I chose this keyword. - Really?
(Touched)
Best Hands!
(Tae Hwan's partner is Ji Hyo.)
- Good. - I'm envious!
- Good for you! - You're envious? I'm so happy.
Look at you. You're wearing matching clothes.
You three look like Marronnier who sang "Cocktail Love".
(They're like Marronnier who sang "Cocktail Love".)
(Excited)
- Tae Hwan doesn't know the song. - You don't?
He doesn't know at all.
(Stop it. He doesn't know that song.)
- Goodness. - Why don't you know?
- He has no idea. - My goodness.
(What's the name of the song again?)
- Tae Hwan doesn't know the song. - You don't?
Gosh, it's so upsetting.
You really don't know this song?
- I've heard of it. - On a gloomy day.
He was like, "What are they doing?"
- Gosh. - It's so sad.
- It is, right? - Goodness.
But you're just like Marronnier.
(Tae Hwan and Ji Hyo are a couple.)
Finally, next up is...
The two of you remain coincidently.
You said you're not Best Eyes, right?
I'm not.
Then you'll be a couple with Kwang Soo.
Sun Bin will be Seok Jin's partner accordingly.
Sure!
Kwang Soo, you've become so reserved all of a sudden.
You're really being serious today.
Sun Bin isn't talking much either.
If they become a couple, we can call this fate.
Ha Young, smile.
(She acts like she's okay.)
All right. We have Best Eyes and Best Punch left.
Please move to your partners now.
(They will go toward their partners at the same time.)
(Eyes will be Seok Jin's partner, and Punch will be Kwang Soo's.)
Please go ahead!
(Where will these girls go to?)
Can I decide not to go?
(Can I play alone without a partner?)
- That's too much. - Where will you go then?
Where will you go?
(Seok Jin and Ha Young are a couple.)
- To me. - All right.
Seok Jin and Ha Young are a team, and so is Kwang Soo and Sun Bin!
Please come this way.
Kwang Soo!
They're doing this like it's real.
(For today, he's really in love.)
(Shy)
- It's been a while. - I know. How have you been?
Great, thanks.
(They aim to make memories instead of winning the race.)
(They're done deciding their partners now.)
Now, you've all became couples.
Looking at the keywords,
if you think your partner is better at it,
you can shout "Challenge" and have a battle to verify the keywords.
Let's start with Yeo Eun first. What kind of dance will you do?
I will express my name with a choreography of modern dance.
(Her dance expressing her name already gained attention on KBS.)
(It was the ultimate, dreamy dance.)
Then can you express Seok Jin's...
name in your dance? Please express his name.
(It's my name.)
When she moves forward, she walks elegantly.
She'll dance to this sad song?
What is that? What just happened?
(Her legs moved like a wave.)
(This is the dreamy dance of expressing Seok Jin's name.)
She did modern dance.
(This is the dreamy, modern dance.)
She looks serious too.
This is how modern dances are.
Everyone, now look at the name she'll express.
She will write Seok Jin's name.
She didn't write it yet.
Here she goes. She started.
That's "J".
(The dancing signature has begun.)
She just wrote "J".
- She's writing "I" next. - There it is.
- That makes "Jee". - "Jee".
But isn't this a bit scary?
I didn't know I would get to see this again here.
This is starting to scare me now.
- She just turned. Goodness. - I saw this last year.
(He's trembling.)
She is like So Min. She is indeed.
She is similar to So Min.
- I completely agree. - Oh, my.
But everyone can figure out which letter she's writing though.
(Squeaky)
What was that?
(What's up with her leg?)
- What was that? - What was that?
Don't dogs pee like that?
- No, they don't. - I think they do.
She just put a period. She's letting us know it's over.
- A period? - She was putting a period.
(Her spirit of art begins to heighten.)
(She puts a period powerfully.)
(Who will beat her in the dance battle?)
- You all saw her dance, right? - We will challenge her.
- Let's get the next one. - Jin Young.
- Why did you say it like that? - Let's challenge the next one.
Let's do the next one. No, Jin Young. Let's not.
- Let's do the next one. - Then I will challenge this one.
We can challenge the next one.
- I'll do that too. Don't worry. - You'll challenge every battle?
"If you want me to do it, I won't."
- "I'll do if you don't want me to." - Okay. Let's try this.
Whose name will you write?
- I'll write Jong Kook's. - All right.
- Will you be okay? - This is great.
What's happening?
(Waving gently)
- She's going to be great. - What was that?
Oh, dear. Hold on.
- She's going at it. - Wait.
- The viewers are as young as 12. - They are.
(Children watch our show. So this is a bit...)
(My family felt uncomfortable.)
Jin Young, this is rated PG-12.
- What's wrong with my dance? - Please tone it down.
- Since young kids watch this too... - What did I do wrong?
What did I do wrong?
The dance was beautiful, but it just had a weird vibe.
Young kids can watch the show. Let this go, and let's try the next one.
- Okay. - As expected, Jin Young...
- can't hold back her talents. - I agree. She was amazing.
Okay. Yeo Eun will show you another dance.
She will show you the best dance.
She has done the dance expressing the name before.
- I'll do a different dance. - That's right.
- She's going to dance barefoot? - Right.
- She won't back down. - A skirt?
If you dance barefoot...
(The song plays.)
I will do a different version of the dance.
It's the same song, but a different dance.
(Squeaky)
- Did she start? - She's so serious.
(From the start, the moves of her modern dance is intense.)
(Dancing lively)
I really think her personality is similar to yours.
I'm so scared.
- I mean... - Stop talking.
- Is it supposed to be like this? - Yes, it is. Stay quiet!
I'm so scared.
(Is she Yeo Eun or Ju-on?)
- She'll dance. Let her be. - Stay out of this.
(Is she a zombie?)
- Let her be. - Stay out of this.
(Roaring)
- She's good. - Give her the money.
- Yeo Eun, you are good. - Please stop dancing.
- All right. You are good. - Stop dancing. What is this?
I can't watch this anymore.
- You were great. - You were amazing, Yeo Eun.
You were awesome.
- I agree. - You all saw it, right?
You are the best dancer.
(Everyone agrees she is the best dancer.)
She is so similar to So Min.
- She is? - Yes.
She's your other self.
Right now, So Min, when you saw her dance,
what did you think?
- It was fun to watch. - Really?
(Yeo Eun is so much fun.)
Stop lying. You said she was weird.
She is so funny.
You are the weirdest member. Yet, you said she was weird.
- You are ridiculous. - I saw the look on your face.
Yeo Eun got the Best Dance!
Next up is the Best Magnet.
So Min, you are saying you are the magnet.
- Right. - Metal sticks onto me.
- Where can they stick? - On my forehead and face.
If you are not confident, don't try.
- Let us have this one. - First, show us.
- How can things get stuck? - Where do they stick?
- They can get stuck on her face. - Really?
She's like a magnet. Everything just sticks onto her.
(Really? It didn't stick.)
- It fell right away. - It just fell from her face.
- How can it fall right away? - Go and sweat.
- No. - Is it stuck?
- It's stuck. - Dance and try it.
- I don't have to. - Everyone can do that.
(She put 2 coins.)
She's not sweating. How is it possible?
Everyone can do that much.
(That's interesting. Is this possible?)
She's not sweating. How is it possible?
- Wait. Let her try this first. - She put more?
(Is this possible?)
I can do it too.
- Hold on a minute. - If both of you can do it... Wait.
- Ji Hyo can do it too. - If both of you can do this...
Whoever puts more wins.
Whoever puts more will win.
Everything can stick onto her face.
- A spoon can stick on your face? - A spoon?
(How about this?)
No way.
Is she supernatural?
Oh, my! She's the magnet!
(Oh, my! She's the magnet!)
Gosh, I just got goose bumps.
(That is so interesting.)
How can that stick on your face?
- How can it stick on your face? - I can do it too.
(Why are you trying to ruin our chances?)
Hold on a minute. I think...
She can do it too!
- Na Eun can do it too. - It sticks on Na Eun's face too.
Everyone can do it? No way.
(She's in trouble.)
Everyone, she's the magnet.
So Min is nervous now.
No one can do this one.
Go, Magnet!
- There's a zone. - There is?
- It's the magnet zone. - I guess there's a zone.
There is a zone where people can put a spoon on their faces?
I am so surprised that Ji Hyo can do this too.
Channel your energy.
(She isn't unique.)
- This one... - You can hang it on your bone?
No.
- This won't get stuck on her face. - Give her the ladle.
(What is this magnetic chin?)
What just happened?
What on earth is this?
She's the magnet!
- This... - Please show us one more time.
(Heroes always show up in times of crisis.)
She's the magnet. This is amazing.
Which of you can do this?
If no one can do this, So Min wins. Sun Bin.
- You can't do this. - I can put the coin on my face...
She's the magnet!
(Even if I dance, it's still on my face.)
What's with you?
She's the magnet!
Can you dance to "New Face"? All right.
(Since you are dancing...)
Please move back.
Dance to the song to seal the deal.
You just need to have the coin on your face and dance to the song.
All right. Play the song.
- You are like a super hero. - Play the song, please.
- You are... - This is so funny.
You are skillful.
Is it on her face?
Here she is, the magnet!
(The magnet is on the move.)
(You are so cool!)
Gosh, I just lost all affection for her.
I mean it.
- I really don't want to see you. - So Min, you did it!
- Why? - I'm sorry, but don't come near me.
(Humans are afraid of heroes.)
We did it. Who'll challenge this? Even if they can, they can't try it.
Who wants to challenge? Na Eun, can you do this?
Everyone, don't try it!
Please don't do it!
Na Eun, don't try it.
I'll give you 20 dollars. Stop it!
Can you dance with the spoon? Play the song, please.
- She's amazing. - Play the song.
(She can dance with the spoon too?)
What's wrong with her?
(The power of the magnet is on!)
(Look at me, you humans!)
- Stop. We won! - Do this move.
(She's the magnet.)
We won't challenge you! Fine, we won't do it!
- Unbelievable. - That was too much.
We did it!
She's the magnet!
(So Min is Best Magnet.)
- No one can do it, right? - So Min is Best Magnet.
(Even paper sticks too.)
She's unbelievable.
Is today's episode about crazy celebrities?
I mean, we were aware of her unique personality.
Now, who is next?
- Jong Kook? - It's Best Cuteness.
- Best Cuteness? - Yes.
Smile.
It's Best Cuteness.
I mean, Jin Young can...
pull off the best cute acts in Korea.
- She is. - She's the best in the world.
Jin Young, can you show us a few acts?
Sure.
You.
I'm so happy today that I could faint.
(Disturbed)
Jong Kook feels uncomfortable. He really does.
- He can't stand watching them. - Hey, Jong Kook.
- You should respond to it. - I did.
- As I told you, - I did though.
- you should exchange... - I'm sorry,
but she's lucky that I didn't butt my head.
(They are certainly different.)
- I smiled. - You have to reciprocate.
- Please do another one. - You have to do the same for her.
- I played along though. - We should do it together.
For you to prove she has the best cute acts, we need to verify.
I have to do it too?
- You should do the same acts. - I agree.
- I should do it too? - You should follow her.
- Let's do it together. - Exactly. You should exchange them.
I agree.
Here you go.
You, Jong Kook.
(Unable to talk)
- We can't accept this. - It's unacceptable.
It's not that. Why do I have to do this too?
- We'll lose because of you. - She wrote this down!
- Did I tell her to write this? - You have to respond.
- She said she was best at it. - You need to play along.
- How many times... - You have to reciprocate.
You two are a couple now.
- Come on. - You have to say, "You, Jin Young".
- Just do it. - Do the same act.
Please do it again.
(We ought to do this.)
- Do it well since you are doing it. - Of course. I should do it.
(Do it well since you are doing it anyway.)
(Frightened)
I got it.
You, Jong Kook.
You.
I'm so happy today that I could faint.
(Follow me!)
I faint.
(He really wants to faint.)
- It's the last one. - I want to faint.
(He can't manage well.)
(This won't be replayed.)
- Is 10 dollars worth it? - Goodness.
What will you do?
Ji Hyo, you.
(He lowers himself to listen to Ji Hyo.)
He lowered himself when she whispered.
That's really nice.
This is also acting cute.
- This is it. - I love it.
- Are you jealous? - Just smile.
That's funny.
(You lose if you're jealous.)
(Whispering)
He's so polite.
(Can they act cute?)
- If you won't do it, stop it. - We will.
- It's nothing. - What are you doing?
We don't have time right now.
We're making a plan.
- We have to go in the water. - Hurry up.
- Just do it. - Okay.
- We'll start. - Go.
Ji Hyo.
I had a scary dream,
so buy me some beef.
Shall I?
- Tae Hwan, you. - Ji Hyo, you.
Go away, both of you.
Go away!
What's wrong? Weren't we cute?
Weren't we so cute that you wanted to bite us?
Aren't we irresistibly cute?
(She acts boldly.)
For now,
both of you did your best,
but no one can act as cute as Jin Young.
- Does anyone want to try? - I do.
Yeo Eun wants to do it.
You're so shameless.
I've never seen anyone like her.
Will you participate in everything?
That sounds good. Let's take a look.
I'll speak with an accent.
- This is great. - I'll speak with a Busan accent.
- She's from Busan. - This is good.
- This is it. - I don't know this one.
It's game over if she says, "honey".
- Shall I start? - Go ahead.
Honey, I really like you.
Will you marry me?
Let's get married, honey.
Whom are you talking to?
Wasn't she...
talking to a ghost?
She was...
- talking to a ghost. - Stop it.
- Try it again. - She saw a ghost.
Did you see a ghost?
- Is this real? - Yes.
She talked to an empty space.
It's very scary.
"Honey, will you marry me?"
Was she talking to a ghost?
- She frightened me. - Wait.
"Honey, will you marry me?"
- "Honey." - She'll do something else.
- Honey. - Honey.
That's it.
She has something else.
Watch, Jin Young. You won't win 10 dollars.
We have something else.
It's an improved version.
Go.
Honey.
(It sounds eerie.)
She talks to ghosts.
She really talks to ghosts.
- Good job. - It's scary.
- Honey. - That was good.
I'd rather go to the Labyrinth.
- Listen, raise your hands. - She's scarier.
You never know.
- "Honey." - "Honey."
Guess what?
- That's enough. - Stop it.
- Stop it. That's enough. - She acts like a ghost.
- I bet it'll become very popular. - May I try it?
Raise your hands.
Will it be Jin Young or Yeo Eun?
Raise your hand if Jin Young was better.
- Yeo Eun was good. - How about Yeo Eun?
- Why? - Great.
It's supposed to be acting cute.
- It's about acting cute. - You have to improve yourself.
This is acting cute.
Honey, will you drink it in one go?
Yeo Eun is better.
I was kidding.
- Who agrees with him? - Jin Young?
I don't like to drink,
but I have a few for drinking.
Sing with me.
On the outskirts of a village, take a shot.
And 21 shots
I'm sorry.
Our viewers are as young as 12.
Listen.
Seriously.
Everyone froze with their arms in mid-air.
On the outskirts of a village, take a shot.
(Everyone freezes.)
Fathers covered their children's eyes while watching TV.
(It's not for children.)
For Best Cuteness,
Jin Young and Jong Kook win.
(Theyre 1st place.)
Good job, Jin Young.
Next is the winner of Best Hands.
(Ji Hyo places 1st for Best Hands.)
Do you do whatever you want?
(She easily passes Flushing the Toilet.)
(Water splashes on Na Eun.)
- It's over. - Already?
Is it over already?
You're so lucky, Ji Hyo.
Next is the winner of Best Waist.
(Na Eun places 1st.)
Her waist is so narrow.
She needs another hole to fit.
(Her waist is as narrow as her wrist.)
My goodness.
If she fits in the next hole,
then she wins.
- She fits. - It's the 24th hole.
(Her waist is 19in.)
Na Eun wins.
(Na Eun places 1st for Best Waist.)
Who's the winner of Best Eyes?
Get ready, set, go.
Tae Hwan is good.
Ha Young is also good.
(They compete.)
- What's going on? - Look at his eyes.
- He's amazing. - He blinked.
(Ha Young places 1st for Best Eyes.)
They won what they said they would.
(Each wins 10 dollars.)
This is the last round.
Will you place 1st for Best Punch?
- Yes. - Is there Best Punch?
This is simple.
Your power will be measured by the machine.
(Can you punch?)
Who wants to try it?
Our magnet will try it.
(So Min goes first.)
He makes me do everything.
- So Min will try. - Here's our magnet.
- She can do it. - I bet she can do it.
Try it.
She might be stronger.
Our magnet will go first.
I make a fist.
It's the basic in fighting.
- You want me to keep it on? - Stop it.
- She's our magnet. - Stop it.
Next is Sun Bin.
Those who want to challenge can go first,
- and Sun Bin will go last. - Okay.
Hold right here.
She's the magnet.
- Hold it. - She can't steal my 10 dollars.
(So Min takes her pose.)
Here's So Min.
I like So Min.
(She throws a nice punch.)
Goodness.
It must be a high score.
(Will Sun Bin be defeated from the start?)
It's 402.
(402 is a high score.)
- You scored 402. - It's 402.
Next is Na Eun.
Will you try?
- You can stand there. - Be careful, Na Eun.
Stand right here.
What is it?
Are you working for her?
- Yes. - Right.
You escort her.
They don't seem like a couple.
- He's her butler. - I'm her butler.
He's either her bodyguard, butler, or servant.
Do you know what's funny about Na Eun?
Instead of stopping Se Chan and telling him to be comfortable,
- she naturally accepts it. - She does.
- Pretty women know. - She accepts it.
You should punch like this.
That's it.
She punched.
(We'll consider that as her punch.)
- No. - Stop it.
Her score is 20. That was it.
That was it.
You already punched.
You got your score. Go back in.
- Go back. - Go back.
Good job, Na Eun.
(Se Chan compliments her.)
You can punch harder next time.
Punch harder next time. It wasn't bad.
(Na Eun fails in her attempt.)
They are...
the couple of darkness.
You don't need to go far.
I bet Jin Young will be good.
Take one step, and punch...
from the side. Try it.
Approach from the side.
Otherwise, you'll bump in here. Do it from the side.
Turn your body to the side.
- Turn it like this. - I got it.
(She gets annoyed.)
This couple doesn't seem decent.
Don't they seem indecent?
- Stop saying that. - Don't say that.
- Don't worry. I'll take care of it. - Thank you.
Use your weight to punch, okay?
I bet her punch is strong.
She seems most dangerous.
- Her punch must be strong. - Please move aside a bit.
- I'll be here. - Exceed 402 points.
(Everyone stays focused.)
(She prepares her punch carefully.)
(What will be charismatic Jin Young's score?)
(She misses.)
(She misses her punch.)
I'm glad I was here.
Does that count?
- It does. - Her score is zero.
As you know,
Ji Hyo is strong.
- Ji Hyo is. - She is.
- She seems like... - They look like...
a couple that you'd see in dramas.
Take a step first.
- Punch? - Right after the step.
He's good at teaching.
- Like this? - Yes.
Why do you ask when you know how to punch?
You don't need to practice.
- Let me try. - You've punched before.
- Let me practice. - You've punched a lot before.
- Stop it. - Fine.
She used to kick instead.
(Be quiet.)
- Like this? - Yes.
Don't get hurt.
That was great.
(Don't get hurt.)
(He gasps.)
I knew it.
It's 378.
You're in first place, So Min.
- The magnet lady is winning. - She is.
Sun Bin has to exceed 400 points.
- Let's go. - I was surprised.
Wish me luck.
- You know by the sound. - Let's see if she exceeds 400.
You can do it.
The winner is determined accurately by the score.
You only have one chance.
(She only has one chance.)
Why am I so nervous?
(She must not feel too much pressure.)
(Kwang Soo, give me strength.)
(She flies like a butterfly...)
(and stings like a bee.)
My goodness.
- That was nice. - Seriously.
(What will be Sun Bin's score?)
- It's 462. - Okay.
(She received a score of 462.)
(She places 1st with her punch.)
She is different.
Sun Bin will take...
- 10 dollars. - All right.
(She acquires 10 dollars with a punch on a different level.)
That was impressive.
How nice!
You have the money for the mission.
Now, you will change into team uniforms...
and start the mission in earnest.
- We are starting now. - This must be worth two episodes.
Let's go.
(They will have more than enough for one episode.)
Should I keep it with me?
Yes.
(They go to the water park to avoid the heat.)
(What kind of a refreshing mission awaits them?)
Let's hurry up and go.
(Let's go, honey!)
(Hurry up and do it.)
My goodness.
It smells like the sea.
Why would the water park smell like the sea?
For goodness' sake.
Is this your first time at a water park?
Why would the water park smell like the sea?
It smells like the sea.
- You're the Magnet Lady. - Yeo Eun.
Why are you tasting the water? It's not seawater.
So Min said that it smelled like the sea, right?
- Yes. - Yeo Eun tasted the water.
(So Min speaks, and Yeo Eun checks.)
She did that.
It will be a disaster if they join forces.
- Pull them apart. - Look at them.
They look alike, too.
(Can you tell Yeo Eun and So Min apart?)
The first mission...
will help you earn money for the future missions.
It's called Tools and Money.
(Tools and Money)
Tools and Money?
Money!
The 7 couples will be divided into 2 groups for a match.
As soon as the mission starts,
the men must choose 1 out of 4 mystery boxes...
on the flamingos,
and deliver the tools to their partners.
After delivering the tools to their partners,
the men will sit with baskets over their heads.
After getting the tool,
the women will run to the well that is filled with gold coins...
and transfer them to the baskets.
The weight of gold coins will determine the amount of money.
(10 cents per 1g will be given.)
All right.
- All right. - It's obvious that...
Ha Young...
is here for the shoot only.
She is determined to win.
She is here for the shoot only.
If there is a change in partners...
Stop it.
Stop it already.
Ha Young is stubborn.
She never loses hope.
I like that she is unchanging.
It's nice.
This is the first round of Tools and Money.
The time limit is three minutes.
Let's go.
I can't believe I am standing next to Jong Kook.
(The toughest couple)
(Jong Kook and Jin Young)
I will be back.
(Between love and loyalty, Se Chan and Na Eun)
I don't think I will be able to run.
(The masters of dancing and hosting, Jae Seok and Yeo Eun)
- Can we switch partners later? - Stop it.
(The wrong encounter, Seok Jin and Ha Young)
Is everyone ready?
(Fly like a bee...)
(to get the best tool.)
Get ready.
Set.
(Tools and Money, the 1st round)
My goodness.
(It starts.)
(Get out of the way, Seok Jin.)
(Get out of the way, Jae Seok.)
(Run)
(The desire to run is in the soul of Running Man.)
- Catch Jong Kook. - Catch him.
- Catch him. - Catch Jong Kook.
(They clash in front of flamingo number 1.)
(Number 1 is mine.)
(Puffed grain snack?)
(He needs another tool.)
(Otherwise, he will get scolded by Jin Young.)
(Don't block my path.)
(He beats the members who are no match for him, )
(and acquires a flipper.)
This is ridiculous.
(Jin Young, I did it.)
- Here you go. - Do I go now?
Yes.
(Jin Young's gold rush begins.)
Hurry up.
(What are our partners doing?)
(Their partners...)
My goodness.
(They're fighting for a turner.)
(I will pick another tool.)
My goodness.
(Is that puffed grain snack Jong Kook discarded?)
Come on.
(You can enjoy fighting. I am going to leave.)
(Give me the turner.)
(After failing to win the turner, which tool will Seok Jin get?)
(A scratcher?)
Here.
(The weaker contestants return.)
Use this.
What am I supposed to do with it?
- Take this. - Hurry up.
(How will she overcome this crisis?)
Come on.
(How can Ha Young win with a scratcher?)
(She can use this method.)
(She uses the scratcher like a sword.)
My goodness.
(They can't believe their eyes.)
She swung it.
My goodness.
(Screaming)
(Ha Young, the lawless)
You could have done better...
with a flipper.
Stop it.
(I will take 1st place and win the rings.)
You could have done better with a flipper.
Stop it.
(Puffed grain snack is delicious.)
- Come on. - Let's go.
You can do it.
Come on.
Hurry up.
30 seconds remain.
You can't put coins in the bag.
(It's too delicious.)
Hurry up, Na Eun.
We don't have much time.
Na Eun, you need to hurry up.
(Se Chan, I think we are doomed.)
(The real race starts with 30 seconds left on the clock.)
You can't use your hands.
Yeo Eun.
Hurry up, Na Eun.
Stop Jin Young from bringing more coins.
Are you eating the puffed grain snack?
(The strongest tool, the flipper, appears.)
Come on, Yeo Eun.
Come on.
Hurry up, Yeo Eun.
You don't have much time.
My goodness.
Why did you do that?
(The gladiator with a scratcher appears.)
The flipper is ridiculous.
In 2, 1.
Jin Young.
- For goodness' sake. - We are rich.
(I am sorry. It was too tasty.)
It's the next group's turn.
Who are in this race?
All right.
Keep that in mind.
(2 people and 2 tricksters are planning head.)
(Suspicious)
I predict that...
it will be a dirty match.
Kwang Soo.
- Let's go. - We can lose this race.
Let's go.
(Poor Tae Hwan.)
Get ready.
(Everyone knew they would do this.)
(The dirty game begins as expected.)
For goodness' sake.
This is ridiculous.
One of them will betray the other.
(The icon of betrayal doesn't disappoint.)
(Good job, Kwang Soo.)
Let's go.
(I will go first.)
Catch him.
All right.
My goodness.
(Run with a flipper.)
(Sun Bin, am I not the best?)
Come on.
(Flailing)
(What am I supposed to do with a turner?)
(Why is he running with a box?)
Here is a flipper.
Bring it.
Come on.
(I will make it work.)
All right.
It's okay.
(Are we doomed?)
(Panting)
(So Min, we don't have much time.)
(Haha, I can receive it well.)
(I am a magnet.)
(We can do it)
(We don't have much time. Here comes a long pass.)
Are you okay? I am sorry.
(It turns out she wasn't a magnet.)
(Meanwhile, Sun Bin and Ji Hyo are getting ahead.)
That's ridiculous.
That's wrong.
- That's wrong. - That's wrong.
You can't use puffed grain snack like that.
Let us go one more time.
Come on.
Good job.
(Sun Bin plays foul without holding back.)
- For goodness' sake. - Good job.
(Disheartened)
(This is ridiculous.)
- So Min lost. - For goodness' sake.
Come on, So Min.
You need to keep going.
So Min, put coins on your forehead.
(Remember who you are.)
You are the magnet.
(The magnet doesn't disappoint.)
Come on.
You can't use puffed grain snack like that.
In 6, 5, 4,
- You are almost done. - 3, 2,
one.
Time's up.
So Min, time's up.
We will weigh the coins.
(Ji Hyo and Tae Hwan has the most. Jae Seok and Yeo Eun has the least.)
This is the start.
- This is war. - This is war.
There are cars...
that will take you to the number one restaurant in Gyeongju...
- in the parking lot. - I guess we're really going.
There are two restaurants on the list.
We'll proceed even if you miss this announcement.
- Goodness. - There are two restaurants...
and each restaurant has different price and menu.
Four teams for Korean table d'hote place...
and three teams for samgyetang place by order of arrival.
(They take a limited number of teams by order of arrival.)
(What? Where are you all going?)
Hey, where are they going? Let's follow them.
What's going on?
What did he say? I didn't hear him.
(They have to arrive quickly to choose a cheaper restaurant.)
Run!
I haven't even worn my shoes properly.
(They have to arrive quickly to choose a cheaper restaurant.)
(They find something ahead of them.)
- Korean table d'hote. - I haven't even worn my shoes.
Yeo Eun!
(Samgyetang is 20 dollars and Korean table d'hote is 15 dollars.)
It's samgyetang and what?
- Korean table d'hote! - Korean table d'hote.
(The couples want to choose the cheaper Korean table d'hote place.)
(Hey, where should we go?)
(We have a lot of money, so let's choose samgyetang.)
We take four teams for Korean table d'hote place by order of arrival.
Four teams?
The seats for the Korean table d'hote place is full now.
(Only Team Ji Hyo chose the samgyetang place.)
If you're not among the four teams who arrived the earliest,
please get off the bus.
(Do you mean us?)
- We have no money. - Well...
- We're short on money. - Make a loan then.
- He gets to borrow money. - Get an I Go Sticker in exchange.
We don't have enough money.
Samgyetang is good for your health.
- I want to eat Korean table d'hote. - No, let's just eat samgyetang.
We don't have enough money.
Samgyetang is good for your health.
- Welcome. - We're in trouble.
- Welcome. - Hey.
(They get on the bus for samgyetang.)
- Welcome. - We have enough money.
- You chose samgyetang? - Yes.
- Let's enjoy expensive food. - Gosh.
Korean table d'hote is way better than samgyetang.
Really? But I wanted to have samgyetang.
We wanted to have samgyetang.
Congratulations for getting aboard this bus.
I'm not sure if you saw what happened earlier,
but Se Chan cared for his partner...
and told her to put her ring off during the game.
Na Eun thanked him and took her ring and bracelet off.
Then she handed them to Se Chan.
(Thank you. Can you hold my ring for a second?)
Really.
- Like this. - Gosh.
(She naturally handed her ring to her butler, Se Chan.)
Don't you have to take this bracelet off too?
Take them all off.
Just in case.
- That was so natural. - That wasn't for show.
- I put them in my pocket. - He was too focused on his act.
She was worried I'd steal them and reminded me...
to give her ring back.
(Don't forget to return it.)
- I was like, "Okay." - You probably acted suspicious.
So I gave them back to her.
- That was funny. - I'm envious of her.
- What's there to envy? - Just because.
We're most envious of the magnetic human.
- Right. - I'm envious.
You're born with an incredible ability.
- It's unbelievable, right? - She's a heroine.
I just think you're really like a frog.
(She's rather a frog than a heroine.)
Then Yeo Eun is like a frog too since the two of us look alike.
You two look a bit like fish.
(What do you mean, fish?)
- Let's stop here. - Gosh.
- Goldfish. - It's great.
Right, you look a bit like goldfish.
- You do. - Yes, you look like carp.
Carp with big eyes.
- Right. - She really looks like one.
Na Eun looks like a kind of wild animals.
- Wild animals? - Wild animals?
- Squirrel. - That's right.
- She looks like squirrel. - Something small.
(Na Eun's butler is falling in love again.)
(She isn't a squirrel.)
She looks like a sika deer.
- Maybe a rabbit. - A sika deer?
(She's shy to hear his butler.)
- Gosh, Se Chan. - Stop it.
- Don't be like this. - You went too far.
- Not at all. - You did go too far.
- Gosh. - Seriously.
(My sika deer is the most beautiful in the world.)
I look like a dried pollack and you look like a hairy crab.
- Se Chan is a typical... - Kwang Soo's like a giant anchovy.
(By taking another look)
- He's like a giant anchovy. - What?
(What on earth is a giant anchovy?)
- Goodness. - For making broth.
- Giant anchovy. - What was that?
- I know what you mean. - The ones with giant poop, right?
Exactly.
You have to take it all out. Otherwise, it tastes bitter.
He also looks like cutlass fish, but let's go with a giant anchovy.
- That explains him perfectly. - What is a giant anchovy?
I'm not sure what it is, but Yeo Eun looks like a kind of fish.
- Hello. - Hello.
(They arrive at the Korean table d'hote restaurant.)
It's really Korean table d'hote.
It looks delicious!
- That soybean paste stew! - Awesome!
This has to be tasty.
(They're impressed to see so many delicious dishes.)
It's warm.
- Gosh, this is... - What should we do?
(From spicy grilled pollack...)
(to mackerel and tofu that will recharge their energy)
What is this?
(It's jeyuk bokkem, the best side dish.)
Can we start eating now?
You can go ahead and enjoy the meal.
- Really? - Do we get to enjoy freely?
- Do we just eat? - Thanks for the food.
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you.
Yeo Eun, eat up.
Thank you for the meal.
Let's focus on eating first.
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you and enjoy!
Look at this kimchi. It's no joke.
It's just incredible.
My gosh. It's awesome!
(Chicken boiled with various medicinal herbs)
(They dig in without having doubts.)
It's delicious.
- I won't do that. - What happens if we make a loan?
I won't borrow money. You'll be okay, but I'll be doomed if I do.
- Are you doing this for the show? - It's not because of the show.
- Really? - Yes.
You're nice.
Suck this in.
(Suck this in.)
(Jin Young melts Jong Kook's stiff heart.)
You definitely need to suck them all in.
- Here. - Okay.
She's great at things like this.
(She's great at things like this.)
(Her cuteness is making Jong Kook go out of his mind.)
(Open up!)
(Eating)
It's good to have someone who takes care of me.
(He realizes it's great to be cared.)
(And Kwang Soo is yet too shy to be cared by someone.)
I didn't put much in it.
Thank you.
Here's a wrap to express my gratitude to you.
(He's thankful and makes her a wrap.)
- Thank you. - Thanks.
Thanks, Yeo Eun.
(Have some tofu too.)
(The other couples care for each other.)
Na Eun, can you put a piece of kimchi on my spoon?
(Glancing)
(What a dork.)
Thanks.
Thank you.
(She's the best.)
Are you done with your meals?
- Yes. - Yes.
All right, everyone.
It's 15 dollars per table,
so the total is 60 dollars.
You have to answer randomly to a question to win the game.
The winning team will not have to pay for the meal.
Okay.
- Do you want to go first? - No, go ahead.
- Okay. - So Min will go first.
- Let's get started. - Ready, go.
Ready, set, go.
What comes to your mind when you look at a mirror?
Magnetic human.
(It totally makes sense.)
What was that?
(Gosh, it totally makes sense!)
Why would you say that?
It's natural to think about it when you look at a mirror.
(She keeps reminding herself that she's magnetic.)
- She knows it herself. - That's the word I was thinking.
Isn't it so cool? Imagine it's the scene from a movie.
- She's indeed a heroine. - She looks at the mirror...
and tells herself that she's magnetic.
- It's so cool. - I'll save the world today.
- She's indeed a heroine. - Indeed.
You live out of a sense of responsibility.
She failed at her first answer.
All right, Na Eun. Get ready.
(She tries to distract Na Eun.)
Set, go.
What's the wallpaper for your cellphone?
It's red.
(So the wallpaper for your cellphone is in red.)
- Na Eun! - She's so good.
Gosh, Ms. Sika Deer!
Don't you think you like colors too much?
- Okay. - I couldn't think of anything else.
- So Min is up again. - She has another chance.
- Let's go again. - It's all right.
- Each of you get another chance. - It's like a shootout.
Ready, set, go.
What was the precognitive dream of your birth?
Korean table d'hote.
(I see. Your parents dreamed of a hearty Korean table d'hote.)
(That's such a delicious cognitive dream of your birth.)
- What a d'hote. - Was it Korean table d'hote?
- Right. - That sounds so hearty.
- Sure. - That's why she became magnetic.
(She'll turn out to be great.)
(Behind her mysterious ability...)
(is the power of Korean table d'hote.)
(So Min fails.)
- It's Na Eun's turn now. - You can do it!
Ready, set, go.
- What's in your bag? - 9 times 9 is 81.
- When do you think you're cutest? - Blue.
What's your favorite girl group?
(If she succeeds this time, Na Eun and Se Chan will win the 1st round.)
- What's your favorite girl group? - Yellow.
- That's a success. - Okay!
(With 3 consecutive nonsensical answers, she wins.)
Okay!
I knew it. She's the best.
- You will advance to the final. - Final? That's awesome.
- This is great. - All right.
So Min fails.
(Se Chan and Na Eun go to the final.)
Sun Bin and Yeo Eun, you are up.
You must answer three questions.
Yeo Eun, you can do it.
Get ready.
(Sun Bin tries first.)
Start.
How do you relieve your stress?
Leggings.
(Incorrect)
- How can leggings be helpful? - You can relieve stress with them.
She said she uses them. We don't know how.
- That's what she said. - Hey.
- Her answer didn't make sense. - We don't know how.
- It was Sun Bin who said that. - Come on.
How can someone relieve stress with leggings?
- Kwang Soo, they are tight. - That's what she meant.
That's how she relieves stress?
- For some, it works. - Of course.
Since she said she uses them to relieve stress, that's the end.
- Incorrect. - You can't do anything about that.
Did my answer really make sense?
- Yes, it did. - But...
We'll start again.
Get ready. Start.
What is your motto?
Water park.
Which role do you want to play?
Meat.
- Hold on. - You took too long.
- Wait. - I wasn't going to...
Which role do you want to play?
(Excuse me?)
(Is playing a piece of meat possible?)
- Hold on. - I wasn't trying to be mean.
You took too long.
I played a fish before.
Playing a piece of meat is possible.
- It's very possible. - Goodness.
- She can play that role. - No way.
- He has a point. He played a fish. - Kwang Soo is right.
- Sun Bin is next. - We'll start again.
Start.
Say a word to the President.
Hello.
Hold on.
Say a word to the President.
(I have to say a word to the President?)
- Hold on. - Hey, you!
Sun Bin, if you have something to say, you can say it.
You did well. Come on!
- Sun Bin, you can talk to him. - Seriously.
Congratulations.
Please make Korea beautiful.
What could she have said?
All right. Yeo Eun, it's your turn now.
I just got the chills.
- It's Yeo Eun's turn. - We'll start again.
That's right. Don't think.
(Her strategy is to be in a daze.)
- Yeo Eun is trying not to focus. - What should we do?
- It's funny how she's in a daze. - No.
Yeo Eun, not focusing on it is great.
- Get ready. - Don't think.
Start.
What do you want to be in your next life?
No walking.
- What did you dream last night? - Stop.
- What was your baby dream? - Straight.
Straight? That's an acceptable answer?
(Yeo Eun manages to answer absurdly 3 times in a row.)
That's an acceptable answer?
- Her baby dream... Hold on. - She did it.
You thought her answer didn't make sense.
Yet, you thought it made sense she relieves stress with leggings?
- That made sense. - That's right.
Have you ever dreamed of going backward?
- I dreamed it last night. - Really?
- Yes, I did. - Are you serious?
The day before yesterday, I dreamed of making a left turn.
(Despite Kwang Soo's claims, Yeo Eun advances to the final.)
The final match is between Na Eun and Yeo Eun.
I was close though.
- I'll try it. - Ha Young will try it.
Jin Young will play too.
Jin Young.
Face each other.
- By the way... - Start.
Do you like soda?
18.
(Looking cheerful)
- Why? - Hey!
(What a cheerful answer.)
Come on.
- I said the number. - The number?
- I said the number. - The number.
(Don't get the wrong idea.)
- Can this part air? - Didn't I tell you before?
She was cute when she said it though.
(Since it's cute and bubbly, it passed the censorship.)
18. Can I do this?
By the way,
it's strange that I don't feel insulted when I hear it.
Exactly. This answer was acceptable.
You have to admit that.
- 1 more time? - 1 more time.
Okay. Let's play it again.
- One more time? - Let's do it over.
- Start. - Start.
- What is your level of cholesterol? - I need to poop.
What is your IQ?
My stomach hurts.
Did you put on fake eyelashes?
20.
- 20? That makes sense. - 20 eyelashes?
(20 eyelashes)
(This completely makes sense.)
- 20? That makes sense. - 20 eyelashes?
- Why? - 20 eyelashes?
Because you said I can't say 18,
I can't come up with an answer.
(Seok Jin and Ha Young win the game by luck.)
- She's good. - Seok Jin and Ha Young win.
(Jong Kook and Jin Young spend 60 dollars for the meal.)
- Na Eun, you should go first. - You can go first.
- Should I go first? - Okay.
Get ready, Na Eun.
(Na Eun and Yeo Eun play the final match.)
Get ready.
Set.
Start.
What does So Min remind you of?
3 times 6 is 18.
(Even you, Na Eun?)
- 18? - Wait. How old are you?
- What's wrong? - Is that how you'll play it?
It's just a multiplication.
You got feisty since you've been working with Psy.
How can you?
So Min is older than you.
It's just a number.
What did she do wrong?
It's the multiplication table.
- I'm sorry. - You are sorry?
(That was sudden.)
If you are sorry, it sounds like you meant it.
(How can you apologize?)
Na Eun, it sounds like you did curse at her.
(You didn't mean that, right?)
Yeo Eun.
We'll start again.
(Na Eun gets a second chance.)
Get ready.
Start.
- Say a word to your parents. - Red.
What do you want to be in your next life?
Everybody, put your hands up.
What's in your refrigerator?
(If she says another absurd answer, they won't pay for the meal.)
- What's in your refrigerator? - Delicious.
- Picked cucumber? - Cucumber?
- Did she say, "pickled cucumber"? - She said, "delicious".
- She said, "delicious". - Did she say, "pickled cucumber"?
- Delicious. - She said it's delicious.
- Are you sure? - She said, "delicious".
- Delicious. - Pickled cucumber.
Okay.
(Na Eun succeeds.)
Na Eun wins!
(Se Chan and Na Eun won't pay for the meal.)
We did it!
(You are the best, Na Eun.)
They won't pay for the meal?
Either 3 teams will pay together and divide 60 dollars among you.
Or one team can pay it all.
One team should pay it all.
- It's 60 dollars? - Yes.
- Let's play a game of luck. - Let one team pay for it.
- Sure. That's neat. - Okay.
- I'm in. - Let's do it.
(The game of luck to choose a team to pay the whole bill begins.)
The person who draws the spoon without the sticker loses, right?
The one without the sticker loses.
- Okay. - The number has to be on it.
It's 60 dollars.
Who will draw first?
Kwang Soo will draw first.
- No, Sun Bin will draw for me. - She will?
- No, you can't do that. - I'm not good at this too.
(What are you talking about?)
- Kwang Soo should draw. - Kwang Soo should draw.
- This time... - Why?
- Men should pick this time. - I agree.
Kwang Soo, you might be lucky this time.
- He has to pick the one without it. - Those jerks.
I wish the game ends here.
- I wish the game ends here. - Show the spoon right away.
(Mark my words. I will be reborn as the Best Hands.)
(My lady, Sun Bin, is watching me.)
(I can't pick the wrong spoon.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - Kwang Soo.
(He picks the spoon without the sticker.)
No way. How can you have predicted this?
It really happened.
Isn't this amazing?
(I have faith in you, Kwang Soo.)
(I guess I shouldn't have.)
(He is unlucky regardless of where he is.)
I feel like this is like a set up.
No, you did pick the wrong one.
Goodness.
How can this be possible?
How can this happen?
This really is amazing.
I'm sorry.
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry for you.
He is scary.
Sun Bin, when you see him like this, what do you think about him?
- Is he cute? - He's cute.
She said he's cute.
Cute Kwang Soo, give us 60 dollars.
(Cute Kwang Soo, give us 60 dollars.)
Thank you for the food.
(They spend 60 dollars in an instant.)
- Goodness. - Let's play it again.
(This is fun.)
Let's go for the second round.
Let's have coffee.
- Shall we play one more for drinks? - Yes.
- 1, 2, 3, 4... - It's for everyone.
- Eight. - Let's play the roulette this time.
- It will cost 40 dollars. - That's great.
- This is for coffee. - For coffee.
For your information,
Se Chan only has 37 dollars. If his name is drawn...
He has to get a loan, right?
He will get an I Go Sticker.
His team doesn't have enough money.
We can't be chosen. If we are, I am in trouble.
I will have to get the sticker.
We'll play it fair.
- Please. - Give it a strong spin.
Get ready.
- Start. - Please don't be me.
(Will Kwang Soo who just spent 60 dollars, be chosen?)
(Or will it be Se Chan who might have to get a loan?)
Please don't be me.
(Or will it be other members?)
(They all have an equal chance. Who will buy the 2nd round?)
Please.
It's Kwang Soo!
(At this point, this is getting boring.)
(He's forced to treat the meal and the coffee.)
How can this actually happen?
How can this be possible?
- How? - I'm sorry.
You really are so unlucky.
(He is putting on a show to praise Kwang Soo.)
He's the unluckiest.
- This game... - Kwang Soo, you really are.
Now that I see it with my own eyes, I can't believe how unlucky he is.
Sun Bin, there's a reason how he became Kwang Soo of 10 Slots.
You just spent 100 dollars. You are Kwang Soo of 100 Dollars now.
That's right.
Please stay away from here. I'm sorry.
Your luck is unbelievable.
I think he might have brought something from the Labyrinth.
- No. - Bring what?
He's always been like this.
How can his name be chosen out of all the names?
(You are so generous, Kwang Soo. Thank you for the coffee too.)
(Current status of remaining amount of money)
The final mission is...
the last chance for those of you to turn the tables around.
- We can turn the tables around. - We just have to do well now.
Let's do this.
It's Search and Stop.
(The last round of mission is Search and Stop.)
(Search and stop?)
Within the time limit which is 30 minutes,
obtain the money in the pouches scattered around the water park.
If even one member of your team gets his or her name tag removed,
the team will have to stop for one minute during the mission.
- The team cannot move an inch. - We can't move.
We haven't played the name tag race for a while.
The female members can only remove the name tags.
The male members can only play defense.
Jong Kook, protect me.
If you are ready, please move to your own starting points.
(Teamwork is the key to this race. What is the ending of the race?)
- That's right. - Since we have the lowest amount...
I think we should know how the pouches look.
- That's the pouch. - It's that yellow object?
We can take that.
We will once we start.
It's likely that there's nothing good inside.
Do you see where the water is rushing out?
It's likely that that there are pouches there.
- Where the water is flowing? - Yes.
They must be in dangerous places.
What about next to the slide?
- Okay. - We can take one each as we slide.
(They must take risks for more money.)
Let's do it.
It's a war.
We can climb up there too.
- That looks fun. - I want to do that.
I want to converse with you instead.
(He doesn't care about the mission.)
I want to have tea with you.
(Mission fees and races are only his excuses.)
Pose like this.
Pull out your lips.
Pull them out.
In 1, 2, 3.
(The couple gets lovey-dovey.)
That's good.
(7 couples are ready for the mission.)
- How about that one? - Let's try it.
We have to find the pouches.
Get ready.
There must be one over there.
- Three. - Shall we go there?
Two.
One.
Start.
(Will they stay safe?)
(The race starts.)
Let's start with that. Look, there it is.
- Where? - It's over there.
This is it.
(They find a pouch.)
(How much is in it?)
- Don't come. I'll do it. - You're tall.
- You're tall. - It's so cold.
- It's so cold. - It's okay. You're tall.
(He backs away.)
- I can do it. - You can do it.
- I can do it, - You can.
- but... - You can do it.
It's much colder than I thought.
It's really cold.
(What?)
Wait, Kwang Soo.
(While Kwang Soo hesitates, Haha tries to beat him to it.)
Kwang Soo.
(He won't let him have it.)
I got it.
Darn it.
(He gets a pouch.)
It's so cold.
Kwang Soo.
(They thought they got it, but...)
No way.
(It's So Min this time.)
No, stop it.
Stop it.
Wait.
Don't do this.
- Haha. - Let's go.
- Are you okay? - Is this how you'll play?
No, we're leaving.
Where are you going?
Let's not fight.
(He runs away.)
Why are you leaving me?
(Here's their chance.)
- Take off her name tag. - No.
(Tearing)
We did it.
(So Min and Haha pause for 1 minute.)
I got one.
(What happened?)
Haha.
(They tore my name tag.)
Thank you, Haha.
Thank you.
We got it.
Let's go.
Let's take a look inside.
How much is it?
- It's 2 dollars. - 2 dollars?
We should check out where there's no one.
- We have the least amount of money. - Right here?
We need to find a lot.
We really do.
Shall we go here?
What's this?
(A pouch hangs in the air on the slide.)
- Why is it over there? - It's over there.
Jae Seok.
(Suddenly water falls on Jae Seok and Yeo Eun.)
(Search and Stop will not be easy.)
(High risk means more money.)
We have the least amount of money.
That's why.
(Despite the water bomb and the slide, )
(they give it a try.)
I'll go after you.
I don't think I can do it.
You'll slide under the pouch.
We're coming down.
(Will Jae Seok and Yeo Eun obtain the pouch?)
- Okay. - Here it goes.
Here it goes.
(The tube slides down.)
(Sliding)
(They fail their first attempt.)
(On their way back, )
(they grab the pouch.)
(They get the pouch.)
We got it.
(How much is in the pouch that was risky to get?)
I hope it's 100 dollars.
It's 10 dollars.
Goodness.
(Jae Seok and Yeo Eun obtain 10 dollars.)
You're doing well.
Go, Ha Young.
Are we going to slide down?
- Remove your mics. - We have to?
Yes.
- I'll go on this one. - Slide down?
There's another one.
Do you want to take this slide instead?
(Seok Jin is scared of darkness.)
(Thank you, Ha Young.)
Is the water deep or not?
- Shall we go? - Let's go.
- Go. - Ha Young.
(Ha Young slides down first.)
Ha Young.
(Flying)
(She grabs the pouch.)
Is the water deep?
(It's time for worrisome Seok Jin.)
(If Seok Jin succeeds, they obtain two pouches.)
(Here comes an old man.)
(He misses.)
Wait a minute.
(He fails to grab the pouch.)
Seok Jin.
Why didn't you grab it?
(Guess what?)
(Jae Seok takes the pouch instead.)
He missed it.
Seok Jin missed it.
Why didn't you grab it?
(Jae Seok and Yeo Eun grab it instead.)
I'll get it.
(He gets sly and takes it.)
Come on, that's mine.
You can't do that.
Why didn't you grab it then?
It's not that much.
How much is it? It's a dollar.
- It's only a dollar. - It's a dollar.
- My goodness. - Where should we go?
Let's go over there.
(There's one on the tree.)
- Gosh. - How can we climb up?
We can't climb up.
(The pouch is too high up.)
(He tries it anyway.)
(Struggling)
(What on earth...)
(What on earth is he doing?)
I'll do it.
(Let's work as a team.)
Do you think I can get on your shoulders?
Are you okay?
On my shoulders?
- Okay. - Are you okay?
Stand up.
(Jumping)
(He takes it.)
(Jae Seok successfully steals it again.)
(He takes it from them.)
Jae Seok.
- Wait. - Let's see.
Come on, Jae Seok.
We were about to get it.
Goodness.
You're so good.
(They can't afford to be polite.)
I'm too scared.
Let go of your body on the cable.
Just close your eyes.
I'm too scared.
- Just close your eyes. - I'm scared.
Close your eyes and let go of your body on the cable.
(It's a zip-line course with 3 stages.)
Do we just hang on?
(The first challenge is zip-line.)
You'll go slowly.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Brave Jong Kook starts.)
(Here comes Jong Kook.)
This is great.
Goodness.
(How can he enjoy it?)
This is good.
(He descends smoothly.)
It's Jong Kook.
(He finishes the 1st stage.)
Here it is.
Here's the pouch.
(He obtains the pouch.)
(However, he must stay alert.)
(The 2nd stage is crossing a bridge that hangs mid-air.)
You cross the bridge.
- Do I cross by foot? - Yes.
Okay.
I didn't know it was by foot.
I didn't know that.
(The bridge seems unstable.)
Okay.
Goodness.
(Even Jong Kook seems scared.)
Gosh, it's dangerous.
Jong Kook is crossing.
Is he?
(I can't do that.)
(He's fully equipped with safety gear.)
(Highest level of difficulty)
(A pouch hangs in the middle of the bridge.)
(For coming this far, he's determined to obtain the pouch.)
- My goodness. - Please come up.
(Jin Young waits for zip-lining.)
I'm so scared.
My goodness.
Start as soon as she's ready.
Wait, what do I do?
Grab onto the rope.
Grab it with one hand.
(She's frightened.)
My goodness.
(Crying)
Did you hear me?
Where's Jong Kook?
Where is he?
(He's doing his best to get money.)
Jin Young can't do this.
Poor Jin Young.
I'm worried about her.
I don't think she can do it.
(She takes a look at Jong Kook who is far away.)
Let go.
(I'll be brave too.)
(If you do it, I'll do it too.)
(She takes the plunge and rides the zip line.)
(I'm so proud of my partner.)
(He arrives at the point where the pouch is.)
Okay.
I found a pouch.
(He finds another pouch.)
Pouch.
Let's go up here.
(They will go up on the biggest tornado slide.)
Come here.
- Is it two dollars? - No.
Is it three dollars?
It's three dollars.
(In order to get the money, they must complete the activity!)
Is it really fast? Its name is tornado.
- It's really fast? - It's fast?
- Shall we take off our caps? - Shall we?
(The slide leaves before they're ready.)
Hang on. Hang on!
(Screaming)
Hold on a second!
(The tube reaches high.)
(Frightened)
(The slide ends after whirling greatly.)
(It was really tough.)
(At that moment)
Kwang Soo!
(Team Seok Jin attacks them out of the blue!)
(Come over here, you guys!)
(Gosh, that hurts.)
Remove his name tag!
(This isn't what I planned.)
Sun Bin, remove her name tag!
(Who attacked whom?)
- Remove it! - Remove it!
- Sun Bin, please! - Ha Young!
Trip her!
Sun Bin, you can do it!
(It's time out for 1 minute if they rip it.)
- Kwang Soo. - Sun Bin, remove the name tag!
Don't lie down.
(She lies down.)
- Sun Bin, remove it. - Remove it.
Sun Bin, eliminate him now.
(Seok Jin is her target now.)
Why is she aiming mine?
(Give me your name tag!)
- Sun Bin, remove it. - Remove it.
- Hold on to it. - Remove it.
(She eliminated Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin must stop playing for 1 minute.)
(We attacked them, but we've been counterattacked.)
Sun Bin is unbelievable.
She's so absorbed in the game.
Sun Bin, I see something over there.
Kwang Soo, there's something over there.
(Their search for pouches resumes.)
It must be filled.
(It's time they found a pouch with a lot of money.)
Come here. Come here now!
Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo.
(Team Orange is after Sun Bin now.)
Kwang Soo!
(Sun Bin, please hang in there!)
No, no!
- No! - Remove her name tag.
(I'll protect my own name tag!)
(Everyone, get out of my way!)
(It's a close battle although she's playing alone.)
- Na Eun, eliminate her. - No way.
Na Eun, remove the name tag.
Sun Bin!
- Se Chan, how can you do this? - Help me.
- Sun Bin! - The service is over.
- You're pulling my hair. - You're pulling her hair.
- It's over. - It's not over yet.
- Take a break for one minute. - It's not over yet.
Kwang Soo, what on earth are you doing?
(Kwang Soo, what on earth are you doing?)
Sun Bin.
Sun Bin, I'm almost there.
(I'm almost there!)
Hold here.
Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo! - What a tough girl you are.
(I'm sorry. I'm busy working.)
Gosh, she's unbelievable.
(Those who are trying to eliminate her are more exhausted.)
She's holding her name tag.
Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo is returning with the pouch.)
(Screaming)
She's a moth too.
Forget it.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Let's give up on this team.)
Seriously...
(You're dead once you come home.)
Hold on. For goodness' sake.
I was almost eliminated.
(How much money did Kwang Soo make?)
Tell me the total amount.
- It's... - There's only one dollar here.
Two dollars here.
(There was two dollars in the other pouch.)
I even went into the water.
(Why did we fight so desperately?)
I wasn't eliminated though.
- For a second, I thought... - We got three dollars.
It should've been 40 dollars at least!
Is my life a joke to you?
(Meanwhile, the other side of the water park is quiet.)
(Haha and So Min found a few pouches so far.)
(Waddling)
(Why can't I go on the tube?)
(Hopping)
(Falling)
(She probably doesn't get along with rubber since she's a magnet.)
(Dragging)
My goodness.
What are you doing? Why are you carrying it?
You fool!
(Come to your senses, you fool!)
What's wrong with you?
Did you use up all your strength?
Give it to me. I'll help you.
Did you sit? That's not it.
Don't do that.
Why do you keep hating yourself?
(When will they ever find a pouch?)
What are you doing?
(Peeping)
Everything's been taken.
(What should we do?)
(Ji Hyo is the only one Tae Hwan cares about.)
(He follows Ji Hyo all day long.)
(She does her best.)
Gosh, I'm tired.
(Where did Ji Hyo go?)
Gosh, it's hot.
(Just like Tae Hwan, )
(Na Eun is busy fulfilling a mission.)
Here it goes.
(Screaming out of joy)
(It looks like a refreshing commercial because of Na Eun.)
What was that?
(She enjoys all the activities without the two guys.)
Lift your feet.
Na Eun!
I love it.
(She rides a zip line this time.)
(She enjoys the leisure activities, and gets money for the mission too.)
(It's a perfect mission for Na Eun.)
(I love this water park.)
Should we do it too?
- This one. - We'll ride this?
The zip line ride.
- My goodness. - We should ride the zip line.
We should also ride the zip line.
(The teams go to the zip line since it seems challenging.)
(Ha Young approaches quietly.)
(She flies like a butterfly, )
(and stings like a bee!)
(Removing)
(Yeo Eun and Ha Young both get 1-minute time out.)
(The weak are the prey of the strong in this race.)
Hey, why did you pass them, and eliminate her?
(A brutal counterattack took place in an instant.)
- Did you scheme it? - Incredible.
What's the matter with you?
(I can't believe that they got us again.)
- You could've eliminated Kwang Soo. - Come on.
- Let's go. - We'll ride it.
(Kwang Soo and Sun Bin will ride the zip line.)
My gosh.
(Kwang Soo and Sun Bin get to ride due to the other teams' penalty.)
It's...
(They get up on the rooftop.)
My gosh.
Goodness.
(Even the spot to get ready for the ride is difficult.)
- I'm stressed. - Kwang Soo.
It's so stressful.
Sun Bin, you really like this stuff?
- In 1, 2... - Hold on. Sun Bin...
- You got this! - Sun Bin, oh dear.
- You can do it. - Hold on!
Don't push me!
(Screaming)
It's too fast!
It's too fast.
I need to get the money quickly.
It's too fast. Too fast!
It's too fast.
(Gosh, it looks fun.)
It's too fast. Be careful. It's too fast!
(He lands safely.)
I'm fine.
I can't go up.
(Kwang Soo successfully rides the zip line.)
Where am I? Oh, my.
(Next up is the problematic bridge in the air.)
I can't look down. What should I do?
- Move back. - Hang on a second.
What if I fall down?
There's one more over there.
There it is!
(The race is nearing its end.)
(Everyone does his best to get more money before it ends.)
- What is this? - A bridge in the air?
Follow me.
- I'll go? - Yes.
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo can't move a single step on the bridge.)
- Let's go. - Hold on.
Don't shake it!
Don't shake it! Don't shake it!
I'm not walking on my own will right now.
Oh, dear.
Where should I hold? No!
This makes no sense. Oh, my!
(The cameraman didn't deserve this.)
I can't even go back.
Sun Bin, I'm sorry!
(My partner, I'm sorry!)
Sun Bin, I'm sorry.
I'm not cool, am I?
Gosh, I can't do it.
(I apologize for being uncool.)
Sun Bin.
I can't look you in the face.
(I can't face you.)
I can't look back.
(The sun sets while he's in the air.)
Hold on.
What should I do?
10 seconds left.
There's none.
- There's nothing? - Nothing.
Nothing?
- Nothing? - The mission has ended.
- My gosh. - It's over.
(The last race has ended.)
(The whistle blows to announce the end.)
Go home, everyone.
Sun Bin, you should go home too.
Leave.
(I hope you'll all go home.)
I want you to go home.
(I want to be alone right now.)
Helicam, go home. Everyone should go home.
I'm fine. Go home.
Save me!
(I don't care about the mission. Save me!)
Sun Bin, you suggested to ride this.
How humiliating is this?
(I hate this zip line so much.)
(The game ends with a couple's sad ending.)
The race is over.
I calculated all the money you have obtained.
We already know the loser.
The couple who won the race...
had the final amount of 246 dollars.
That's too much.
(Which couple had 246 dollars?)
Ji Hyo and Tae Hwan.
(Ji Hyo and Tae Hwan wins.)
(It's unbelievable. We won!)
Gosh, how incredible!
They left so much money.
- 240 dollars? - Yes.
How many pouches did they find?
Here's the ring, Tae Hwan.
He's a man, yet he'll take the ring?
What a shame.
Gosh, I wanted to give it to her.
Ji Hyo gets to bet her die...
once again after last week.
- Yes! - My goodness.
Thank you, Tae Hwan.
The couple who will become the two facial stickers is...
For your information, this couple...
lost by two dollars.
Really?
How unlucky.
- I wonder who it is. - Two dollars is so close.
- By any chance... - No way, it's not us.
Kwang Soo and Sun Bin.
(Kwang Soo and Sun Bin may be the losing team.)
- Yes! - Kwang Soo!
(The unfortunate couple ran out of their money quickly.)
You have 83 dollars left.
(Kwang Soo and Sun Bin have 83 dollars left.)
Is it the team with 81 dollars or 85 dollars?
Jae Seok and Yeo Eun have...
(Jae Seok and Yeo Eun may have lost.)
(They started off with the least amount of money, )
(but they saved money tenaciously during Search and Stop.)
They have 80 dollars...
- Plus 5 or 6 dollars? - Plus 5 dollars.
- It must be 85 dollars. - 80 dollars plus how much?
- Please... - No way...
Plus five dollars.
(Jae Seok and Yeo Eun have 85 dollars left!)
(It was a really close game, but Kwang Soo lost by two dollars.)
- Thank you! - They struggled so much too.
- Amazing. - Thank you.
- Let's play once again. - Thank you.
- Hilarious. - Kwang Soo.
You were poorer than I thought.
- What? You worked so hard. - What did you do?
When I was on the top,
a rescue party actually came and saved me.
- I'm serious. - We came down on a lift.
- Really? - Yes.
I dived into the deep water...
and took a bunch,
but there was only one dollar there.
(He finds it totally unfair.)
I went underwater.
- There was one dollar there. - There was nearly nothing.
You got us a meal today...
(Thank you for the meal and the coffee.)
I started with 200 dollars.
- Thank you. - You began with 100 dollars.
- Thank you, Kwang Soo. - We went bankrupt.
- We went bankrupt. - We began with 100 dollars.
Sun Bin said she wanted to ride the zip line.
Sun Bin, I'm going to kill you.
(Love can kill.)
Gosh!
I guess your love has waned too.
- Kwang Soo, thank you. - She looked at me as if...
I was a bug when I was hanging.
She was like this.
I saw.
How lucky.
- What a heartwarming finish. - It was full of twist.
Team Ji Hyo won the race.
Place the members' faces.
- Hold your anger. - Seriously...
- I'll get 2 Stickers again? - With 3 Stickers...
Ji Hyo won last week too. I lost once again...
after last week.
Why did you put Se Chan and me together?
You just need to avoid getting one.
Here I go.
Get 6, number 6.
- It can't be 3. - Please be 6.
- If we're chosen, it'd be amazing. - Seriously...
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(You must depart right away after getting 3 Stickers!)
(Who will be chosen this time?)
- Please, please. - One, two,
- three. - Gosh, Se Chan.
Let it be number six.
- It can't be number 3. - Let it be 6.
- Let it be number six. - It's okay.
- Number 6, number 6. - Please.
- Number six. - It's okay.
- It's number five! - It's Haha!
(Haha is chosen.)
(It's me?)
(Kwang Soo is saved, and Haha gets 1 Sticker.)
- Kwang Soo. - Ji Hyo.
Kwang Soo wasn't chosen.
What a twist!
- I can't believe it! - It's over.
Really?
- My goodness. - Why...
- Kwang Soo has 1, and Haha has 2. - Great job, Tae Hwan!
I wonder...
why Kwang Soo is happy.
- Kwang Soo is lucky. - I overcame my two Stickers again.
- This week... - If I'm chosen, I'm taking you.
(I'm taking you down with me.)
- If I'm chosen, I'm taking you. - This week...
Why are you happy?
(Haha promises that they'll be together.)
(Speaking a vulgar language)
(You're the only one I will choose.)
Seriously...
(The race ends in a cheerful vibe.)
Let's give a round of applause.
Great job.
(We thank the best 7 guests who performed superbly in Gyeongju.)
The two Stickers...
have been stolen by one of you.
(They keep suspecting and lying to each other.)
(They can only deduce with the clues.)
(A thief versus a sheriff)
(Hunt down the thief with clues and your sense only!)
(Who would be the thief?)
(Who would it be?)
Hide right here.
(A Thief Among Us)