Hello. Hello. Hello, everyone.
(The rain marks the end of summer at SBS Prism Tower.)
Haha, I have something to tell you.
- Haha. - It's good to be stylish,
but you dress way too young...
for a middle-aged man.
- Do you know that? - You look ridiculous.
- Seriously. - Come on.
- Don't say that. - Listen.
Don't call me a middle-aged man.
She is wearing a nightgown.
It's not a nightgown. It's fashionable these days.
- Fashionable, my foot. - Don't you know what a robe is?
- Did she just wake up? - I thought I was in a hotel.
Seeing Ji Hyo,
- I thought I was at a resort. - It's fashionable.
I thought I was at a resort in Sokcho.
My goodness, we have a professional golfer with us.
(So Min, nice shot.)
So Min, you look like a model for golf wear.
That's right.
- Good shot. - Nice shot.
Nice shot.
(Wear your confidence.)
Last week, my best friend, Se Chan, let me know...
- that he was watching... - Kwang Soo, why didn't you do it?
my performance on TV.
- He sent me a message. - Your performance was on.
He is different from someone who doesn't care about me.
(Kwang Soo is the one who doesn't care about Jong Kook.)
It's not like that.
- Kwang Soo is in trouble. - I am sorry.
When Jong Kook arrives in the morning,
he looks at me while he goes, "Se Chan, my best friend."
"My best friend".
This is how I survive.
- That's right. - I did watch your performance.
- I just didn't talk about it. - Promote my song on the radio.
Listen to me!
I watched your performance too!
I just didn't text you about it.
- I am sorry. - My goodness.
- Are you okay? - I am sorry.
- Your neck turned red. - I just didn't talk about it.
- Don't be ridiculous. - I am sorry.
- I acted without thinking. - Your neck turned red.
I am sorry.
(The family is ready to welcome the day.)
Today, you will have the summer vacation special,
Couple Retreat.
What does that entail?
(Couple Retreat)
There aren't enough women for the retreat.
- No, there aren't. - There needs to be couples.
Do we have guests?
- No way. - Lee Sun Bin.
(Is it the hot Lee Sun Bin?)
- Son Na Eun. - Na Eun?
(Is it the fawnlike Na Eun?)
For this retreat, we have prepared something.
- What is it? - Please come on in.
(The ones to fill the empty spots...)
(are coming.)
(Who are the guests?)
- Who are the guests? - We will be paired today.
Do we have guests today?
- Do we have guests today? - That must be it.
I guess we have guests.
- Why are you bringing those boxes? - That can't be it.
(They get boxes instead of guests.)
Why are we getting boxes instead of guests?
- Why are we getting boxes? - There are six boxes.
(What are these 6 boxes?)
What are these?
- There aren't enough women today. - No.
Two of the male members will be female students for the day.
(2 male members will be female students for the day.)
You'll go on an exciting 4-on-4 field trip.
All day?
I hate to dress up as a woman.
- I'll pick the last one. - I choose five.
I've made up my mind.
Please stand in front of the boxes you have chosen.
I'll choose this one then.
I'm really not sure what's what.
There are members who I wish wouldn't dress up as women.
They're Jong Kook and Seok Jin.
If I dress up as a woman...
It's because when Seok Jin dresses as a woman,
he looks exactly like the granny...
who used to run a stationery when we were young.
(He brings back old memories.)
- Exactly. - I'm serious.
I wondered why he looked so familiar.
She used to make toffee for us.
He looks so much like her in women's clothing.
(The race will be about their old memories if he gets picked.)
All right, everyone.
Those who pick the box with a wig in it...
will become the female members for today.
- What? - Something's in my box.
There's something.
(He finds a blonde wig in his box.)
It's a wig. Okay!
(Jae Seok gets picked.)
Great!
It's a wig. Okay!
(There's a red wig in Seok Jin's box.)
Yes!
(Seok Jin will be red-haired soon.)
- How can you both get picked? - Yes!
- I hate it. - Who got picked?
We're just too unlucky.
- You're the unluckiest. - Seriously.
- I admit it. - We're too unlucky.
What is this? The princess...
It may be better this way for Seok Jin.
- I can't believe it. - Goodness.
(Stay tuned to check their girly sides.)
Jae Seok's name will be Janny for today.
- Janny? - Goodness.
- It sounds nice. - I like the name.
Am I Jinny then?
- Seok Jin... - Jinny?
will be Seok Ja.
- Seok Ja? - Seok Ja...
- Hold on. - Why is my name Korean?
Because your name starts with Seok.
(It's to make the name similar.)
Indeed.
His last name should be changed too.
- I know. - Seok Ja.
- That's funny. - Seok Ja.
- Seok Ja. - Seok Ja.
We'll now begin the Running Man, Couple Retreat.
Today's race is...
Couple Retreat: Find the Scene Stealer.
(Couple Retreat: Find the Scene Stealer)
Among you, there's a secret couple.
What?
(There's a secret couple...)
(among us?)
Did someone receive their mission already?
The rest will win if they find the secret couple before the race ends.
The secret couple will win if the rest can't find them.
The losing team will receive a severe penalty today.
Until the race ends...
It's not me.
(It's you for certain.)
- I know it's you. - It's not me!
- I know it's you, punk. - No!
It's not me.
- Isn't it you? - It's not me.
- She did it once. - Not me.
- Ji Hyo. - It's not me.
I swear.
- Isn't it you? - I think it's her.
- I'm telling you the truth. - Everyone says they aren't the one.
- Not me. - The secret couple...
doesn't know they are the ones yet.
- They don't know? - Really?
- They don't know yet. - I see.
They don't know yet.
- Why did you grab me? - I'm sorry.
- Goodness. - I'm sorry.
They don't know yet.
They don't know?
- We... - We doubted each other for nothing.
- They don't know yet. - We only suspected each other.
The winning couple in each mission...
will be given a hint about the secret couple. Please do your best.
Now, we'll get changed into uniforms and go on the retreat.
(Let's start the exciting retreat with Janny and Seok Ja!)
I just can't stand watching Jae Seok and Seok Jin.
Goodness.
(Janny with blonde hair)
Give these bags to each member.
- Goodness. - Goodness.
My hair color is like Milla Jovovich's.
(The charismatic female warrior, Seok Ja)
- What? - Milla Jovovich.
- I thought it was World Cup. - What?
(He looks like the one who came out on the streets to cheer.)
Aren't you here to support the national soccer team?
- What? - I can't stand them.
- Excuse me, lady. - You look like a poodle.
I thought there was still a World Cup match going on.
(Calm down, ladies.)
Like I told you earlier, you will do missions as couples.
You'll be divided into couples through a simple way.
The male members will be seated in the bus first.
The female members will get on 1 by 1.
They will sit next to a member whom they wish to be a couple with.
For the four female members,
if the member you want to partner up with already has a partner,
you may shout, "You, come out."
Then the male member will get to choose between the two.
Whom should I choose?
"You, come out." Is it really necessary?
This is supposed to be exciting.
- Come on. - I mean, in the past...
- What are you talking about? - What do you mean?
- This isn't... - Goodness.
Try appealing yourselves.
Who wants to partner up with me?
I'm sorry, but please don't come.
Please.
You've got my attention.
(I'm attracted to bad guys.)
- Don't come. - Today,
- he'll be my partner. - Now,
- I have my eyes on you. - Jong Kook.
It's time to consider meeting someone older than you.
(How do you like a woman who's 10 years older than you?)
- I'm serious. - What do you think?
- Really. - Goodness.
- Consider meeting older women. - No, thank you.
(Please let me avoid Seok Ja.)
Boys, please get on the bus first.
- Make yourself comfortable. - Sure.
I didn't know So Min was this pretty.
So Min is so pretty today.
- So Min is pretty. - I know.
She's like an angel.
- She's pretty. - She's amazing.
I want Ji Hyo.
I want to partner up with Ji Hyo.
(Why do I miss her smile more today?)
Jae Seok will be too tiring.
(I'll rather choose a fire pit.)
I know.
- Seok Ja, you'll go in first. - Don't touch him.
- You'll choose a male partner. - Don't touch my Jong Kook.
I have no intention anyway.
(I'm going to meet my partner who will join me and my mature charms.)
Gosh, it's crazy.
(Whom should I choose?)
- Ji Hyo or So Min. - Seok Ja is coming.
- She's coming. - Pretend to sleep first.
(He pretends to sleep as if he ran into a bear.)
I have no one to choose.
- It's crazy. - Seok Ja.
Why are you sleeping?
I'm going to sit next to the person who is sleeping.
- I had a great sleep. - Goodness.
- Haha. - Who's sleeping?
- I thought you were sleeping. - I just woke up.
I'm going to sit next to the person who has his eyes open.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
I've made up my mind already. I'm going to sit next to you.
(Seok Ja will sit next to Jong Kook.)
- Please don't. - Nice!
- Don't do this. - You look great together.
You're attractive too.
- Not me. - You're attractive.
I have longer hair than you.
Didn't you suggest me to team up together before?
- Do that. - Come on.
- When you're cool. - You look great together.
(Janny takes a look at what's going on inside.)
I guess they're stopping him from sitting down.
- That's why it's taking long. - They're refusing him.
- Drink this. - I have it over there.
You have such nice hips.
(So Min compliments Janny's hips.)
(She's immersed in the role play.)
(So Min is helpless.)
You do have a problem.
"You have such nice hips."
She was taking out the water, and her hips looked so plump.
(Spitting out)
My goodness, you...
- Okay, I'll do it this way. - Goodness.
I'll choose between the strongest one and the youngest one.
I'll keep my words...
(Would you sit over there?)
(The red shuttlecock bounces here and there.)
What are you doing?
I'll sit here.
- Don't. - Hey!
- Is it okay for him to do this? - You can't sit here.
- Five. - He sat down.
4, 3, 2...
(He almost partners up with Kwang Soo then gets kicked out.)
Make him sit down.
(Everyone's desperate despite their different reasons.)
(Shouting)
- Jong Kook! - Sit down.
- He sat down! - Jong Kook!
- No! - He sat down.
Good.
It's against my will!
- Good. - My goodness.
I don't like you either.
- I really hate to be your partner. - Same here!
Goodness.
Next up is...
you, So Min. Go ahead.
(Whom should I choose as my partner?)
- So Min, make it quick. - Okay.
- So Min, this way. - Hello.
So Min, come to me.
She's so pretty.
(She's excited to find out what lies ahead of her.)
- You're so beautiful. - Take it easy and choose.
So Min, you know I complimented your dress today, right?
I told you that you're pretty.
If you choose me, you'll get to experience, "You, come out."
- Things may change. - Try it.
Raise your hand if you want to be my partner.
- Me! - Me!
- I'm serious. - Me!
(Please choose me.)
Put your hands down if you want to be my partner.
(She's enjoying this opportunity.)
Put them down quickly.
- Hey. - Raise your hands.
- They listen to you so well. - Put them down.
Stand up. Sit down.
Gosh, it's so exciting.
Tell me the person you have in mind.
I don't know about anything else, but I wish you to be at peace.
- So Min. - Choose me.
- Goodness. - Seok Ja, come out.
- What? - Gosh.
- Seok Ja, come out. - What?
Seok Ja. Okay, So Min!
(Welcome, So Min.)
- But this is... - Thanks, So Min.
She chose Se Chan.
- Se Chan isn't worth this much. - Wait a minute.
- You need to choose now. - What?
- You have to choose between us. - Okay, Seok Ja.
You're out.
Seok Ja, you're out.
(It wasn't necessary to ask.)
- Seok Ja. - So Min!
- Okay, sit down here. - Okay.
- Get out of the bus. - You have to go again.
- Get out. - I have to leave?
Seok Ja, get out.
- So Min. - Gosh.
(Se Chan and So Min are a couple.)
- What happened? - Goodness.
- What? - I got kicked out.
- It's no joke today. - It's Ji Hyo's turn.
They don't let you sit down.
- Why? - They push you away.
- Ji Hyo! - Goodness.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo, come sit here.
Make yourself comfortable.
- Ji Hyo, be free. - Ji Hyo.
(They're the same anyway.)
- You'll argue with Kwang Soo. - Take it easy and choose.
You'll get nagged if you're with Jong Kook.
(Will Haha succeed in persuading her?)
- Why not? - Good. Nice.
(Sincerity always works.)
Mapo-gu.
We're neighbors.
I might be partnered up with Seok Ja.
(They only have Janny and Seok Ja left.)
What should I do?
- It was Seok Ja from the beginning. - What took you guys so long?
Go away!
- Look at him. Isn't he so ugly? - Goodness.
- Gosh, he's so ugly. - Go to him already. Sit down.
Seok Ja was going to be my partner all along.
(Kwang Soo and Janny become a couple.)
This is making me mad.
- Seok Ja, come here. - Jong Kook doesn't have a partner.
(Laughing)
If you sit next to him, it's over.
- Jong Kook doesn't have a partner. - This is unfair.
- Okay. I'm going to sit here. - There you go.
(Jong Kook and Seok Ja become a couple.)
- Didn't I tell you? - You were right. We are a couple.
You are done picking your partners.
Now, we are going to be on our way.
(They set out for their retreat.)
- A secret couple is among you. - Hold on.
We will start Sentence in Five Seconds, and the first hint...
- of the secret coupe is at stake. - Sentence in Five Seconds?
(Sentence in 5 Seconds?)
I'm very logical.
You must make a sentence that makes sense within five seconds...
with five keywords given to you in the order received.
- For example, keywords are... - It has to make sense.
"Jae Seok", "Jong Kook", "love", "tear", and "zombie".
Jae Seok loved Jong Kook too much that he became a tearful zombie.
- You can make a sentence like this. - That was good.
- You must make the sentence... - It's not hard.
- It's not hard. - He created a story.
(Who will be the winner?)
We have to use the keywords in order.
Oh, my. I'm getting nervous.
It's me, it's me
The person who'll use the xylophone today is me, it's me
He's scary when he sings the song in disguise.
- He's really scary. What's wrong? - He looks creepy.
(He looks like a possessed girl in a foreign film.)
I guess he's into that song now.
- Goodness, I hate him. - I don't like him.
I'll show you.
- Get ready. Start. - Get ready. Start.
Because Son Na Eun looked like a squid, I was afraid she'd...
be in my dream, but she looked like Park Na Rae, a wanted woman.
(Because Son Na Eun looked like a squid, I was afraid she'd...)
(be in my dream, but she looked like Park Na Rae, a wanted woman.)
That didn't make sense.
- Why? - It didn't make sense at all.
How can you say Na Eun looks like a squid?
- Na Eun doesn't look like a squid. - Goodness. You're unbelievable.
(I was rushing, so I couldn't get my thoughts organized.)
In my dream, Na Eun was eating a squid,
but I got a call from Na Rae suddenly...
and found out I was a wanted man.
- What was that? - Why? It made sense.
No, it didn't.
- Of course it made sense. - For this mission,
there should be only one story from start to finish.
Jae Seok's sentence is good enough to be printed in papers.
- It should be as good as this - It shouldn't be as good as that
(It should be as good as this)
- Why do you keep singing that song? - What do you mean?
- Of course, I should. - Jong Kook.
Can I start after we see the keywords?
- No, you can't. - Is he going to play again?
- I was the first one. - We'll give him one more chance.
- We should just move on. - That's not fair.
If he was going to get another chance, I could've gone first then.
- Don't you agree? - You're right.
- But why is Jong Kook angry? - I don't know.
- That's right! - I don't know.
- Whenever we play games... - I'm angry when I play games here.
- Be quiet. - Viewers, do you know why he's mad?
If anyone knows why he's mad, please write on our board online.
- Why is Jong Kook angry? - Why did you say that?
- Stop picking on Jong Kook. - When I don't like something,
- I can express my feelings. - But your feelings...
- Do we have to accept everything? - I'm sorry, but excuse me.
I think I just lost my hearing in one of my ears.
Haha.
- Your ears are bleeding. - My ears are hurting too.
- Haha, I'm losing my hearing too. - This happens in life.
The citizens of our country had to fight for our country.
You're scaring me.
(Se Chan fails.)
- All right. Ji Hyo, you'll go next. - Ji Hyo.
Get ready.
- Set. - You can do it.
- Don't rush. - Start.
Jae Seok put on a wig, farted while watching an adult film,
and put on the skinny jeans.
- That was great. - That sounded weird.
The skinny jeans should've been ripped.
- It could've worked with that. - She should've said that instead.
- It was a bit lacking. - She should've said it ripped.
Jae Seok put on the wig and was copying an act in an adult film.
Wait, So Min.
(What did you say?)
- What did you say? - She said you copied the film.
- That came out of nowhere. - Why would he copy that?
- Why would he do such a thing? - Hey, you.
- That made the most sense. - I can't believe you.
- She has a lot of problems. - What's wrong with you?
(Ji Hyo fails.)
- Haha, you should try. - Haha, you're up. Get ready.
- All right. - Start.
- Geun Sik's first love was Byul. - Oh, my.
But Mr. Kim... Darn it.
("Geun Sik", "first love", "Byul", "Kim", and "mother-in-law")
(What happened between Geun Sik and Byul?)
- What are you doing? Hey. - This...
You always...
(Haha fails.)
Watch and learn.
I was looking at the stars with Geun Sik's first love.
I saw the mother-in-law who was bringing me the dried laver.
- That would've worked definitely. - Of course, it would.
- That's right. - Your sentence was perfect.
You would've approved my sentence.
- Okay. - Get ready.
- This is easy. Start. - Go for it.
Turbo was eating ramyeon after their comeback. Because of ramyeon,
I got gout. Because of gout, I got a runny nose... This is hard.
- That was hard. - Come on. What was that?
- That was horrible. - Mine was hard. Try it yourself.
- Try it. - Long time ago...
- Try it, Jae Seok. - Turbo was eating ramyeon...
You should stay out of this. Hey, try this.
(Haha, stay out of this. Janny, try this.)
- Try it. Do it right now. Start. - Wait.
Don't think too much. Just do it.
- I will give this a try. - No, don't do it.
- Jae Seok, you have to do it. - Wait. Why did you hit my nose?
- Why did he hit my nose? - Try it. Start now.
- This is funny. - Start.
- Watch. - Okay.
Turbo was eating ramyeon, and Jong Kook who has gout came.
He had a runny nose because he was filming in the cemetery.
(I'm faster and more accurate than anyone else.)
- That was good actually. - See?
- You're good. - That was good. Do it like this.
I will try this. It's not hard.
- Get ready. - Let's do this.
- What are my keywords? - Start.
You're bald, Jeon Do Yeon.
Ryu Su Jeong is a viper.
- Grand Award... - He failed.
Don't just read the keywords.
- He just read them. - Don't read the keywords.
- Were you doing pansori? - That was horrible.
(You're bald, Jeon Do Yeon)
- Ryu Su Jeong... - Viper has gotten the Grand Award
They weren't testing your vision.
- I made my wife into a viper. - You were testing your vision.
- What are you doing? - This is hard.
(Seok Jin fails.)
- Kwang Soo. Get ready. - I'll do it now.
Kwang Soo, go for it!
Start.
So Min's molar hurts so much. So she's a romantic? She likes...
- cucumber kimchi. It's on sale. - Hey, you.
(So Min's molar hurts so much. So she's a romantic?)
(She likes cucumber kimchi. It's on sale.)
Hey, what on earth are you saying?
- Hey. - Goodness.
- He was terrible. - Kwang Soo.
- Are you testing your vision? - His vocabulary is so poor.
- Hold on. - You must go back to kindergarten.
No. It was just that I couldn't see.
(Kwang Soo fails as he gives the worst sentence.)
- Jae Seok, let's see what you got. - At last, here's the expert.
- Let's see how Jae Seok does. - Watch me.
The moment you get it wrong, I'm going to kick you.
Let's do this.
- Kwang Soo, if I get this right, - This is impossible.
- we'll get a hint. - Do it well.
(I'll get us the hint.)
For 10 years, I have never felt nervous.
Your lips are pale. Why are you lying?
- Stop shaking your legs. - Be quiet.
(Janny, the fluent tongue)
- Don't be nervous. - Get ready.
- I'm going to count five seconds. - Okay.
Start.
I went to a club and played the James Bond game,
but I found a flying chair at the club.
(Laughing)
(But I found a flying chair at the club.)
Goodness, Jae Seok.
(When you are feeling embarrassed, just laugh.)
- You little... - You couldn't do yours.
- What was that? - You couldn't do it either.
He was the worst.
- I'm so embarrassed of him. - Kwang Soo, I'm sorry.
- That was close. - By the way,
he might've rigged the game because he's the secret couple.
(Janny was looking at the big picture not to get caught?)
That makes sense.
- We have to... - That was weird.
doubt the members who seem strange to us.
If they are too strange...
Then I should start with you, Jong Kook.
It's because you were terrible at this game.
- We should suspect you first. - Fine. Do it then.
We should suspect you and the old lady from the stationery.
- Jae Seok! - To be honest,
she did seem a bit suspicious to me.
- That's right. - Hey, you.
We will give the hint to the couple we think was closest to succeeding.
- They are Jong Kook and Seok Jin. - That's right.
- Give us the hint. - Actually, our sentences...
made some sense.
After you check the hint, the paper will be destroyed.
This is a hint about the secret couple.
- It's up to you to share it or not. - Goodness, I was close.
Check the hint now.
- We shouldn't share it now. - No, you should share it.
But Jong Kook knows better. Will you share it?
- Then we won't share hints either. - Goodness.
We will share the hint later.
- We will destroy the paper. - The first hint is...
The first one won't be a crucial hint.
(What was the first hint?)
(They arrive excitedly at the first destination.)
- There are tadpoles here. - Really, Ji Hyo?
- They are real tadpoles. - There are so many of them.
- I haven't seen them in ages. - There are tadpoles here.
- They released them. - There are a lot of them.
They are my friends.
I have so many friends.
(So Min feels excited as she meets her friends.)
- You have so many friends. - I forgot about my old friends.
- I don't remember them. - Everyone.
We are going to start our fun retreat.
I played with them a lot because I didn't have toys growing up.
I played with tadpoles and frogs.
What? What is this?
- Is this the class leader? - It's the class leader.
- You are the class leader? - Are you the class leader?
- No, the class leader called me. - Why do we have a class leader?
(A call from the class leader. Did we have a class leader?)
- Hello? - This is your class leader.
What did you say?
- The class leader called you. - Who are you?
- It's Chul Min. - He's turning into a liar.
- You should've at least hidden. - He's so brazen.
- At least conceal yourself. - What are you doing in front of us?
(This is ridiculous.)
- You should've hid somewhere. - You are so shameless.
- Hey. - You're right in front of us.
Just tell us.
- Hey, the class leader is calling. - Hi, class leader.
- Hold on. I'm going to college? - I think I can hear his voice.
- I can hear him too. - Who is this?
- Let me ask you this. - Who is it?
- I'm in college now? - Yes.
Hello, this is your class leader. Have the six of you arrived safely?
(Have the 6 of you arrived safely?)
- 6? You meant to say 8. - You're looking at us.
(There are 8 of us.)
(Why is the class leader saying there are only 6 of us?)
What? Only six of you went.
- Can you check again? - I just got the chills.
Are there ghosts?
(We told you. There are 8 of us.)
- I seriously got the goose bumps. - Hey!
- Look at us. There are eight. - All right.
- Let's count ourselves again. - Then two of us...
- are ghosts? - 1. Say 2.
- 2. - 3.
- Say 4. - 4.
- 5. - 6.
- 7. - 8.
- We're eight. - What is this?
(There are 8.)
(They got a mysterious call from their class leader.)
- What's going on? - Two are invisible?
(The class leader asked if the 6 of them arrived.)
Let me announce the real theme of today's race.
Summer vacation horror special,
Find the Ghosts.
(Summer vacation special: Find the Ghosts)
Two of you have a different identity from the others.
- Before the race ends, - Who are they?
- you have to identify each other, - I'm not.
and the surviving team will win.
The losing team will receive a scary penalty.
It's a horror special.
(The losing team will face a horrible penalty.)
(The trip started out fine, but a surprise is waiting for them.)
(Escape the empty school at dawn.)
(Which team will go through this horror?)
- Let's see. - You'll get hints about ghosts...
if you complete a mission.
The hint that was given on the bus was also about the ghosts.
Think about it. You should share it with us if it's about the ghosts.
MT stands for mystery thriller.
(MT turns out to stand for mystery thriller.)
(Laughing)
MT stands for mystery thriller?
Thriller...
(Is that the right spelling?)
- It starts with T. - Doesn't it start with S?
- It starts with "Th". - "Th".
- "Th". - It's S.
It's "Th".
It starts with "Th", not S.
- Thriller. - Thriller.
- "Th". - Really?
- It was a horror special. - Hold on.
- Let's move back a little. - I got it.
If we're to find ghosts... Hey, you ghost.
What's with you?
What are you doing?
- You're a ghost. - This is ridiculous.
We've found one.
And here's a grandma ghost.
(Janny thinks Seok Ja is a ghost.)
He's a Hong Kongese grandma ghost.
- Hong Kongese grandma ghost. - You're a poodle ghost.
You're a stationery store ghost.
(The grandma ghost has dyed her hair red.)
- I know who the ghosts are. - So do I.
You don't have a shadow.
What about you?
There's no sun.
You don't have a shadow.
It's raining.
- There's no sun. - You don't have a shadow.
- What are you talking about? - You don't have a shadow.
Now, there is something you should check secretly.
Your identity is in the bag with your name on it.
Check it secretly with your cameraman.
We're finding out now?
Right now?
Then why did you grab me by the neck?
I didn't even know.
We're finally finding out.
(They are not allowed to share their identities with each other.)
My goodness.
Let's see.
- My goodness. - What are you?
(Which two of them have special identities?)
I'm not a ghost.
Hey!
There's no sun.
(It's hard to read their faces.)
(Why is Ji Hyo giving her cameraman a high five?)
(Everyone is aware of his or her identity now.)
(You're obviously a ghost.)
- It's you, right? - No.
- It's you. - It's not, I swear.
- It's you. - Why did you give him a high five?
- Me? - A high five.
Because I'm not a ghost.
I'm not a ghost. I swear.
- You're suspicious. - Hey. You even got the hint.
(A moment ago)
(Ji Hyo...)
(is a human.)
(She gave her cameraman a high five to celebrate that she's a human.)
Two of us are ghosts.
(Jong Kook is sure Ji Hyo is a ghost.)
I saw Jae Seok's identity.
You did? Is he a ghost?
- Yes. - He is?
Ji Hyo is definitely a ghost, right?
What are you doing?
He's a human.
(It's so random.)
What makes you think so?
Because it hurt.
- Because it hurt? - You're a human.
What?
(Slap)
- Did it hurt? - Did it hurt?
It hurt a lot.
It hurt.
You're a ghost if you don't have any mole on your neck.
- Why? - That's how it is.
You don't have any. You have one.
- You have one too. - Is this how we're going to play?
I'm a ghost.
What do we even have to think about?
You have a red mole.
It's red. You have to remove it at the dermatologist.
- Really? - It's not a good thing.
Stop the nonsense already.
I feel like I'm possessed by a ghost.
Aren't you a ghost?
- If you eat a goat's poop... - All right.
You all know your identities now, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
Then let's move to another place...
and start a mission where you can obtain a hint about the ghosts.
- I need it. - Okay!
- Let's go! - What's with you?
- He's a ghost. - He's a ghost.
He's possessed by a ghost.
(Who are the ghosts?)
Are we spinning again?
- It's a game. - Isn't that the spinning equipment?
Is it a relay?
Are we spinning again?
We're not spinning?
That's good. We might throw up.
- Right. We all easily become sick. - We're not good at anything.
What is this?
We might be able to see who the ghosts are.
We'll probably put a stocking over our head.
This mission is called Relay Stocking Olympics.
You have to pass through the four sections...
within 100 seconds.
When one team finishes the race,
- you get half a hint. - I see.
If both teams succeed,
you'll get the entire hint.
- I see. - We have to get the hint.
Please form 2 teams of 4...
- and go to the starting point. - Okay.
2 teams of 4?
- Let's just stick to these groups. - Let's do that.
- No rock-paper-scissors? - Let's just stick to it.
- Listen to me. - Let's just do it this way.
- Let's play a game. - It's a hassle.
If it's a hassle, why doesn't he just stay home?
(I'm sorry, but why bother?)
- Gosh. Se Chan. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
Jong Kook is hurt.
Who doesn't know that? Why would you say that?
- Why would you say that? - Who doesn't know that?
(Why is he hurt?)
Everyone will put a stocking over their heads.
You can start the race only when the member before you is finished.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Okay. - Kwang Soo, please move.
Ji Hyo would work hard to avoid suspicion.
If she is a ghost, she will work hard.
(Ji Hyo is definitely a ghost.)
(I'm a human.)
(Humans should try to complete the mission and obtain hints.)
(Ghosts would try to hold the humans back.)
(Ji Hyo, Jae Seok, Haha, Kwang Soo)
I haven't done this in a long time.
Pull it over my head?
Gosh.
Jae Seok, you look amazing.
- You're amazing. - The king is back.
Your face is a mess.
Kwang Soo looks like Squidward.
(A squid on land)
It's a mess.
- Squidward... - Kwang Soo.
Ji Hyo, show us your face.
(It looks horrible.)
This is priceless.
- Ready. - Hold it.
- Like this? - Yes.
- Go. - Run.
- You have to succeed. - You have to succeed.
(It's hard to even get close to the beans.)
If you don't succeed, you are a ghost.
Ji Hyo looks okay.
- Go farther. - She doesn't look bad.
Good.
Look at the beans.
- Look at the beans. - Look at the beans.
(Struggling)
Unbelievable. Ji Hyo can look ugly too.
Well... There you go. Good.
Good. Ji Hyo is amazing.
- Two. - There you go.
You're doing great. You're fast.
Keep going.
- Three. - Yes.
She's good at everything.
- Four. - Okay.
- She's good at everything. - The last one.
- Five. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo is done moving 5 beans.)
Okay.
The king is back.
(I'm the king of face today.)
(He's unbelievable.)
He's amazing.
(Pay respect to the king's face.)
- Look at him. - No one can beat him.
Good.
We should take a picture.
We have to make it.
- Okay. - He's unbeatable.
We have to take a picture.
- Take one from here. - Go away.
(The picture of the king is saved in my phone.)
How can he look like that?
- Let's do this. - Okay.
Let's get the hint.
(The ghosts would try to fail the mission.)
Time is passing by.
Isn't that obvious?
(Annoyed)
(You're right.)
- I'm just warning you. - Of course, time is passing by.
- Okay. - It's hard, right?
It's hard.
- How many more? - Just one more.
- Success. - Okay.
(Jae Seok calms down, and finishes his task.)
He's done.
- You're going too fast. - All right.
- Oh, my. - What happened to his lips?
- Hey. - Isn't that a goby?
(Isn't that a goby?)
- It's a nutria. - Amazing.
(Haha has to hit two go stones off the board.)
What happened to his lips?
- Hey. - Isn't that a goby?
(Missing)
My lips looked like that too.
Hey.
- Slow down. - It's hard.
I did a good job.
- Are you failing on purpose? - Exactly.
- He's suspicious. - It's hard.
(Haha's continuous failure is making the others suspicious.)
- You're suspicious. - He must be a ghost.
- He's a ghost. - It's too obvious.
Hurry up. Time is ticking.
- He's failing on purpose. - He's a ghost.
I'm doing my best.
Are you sure?
I swear.
(Haha has been suspicious. Is he a ghost?)
- I swear. - He's suspicious.
- He's so bad. - It's hard.
What?
Okay.
(Haha finally finishes his task.)
Gosh.
(Haha has done a bad job. What is his identity?)
Come here.
- The best player is up. - Go on, Kwang Soo.
Go on.
(He only has 5 candles to blow out.)
(If he succeeds, he earns half of a hint about the ghosts.)
(His skin is very resilient.)
You're doing well.
(Kwang Soo looks like a squid.)
You're doing well, Kwang Soo.
- Hurry up. - He looks hilarious.
Move forward a little more.
Blow the candles.
What's the name of that large rat? Is it called nutria?
- He looks like a nutria. - You got it.
(He blows out 5 candles.)
- Okay. - He got it.
He was quite fast.
He was definitely fast.
(Will they get half of a hint about the ghosts?)
2 minutes 20 seconds.
- What's the time? - 2 minutes 20 seconds.
(They fail to earn the hint.)
Isn't that 100 seconds?
- Gosh, it's 140 seconds. - I was embarrassed.
Haha was being very strange.
- No, I wasn't. - He was careless at the end.
Tapping it a few times didn't work. I did it very carefully. I swear.
I've played it before.
- It's not that hard. - If you tap it...
(Haha was being especially slow today.)
- It's different from tapping. - He couldn't do it quickly.
I don't think he's good at it.
As you clear the mission,
there are ghosts among you.
Pick four members randomly.
We'll give you one last chance.
If you succeed,
I'll give you a hint about the ghosts.
Okay.
It's the four of us.
- It's the four of you. - Here we go.
(Jong Kook is up next.)
Jong Kook looks very scary.
- I think he closed his eyes. - That's not how you wear it.
(Jong Kook's robot-like face looks more frightening than a ghost.)
These are different.
- Didn't we use them before? - Are they smaller?
(He succeeds 1 immediately.)
He's good.
- Try that one. - It's not easy.
- Take your time. - Hit the one on the top.
Try the other one.
- No, it doesn't work. - He's good.
Hit the one on the left!
- The left. - I got it.
Blow out the five candles.
Pull harder.
- Come here. - You can do it, So Min.
Hurry up, So Min.
Blow out the candles now.
Blow.
(So Min walks heavily.)
Blow from there.
- You have 20 seconds. - 20 seconds.
We need the hint.
- Hurry up. - We need the hint.
Look at her.
- Where are you aiming? - The candles are here.
Come on.
(She uses her hand.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
(What is she trying to do?)
The stocking is pulled down too low.
- Pull it up to the chin. - Pull it up.
You're good. Try it.
It'll work.
Blow out the candles now.
Blow them out.
- Blow them out. - Blow.
- Blow out the left one. - She's stuck.
- There you go. - She made it.
(Thanks to Jong Kook's help, So Min succeeds.)
You made it.
Good job, So Min.
(Relay Stocking Olympics' Round 2 is over.)
The time limit is 150 seconds.
Your record is 149.82 seconds.
(They clear the mission miraculously.)
That's right.
Let's catch the ghosts.
It'll be given to everyone.
- Here's the hint. - The hint is given to everyone.
- Okay. - All right.
I can prove that I'm not a ghost.
(What's the second hint?)
Let's take a look.
- "Legal name"? - What's this?
What does that mean?
- It's half of a hint. - What?
It's someone who uses a nickname.
It's Haha and Ji Hyo.
(The ghosts may be Haha and Ji Hyo.)
- There's only two. - What is this?
The hint can either be...
the ghosts use nicknames...
or not.
You only received half of a hint.
- Then it's useless. - Right.
There's something that you're missing.
There are more who use nicknames.
- There's Janny. - Seok Ja?
Come on, those don't count.
Those don't count.
Yes, they do.
Why would I be given a nickname?
Hints in the beginning are usually general.
- If it's about nicknames... - That's not right.
Didn't we get a specific hint in the beginning?
You should tell us.
It's pointless to keep it a secret.
Since many of you want it, we'll share the hint.
- The hint was... - We don't have a reason to hide it.
This is what I find funny.
Both of you saw the hint.
Does Seok Jin need Jong Kook's permission?
(Seok Jin is controlled by Jong Kook.)
By the way,
I'm sure that Seok Jin is a ghost.
I keep hearing an echo.
He keeps repeating...
what Jong Kook says.
He's like a bird...
that imitates what people say.
Hello, hello.
- Tell us. - He's like that bird.
I'm glad that you're on my side.
I'm serious. Okay.
Let's share the hint.
This hint is actually quite general.
"One of the ghosts is unlucky."
(The hint is "one of the ghosts is unlucky.")
You should share the hint with us. We won't share it next time.
(With this hint, they can narrow down the possibilities.)
"One of the ghosts is unlucky."
One of them is unlucky.
It depends on who's very lucky...
- or unlucky. - By the way,
Haha is also unlucky.
(They start to suspect those who are unlucky.)
Some of us won't be able to eat.
I really want to eat.
If you clear this mission, you earn a Meal Card and a hint.
- Okay. - Meal Card?
We're known to be unlucky when it comes to meals.
I'm the unluckiest.
We won't get to eat again.
- I'll drop out of this game. - I'll win.
(Give us the loser's meal.)
This mission is called...
Guess the Movie.
(Guess the Movie)
It's an individual game related to movies.
- Is it an individual game? - Movies?
Choose the time at which you want to listen.
We'll play the audio of the movie at that time for 10 seconds.
- Do we guess the movie title? - I'll definitely win.
Guess the movie title based on the audio.
I watch so many movies.
- Is it an individual game? - Yes.
(Se Chan is very confident.)
You win a hint and a Meal Card for a full course meal.
- Okay. - A full course meal?
The next three members get a Meal Card for a midsize meal.
The last four members...
will get a Meal Card for a small meal.
I've been unlucky with food these days.
It's driving me insane.
- Let's start with Se Chan. - Me?
- For the first movie, - I'm really bad at this.
- tell us the minute and the second. - Se Chan starts.
Let's see.
(He must choose the time wisely.)
- I pick 48 minutes 40 seconds. - That's a bad choice.
(He chooses 48 minutes 40 seconds.)
That's a bad choice.
- It's hard to say. - Here's the first movie.
- It's my turn anyway. - Right.
At that time, for a 1.5-hour movie...
- It's a boring part. - That's right.
- It's boring. - It's before things happen.
You'll hear it exactly for 10 seconds.
10 seconds? Let's go.
Play the movie.
- Aren't we leaving? - Yes.
Say hello to my nephew.
It's a Korean movie.
- It's difficult. - I have no idea.
I only heard footsteps.
- I have no idea. - Where did they go?
- You have to make a guess. - They were talking while walking.
(He tries to make an inference.)
It's impossible to know.
Which movie related to fish were you in?
(He asks all of a sudden.)
It's not about fish.
It's called "Collective Invention".
- It's "Collective Invention". - No, it's not.
- It's... - It's...
- a famous movie. - What is it?
- So Min is next. - Whose voice was it?
One hour.
40 minutes.
- 1 hour 40 minutes? - Yes.
- It's a recent movie. - Play the movie.
If he's a ghost...
Gosh, this is easy.
(The line sounds familiar.)
(They know the answer.)
- It's so easy. - Be quiet.
It's obvious. She picked a good time.
- She picked a great time. - Goodness.
I didn't hear it.
I know the actor's name.
- She couldn't hear it. - I couldn't hear it.
She's a ghost if she guesses wrong.
So Min.
- You have three seconds. - I don't hear well.
(She ponders.)
- Two. - "Friend"?
No, it isn't.
The movie relates to today's theme.
What do you think, Jong Kook?
I know the answer.
(Will his answer be correct?)
- Are you... - "The Wailing".
(Jong Kook is correct.)
It's so obvious.
(It's the highlight scene that So Min selected.)
(This is the scene that Se Chan selected.)
Say hello to my nephew.
She's a ghost.
How can she not recognize it?
We said that the movie relates to today's theme.
- She may not know. - I watched "The Wailing" twice.
- Right. - The sound wasn't clear.
Let's start with So Min.
1 hour 20 minutes.
- 1 hour 20 minutes? - Yes.
- Play the movie. - What if it's an hour long?
It may be a scene without lines.
The sound may not be clear.
(What kind of background music is it?)
(He pretends to know.)
I think the movie ended.
- This is... - It's a foreign movie.
- Which song is it? - Is it that movie?
- It's a foreign movie. - Which song is it?
Isn't it a foreign movie?
I don't think I'll get a chance to answer.
- I don't recognize it. - You have three seconds.
- 3, 2, - So Min.
- I have no idea. - 1.
"Christmas in August"?
1 hour 5 minutes.
Here's 1 hour 5 minutes.
I might get a chance.
Play the movie.
(Panting)
Is it an adult movie?
Dear fellow students.
Fall is coming to an end...
- I got it. - I got it.
- Fall is coming to an end... - I got it.
(I got it.)
- "Dear fellow students." - "Fall is coming to an end."
"Fall is coming to an end."
It's a school movie.
- A school movie? - A school movie?
Is that a thing?
It's a school movie.
(Seok Ja shows off his broad vocabulary.)
You have three seconds.
It features Kim Soo Hyun at the end.
- Three, - Was it Sulli?
- two, - No .What's the title?
- one. - Hold on.
He's failed.
I don't remember the title.
- It's not that one. - Seok Ja.
(It's Seok Ja's turn.)
1 hour 33 minutes.
- 10 seconds from 1 hour 33 minutes. - The movie would be over.
- No. - It'd be over.
Play the movie.
The movie is over. There are only subtitles.
- The credits are rolling. - Please be quiet.
It's the credits.
It's over.
My huckleberry friend, Moon River
(He suddenly sings.)
- Moon River - I got it.
- Moon River - What is it?
(Seok Ja just shows off her singing skills.)
My huckleberry friend
Three,
- two... - "Miss Granny"?
- No. - It's not that one.
"Whispering Corridors".
- Gosh. - "Whispering Corridors".
It doesn't have that kind of music.
It's a school movie with ghosts.
I know this one.
(Se Chan says he knows the answer.)
Please don't say the right answer.
58 minutes 30 seconds.
- 58 minutes 30 seconds. - We're close.
Play the movie.
(What kind of part would it be?)
What would we be doing?
I'd be an architect, and you'd be a pianist.
I got it.
(I'd be an architect.)
- I got it. - Amazing.
I'd be an architect, and you'd be a pianist.
(Kwang Soo's choice was perfect.)
I know this.
I got it.
Unbelievable.
It's this movie.
- Kwang Soo. - I knew this one.
- "Architecture 101". - That's right.
Gosh.
(Architecture 101)
(Kwang Soo chose a dating scene.)
(The pretty voice...)
(was Suzy's.)
(The music was from a scene where the man looks around the house.)
"You'd be a pianist, and I'd be..."
- I knew this one. - It gave me goosebumps.
You heard everything.
I'll find the ghosts.
- I'll find them. - Aren't you a ghost?
You're a ghost yourself.
Let's go. The next one.
55 minutes 18...
55 minutes 17 seconds.
Play the movie.
(If Kwang Soo gets it right, he will win first place.)
- Isn't that what the law says? - What are you talking about?
It's illegal to stop the guardian from visiting.
Then...
(The dialect and the content are unusual.)
You...
I know this one. I definitely know this one.
I can bet my everything that I know it.
- You don't know this one? - Wait.
I know this one.
(Excited)
(Song Kang Ho talks about the law in Busan dialect.)
(The correct answer is "The Attorney".)
(This famous movie featured Song Kang Ho and the late Kim Young Ae.)
(Kwang Soo made an excellent choice once again. Will he win?)
- "Barefoot Ki-bong". - It's not that one.
- Barefoot Kwang Soo. - Can I say the answer right away?
I know this one.
- Can I say it? - I know this one.
- Just say it. - My answer is...
Okay.
- "The Attorney". - That's right.
- It's correct. - All right.
(Janny wins first place.)
(That's right.)
- I thought it was "The Lawyer". - He thought it was "The Lawyer".
(Seok Ja is so charming.)
- "The Lawyer"... - "The Lawyer"?
That's right.
Jae Seok...
- won a hint... - Oh, my.
as well as a full meal.
(I can't believe this.)
- I'm jealous. - Now...
I'm so frustrated I lost the chance to Jae Seok.
- Really. - Let's continue.
We'll determine 2nd, 3rd, and 4th places.
- Let's start. - I still have a chance.
Here we go. Ji Hyo.
- One hour... - One hour...
- five minutes... - five minutes...
- 30 seconds. - 30 seconds. Play the movie.
(What movie is it this time?)
It sounds creepy.
(Is something being dragged?)
It must be a thriller.
- I'm getting the creeps. - That doesn't help at all.
- It sounded creepy. - Something is being dragged.
- A person might be being chopped. - What are you talking about?
"Train To Busan"?
You thought someone was eating something, right?
- It's not that. - Haha.
Someone is approaching something.
1 hour 21 minutes 7 seconds.
- 1 hour 21 minutes 7 seconds. - It'd be near the climax.
Play the movie.
- Help! - Soo Yeon.
(Sisters call each other hurriedly.)
(And they run.)
The answer is,
- "The Host". - That's right.
No?
- No. - I thought it was right.
"The Host".
- That's right. - No.
- It's not that one. - I thought it was right.
(It's becoming more and more confusing.)
5 minutes 15 seconds.
- 5 minutes 15 seconds. - It's the beginning part.
- The movie would have just started. - Play the music.
You haven't even started eating your popcorn by then.
They're driving.
I picked the wrong part.
It's a driving scene.
Hold on.
All I can hear is the rain outside.
- Is it playing? - Hold on.
- Is it on? - All I can hear is the rain.
- I can't hear anything. - The rain outside...
is louder.
You're no better than me.
You have to choose somewhere after an hour.
- What's your answer? Three, - I might have a chance.
- two... - My answer is,
"Inside Men"?
(Wrong)
- So Min. - I had no choice.
So Min.
1 hour 30 minutes 33 seconds.
Play the movie.
(Panting)
Just hearing the sound is...
Gosh.
- They don't say anything. - I might have a chance.
(Groaning)
- I might... - Is this okay?
Can we air this?
(My goodness.)
(Is this suitable for broadcasting?)
What will happen?
Tell us.
I'd like to hear some more.
- Just a little bit more. - A little bit more.
We want to hear more.
(You'll soon find out.)
- That was close. - Someone came in.
- No. - What was that?
- It must be a bathroom scene. - A bathroom scene?
- I think I know it. - Like this.
- What's your answer? - I think I know it.
(Does Jong Kook know?)
- Three, - What is it?
- two... - "A Tale of Two Sisters"?
- I think I know. - "A Tale of Two Sisters"?
What?
(Correct)
Really?
(Is it really correct?)
What?
I knew it from the beginning.
- Because they're sisters? - Because they're sisters.
- Because they're sisters? - How did you know?
I thought I'd get this one.
How did you know?
- I thought I heard Im Soo Jung. - I had no idea.
- Amazing. - I had no idea.
(It was definitely Im Soo Jung's voice.)
(The groaning was...)
(from physical exertion.)
(The members imagined something naughty.)
It's Jong Kook's turn.
Tell me where you want to play the movie.
It doesn't take so many turns to get it right.
One hour.
10 seconds from 1 hour. Play the movie.
It's music again.
(Someone is running with beautiful music playing.)
It's music.
It must be a bed scene.
- It's a train. - How do you know?
- It's a train. - "Don't go." Is it like that?
- It's a train. - It must be a bed scene.
- A train is running. - A train...
(If it is a train...)
It's "Galaxy Express 999".
(Could it be "Galaxy Express 999"?)
Are you kidding me? "Galaxy Express 999"?
"Snowpiercer".
- No. - "Snowpiercer".
It's obviously a Mugunghwa train.
Or it's a Saemaeul train.
(The sound is...)
(from the horses' hoofs.)
(It's from...)
(the movie, "Marathon", featuring Jo Seung Woo.)
- All right. - Seok Jin.
It was definitely a train.
- You have to choose the second. - Someone is on a train.
50 minutes 20 seconds.
Play the movie.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook need just one more point.)
(Who will win the midsize meal?)
What is this?
(They're imagining naughty things again.)
What's going on?
- Is it R-rated? - Wait a minute.
- Can this be aired? - What is it?
Goodness.
- Is it R-rated? - Is it basketball?
This is a big hint.
Is it in the train?
(What could it be?)
They chased after a train.
- I know the answer. - Didn't they chase a train?
Which movie is it?
The answer is "Assassination".
That's not it.
- It's not a dark movie. - No, it isn't.
Which movie is it? It's too difficult.
20 minutes 12 seconds.
(He picks 20 minutes 12 seconds.)
Play the movie.
I'd be impressed if you guessed right.
You're very impressive when you run.
I know the answer.
(The determining hint is "when you run".)
(What is his answer?)
- "Marathon". - That was amazing.
Yes!
(The answer is "Marathon".)
(Kwang Soo wins a midsize Meal Card.)
(Kwang Soo is lucky today.)
What happened?
Gosh, he's so lucky.
- What's going on with you? - What's wrong with you today?
Are you a ghost?
(Tell us honestly.)
He must be a ghost.
No matter what I do, you accuse me of being a ghost.
- Goodness. - He must be a ghost.
Now,
Jae Seok gets a full-course meal.
Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and So Min get a midsize meal.
The remaining four get a small meal.
Too many get a small meal.
- Janny. - Is there something for me?
It's a hint.
In 1, 2.
It's an envelope.
Share the hint with us.
- It's a hint. - He won't share if he's a ghost.
- He'd share if he isn't. - Right.
Why wouldn't you share it with us unless you're a ghost?
(They demand that he shares the hint.)
(What kind of hint did he get?)
- Wait a minute. - Share it with us.
(There are women among the ghosts.)
Come on.
(What does the hint say?)
- Tell us. - It's up to you to decide.
- What's wrong? - This is big.
- Tell us. - What does it say?
Gosh, it's big.
What is it?
- It's an individual competition. - I got creeped out.
- Is it that shocking? - Yes.
- Is it specific? - Yes.
Shouldn't he tell us the hint?
We worked together.
It's because Jae Seok is a ghost.
It's not really shocking.
- What is it? - I can share it with others.
- What is it? - Share it with us.
I can share it with others.
You should.
Gosh, it's not a helpful hint.
- What is it? - I forgot that I'm a woman.
(What did he say?)
- What's wrong? - I forgot that I'm a woman.
(Half of the members are women.)
Some ghosts are women.
- There are women. - I see.
(Janny and Seok Ja are beautiful women today.)
What's wrong with you, Janny?
Come on, Janny.
- A ghost is a woman. - It's not very helpful.
- We have four women. - I'm such a fool.
- That means it's among all of you. - I know.
We suspected that already.
This is annoying.
Based on that, it's confirmed that he's not a ghost.
Congratulations.
He wasn't a ghost after all.
I'm so annoyed.
(Which one of them is a ghost?)
He's human after all.
Let's forget it and eat.
Okay.
Can you give me some food, Jae Seok?
What kind of stew is that?
It looks so delicious.
- We can eat it too. - We get sujebi.
- Sujebi is good enough. - Look at the eel.
It looks delicious.
I understand why people watch mukbangs.
We can hear the sound and smell it.
- It'll be delicious with the broth. - Right.
I dipped it in the broth.
The food is great here.
How is the food?
(Impressed)
The broth is excellent.
It's so good that I want to offer it to someone.
I'm not joking. It's delicious.
Aren't we doing this today?
What?
What did you say?
(Give me one bite.)
The performance with dried laver is over.
(The business is closed.)
- I'm sorry. - There won't be any performances.
- That's outdated. - We did it already.
Why are you repeating what we've done?
- Hey. - I thought he was doing...
- Ji Hyo. - something funny.
I'll make us eat in one go. Do you want to share the food?
- How? - In one go.
This will work.
Today's a day to eat chicken. Here's a chicken.
(He offers a chicken.)
- Here's a chicken for you. - He's sharing it.
- This is... - What is that?
Isn't it too small?
It's because it's a young hen.
- It's too small. - They're easier to eat.
- Can you give me a bigger one? - Have it all.
Would you like some? It's my favorite.
I saved it for you.
I'm sorry, but I don't like chicken.
- Is that so? - Yes.
(I'm sorry, Jong Kook.)
(Is that so?)
- Is that so? - I take that back.
(Did you say you don't like chicken?)
No, I take that back.
I'll eat it anyway.
It's delicious.
- It's fresh. - No, it's mine.
- It's mine. - Don't eat it.
- It's delicious. - Give it to me.
This chicken is delicious.
Don't be angry.
- I love chicken. - Okay.
Jong Kook, you succeeded.
Really? What will you give me?
- He can't do that. - Getting food wasn't my intention.
Are you doing something, Haha?
- Is he Jung Dong Nam? - I'm Jung Dong Nam.
(Haha puts on a performance.)
He's exactly like him.
- He deserves it. - He's exactly like him.
Bring me your bowl.
- That was impressive. - Thank you.
- Goodness. - Excuse me.
Could you pay attention?
Give him some sujebi.
What have you prepared?
Gosh, it's embarrassing.
- Let's think. - What was that?
(They feel sorry for her.)
Can you be more committed to it?
You put too much trust in Seok Jin.
Are you starting a fight with him?
- You shouldn't trust him. - You promised.
Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo becomes pathetic because of Seok Jin.)
- Ji Hyo, I have an amazing idea. - What?
(Believe me, Ji Hyo.)
- I did it, Jae Seok. - What?
- It's a dried laver facial mask. - That's great.
She fails again.
(They feel sorry for her again.)
You're making me lose my appetite.
- You said it'd work. - You're making me lose my appetite.
(Hitting)
(You said the dried laver facial mask would work.)
- Ji Hyo. - You said it'd work.
Ji Hyo.
- You promised. - I like what you did.
It was realistic.
That was great, Ji Hyo.
I liked the sound when she hit his head.
It's his first time being hit like that in 40 years.
The sound was loud.
I haven't heard such realistic sound in a while.
(Who's really a ghost?)
(It's nighttime.)
(M University)
(It starts...)
(at a deserted school.)
The final mission is called...
Escape Mystery Thriller Race.
- Really? - It's an escape.
(Escape Mystery Thriller Race)
It's Escape Mystery Thriller Race.
(It's the last chance to find out the secret couple.)
Once you enter the building,
the doors will close immediately.
You have the chance to escape...
when the door opens once for five minutes.
Only once?
If two humans escape, humans win.
If one of them is a ghost, the ghosts win.
(The two who escape must be human for humans to win.)
During the race, humans can eliminate...
the ghosts by tearing off their name tags.
(Humans can eliminate the ghosts by tearing off their name tags.)
The ghosts can't tear off name tags.
Right, but if a human tears off a name tag...
of another human, humans lose immediately.
(They must eliminate only the ghosts.)
It requires thinking.
Isn't the chance too low to win?
You may guess other members' identities based on the hints.
You may find out by going on the ghost elevator.
- What's that? - What is it?
(There's a ghost elevator.)
The ghost elevator operates when three people are in it.
If 2 of them are ghosts, the elevator stops on the 4th floor.
(If 2 of them are ghosts, the elevator stops on the 4th floor.)
(It's a chance to determine the ghosts.)
- Two ghosts? - This is scary.
- Isn't this too scary? - It's really scary.
Is it okay if only one of them is a ghost?
It'd be scary if it stopped on the fourth floor.
- Goodness. - 1, 2, 3, 4, open.
When you can use the elevator will be announced.
Only the three members who arrive first may use the elevator.
If you get on the elevator, you can find out who the ghosts are.
- You can find out. - We'd find out then.
Escape Mystery Thriller Race begins now.
- Okay. - Okay.
It's a thriller.
Jong Kook seems suspicious.
Jong Kook...
gets angry no matter what.
He has a strange mentality.
- I can't tell. - What I said was correct.
We should beat him up.
I know.
We can work as a team.
It's possible with the three of us.
(Are you sure it's possible?)
I think Ji Hyo is a ghost.
So Min might be a ghost too.
(Everyone thinks Ji Hyo is a ghost.)
Why does everyone think I am a ghost?
I think it might be...
Seok Jin...
(Ji Hyo is suspicious of Seok Jin...)
or So Min.
(Ji Hyo is suspicious of Seok Jin and So Min.)
(She makes scary sounds.)
(A ghost or not, she is crazy.)
(Meanwhile...)
(Sighing)
I don't think anyone is suspicious of me.
Who is the other ghost?
(Who is the other ghost?)
Please check your identity in secret.
(Jae Seok's identity was...)
(a ghost.)
My goodness.
(He is at the final race.)
If I make a mistake and get branded as a ghost,
I will end up roaming the Earth forever.
You need to do well.
If we make a mistake, we will end up roaming the Earth forever.
We need to move onto the afterlife.
(He needs to lure a human being and escape.)
The race will start now.
(They get ready for the race.)
In five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
- The race begins. - Let's go.
My goodness.
Let's look for hints.
Okay.
Se Chan.
The race starts.
(Ghosts versus humans. How will the final race end?)
It's important to find the hints quickly.
I need to find them quickly.
Are there different sets of hints...
for ghosts and humans?
The humans win if they escape together.
Who are the humans?
(The humans win if they escape together.)
I need to find them.
I need to know...
I need to know who the humans are.
(The ghosts win if a human and a ghost escape.)
I am scared.
(Who is the other ghost?)
I am famous for being terrible at finding hints.
(He finds a hint.)
My goodness.
(There is a comedian among the ghosts.)
It could have been disastrous.
(It's a hint about me.)
"There is a comedian among the ghosts."
My goodness.
(He discards the hint right away.)
- Did you find a hint? - Yes.
What does it say?
I can't tell you.
(It's a crucial hint.)
I can't tell you already.
Do you want to be penalized?
At this rate, you will receive a penalty.
Let's focus on finding as many hints as possible.
- Did you find anything? - Not yet.
Is it a crucial hint?
No.
(It's just that the only comedians are Seok Jin, Se Chan, and me.)
Isn't this hint...
too crucial?
It's like giving away the answer.
(Where are you, hints?)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Kwang Soo, come here for a second.
(Se Chan calls for Kwang Soo with urgency.)
What is it?
(Does he have an important hint?)
For goodness' sake.
(Are you scared?)
(It's fun to pull a prank on Kwang Soo.)
Are we allowed to go upstairs?
Kwang Soo is scared.
(Did you think I was done?)
Stop it.
I will hit you before the end of the race,
- okay? - I am playing a ghost.
That's the concept of the race.
(He continues to annoy Kwang Soo.)
For goodness' sake.
Do you think I will be scared?
(The long one and the annoying one)
What is your problem?
Aren't the ghosts at a disadvantage?
(Janny is looking for hints.)
These lockers are empty.
(He finds another hint.)
(He finds it before Jong Kook does.)
My goodness.
(Running)
(What is the hint?)
It must be a hint regarding the humans.
(There is a man among the humans.)
What is this?
What kind of a hint is this?
"There is a man among the humans"?
For goodness' sake.
What kind of a hint is this?
(Hints on the humans are very vague.)
For goodness' sake.
I am scared. Why am I so scared today?
The ghost elevator has opened.
(The ghost elevator has opened.)
(The ghost elevator operates when there are 3 passengers.)
(If 2 passengers are ghosts, the door opens on the 4th floor.)
(Ghost elevator)
(It's a good chance to identify the ghosts and humans.)
The ghost elevator has opened.
The three members who arrive first may use the elevator.
(Only those who run can get on the elevator.)
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, and Jong Kook head to the elevator.)
Let's go.
- Seok Jin. - Are you getting in?
- Of course, I am. - Let's go.
We need one more person.
I am here.
Those who have a high chance of being a ghost should get in.
- There are 3 people. - 3 passengers have arrived.
Please get into the elevator.
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Kwang Soo enter the ghost elevator.)
Wait a minute.
I will know if I watch from here.
I will see if it stops...
at the fourth floor.
- Let's go to the 5th floor. - It's heading to the 5th floor.
If it stops on the fourth floor, both of you are ghosts.
- What? - It means both of you are ghosts.
If it stops on the fifth floor, only one of us is a ghost.
(If 2 out of the 3 passengers are ghosts,)
(the door will open on the 4th floor.)
(It's time to see if it will open on the 4th floor.)
My goodness, it stopped.
(The door opens.)
I got goosebumps.
My goodness.
No way!
(That means there are two ghosts.)
- That means there are 2 ghosts. - 2 of us are ghosts.
(The other ghost is Kwang Soo or Seok Jin.)
- This is insane. - This is insane.
Did it stop on the fourth floor?
So two of them are ghosts?
It seems like the elevator stopped on the fourth floor.
(Everyone freaks out.)
- It stopped on the fourth floor. - Who were in the elevator?
- I don't know. - Who were in the elevator?
What is going on?
Are you ghosts?
- For goodness' sake. - Wait a minute.
- Are you ghosts? - My goodness.
I got goosebumps.
What happened?
What is it?
The two of them are ghosts.
They are ghosts.
I am not a ghost.
- They are ghosts. - I am scared.
Does that mean there are two ghosts among you?
- It stopped on the fourth floor. - Then two of you are ghosts.
Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, and I were in the elevator.
- I am serious when I say this. - The three of you were in it.
Kwang Soo and Jae Seok are ghosts.
I am not a ghost.
Kwang Soo has to be a ghost.
(Kwang Soo is always the number 1 pick.)
- I am not a ghost! - Yes, you are.
(Who is the other ghost?)
(After the incident at the ghost elevator)
This is driving me crazy.
I need more hints.
(Between Seok Jin and Kwang Soo, who is the ghost?)
I need to find more hints.
(Looking around)
(He finds a hint.)
(Let's hide first.)
What?
(There is a singer among the ghosts.)
"There is a comedian among the ghosts."
"There is a singer among the ghosts."
Wait a minute.
This is...
(That means...)
(Seok Jin meets both conditions.)
Wait a minute.
If three pairs escape.
(Is Seok Jin the most likely to be a ghost?)
One person will be left.
- What is it? - Are you a ghost or not?
I am human.
Are you really?
Which hint did you find?
Think about it.
- It's crystal clear. - Then remove Jae Seok's name tag.
(Then remove Jae Seok's name tag.)
- The hint I found... - That's a bit...
The hint I found...
suggests either you or Jae Seok is a ghost.
(Does the hint Ji Hyo found point to Janny and Seok Ja?)
Isn't this a hint?
(A moment ago, Ji Hyo found a ghost-related hint.)
This is incredible.
"One of the ghosts is wearing glasses."
(One of the ghosts is wearing glasses.)
It's either you or Jae Seok.
I know for certain.
You're wrong.
Jae Seok is here.
(Be quiet.)
- Prove to me that it's not you. - What?
- If it's not you, rip his name tag. - This will end too quickly.
- What? - Everything will end.
It won't be fun.
- Seok Jin. - What?
You're a ghost.
I'm human.
If you know that...
the other person is the ghost, why won't you rip their name tag?
That's not true.
- Everybody. - Listen.
(Can you look at this?)
"One of the ghosts is a singer."
(If that's the hint, Seok Jin has to be the ghost.)
You get it, right?
Rip it. Rip my name tag.
He's a singer too. He released so many albums.
Me...
See?
- Are you flustered? - Why are you stuttering?
I'm a comedian.
Me too.
(Is that how you like to play this?)
- What's that? - There's a comedian too.
(Ta-da)
What's that?
You just said you're a comedian.
- That's you. - See?
Look.
- You're so shameless. - Watch.
- You're a comedian. - You're a singer...
You released an album. You're on the music chart.
Seok Jin.
Rip it.
Can I?
(At the same time)
(Haha finds a hint after a long time.)
(Let me see.)
(Thinking)
(There's a ghost who has an older brother.)
Kwang Soo is the oldest child. So is Jae Seok.
Does Seok Jin have an older brother? He does.
Seok Jin has an older brother.
I remember saying that to him.
I asked if his brother was older than him, how old he'd be.
Don't be too preoccupied with me.
- All the hints I have... - I'm human.
point to you.
It's Jae Seok.
- Come here. - Why?
Hurry.
- Hey. - You ghost.
You're a ghost. Stop pretending to be human.
- It's not me. This is wrong. - Come here.
That's up to me to decide.
You got it all wrong. What are you doing?
(Calm down.)
(Ripping)
(She rips his name tag.)
Turn around, Seok Jin.
- He has to be the ghost. - For sure.
If that hint is right,
- you can rip my name tag. - Seok Jin is out.
- Seok Jin is out. - What?
Seok Jin is out. Ghost Seok Jin...
- is out. - Right.
I said it was Seok Jin because...
my hint said the ghost had an older brother.
- You're a ghost. - So you're human.
(Seok Jin was a ghost.)
(Ji Hyo eliminates the first ghost.)
- I told you I'm human. - Seok Jin is out.
Ghost Seok Jin is out.
It is him.
(He thought so.)
I was right. He is a ghost.
I have to survive by myself.
(Jae Seok is the only ghost left. He searches for humans.)
I have to find it quickly.
(The other members are busy looking for hints.)
Oh, gosh.
- Kwang Soo. - What?
I don't understand the rules, so you can carry on.
(Hissing)
Hey.
- Hey, Se Chan. - Sorry. Don't rip my name tag.
- You... - That was the end.
I'll stop.
- I'm sorry, Kwang Soo. - Fine.
(I'll let you go this time.)
(He makes ghost sounds again.)
Fine.
You're not scary.
(I'm not scared at all.)
Okay.
What I'm wondering is...
What?
(What?)
(Haha finds another hint.)
I want to know if it's a male or a female.
(What is Haha's hint?)
What?
(What?)
(What is this?)
This world is filled with insecurity.
(What? What's that?)
Whom should I trust?
Oh, my.
I need to trust the hints.
(Ji Hyo accidentally finds a hint.)
What's this?
(It's a little bit different.)
"If you would like a hint,"
"call the class leader." Who's the class leader?
(The class leader?)
(Earlier today)
(They got a call from the class leader.)
(You need to call him back?)
(Let me hide first.)
(Please pick up.)
What's wrong with you?
Look at him.
I didn't see you.
Hey, Janny.
- Hey. - Janny.
Really?
- Ji Hyo. - What?
How could you do this to me?
What is wrong with you? Why are you being so clingy?
- I told you. - No.
We have to escape together.
Okay. We still have time.
But you just got a hint.
- Yes, I did. - Can you share it with me?
No, I was calling,
and I saw you. Let me call first.
- Give me the hint. - Okay.
- My gosh. Jenny... I mean... - Hold on.
- Check it, and let's get out. - Okay.
(What's that phone about?)
This is driving me nuts.
How did he know I was here?
(She's anxious.)
(Please pick up, class leader.)
Hold on. Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo ripped Seok Jin's name tag?
He was a ghost?
I just got goosebumps. Look.
Look.
This doesn't make sense, right?
This doesn't make sense.
Class leader?
(It's me.)
I'm the class leader's mom.
My son went on a trip three years ago and...
(My son went on a trip three years ago and...)
I just got goosebumps.
(It was an unexpected call.)
(He asked if the 6 of them arrived safely.)
(The class leader died 3 years ago from a tragic accident.)
(Haha also found another hint.)
(What?)
(The ghost didn't enter the Labyrinth.)
(One of the ghosts didn't enter the Labyrinth.)
(That doesn't make any sense.)
(Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and Seok Jin all went into the Labyrinth.)
(There were supposedly 2 ghosts in the elevator.)
(But one of the ghosts haven't been into the Labyrinth?)
How do I explain this nonsense?
I'm so confused.
I'm a ghost.
Listen. This doesn't make any sense.
I'm a ghost. Why should I be scared?
(I'm a ghost. Why should I be scared?)
The class leader...
was a ghost.
(The class leader who called was a ghost.)
(The elevator stopped on the 4th floor because there were 2 ghosts.)
(That's strange.)
There are not just two ghosts.
- You're a human. - I'm a ghost.
Is the class leader dead?
When we were doing missions in the beginning,
there was a secret couple, so that means there are two people.
That's why I thought there were two ghosts.
It was a retreat with the ghosts...
There are two humans then.
(They said there were two people who had different identities.)
The class leader said, "Did the six of you arrive safely?"
"Did the six of you arrive safely?"
He can only see the six of us.
So that means there are...
six ghosts.
(There are 6 ghosts.)
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Se Chan, and So Min are ghosts.)
(Either Haha or Kwang Soo is a human.)
Hold on. Let's bring this back to square one.
Let's think about this again. Wait.
Let me look for some more hints.
But it's you, Kwang Soo.
I'm not. I've been clarifying myself since the beginning.
Haha, you're a ghost.
- Me? - Yes.
Do you know why I'm not a ghost?
Why not?
Think carefully.
You're a ghost.
I did my best today.
(Who's the ghost from these two?)
Hey, Haha. Go. Let's split.
- Let's split first. - This is strange.
Let's split first.
Let's go.
Maybe it's So Min.
So Min is alive.
So Min...
I think...
Kwang Soo still...
doesn't understand the game. He's stupid.
Hey, come here.
He's stupid.
- Come here. - Sorry.
- Come here. Hey. - No.
- I was joking. - Come here.
- You startled me. - Hey, come here.
I don't care if you're a ghost or a human.
- Oh, gosh. - Come here.
- Were you listening? - Fine. Just come.
Were you eavesdropping?
Hey, I don't care who you are. Come here.
Let's just...
Hey, let's just put an end to this.
(You'll die, and I'll live.)
(He runs away.)
(Locking)
- Go away. - Come here.
- It's you. - I tried to understand...
when you said things in front of me,
but how dare you talk behind my back?
- Open this. - Kwang Soo.
- Open it. - Kwang Soo.
- I want to speak to you. Open this. - Kwang Soo.
This is my last warning.
(Bowing)
Don't get caught again.
Salute.
(He salutes the stupid man.)
I'm sorry.
Watch out.
Goodness.
(Jae Seok got a hint about the class leader.)
This is driving me nuts.
I'm sure Ji Hyo is human.
- Jae Seok. - My gosh.
- So Min. - Yes?
You're a ghost.
(One of the ghosts is a male.)
You are too.
I'm not a ghost.
You are.
I'm not.
(Jong Kook walks over.)
Say it. It's about time.
- Be quiet. - Ghost, say it.
We're all ghosts.
- Right. - Right?
Say it.
You're a ghost.
- I'm not sure. - She is.
She's a ghost,
- and you are too. - I am.
Are you a ghost too?
See? It's weird.
Let me explain.
You, you, or I...
have to lure humans and get out in order to win.
- Right. - You understand, right?
I think...
the last ghost is Kwang Soo.
- Haha or Se Chan is human. - Haha.
Se Chan is a ghost.
- Really? - I think he's human.
- No, because... - Let's...
Let's split, and as I said,
- I'm a ghost... - Let's get on the elevator.
- Okay. - Yes?
You can go.
(The ghosts separate to find more hints.)
Get going.
My gosh. There isn't much.
Why can't I find any hints?
This is driving me nuts.
(Why?)
(He bumps into somebody.)
Jong Kook is out.
Ghost Jong Kook is out.
(If Jong Kook is out,)
(it was a human besides Ji Hyo who ripped his name tag.)
My gosh.
(It gives her goosebumps.)
Who ripped his name tag?
(Who was it?)
(Was it Haha?)
All right.
I'm soaked in sweat.
(Or was it Kwang Soo?)
I'm sweating so much.
(It's 10 minutes before the end of the race.)
10 minutes before the end of the race.
I need to find more hints about the humans.
That's the only way for me to survive.
I can't trust anybody.
(If she exits with another human, they win.)
They are all ghosts.
- They are all ghosts. - This is no joke.
(If a human exits with a ghost, the ghosts win the race.)
I have to find more hints.
(Is Haha human?)
Who's the human? I'm so scared.
(Or is it Kwang Soo?)
- Kwang Soo. - What is it?
Did you find a hint or not?
- I only found one. - What are you?
That's why I ripped Jong Kook's name tag.
(He saw the hint, and got Jong Kook out.)
(Hold on. Kwang Soo eliminated Jong Kook?)
(Is Kwang Soo human then?)
- You ripped his? - Yes.
- Are you sure? - I ripped it.
(Kwang Soo has to be human if he got Jong Kook out.)
When is the ghost elevator opening?
We just need to get on it with another person.
I have two people I'm suspicious about.
The three of us can get on the elevator.
Right.
Kwang Soo.
- Are you a ghost? - No, I'm not.
I ripped Jong Kook's name tag.
- Really? - Yes.
You should come with me then.
I'm sure.
Kwang Soo, you lose if you go with Haha.
- Come with me. I'm a human. - Because Ji Hyo and I...
I didn't find a hint yet.
She ripped Seok Jin's name tag, so she's 100-percent human.
What was the situation? Tell me.
We were just talking, and I ripped it.
I saw the person ripping his name tag.
(I'm sorry.)
(Is Haha really the witness?)
(Is Kwang Soo lying about ripping Jong Kook's name tag?)
- Did you really rip his name tag? - Yes.
The ghost elevator has opened.
(It's an announcement...)
(about the opening of the ghost elevator.)
- Let's go. - Sure.
- Let's go. - Go.
Let's go together.
Where are you, Kwang Soo?
It's okay. We can get there first.
Let's go.
(The 3 who arrive first get to go on the elevator.)
- Let's get on it. - Let's go.
(It's the last chance to check each other's identities.)
(Ji Hyo, Haha, and Kwang Soo get on it.)
This is scary.
Let's see where it stops.
Did they get on it? Let's go to the fourth floor.
(The elevator stops on the 4th floor if there are 2 ghosts on it.)
(What floor will the elevator stop on?)
(It didn't stop...)
(on the 4th floor.)
We were right.
We passed.
See? Did you see that?
(2 out of 3 of them are humans.)
There's one ghost in here. That's the most likely possibility.
That's right. There's either one ghost or none.
- There's 1 or none. - There are 2.
There are two, Kwang Soo.
Let me share my hint with you.
There are...
six ghosts. Did you know that?
Because...
the class leader is a ghost.
(Kwang Soo and Haha didn't know that.)
- Did you get that hint? - Yes.
The emergency exit for two people has opened.
(The emergency exit is open?)
Ji Hyo, I ripped Jong Kook's name tag.
(Why is he changing his words?)
- You ripped Jong Kook's name tag? - Yes.
- You said you saw it. - I ripped it.
(Why is Haha saying that he ripped it?)
I ripped it.
I swear. I'm the Mapo Sheriff.
Look at my eyes. I really ripped it.
I don't think I need to respond to that.
I'm serious.
(Who are these two?)
(Who's the real human?)
Think about it.
If you don't listen to me...
Listen.
Kwang Soo, Haha, and Ji Hyo got on the elevator.
Ji Hyo is a human for sure.
We have to make Ji Hyo think that he's human...
so that she takes him with her.
That's how we'll win.
Ji Hyo, tell me if you ripped Seok Jin's name tag.
Haha. I got a great hint.
- I got goosebumps. - What is it?
- You have to trust me. - Really?
- Ji Hyo. - Hey.
- Don't you trust me? - They're all ghosts.
- There are six ghosts. - Look.
Aren't you going to trust me? I'm not going to say anything.
It's weird if she doesn't pick me.
- I swear. - So Min.
I ripped it on the second floor.
- Ji Hyo, you saw how I reacted. - Fine. Turn around.
- I'm the Mapo Sheriff. - Fine.
You don't get to decide. I can too.
If you ripped Seok Jin's name tag, come with me.
(Is it a ghost's lie or a human telling the truth?)
(There's 1 minute left until the exit closes.)
- Turn around. I get it. - I'm the Mapo Sheriff.
(I can't get lured by a ghost's lie.)
Who ripped Jong Kook's name tag?
Jae Seok saw me.
Haha ripped Jong Kook's name tag.
Yes, it was him.
(Ghost Jae Seok says it was Haha.)
(It's me, Ji Hyo. Don't you get it?)
I ripped it.
Haha ripped his name tag.
(He says Haha is human.)
Go away.
(He's on the same side as Jae Seok.)
Let's go.
Haha, one of the hints said that a ghost...
was a singer.
(Thanks to Jae Seok, Ji Hyo chooses Kwang Soo.)
- That's Jong Kook. - She's right.
- That's Jong Kook, you stupid. - Let's go.
That was close.
(Open the gate of the truth.)
(Did we win the race?)
We made it.
(Was Ji Hyo's choice right?)
Are you really human?
- He's human! - No?
- Are you? - Team Ghost wins.
(Team Ghost wins.)
(Kwang Soo, were you a ghost?)
- I told you. - He's a ghost.
We won the race.
Jong Kook and I...
(Haha and Ji Hyo were the only humans.)
Team Ghost!
(They celebrate their win by jumping up and down.)
(Actually, Janny played the crucial role in helping Team Ghost win.)
(She was the first to find out that there were more than 2 ghosts.)
(Ghosts need to cooperate in order to possess humans.)
You, you, or me.
(He gathered the ghosts.)
We need to possess the humans and get out to win this race.
(Who else is a human other than Ji Hyo?)
(Haha became sure that Jong Kook was the ghost and eliminated him...)
(after getting a hint about a ghost who hadn't been to the Labyrinth.)
I think Haha eliminated him.
(Haha was the human who eliminated Jong Kook.)
(So Haha is the human.)
- Who eliminated Jong Kook? - Jae Seok saw me.
(Janny played the intense mind game, and led Team Ghost to win the race.)
Ji Hyo, we were almost there.
- Ji Hyo, good job. - From the beginning, you...
You didn't tell me when I asked you.
That confused me.
I thought I was the main lead today.
- So the humans are the main leads. - I know.
I thought so too.
- All day long, I... - I thought the same.
(The race ends.)
Team Ghost wins today's race.
Is it Team Ghost or me alone?
- It's Team Ghost. - Team Ghost.
Come on.
- I mean... - It's not you alone.
- I asked because I didn't know. - That ghost.
He looked familiar,
and now, I realized that he's like the subway ghost from "Ghost".
- That's right. - What?
- Why am I like the subway ghost? - He's right.
Team Human is the losing team of today's race.
Haha and Ji Hyo will receive the penalty.
The penalty, seriously. It's driving me crazy.
The final penalty is called...
Give Me My Name Tag.
Haha and Ji Hyo's name tags are...
hidden in the basement.
- Goodness. - It must be scary.
They'll go in without any cameramen.
They'll be able to go home only after they find their name tags.
It sounds scary.
Is it because Haha and I didn't go to the Labyrinth?
(Why are you doing this to us?)
(The night deepens.)
(The lights get turned off one by one.)
(Welcome, you haven't seen the red lights for a while, have you?)
(It's a haunted house full of ghosts.)
Oh, my. Where is my name tag?
(Crying)
Don't cry.
Ji Hyo, what should we do? Goodness.
- Gosh. - You scared me.
Please find my name tag for me.
Don't cry.
(He's on alert.)
Gosh!
(Gosh)
(Haha's known to get easily frightened.)
Gosh, I'm going crazy.
(Will he succeed in finding his name tag?)
(He's really scared.)
(What are these fireworks?)
(Ji Hyo steps on them furiously.)
(Ji Hyo takes the lead for the scared Haha.)
I think our name tags are in here.
(They enter the designing room in which some creepy music is on.)
Stop singing.
Haha, stay behind me.
- Okay. - Stay behind me.
- Haha, come this way. - Hold on.
- Haha. - I found your name tag.
- Where? - Over there.
There.
(He finds Ji Hyo's name tag in the cabinet.)
Ji Hyo, you won't leave me behind, will you?
Gosh, no way.
- Here. - What?
(Handing him the flashlight)
(Don't tell me that you'll leave me here.)
- Here. - Ji Hyo.
Haha, I found mine.
I shouldn't have told you that.
(This must not be real.)
Ji Hyo, you're joking, right?
(Ji Hyo found her name tag, and escaped alone.)
Why did they make it so hard to find mine?
(He complains to the staff.)
(Screaming)
(He ended up not being able to escape from the haunted house.)
This never ends.
Aren't they the same with different names?
(It's still not over.)
(The 3rd part of their global project)
(The Running Man members have recommended 8 places to travel.)
(But they can't go just because they want to.)
(Only for Running Man,)
(the staff members have selected 8 places to travel as well.)
(It's the Running Man members versus the staff.)
(They must win against the staff.)
This is really stressful.
Are you a psycho?
(Half and Half Tour)