(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by the bloggers)
(Shark cage, USA)
I was scared.
(Cage of Death, Australia)
(Fly Toledo, Spain)
(Active volcano in Mount Bromo and Ijen, Indonesia)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan)
(Nevis Swing, New Zealand)
(Insano water slide, Brazil)
(And)
(Members will depart on the day of the shooting.)
(They were half in doubt, and their speculation has become the reality.)
(Members' account of their travel to Japan)
(Whatever it may be, this will be beyond their imagination.)
Is this how you put this on?
(And today,)
(these two will accompany the members on their journey...)
(and join Running Man.)
(The youngest member is witty.)
(Se Chan's nickname is Strawberry.)
(So Min's dangerous first kiss)
(Some people said they heard bells ringing.)
(The only thing I remember is the smell of his saliva.)
(So Min is very outspoken.)
(The two new members will take part starting from today.)
(It's a sunny day in April at Hangang Park.)
I'm scared.
My goodness.
(Opening)
Hello. Hello.
(It's her first day with Running Man.)
My gosh, look at all the cameras.
(Jeon So Min joins as a new member.)
(Forget the modest princess.)
(She has changed completely to befit the show.)
(She is a charming woman with a little bit of twist.)
(Jeon So Min is ready to start shooting.)
What's your resolution?
I was told to prepare myself.
So I did, but what's that?
What's that?
(A mysterious set welcomes the newcomer.)
I'm not going to get hit, right?
I'm so scared.
Why is there no one here?
Should I go in?
You can go in.
Why is there no one here?
Do I go in there by myself?
(She repeatedly asks why no one is here.)
(She decides to open the suspicious door.)
(Opening)
My gosh. Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Welcome to Running Man. - Thank you.
I'm scared.
Welcome.
- It's safe, right? - Yes. You can wait over there.
(A luxurious waiting room waited for her.)
- Can I eat this? - Go ahead.
I know that you guys aren't usually this nice.
I've already heard so many things about this show.
(I heard rumors about you people.)
I heard you guys are bullies. People said that you guys are bullies.
(She's a scary woman who says mean stuff with a smile on her face.)
But why is there no one here?
You'll soon find out why.
(While So Min is being treated luxuriously,)
(a black van enters the site.)
(Opening)
Hello.
(It's the guy who's always funny.)
Don't you think this set is a bit too much?
(Yang Se Chan also joins as a new member.)
(He makes everyone laugh whenever he appears on TV.)
(The master of comedy finally joins Running Man.)
(What's this suspicious-looking room?)
- Hey. - Hi, Se Chan.
We're the new members of Running Man.
(I'm not alone any more. It's nice to see you.)
- It's nice to see you. - Se Chan, welcome to Running Man.
You startled me. Nice to see you guys.
(Congratulations on joining Running Man.)
Congratulations.
I thought people mistook us as a couple.
Me too. I was so surprised.
- Here. They said we could eat this. - Really?
(Now, all they have to do is enjoy their luxurious waiting room.)
- They're looking at us funnily. - No, don't worry. It'll be fine.
- They kept looking at me like that. - No.
- How did they look at you? - It looked like...
they knew what was coming for me.
- I even gave you a flower necklace. - He's right.
I got scared because I thought this would give me an electric shock.
(She must have a lot of misunderstandings about our staff.)
Do you think this is an American variety show?
Why are you so scared? Don't worry.
- Why didn't you eat anything? - The food here? I did.
Eat something. I can't be the only one.
My goodness, I can't believe this. You're incredible.
Fine, I'll eat.
(How will their future unfold?)
- Look. They built a set. - What's that?
It's a new set.
- Hello. - Hello.
Look at the weather.
- The weather is so nice. - It's beautiful.
To celebrate the beginning of spring, we're going to start...
- a new project for 2017. - Yes!
Here's what the new project for 2017 will be.
It's called Global Race.
- Global? - Global Race?
Until now, you have visited the major parts of our country.
Through Global Race, you'll be running in other countries overseas.
(It's the first step for them to run farther.)
You all know about the new members, right?
- Yes. - Yes. It's So Min...
- 9012! - and Se Chan.
- We are one! - 9012!
- We were one from birth! - Yes!
- 9012! - Forever!
Here are the two new members who'll be joining you for Global Race.
- Welcome, Se Chan and So Min! - Come on out!
I'm so excited to see So Min...
and Se Chan.
(The door is still closed.)
- They should hurry up and come out. - They're here.
- Are you going to stay there? - Se Chan! So Min!
I think I hear them. Should we go out now?
Yes.
(Shall we slowly show ourselves?)
(What's going on?)
- What's happening? - What? Stop it!
(Why are you doing this to me?)
(The waiting room starts to move.)
(What is the secret behind this waiting room?)
- Aren't they going to come out? - Why aren't they coming out?
- Look! - What's that?
(The excavator pulls the container out.)
Isn't that an excavator?
Gosh, don't do this. Stop it!
Guys!
- My gosh, what's happening? - That's already too high up.
- That's dangerous. - My gosh, what is this?
- Please help us! - So Min!
(The bullies have prepared something for the newcomers.)
- What if this falls? - This is crazy.
It's too high. This is too high!
(Is this really necessary?)
I would've cried if it was me up there.
(We prepared a new kind of high-rise studio for you.)
What is this?
(And...)
(there are 6 ice showers welcoming the members who are on the ground.)
- What's this? - This is water.
- What are you doing? - We're doing this from the start?
- We're supposed to be one. - We're going to get wet already?
Kwang Soo got his hair done today.
What is this? Please explain.
The waiting room that's hanging from the excavator...
is a new mission to welcome the newcomers to the show.
- It's called "Risky Waiting Room". - And?
- They are 15m above the ground. - It's really high up.
- Their mission is to come down. - Okay.
They can use two methods to come down.
- What are they? - What are they?
The first method is...
to go down yourselves by using a ladder or a rope.
What did you say?
(You want us to go down ourselves?)
So Min, you were right. They really are bullies.
- What is this nonsense? - The second method is...
The waiting room will descend 3m every time...
- a member gets an ice shower. - My goodness.
They should rappel down.
- They should know how to do that. - This is nothing.
- She's right. It's nothing. - This is for babies.
It's not up to you to decide. It's up to the new members.
If they decide to come down themselves,
no one here will have to receive an ice shower.
My goodness, but how will they come down from there?
So they're the ones who'll be deciding everything?
- Why? - Yes. They're your family now.
They should be grateful that they got picked for the show.
(They should just be quiet and be thankful.)
- Why do we have to go through... - Is he trying to act like a senior?
- My goodness. - No, I'm just saying.
- Why do we have to go through this? - He's so mad.
I think Jong Kook will be the one to get the ice shower.
- You're going to get chosen. - Guys, listen up!
- No, I'm just... - Se Chan, show him!
You guys can jump.
You need to make a good first impression.
Can you please sacrifice yourselves?
No way. What are you saying?
- She's really brazen. - Aren't you scared?
- How can you stand there like that? - Please help us.
Shut it!
"Shut it"?
I didn't say that. It wasn't me.
- I love you too! - They get to decide, right?
- I will always be on your side. - It was Seok Jin!
You guys heard what Jong Kook and Seok Jin said, right?
I'm going to kill you later!
What? Do you want to get killed by an ice shower?
Seok Jin, do you want to get killed by an ice shower?
(What will the newcomers decide to do?)
- Kwang Soo! - Yes?
Would you like an ice shower?
- No! - Then dance for us.
(Then show us your dance moves.)
(If that's what you want)
(I'm your dancing machine.)
- That's not a dance. - He should get wet.
Okay, Kwang Soo. Move to the right.
- He got exempted. - Yes.
- Jong Kook! - Yes?
Do an acrostic poem with So Min's name.
What?
- Fail! - Yes, he failed.
Jong Kook, move to your left.
Okay!
That's great.
(He should experience failure from time to time.)
- Jong Kook will get... - I know I'll get it.
the ice shower. He already knows that.
I'll get hit by an ice shower today, but you'll get hit by me every day.
(You'll get beaten every week.)
- I'll beat you every week. - Se Chan!
- Did you hear what Jong Kook said? - What did he say?
He said he'll beat you after he receives the ice shower.
Jong Kook! You can move to the right!
- Should I go? - Yes, go to the right. I'm sorry.
I should've known better.
- I should've known better. - Okay.
Se Chan knows what he's doing.
So Min wants to say something to Jae Seok.
Please show us your fist dance.
- I can do that for you. It's easy. - It's this dance.
- It's simple. - So Min, you're discriminating.
- This is nothing. - Okay, you can move to the right.
(After a short dance, he gets exempted.)
- Hey, this is unfair. - This is crazy.
- I can do it too. - I can dance too.
(This is so fun.)
Are you satisfied?
That's not enough.
So Min. Se Chan.
Haha, what did you think of me?
To be honest, I like you a lot more than your brother.
Move to your right. That was great!
- Seok Jin! - Yes?
(Seok Jin, you can...)
Go to your left.
(He sends Seok Jin away from the group.)
- Ask me questions. - Just go.
- I can do it too. - That's incorrect.
- Look. - Go over there.
(Seok Jin is desperate.)
Goodness.
- Ji Hyo. - Se Chan.
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
So Min said you should go this way.
Thank you so much, So Min.
- Seok Jin will get it, won't he? - Thanks!
- Seok Jin should go first. - Really?
- Hey! - Thank you, So Min.
Give me one more chance.
- You don't have another one. - Don't.
Why were you disappointed to see us?
I already knew it from the article.
I was only disappointed in the morning.
- In the morning? - Yes.
Let's go back. We made our decision.
Choose between parachuting and ice shower.
In 3, 2, 1.
- Ice shower. - Ice shower.
Choose one member who will get an ice shower.
(Who will make the sacrifice?)
- Stand under the ice shower. - Do you mean me?
- I mean everyone. - Everyone?
Everyone?
(Will Seok Jin get the ice shower?)
That's a lot of water.
A shower in the beginning is harsh.
Could you consider it one more time?
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
So Min has something to say to you.
Tell me, So Min.
- I'm sorry, Kwang Soo. - For what?
For everything.
- Gosh, for what? - He's scared.
Why are you sorry?
She's sorry for betraying you during the last shoot.
It's completely fine, So Min. Just do better next time.
I'm sorry for everything.
Why are you sorry for everything?
I'm so sorry for everything.
Everything is my fault.
(Why is she apologizing?)
Did they choose parachuting or ice shower?
It's obvious.
Parachuting isn't possible from there.
(Someone has to make a sacrifice.)
What did Se Chan and So Min choose?
- One. - Please.
- Two. - I haven't done anything wrong.
- No way. - Three.
It's me.
(The shower turns on.)
(Seok Jin gets an ice shower.)
(He's happy as long as it isn't him.)
- Congratulations. - I love you.
You wait and see.
- I'm sorry. - Goodness.
I'm sorry, Seok Jin.
Thank you. Please wait for us.
- They're going down. - We're descending 3m.
We're descending.
I feel bad because Seok Jin put on a lot of hair powder today.
The ground became dark.
It's the stage set. I was startled.
- I thought the stage became black. - It's the original color.
I was startled.
They're filling up the water.
(They hope it's Seok Jin again.)
- Are you filling up the water? - Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - What are you doing?
Please make your second choice.
Will it be parachuting or ice shower?
(Which will they choose?)
(Will they parachute and make everyone else happy?)
(Or will they make someone get an ice shower?)
Let's make it fun.
Haha.
- Haha is next. - Yes, So Min.
Thank you for buying me meat.
No problem.
I'll always give it to you for free.
Haha, the meat was really delicious.
(Haha, you're awesome.)
I choose Haha.
(Haha gets an ice shower.)
I don't know what to say.
(Didn't she thank him just now?)
- Did you buy the meat? - No, he bought it for me.
Why did you choose Haha then?
We aren't very close.
He still bought you meat.
It was at Haha's restaurant.
- I don't know what to say. - He offered it for free.
Don't you think it's okay since we aren't so close?
It's your choice.
We're in trouble.
What did Se Chan and So Min choose?
In 3, 2, 1.
- What? - That's right.
- Gosh. - Okay.
(Is it me?)
(Haha is chosen for an ice shower.)
- Hey. - Se Chan.
- How could she be so ungrateful? - So Min.
I love you, Se Chan.
- Thank you. - What's the reason?
I'm sorry, Haha.
It's because we aren't close.
Are you close with anyone here?
She's grateful for the meat. She wants to be friends with you.
Thank you, Se Chan.
Don't worry, Jae Seok.
Now that Haha is wet, his sleeves will fit him.
- They shrank. - They became longer.
He can do the Korean mask dance.
- Look. - He should dance.
Aren't they too long?
(This isn't fashionable.)
It looks ridiculous.
- There's Young Jin, Haha's stylist. - Stop it.
- Where is he? - Look at him.
- It's Young Jin. - Young Jin.
He's Haha's stylist.
- Haha dresses exactly like him. - Go away!
- Go home. - He's Haha's muse.
He's Haha's muse.
He's Haha's mentor.
Go inside the car.
Haha dresses exactly like his stylist.
(He copies Young Jin's fashion style.)
(The Waiting Room is 9m above ground.)
- Who was your partner, So Min? - You.
- Who was on your team, Se Chan? - You.
You can depend on us, Kwang Soo.
- Don't pick me. - We'll be on Kwang Soo's side.
(They claim to be on Kwang Soo's side.)
- Really? - Young Kwang Soo.
- Young Kwang Soo. - Let's go.
- Kwang Soo, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- Next is Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo.
- It's Kwang Soo next. - Please don't do it.
He doesn't know. He's the only one who doesn't know.
It's their rule.
When they say, "Don't worry, Kwang Soo,"
they mean he'll get an ice shower.
I don't like this. Don't talk to me.
Don't even call me my name.
They said that it's our rule, but let's break it.
- Okay. - Let's break it.
(Will they break the rule?)
Will we get in trouble if we choose Jong Kook?
(What?)
He won't catch a cold because he's healthy.
Catching a cold isn't what's important.
He won't catch a cold because he exercises a lot.
The other members are older.
It's okay to choose Jong Kook since he's physically fit.
(It's a big risk.)
Listen to me first.
Why am I being persuaded by you?
I feel like that's what's happening.
Shall we go for it?
(Will they take a risk?)
(Will they take the risk and choose Jong Kook?)
I feel bad for him, but let's do it.
(Is it a thoughtless decision?)
Whom will you choose?
In 3, 2, 1.
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
(They choose Jong Kook.)
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- We're on your side. - You're the best.
Let's go, Kwang Soo.
- It's you. - Why are you cheering for me?
(No news is good news.)
- I mean it. - Kwang Soo.
Stop it.
(He doesn't trust them.)
(Everyone wants it to be Kwang Soo.)
- It's not me. - It's definitely you.
Gosh, what should we do? I'm scared of Jong Kook.
Gosh, I'm scared of him.
So Min had her eyes on Kwang Soo.
I thought they would choose him first today.
Seriously.
So Min had her eyes on Kwang Soo the most.
Kwang Soo, why did you betray me last time?
I didn't betray you.
So Min betrayed you.
(It was So Min.)
It wasn't me. It was So Min.
I'll change my mind.
- What? - Shall I change my mind?
(Will she change her mind?)
(Will you?)
Do you want to get an ice shower?
(It's a struggle between the powerful and the powerless.)
Shall we change or not?
- Change it. - Say it in three seconds.
Don't change it.
Don't change it? Okay, stay there.
- Change it. - Change it?
- Change it? - Change it?
- Are you sure? - Darn it.
- Shall we change it? You decide. - Hey!
- In 3, 2, 1. - 2, 1.
(What will Kwang Soo choose?)
(Kwang Soo usually makes bad choices.)
(If he doesn't change it, Jong Kook will get an ice shower.)
(What will be Kwang Soo's answer?)
(He spits.)
Gosh. Hey.
How old are you?
Goodness.
(How dare they test him?)
Change it.
- Change it? - Change it?
He told us to change.
(Did he make the right decision?)
What's going on?
They'll change.
- Didn't they choose Kwang Soo? - Maybe not.
- He told us to change. - He did.
It's unfortunate. I wasn't going to choose Kwang Soo.
I also chose him at first, but we have no choice now.
- Cover this side of your face. - In 1, 2.
- Kwang Soo. - We choose Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- We changed our mind as you told. - We did what you told us.
- Did you change it? - Yes.
- We changed because you told us. - Listen up.
Here's the person to get an ice shower.
(Who is it this time?)
It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo gets an ice shower.)
(How dare they?)
It was so obvious.
- You told us to change. - Thank you.
- Kwang Soo. - Thank you.
- You told them to change. - You told us to change.
- Wasn't it me? - No, it wasn't.
- It wasn't? - No.
Who was it?
It was Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook? - It was Jong Kook at first.
- Me? - That's great.
You told them to change it.
Am I next?
No, we'll change it.
My goodness.
They have us in their hands.
Let's go once more.
Let's go for two people at once.
- Right. - This is easier.
- Choose 2. - You'll descend 6m.
Okay, Se Chan.
- That's right. - I choose Kwang Soo.
- It's okay. - Will you choose two?
You can choose the same person.
- You can choose the same person. - I recommended you.
- Okay. - Everyone knows that.
- Everyone does. - Okay, Jong Kook.
I recommended you immediately.
- Thank you, Jong Kook. - You're welcome.
Jong Kook is the best.
They can parachute down.
Whom shall we choose?
Please choose again.
(It's time to choose the 4th victim.)
Should we choose Kwang Soo and ask him again?
- Kwang Soo? - Yes.
- Let's cover our mouths. - He just looked at us.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
(Worried)
We have to choose between Jong Kook and Jae Seok.
(They'll choose one more person.)
- It's hard. - It's so hard.
(The scary one or the national celebrity?)
Kwang Soo, should we change our minds or not?
- What? - Should we change our minds?
Don't change your minds.
Don't.
- No? - Why are you doing this to me?
I've already been splashed.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
They're taming you right now.
Guys!
I can see that Se Chan and So Min look down on you.
You guys are the youngest.
I've been the youngest for the past seven years.
- You were not our youngest member. - Who is it then?
It was Seok Jin.
- Really? - You didn't know?
- I didn't. Now, it makes sense. - Now, you know.
- I always thought you were so cute. - Right?
- Seok Jin ages backwards. - Really.
Seok Jin is so immature.
- That's right. - You didn't know?
Should we change our minds?
- Don't. - What?
- Do whatever you want. - Don't change your minds.
- No? - No.
He says no.
(The new members are playing around with Kwang Soo.)
The decision has been made.
(It's time for the 4th ice shower.)
We've chosen two people this time.
- All right. - Okay.
That sounds good.
(Kwang Soo has no idea.)
Two people will be splashed with water.
One, two...
I bet it's Jae Seok.
- Three. - I agree.
- Okay. - What?
(Splash)
I bet it's Jae Seok.
(Is it Jong Kook or Jae Seok?)
(Splash)
(Bye, guys.)
(See you on the ground.)
What happened?
It was Jong Kook.
This is nice.
(Thanks, new members.)
- I'm sorry. - Are you okay?
- Oh, my. - I'm sorry.
I'm so glad...
- you're here. - Look who is here.
You can come down now.
- Come down. - Please cover me.
- Oh, my. - Come down.
Come out.
I won't be able to like them.
- They're here. - Lay him down.
- Se Chan. - Hello.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
I'm sorry.
- Wait. - I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
(The members welcome them first then force them out.)
- No! - Catch them.
What are you doing?
- Press the button. - What are you doing?
- Let us welcome you. - I have no extra clothes.
- I have no other clothes. - It'll be fine.
- It'll be all right. - Come here.
- It'll be okay. - I have no other clothes.
It's going to hurt.
Press the button. Seok Jin, press the button.
Don't do it!
(Splash)
(Once you're in, you can't get out.)
(The welcoming ceremony is over.)
Party time!
We have new members.
Please welcome Se Chan and So Min.
Hello.
Se Chan.
- Well... - So Min.
- Let me talk about So Min. - So Min.
- Recently, she betrayed Kwang Soo. - Right.
Many viewers loved it.
We've never had a female betrayer.
- I'm not a betrayer. - Actually, we've been wondering...
who will be the next betrayer.
- I didn't expect it to be a girl. - Right.
As Jong Kook said, we now have a female betrayer.
- It's refreshing. - It is.
It's very refreshing.
- It's good news. - You're right.
Please welcome Se Chan too.
Hello.
Se Chan did an amazing job...
every time he appeared on Running Man.
- He blended in very well. - He did a great job.
I like him so much.
- I heard he recommended me. - I strongly recommended you.
Really?
I put as much effort as I put into my workouts.
It almost worked against you.
- It almost did. - I recommended you too strongly.
You must have made a fuss.
If you had been quiet, it would have gone more smoothly.
They thought you bribed me.
(Suspicious connection between Jong Kook and Se Chan)
- I recommended you so strongly. - Don't do that from now on.
I shouldn't.
Se Chan and So Min joined us.
As the producer said,
Running Man is starting over...
from this episode.
This is a very important time for us.
- You're right. - If we fail, we'll blame those two.
That's great.
- Guys. - I feel so relieved.
We'll give you guys an excuse.
Don't worry. If we fail, we'll all fail together.
- Not just us? - No.
- Don't worry. - Don't worry.
With the new members,
let's start Global Race.
- What's Global Race? - Are we going abroad?
Spring is here. Many television shows...
and people around us go on trips abroad.
- They do. - You're right.
- So many do that. - We've decided...
to send some of you...
on a trip abroad.
(Are we going abroad?)
- How many? - Only some of us?
Not all of you can go.
- I see. - I see.
We'll decide who will go through the race.
I'll show you the places you'll be visiting.
- Okay. - Please look at the screen.
What are the places?
(Hawaii)
(A paradise on the Earth, Hawaii)
Hawaii?
(Are we really going there?)
- I really want to go. - Seriously?
Hawaii.
(They've never been this eager before.)
(Beautiful sunshine and sparkling ocean)
(Dangerous tourist attractions)
What do you mean by dangerous tourist attractions?
Look at that.
(What's going on?)
(Dangerous tourist attractions?)
(You've never experienced a sea like this.)
(Shark cage diving)
- That looks scary. - That's so scary.
- We can't do that. - Are you out of your mind?
We can't do that.
(See you soon.)
(Australia)
(Are they crocodiles?)
- They're crocodiles. - Gosh.
It says, "Experience crocodiles."
I can't do that.
I can't trust the cage.
(Cage of Death in Australia)
(A country with enjoyment and romance, Spain)
(Ziplining at a height of 180m)
- I can't do that. - My goodness.
I can't do that.
- That's too high. - It's a zipline.
That's crazy.
(Indonesia)
That's an active volcano.
Why would we go there?
Isn't that a fiery pit?
(A volcano tour in Indonesia)
Are you planning to terminate the show?
(Is this the last episode?)
It seems like...
- What's that? - That's not okay.
- That's not okay. - We shouldn't do this.
(Japan)
The whole building is haunted.
- Ghosts appear. - Ghosts appear.
It's included in Guinness World Records.
Really?
I won't be able to sleep for six months.
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear in Japan)
(New Zealand)
- I can't do that. - This is not okay.
My goodness.
(It's 160m high.)
- What's that? - That's not okay.
- What's that? - How will we do that?
Why has the show changed so suddenly?
Do you mean that it'll be the end of us?
Why does it say "the end"?
- Oh my. - That's...
That's too much.
You've just seen...
tourist attractions that many people wish to visit...
- You're lying. - before they die.
Who wants to go to those places?
Why do you have to do this right after we join?
You won't visit all of the places you've just seen.
Each of you will win points as you clear the missions.
- Points? - Is it an individual game?
Each week, the member with the lowest score...
will get a Tour Sticker.
The one who accumulates 3 stickers 1st...
will have to visit...
one of the places.
That's too harsh.
You must have wanted us to do our very best.
Briefcases, please.
- What? - What?
(It feels dangerous.)
Why are there only six of them?
In the briefcases are...
two No Tour Cards,
two Solo Tour Cards,
and two Couple Tour Cards.
You'll exclude briefcases one by one.
The one with the lowest score...
will choose one briefcase among the remaining ones.
There's no choice.
We shouldn't exclude No Tour Cards.
We should exclude the right ones.
- I'm confused. - Now,
Se Chan and So Min will...
exclude two briefcases.
- Do a good job. - There are only two No Tour Cards.
Do a good job.
So Min is usually lucky.
(Will she turn out to be lucky?)
Exclude a Solo Tour Card.
(She's examining the briefcases.)
(She chooses number 3 without hesitation.)
- Good job. - She's so brave.
Se Chan, go.
They must have put a lot of thought in it.
Exactly. Do some analysis.
Those who think a lot usually get in trouble.
(Se Chan is thinking hard.)
Four.
Four is usually associated with bad things.
(He believes briefcase number 4 has a bad card.)
People these days don't believe in that.
(Se Chan chooses number 4 after thinking carefully.)
- Okay. - I choose number four.
Let's open So Min's briefcase.
- Please. - I hope she'll bring us good luck.
- It's important. - I hope she's lucky.
(Please eliminate a bad card.)
- It's a Solo Tour Card. - Okay.
(A Solo Tour Card is excluded.)
Good job.
- It's excluded now. - Good job.
- Good job, So Min. - Is it a good thing?
- It's a very good thing. - Really? Is it?
- You're so lucky. - You brought us good luck.
So Min is lucky. So Min is so lucky.
The staff members are shocked.
They're taken aback.
(What's in Se Chan's briefcase?)
(Will his analysis pay off?)
- Except Solo Tour Card... - Is he unlucky?
- What's in it? - Guys.
I'm sorry.
(One No Tour Card is taken away.)
- I picked a No Tour Card. - You two are complete opposite.
They did put a bad card in this fourth briefcase.
(He's a new unlucky guy.)
- There are no exceptions here. - He's really unlucky.
- He should've picked the 6th one. - Or the 1st.
Jae Seok. Then get the sixth briefcase.
- Can I? - Sure. We'll switch them later.
- Can I choose one then? - Sure. Go ahead.
(Jae Seok, known as the unlucky guy, tries.)
- Goodness. Hey. - Let's see it.
(He's confident today. What will be in the 6th briefcase?)
Lately, I am not that unlucky.
I had a hunch that he should have picked the sixth briefcase.
I am 100 percent certain there will be a No Tour Card.
(Of course.)
- You never pick something useful. - I knew it.
(Why do you get your hopes up?)
- Why did you pick on me? - Goodness.
- You are also unlucky. - That's what he picked.
- You are truly unfortunate. - I guess I am really unlucky.
(His reputation is everlasting.)
The new Running Man's project...
is a Global Race joined by new members of the program.
(Global Race)
(With 3 Solo Tour Cards, one can go on a trip.)
(Who will be chosen?)
(Global Race)
(They are heading to the next dangerous place.)
- Kwon Ryeol. I have to buy that. - Congratulations.
All right. We will set out now.
(They sit where they want to sit.)
- You are all seated. - Yes, we are.
Is there anyone who wants to switch seats?
- Why? - Does our seats play a role?
Are you up to something?
We are going to do something while we move to our next place.
Our seats must mean something.
(Why does he want our seats switched?)
- I like my seat. - I want to change my seat.
So Min. Come here.
- Go away. - How can you just sit here?
- Why are you here? - We can't continue with our show.
(Their first instinct is to switch first.)
- There's no room! - Ji Hyo!
- Hold on. - We are all set.
Can you move?
- Four people can sit in the back. - Exactly.
Jae Seok. You should sit up front since you are like our captain.
Okay. Fine. I will sit here then.
- I will accept your recommendation. - Kwang Soo. Sit here.
Why don't we put all the unlucky members in one team?
(Observation 1: Kwang Soo can't look So Min in the eye.)
Do you remember how you pushed me before?
You pushed me, but you are not pushing Jae Seok.
(Observation 2: He picks a fight with Se Chan for nothing.)
(Then does it mean...)
Kwang Soo, do you have feelings for So Min?
- It's not that. - Stop chasing her.
As I told you before, So Min doesn't have the slightest interest in you.
- Don't flirt with her. - Jae Seok, the feelings are mutual.
She and I were never each other's love interests.
You seem to like other women though.
- What do you mean? - He liked every female guest.
- On every episode... - He does really like them.
He has never looked at me the same way.
I don't have feelings for you. What can I do?
(He falls in love with the touch of their hands.)
(But with So Min, he didn't fall in love. Rather, he bickered with her.)
- Really? - You are just a good colleague.
- I still don't feel that way. - Are you certain?
- You are all seated, right? - Yes. What is it?
By the location of your seats,
So Min, Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and Jae Seok will make one team.
- The seats did matter. - Just like this?
So this is our team?
Goodness. I already have two traitors on my team.
- They are more likely to betray us. - Jae Seok. You have three.
(He's a super rookie in the world of betrayals.)
The worst thing about Se Chan is that he's the new unlucky traitor.
(Se Chan, a symbol of misfortune)
- He has all the negative aspects. - No, I am not. I am not unlucky.
- You are full of misfortunes. - No, I am not.
No, I won't betray. I trust you.
Why did they use people?
- So Min. - Yes?
- You just told your first lie. - Goodness.
(She's getting ready to betray.)
- This is your problem. - You're making me mad.
- Are you preparing to betray me? - No, I am not.
- Don't backhit me. - I won't.
- Did you mean "backstab"? - "Backhit"?
I didn't mean to.
- Are you trying to picking on him? - I am.
- He wants to be involved. - It's because I have to show...
- them this is a tough show. - He wants to join the fun.
He's being mean to the new members.
He is the baby of that team.
Hey, our baby.
- Goodness. Aren't you a cutie? - Good boy.
(Seok Jin still suffers.)
- Jong Kook is the team leader. - Gosh.
Se Chan was sitting here before.
We will start the mission now.
The mission is "Nonsense Quiz".
(The second mission is "Nonsense Quiz".)
- What is that? - It will be 4 on 4.
Members from the winning team will earn points individually.
Right. This will be played individually.
You have to respond to the questions with unrelated answers.
If you give unrelated answers three times in a row, it's a success.
The team with more members who succeed is the winning team.
The winning team will earn 1 point. The losing team will lose 1 point.
- We're good at this. - Seok Jin.
Can we talk nonsense or does it have to make a bit of sense?
- You can talk nonsense. - Really? Okay.
Seok Jin has the upper hand in this game.
He usually talks nonsense.
(That jerk...)
- He does. - He doesn't make sense.
It's true indeed.
I don't remember when I last had a proper conversation with him.
- He doesn't put any effort into it. - Wait. I'm going to hit you today.
Stop hitting him.
He really talks a lot of nonsense.
Which team will go first?
- Our team will. - Okay. They can go first.
- Will you go first, Seok Jin? - You can start with Seok Jin.
Start. What did you do when you woke up today?
Lion.
- What are you doing? - What?
- Wrong. - Come on.
So this is how you play.
Now, I figured it out.
Seok Jin. I told you we should play after we see them play!
- You can't do that now. - I get it now.
(We can call this Seok Jin's game.)
- He's out. He failed. - If you ask that question...
- He failed. - No, I didn't.
- If you hesitate, you fail. - The questions are not specific.
- The range of questions is wide. - Here we go.
Ji Hyo. Get ready.
Start. What is in your refrigerator?
I'm hungry.
- What is your wish? - I am sleepy.
- What do you want to do now? - I want to sleep.
(You want to sleep? That makes sense!)
- Why? - You want to sleep?
(Ji Hyo fails.)
(I just told you my specialty.)
- I want to sleep. - That made sense.
- What's wrong with that? - You said...
- you want to sleep. - But you don't want to.
- That's what she wanted to do. - We agree. We admit her mistake.
- You did want to sleep, right? - Ji Hyo failed.
- Both of them failed? - Haha. It's your turn.
- You were close though. - Goodness.
Start. Which member is your favorite?
Raise my fee.
- What is your phone's wallpaper? - My house is ruined.
- What do you want from me? - My second child was just born.
- He succeeded. - Great.
(Haha is the first to succeed.)
All right.
This is really nervous.
It goes so fast.
- Get ready. - Have your answers ready.
Start. What is your motto?
The weather is very nice.
What do you want to say now?
- When will you fix me a date? - What?
(Jong Kook fails.)
"What do you want to say now?"
- His answer made sense. - Why did you say that?
- I didn't know. It does make sense. - Goodness, Jong Kook.
Your answer should have been something like "red".
- Let's do it again now. - Why would we do that?
(I could have just said anything.)
- Jong Kook fails. - Great. We can do this!
(Only Haha succeeded.)
- It's not that. - Let's be clear on this topic.
- You must be really lonely. - I think he meant it.
- I meant it. - I guess so.
- What is your ideal type? - What do you mean?
He likes tanned women with thick thighs.
No, that's not true. That's not my ideal type.
- Isn't that Hyo Lyn? - I don't know my type.
- Hyo Lyn it is! - Yes!
(That's correct!)
(Here is your other half.)
- I don't have an ideal type. - It must be Hyo Lyn.
- She's the Beyonce of Korea. - I have no standards about looks.
Really. I don't have them anymore.
(Don't lie.)
- That's not true. - You're lying.
Let's see whom you marry.
I really don't have any standards about looks now.
- It's our turn. You saw it, right? - All right.
(I'm going to be in charge of the xylophone.)
- Here we go. - Wait.
- Give it back. - Why?
- I'm going to do it. - But it's your team's turn.
- He hosted "Star Golden Bell". - Stop it.
- You are not the only host! - What did you say?
Have you ever hosted "Star Golden Bell"?
(Seok Jin, the legendary host and the ruler of xylophones)
I am a host too!
I am a better host!
- I agree with you on that point. - He has experience.
(I haven't touched a xylophone in ages.)
- All right. - I'll go first. Watch and learn.
- So Min. Kwang Soo. Watch me. - Only two of us have to succeed.
- I will copy you. - All of us could have succeeded.
Don't give a long answer just because the question is long.
- Keep them short. - Watch how I do this. Observe.
(Jae Seok seems unusually confident. Will he succeed?)
- Who is your role model? - Poop.
(Poop is his role model?)
- Hold on! It makes sense. - It makes sense!
- Poop is his role model. - It's true. He failed.
(Did Jae Seok fail?)
- His role model is indeed poop. - Hey.
He told me that his role model is diarrhea in 2017.
Before shooting, he did confess that his role model is poop.
Besides, he's unlucky as poop.
(Was he unlucky since he was trying to take after his role model?)
I am always unlucky.
- Hey, how can it be my role model? - Right.
- It is completely true. - You said your true role model.
I thought whatever the question was, poop wouldn't make sense.
(This is how he got a fragrant role model.)
- It did somehow make sense. - Didn't it make sense though?
- Pull yourself together. Se Chan. - I will.
Start. Which part of your body itches?
My knee hurts.
- What is your nickname? - I am a strawberry.
(Is Strawberry your nickname?)
(Se Chan fails because it makes so much sense.)
- Why did you say that? - Is your nickname Strawberry?
- It is not. - Is it Strawberry?
- Why did you say Strawberry? - Come on.
- He is just like his brother. - He is.
- He's just like Se Hyung. - We are brothers.
Your brother lost every game on Saturday.
Don't badmouth my brother. He's good at games.
Don't you dare look down on my brother.
- I won't let you live. - How heartwarming.
- Don't bring family into this. - You are so nice.
(Their brotherly love is overwhelming.)
- Kwang Soo. Stay on your toes. - I will.
(I must succeed.)
Start. What do you want to tell your girlfriend when you have one?
Australopithecus.
(Australopithecus?)
(To my future girlfriend,)
(you are an Australopithecus.)
- Do you mean that? - What's wrong with that?
(Kwang Soo fails.)
What was wrong?
Would I really say that to my girlfriend?
No, that's not what I meant.
- Your answer... - It makes sense.
shouldn't make any sense.
- She could look like an ape. - Right.
- What did you say about my girl? - It's possible.
So Min, you're our only hope.
- Please, So Min. - Goodness.
Get ready.
(So Min distracts herself.)
What are you looking at?
She won't make eye contact. It's her strategy.
That's a good idea.
- So Min. - Say nonsense.
You're up, So Min.
Get ready, set, go.
- What are you looking at? - An apple.
- She lost. - What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
We got poop, strawberry, apple, and Australopithecus.
(Their answers are short and strange.)
What about my answer?
We won!
- I won't look at the camera. - Come on, So Min.
What are you looking at?
I was about to say "camera".
She was looking at the camera,
and the red button reminded her of an apple.
What kind of answer was that?
Look at this.
Jong Kook, Haha, Ji Hyo, and Seok Jin earn one point each.
(They earn 1 point.)
We did a good job.
It's possible that we'll get punished.
Did we lose one point?
My goodness.
We have to determine who has the least score anyway.
Each of you should choose whom you'll compete with.
- I'll compete with Haha. - Okay.
- Show us, Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- Haha is too good. - No, I'm not.
- Who starts first? - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo starts. Ready, set, go.
Say something to your wife.
I love you.
(He says after a pause.)
(He says he loves her after a moment of hesitation.)
He said it too late.
- It took him a while to say it. - Wait a minute.
My original answer was, "You're being ridiculous."
(He almost couldn't return home today.)
His wife is in a postpartum care center right now.
She's still there.
- I thought you'd say, - He can't say she's ridiculous.
"poop" or something.
- My answer was, "I love you." - You responded late.
You should air it.
Don't edit out the part when I say I love her.
- Okay? - He loses one point.
(The staff prepared something special.)
Say something to your wife.
(To Go Eun)
I love you.
(Congratulations on your second child.)
Can't we get a point because our team lost?
Haha lost a point, but Kwang Soo earned one.
What about me?
- Kwang Soo's score is zero. - Okay.
Haha as well.
- It's because he lost. - Zero?
Okay.
This is important.
I don't want to get the sticker.
- Are we really going? - Yes, we have to go.
- It must be difficult. - I don't like haunted houses.
Here's why.
- Do you know Kim Hyun Ki? - I know him.
When he worked as a reporter,
he visited haunted houses in Japan.
- At that time, - Did ghosts appear?
he heard ghosts on the walkie-talkie and the radio.
- It's very scary in Japan. - Once you go to...
a haunted house in Japan, you feel confused for days.
- Have you been there? - I heard about it.
Then stay quiet.
- I only heard it. - Stay quiet unless you went there.
Don't try to brag.
I just heard it.
The crocodiles were scary too.
They come through the wire fence.
(Global Race)
(The most dangerous tourist spots selected by travelers)
(With 3 Solo Tour Cards,)
(one can go on a trip.)
(Who will be chosen?)
(Global Race)
(SBS Prism Tower)
Something smells good. It's not what I thought.
- What's this? - I thought they were watermelons.
What's going on?
Didn't we lose?
- Come here. - Yes, we did.
All right. Here's the next mission.
It's a unanimous OX quiz called "Danger Next Door".
(The second mission is "Danger Next Door".)
("Danger Next Door"?)
- What is it? - "Danger Next Door"?
(Why is everything dangerous?)
It's a unanimous OX quiz.
(What's the dangerous secret hidden next door?)
Please take a seat on the cushion laid out behind you.
Which cushion you take is up to you.
(Is it up to us?)
(That sounds most suspicious.)
Let's see.
- There's something by the entrance. - Wait a minute.
- This is the entrance. - There's something here.
- Are you sitting there? - Something might come out.
Something might come out.
I trust Se Chan.
- Me too. - Something is going on.
What could it be?
I hear some murmuring inside.
What is it?
(Everyone takes a seat nervously.)
Here are the rules. As we have new members,
we'll give an OX quiz to know each other's preferences and thoughts.
The number of people with an opinion of the minority decides how many...
are sent to the room next door starting from the right.
I shouldn't sit here.
(Why are you telling this now?)
- I had no idea. - You should have told us before.
This isn't right.
- Come on. - This is great.
- It's what Jong Kook said. - I told you.
- This isn't right. - Jae Seok.
- You can't sit there. - You have no choice.
- Go back. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- No way. - Play fairly.
I thought something good would come out.
That's why...
So Min told me...
something would come out from next door.
Hey!
We have to go in there instead.
She sat near the kitchen,
so I thought food would come out.
All the unlucky members are sitting here.
Let's do well.
(No one knows what's inside.)
In the room next door...
(What's in the dangerous room?)
There are dangerous punishments.
- Pardon me? - Punishments?
(It's a compilation of the "best" punishments on Running Man.)
There are amazing prizes as well.
- That's right. - There are also good things.
(There's a variety of benefits.)
If you win a prize, you earn a point.
If you get punished, you lose a point.
Those who can't go in the room will get a chance.
- What is it? - Based on the members' reactions,
- guess if they got a prize or not. - Can you decide to go in?
One person can volunteer to enter.
This is better.
- It depends on how we act. - Okay.
That's right.
They can trick us.
If you have a unanimous opinion,
you'll get one No Dangerous Bag Card.
("Danger Next Door" starts.)
Here's the first question. Please answer honestly.
"I had my first kiss before I was 20."
(Their hearts start to flutter.)
Are we being really honest?
Mine is unclear.
- I think... - One, two, three.
(Haha, Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo raise O.)
(Seok Jin and So Min raise X.)
There we go.
(Moving)
(Two members enter the room.)
- What's going on? - No.
(Jae Seok and So Min are selected.)
- What's going on? - Am I also going in?
I'm not, right?
Okay.
(What's inside the room?)
- No! - What's going on?
(He keeps screaming.)
It must be a punishment.
What's going on?
- They're being punished. - It's a punishment.
I think I know what it is.
- They're being beaten. - It must be a punishment.
Who thinks it's a prize and wants to go in?
This can't be something good.
- Here's why. - It's definitely a punishment.
I heard other people inside.
- No one wants to go in? - No.
It's delicious.
(She laughs emptily.)
She said it's delicious.
- She was screaming before. - That was a late reaction.
The naengmyeon tastes great.
It's really delicious.
They're coming out.
(Was it a prize or a punishment?)
It was a punishment.
(They were punished.)
It was a punishment indeed!
- It hurts. - So Min.
Look at So Min.
They have clothespins.
I knew he was unlucky.
It hurts.
Take them off.
It really hurts.
You can't hide your reaction.
Suddenly, she said it was delicious.
"The naengmyeon tastes great."
What was delicious?
I shouldn't have sat here. I really shouldn't have.
Gosh, I was so startled.
We asked if your first kiss was before you were 20.
Two members raised X.
- Who were they? - Seok Jin and So Min.
Wait.
Was Jae Seok's first kiss in high school?
It's unclear because it was when I was a senior.
- It was during winter... - Stop lying.
(What are you talking about, Jae Seok?)
Don't pretend like you had your first kiss then.
- Goodness. - Stop acting.
He pretends to be strong.
- Did you lie? - You didn't kiss.
- Whom was it with? - Hey, do you believe me?
- No. - No?
- What are you talking about? - This is driving me crazy.
My goodness. Hey.
Wait a minute.
- Did you raise O, Haha? - Of course.
- How old were you? - It was early.
- How old were you? - I was an expert at kissing.
Stop joking.
- How old were you, Se Chan? - I was a sophomore.
- I was also an expert. - Wait a minute.
(Their childhood was full of love.)
I also like to kiss.
Is this a competition?
- Is it? - I was three.
- What did you say? - I was three.
(He gets competitive.)
How about you, Kwang Soo?
I was in seventh grade.
- Stop joking. - It's true.
- He said it was at home. - It was.
- Kwang Soo. - That's early.
Apologize. That was too early.
The girl was older.
You were wild.
What?
(She means that he was mature.)
I wasn't wild.
We had our parents'...
- You brat. - It wasn't like that.
- We had our parents' permission. - From that early age...
- It wasn't like that. - You punk.
- It wasn't like that. - You brat.
What about you, So Min?
When I was 21, at a bus stop.
- That sounds very romantic. - Yes.
- When there were no buses? - How?
Yes, the buses had stopped running.
How did it happen?
It was sudden.
The guy suddenly kissed me.
(It was sudden.)
(The quiet night air...)
(was filled with my heartbeats.)
(She suddenly felt the boy's lips.)
It was sudden. The guy suddenly kissed me.
- Was he your boyfriend? - Yes.
- It was very short. - How did it feel?
After the kiss, weren't you embarrassed?
Sometimes, it becomes awkward.
- Yes. It was my first kiss. - It can become awkward.
- People say you hear bells ringing. - And?
(How was So Min's first kiss...)
(at a bus stop when she was 21?)
It was my first kiss.
- People say you hear bells ringing. - And?
All I remember is the smell of his saliva.
Gosh.
(The smell of his saliva)
- Don't give us too much details. - Gosh.
So Min, don't say something like that.
Don't ruin my fantasy.
(Her first kiss was gross.)
Please.
- Can we switch places? - Of course.
- Switch however you want. - It might be food this time.
In any case, I don't want to sit here.
So Min. It might be food.
Do you want to switch with me?
- Seok Jin will sit at the end. - It must be food this time.
Doesn't it sound like they're cooking?
Here's the second question.
In relationships,
I usually get dumped.
My pride is at stake.
One, two, three.
My goodness.
What's the result?
Kwang Soo is showing an X.
What?
Jae Seok is showing an X too.
(Four of them are sent to the next room.)
- Jae Seok is showing an X too. - Why?
What's with you?
- How many are going in? - How many are going in?
- How many are going in? - Am I going in too?
- How many are going in? - Again?
(Is it a penalty or a reward?)
Is it four?
(Shouting)
(Why are they shouting?)
All right.
Does any of you want to participate?
(The next room is dangerous.)
(They're screaming.)
I won't.
(Se Chan raises his hand.)
I want to participate.
- Would you like to participate? - Yes.
(Se Chan will participate.)
(What's in the next room?)
Go in.
Oh, my.
(What does he mean?)
Come out.
Really?
(It's fried chicken.)
It's food.
It tastes so good.
- Each gets a whole bucket. - It's a whole bucket.
(It was a reward this time.)
It tastes amazing.
(Se Chan wins fried chicken and one point.)
Haha, I told you to come.
(It's so tasty that it's dangerous.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Did you show an X?
(Kwang Soo doesn't get dumped?)
I know many cases.
We know many cases. Why did you show an X?
I don't usually get dumped.
- I know about three cases. - That's...
My girlfriend cheated on me, so I dumped her.
It's you that got dumped.
(It's you that got dumped.)
What are you talking about?
What makes you say that?
She left you first.
She cheated on me, so I dumped her.
Hey.
She turned out to have another guy.
- Kwang Soo. - I broke up with her.
Kwang Soo.
- You know this story, right? - Kwang Soo.
Everyone except you was aware...
that you got dumped.
I know what happened, and you got dumped.
That's not true.
(We root for you, Kwang Soo.)
- So Min, what did you show? - I showed an O.
How many boyfriends have you had so far?
I've had three.
- What? - Only three?
- Are you sure? - I had three serious relationships.
That's so few.
In the three relationships, how many times did you get dumped?
Twice.
Why has everyone become so quiet?
Why are we so quiet?
- Have some chicken. - By the way...
It's okay.
- So Min. - Give her some water.
You should eat a lot of good food.
So Min, did you dump the other one?
He cheated on me,
and I clung to him.
- Later, I dumped him. - That's enough.
(That's enough.)
Stop it now.
We understand. Stop it.
- Wait. - I took revenge.
You said Kwang Soo is the one who got dumped.
It means that you got dumped all three times.
That's not true.
So Min is the female version of Kwang Soo.
- It's not like that. - You and I are the same.
No. He cheated on me, and I wanted to forgive him,
but he still didn't wish to come back.
The girl told me to get lost.
(They're the same.)
She said she didn't want me. We're the same.
- Both of you got dumped. - No.
Don't ever call me since I dumped you.
(All of the sudden)
(Whom are you talking to?)
- Whom are you talking to? - What?
- Who are you talking to? - Is he here?
- The cameraman? - Is it the cameraman?
No.
Call me. It's still not too late.
Give me another chance.
My goodness.
(Clingy)
(Dangerous tourist attractions)
(They'll visit the most dangerous tourist attractions.)
(Global Race)
(The one who gets 3 Tour Stickers will go on a trip.)
(Who will go on the dangerous trip?)
(Dangerous tourist attractions)
Here's the next question.
"I'm 1 of the 3 most handsome members in Running Man."
- Of course. - One...
One,
- two, - Of course it's an O.
three.
Okay.
- It must be unanimous. - Okay.
(Unanimous)
- Is it unanimous? - It's unanimous.
- Yes! - Yes!
It was too easy.
- You shouldn't have asked this. - It's obvious.
Everyone has their unique charms.
It's hard to say who's the most good-looking.
Number one would be Ji Hyo.
- Of course. - If we're only talking about looks.
Tell us what you are.
I'm number two.
- What? - Number two.
You look like the master in "Drunken Master".
You look like the red-nosed master.
He's right.
- The master in "Drunken Master"? - He's right.
- The master? - He's right.
Do you mean the man who does this?
(Speechless)
How can you be number two?
You look like the master in "Drunken Master".
Okay. For me,
it's hard to say who looks better between Ji Hyo and So Min,
but I'd be number two.
What did you just say?
- You're unbelievable. - What did you just say?
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, you're number eight.
(Not a chance)
- Are you out of your mind? - Get lost.
You're so shameless.
- He's out of his mind. - He's unbelievable.
Get off me.
- It's so annoying. - Get off me.
Let me tell you one more time.
- I'm 2nd. So Min is 3rd. - What about me?
You're uglier than me.
My goodness.
We have different charms.
Number eight would be Se Chan.
(That's one thing for certain.)
(Shocked)
- I agree. - Don't say that.
I agree.
Se Chan, you're the last.
- You're number eight. - Are you serious?
To be honest,
as he is ugly, I was afraid I'd hurt him...
if I say he's ugly.
- You're lying. - You really are ugly.
- Kwang Soo. - I mean it.
Apart from your height, you're no match for me.
It's so infuriating.
- Do you want to see? - Kwang Soo.
I had a hard time choosing between you and Se Chan.
Don't say that.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
Me?
You can be first.
- You're number one. - You can have it.
So Min would be number two.
- All right. - Number three would be...
Do you mean So Min is not as pretty as you are?
(Can't So Min be number one?)
- She isn't? - She isn't?
You know that?
She's never as pretty as you are, right?
What can I do about that?
(Embarrassed)
(I'm sorry I'm so pretty.)
What can I do?
- You're honest. - You're right.
Number eight?
- Tell us who you think is last. - Number eight?
Yes.
- Be honest. - It's neck and neck.
- Who? - Pick one.
- Tell us. - Just pick one.
Jae Seok and Se Chan are neck and neck.
(Jae Seok versus Se Chan)
- Ji Hyo. - By the way,
does she hate guys whose mouths stick out?
- Hey. - I mean...
- Come here. - I mean...
- Come here. Look at Kwang Soo. - Leave me out.
- Don't pick me, seriously. - Look at Kwang Soo.
He looks so ugly right now.
- Look at him. - It's because I got splashed.
- Am I ugly? - Se Chan just gave me goosebumps.
Listen to what he just said later.
- What did I say? - He said to himself,
"Really? Me?"
- Come here, Kwang Soo. - Really? Me?
(Has he never been called ugly?)
(Ugly? Me?)
- Am I really ugly? - "Am I really ugly"?
I think he's being serious.
The Yang brothers are nuts.
- Don't talk about my family. - Fine.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I'm wondering who So Min thinks is in last place.
- Me? - Purely based on our faces.
- I have a unique taste. - So who is it?
(Staring)
(He's still in last place.)
You...
Come on. This won't do.
(They applaud her for being objective.)
- Welcome, So Min. - She's good.
- She was being honest. - This is war, So Min.
It's war, So Min.
I'll explain it so that you can understand.
- Do it. - Listen. Ji Hyo is in first place.
- Right. - She's in first place.
So Min and I...
are in 2nd place. We're both in 2nd place.
- For goodness' sake. - For goodness' sake.
(They get mad at each other.)
- Do you want me to headbutt you? - My goodness.
Do you want me to hit you with my double eyelid?
(Everybody thinks they're last, but they think they're second.)
And the rest of you can pick your spots.
No way. Don't group me with them, Haha.
- Don't do that to me. - Come on.
(Everybody else is the same.)
- What are you talking about? - Hey, Kwang Soo.
Haha's face is so common...
that 40 percent of our staff members have his face.
Look. If you find anybody with protruding lips,
they look like Jae Seok. Here he is. It's Jae Seok.
It's Jae Seok. They look exactly the same.
(It's Jae Seok's twin.)
They look the same. Put this cap on. They look the same.
- It's Jae Seok. How can you say no? - Hey.
(He's just slightly taller.)
- Right? Watch. - Hey.
(This is not it.)
(There's a group of people who look like him.)
If they wear glasses and a cap, they all look like you.
- Put it on. - There's another one here.
(Cap, glasses and protruded lips equal Jae Seok.)
- Don't do this to me. - What's going on?
- What's going on? - You're driving me nuts.
(It's okay. We're all living happily.)
- I'm sorry. - Don't worry.
- "Don't worry"? - Don't worry.
He's got the Korean face. I didn't realize it before.
(This is the new paradigm of Korean men.)
(Find the real Jae Seok.)
Here's the next question.
"If Earth is destroyed and only these members are left,"
"there is someone here I'd like to date."
(I'd like to date one of the members if Earth was destroyed.)
- This is too difficult. - Hold on.
(These questions are getting difficult.)
Let's be honest with ourselves.
There are only eight people left on Earth.
Wait. There are only eight people left?
- Yes, there are. - He's the ugliest in the world?
What are you saying? We are similar.
- No way. - Why me?
(You're 1st from the bottom.)
(We respect you.)
That's what it is.
- Am I that ugly? - Under this assumption, you are.
(We don't understand why he doesn't get it.)
One, two, three.
- Yes. - This is so obvious.
(2 people are chosen.)
(It's Jae Seok and Se Chan.)
- How many people is it? - I'm worried about this one.
- My gosh. - Two people, right?
- Is it three? - Is it?
It's two.
Come in. It's three.
(You're here already so join us.)
(He's splayed out.)
- It's 3. Come in. - It's 3.
(He's dragged.)
It's 2. It's 2, Seok Jin.
- It's 3. - Drag him. He can get the penalty.
- Do you want to save him? - No.
- He's in there already. - I'm not playing again.
It's two!
(Why me?)
(Laughing)
Come back out.
(What was in the room next door this time?)
It was two. Why did you drag me in?
(We're sorry if any of the viewers were having dinner.)
This isn't fair.
- This is great. - Even when we were inside,
they wouldn't paint my face, saying I was already ugly.
(It looks like someone painted his face already.)
- They said he was okay. - They said I was ugly enough.
They said they could leave him be.
Why did you drag me in?
- Seok Jin looks the prettiest. - He looks the most decent.
(You're the prettiest.)
Who cares?
Two people said no. They won't date anybody here.
- Who were they? - It was me.
- Why? - To be honest,
So Min and Ji Hyo are like family to me.
- That's why. - What? You can't put it that way.
- I'm serious. I thought about it. - What about the rest of us?
I think it'll be a no.
I bet you'll be the most easily convinced.
Ji Hyo and So Min are very charming,
but they're not my style.
(I'm sorry, but it's true.)
I can win Jae Seok over with one finger.
(One finger is enough.)
- Come on. - That easily?
Hey, that's impossible.
Watch out.
(Pointing)
If it comes to that situation, he'll be at Ji Hyo's door all night...
saying, "Ji Hyo, give me a minute."
(Open the door for me, Ji Hyo.)
Hold on. We have to ask the others.
- Did you say yes? - I did.
- I want to date Ji Hyo. - Really?
- He's talking about the present. - The world doesn't have to end.
(It's a confession from the ugliest to the prettiest.)
The Earth doesn't have to be destroyed. She's very charming.
She's beautiful.
I'm sorry to say this, but it'll look just like this.
When the world comes to an end, the four of you will be there,
- and we'll be here. - Don't say that.
Don't say that. I don't belong here.
(They all fight back.)
Don't say that to me. I don't belong here.
- I'm disappointed in you. - Wait.
- Did you dress up, Kwang Soo? - Hey, look.
- Don't we look like a tribe? - Not me!
- I didn't dress up! - It looks like you did.
(It's the ugly tribe.)
(The OX quiz continues.)
- Is it 2? - It's 2 again?
(They continue to earn points next door.)
What's this?
Hey. You...
(Who'll become the chosen tourist?)
I've seen you in a cartoon.
You all answered unanimously,
so you can remove one briefcase.
One person can remove it.
- Who wants to go? - Let's have So Min do it.
- You should. - Should I?
She has good senses.
(Two hours ago during the opening hour,)
(she removed the Solo Tour Card.)
(Would her luck...)
(work this time as well?)
(There is 1 No Tour and Solo Tour Card each and 2 Couple Tour Cards.)
Pick the Solo Tour Card.
Please. That's what I want too.
(Please get rid of...)
(the Solo Tour Card.)
(She picks number 2.)
- Okay. - I pick number two.
I don't know about this one.
(They're all worried.)
Okay, pick this one. Go ahead, So Min.
She picked this one.
As long as it's not the No Tour Card.
- Please. - One, two.
(What is in the briefcase that So Min has picked?)
- It's the Couple Tour Card. - It's the Couple Tour Card.
(Couple Tour Card)
(At least it's not the No Tour Card.)
This is not bad.
- Good thing it wasn't No Tour Card. - Exactly.
- We have one left of each. - We just need the No Tour Card.
We have one of each card now.
- We still have hope. - This is why it's 50-50 chance.
There's the Couple Tour Card left.
You can erase your makeup, and we'll move onto the next game.
- All right. - Okay.
(They move onto the next dangerous game.)
(Global Race)
(The most dangerous tour sites chosen by bloggers)
(With 3 Solo Tour Cards,)
(one can go on a trip.)
(Who will be chosen?)
(Global Race)
Before we play the last game, divide yourselves into two teams.
- Is it up to us? - It's 4 on 4?
It's up to us?
(We have to make our own teams?)
(Then...)
- It worries me to be on your team. - Isn't this fine?
Please choose carefully. This is your last chance.
Who has the same number of points as me?
- Me. - Him.
- You too? Go there then. - Yes.
Why are you handing over the burden?
- That's what I'm saying. - No, you just have to come over.
- You just have to come over. - Switch with him?
(Sure)
- Don't go. - Jong Kook.
(It's an unfair trade.)
Where are you going?
(That's a huge imbalance.)
- He's so weird. - What's wrong with you?
- This is not fair. - I'll say this.
There's no advantage for being strong.
Why are you telling us that?
- What are you saying? - What are you saying?
(Do we look that weak?)
- Hey. Let's do this. - All right.
- This looks good. - These are the teams.
(Seok Jin, Jong Kook, and Haha lead with 1 point each.)
This mission is your last chance to earn your points.
It's called, "Dangerous Gathering".
- You have to find something. - "Gathering"?
Pick who's going to go first,
and you can hide behind the curtains.
The other team will stand on any one spot...
from the square that lists numbers 1 to 4.
Each spot can hold up to three people.
Add your numbers together...
- to earn your points. - I might lose all my points.
- I'm minus 2... - You're minus 2.
so if you pick me, I'll be minus one.
(You'll earn the added points.)
However, since Kwang Soo is minus 1 and Jae Seok is minus 2...
(If you combine these 2...)
- We're nuclear bombs. - Right.
(They're the bombs.)
- This is awesome. - Okay.
It's better to have more minuses.
- That's right. - Minuses are good.
We just have to avoid Se Chan.
This is bad.
(They're full of minuses.)
But you have me. Don't worry.
If you land on us, you'll get destroyed.
This isn't beneficial to us.
Let's separate ourselves.
Go ahead.
Well...
It'll be bad for us whatever we pick.
It's good if they pick me.
- It'll be good for us. - Exactly.
So I have to stand by myself.
- Let's separate. - Let's all separate.
Is this good?
We're competing against them,
but I'm also competing against Jae Seok.
(They're racing for last place.)
- We're both minuses. - If I become minus two...
If I pick Se Chan,
- it's over for me. - It'll be the worst score.
Jae Seok.
If you pick Se Chan, you have to book a flight to Japan.
(Goodbye)
You can pick first since you're last place.
- My goodness. - You can go.
- It's competition again. - This is an individual race...
- so let's do rock, paper, scissors. - Do rock, paper, scissors.
- As long as we don't get this. - Exactly.
- Avoid Se Chan. - As long as I don't get this.
- Rock, paper, scissors - Scissors
- What do people usually... - When it comes to numbers...
They're always unlucky so I can't predict what they're going to pick.
(It's impossible to analyze them.)
I don't know what to do.
(I think Jae Seok will pick this.)
(That's right. You're right.)
You're right.
(They want Jae Seok to pick Se Chan so that he comes in last place.)
(What would the result be?)
Rest of you, please face the other way.
What number did you choose, Kwang Soo?
I pick...
(Hesitating)
Number two!
(Kwang Soo picks number 2. If he picks Se Chan, he's last.)
My gosh.
What am I supposed to choose?
(He only has to avoid Se Chan.)
(Opening)
(Who's standing on number 2?)
(It's Haha.)
(Kwang Soo picks Haha.)
(He has 0 points now.)
(It's between me and Jae Seok.)
So Min is next.
I don't know what to do.
I pick number three.
(She picks Jong Kook.)
I was going to do that.
(Don't say anything, So Min.)
(So Min also has 0 points.)
It's Jae Seok's turn.
(Come here, Jae Seok.)
- What's left now? - Number 1 and 4.
(Number 1 and 4 are left.)
(He has to avoid Se Chan on number 1.)
(Sighing)
- I'm done if I choose Se Chan. - You are.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan are both last place with minus 2 points.)
(He has to avoid losing more points so that he doesn't end up last.)
(He picks a number. He walks towards it.)
(What number did he pick?)
(What?)
(Did he pick Se Chan?)
(My gosh)
Jae Seok is done for!
(What happened?)
(3 minutes ago...)
I choose number one.
(He makes up his mind.)
(You're coming here?)
(He's ready to welcome Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok is done for!
(Boiling)
This is unbelievable.
(Let's worship Jae Seok.)
- He's so unlucky. - This is so strange.
(Jae Seok has minus 4 points now.)
He's doomed!
- My gosh. - How's this possible?
Book him a ticket to the shark cage in Hawaii!
He has no time to waste!
(He's getting closer to meeting the sharks.)
- Why did you go to number one? - But...
- You don't know yet. - We do not.
- We don't know yet. - We have Se Chan.
- These two might stand together. - That's right.
We might stand together.
(What will happen to Jong Kook's team?)
These are the points.
Look. I'm sure...
- minus 2 and 1 will go together. - Of course.
Even if I pick it...
You'll be minus 2.
I'll be minus 2 and Jae Seok will still lose.
- As long as you don't get Jae Seok. - You have to be careful.
It's between me and Jae Seok.
(It's a race against the losers.)
- No, no. - Let's stand together.
- You have to go together. - We have to.
It's useless otherwise.
The best you can do is a tie.
(The minuses have to team up for Jae Seok's sake.)
- We have to hope Se Chan picks us. - I got it.
(Would Se Chan avoid them?)
Haha.
Where will you go?
(I choose 2.)
(He picks number 2 without any pressure.)
(Don't come here, Haha.)
(Where did he choose?)
(He picked So Min. He has 0 points.)
(It's okay as long as he's not last.)
(We want you so much, Se Chan.)
Ji Hyo.
(Next is Ji Hyo with 0 points.)
Pick, please.
(If Ji Hyo picks Jae Seok, he's automatically in last place.)
(You're not coming to us, right?)
(She passes by.)
(Good job, Ji Hyo.)
Jong Kook and Se Chan, you can pick together and check.
Please go in.
(If Se Chan picks 3, he's last. If he picks 4, Jae Seok is last.)
(Who'll be the first runner-up for the dangerous tour?)
(Is it Jae Seok or Se Chan? Who's the unluckiest one?)
(Se Chan picked number 3.)
(Se Chan got unlucky again.)
Really? Are you serious?
He's so unlucky.
(Jae Seok is not last anymore.)
- Really? - This is impossible.
- Are you serious? - He's so unlucky.
He's so unlucky.
- He's so unlucky. - He's so bad.
- He's so unlucky. - He's so unlucky.
(Even the staff's in awe of his "great" foresight.)
(10 minutes ago...)
- You can pick ours. - Go ahead.
Can I do this?
- Sure. - It's up to you.
- I'll pick this. - You get first pick.
(He assigned the rest of his team.)
(While he picked number 3 and assigned the others,)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo stood on number 3.)
I'll go first.
- I'm safe. - How?
I understand him now.
- I finally got lucky. - I understand him now.
- He's the ticking bomb. - He is.
You're incredible.
- He's the bomb. - It's not a prank, right?
It's not. We're here from the beginning.
- He's the bomb. - This was the original.
Se Chan is in last place with minus five points.
Jae Seok survived.
Let's see what happens to Se Chan.
- There's the No Tour Card. - We'll go to the lobby,
and you'll pick either No Tour, Solo, or Couple Tour Card.
There's Couple Tour Card.
What if he picks Couple Tour Card and takes Jae Seok?
If I pick Couple Tour Card, I'll take you.
- Se Chan. - Se Chan.
Se Chan. Calm down.
- Why? - Calm down.
- Let me breathe. - There's No Tour Card.
- That's right. - There is.
- Let me breathe. - There's one of each.
(It's the moment of truth.)
This is fun. It's fun until the end.
- Those briefcases are scary. - This is exciting.
- Se Chan. - Yes.
(Se Chan's decision remains.)
Pick a briefcase.
I'll be so happy if he gets the No Tour Card.
(Everybody will be happy that way.)
- Be calm, Se Chan. - I'll be calm.
(This doesn't just involve you.)
- I'll pick. - Go.
It won't be easy.
- I pick five. - I knew it.
(He's certain.)
- You knew? - I did.
- I thought so. - I won't open it.
- Se Chan picked five. - I knew it.
For transparency, please open number six.
This is fun. It's exciting. How nervous.
- I hope it's not the No Tour Card. - What is it?
(Please don't be.)
(What is in briefcase number 6 that Se Chan didn't pick?)
- What is it? - Solo Tour Card.
Solo Tour Card.
(The Solo Tour Card is out.)
He escaped the solo tour.
(It's still possible he picked the Couple Tour Card.)
- He escaped the solo tour. - I'm relieved.
- I'm relieved. - What did I say?
- Congratulations. - Good job.
Wait. Jae Seok wanted him...
to pick the No Tour Card, and he looks so sad now.
- Why do you look regretful? - Inside that briefcase...
is either a Couple Tour or a No Tour Card.
Would you like to switch...
- or not? - Se Chan...
(Se Chan has one last chance to switch.)
(Will he take the chance or refuse?)
I need the No Tour Card, right?
- Only think about that. - No Tour Card, right?
- Think about that card. - That's what you need.
- I picked number five, right? - Yes.
- Don't hesitate. - I will...
This is your first time starring on the show as a member of the show.
(Haha recommends the briefcase number 1 since it's his 1st time.)
(This is his first appearances as a regular member.)
(This is the first episode of the global project.)
(This suggestion sounds tempting. Will he change?)
I will switch.
- Really? - The first briefcase?
(He kept making the wrong decisions. He feels he must change his choice.)
- I think I must change my decision. - You think so?
(He really changed?)
We will open the briefcase Se Chan has selected.
(The member who will go...)
(to the dangerous tourist attraction depends on this briefcase.)
(If a No Tour Card is inside, Se Chan won't go on a trip.)
(If a Couple Tour Card is inside, a member will go on a trip with him.)
(What is inside the briefcase number 1?)
(He picks the Couple Tour Card.)
- Wait. Hold on. - You have to...
(This is crazy. Goodness!)
(He checks the briefcase number 5.)
- You are amazing. - This had the No Tour Card.
- This is crazy. - What is wrong with you?
Is this true? That was the Couple Tour Card?
(He is truly the unluckiest one.)
He is the unluckiest.
(This is the class of new master of the misfortunes.)
You had the No Tour Card right here.
He's the king of misfortunes.
(Se Chan will choose his companion.)
The rest of the members will turn around.
- He'll remove a member's name tag. - Okay.
- Is there a point of this? - All right.
We never know whom Se Chan will choose.
- Se Chan. Choose whoever you want. - All right. I will.
- I'm not even worried. - Choose whoever you want.
No one will scold you.
- Who is the companion... - I'm nervous.
that will join you on your trip?
(Why are all the cameras filming me?)
(When you said you will choose me as your companion 30 minutes ago,)
(I've never imagined I would be in this position.)
(He's thinking hard.)
- Why are you behind us? - Exactly.
(Let's see whose name tag is the softest.)
- You startled me. - Hey.
- Hey. You really startled me. - What are you doing?
- You are going too far. - Hey! What's wrong with you?
- Let's see whose name tag is loose. - Hey.
(She gets goosebumps.)
- Did you have fun today? - Hey.
- You had new members today. - It was fun.
What did you say before?
- I am the unluckiest? - Se Chan.
You really startled me.
Okay. I will be running from here...
- and remove that person's name tag. - Okay.
(This is nerve-wrecking.)
(Take care, Jae Seok.)
(Running Man is really fun.)
- Off I go. - Please.
(Who will get closer...)
(to the dangerous tourist attraction with Se Chan's Couple Tour Card?)
(No way!)
What?
(Haha. Why don't you join me?)
(We survived!)
It was Haha.
(Jae Seok is safe.)
That was a good choice.
Haha. Spare me this once. I'm sorry.
(Haha encouraged him to change the briefcase.)
(Se Chan punished him with the Couple Tour Card.)
- That was great. - He picked the right person.
- We survived. - We did.
(Haha is mad.)
- You can do it! - That was a surprise.
Haha and Se Chan will each get...
one Tour Sticker for Global Race.
(Who will collect 3 Tour Stickers and go on the trip?)
(Few days later)
(April 10 at Incheon International Airport)
We are at the airport.
Are we really going to Osaka?
(They are half in doubt.)
- Take care. - Bye.
(Are we really saying goodbye here?)
- I guess they're really going. - Take care of them, So Min.
- Are you really going? - Take care, Ji Hyo.
- They are really going. - It's happening. What will we do?
- How can this happen? - Will we come back?
(Can we come back today?)
- I have a live radio show tomorrow. - I have to come back.
Ji Hyo. Once we go through here, we are really going.
- Haha. We already have our tickets. - We can't come back out.
(The staff suddenly informed them about their departure.)
(Did they really go abroad?)
(Few hours later)
(They really went! Having no twists is the element of the surprise.)
(They are in the center of Osaka.)
(Seok Jin, So Min, and Jae Seok are dispatched to Japan.)
(Welcome to Taiwan, the city of delicious food)
(A unique trip)
(Haha, Ji Hyo, and Se Chan are distracted to Taiwan.)
(On this island, there's a magnificent view of the blue sky.)
(Running Man members are here,)
(but it turns into a nature documentary.)
(Wondrous stories are unfolded on this wondrous island.)
(Jong Kook, Do Yeon, and Kwang Soo are dispatched to this island.)
(To find the taste)
(To find the hidden mission)
(Body language)
I can already smell the food.
(Food trip in Osaka)
(They are overly motivated.)
(He runs into a pole.)
(The core of his motivation is damaged.)
(Jae Seok takes the lead since Seok Jin is injured.)
(Do you know that place?)
(She's kindly explaining it.)
(After listening to her)
(We can communicate telepathically in Osaka.)
(It's a blockbuster race on a global scale.)
(We are the world)
(Through this race, they become one with the whole world.)
He's a running man.
(Ripping)
I ripped it.
(And)
(They discover a shrine of variety shows in Osaka.)
(Are they at a public bathhouse?)
I will be back.
Hey.
(He suddenly shows up on camera.)
(What is next week's mission that made them go naked?)
(Running Man)