(2017 Running Man's Global Project)
(The most dangerous tourist attractions in the world)
(Last week, the 6 members of Dangerous Trip were decided.)
(Jae Seok picked the dangerous tourist attraction.)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear in Japan)
(It's a place no one wanted to go.)
(We are spared.)
(It takes about two weeks to get a visa for the shoot.)
(The production team hosted a party during the wait.)
(Can we eat the food?)
(The clueless members were forced to go to Russia and Mongolia.)
(The mission for Team Mongolia: Meet the nomads and milk sheep.)
(The mission for Team Russia: Catch king crab and 10 seafood.)
(It's not a simple trip.)
(Their success will exempt 2 people from Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(The team leaders hold the key to exemption.)
(Thus started Dangerous Trip: Last Chance in Mongolia and Russia.)
(Ji Hyo, I can carry your backpack.)
(The two team leaders overuse their power.)
(The rest of the members fight to move up the ranks.)
(Aren't you uncomfortable?)
My goodness.
(Look at me, Jong Kook.)
(The members' fierce loyalty helps everything go well for Team Russia.)
(They struggle every step of the way.)
(The 2 middle-aged men and 2 women quarrel.)
(Who will complete the mission and win exemption?)
Where do we go?
Let's order a lot of dishes.
- We shouldn't do that. - Let's find a restaurant first.
We should save up money. We haven't found a place to stay.
This feels like Gwanghwamun.
Is there a place that resembles Hongdae?
- Seok Jin. - Hongdae.
- I am thirsty. - It's a hotel.
Isn't this a hotel?
It will be expensive, right?
- It looks very expensive. - Shall we ask...
how much it costs for a night?
Shall I ask, "How much for one day?"
This hotel is nice and clean. It will be nice to sleep here.
Excuse me.
Hello. How much is it for one room for a day?
"Supreme corner room".
(Even the cheapest room costs 260 dollars.)
(Seok Jin is in a dilemma.)
There is a hamburger joint.
Shouldn't we wait for Seok Jin?
He will come. The bun is black.
- Maybe it uses squid ink. - How much does it cost?
We should buy a hamburger...
and divide it among the three of us.
Then we can have a meal. What do you think?
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo.
Please exempt So Min and me.
(Thank you, Jae Seok.)
Also...
(Also)
If you must choose one, exempt me.
(If you must choose one, exempt me.)
(Thank you, Jae Seok.)
- Okay? - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
"If you must choose one, exempt me."
- He wants to be exempt. - So Min should go.
She should experience it.
No, I will seriously...
pee my pants.
Can you not say things like that?
- But I get scared really easily. - I could really pee my pants.
- I know. - He's back.
- How much is it? - It won't work.
- How much? - We have about 500 dollars left,
but it's 250 dollars.
- Goodness. - Seriously?
For two rooms.
But they offered discounts.
(Do luxurious hotels offer discounts?)
It went from 230 dollars to 150 dollars.
(Just in case,)
(he asked for a discount.)
- Excuse me? - Any discounts?
(If that's the case)
- Two? - Yes.
Let's see.
150 dollars? It's affordable.
(We'll give you a huge discount.)
But for 2 rooms, it's still 250 dollars.
(It's still expensive.)
(Shall I grab some candies and leave?)
We have to save as much as possible.
Free internet is available.
- Free internet? - Yes.
(Poor traveler is busy taking candies.)
Okay.
- I'll go discuss with my friends. - Do you know?
- Then we'll come back again. - Okay.
Thank you.
- He asked for discounts at a hotel. - It's 250 dollars.
But it really worked.
He didn't even hesitate.
Careful.
- Ji Hyo. - How about we...
- try this? - Let's try this burger.
It looks delicious.
- Let's share. - It's five cents.
- Let's buy some and share. - Sure.
(During the 13th century, Genghis Khan searched for food...)
(which could be eaten on horses.)
(He came up with the idea of flattening lamb crumbs,)
(and it became the first try of patties.)
(Am I too dark?)
Excuse me.
Can I have one black burger?
Feel free to speak in Korean.
Are you Korean?
- You're Mongolian? - But you're so good.
(He studied at a university in Korea.)
I graduated from a Korean university.
That's where you graduated?
I almost thought you were Korean.
Then we will have two orders of single black burger.
Those black buns look fascinating.
- They do. - Before we head out,
let's ask him where we can find nomads.
- Is that right? - Yes.
Why don't we just call it a day and go to a hotel?
(Ji Hyo, I'm a bit tired.)
We're all tired.
- 8:30am tomorrow. - Let's end it for today.
We won't be going anywhere even if we find something out today.
(Jae Seok, I guess you want to go to the Labyrinth.)
Look.
She's being way too strict.
Okay.
(Don't forget to be nice to me in Mongolia.)
She records on everything.
(For black burgers)
They're all wearing black gloves.
Look.
Isn't that interesting?
Look here.
They're wearing gloves.
- Black burger... - Do we have to?
- We're wearing black gloves. - We need to follow their rules.
This is actually fun.
- It's fun. - I wiped my hands for nothing.
It's so funny that it's also black.
- These gloves... - Let's wear them for milking sheep.
What do you think?
- Look. - Well...
Let's keep these gloves for later.
Or we could ask for extra gloves and use them for tomorrow.
- Black burger. - What do you think?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Gosh.
(Dropping)
(So Min never lets us down.)
- Gosh. - Try them. It's delicious.
I've never tasted anything like this before.
It's sweet.
- Is that so? - Yes.
It reminds me of that.
- It's delicious. - It's a Mongolian hamburger.
(Its taste is totally different from how it looks.)
- It's good. - It's really good.
The buns are crunchy.
I love the fries in Mongolia.
- It's good. - Really.
Be careful not to bite your finger.
They're all black.
(Both the buns and the gloves are black.)
You might bite your hand.
- This is incredible. - It's tasty.
We came to Mongolia for the mission.
It's to meet a nomad who's a descendant of Genghis Khan...
and milk their sheep.
Where should I go to meet nomads?
Terelj is the closest from here.
- It's called Terelj. - Terelj?
Terelj?
- Is it Terelj? - Yes.
- The person has to have this name. - What was that?
- What was that? - Bourgeois?
- What? - That means "middle-class".
- That's very irrelevant. - What was that?
- Borjigit. - Borjigit.
(Of course, he knows.)
- So it's the correct name. - I'm from the Borjigit.
(Did they meet a Borjigit already?)
- Really? - Yes.
By any chance, does any one of your family members run a sheep farm?
(If his family is a nomad, they get to clear the mission in one day.)
(Will they be able to meet a nomad right away?)
- No. - Oh, I see.
Where should we go to look for them?
- Where? - Yes.
He said there's a place an hour away.
(They decide to move to Terelj.)
- Really? - Yes.
(They drive across the vast plains, looking for a Borjigit.)
(Running Man runs in the vast wilderness.)
(The possibilities are low, but they won't give up.)
(They search everywhere.)
(Their journey doesn't go the way they want.)
(Will Team Ji Hyo get to meet a Borjigit nomad?)
- Right? - Are you the one?
- Are you a Borjigit? - Goodness.
Wasn't the burger great?
- It was. - We made a perfect choice.
Let's just go to the Korean restaurant.
Why would you have Korean food when you're in Mongolia?
His taste really doesn't go with mine.
- There's another restaurant. - It's a restaurant.
(They find another restaurant nearby.)
- It smells like lamb meat. - They sell food.
- It's a restaurant. - They sell food.
What's lamb meat in English again?
Come this way.
Let's order a dish and share.
We have enough money. Let's just have as much as we want.
(What did you say?)
We have to eat breakfast tomorrow morning too. We have to save money.
Your taste really doesn't get along with mine. This is not great.
- Ji Hyo. - Goodness.
Just send him to Japan first.
- He doesn't need to milk sheep. - Our tastes really don't meet.
Soo Yeon, I'm saying this since Jong Kook isn't here.
Who is Soo Yeon?
- It's her real name. - I'm so confused.
Call me Ji Hyo, please.
- I see. Ji Hyo. - Or team leader.
- Team Leader Ji Hyo. - He calls you that to tease you.
- So Min, do you have another name? - No.
My family calls me Parrot.
- What? - My dad thinks I'm too talkative.
I see you're the same at home too.
- It's good. - It's a city.
(She can chat about anything.)
It's like we're exploring the world by walking.
Right, wearing a backpack.
There are so many people here.
Right.
(Parrot So Min doesn't let you down in Mongolia either.)
I see you're the same at home too.
- Let's order food now. - Let's do that.
Now, you can order food.
But before that, we'll give you a mission.
We can't eat in peace.
- Seriously. - We came all the way here.
The real mission starts tomorrow.
Let's just eat.
- I'm tired. - When can we use the Chance Card?
You will get to use it tomorrow.
Oh, right. I almost forgot about it.
This is my first time being in a team with a Chance Card.
Because...
- Gosh. - Hey.
You keep throwing dirt on our names.
- You just talked bad about us. - You found Suzuki...
because of us.
You're right, but still, it's my first time.
So you're laughing at us.
Not at all. I respect you.
- Ji Hyo. - The other team.
I wonder what the other team is doing.
It's useless to know. Stop it.
- Don't change the subject to them. - Let the show focus only on us.
- I wanted to do it. - They're going to stop filming.
- So Min, stop. - What are they doing?
(What is the other team doing?)
- What are the other teams up to? - Up to?
(It's the pose they did in Japan.)
(What is the other team up to?)
- Hey. - Stop that.
They're going to start filming them.
- Let us be the main characters. - Let the show focus only on us.
There's no need to wonder.
- All right. - Let's hear him.
- So... - Give us the menu.
I'll tell you a Mongolian custom.
Here, you shouldn't have leftover food.
- So... - I saw a Mongolian customer...
leave food.
- I saw it too. - Right?
- They left some of the bun. - What are you talking about?
I thought that was their gloves.
(The leftovers were a lot that he thought they were gloves.)
You went too far.
- I'm serious. - Stop that.
I was confused if it were the food or the gloves.
Don't add to my comments.
We're having a conversation here.
Anyway, I was confused.
So the mission is...
called No Leftovers. This is your mission.
So we have to eat them all.
You can order one dish per person.
But the menu is written in Mongolian.
(The menu is written in Mongolian.)
The staff will pay half the amount...
if you order a dish each and finish all the food.
- You'll pay for half. - Look.
Look for the word "lamb".
(Let's see.)
The language is...
It says, "wow."
I really don't know.
(They have no idea.)
We will briefly tell you what they are.
Among them...
are peanuts, fish soup,
lamb dumpling soup, and lamb noodles.
That sounds delicious.
I don't think I can eat the noodles.
- It'll be delicious. - I can handle grilled lamb.
- There's water. - Water?
There's horse meat.
(It doesn't sound familiar at all.)
- What is that? - I haven't had it before.
I've never had it before.
- There's also cow liver, - Cow liver?
lamb chops, and flower bun.
(Their dinner depends on their choices.)
- We have to choose well. - This must be flower bun.
Look. It looks like it.
- No way. - Look here.
- Stop the nonsense. - It's pronounced like it.
- I can't read it at all. - This must be horse meat.
Just because it starts with an M?
This must be it.
(Trying to pronounce the word)
(Mongolian is so easy, right?)
- Can't a local... - My goodness.
read them out once...
- Can't you read them out for us? - for us?
Number one.
- That must be dumplings. - That must be dumplings.
Number two.
(Number 2)
(What is that?)
Number three.
(Number 3)
(What did you say?)
Number four.
(The more they hear, the more confused they become.)
Number seven.
Number eight.
(Number 8)
(I know this.)
I know what that means.
- It means pine nuts. - That's a horse.
Number eight means pine nuts.
- Which? - This.
("Camap" means pine nuts.)
- It's pine nuts. - This must be peanuts.
I know this one.
Then let's order it.
(Let's order it to be safe.)
Why would you order pine nuts? I'm hungry.
- I mean... - What's wrong with you?
Our tastes are so different.
Why would you eat pine nuts when you're hungry?
- We should try it. - It's because...
if we finish it, the staff...
- will pay half the price. - It's because they'll pay for half.
- We should order pine nuts. - Let's order it.
I just don't understand. Why would you eat pine nuts?
- It's our dinner. - You want lamb barbecue, right?
- But it's not here. - I know, but...
- Here... - Just eat pine nuts.
(Just eat pine nuts.)
Why?
- Just eat them. - It sounds like a curse word.
On the way here, udders got us in trouble.
(In the middle of Mongolia,)
(she shouted the word, "udders".)
Now, it's pine nuts.
- It's pine nuts now. - Why would you eat pine nuts?
You guys are ridiculous.
We should have something good. What's wrong with you?
Then let's do this.
- Let's all choose one dish. - Okay.
Number five sounds like barbecue.
I'd choose either number 2 or number 5.
I choose number five.
Ji Hyo, choose one.
I choose number one.
- Number one? - Yes.
Think carefully.
- Don't order horse meat. - This is hard.
Don't order water either.
Number four.
Okay, number six.
You've chosen numbers 1, 4, 5, and 6.
- Okay. - The order has been made.
We'll let you know which is which when the food is ready.
The order has been made.
I hope I won't get horse meat.
While waiting for your food,
do you want to learn how to play the Mongolian rock-paper-scissors?
How do you play it?
The rules are same as Korean game. You play it with your fingers.
You show one of your fingers at a time.
Thumb beats index finger.
Index finger beats middle fingers.
(There's a hierarchy between fingers next to each other.)
(In other cases, the game is tied.)
Each finger can beat the finger next to it.
- Let's try it. Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- 1, 2, 3. - 3.
(Little finger beats thumb.)
- I win. - You win.
Yes.
- Little finger beats thumb? - Exactly.
- Ji Hyo, play it with me. - Each finger beats the next finger.
- You can say rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(It's a practice round.)
(Shocked)
(It's just a game, but it is still offensive.)
- You win. - You win.
Ji Hyo, that was offensive.
How could you show that finger?
You're unbelievable.
- You wanted to win so much? - It's just a game.
It's just a game.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(It's just a fun game.)
- Hey. - I don't think we should play this.
We shouldn't play Mongolian rock-paper-scissors.
- It hurts my feelings. - I can't do this.
Seok Jin, rock-paper-scissors.
- You win. - I won. Give me your hand.
(Jae Seok wins.)
(Moving)
What was that?
- Why did you hit me? - Why did you hit him?
I just wanted to.
- Why did you do that? - Why did you do that?
- I just... - That was so unexpected.
- I was just looking at them. - Why did you do that?
That's why she's...
He kept moving his hand. That's why I wanted to hit it.
Our food must be ready.
- It's coming. - It's coming.
(Will they finish their food and pay only half the price?)
I'm worried.
(Will it be a painful dinner?)
The first dish will be served.
Which number is it?
(Will their order turn out to be successful?)
(The youthful city, Vladivostok, Russia.)
I want to get something to eat.
Should we find a place?
- Sure. - Let's take a break.
(They want to get something to eat.)
It's pork, chicken...
- What is this? - Hello.
(They found a kebab place.)
- It's kebab. - It's kebab.
(He recommends a dish.)
They sell dumplings.
It says, "It's hot," in Korean.
Wait. It's from Korea.
It says, "It's hot."
- It's from Korea. - It's from Korea.
Let's try their dumplings. It seems famous.
Should we get kebabs and dumplings?
(They order kebabs and dumplings.)
Where should we sit? Let's find a nice place.
- What about over there? - Sure.
- Let's make a toast. - Okay.
With our kebabs.
Regardless of the mission,
I'm happy to be in Russia with you guys.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you, Jong Kook.)
Let's complete our mission.
(They munch their food without saying many words.)
It tastes good.
(Jong Kook seems to be pleased too.)
(Seagulls)
(Our captain is having a meal.)
Go away!
The seagulls have eyes on our food. Be careful.
What is this?
(They have eyes on the dumplings.)
What?
Do they eat these? I don't think so.
Hey, you shouldn't feed them.
(Out of curiosity, Kwang Soo throws a piece of dumpling.)
(The seagull approaches.)
They'll keep coming.
You shouldn't do that.
Hey, what are you doing?
(Everyone loves dumplings.)
(Just then)
(Screaming)
They're all coming here.
Gosh, it's your fault.
(Kwang Soo, it's your fault.)
You shouldn't feed them salty food.
Gosh! Hey!
Gosh, what is this?
(Kwang Soo is surprised too.)
Why did you do that, Kwang Soo?
(Kwang Soo communicates with animals even in Russia.)
I'm sending you to Japan.
Book your flight ticket now.
- Jong Kook. - Book your flight ticket now.
He's so annoying. I can't stand him anymore.
- I've decided. - Okay.
(It's decided that Kwang Soo is going to Japan.)
Okay, it's decided.
- It can change, right? - What?
Tell me right now if it's unchangeable.
(His attitude has changed.)
What is that supposed to mean?
- It's unchangeable. - It is?
- It's unchangeable? - His attitude is so bad.
- Stop it. - Is it really unchangeable?
Is it unchangeable?
It can change, right?
Look at him.
Of course.
- Okay. - Don't act up.
- Okay. - You're losing your points.
- Our guide. - Yes.
What are we supposed to do?
I think we should ask this.
(Stammering)
- What does that mean? - Where are fishing boats?
- Where are fishing boats? - You're well prepared.
I'll find pictures of king crabs...
- and show them. - Okay.
I like this about you.
Are you...
- in that position? - What do you mean?
Aren't you on the same level as us?
It's not like that.
Don't you see I'm sitting next to Jong Kook?
Remember the rank.
What is that supposed to mean?
(You've been getting on my nerves.)
"What is that supposed to mean?"
What are you talking about?
- Remember the rank. - What rank?
Pull yourselves together.
You pull yourself together.
(You pull yourself together.)
You might regret later.
(Let's see who wins.)
We should ask directions.
Why don't we ask the man who was kind to us?
- The kebab guy? - The kebab guy?
- He was so kind. - We bought their food too.
- Let's go. - Okay, let's go.
(Jong Kook's word is law.)
- Let's go and ask. - Excuse me.
- What should we say? - Show him the pictures.
How do you say, "Please help?"
(Please help.)
(He asks the question he prepared.)
(What is he saying?)
- King crabs. - King crabs.
(They have to use gestures.)
(They explain fishing with gestures, while saying, "king crabs".)
(Do you understand?)
- King crabs. - King crabs.
(He suddenly nods.)
Moscow?
He recommends Russky Island.
- Russky Island? - An island?
Russky Island?
- How do we get there? - A boat?
(Is there a boat near here?)
(What does his gesture mean?)
What does that mean?
You can get there by car.
We can get to the island by car?
- Okay. Thank you. - Thank you.
(Let's try.)
(They're on their way to the king crab fishing boats.)
Does any of you want to freshen up your mouth?
- Me. - Okay.
- Me too. - Tell me.
- Why? - Are you good?
- Why? - I brought something.
What did you bring?
- What's that? - It's chewable toothbrushes.
- Chewable toothbrushes? - Chewable toothbrushes.
(When they visited Se Chan's place,)
(Ji Hyo got him chewable toothbrushes.)
(No one expected they'd come in handy someday.)
- I like it. - I brought them from home.
- You still have them? - They're new.
I like it.
- I'm well prepared... - Se Chan is great.
as the youngest member.
You might not go to Japan.
Thank you.
Se Chan cares about every member so much.
In addition to the toothbrushes, he even brought the waxing cream...
for us.
- I saw it. - Really?
- We can them tonight. - Foot packs?
I have the foot packs, and I also brought mask packs...
to hydrate our skin.
- I brought four aloe mask packs. - We can sleep after using them.
Please give me a big hand.
He's very good at these things.
- He's like that. - I agree.
That's enough, okay?
You aren't Jong Kook.
We're of the same rank.
Why do you keep bossing me around?
I don't like your attitude.
Not mine, right?
Speak to me with respect.
Stop it, Haha.
- Respect the hierarchy. - What hierarchy?
What gives you the right?
I'm the second best fighter.
Come on.
Shall we fight against him?
- What? - We can be a team.
You don't need to be a team.
- Why not? - You just don't.
It looks pretty.
(This is Russia.)
It's beautiful.
It's like Europe.
This is Russia, isn't it?
The view is more beautiful in real life than in photos.
(They enjoy the view of Vladivostok.)
(It's amicable among the members.)
The good weather makes everything look beautiful.
Isn't it different from what you expected?
- Right. - I thought it'd feel tense,
- but it's beautiful and detailed. - Things are small and cute.
What makes you say that things are small and cute?
- Those. - What?
Those buildings...
- are cute. - Which ones?
There are no large buildings.
Isn't it because they're far away?
- They're all big. - It's because they're far.
Is it because they're far away?
You shouldn't talk to me like that.
I wanted to tease you.
- I'm sorry. - Kwang Soo.
- I'm sorry. - Look.
- I see something. - Gosh.
(They arrive at Russky Island.)
It looks nice.
We could use any boat for fishing.
- There are a lot. - How about the big ones?
- I've been on a boat like that. - Me too.
- Let's get out. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(They must rent a boat.)
Hold on. Where's the captain?
(It's completely deserted.)
(Where is everyone?)
That's the only boat possible for fishing.
We have to catch king crab.
(That's the only boat big enough to fish.)
Shall we ask?
- Let's do that. - Okay.
Let's go.
Shall we ask these men?
How about him?
- Should we ask him? - Okay.
The other boats are too small to catch king crab.
- They're too small. - Right?
How do we catch them?
Is the boat equipped?
(They say hello in Russian.)
(He always gives a friendly smile.)
(It's a Russian captain.)
- Let's ask him. - He looks amazing.
- He looks great. - King crab.
(He speaks with gestures.)
- King crab. - You look great.
Is fishing possible?
Is it possible to catch king crab?
(He shows a photo.)
(Is it possible to catch king crab on this boat?)
King crab fishing?
(It's possible to catch king crab with this boat.)
- King crab? - Really?
(What does that hand gesture mean?)
Can you ask if we can ride the boat?
(They must catch king crab on the boat to avoid going to Japan.)
(Will the captain permit Team Jong Kook?)
You can get on the boat.
- We can? - You can get on the boat.
- We can get on the boat? - Can we catch other fish?
Not just king crab.
(Can you catch other types of seafood?)
He says it's possible.
(Team Jong Kook gets lucky and goes fishing.)
The boat is amazing.
- I've never been on such a boat. - Goodness.
- This is great. - It is.
What if we eat instant noodles here?
- That's a good idea. - We can eat king crab.
We can add king crab to the menu and eat outside.
- You're the third in rank. - Why?
- You brought instant noodles. - I did.
- I came prepared. - You did a good job.
- Do you remember the mission? - Yes.
We're off to catch...
king crab and 10 types of seafood.
We clear the mission if we catch king crab...
and 10 types of seafood at the same time.
- Definitely. - Even if we catch sea snails...
Those count.
You can't say they aren't a type of fish.
We accept anything that's edible,
but sea snails in different shapes count as one.
- Of course not. - Oh, come on.
- Come on. - We're not that silly.
Don't you know us?
You know we aren't that silly.
I'm telling you this because I know you guys too well.
(He knows them too well.)
It's because he knows us too well.
Tomorrow,
I don't plan to ride boats.
It's either you go to Japan...
or clear the mission today.
- Clear the mission today. - Did you bring gloves?
- Why do you ask? - If not, I'll give you mine.
No, I didn't bring gloves.
- I brought you a pair. - Thanks.
I'll push you into the water.
(He's so annoying.)
Goodness, Se Chan.
He's impressive.
- Here you go. - You're prepared.
- Okay. - Did you bring two pairs?
Do you think they look good on Jong Kook?
Did you steal your mom's?
He looks cool like a gangster.
A gangster?
I didn't mean it in a bad way.
- What did you call me? - Se Chan.
- He holds grudges. - Do I seem like a gangster?
That's not what I meant.
Try the grip. Aren't they nice and tight?
Aren't they perfect?
- You must decide now. - Yes?
What will you do?
Do what? Do you have a secret plan?
- Do what? - We don't have a secret plan.
(2 hours ago when they went to buy Coke)
(Kwang Soo thought it's unfair.)
(What's wrong with him?)
(What's so great about being a team leader?)
(Why don't we rebel against him?)
Will you keep obeying him?
(I can't bear it anymore.)
(They dreamed of rebelling against the team leader.)
(What are you planning to do?)
- We don't have a secret plan. - Do what?
Se Chan is being annoying.
You find him annoying?
(Are you sure about that?)
- What do you mean? - Wait.
Are you sure you're not a gangster?
(Are you sure about that?)
Either take off the gloves or the sunglasses.
Do at least one.
Why don't you take off Lee Byung Hun's jacket?
Do something.
(Lee Byung Hun's jacket?)
(Let's go to Vodka and have a glass of Vladivostok.)
- My shoulders hurt, Jong Kook. - Really?
How about now?
(My members shouldn't be in pain.)
Jong Kook.
That feels good.
How about yours?
- It feels great. - Doesn't it?
It feels so good.
(It's 10 dollars for 30 seconds' worth of service.)
- He's asking for money. - Are you paying him?
- Here you go. - Great.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
He's the tall one.
- What did you say? - He's the tall one.
- Isn't the pronunciation wrong? - You're a tall one.
- You're the short one. - I'm the short one.
(They mimic the Russian pronunciation.)
- He's the old one. - He's the gangster one.
- He's the gangster one. - He's the bad one.
(They call him the old, gangster and bad one.)
We were being funny.
- Come on. - It's a joke.
We're having fun.
You should understand.
Come on.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Okay, let's go.)
I feel great.
I feel good too.
(Like the passing wind)
(The silly men are excited to be in Russia.)
This is great.
Kwang Soo is also a type of fish.
(He's also a type of fish.)
Didn't we catch one already?
I'm not a fish.
Doesn't he count if we put him in the fishing trap?
Why would I go in there?
You should go in if we catch nine.
What are you talking about?
If you flap in the fishing trap, we'll accept it.
Do I have to flap?
- I have to flap? - Let's go.
Let's do it.
- We got one already. - What?
- Goodness. - Kwang Soo.
- You can do it for the team. - How can I go in the fishing trap?
- Can't you do that much for us? - I know.
He has to flap.
(The boat of love...)
(heads towards northeast.)
It's the Russky Bridge.
It's red, blue, and white.
(With colors of the Russian flag, it's also called Russian Bridge.)
This will be our memory. What should we do then?
- We must take photos. - That's right.
- Let's take photos. - To keep memories...
- Take photos. - Jong Kook.
He's in a good mood.
- To keep memories... - Take photos.
Let's take photos.
(I miss home.)
- It looks great. - It does.
- I feel great. - Isn't this good?
It's a great day. We'll get lucky and catch something.
We're on a boat.
(What is it this time?)
(Doesn't he get motion sickness?)
Shall we do a scene from "Titanic"?
- I'll do it. - I will.
- I will. - My nickname was Kate Winslet.
Hold on. Let's go based on the hierarchy.
Why do you keep saying that?
What hierarchy?
What are you talking about?
Who will play...
- Leonardo DiCaprio? - I'll play Kate Winslet.
Let's reenact a scene from "Titanic".
- That sounds good. - We need some good photos.
- We're here after all. - You're right.
You're always right.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(This is tiring.)
This looks nice.
"Titanic" is such an old movie.
I know.
It was Jong Kook's idea.
Old people always want...
to reenact the scene on a boat.
- Let's try it. - Sure thing.
I'll play Kate Winslet.
(Leave it up to me.)
- Kwang Soo is... - How about here?
- very sly. - Shall we stand here?
Shall we stand here?
(Everything is ready for the scene from "Titanic".)
Go up.
Don't be afraid. In 3, 2, 1.
- I'll hold you. - Go.
(Kwang Soo plays Korea's Kate Winslet.)
(It looks as good as the original movie.)
I can't do it.
(He gives up easily.)
- I'm giving up. - You're giving up?
Come on. One.
I'll hold you.
Here you go. In 3, 2, 1.
(Will Kwang Soo make it?)
He's crawling up.
I can't do it.
(I'll go to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
Spread out your arms.
Spread them.
(Just reenact the scene.)
Your arms.
(Screaming)
- It's all because of you. - Exactly.
- Hey, you should stand up. - Kwang Soo.
I am not joking when I say this.
(Haha finds this too funny.)
I think he's such a coward.
- Let me try. - Okay. Haha, you try it.
In 1, 2, 3. Great!
I am the king of the world.
(This makes me the second in command now.)
(Scaredy-cat Haha succeeds in acting the part.)
All right. I am ready. Let me try.
(Now I am 3rd in command.)
(With the perfect posture, Se Chan succeeds.)
- Nice! - Okay.
What was it? Captain, sound the horn.
(He sounds a fanfare for the success.)
Okay, you did it.
- Only Kwang Soo failed. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo failed. - He failed.
(This determines his rank as the 4th in the group.)
- Hey, Kwang Soo failed. - Great!
(Gosh, this is driving me crazy.)
Do you want to try it again?
- I'll try it again. - We'll hold you. Why can't you try?
- Let me try again. - All right.
(Kwang Soo tries to act the scene once again.)
We are going to hold you.
(They get ready to expose his bottoms.)
Jong Kook.
- Do it now. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Get on the banister. - Step on the banister.
(I won't fail for the third time.)
I'm sending you to Japan. Book your flight ticket now.
(It's a love story between a man...)
(trying to send Kwang Soo to Japan and a man trying not to leave.)
(This is a miraculous drama that Kwang Soo will show.)
Stand up.
- Stand up. You'll be fine. - Stand up.
- Stand up, Kwang Soo. - Get up.
- Stand up. Use your leg muscles. - Stand up.
- Use your leg strength. - In 1, 2...
Use your leg strength.
- In 2, 3. - Go!
(Comedians from Korea are funny.)
I can't do this. I can't!
- You can't do this? - I can't do this.
- He can't do this. - This is for the show.
Hey, come on.
What are we going to do?
- All right. - We succeeded though!
- Kwang Soo failed. - You are ranked first for the trip.
(Kwang Soo is about to embark on a trip.)
(Will Kwang Soo have a chance to turn the tables around?)
(Team Mongolia must meet nomads and milk the sheep.)
(Team Russia must catch king crabs and 10 different types of seafood.)
(If they fail, a trip to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear will be decided.)
(2 members whom the team leaders choose will be exempted.)
I told you to stop!
(This is their last chance. Who will be able to survive?)
Our food must be ready.
- It's coming. - It's coming.
(Team Ji Hyo is waiting for their mysterious dishes.)
(If they finish eating them, the staff will pay half of the bill.)
I have a bad feeling about this.
(If they don't finish, they will pay for the whole bill.)
The first dish will be served.
Which number is it?
(What is their first menu of their first dinner in Mongolia?)
- This is... - Which number is it?
This is a bowl of lamb noodles.
- Here they are. - What is this one?
This looks interesting.
- We... - There's no barbecue dish.
There isn't one?
- We ordered a lot of soup. - We ordered flower buns. Great.
- This is driving me crazy. - All of our dishes are brought out.
(What did each member order?)
- All right. - There are only three dishes.
- Who ordered number one? - I did.
Ji Hyo, you ordered number one.
(Number 1 of the menu that Ji Hyo ordered is...)
- You ordered flower buns. - Yes! I ordered flower buns!
- Number five Seok Jin ordered... - Yes.
(Number 5 of the menu that Seok Jin ordered is...)
You ordered fish soup.
This is it.
(Fish soup sounds a bit strange.)
I don't like soup.
(Mongolian spices and oil from the fish are mixed in the soup.)
- And... - Yes?
- The lamb noodles... - Yes.
(The lamb noodles hold the key now.)
Which number was this?
(Please don't let it be mine.)
(To be honest, I don't think I can eat the lamb noodles.)
- The lamb noodles. - Which number is it?
It's number six.
That's yours.
(You picked it, Jae Seok.)
Number four on the menu which So Min ordered is water.
Sorry?
I ordered water?
- This is the lamb noodles? - Yes, it is.
- I have the fish soup. - I have water.
I'll be better off with water.
- That's what you two ordered. - Is this fish or sujebi?
- Let me taste it. - It's not nurungji.
(Ji Hyo who's the judge of local food, tastes it.)
Try it.
- Seok Jin, it's tasty. - Is it?
This tastes amazing.
This is really flavorful.
- It's delicious. - It really is.
- This tastes like fish jjigae. - I agree.
- This doesn't taste fishy at all. - It tastes like dried pollack soup.
- This does taste like that soup. - I got it.
- This tastes good too. - Seok Jin, you'll like this.
- This is tasty. - This is your sort of food.
Can we get more plates?
- Can I try? - You can try that, Seok Jin.
(He tastes Jae Seok's dish too.)
Gosh, I don't like this.
You don't like it?
This one has a lot of lamb meat though.
He told us that he really likes lamb.
That's right.
- This tastes like lamb. - Well...
I don't like dishes that has a strong smell of lamb meat.
- You don't like the smell, right? - Right.
I miss the burger we had.
A burger would taste so good.
I really miss it.
By the way...
(He lets out a sigh.)
- This... - They gave us a big portion.
This makes me miss home.
(This makes me miss home.)
(Honey, I won't complain about the side dishes now.)
(We recommend this for husbands who complain about food.)
- People here might enjoy this. - I am not joking.
- I'd eat steamed lamb meat, - As I told you before...
- but I don't eat lamb soup though. - This has a strong flavor of lamb.
- The smell... - The smell is really strong.
By the way, we have to finish eating everything here?
What are we going to do?
- I didn't eat a lot. - This feels like a waste.
(Paying for everything feels like a waste of our money.)
- Kwon Ryeol likes food. - You should try some.
But you didn't give me a bite of the burger.
(He was waiting for this moment.)
(Two hours ago)
The staff members should try some.
What should we do?
(You weren't going to share yours with us?)
How can you say that while you eat this?
- But you are giving me this. - Hey, you should try it though.
- But still. - Right.
You ought to try different cuisines of the world.
- Have some to taste the dish. - The broth is really rich too.
- Try the soup. - It's not that bad.
- Taste it. - The soup is really rich.
How is it?
(He nods his head.)
Do you like it?
This tastes like the rich version of ox bone soup.
- Really? - Do you mean it?
- Since he likes it, give it to him. - Let him finish everything.
Do you want to go and have the burger before the restaurant closes?
(Poor Kwon Ryeol. I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.)
- How do we say, "thank you"? - Thank you.
- That was "thank you". - No, it wasn't.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(It's time for them to sleep, but where will they sleep?)
(The street welcomes the members.)
Hey, this looks like...
- Tomorrow morning... - This looks great.
Now we are in Mongolia for certain.
This is a department store.
This is nice.
- We have to look for lodgings. - That's right.
- Where can we find hotels? - Where are the hotels?
Where can we find hotels?
We have to find the hotels.
(While middle-aged men are lost..)
What are you searching online?
Hotels. She's looking up hotels online.
- Online? - Yes.
We are looking for a hotel nearby using the map.
Gosh, this is it. I found one.
This is where we are now.
- If we go farther, there's a hotel. - Let's go then.
We have to go this way?
- It says to go straight for 500m. - This way?
I want some soup.
- What? - I want to have some soup.
- Don't you? - I do.
- We should have some ramyeon. - We ought to.
We will look so bloated tomorrow morning.
What is this? Isn't this a hotel?
- There is one. - This is a hotel.
- Let me go and ask the rate. - I hope it's cheap and reasonable.
- Should I go with him? - All of us shouldn't go in.
So Min, come here. Don't make things harder than they are.
Yes.
(Darn it.)
- Hey. - What?
- For a room, it's 200 dollars. - What?
If we book two rooms, it will be about 440 dollars.
- We can't stay here. - Could we lower the rate?
If we join their membership, they will give us a 20 percent discount.
What are you talking about?
(Seok Jin is quite well-informed.)
If we join...
- Or we can... - When will we milk the sheep?
It's been a while since we arrived.
- We don't even have a hotel. - Exactly.
- We haven't done... - We might end up on the street.
Let's go to another hotel.
- Let's go. - To another hotel.
- Let's keep going up. - Jae Seok...
It's so expensive.
That one looks expensive too.
There aren't that many people on the street here now.
That hotel is big too.
- Besides, - Even Mongolian locals went home.
I'm getting tired now.
- There's a hotel. - Where?
That one. Doesn't it say, "Premium Hotel"?
(They find a hotel after walking for 20 minutes.)
- Where is it? - There. It's across the street.
The rate might be reasonable, right?
- Let's go in. - Let's go inside.
- I'll go talk to them. - Make it happen.
I will come back with good news.
- Okay. - You can do it!
(Seok Jin is playing an active role today as a negotiator.)
- Two rooms? - Are there two vacant rooms?
What is the rate for one room per night?
For one room, the rate is 100 dollars per night.
- 100 dollars? - Yes.
Could you give me a discount?
- Discount? - Yes, please.
We are like brothers.
How much will it be for two rooms?
(Will Seok Jin be able to bargain for the rooms?)
(Nervous)
When we landed at the airport in Mongolia...
(We had a great start.)
I had a good feeling about the trip.
At night, I feel a bit lonely.
- I'm lonely too. - I don't know where we are.
Hey!
Let's go in. This hotel is nice.
- How much is it? - How much?
With the discount, for two rooms,
- How much was it? - it's 160 dollars.
- That's really reasonable. - For 2 rooms, it's 160 dollars.
- Gosh, it's cheap. - That's a good price.
Breakfast, wireless internet, and taxes are included in the price.
- They provide breakfast too? - Yes.
- Seok Jin, this is great. - I think...
Let's go in. This is nice.
- This looks clean. - Exactly. It looks nice.
This hotel is nice.
- Goodness. - This is great.
- This room is excellent. - It is indeed.
This is a good room given it cost us 90 dollars.
- This only cost us 90 dollars? - Yes.
This is amazing.
- This is so nice. - This is really good.
This is nice, but Ji Hyo, I found something interesting.
- The bed is really high. - You're right. Isn't that too high?
Why is it so high?
I have to jump to get on the bed.
If we fall, we might get injured.
If Haha were here, he probably had to jump high.
Shall we eat now?
Do you want to eat now?
- Shall we eat now? - What did you bring?
Let me show you.
(So Min opens her enormous luggage.)
- There are cup noodles. - That looks delicious.
I am going to eat jjajangmyeon.
There is more.
You are incredible.
She brought a parka.
She might need a parka...
- when the weather turns cold. - I can't believe you.
- Are you climbing Annapurna Massif? - That's hilarious.
So Min, don't you think this is too much?
I thought it might be cold.
So Min.
This is too much.
I didn't know it would be so warm in Mongolia.
- Why did they scare us so much? - I thought it might be cold.
- Okay. I will wash up first. - Go ahead.
How refreshing.
(It's bedtime for the friends of 20 years.)
- Did you finish washing up? - Of course.
Look at this bed.
(The high bed makes Jae Seok feel playful.)
I have to climb into the bed.
Why do I need to hike up here?
I will die if I fall off.
It's very high. You can't climb into it easily.
(I am Yu Jae Seok, the healthy man.)
(Jumping)
- You should jump in one go. - Try it.
(I will show you.)
(Bumping)
(He embarrasses himself.)
The mattress got pushed back.
Give up.
(This man in his 50s has a pajama party.)
(He can't control his good cheer.)
For goodness' sake. This bed is weak.
(The two comedians film an action movie at night.)
It's over there.
(The two elegant actresses...)
(are cleaning up the room for a good night's sleep.)
My goodness.
Are you okay?
- My goodness. - It hurts so much.
Ji Hyo, I didn't crack my skull, did I?
Your head made such a clear sound.
(They burst out laughing.)
- My goodness. - That was hilarious.
Your head made a loud sound.
It was loud, right?
It was a very clear sound.
So Min is hilarious.
(So Min is so cute.)
- Let's go to bed, So Min. - Goodnight.
If you are hot, remove the duvet. If you are cold,
you can wear these socks.
Goodnight.
(So Min puts on a sheet mask in the dark not to disturb Ji Hyo.)
(Ji Hyo lights the room with her cell phone for So Min.)
(So Min, you are...)
You are very bright.
You are optimistic.
I am very pessimistic.
My goodness.
(They have a conversation in the time of their own.)
(It's not a night of 2 actresses, but 2 sisters.)
I am experiencing...
a new kind of work in a new kind of environment.
It's something I haven't tried before.
That's right.
(The youngest member reveal her heart to Ji Hyo.)
Come here.
(The night that is filled with fatigue and laughter deepens.)
(The day of the mission rises.)
(They must meet a Borjigit today.)
In this nice weather, you will leave to find the nomads.
Here is the important thing.
When you go to your friend's house...
for the first time, you bring a gift.
- There is a traditional market. - A traditional market sounds fun.
A traditional market sounds fun.
Let's hit the road.
- We must complete the mission. - A traditional market sounds fun.
- Let's go. - The sunlight is strong.
(They hurry up and leave for the market.)
It's that way.
- It's so big. - Where is the entrance?
(They arrive at Naran Tuul Market.)
It's the traditional market of Mongolia.
It's similar to the one in Korea.
- It really is. - Right?
- There are fruits. - They use the same parasols.
Seok Jin, it will take too long...
if we move in one group. Let's split up...
- into groups of two. - That's a good idea.
It hurts my feelings that you want to split up.
- Give me some money. - Let's buy two beverages.
The aftertaste is that of jujube.
I stepped on gum.
(I stepped on gum.)
- Gum? - My goodness.
- She requires a lot of care. - She requires a lot of care.
(The gum stretches.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
I was surprised when I felt a tug on my foot.
Thank goodness you didn't step on poop.
(A few hours later)
(Ji Hyo's team steps on poop.)
(What will become of their journey to find a Borjigit?)
- My goodness. - Let's go.
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
- I will see you later. - See you later.
I can't believe I am stuck with Seok Jin.
- Come here. - What should we do?
They are nomads...
who live on the grassland.
We should buy something that is useful for the nomads.
- An umbrella would be nice. - That would be cute.
Toys. I heard industrial products are valuable here.
Let's keep going. Doesn't it feel like...
- a five-day market in Korea? - You are right.
It's the same as the market in Korea.
- There are a lot of hats. - There are a lot of hats.
- This is fun, So Min. - Look at the towels.
Aren't they cute?
What?
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
(They find Kwang Soo in Mongolia.)
(Kwang Soo in Mongolia)
Kwang Soo, you shouldn't be here. You should go and catch king crab.
The mannequin has big eyes.
(Worry about your own mission. I am doing well.)
- Kwang Soo is here. - He is in Mongolia.
Shall we take a picture with it?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Shouldn't you go and catch king crab?)
This must be the traditional costume.
It's probably expensive, right?
- It looks expensive. - It's pretty.
It's very pretty.
The fabric is thick. Wait, it's not that thick.
It's pretty.
Which one do you like? You will look cute in this one.
- It's pretty. - Pick the one with two colors.
You should try on the blue one or this one.
(Ji Hyo holds the bag for So Min.)
- Thank you. - It's pretty on the inside too.
(So Min tries it on.)
It's cool.
(The familiar sight makes her sing the background music.)
Chun-Li.
You look cute.
(Wearing deel makes her look like Chun-Li from Mongolia.)
How cute! You should buy it.
How much is this?
It's 95,000 tughrik.
That means it's about 40 dollars.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin will scold us...
- if we buy these, right? - They will say we wasted money.
(While they are 100 percent sure they will get scolded,)
(Ji Hyo tries on deel since it's pretty.)
Why do I look like a man?
Don't I look like a man?
(She looks like a mischievous boy who kicks a ball on the grassland.)
(The fashion nomads, Ji Hyo and So Min, are here.)
(The gallant man and the cute Chun-Li)
(Instead of milking sheep, they try on clothes.)
(The immature Ji Hyo and So Min have a fashion show.)
(They cost 95 dollars in total.)
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin will scold us if we buy these, right?)
Jae Seok and Seok Jin will scold us if we buy these, right?
- I look good in these sunglasses. - I look amazing in them.
Don't they look good on me?
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin are even more immature.)
(They have been spending 30 minutes on sunglasses.)
- Don't they look good on me? - They look good on me.
(Is he the Mongolian version of Son Ji Chang?)
You should buy them.
(They are perfect for your face.)
They are perfect.
- People are laughing at me. - You should buy them.
Even the owner laughed at me. Do you think I should buy them?
(They are perfect for you.)
Look at this. These sunglasses go up when I smile.
(Going up)
(His facial muscles are an elevator.)
(That customer is funny too.)
(The owner bursts out laughing for the 2nd time.)
You came here to buy presents for the nomads.
- You are right. - We can give them sunglasses.
- We can give them sunglasses. - We can give them sunglasses.
Please ask her if the nomads wear sunglasses.
The nomads wear sunglasses. They wear them often.
- Do they wear them often? - Of course they do.
We will buy a pair of sunglasses.
Let's buy a pair of sunglasses.
(After a fashion show, they buy a pair of sunglasses as a present.)
This is a market too.
- This is a market too. - Yes.
We will find more products here.
- I smell cheese. - I smell cheese.
- I smell cheese. - There is cheese.
I think they sell meat too.
(There are dairy products from sheep and cows.)
What is this?
- What is this? - It's aaruul.
- What is it? - It's hard yogurt you can chew on.
(Aaruul is dried dairy product from the nomads.)
- May I try one? - How much is it for one?
(They take a bite.)
(My goodness, it's the taste...)
(of the grassland.)
(Wait a minute.)
(This is...)
This is a bit...
(It's too different for us.)
- Aaruul is... - It's not for us.
(After their shocking encounter with aaruul,)
(they see it again as a welcome food from the nomads.)
(Will they eat aaruul from the Borjigit?)
(It's a snack shop.)
- Hello. - Hello.
These are very pretty.
Look at this.
Ma'am, please give us 2kg.
Candies and these.
These look like toys. Kids must love them.
Let's take some of those too.
We'll have 2kg of the candies and these.
They look tasty.
Excuse me.
Is your last name Borjigit.
Is your last name Borjigit?
(She could have a nomad relative if she's Borjigit.)
(But she has a different last name.)
Is there anyone with the last name, Borjigit, around here?
I'm not sure about it.
(People with that last name are hard to find even in the city.)
We have to find a nomad whose last name is Borjigit.
(Will they be able to find them?)
- We bought a lot. - Where are the kids?
I wish we could meet them.
We should. Let's go that way.
(Where are the two female members?)
(Laughing)
The sisters are so cute.
The price was reasonable, right?
Right.
We won't get burnt now.
Right?
I guess I'll take off my T-shirt and wear this.
(Linking arms)
Getting out of hands.
Let's go. It's Jae Seok.
(They find Seok Jin and Jae Seok walking ahead of them.)
(They walk on without knowing.)
- Careful. - Gosh.
Let's surprise them from behind.
(They're immersed in window shopping.)
- My gosh! - Goodness!
(It's so fun to startle the middle-aged men.)
- You startled me. - You startled me. Gosh.
- You startled me. - Did you buy those clothes?
- Yes. - It's matching clothes.
We bought some gifts.
We bought candies for them.
- Great. You guys bought snacks... - These too.
and we bought daily items.
- Right. - That's great.
Let's head out then.
- Okay. - Good.
(They finish buying gifts for the nomads.)
There are restaurants 20 minutes away from here.
- Let's go. - Let's head there.
I'm hungry.
- I'm spotting food now. - I see restaurants.
- Great. - I see restaurants now.
Let's pick one and go in.
- There are lamb drawings. - "Mongolian food"?
Yes.
(They run into a stranger with the traditional clothes on.)
- Excuse me. - Borjigit?
- Right. - Please ask him.
What is your last name?
It's Khalkha.
Where can we meet Borjigit people?
We're looking for a nomad whose last name is Borjigit.
Where should we go?
There aren't many with that last name. You need to search carefully.
(Will this stranger be their savior?)
What?
(20 percent of Mongolians are Borjigit, but there seems to be 0.)
(If they fail to find one, they won't get to complete the mission.)
(Everyone said it's hard, but they won't give up.)
(They only have half a day left. How will the things turn out?)
What is that?
- Is this a restaurant? - What is this?
- What is this? - A restaurant?
- It must be a restaurant. - It is.
- It says "gimbap". - It's a Korean restaurant.
- What is that? - They sell Korean food.
"Jeyuk bokkeum, gimbap".
(They find a menu written in Korean.)
- They also serve Mongolian food. - They sell both.
- Shall we go in here? - They serve both kinds.
Let's go in and order what each of us want...
since they serve both kinds.
Let's go in.
(They enter the fusion Mongolian restaurant.)
- Two orders of kimchi jjigae. - Jeyuk bokkeum too.
- Are you having jeyuk bokkeum? - Okay.
We must remember that we're not here for travel.
I need to get to work.
- Work on what? - You know,
Chan Hyuk is from Mongolia.
He once lived in Mongolia.
(Maybe he has a Borjigit friend?)
Akdong Musician.
(Akdong Musician is the acoustic duo from Mongolia.)
We've been living in Mongolia for two years with our parents.
I didn't know what would happen, so I got his number beforehand.
- I see. - That's a great idea.
That's amazing.
I've never tried calling him before though.
I see.
He might not answer it then.
(Their last hope is Chan Hyuk.)
(Chan Hyuk, do you know Borjigit by any chance?)
- Hello? - Chan Hyuk!
Who is this?
(Hi, I'm the national host, Yu Jae Seok.)
It's Jae Seok. Hello?
- Hey. - Hello.
Were you surprised? Chan Hyuk.
- He's not even close to him. - I visited Mongolia.
- Oh, because of Running Man? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Did you live in Ulaanbaatar by any chance?
Yes, I did.
For how many years?
I lived in there for about five years.
- Good. - He would know then.
- It's interesting. - What were you doing?
Why would you ask that?
We have to find a nomad whose last name is Borjigit.
- What? - Borjigit.
Borjigit?
(He lived in Mongolia for 5 years.)
(At least one of his friends in Mongolia must be Borjigit.)
I've never heard of that name before.
- Oh, no. - That's not good.
You should've lived here longer, Chan Hyuk.
Well...
Ask him another place other than Terelj to meet nomads.
Is Terelj the closest place?
That's the most famous place.
Then we should go there.
- Yes. - Let's go there.
- Thank you. - Thanks, Chan Hyuk.
Thank you.
(Thanks for taking Jae Seok's call when you're not even close to him.)
I guess there aren't that many people with that name.
(They won't be able to milk sheep at this rate.)
I know.
Don't you think the distance between the houses will be very far?
- Right. - It's vast after all.
If we couldn't find them in one house,
we would have to take a long time...
- to arrive at another house. - She's right.
I think we should rent horses.
(I think we should rent horses.)
(Do they rent out horses in Mongolia?)
- Can you? - Sure.
They'll rent out ponies probably.
(No, they're big horses. Cowards won't be able to ride on them.)
- They're ponies. - Let's do that.
(Whatever the case, they must head to the wilderness.)
Let's do that.
Let's eat first and move on.
- Goodness. - Great.
(Their soul food is served to relieve their anxiety.)
- Thank you. - It smells so good.
Can we have a bowl of rice?
(It reminds you of your mother's cooking.)
It's great.
My stomach feels much better with this.
- Does it? - Yes.
(They need to have spicy food even when they're outside of Korea.)
Mongolian dishes will be served soon, right?
(Mongolian dishes will be served soon, right?)
(Laughing)
- Well... - What?
Why do you keep glancing at the staff?
(Did you notice it?)
- My goodness. - Seok Jin did?
- I didn't. - Well...
One of the staff said this a moment ago.
"It's good to have Korean food, but since we're in Mongolia,"
"let's film your enjoying Mongolian food."
But he again mentioned not to mind what he said.
So Seok Jin has been glancing at that staff.
(Seok Jin felt uncomfortable ever since then.)
He really missed Korean food,
but he pretended to like Mongolian food.
(He couldn't express how he really felt.)
(Mongolian food?)
(He shouted for Mongolian food and tried to avoid Korean restaurants.)
(At last, he chose the restaurant where he can have Korean food too.)
He went, "Yes, Mongolian food."
- And he... - I felt uncomfortable.
whispered...
that he craved kimchi jjigae.
(Seek Jin's honest opinion.)
But on the outside...
I wish I could taste another Mongolian food.
It's good to see you work hard.
Sure.
(It's good to see him work hard.)
(Now that they're done eating, let's go to the wilderness!)
- Let's go! - Go, go.
Now, we're heading to milk sheep.
I don't think I can milk sheep though.
1L is quite a bit.
Are you sure you're worried? I think you're sleepy instead.
Still, I have to participate in the filming.
I can't just sleep right away.
I heard it's at least a 2-hour trip to the wilderness.
It takes at least 2 hours from here.
There won't be any restrooms either.
It feels like we're going far away.
- We're going far away. - Look at the sky.
- It's pretty. - Right.
It's starting to feel real that we're in Mongolia.
- Mongolia. - Look, it's yurt.
Yurt!
Don't they look like marshmallows?
(They spot yurts which are the symbol of Mongolia.)
We're escaping from the stuffy city.
(Taking pictures is a must...)
(when witnessing an amazing landscape like this.)
(Taking photos)
- What's that? - It's a statue of Genghis Khan.
It's so cool.
(The huge statue of Genghis Khan is looking over the vast meadows.)
(Taking pictures)
I love it here.
(I love Mongolia.)
It's so extensive.
There are many houses at the foot of the mountain over there.
- That mountain looks amazing. - It's so cool.
- The mountains have no trees. - No.
- It's covered with grass. - It's interesting.
They're bald.
Why are the mountains covered with grass?
- Didn't I just say that? - You did.
You never know which part the producer will use.
(He cares about the producer.)
We should say it a few times so he can choose the best one.
(It's for the producer's sake.)
Oh, there are cows.
I see milk cows.
(They finally find milk-producing animals.)
They must be happy.
- The cows here look so happy. - This is nice.
They can just graze anywhere.
There's so much grass.
We're in trouble.
I haven't seen any sheep on the way yet.
- Really? - Yes.
I only see cows.
We have to find sheep, and the owner has to be a Borjigit.
This is hard.
They're sheep! Are they cows?
- They're sheep! - They're sheep!
- Are they goats? - Are they goats?
Are they goats or sheep?
- They're goats. - They're goats.
- They have beards. - Are they goats?
I got so excited.
- I thought they were sheep. - There are no sheep.
How can there be no sheep in these vast meadows?
(Will we be able to even start the mission?)
(Team Mongolia's mission is meeting nomads and milking the sheep.)
(Team Russia's mission is catching king crabs and 10 kinds of fish.)
(If they fail, they'll be sent to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(The team leaders can exclude two members from the trip.)
Stop it!
(The last chance: Who will survive?)
We have to show them.
We can't lose to Team Mongolia!
- You're right! - You're right!
They're just old men!
- You're right. - You're right.
We should win. We should show them the power of youth!
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
We know only one word.
- Success! - Success!
- What? - Success!
It's success. Show them.
- Success. - Success.
We each need to catch three kinds.
- Good. - 2 or 3.
Jong Kook, you can catch just 1. We'll catch 3 each.
Don't tell me what to do.
(I'm the team leader.)
- Are you crazy? - It's my choice.
- What's with you? - I decide what I do.
You have to catch fish.
I just need to enjoy.
- You're right. - I'm happy.
- You're absolutely right. - Right?
As soon as we arrive,
let's get to work.
- Okay. - Good.
- Is this "Real Men"? - Exactly.
I don't know anymore.
At first, I thought it was just role-play.
But we've been doing it all day.
- I know. - I'm confused.
It's not role-play.
- Applause. - Applause.
(They begin the operation with an applause.)
(Fix a herring on the hook.)
I don't have a fishing rod.
(Lower the hook to the bottom of the sea.)
(Wait 20 to 30 minutes without moving the fishing rod.)
Do we just wait?
(It's important to reel in the line at the right time.)
It's on the bottom?
The crab approaches and...
(Near the coast, they use a traditional method.)
(If you're lucky, you can even catch many king crabs.)
Does it catch just one?
(Will Team Jong Kook succeed in catching Russian king crabs?)
Try it.
(While waiting for king crabs, they try catching 10 kinds of fish.)
Our leader.
(Jong Kook demonstrates.)
He's not even affected by the result. Why is he doing that?
Should we start a riot?
Kwang Soo, don't betray us.
I want to...
push him into the sea.
I want to kick him into the sea.
I want to kick him.
Sir, I think these guys will kick you into the sea.
Be careful.
(Jong Kook, watch out for these betrayers.)
What are you doing?
Kwang Soo and Se Chan were talking about it.
(Do you like experiencing horrors?)
Hey.
- Is this how you're going to do it? - I'm just playing.
Here are fishing rods.
(With additional fishing rods, they'll start the mission.)
Let's do this according to the hierarchy.
Since when do we have a rank?
- What is this? - You use your hands.
(Jong Kook is fishing relaxingly.)
Okay.
(Tense)
I feel something.
(Already?)
(Everyone's stirred up.)
Do you feel something?
Maybe not.
- Yes. - Yes?
(It's there.)
- Did you catch something? - I think so.
(Excited)
Wait.
(He reels in the line carefully.)
I've never seen this before.
It's heavy.
(He's battling with the fish.)
You must have caught something.
- You caught something. - You caught something.
Are you sure?
(What will be on the hook?)
What is it?
(He catches a fish.)
(He catches a big one as soon as he starts.)
It's a flatfish.
(Flatfish)
- It's cute. - You caught one.
Can you remove the hook? You're so brave.
(Se Chan skillfully removes the hook.)
There you go!
(They catch 1 out of 10 kinds of fish.)
There you go. I caught one.
- I caught one! - What did you catch?
- What is it? - I told you!
What is it?
What happened?
What is that?
- It's a pollack. - It's a pollack.
It's a pollack!
You can really catch them.
I felt it.
- We caught a pollack! - Haha caught it!
This is amazing.
- I feel so happy. - Take a picture.
You caught it.
1, 2, 3.
(Monthly Running Man)
- Okay! It feels good. - Did you catch one?
Really? The rod is bending.
It's a pollack!
Okay!
It's huge.
There are so many pollacks. Kwang Soo, remove the hook.
- Me? - Don't slack off.
(You can't even touch a fish.)
You do the chores.
Hold the fish with your hands.
- Hold it there. - Wait.
Hold it with your hands.
Wait.
Remove it.
Stronger. There you go.
Put it in the bucket.
Don't squeeze it.
There you go.
Be careful.
(After doing so many chores...)
I want to catch one too.
Give me a fishing rod.
Catch one.
(I'll catch a big one.)
(Hasty)
(Busy)
(What is he doing?)
It ran away.
Here we go.
(Kwang Soo approaches Haha.)
Our lines might get tangled. Go away.
Haha. How can you say that?
I'm doing great here.
(Don't cause me any trouble.)
I caught one!
- Again? - Again?
Se Chan.
This is big.
It's coming up!
- It's a flatfish! - It is!
Good!
Great. Kwang Soo, hurry and remove the hook.
Wait, I'm stuck.
My arm. Get me off.
Gosh, you're such a handful.
- What should we do? It's torn. - It's torn.
Wear gloves.
What is this?
(He's such a high-maintenance member.)
- I think it's a pollack. - Is it a pollack?
(Everyone's doing great except Kwang Soo.)
- A pollack! - Yes!
It's a pollack!
Did you catch another one? Again? What is it?
- It's the biggest so far. - What did you catch?
Is it a pollack again?
Gosh.
Today's champion. I caught two at once.
2 birds with 1 stone.
Call me Pollack from now on.
I'm the best pollack catcher.
Lower it to the bottom.
If you stay still, it'll start to move.
Then raise the rod and reel in the line.
It'll start to move. Keep it on the bottom.
Did you catch one?
- What do I do now? - Reel in the line.
No. Reel in the line.
No. There you go.
- Did you catch something? - I caught something!
- Kwang Soo caught something! - Look at this!
(Finally, Kwang Soo also catches a fish.)
Kwang Soo finally caught one.
- I caught something. - Kwang Soo.
I definitely caught something.
I think I caught a shark! It feels like a dolphin!
Here it comes.
(He caught something heavy.)
(What type of seafood did he catch?)
Here it comes.
Gosh, Kwang Soo. Pull it up.
- What's that? - What is it?
- Did I catch something? - Pull it up.
(What is it?)
What did I catch?
(What's this?)
This is amazing.
What happened?
How did I catch this?
Did you catch this?
(What is your name?)
I caught a starfish.
- He caught a starfish. - I caught a starfish.
- It's a starfish. - He caught a starfish.
I caught a large starfish.
He knows how to entertain.
I caught a starfish!
(He catches a rare starfish.)
- I'm embarrassed of myself. - I felt something heavy.
(They have caught 3 kinds in total.)
I caught a mysterious being.
(Kwang Soo is impressive.)
(Currently, they caught three types of seafood.)
(Team Ji Hyo looks for sheep.)
There aren't many houses.
We're traveling off-road.
- Okay. - Goodness.
(They approach off-road to find sheep.)
(At that moment,)
(something catches their attention.)
Unbelievable.
This is incredible.
Mongolia is...
- amazing. - It's incredible.
(They arrive at...)
(the plain in Terelj.)
It's so peaceful here.
I've never seen it.
It's a peaceful place.
This is amazing.
(Mongolia is impressive.)
- It's impressive. - On a horse, Genghis Khan...
- Right. - conquered the world.
(The spirit of Genghis Khan remains.)
- Is that a hawk? - Isn't that an eagle?
Is it an eagle?
It's a large bird.
(They even see a hawk.)
- It's so beautiful here. - It's right in front of us.
There's absolutely nothing here.
I know.
You won't bump into anything even if...
- you drive with your eyes closed. - Exactly.
I've never seen such a wide plain.
(They keep driving without an end.)
- How is this possible? - I know.
The plain never ends.
Where are the sheep?
I bet we could find a flock of sheep here.
- We have to find Borjigit. - That would be great.
- We must find a Borjigit first. - We need to find them.
Borjigit has to be the owner.
Borjigit.
It's so wide here.
How can we find a Borjigit?
Can we find a descendant of Genghis Khan in such a big place?
(Where could a Borjigit be?)
- It's so far away. - It really is.
(The off-trip starts to become difficult.)
- What if we think... - I found sheep.
- I found sheep. - There they are.
- That must be it. - They're sheep.
There they are.
There are so many.
That must be 100 sheep.
That must be the place.
(They finally find Mongolian sheep.)
Are those wild dogs?
- Where are the dogs? - No.
- They're running ahead. - Goodness.
They're very aggressive dogs.
I know. They seem aggressive.
They're Mongolian dogs.
(It finally feels like Mongolia.)
Is this the place?
It must be it.
(A flock of sheep in the mountains)
(They arrive at a nomad village.)
- Gosh. - The wind.
- We traveled very far. - It was far.
It's very windy here.
By the way,
- It was so far. - if we can't find Borjigit here...
There is no other village here.
There are a few cautions to take related to customs.
Perhaps you saw them already.
- Did you see the dogs? - Yes.
They were very aggressive.
The dogs here are very aggressive.
- I know. - Right.
This is how the nomads say hello.
It means, "catch the dogs."
(Hello means, "catch the dogs.")
I thought these were rocks.
- They're goat poop. - They are.
- Are they poop? - Yes.
- That's interesting. - It's goat poop.
- Stop it, So Min. - Why are you touching it?
Why are you touching the poop?
People stir-fry goat poop and eat it.
- What? - You can't eat goat poop.
- Who eats stir-fried goat poop? - It's used as medicine.
It's good for constipation.
Who eats stir-fried goat poop?
You can look it up. It's true, everyone.
- You stir-fry goat poop? - It's good for constipation.
- You can't eat it stir-fried. - Do you want some?
Feces have been used as medicine.
However, they could be infected with virus or bacteria.
I recommend you not to consume them.
(It's confirmed by a professional.)
Don't step on it. So Min will eat it later.
We don't have time.
Let's say hello and ask people.
- They're riding motorcycles. - Let's ask if they're a Borjigit.
(They practice saying hello.)
(Due to the sound of their voice,)
(the Mongolian nomads come outside.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
(They meet the nomads for the first time.)
Hello, sir.
(Hello.)
(They finally meet Mongolian nomads.)
- Here's what's important. - In Mongolia...
These people have to be...
- from the Borjigit line. - Right.
- That's the most important. - They have to be Borjigit.
If they are, we're good.
- We just have to milk the sheep. - Then we can leave.
- Pardon me. - Shall we ask?
(Are you part of the Borjigit tribe?)
(Are you Mr. Borjigit?)
(They traveled for 3 hours.)
(Is he part of the Borjigit tribe?)
(Is he a descendant of Genghis Khan?)
- He's of a different tribe. - I see.
(He isn't a Borjigit.)
Is he part of a different tribe?
He isn't Borjigit.
Let's not be discouraged. There are other people.
- Are you a Borjigit? - Are you?
(Are you Mr. Borjigit?)
(Is the other man a descendant of Genghis Khan?)
(He shakes his head.)
Are you not?
- They're from the same tribe. - I see.
- I see. - Are you from Borjigit tribe?
(No, we're part of another tribe.)
- They aren't here. - Goodness.
(Is there no Borjigit around here?)
(He feels sorry.)
- What's this? - What is it?
It's Mongolian snuff that they offer to the guests.
- Snuff? - Snuff?
I read about it before.
Open the lid, sniff it, and turn it with your right hand.
(Offering snuff is a welcoming custom.)
- Don't close it. - Where do I put it to sniff it?
- Put it on the back of your hand. - I'll put it here.
(Rejecting the snuff is considered rude. Pass after sniffing lightly.)
(He's friendly.)
Do I sniff it?
- I've seen it in movies. - Sniff it.
- It seems like... - This is great.
(It's not made with tobacco leaves but with spices and herbs.)
(As such, it cleanses the nostrils.)
(It smells very good.)
Where is it?
(It's an unfamiliar fragrance.)
We should sniff it.
- The fragrance is... - Does it have a fragrance?
How shall I describe it?
I can't find it.
- I never smelled such fragrance. - I found it.
It's refreshing.
Haven't you seen it before?
That's not how you do it.
(That's not how you do it.)
(It's how it's done in movies.)
Goodness.
(He imitates people in movies.)
Don't do that.
- How do I do it? - Give it to me.
- It's interesting. - It's refreshing.
Take a little. Hold it first.
- Hold it tightly. - It's refreshing.
Block one nostril.
You don't have to do that.
It has a fragrance.
(What is this fragrance?)
- It has a pleasant fragrance. - It's pleasant.
(It's unfamiliar, but they like it.)
It's interesting.
Can we visit their home?
Is that okay?
(Welcome)
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you.)
These dogs are calm.
They're friendly.
(Welcome)
- May we go in? - May we go in?
(They enter a ger for the first time.)
It's warm inside.
It's really warm inside.
(It's nicely decorated.)
- This is amazing. - It's great.
It's very...
- cozy inside. - It's cozy.
This is for ventilation.
- Look at this. - What's this?
It's warm around here.
- They heat this up. - Right.
We have a gift for you.
(They give them gifts they bought at the market.)
(It's nice to meet you.)
Thank you.
- It must be a heater. - What is this?
- It's boorsoq. - Boorsoq?
(Boorsoq is fried dough.)
(It's one of the main snacks for the nomads.)
I've seen that on TV.
- Don't they also offer tea? - Right.
- They usually offer tea. - To offer tea?
- For guests, they serve tea. - Do they serve tea?
- They will give us tea? - Yes.
- They are already here. - By the way...
Look, the water is boiling.
It's so warm in here. I saw this on TV.
(She pours cow's milk into the boiling, hot water.)
I thought...
(She pours milk into the boiling, hot water.)
- This is cow's milk. - Cow's milk? I see.
- This is made of cow's milk? - Yes.
When I saw this on TV, I was really curious.
Jae Seok, I was curious about this too.
After that, this turns into a thick liquid.
It's really warm in here.
I think on a windy day, this must be so warm and cozy.
What is that?
There's a television.
Goodness, there's a TV here.
(Let me introduce his house.)
(His house has a solar plate...)
(and a satellite TV.)
He's slowly showing off his house.
He is.
(He pushes the buttons on the remote control.)
Look. He's using the remote control.
By the way, I'm quite curious.
- We have to find a Borjigit. - Borjigit tribe.
- Borjigit tribe. - Borjigit...
It's Borjigit.
(Steaming)
(The steam fills the room.)
It's overflowing.
- Gosh, it startled me. - The fire is so strong.
- It stopped. - This is...
- This... - What do we do?
- It's all right. - Okay.
Yes?
Goodness, this is what she said.
"You should have kept an eye on this."
"We have guests over now."
"All you do is sit and do nothing."
- That's probably what she said. - Come on.
(Goodness, you should have kept an eye on this.)
(We have guests over now.)
(All you do is sit and do nothing.)
- I can... - I don't think he's wrong though.
I can express feelings in this world.
- She is skimming it. - It looks delicious.
It smells savory.
(The nomads' favorite drink is about to be ready.)
This sort of...
It has a great smell.
That...
- What is she saying? - She will filter it with a net.
She said she will pour the tea, and we will drink that.
- Really? - Yes.
You are actually right.
- He's right? - Didn't I tell you?
I can translate feelings.
This is such a mystery.
- He's right on point. - I can translate feelings.
Seok Jin, I know everything.
Where do you get the water?
I see. There's a well here.
There's a well.
How do you know all this?
I know everything by the feelings.
- They get it from there. - You said there's a well.
You are completely right.
Thank you.
Since I am the leader...
No, you are not the leader. Thank you.
(They receive a cup each.)
It's milk tea.
(Milk tea)
I can smell the milk.
(They take a sip of the tea she prepared with the utmost care.)
Gosh, it's hot.
(A savory smell disperses inside their mouths.)
Can I put this in the tea?
(Let me see.)
- You can. - This is...
It's sugar?
Seok Jin, why don't you sit and drink the tea?
- I'm just putting the sugar in. - You can ask me to pass it to you.
- This isn't polite. - Why isn't it polite?
- Do you know about their manners? - Long time ago...
Do you want to get smacked here?
- If you did this a long time ago... - Please sit down.
(I see. I was impolite.)
- Just sit down. - I'll sit here and talk.
You might have been fed to the eagles a long time ago.
(She takes care of the staff as well.)
You probably were fed to the eagles.
No, that wasn't what I meant.
By the way,
we have to meet someone from the Borjigit tribe.
Are there anyone from that tribe?
- He shook his head. - What if no one is here?
(I don't think they are around here. Go to the other side to meet them.)
She said they are not around this area.
She said you can go to the other side.
No one from that tribe is here?
That's what she said.
Since we have a long way ahead of us,
we have to get going.
I know that drinking everything is an etiquette.
(That's all right.)
Has the etiquette changed? We don't have to finish it?
We don't have to finish the tea?
He told us to drink as much as we want, didn't he?
Then I will drink only this much.
(His skill doesn't even surprise us now.)
(His translation of feelings is 100 percent accurate.)
- Things have changed here too. - He is...
He translates...
- That's what he said. - using his hunches.
"Oh no, you don't have to finish if you don't want to nowadays."
- "Drink as much as you want." - You are amazing.
- You really are. - Aren't I?
(You don't have to finish if you don't want to nowadays.)
(Drink as much as you want.)
All right then. Anyway, thank you.
We should get going.
(Thank you for your invitation. You are too generous.)
- It's so warm in here. - Thank you.
Walk to the right side when you come out.
We just heard that too.
Don't pretend you knew about it beforehand.
(They must go to find the Borjigit tribe.)
- I have to pee though. - Me too.
Where can we pee?
- I think we have to pee over there. - I think so too.
- You have to climb over that hill. - I have to visit Mother Nature.
- Aren't people here generous? - They are.
Your translation skill surprised me again.
- You saw my skill, didn't you? - Goodness.
- It's over there. - You were awesome.
I can communicate with the whole world.
Jae Seok, you were so good at guessing through their reactions.
- Don't you worry, Ji Hyo. - You were guessing.
We will be back after we take care of our business.
(It's time to release before they start a long journey again.)
- I must go too. - I'll go with you.
- I'll go to the back. - Men and women are separate.
As long as there are no cameras, I can take care of it.
If there are no cameras, we can pee while facing the mountain.
- I'll keep a watch. - Are you going that way?
- Yes, we are going this way. - Then we will go this way.
(They are on their way to empty their stomachs.)
(Turning back)
(Are the cameramen still filming us?)
- Don't let the camera drone fly! - Where is that camera?
How can you let that camera fly at this time?
This is so funny.
(Will Team Ji Hyo be able to find a Borjigit?)
Hey, don't zoom in.
(Meanwhile, Team Jong Kook is still fighting with the king crabs.)
Again? Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(It's another flatfish again.)
I think it's another one.
(Oh, no. It's a flatfish again.)
Why do they keep biting our bait?
I wish we could catch a different type.
But it seems that's not happening for us.
(The sun is already setting.)
Okay. When we catch these fish now,
I don't feel excited.
(They keep catching the same kinds of fish.)
(What good is it if their bucket is full with fish?)
(What is that?)
Hey, scoop up the jellyfish!
- Where? - Hurry. It's getting away!
(It's swimming away.)
(He catches a glimpse of a creature that resembles a jellyfish.)
(This is a new species at last!)
- Where? - Hurry. It's getting away!
I need a scooping net. Where?
- Where is it? - It's heading towards that way.
(He equips himself with the scooping net.)
(It's time for Kwang Soo to catch one for the team.)
Se Chan, hold on.
(I will catch you soon. Wait for me.)
The jellyfish is here. Kwang Soo, it's right here.
It's right there. Hurry!
(He spots his target.)
(After he gets close to the target reaching out his long arm...)
- There you go. Nice job! - A jellyfish!
(He captures it instantly.)
- A jellyfish! - Nice job!
(What is the species of this creature?)
I got a jellyfish!
(They acquire the 4th species, salpa, which resembles a jellyfish.)
(Swinging)
Oh, he got 1. Did you catch 1?
(A fish bites Kwang Soo's bait that's been put out before.)
(It feels like it might be a king crab. Could it be?)
Did we catch one?
(Hurry)
(Faster)
- Did you catch it? - Yes.
- Did you catch it? - Yes, I did.
(This feels different from before.)
(Did he catch something?)
I caught a king crab! I got a king crab!
Really?
(Is this really happening? Did you really catch a king crab?)
King crab!
I got a king crab!
(After struggling with the tough sea of Russia,)
(did Kwang Soo catch a king crab that everyone has been waiting for?)
(Can Team Russia catch a king crab...)
(and accomplish their final mission?)
(Team Jong Kook continues to catch fish with this momentum.)
(These 3 underlings decide to revolt against the team leader.)
(Who will be the victor of this muddy fight for rankings?)
(Kwang Soo wins against the members by winning her heart.)
(A secret date with a pretty blonde in Vladivostok)
(I love you, Kwang Soo.)
(Meanwhile, Team Ji Hyo isn't distracted.)
(They milk the sheep with the Borjigit tribe.)
This is amazing.
(At last, the truth of this dangerous destination unfolds.)
(You'd better be careful...)
(because...)
(Dangerous Trip Finale: Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear)
(Recommend a destination of your choice! Members will visit.)