(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(Those with 3 I Go Stickers must travel with another member.)
(Haha and So Min were chosen to receive a penalty.)
(So Min's destination is...)
(Indonesia Manual Wooden Cable Car.)
(So Min's partner is Kwang Soo, the penalty maniac.)
(The day finally came.)
(Kwang Soo and So Min leave to receive the penalty.)
(Indonesia Tiger Moth Tour started.)
(The only money they got was the allowance from the members.)
(They had to pick envelopes that seem to contain a lot of money.)
(Kwang Soo picked Jong Kook, Seok Jin, and Jae Seok's envelopes.)
(So Min picked Haha, Ji Hyo, and Se Chan's envelopes.)
(Kwang Soo received 96 dollars and So Min received 54 dollars.)
(Let's see you in Indonesia for Indonesia Tiger Moth Tour.)
(They finally go to their destination.)
(A steep cliff and violent waves)
(The riders must fight against the waves on a wooden cable car.)
(The rough journey starts now.)
(Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game)
(Find the one who is speaking the truth.)
(The fierce battle for the truth between the tiger moths starts now.)
(It's an autumn day that contains the abundance of Chuseok.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- What is this? - Hello.
Hello.
What is this?
This must be a historic site.
(C rest stop has a statue of a Goguryeo warrior on a horse.)
Is that Genghis Khan?
(Does he think he is in Mongolia?)
Genghis Khan?
- Why would Genghis Khan be here? - Seriously.
Why would Genghis Khan be here?
I see.
It looks like a statue of an unknown warrior.
We need to take a look at Haha's outfit.
(The statue isn't the only thing we need to take a look at.)
(He is armed with an outfit of bright colors.)
Everyone was laughing when he came in.
(The fashionista who spreads hipness in North Chungcheong Province, Haha)
He is wearing Lee Deok Hwa's clothes again.
I burst out laughing as soon as I saw him.
(He is wearing Lee Deok Hwa's clothes again.)
It's morning soccer league fashion.
Chris Brown.
- What? - Chris Brown.
- For goodness' sake. - Be quiet and eat the brownie.
- Chris Brown, my foot. - He doesn't dress like that.
- You have toothpaste on your shirt. - Where?
(You should worry about yourself.)
Really?
- Where? - Really?
- It's all over the shirt. - He wears it at home,
at a shoot, when he sleeps, and when he works out.
He is well-known for not having a lot of clothes.
- Listen. - I should buy him clothes.
I really have multiple sets of the same items.
- I plan to post a picture of them. - I see.
After the late Steve Jobs...
(He only wears black clothes.)
- He is incredible. - It's comfortable.
- You should post a picture. - It's comfortable.
- He only wears one outfit. - His fashion never changes.
- It's comfortable. - He only wears one outfit.
So Min wants people to talk about her outfit, too.
- No, I don't. - Her outfit matches Jae Seok's.
You should pull down your pants a little.
- Look at her pants. - Seriously.
- You pulled up your pants too high. - Listen.
Don't say such things to So Min.
- Why not? - So Min will find it funny.
- She will pull up her pants higher. - That's right.
She will pull them up to her chest.
She will wear them as a top.
She will pull them up to here.
She takes things to extremes.
These pants come with suspenders.
My goodness.
Kwang Soo got his hair cut.
I got my hair cut.
- It's refreshing to look at. - He looks like a human being now.
A haircut is necessary.
People said a haircut will make him look better, but he looks the same.
(He looks the same.)
You say that because you are used to my changing styles.
Didn't Ahn Jung Hwan have that hairstyle in 2002?
- The windswept hairstyle. - What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
(He tries a kiss on the ring.)
All right.
(The producer cuts them off.)
He knows when to cut us off.
- That was clean. - He knows we are out of ideas.
- "All right." - It's time to move on.
We have an announcement to make before the start of the race.
- Okay. - My goodness.
Similar to So Min and Kwang Soo,
Haha and Se Chan had planned...
to go to Giant Canyon Swing to carry out their penalty.
(They were supposed to go to Giant Canyon Swing in September.)
Why aren't they going?
Due to complications,
the media visa is getting delayed.
They don't have the media visa yet.
Before the end of this year...
- Our penalty is gone. - Nice!
- Yes! - Really?
- Let's pass! - That's complete nonsense.
- There is no way we can go. - Can a penalty go away like that?
- Look for something in Korea. - It's still valid.
(The situation can't be helped.)
I learned about this...
from "Live Info Show".
- The longest zipline... - That's right.
- in Korea was just made. - A zipline.
- Send them over there. - It's the longest zipline in Korea.
(The length of 389m promises to make them forget about the US.)
Why would you watch something like that?
Seriously.
- It's incredible. - It's on par with the one in Spain.
You can get a beautiful view of the nature.
Seriously. It will be beautiful.
- It will be incredible. - The view will be beautiful.
- Thank you for a nice input. - All right.
I bet my entire fortune Jae Seok will end up on it.
(I bet my entire fortune Jae Seok will end up on it.)
Seriously. It will happen before this year passes.
- Hey. - Jae Seok...
Jae Seok will hit his own mouth...
and say that he shouldn't have said anything.
I bet you will sit next to him with your entire fortune.
I bet he will be holding a crocodile.
- He will be holding a crocodile. - That's right.
(Kwang Soo and Jae Seok enjoy the longest zipline in Korea.)
- For goodness' sake. - A crocodile.
That's right.
Anyway, we must complete the penalty before the year passes.
That's why we came up with a plan to replace it with another swing.
The original destination was Giant Canyon Swing.
When we visit Australia for Kwang Soo's penalty,
we will visit New Zealand as well.
- That's a good idea. - You will go to New Zealand.
Then they can go on Nevis Swing.
(Let's go to Nevis Swing, the place the crew recommends.)
(It's the biggest swing in the world.)
(It's a destination the members were the wariest of.)
That's a good idea. They always find a way.
- Are you saying we will go on it? - Why?
The zipline that was on "Live Info Show"...
- would be preferable. - Seriously.
Nevis Swing seemed intense.
It sounds like...
we should come to an agreement.
Since it isn't the destination we picked,
What do you think about the change?
- My head hurts. - They should do it.
As a viewer, I am curious.
The viewers would be upset...
- if they don't hold their promise. - For goodness' sake.
Those crazy swings should be destroyed.
They must be frustrated.
I am glad I won't be going on that swing.
That place would make a nice alternative, too.
- Which place? - The one from "Live Info Show".
Did you invest in that zipline?
You brought it up so many times.
Isn't it better than Nevis Swing?
It's definitely better.
- It's much better. - You won't have to go abroad.
Would you please let us choose from a few options?
- The one in New Zealand is... - We will look up all the swings.
We will look up all the swings.
There is a swing in Jamsil, too.
Let's move on so that we can relocate to the shade.
(The producer cuts them off.)
Finally, Indonesia Manual Wooden Cable Car...
Is the talk over?
Are we really going?
You are really going.
You are going.
(Do we really need to go?)
Since the two countries are close, choosing either of them...
If I choose either of them, the production cost will be reduced.
- The plane tickets. - You are right.
- They can visit the two countries. - That's right.
The three of you should go.
Will one person see crocodiles and ride the swing?
Haha, you are in trouble.
(Am I going as Kwang Soo's plus one?)
You have to see the crocodiles, too.
Why do I need to go?
Seriously.
- It's your penalty. - I get that, but...
I get that it's my penalty, but...
Can I shave my head instead?
(Can I shave my head instead?)
Let's say for now that you are going.
(The producer is resolute.)
He isn't interested in Haha shaving his head.
- I guess he really wants you to go. - Seriously.
He doesn't care whether he shaves his head...
- or not. - That's right.
He and I can go to Brazil and get Brazilian waxing.
We can do that.
All right.
(He isn't interested in waxing either.)
- Will it end like this? - All right.
He doesn't care whether you get Brazilian waxing or not.
Not too long ago, Kwang Soo and So Min rode...
- Indonesia Manual Wooden Cable Car. - Yes.
(They are done with their penalty.)
How was it, So Min?
What is it?
I survived on the allowances you sent me.
That's right.
We had a race with that money.
- Really? - I got 100 dollars.
(Their race piques the other members' interest.)
- So Min got 50 dollars. - Really?
All right. So this is the race we have prepared for today.
It's Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game.
(The crew prepared Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game.)
- Truth or Dare? - I used to host the show back then.
Kwang Soo is good at this game.
I like this game.
This game will be an individual match.
There will be four rounds in total.
- It's an individual match? - Yes.
We will watch the clips from Tiger Moth Tour in Indonesia soon.
Questions of the game will be based on this trip.
(Questions about their trip will be presented.)
Kwang Soo and So Min will read the question...
and choose either one of Truth or False Cards.
(Kwang Soo and So Min will choose either one of Truth or False Cards.)
Answer according to your cards, and claim that you're telling the truth.
We have to find out who's telling the truth.
Other members will listen to So Min and Kwang Soo...
and choose the person you think is telling the truth.
(Members must choose who they think is telling the truth.)
Whoever chooses the correct member will be exempted from the penalty.
From what penalty will we be exempted?
Whoever makes the wrong guess will face the penalty...
and receive a penalty badge.
The penalty badge is at stake for every round.
- I see. - It's for every round?
Kwang Soo and So Min. Regardless of the result of the rounds,
you will be exempted if the majority of the members chooses you.
If you aren't chosen by the majority, you'll face the penalty...
and receive the penalty badge.
(Whoever isn't chosen will face the penalty and get the badge.)
After the race,
two members with the most number of penalty badges...
will get to proceed with Chuseok live travel broadcast.
(2 members with most badges must broadcast on Chuseok about traffic.)
Goodness, this is the worst.
- Broadcast on Chuseok? - You want us to do a live show?
You want us to do a live show?
(Are you serious?)
(2 members will deliver a live segment on Chuseok in real life.)
On which date though?
- It will be on October 8. - Sorry?
- October 8? - The 8th?
- It's the last Sunday. - The last Sunday of the holidays.
- I bet the traffic will be heavy. - The traffic is the worst then.
- I really don't want to do this. - Where will we broadcast?
- 2 of us will do it? - Yes, 2 of you will do it.
- You know how it looks. - Basically, I...
(A man only gazes afar while the announcement is made.)
- He only tells lies. - It's all a lie.
I can't focus on the game today.
He keeps asking me the questions.
"Is it over?"
(I can only think about how I will be on that swing.)
Unless it's hilarious, I don't think I can laugh today. I keep...
- I can see the despair on his face. - You should go and face it then.
You should get on the lane bound for Seoul and go to Seoul.
(You can go home early today.)
Lane bound for Seoul?
You can just head to Gimpo International Airport.
- I must get on it after my work. - I mean it's...
All right. We will begin Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game now.
- All right. - Excuse me.
- I should do my best then. - I must make the correct guesses.
Otherwise, I'll work during the holidays.
- Tell me the rules of the game. - I need to try my best today.
- Everything? - I wasn't paying attention.
This will happen in the morning of the eighth?
We'll end up getting on the Nevis Swing.
(Don't even worry about the game. We'll end up going there.)
This is the 1st round of 4 rounds.
Let the first round of the Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game begin.
We're starting? Gosh, I need to do a good job.
I have to do well today. I'm serious.
To be honest,
- I'm free on the last day. - Right.
But I don't want to come in for work on the last day of the holidays.
- We'll spend at least two hours. - Exactly.
I'm not chosen for the penalties that we have to go abroad because...
I'm not scared and because I actually want to go.
- But I don't want this penalty. - Is that so?
- But I think I might get this. - Why don't you like this penalty?
- What's there to like it? - Why do you say that?
- I have to come in on a day off. - Let's help Jong Kook get this one.
- Because it's not a scary ride? - Right.
- So this is bothersome to him. - He doesn't want to waste his time.
Let me ask this.
What's your plan on the last day of the holidays?
(Why don't you want to put aside time on the last day?)
I need to work out.
- I must exercise. - Hold on a minute.
- I have to work out. - You only need to work out.
It's annoying to go back and forth.
But the idea of coming to work on that day is the worst.
- I agree. - But still.
On this round, a meal ticket at the rest stop is at stake.
(1st round of Truth Game)
The member who gets the answer will win a meal ticket.
- The food there is great. - This is amazing.
The member who gets the wrong answer will not be allowed to eat...
and will receive a penalty badge.
We win when we get the majority of the votes, right?
Kwang Soo and So Min.
The one who gets the majority of the votes can eat.
- Or you'll get a penalty badge. - I might not get to eat.
Kwang Soo is terrible at lying, but So Min is just as horrible.
- They easily get flustered. - Besides, they tell small lies.
Our credibility is in the gutter.
I can spot his lies when I observe his face,
- but not So Min. I don't know hers. - I don't know her well.
- But she gets flustered. - But...
don't you trust me though?
- No way. - What nonsense are you saying?
No, we don't trust you.
So Min tends to tell small lies...
instead of lying about important stuff.
But...
the only thing he does in his life is lie.
How could you? How could you criticize about my life?
- She's not wrong though. - What do you mean...
- by that? - She's right.
His life is filled with lies. It's true.
What do you mean my life is filled with lies?
I'll play the first video of the Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game.
All we have to do is choose, right?
What kind of a clip is this?
It's been a while hosting a show while sitting down.
- While sitting down? - I'm serious.
- We are sitting down. - We're watching clips.
Let me play the clip.
Play the video.
(The video for the 1st round is played.)
(The 1st question of the Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game)
We are really going.
(2 weeks ago, Incheon International Airport)
(We are really going to Indonesia at last.)
- There are so many people here. - I can't believe this is happening.
Am I going to Indonesia or Australia?
There are so many people.
They must be going to Indonesia...
- to receive the penalty. - What are you talking about?
Come to your senses.
You should wash your face on the plane.
(They set out to Yogyakarta which takes 10 hours in total.)
(From Jakarta to Yogyakarta, it takes 1 hour and 20 minutes.)
(9pm, at Adisutjipto International Airport)
- Hey. - Goodness.
This is nice.
(Various cultures coexist in Indonesia.)
- Was that good? - It was so good.
(Noises fill the airport.)
- You got to try it? - Kwang Soo surprised me.
- He's the Prince of Asia. - Right.
(Welcome, Prince of Asia.)
Pay attention to his face now.
- So Min told me... - But the thing is...
she was disgusted by his facial expression then.
(They're excited to see Kwang Soo.)
Look at that face.
(He puts on a look as if he's the national guest.)
But the thing is that...
- he never does this with his hands. - That's my point.
- He doesn't do that. - He rarely does this.
- But aren't you envious? - But this...
(They welcome the betrayer couple.)
- There were so many people. - Lee Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo! - Look at you.
Kwang Soo is so popular.
It's not something that we can witness in Korea.
Look at his unusual smile.
(But at the thought of the penalty, he gets sad.)
We really came.
This is where we finally ended up.
I had no idea that we'd be here.
(The Tiger Moth Tour begins. What kind of misfortunes awaits?)
We're here.
- We are finally here. - Your hotel is nice.
- Gosh, that's a fancy hotel. - That's a five-star hotel.
Tell us about our schedule.
We were informed the seventh floor is the lobby.
I'll share the schedule in the lobby.
We prepared a meal since we figured you'd be hungry.
And you can have a good night's sleep.
You'll face the penalty tomorrow. That's the schedule.
Then we can sleep tonight?
(Since tomorrow will be a long day, they're letting us rest.)
(They arrive in the lobby at ease.)
You jumped in Korea, remember?
- Do we have to do it? - Let's jump again.
- We arrived here. - You know how it works, right?
- We'll jump, and we'll be here. - We arrived here from Korea.
1, 2, 3.
(Jumping)
(What on earth are you doing?)
(But they're doing their best acting the scene.)
- Why didn't, did you edit that? - Why didn't you edit it?
- You promised us. - Why didn't you edit that?
- But no one does that nowadays. - Right.
- That... - I used to do that.
- Didn't "Wooroemae" use that? - Exactly.
(Didn't "Wooroemae" use that?)
So Min suggested doing it.
1, 2, 3.
(This technique was seen in "Wooroemae" in 1986.)
(Where are you, villains?)
(Grabbing him by his collar)
What are you doing? What's going on?
(What is your problem?)
- It's from this morning. - What's wrong with you?
(From this morning?)
(She grabbed him by his collar in the morning,)
(and it continues even in Indonesia.)
- Combine it from the morning. - What's wrong with you?
How can they combine the two clips?
This is so weird. Are we in Indonesia?
We are in Indonesia, right?
- Yes, we are in Indonesia. - We're in Yogyakarta.
Anyway, you have arrived in Indonesia.
Since it's been a long day, give us your bags. We'll move them for you.
Hand us your bags.
We'll give you the cards for your rooms.
Kwang Soo, you have Room 549.
- So Min, here's yours. - Thank you.
It's Room 501.
Can't I put the bag in my room?
- No, let us. - I can do it.
- Something's going on. - I can do it.
- They gave us the card, but why... - You can't give them that easily.
You willingly gave them your luggage.
You have received the cards for your rooms.
Take a brief recess, and we'll resume later.
We can go up now?
- Yes. - I can take a shower now?
Yes, you can. Do whatever you want.
(But what about our bags?)
Can we take our luggage?
I need my luggage to wash.
Why did they take the luggage?
(But the luggage the crew took hasn't moved.)
Your luggage...
has been confiscated by the crew.
(It's confiscated by the crew?)
(Confiscated!)
(No way.)
What are you doing?
- I saw that coming. - This is so awkward.
Seriously. Why did you give it to them?
- You fell for it so easily. - What are you doing?
- The producer isn't normal. - It's confiscated?
There's a reason that we took away your luggage.
It's right in front of us.
I can just take this, can't I?
How could you...
There are only two ways of retrieving your luggage.
You will have to either accomplish your given mission.
Or for 30 dollars, you may take...
- 30 dollars? - 1 item.
(They must pay 30 dollars per item.)
(Unbelievable)
I only have 50 dollars.
- Isn't it three dollars? - This is stealing.
They're thieves.
Do we pay if we fail the mission?
- If you clear the mission... - Can we take it?
If you clear it, you may take the luggage for free.
I keep asking, but did I do something wrong?
- All my things... - Our trip here was too easy.
I thought it was strange.
Indonesia Tiger Moth Tour...
has started.
Here's your first mission.
Let's start Catch the Bag If You Can.
- There's a title. - Did someone...
come up with the title?
We do a lot of research.
(We work hard constantly.)
Catch the Bag If You Can.
There's a traditional Indonesian game called Spoon and Marble Race.
- Spoon and Marble Race? - You must pass the goal while...
holding a spoon with a marble with your mouth.
Didn't we play that often?
- Right. - Right?
We're in a hotel, so we can't run.
Hold the spoon in your mouth. Without dropping the marble,
transfer it to the person next to you.
You succeed if you place the marble in the cup.
- This is easy. - Are we on the same team?
Yes. You have 60 seconds.
You succeed if you place over 10 marbles in the goal.
- This is possible. - I agree.
They're given a mission as soon as they arrive.
I bet it was annoying.
I couldn't believe it.
(Let's make 10 marbles in the goal.)
10 marbles in 60 seconds means you succeed.
You may take your luggage without paying.
If you fail, you must pay.
- Okay. - Get ready.
Let's do it.
Start.
(Spoon and Marble Race starts.)
(Being careful)
It's similar to the marble game during childhood.
- It doesn't seem hard. - It wasn't.
- They should move faster. - We play games often.
Kwang Soo is getting faster.
So Min should lower herself to make it faster.
They should have switched places.
Transferring the marble is easier.
So Min wanted to do it.
- I see. - Marbles are heavy.
They might knock over the cup.
- It isn't difficult. - 30 seconds passed.
You have 10 seconds.
- He's good at receiving it. - Right.
How many are there?
- 3, 2, 1. - We did it.
(How many marbles are in the cup?)
Time is up.
Let's count the marbles.
My teeth hurt.
(It's time to count.)
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8.
(Currently, there are 8 marbles.)
(Did they place 10 marbles?)
- Is it less than 10? - They have 8.
We cleared the mission in one go.
- 8, 9, 10. - We have 10.
(They succeed.)
We have 10.
- We made it. - Didn't we?
- We work well as a team. - That was fast.
It was hard to succeed.
(They feel overwhelmed.)
- We worked well together then. - Right.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo could put 11.
Of course. We would make it easily.
- Did you think you said the answer? - Yes.
(She was nervous.)
- I shouldn't say anything. - You shouldn't.
- We made it. - It was almost impossible.
(They can take the luggage for free.)
- You cleared the mission. - Okay.
- Our teamwork makes it possible. - You'll get your luggage.
Between the two of you,
choose which luggage you'll open.
- Must we choose one? - I have everything in it.
- Can't we open both? - Do we open only one?
You can open only one of them.
You didn't tell us before.
You're so mean.
You must take items in the luggage.
I want to slap Chul Min on the neck.
- I'm serious. - What do you have in your bag?
- What do you have? - I have everything.
- Me too. - I have two luggage.
I have everything in my luggage. Let's open mine.
I will let you if you pay me 2.5 dollars.
How about 2.3 dollars?
- Pay two dollars. - I don't have much money.
Let's open mine. I'll pay you two dollars.
- I can't give more than two. - Okay.
- Two dollars? - Okay.
(They agree to open Kwang Soo's.)
Kwang Soo pays two dollars to open his luggage.
- Okay. - Goodness.
- I gave her two dollars. - Let's open his.
(Current mission money status)
- So Min has 56 dollars. - Kwang Soo has a lot.
(He finally opens his luggage.)
Here are the toiletries.
You have nothing in it.
You can only open it once.
- I'll take my toiletries. - You can only open it once.
Show us what you have inside the luggage.
I have this.
(Is that a game player?)
Why did you bring it all the way here?
We have a lot of free time.
- Why did you pack that? - Why did you take a game player?
He has the wrong attitude.
- He has no common sense. - I agree.
(Goodness)
You shouldn't waste electricity at the hotel.
Electricity?
What's wrong with using it?
- Put back the item that you chose. - Okay.
(He puts it back in the luggage.)
What's this?
- It glows in the dark. - Why did you bring it?
- Why did you pack that? - What for?
- Why did you take the frog? - What is it for?
It's for sleeping.
(Frog that glows in the dark makes him sleep better.)
I get scared to sleep in unfamiliar places.
You may take only one item...
from your luggage.
I must take toiletries.
To take an item from the luggage,
throw an Indonesian coin into the luggage.
(He may take the item that he hits with a coin.)
You may take the first item that you hit with the coin.
You should tell us before.
- Why didn't you? - Is there another mission?
- That's so unfair. - Come on.
That's horrible.
- Let's be fair. - Goodness.
There are too many missions.
- Does that make sense? - That's too much.
We already cleared the mission.
How could you, Chul Min?
Am I going to New Zealand?
(He only thinks of himself.)
Watch the video. Forget about New Zealand.
I can't concentrate.
What about the two dollars that I paid?
- Throw the coin behind the line. - I remember these boxers.
(Which boxers?)
- I remember them. - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Remember the ones you showed?
- I wore each of them. - Remember?
(It was during a family special.)
I remember the rainbow boxers.
- Is it that one? - Yes.
- Do you still have them? - Didn't they rot?
Kwang Soo likes those colors.
- Didn't they stretch? - No, they didn't.
They shrank when I washed them.
This is an Indonesian coin.
Excuse me, Mr. Producer.
(She calls the producer.)
Can you tell us if there's another mission?
- Is it the last mission? - It should be.
- It's the last. - There can't be more.
Who throws the coin?
- One of you can do it. - It's me.
(Trust me.)
- Can you do it? - Of course.
I don't think you can.
There's something that we brought.
It's called slime monster.
- Try to throw it. - It's hard to throw.
(He throws the slime monster to test it.)
- Gosh. - It's okay.
- What do you mean? - I'll try again.
It's not okay.
(The grip isn't so bad.)
- It's good enough. - It won't work.
- I don't think so. - It doesn't matter.
Throw the coin instead. Kwang Soo.
(What's going on?)
(The slime monster is everywhere.)
- Gosh. - What happened?
It's all over my clothes.
What is it?
- It's slime. - What?
Please say, "challenge".
(He decides to throw the coin.)
- It's because of the slime monster. - Can he take the whole luggage?
(It's not as easy as he thought.)
- Goodness. - Wait.
Can you pull it toward the right?
(Hello.)
It's still here.
(He finds more slime monster.)
It's everywhere. What's going on?
- It's like cell division. - What is it?
Did it reproduce?
What's going on?
I keep finding more.
It's slime monster.
(It's an invasion of a green monster.)
My clothes turned green.
Challenge.
(He plays the game.)
(Question for Round 1 of Truth Game)
- Please. - Is this the question?
I remember it.
(He throws the coin to determine which item to take.)
- The coin could fall in between. - Which item did it hit?
It's the first item that the coin hits.
(Here's the first question.)
Which does the coin hit?
It's where the coin lands.
(Which item did Kwang Soo get?)
- Is it the first item that it hits? - What is it?
This is the question.
- Do you remember it? - I remember it clearly.
What was in his luggage?
- Boxers and toiletries. - A game player and a bag.
- Medicine. - Glow-in-the-dark frog.
It's not easy for the coin to land on the frog.
Kwang Soo and So Min.
Choose an envelope, and decide whether it's true or not.
- Really? - True or false?
Is it only one of them who tells the truth?
- That's right. - Is that so?
(Which will Kwang Soo and So Min choose?)
Please come to the front 1 by 1.
- Make your statement. - Is it a statement?
- I state that... - We must listen carefully...
when Kwang Soo makes an argument.
I say that it's true.
He looks relaxed.
- Also, - His face looks relaxed.
the coin landed on my underwear. I remember it clearly.
I remember it clearly.
(He says the coin landed on his underwear.)
Round 1 is easy.
You know it by looking at my face.
- Right. - Yes.
Will you only say the truth?
Yes. I'll only say the truth.
During Indonesia Tiger Moth Tour,
- did you sneak into So Min's room? - Sorry?
No, I didn't.
- What's with the glow-in-the-dark? - Sorry?
- The frog. - Did someone give it to you?
- Everyone's curious. - I bought it.
I don't like to sleep in the dark.
Did you buy two and give one to someone else?
This game doesn't work that way.
(Speechless)
When was your last kiss?
- Excuse me. - What's with you?
Do you have a girlfriend?
Shut it.
- I don't. What's with you? - You don't?
Tell us the truth.
I'm telling you the truth.
He's getting angry.
We have to find the truth.
It's a truth game.
It's not the kind you play when you drink.
Why are you so worked up?
- I mean... - You look angry.
When you lie, you tend to say a lot.
Your explanation gets long. But let me tell you.
- Where did the coin end up? - Look at the bag.
Which item is taking...
the most space?
- The game console? - Exactly.
It has a solid surface and takes up a lot of space.
Also, I think it was intentional.
He probably wanted to play games so badly.
(So Min says the coin ended up on the game console.)
Let me ask you one more question.
(Jae Seok wants to ask another question.)
What material was your toiletry bag?
What's with you?
(Stop pretending to be sharp.)
Stop playing detective.
- What was the material? - What's with the way you speak?
- Was it cloth? - Let me stand up.
- What was the material? - What?
- Am I a criminal? - What was it?
Cut it out.
It's not easy for the coin to end up right in the middle.
Did it go in directly or bounce in?
To be honest, I don't remember.
- You don't remember? - I don't.
Kwang Soo is telling the truth.
Let me explain.
Stop trying to manipulate us.
You're like Solomon.
Kwang Soo is telling the truth.
- Gosh. - You're telling the truth.
My goodness.
We don't have to hear anymore.
Are you being honest?
Of course. Kwang Soo packed the game console himself.
- It means he wanted to use it. - Then...
did he play games that night?
He said he did.
- He said he did. - What?
If he got the game console, he must have played games.
What is she saying?
- I mean... - He played alone?
- I didn't play games. - How can you not know?
She's either lying or talking gibberish.
I'd guess Kwang Soo is telling the truth,
- but I hate to see that face. - What do you mean?
(Jae Seok hates that Kwang Soo looks so confident.)
- It's disgusting. - It's disgusting.
- He looks so confident. - Right?
His face is disgusting.
- No, listen. - Your face is disgusting.
Gosh.
- I'm telling the truth. - If you want to shoot on the 8th,
- do whatever you want. - Oh, right.
- I won't say anymore. - I forgot about that.
- Let's have a good start. - That depends on this.
It'll decide whether we'll shoot on the 8th.
(Who is telling the truth, Kwang Soo or So Min?)
- One... - Hold on.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
This is huge.
If you get it wrong, you won't get any food.
One.
(If they get it wrong, they'll get a penalty badge.)
- 2. - 2.
It'd be absurd if I lose.
Three.
(Whichever attracts more supporters will get to eat.)
(Whom will the members choose?)
- All right. - I choose So Min.
(Jae Suk and Ji Hyo choose So Min.)
(Kwang Soo attracted more supporters.)
Gosh! This is frustrating.
Why would you choose So Min?
Kwang Soo was so calm.
So Min looked so frustrated.
Which item did Kwang Soo get?
Please put on your earphones.
Let's see it.
- Let's see it. - If Kwang Soo lied,
it means he's a real actor.
So Min looked so frustrated.
You're a real actor.
So Min looked so...
Let's watch the video.
- Gosh. - Kwang Soo looked so natural.
So Min is still innocent.
Please. I'm worried.
(They can get only one item. Where did the coin end up?)
(The game console is right in the middle.)
- The game console was there? - It was there?
Then the coin might have ended up there.
- The game console was there? - Just watch.
(Did the coin end up on the underwear bag?)
(Game console)
You're getting the game console.
Hey.
(I can't believe this.)
He got the game console.
- The game console? - I got it right.
Did I win?
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo get it right.)
- We got it right. - So Min.
- So Min. - We got it right.
(The ones who were fooled by Kwang Soo will get no food.)
(The only item they will have is the game console.)
Kwang Soo.
Can you wash your body with the game console?
Why did you bring that?
You won't play games here.
I thought we wouldn't have a lot to do.
(I wanted to play games during our free time.)
Hold on.
- I was telling the truth. - Hold on.
Thank you for believing me.
Thank you.
It's Jong Kook's fault.
You led us on.
Jong Kook said it too loudly...
in the beginning.
- Right? - It's Jong Kook's fault.
Jong Kook got so many in trouble.
Stop doing that.
- I... - It's all his fault.
overlooked one thing.
I thought I was very close with Kwang Soo, but I wasn't.
(I wasn't so close with Kwang Soo.)
- You were being fooled. - I didn't know that.
- You were fooled. - I didn't know.
I thought I was close with him.
Kwang Soo was fooling you with that sly look.
Haha, why do you never trust me?
- I trusted you. - Why do you never trust me?
- I trusted you. - Does it make me a bad person...
and So Min a good person?
What is going on?
Everyone's apologizing to So Min.
You've lost your innocence.
- What? - You've lost your innocence.
Before, it showed when he was lying.
(Tiger Moth Tour Badges)
Order whatever you want.
Let's go.
- It's coming. - It's coming.
This is the charm of rest areas.
Who ordered pork cutlet? It looks so tasty.
This rest area has their own dishes.
It's stew.
It looks tasty.
It tastes so good.
(Let's enjoy our food.)
Are we really not getting any food?
Really?
It looked like the food was already ready.
The stew...
(Only Kwang Soo and the smart ones can enjoy lunch.)
It tastes amazing.
Is there no lunch for us?
I'm sure there's another chance.
Are we really having no food?
(They were fooled, and they get no food.)
Seriously?
(Aren't you giving us any food?)
I get no food at home or at work.
(I'm so sad.)
You get no food at home or at work?
Where can I eat?
You get no food at home?
- Where can I eat? - Prepare your own food.
- What? - Prepare your own food.
I thought you were on a diet.
I look thinner, right? I've lost 2kg.
(He's lost 2kg.)
Why are you not giving us any food?
(Everybody's laughing except for one person.)
(Panicking)
- What's wrong? - He thought about Nevis Swing.
- I thought about Nevis Swing. - Stop it.
I can't get this song out of my head.
(Swing, swing, swing, my baby)
(He's going to ride Nevis Swing with Se Chan.)
It keeps on playing in my head.
I can't stand it anymore.
(They're upset.)
Ji Hyo, give me some.
That seemed natural.
That seemed very natural.
(What are you doing?)
It looked very natural.
Gosh.
(Seok Jin was stopped by Jae Seok.)
What am I doing with a spoon in my hand at 50?
- Gosh. - Seok Jin.
I used to do that back in middle school.
One of my friends is a managing director of a company.
(He's upset.)
He's a managing director.
Another one is a senior managing director.
I have money too.
A friend of yours is retired even.
Observe the rules.
- What's with you? - Don't break the rules.
At your age.
Think of your age.
I can at least eat the salad, right?
If you don't even let me eat the salad, I'll get mad.
Do you have to eat it?
(Jae Seok stops him.)
Hey.
You punk.
I'm seriously getting angry.
I mean it.
(Seok Jin is not even allowed to eat the salad.)
Let me at least eat the salad.
- I got him. - Let me eat the salad.
Give up.
- I'm going to drink some water. - Give up.
Gosh, it's so annoying.
(All Seok Jin got was a sip of water.)
Please take the same seats as before.
(Good luck, Haha.)
It's you, right?
- Hey. - You're riding Nevis Swing with me.
Aren't you scared? Why are you so lively?
We're not there yet.
Gosh.
I'm so jealous of you two.
(I love New Zealand.)
- Really? - Yes.
This is why you never get penalized.
But you'll get penalized today.
Kwang Soo would never take you with him.
Why don't we do this?
Se Chan and I will ride the swing,
and you can just hang on to the rope.
(Just hang on to the rope.)
(That sounds fun.)
- He'll die. - Hey.
And...
put some oil on your hands beforehand.
(It'll be exciting.)
I'm sorry.
(Scared)
That was risky.
I haven't heard Seok Jin's scared voice in a long time.
- This time, - He wants me dead.
Jong Kook got seriously angry.
Seok Jin was looking Jong Kook in the eye,
but then...
(Seok Jin lowered his eyes.)
I can't help it. I'm older than him,
but I can't help it.
You'll pretend you're not scared even if you are, right?
I won't.
Even if he's scared,
he'll just say, "This is a bit scary."
- You're right. - It's not funny at all.
- Right? - You're right.
- "This is kind of scary." - "This is a bit scary."
- "This is scary." - And then, he'll jump.
- And then, he'll jump. - "This is not easy."
It's because he's Kim Jong Kook.
- Right? - Right.
- He has to do it. - It's hard.
And I'm Haha.
Hey, you.
- This isn't a special about that. - It's driving me crazy.
- Keep your mouth shut. - Hey!
You should've told me at the end.
- I can't focus. - Right now...
I'm about to lose it.
All right.
I'll play the clip for the second round of Tiger Moth Tour...
Truth Game that the loser of the game will broadcast live on Chuseok.
- Please put on your earphones. - Wait. This is...
As you've seen before, look how good Ji Hyo is at this.
- We must be very observant. - I must follow Ji Hyo's decision.
I'm going to get it right now.
All right. We'll play the clip now.
Play the video.
(Who will get the penalty badge?)
(The 2nd question of Tiger Moth Tour)
Why did you bring that here?
You wouldn't even play with it.
Tell him you'll give him the money and do it again.
- Kwang Soo... - Can't I get a chance with money?
I will sell this device.
(He's selling it rather hurriedly.)
It's expensive.
All right. First off, take out your gaming device.
- I don't need this. - If that's the case,
give me five dollars, and I'll give you another chance.
- Just one. - What do you think? Should we pay?
Pay him, and let's do it again.
You gave me 2 dollars and 3 dollars.
(They earn another chance after paying 5 dollars.)
I counted the money, and it's five dollars.
(Let's do well this time.)
- It's So Min's turn. - Okay.
Take out the gaming device. You might select that again.
- That's so big. - The controllers...
(The controllers are separate.)
- The controllers... - Let me throw it this time.
I can't take them out?
- I can take them out too, can't I? - They are part of the device too.
- I can take them out though. - Take out the device only.
(What?)
You could've taken them out together if they were connected.
(Whispering)
She told me to hit you once.
(Producer, let me hit you.)
This device has neither the cables nor the controllers.
The only thing I can do with this is to hit someone.
(It's heavy.)
- That's the only thing I can do. - Fine.
- You can take out the controllers. - This is bad.
- Okay. - We'll let you do that.
- He ought to exclude them. - That's right.
Kwang Soo, move. Let me practice.
(Kwang Soo, move. Let me practice.)
(Throwing)
Hey.
What are you doing? I can't exactly go into your room.
- Come on! - Don't say something like that!
- Your lines are so lame. - No, the rule...
- It was the rule. - That was terrible.
- That was the rule of the game. - Your line is disgusting.
That's the worst line of today.
- It's really disgusting. - What's wrong with you?
It was like a joke.
- It was harder than it looked. - What was that?
(No one is interested in this fleeting romance.)
- You may start now. - Okay.
- Let's go. We can do this. - I'll try now.
Let me try it.
- You'll try it now. - Yes.
(She desperately needs toiletries to wash away her long day.)
(Will her coin land on the toiletries?)
(It did land on something.)
Where did it go?
Where is it?
(It lands on top of the padded vest.)
- It fell here. - It did fall on top of that.
They aren't clothes.
- It's your padded vest. - What is this?
- Why did you bring it to Indonesia? - I mean...
I wrapped the gaming device with this to avoid breaking it.
(I didn't have bubble wraps.)
I didn't bring this to wear.
- Congratulations. - I wrapped the device with this.
You think I'm crazy? Why would I bring this...
- to Indonesia? - This is a duck down vest.
(It looks warm.)
This isn't the end. Aren't you hungry?
- Why don't you have your meal? - Goodness.
What do I wear tomorrow then?
Wear this.
I don't need this.
(They head to the restaurant with the warm, padded vest.)
Hey, what time was that?
Gosh, you were on a tight schedule.
We were just starting.
(They began their journey at 9am, but the current time is 11pm.)
- Aren't you hungry? - Yes.
We'll start the mission for your dinner.
How many games did you play?
- The whole day is over. - It's only the beginning.
There's a mission for dinner?
- I'm so sick of missions. - Before...
Currently, you're carrying out the penalty in Indonesia.
- You said we'll rest. - We even played...
games from the flight to Indonesia because she wanted to play games.
Did I hear it wrong? He said we'll have to do a mission?
We're going to start a mission for your dinner.
Take out an item that you need from your luggage.
It's the luggage again.
- The luggage? - Take out an item...
- from the luggage. - Just one?
(It's a special chance for them.)
(They take out an item they need from their luggage.)
Take out only one item.
- Will you take out toiletries? - Yes.
I got mine.
- You took out your toiletries. - Yes.
- What about you, So Min? - Wait, no.
I should take out the outfit for tomorrow.
I can't take out the whole outfit?
(A whole outfit)
- Should I allow that? - Yes, please.
- But that's not fair. - So...
I'm okay with that, but the viewers might think it's unfair.
Hey, shut your mouth.
It looks like he's favoring you.
Just take out one item that you really need.
Pants.
Pants. Which one should I wear?
(She's seriously worried.)
They look the same. Why are you thinking about this?
- No, they're different. - What?
- They're different. - I thought you had the same pants.
How are they different? Even the lengths are the same.
This pair has buttons, and this pair has a zipper.
This is a high-waist pair.
But no one will know about the buttons or the zipper except you.
Please choose one for me.
(Stop talking, and choose one.)
That one.
- This one? This? Okay. - Yes.
(She chose a pair of pants with buttons for tomorrow.)
All right.
It does look like they're on their honeymoon.
You'll have your meal soon. Bring the food in, please.
(It's time for dinner they've been waiting for.)
- Thank you. This looks tasty. - What is that?
Your dinner will be a traditional dish of Indonesia.
This is Indonesian stir-fried rice, nasi goreng.
I know this dish.
And this is called ikan gurame.
This is made with a fish called gurame.
I see. This is a gurame.
All right. You can...
only eat this through your decisions.
Your choice, the mission for your dinner.
Will you choose the item you need?
Or will you choose delicious dishes to fill your empty stomach?
(Will they choose the item they need or the food to fill their hunger?)
Depending on your choices, you can get either the item or food.
To be honest, I'm hungry.
This is a new way of stressing me out.
(To wash or to eat.)
This isn't a team mission, is it?
- She can choose the pants or this. - That's correct.
I can choose either the toiletries or the food.
I'll choose the pants. You should choose the food and share it.
You want us to share?
I'll choose the toiletries. Or you can pay me two dollars.
Give me two dollars in exchange. Or this deal is off.
Okay. Hurry.
- We don't have time. I'm hungry. - Let's rock-paper-scissors.
- And then what? - The loser will pay two dollars.
- The loser can make a choice. - If I lose,
I'll give you two dollars and take my toiletries.
- And we share the food. I'm in. - Yes.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min wins.)
Give me two dollars. Give it to me.
- I'll save up 30 dollars like this. - I have to take out a loan soon.
And it'd be better for me to buy the items.
- Give me my two dollars. - What's happening now?
I'll choose the stir-fried rice.
Then I'll choose the toiletries, okay?
All right.
- We'll take out the pants. - Okay.
I chose the toiletries.
I used up all of the singles.
(Kwang Soo pays 2 dollars.)
Try this. This is good.
(A tasty dish brings peace to them.)
I think this is a spicy pepper.
- Was it good? - It was so good.
- It's really tasty. - This is delicious.
- It smells great. - It's like it's their honeymoon.
- But they don't like each other. - It's good.
- They were forced to get married. - Exactly.
(They're quiet at last. They're finally in peace.)
I really like the rice.
I like how dry it is.
- You like it dry? - Isn't it tasty?
What do people call this kind of rice?
(He's referring to Annam rice.)
- Wasn't the rice offered to Buddha? - No, that wasn't it.
(There he turns into a klutz again.)
That's from the story of Simcheong, and she offered 300 rice bags.
Oh, right.
You're going to lend me the cleansing foam, right?
(I'm sharing my food.)
Why aren't you answering me?
- You'll let me borrow it, right? - For a dollar.
- No. - For a dollar.
- You ate my food. - What are you doing?
You're eating my food, and you also took the toiletries.
It's so hard to meddle with you right now.
I hate this power struggle with you.
Promise me in front of the cameras.
That you're going to lend me your cleansing foam.
For a dollar,
I'll lend you the toothbrush and cleansing foam.
Then stop eating. Don't eat.
Didn't I pay for this fair and square? I gave you two dollars.
This is so interesting. What is this?
(I can't hear anything.)
For a dollar, I'll lend you a toothbrush, toothpaste,
shampoo, and conditioner.
I can't give you more than these.
- You get shampoo and conditioner. - Then take just a spoonful.
Goodness.
(How can she be so mean? Who is this girl?)
You made a promise. Have your spoonful, and give up.
Eat up.
Fine.
(Gobbling up)
(I'll only have a mouthful.)
(He eats every grain of leftover rice on the plate.)
Don't you think this is too much?
Give me 50 cents.
You ate 50-cents' worth of food. Give me 50 cents.
That would be 50 cents.
I won't give you the money.
- Why? - I had a change of heart.
(He changes his attitude.)
(Why?)
I didn't say out loud that I was going to pay you.
(He is true to his reputation.)
I don't need to pay you, and I won't lend you the toiletries.
(Now that he's been fed, he's feeling sleepy.)
Excuse me?
(What a jerk.)
Give me water, please.
Water, please.
(He's very satisfied with the stir-fried rice.)
This is good.
Give me. You said you'll give me the money.
I got you on the cameras.
It's a promise you made with your fans in Indonesia.
No matter how hard...
Why are you bringing my fans into this?
This is a promise with all those fans at the airport.
(We believe in you, Kwang Soo.)
As the Prince of Asia...
You're talking trash.
What on earth are you saying?
Keep your promise.
(The first meal of Tiger Moth Tour ends with them fighting.)
You may go to your rooms now.
(It's 1:30am.)
After you get some sleep,
we'll go to Indonesian Manual Wooden Cable Car at last.
(They go to Manual Wooden Cable Car tomorrow.)
- Do you have... - I'm not surprised.
any good news? We heard nothing good today.
That's why we have good news.
(Good news?)
You're given one more chance to open the luggage.
Here's your second mission to open the luggage.
It's called It's 4am, Not 4pm.
(It's 4am, Not 4pm)
(In Indonesia, it's 4am, Not 4pm?)
(Was the rhyme intentional?)
"It's 4am, Not 4pm"?
- Isn't it incredible? - What a great punch line.
You mean the good news is...
you allowing me to take...
one item out of so many from my luggage?
(He's speechless.)
Can you just give back my luggage? It's ridiculous.
How could you...
Here's the mission called It's 4am, Not 4pm.
When it's 4am in Indonesia,
it's 6am in Korea.
- Right. - Call other members at that time...
to proceed the mission.
You may call any member.
You fail immediately if you hear any assigned taboo words.
You get a chance to open the luggage if you succeed.
The taboo words you have to avoid...
will be given at 4am at the corridor on the 5th floor.
Have a good night.
(They get three hours of sleep.)
(He's speechless again.)
Look how sad I look.
(She tears up.)
You just look sleepy.
Go to bed now.
- Go to bed. - How can I sleep without changing?
Keep these clothes on.
Is that all?
Will you give them to me?
- I'm sorry. - I need to wash up.
- I don't have much. - I must brush teeth for your sake.
- That's why... - It's okay.
I won't talk much with you tomorrow.
(He won't talk to her tomorrow.)
Let's go.
(You're watching Indonesia Tiger Moth Tour.)
The mission starts at 4am. It must be 1am then.
We had to clear another mission after three hours.
- It was terrible. - We had no food or sleep.
- We couldn't even wash. - We couldn't sleep.
We can tell from your facial expression.
It's horrible in Indonesia.
It must be worse for Nevis Swing.
- We won't go. - I can imagine.
No way.
(He sighs.)
(They go into their separate rooms.)
- Here it is. - Lend me your foam cleanser.
- Please? - This is what I earned.
I have to wash my hair.
(She begs Kwang Soo.)
Please, Kwang Soo.
I'll lend you the game console.
What can I do with this? May I sell it?
What's this?
May I sell it?
(He finds something on the game controller.)
- It's the slime monster. - It is.
It's everywhere.
It's on all of my items.
Please, Kwang Soo.
I beg you, Kwang Soo.
- What? - Foam cleanser.
(She begs for his foam cleanser.)
(Kwang Soo decides to be generous after she begs desperately.)
- Don't give it to me now. - Take it now.
How can I use it later?
(He gives her the foam cleaner on her hand.)
There isn't even much left.
(She sighs.)
How can I use it if you give it to me all at once?
- Keep it somewhere. - Where?
What can I do with it?
I can only give it to you now.
I don't have a place to store it.
- Give me a plastic bag. - I'll do it carefully.
- They will get mixed. - Let me do it.
- They will get mixed. - What's this?
(What is this?)
- It's the slime monster. - Why is it here?
(The slime monster is everywhere.)
I never opened the bag. How did it get in here?
- It's the slime monster. - Is it a real monster?
(What's it made of?)
- Why is it here? - Where did it come from?
I don't know.
Is the monster alive? I keep finding more.
Seriously.
- What else can I do? - I can't use it if you give it now.
Give me a lot of conditioner.
Give me more. I have long hair.
- I have long hair too. - My hair is longer.
(They argue about hair length.)
I'll help you later.
Give me more. That's enough only for the tip of my hair.
I need to wash the back.
Use the soap. I don't have much left.
There's no soap either.
Hey, stop it.
(They argue over little things.)
Give me some toothpaste.
Are we prisoners?
- What are we doing? - Are we prisoners?
What's the reason? Is this necessary?
You're on Indonesia Tiger Moth Tour to be penalized.
Are they on "The Law of Jungle"?
It's terrible.
(Around 4am)
It was so tiring.
(2 minutes before 4am)
Hello.
- What time is it over there? - She looks like a frog.
It's 4am.
- My face was swollen. - She looks like a frog.
(What's going on?)
Hello.
He's a ghost in the subway.
He looks like a wrestler.
Current time 4:01am.
(It's 6am in Korea.)
The luggage in the 7th floor lobby is open.
- Pardon me? - You may not go.
The member to clear the mission...
may take...
the items of his or her choice in the black bag.
(Pack your items in the black bag.)
Is this necessary?
Just give me my things.
Please.
You may move once you get another member on the phone.
You must keep them on the line until you take your items.
You aren't allowed to tell them not to hang up.
You fail the mission if the other says the taboo words.
(The other must not say the taboo words.)
He can't say the taboo words or hang up?
Right.
The taboo words are "Let me sleep" or "I'm going to sleep."
Please start the mission.
(So Min tries calling someone right away.)
- Hello? - Se Chan.
I had an event,
so I was at the airport back then.
- I see. - It's me.
(She gets lucky.)
Hello, So Min.
(She must prolong the call.)
- What's up? - Se Chan.
By the way...
Can you sing me a song?
(She asks for a song.)
What? A song?
Can you sing me a song?
(She asks him to sing at 6am.)
- Are you drunk? - No, I'm not.
(She sounds drunk.)
What's going on?
I thought she was drunk. She kept saying nonsense.
It'd be funny if Se Chan said something strange.
(I couldn't sleep at the thought of you.)
I'd be in trouble.
I'll call Seok Jin first.
(He calls Seok Jin.)
- Did you call me? - Seok Jin wouldn't pick up.
- I bet he's sleeping. - I couldn't answer.
(He's not helpful at all.)
How about Jae Seok?
(He calls Jae Seok next.)
(Will diligent Jae Seok pick up?)
- I couldn't hear the phone ring. - You couldn't?
You called me back.
I called you back later.
I think he's sleeping. I'll try Se Chan.
The number you have dialed is busy.
It must be So Min.
- Hello? - Se Chan.
(She enters the 7th floor lobby.)
Can you sing me a song please?
- Are you drunk? - No I'm not.
Why would I drink at work?
It's so out of the blue.
It's because I suddenly missed you.
What time is it over there?
Can you sing me a song?
He's such a gentleman.
- What? - You have a good voice.
(You have a good voice, Se Chan.)
Right now,
I'm tired.
I can't sing for you now.
Really?
He was close to saying the words.
- Normally... - Are you on a mission?
(She has to hurry before he hangs up!)
- Are you on a mission? - Me?
- Yes. - No, I'm not.
- It's not that. - Really?
Excuse me, but where are my pants with buttons?
You took them from me.
It's nothing.
(Meanwhile...)
I'll call Haha.
(He tries to call Haha this time.)
- He wouldn't pick up. - Of course not.
- He would be sleeping. - He's sleeping.
He wouldn't pick up.
Why does everyone sleep so much?
I'll try Jong Kook. He recently finished a project.
(He failed again.)
I heard the phone ringing, but I didn't pick up.
Really?
Who would anyone be up at 6am?
When he calls me early in the morning, he's usually drunk.
That's why I don't pick up any calls at that time.
(Kwang Soo likes drunk dialing.)
(Sad)
(Why don't you try calling Ji Hyo?)
Why don't you try calling Ji Hyo?
She'd be sleeping anyway.
(She's only awake in the afternoon.)
She's definitely sleeping.
(He tries calling Ji Hyo as his last hope.)
- Change the caller ringtone please. - Okay.
- She's had it for four years. - I'm tired of it.
- Kwang Soo. - Ji Hyo.
(She's awake at this hour?)
- Yes? - Why are you awake?
I'm with someone.
- What? - Where are you?
I'm in Indonesia.
Where in Indonesia are you? I'm in Indonesia too.
Right. You're in Indonesia too, right?
- You were in Indonesia? - She was in Indonesia too.
- Really? - Really?
- That's unbelievable. - You had a shoot?
Really?
I was so surprised.
I have to go. We've been talking for eight minutes.
Are you hanging up on me?
Bye. I have to go.
Really? Okay.
(Kwang Soo appears.)
I mean...
- Bye. - How long will you be here?
Bye.
- Really? - Sorry?
Is this all the hats? I brought more.
(Kwang Soo has to buy time.)
- Hey. - Who is it?
Did you have breakfast?
Who is it?
Aren't you tired?
Get some sleep.
Hey.
Ji Hyo.
(Kwang Soo is angry.)
He looks seriously angry.
I don't remember it.
- That's hilarious. - I don't remember it.
Why are you awake at this hour?
Aren't you tired?
She's okay. Her voice sounds fine.
I'll call you soon.
Ji Hyo.
(Kwang Soo focuses on moving the stuff.)
It fits.
So Min is calling me.
- Don't get it. She's drunk. - Please answer it.
- She's drunk. - Ji Hyo.
(I'm not drunk.)
- She's drunk. - I thought she really was drunk.
- Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, this is So Min.
(So Min is talking to Ji Hyo?)
- She hung up on me. - This is So Min.
Why are you awake?
It's too late. Go to bed.
(I still have a lot left.)
Call me later.
You're definitely going to Australia.
(So Min, I'm taking you to Australia.)
(After three hours of war,)
(the penalty day starts.)
Good morning.
(After three hours of war, the penalty day starts.)
Aren't we jumping today?
(We should teleport.)
Let's jump to the cable car.
- To the cable car? - Yes.
Isn't it...
Let's try.
Please use the best one.
(We'll jump many times.)
1, 2, 3.
- They used it. - You used it.
I'm touched.
(I'm really touched.)
1, 2, 3.
(They succeeded after 7 tries.)
- This is fun. - We're inside now.
This is fun.
Was it really necessary?
(They can't teleport anymore.)
Are we going to keep doing it?
(They'll move by a car from now.)
It's getting a bit boring, right?
We'll give you a mission where you can win additional fees.
Additional fees? We don't have to pay to play, right?
- You'll compete with each other. - Okay.
We'll compete with each other? That'd be weird.
I'm ready for anything.
I'll give you a quiz on Indonesia.
- On Indonesia? - If you say the right answer,
you'll get five dollars.
- Five dollars? Okay. - Okay.
Here goes the question.
In Indonesia,
you should not touch a certain body part of a child.
- Which part is it? - What about adults?
(Thinking)
Let me answer. Are there options?
No, there aren't.
- Let me answer. - I was faster.
The head.
(Which part of a child's body should you not touch in Indonesia?)
- The head? - Yes, including hair.
- Correct. - Wait.
We'll give you the money later.
Indonesians consider the head sacred.
If you touch someone's head,
they think you're intruding into his or her soul's shelter.
- You knew the answer? - Yes.
- You're lying. - I'm serious.
It's even worse to touch the head with your left hand, right?
No. Is that correct?
- Is it true? - If you touch the head...
with your left hand, it's unacceptable.
Exactly.
You should never touch children's heads, thinking they're adorable.
You really knew it.
Anyway, So Min won five dollars for question number 1.
Right.
Here goes the next question.
I'm getting serious. I'm serious.
(The second question)
In Indonesia,
how do girls greet...
each other?
Let me answer.
They pretend they kiss the other on the cheek.
Isn't that the French way?
(Isn't that the French way?)
You're such a know-it-all.
- Correct. - Yes!
What?
They kiss the other on the cheek.
(Kwang Soo wins five dollars.)
I think I've seen it.
- It gave me the chills. - How?
Like this?
(What are you doing?)
It's called cipika cipiki.
- Cipika? - Cipika?
- Cipika. - Cipika cipiki.
- Cipika cipiki. - Cipika cipiki.
What about between a guy and a girl?
(I'm suddenly curious.)
- They don't do it. - That's what...
they'll decide by themselves.
I'm just curious.
The next question is about a gesture.
I'll make a certain gesture.
Guess what it means in Indonesia.
Here we go.
(What does this gesture mean in Indonesia?)
Let me answer.
You're stopping your sweat...
from going into your eyes.
Stopping your sweat from going into your eyes?
- Wrong. - Why do you know so much?
It must have been close.
- It wasn't close at all. - No.
- He was just teasing me. - Did you make a deal?
(What does this gesture mean in Indonesia?)
"Stop it."
- Wrong. - Let me answer.
(Wrong)
Go to the left.
(Go to the left.)
Wrong.
Let me answer. "Don't come here."
- Wrong. - "I'm drunk."
"You're stupid."
It doesn't have a good meaning.
Let me answer.
"Get lost."
- I was going to say that too. - Wrong.
I thought the same.
It doesn't have a good meaning?
In Korea, we do this.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
No.
"You're nuts."
Please use proper words.
- Let me answer. "A crazy person". - "A crazy girl".
- "A crazy person". - "A crazy girl".
The correct answer is, "A crazy person".
(Kwang Soo wins 5 dollars.)
You have to say, "Let me answer" first.
The producer...
didn't say you could answer.
I was faster.
- Why did you let him cheat? - Cheat?
You took the money without permission too.
You didn't have the permission.
But I gave you my stuff.
Do you expect me to do everything your way?
How much do you expect me to give up?
Can't you be more generous?
(They're arguing like real siblings.)
You're going to Australia with me.
(You're going to the crocodile cage.)
(You're a crazy person.)
(They touch each other's head with their left hands.)
(They insult each other in the Indonesian way.)
You're both out of your mind.
- You two are crazy. - But you're cute together.
Here goes the second mission.
It's pretty simple.
It's Kwang Soo's favorite, roulette.
What's my favorite?
Both of you will spin two wheels.
The 1st wheel has numbers 1 to 8 on it.
The other one has plus and minus signs on it.
The numbers determine how much you will get.
If I get a minus sign, do I lose money?
- We'll take it away. - And...
you can even end up with a minus amount, right?
(So Min gives it a try.)
I should pick a good number.
The number is not important.
1, 2, 3.
It doesn't make any sound.
- What's that? - On the way here,
- Is it broken? - it broke.
Aren't you supposed to throw a dart?
It won't stop spinning.
(Which number will So Min get?)
- It's a 6. - It's a 6.
- 60 dollars. - 60 dollars.
I hope I get a plus sign.
(As she got a big number, she has to get a plus sign.)
(If she gets a plus sign, she'll have more money than Kwang Soo.)
That's the sound it should make.
(Will So Min get plus 6 or minus 6?)
- It's a plus sign. - Oh, my.
(Plus 6)
I'm getting 60 dollars.
Did you see? Please capture this. I'm getting 60 dollars.
You're getting 60 dollars.
I knew it.
- I'm so lucky. - So Min...
has won 100 dollars in this car.
I won 100 dollars.
(So Min won 100 dollars in the car alone.)
It's Kwang Soo's turn now.
Let me hold it for you.
I'm already ahead of her.
Kwang Soo is ahead of So Min.
(The roulette can turn the situation around.)
(Will Kwang Soo be able to maintain the first place?)
I'm getting dizzy.
(The result is out.)
It's an eight.
- It's a 1. - It's a 1?
It's 10 dollars.
It's a one.
(Kwang Soo got the smallest number.)
Will it be a plus sign or a minus sign?
It won't make a big difference. Take it easy.
Start.
Is this even worth anything?
(Does it matter if he gets plus or minus?)
- You never know. - I'm neither happy nor sad.
I'll spin it.
(It's still better to get a plus.)
(Would he win or lose 10 dollars?)
(It's a minus.)
It's a minus.
He got a minus.
I turned it around.
I turned it around completely.
- Kwang Soo is so bad. - He got minus 8.
All the roulettes...
What if you spin it again,
and if you get a plus, you can take 20 dollars.
If you get a minus, you lose 20 dollars.
- Just plus or minus? Not this? - No.
What if you spin the plus or minus,
and if you get a minus, you lose the 15 dollars you won.
- You'll lose everything. - You'll get zero dollars.
- But if you win... - You'll get 20 dollars.
If you get a plus, you get 20 dollars.
Okay.
(He can win 20 dollars if he gets a plus.)
Good luck.
I hope you're happy.
(He spins it as best as he can.)
Please.
(If it's a plus, he gets 20 dollars. If it's a minus, he gets 0.)
- Okay. - What will it be?
This is the question.
- It's a minus. - I remember now.
- I don't remember. - He is...
- really unlucky. - He is, right?
Please come forward, and take the truth or false cards.
- You didn't know the question. - You remember, right?
Yes, I remember.
(Who will tell the truth, and who will lie?)
Gosh.
I can't trust them.
I'm going to look at their eyes.
I'll tell you exactly what happened.
Kwang Soo is usually unlucky,
but sometimes, he gets lucky in the beginning.
- Right, right. - He got a plus and won the money.
(So Min claims that Kwang Soo got a plus and won the money.)
That's right.
- Let me tell you this. - Kwang Soo did.
- So Min is convincing. - She's calm.
I had much more money than her.
I started with 100 dollars, and she had 50.
In the end...
I can say the result, right?
It doesn't matter.
In the end, I lost.
(In the end, I lost.)
She overtook me.
(Kwang Soo claims he got a minus, and So Min overtook him.)
That wasn't the only game.
- There were games after this. - There were, right?
-That's right, So Min. - There weren't games like this.
I don't have much to say about this.
It's either a plus or minus.
Excuse me, but are you listening to the radio?
(Excuse me, but are you listening to the radio?)
What are you doing?
Can you lower the volume?
- I don't really know him. - I thought this was free time.
I'm still debating.
- You're listening. - Right.
I lost most of my money here.
You punk.
(You punk)
Stop lying. Tell the truth.
(What punk?)
(Stop lying. Tell the truth.)
I was watching you.
Who are you, mister?
Who are you?
Punk, I was watching you. Stop lying.
- You punk. - You punk.
Kwang Soo.
You're telling the truth.
(Kwang Soo, you're telling the truth.)
Thank you. I'm serious.
Again?
(Nobody believes him, but Jong Kook does.)
You're indeed Justice Kook.
If you're lying, you're in trouble.
- Please give us some advice. - What's this about?
So Min suggested this game.
He lost, so he asked So Min to play another round.
That's why there were other games after this.
- No. - Mister.
I've been watching you.
- If you think... - Excuse me.
Keep watching me then.
- Don't say anything. Just watch. - All right.
Sure.
- You're right. - You were watching me.
- Why would you speak now? - That's true.
I'm telling you everything.
- Whatever situation... - Kwang Soo.
I'm being honest.
- He doesn't look confident. - He's sweating.
No, it's oil.
Listen to me. I'm serious.
I started going downhill...
Stop it, you punk.
You punk.
(Kwang Soo explodes.)
I let you go a few times.
- Fine. - Do you want to be handcuffed?
I think you are right.
- I am. - Give me a vote.
Please give me a vote. I'm certain.
All right.
We won't be using these cards for this round.
We'll decide using the Car of Truth.
(They'll decide using the Car of Truth.)
- Car of Truth? - In the parking lot,
there are two buses with Kwang Soo and So Min's names on them.
Please get on the bus of the person you think is telling the truth.
However,
the penalty for this round is a very scary ride.
(If you make the wrong choice, you get a scary penalty.)
(The staff members already tried it out.)
(They couldn't recover from it.)
Let's end this here.
Oh, my goodness. I don't like rides.
This is so difficult.
Please make up your minds.
Let's move to the Car of Truth.
(If you want to avoid the penalty, you must get on the Car of Truth.)
(It's time to choose.)
Come here, everybody.
Please come.
- Jeon So Min. - I'm serious.
- Jeon So Min. - I think you know.
- I'm truthful. - Truth gets told,
and justice wins.
I think So Min is lying.
That's what I thought from the beginning.
I lost in the end.
I was ahead of her by 50 dollars, but I lost.
Remember the first time.
Kwang Soo is really good at lying now.
I'm serious.
- You punk. - There he goes again.
What?
If you're lying, I won't leave you alone.
Is he a mental patient?
- What is wrong with you? - I won't leave you alone.
Jae Seok, trust me this time. I'm telling the truth.
I think it's So Min.
(Ji Hyo uses her instincts.)
- Okay. - Really.
I'm serious, Haha.
Okay.
You have to go on the ride.
I'm serious.
Se Chan.
Please trust me this time.
Haha, let's go.
Haha.
- Go away, you liar. - It's over.
Once you get on, it's over.
It'll most likely be you.
- Hold on. - He usually doesn't talk a lot.
He doesn't talk a lot.
When he's lying...
I know we're going on the Nevis Swing together,
but don't try to control me.
Follow me, Haha.
You're a coward.
- Hold on. - Follow me.
- You're going to get on, right? - Where are you going to go?
- I don't know yet. - Don't regret it. He's wrong.
I'm honest.
Let's see how this looks.
(He peeks into So Min's bus.)
I'm here,
- your younger brother. - All right.
- Se Chan. - Yes, brother.
Think about how terrible you felt when you lost to Kwang Soo.
- Right. - Think about it.
Even if we get lied to,
- it's better to let So Min fool us. - I agree.
I'll get on this bus.
Do I have no credibility?
No, this is better.
This is so unfair.
Am I not credible?
I can't believe Haha went there.
Are you still debating, Ji Hyo?
No, I think it's Kwang Soo.
If Ji Hyo gets this right,
I feel sorry for your previous boyfriends.
(You can never lie to her.)
They can't lie to you at all.
- She knows everything. - She's good at this.
- Somebody's coming. - Seok Jin.
(She touts them with prizes.)
- Okay. - Look at this.
- Seok Jin. - I have low energy.
Enjoy the ride.
- Enjoy the ride. - I'll drink it up.
- Ji Hyo. - Watch her.
I wish you luck.
I'm so tired these days because I'm babysitting.
- Have one. - It's ginseng.
(They love the free gifts.)
(Gulping)
- This is sweet. - It's good.
- It's the pure extract. - It's good.
I like this.
Thank you. Oh, really?
- The bus can't leave. Come. - Me?
It's time to go. Why aren't you coming?
What do you mean?
- That wasn't the plan. - He told me something.
I'm certain.
- Why are you trying to take me? - Don't go.
- Seok Jin, why do you think so? - We took a vote,
and you're the most gullible one from here.
(He's so gullible.)
- Seok Jin. - Why do you think so?
Seok Jin, that bus is cooler.
(It's at least cooler.)
(He gets up without a second thought.)
Let go.
- It's so hot here. - Focus.
- It's so hot here. - Focus. Focus!
- Seok Jin. - He doesn't care.
You'll be punished for sure.
You'll be punished.
Okay.
(I don't like the heat.)
- Who is it? - It's Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - All right.
- Isn't it cooler here? - It's So Min.
- Okay. - It's a lot cooler here, right?
- Good job. - Why aren't they coming here?
- Good job. - Let's go.
(How will Kwang Soo and So Min defend themselves?)
As long as more people don't come here...
Aren't you certain though?
- I'm not. - I'm not.
- Look at this situation. - This is the strange thing, Ji Hyo.
Let's do the opposite of Jae Seok.
- For sure. - Let's do that.
You have to ride the Navy Swing anyway. Do you want this too?
(You have to ride the Navy Swing anyway.)
Isn't it the Nevis Swing?
Is it? Nevis Swing.
(It's the same thing.)
I'm telling the truth.
(If Kwang Soo's claim is a lie, they both get punished.)
This is the truth.
I think So Min...
She didn't act like it was unfair.
She looked like she was pulling our legs.
- I think... - That's why.
I see her motive in wanting to take the members.
(Is So Min's plea a lie?)
We have a lie detector ready if you need it.
The one you put your hand on?
I can do it.
- Should we try it? - I can do it.
(They bring in a special equipment.)
Put your hand on this.
(It's a lie detector.)
- All right. - Your hands are sweaty.
- So Min. - Yes.
- Is this a lie or not? - It's not.
It's the truth.
- Are you certain? - I am.
(She says she's not lying.)
(What will their special equipment make out?)
I am.
(Zapping)
That stings.
No.
Can we change our minds?
- Gosh. - Hold on.
This made me lose trust in you.
I'm telling the truth.
Wait. This is saying she's lying.
They're both actors,
so they're great at acting. They'll always trick us.
I can't act without a script.
- What do you mean? - I can't do it on the spot.
- Put your hand on this. - Ad-libbing?
Try it again.
I can't act without a script.
This is not acting. This is for real.
- Are you sure? - This is the truth.
Should we trust her?
I'm getting anxious.
I'm telling the truth.
- Are you certain? - I am.
(Will it be true this time?)
(It's the truth.)
It's fine. Please take this away.
We'll trust So Min.
Hold on. Why was she...
- so surprised? - I know, right?
(Was she surprised...)
(that it was deemed to be true?)
Why was she shocked by the result?
No, I thought it was going to be a lie.
- You never know. - If she was telling the truth,
she would have been like, "Right?"
But she was surprised. That's strange.
Listen to the way she said it.
If she was lying,
she would have breathed in while saying that.
But she breathed out.
There's such thing.
I think she's telling the truth.
Wait.
- He's just... - There's such thing?
- guessing today. - There is.
If somebody else said that, you would have disagreed.
- Her exclamation... - Am I not right?
She was surprised that this was right.
- That's what she meant. - Are you sure?
Of course, I am.
We're not doubting her anymore after what Jong Kook said.
He's so convincing.
- Do you want to try it? - No, I'm scared of it.
- Why? - It scares me.
Try it.
- Try it. - Put your hand on it.
(Seok Jin becomes a subject to verify the special equipment.)
- Why are you ramping it up? - I'm not.
Ask me a question. I'm getting sweaty.
Wait. Do you have...
a question for him?
That burns.
He's full of lies.
- That burns. - I didn't even ask a question.
He's a liar.
He's a liar himself.
The lie detector is confusing us.
This is confusing us more.
Can we try this on Kwang Soo?
They're probably doing it.
They probably are.
I'll answer truthfully to your questions.
"I'm lying right now."
No.
(He says no.)
I'm confident.
(What does the lie detector think?)
I got a minus. Look.
(It thinks he's telling the truth.)
"I'm lying right now."
I'm confident.
No.
I'm telling the truth.
(He gets asked the same question.)
(Zapping)
(It's a lie.)
(Were you lying, Kwang Soo?)
You punk, you can lie to us one time...
- but not twice. - You can't lie to us twice.
The culprit always returns to the scene of the crime.
I'm telling the truth.
Please give me another chance.
"When I went to Indonesia,"
"I went into So Min's room."
I didn't.
(He says no.)
I don't know why I should be doing this.
"I went into So Min's room." Yes or no.
- No. - No? Are you sure?
Why should I be doing this?
(He says no again.)
This is how truthful...
(It's true again.)
Then,
"So Min came into my room." Yes or no.
No.
(He says she didn't come into his room.)
(Zapping)
(It's a downright lie.)
I was thinking.
She came when we were filming.
- She came. I'm right. - My gosh.
I know this sounds weird,
but she came to film.
I'm being honest. This is a malfunction.
Please give it back.
You can't just take it back.
What does that make me?
(It leaves many questions behind.)
Can you give me that?
- Let's see how you usually are. - Is this what they used?
Spin it three times.
I don't know.
Spin it like how you did before.
This is how it felt like.
(It's the same roulette Kwang Soo said he got a minus on.)
See? You get lucky sometimes too.
Try it again.
If you get a plus, you are done.
See? It works.
- He can get a plus. - What's going on?
(The third spin)
See? He got a plus all three times.
This is so interesting.
A lie detector? A roulette?
- That's how it seems. - He doesn't have to...
get minuses all the time.
He got pluses all three times.
It always goes the opposite.
That's the strange thing. It gives me goosebumps,
but I got a minus last time.
Please prove yourself. Spin it for the last time.
Today's a weird day for me.
(If you're telling the truth, prove yourself.)
(The last spin...)
(is a plus again.)
See?
- Who am I supposed to trust? - Fine.
This might seem weird.
It was weird that I got four pluses in a row.
However, that day...
(Why is Kwang Soo getting lucky all of a sudden?)
What am I supposed to do?
I did get a minus. How am I supposed to prove it?
This is what happened today, and it was different last time.
(What is he saying?)
Okay. It's strange.
- What is he saying? - I know it's strange.
"What am I supposed to do?"
(Is it Kwang Soo or So Min who's telling the truth?)
I'm being honest.
(This is where the truth will be revealed.)
Why are we going bungee jumping?
- No way. - I won't do it.
- We won't do it. - We can't.
We can't bungee jump.
- We can't. - It's the one that springs up.
- Is it zip lining? - Seok Jin and I did it before.
- This is it. - That's right.
I don't like bungee jumping, but I don't like this either.
This is driving me nuts.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I keep saying this,
but this made me wet myself a little bit.
What am I supposed to do about the Nevis Swing?
- Stop it, Haha. - Gosh.
Stop it.
Stop talking about the Nevis Swing.
I'd rather become their honorary ambassador.
It's a slingshot.
- Have you decided? - Yes.
I'm telling the truth.
I believe...
- the pieces of the puzzle... - Were you telling me the truth?
came together on the bus.
I don't know about these two.
Please make your final decisions.
If you think it was a minus, please pick Kwang Soo.
If you think it was a plus, please pick So Min.
Please decide.
(If it was a plus, you need to pick So Min.)
One,
two...
(The person with more votes gets the penalty exemption.)
(What will the 6 members say?)
- Three. - I have no idea.
(It's 3 on 3.)
- It's 3 on 3. - It's a tie.
- Seok Jin... - That means Kwang Soo...
has to go on.
Really? Why?
If there's a tie,
Kwang Soo has to go on.
He lost in the Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game.
Let me reveal the answer.
I don't know about this.
I hope you're happy.
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and Se Chan picked plus.)
Please. Let it be a minus.
Please.
(Was it a plus or minus?)
(It's a minus.)
It doesn't work for you.
- It's a minus. - It is.
- It's a minus. - It's a minus.
(Seok Jin, Haha, and Ji Hyo get the penalty exemption.)
You were telling the truth.
Didn't we win? We guessed it right.
See?
- So Min. - Where did she go?
- So Min. - My gosh.
So Min, this won't do.
I won't trust her anymore.
Remember what I said?
(It's so unfair for him.)
Please come forward.
You must convince the members according to what your card says.
Your goal is to get as many on your side as possible.
(He was supposed to tell the truth,)
(and he spun it the same way he did in Indonesia.)
See? It works.
See? He got a plus all three times.
See?
(He got pluses four times in a row.)
This might seem weird.
What am I supposed to do? How am I supposed to prove it?
This is what happened today, and it was different last time.
(You should've been honest beforehand.)
There are four members who got selected.
So Min, come on.
Only 2 out of 4 will go on the ride.
- Okay. - Okay.
We prepared some rice cakes.
2 are filled with honey, and 2 are wasabi.
I can't do this.
Gosh.
(2 are honey-filled rice cakes, and 2 are wasabi.)
I think this is honey, Jae Seok.
- Be quiet. - Go away.
(It's all thanks to you that we are doing this.)
The unlucky members can choose first.
- Kwang Soo, choose. - He is right.
It will be funny if the ones Jong Kook and Se Chan didn't pick...
- contain wasabi. - That's right.
- Hurry up. - That's why we will pick first.
- We will try our luck. - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
- I pick this one. - Okay.
We really are unlucky.
(Kwang Soo picks the rice cake Jae Seok wanted to pick.)
- He chose the heavy one. - I had a good feeling about it.
I felt an affinity...
- the moment I laid my eyes on it. - I bet you like that one.
- I knew it. - I like this one.
- I like this one. - I did, too.
- I will pick this one. - Okay. That's good.
(They finish choosing the rice cake.)
What's inside?
How did the unlucky members do?
- Shall we go? - I hope mine contains honey.
(It's time to choose who will go on the slingshot.)
(The one with wasabi rice cake are the lucky winners.)
(Which 2 members were chosen by wasabi rice cake?)
- In 2, 3. - Wasabi will hit them hard.
(They put rice cake in their mouths at the same time.)
Wasabi will hit them hard.
It hit Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok is enduring it. - That's right.
(My goodness.)
Does mine contain honey?
It hit Se Chan.
- It hit Se Chan. - It hit Se Chan.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan eat wasabi rice cake.)
It's Jae Seok and Se Chan.
Are they okay?
Is it sweet? How does it taste?
- It's Se Chan. - It's Se Chan.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan are chosen to go on the slingshot.)
Se Chan is struggling.
(Jae Seok pretends like it isn't him.)
Jae Seok, you will die if you eat it.
(Don't pretend like yours isn't wasabi rice cake.)
- Look at him. - Gosh, I can smell it.
Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok. - Brush your teeth.
You have wasabi on your front teeth.
(Wasabi colors his teeth green.)
I can smell wasabi from here.
Doesn't it make your teeth tingle?
(With the taste of wasabi in their mouths,)
(Jae Seok and Se Chan board the slingshot.)
How should we position our heads?
- My goodness. - This is happening for real.
They're pulling the ropes now, right?
Make it tight like a slingshot.
I am so scared.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
(The slingshot is ready to be launched.)
- I am already scared. - Wait a minute.
- Wait a minute. - My goodness.
Please stop. Please stop.
(Please stop going up.)
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute. - My goodness.
Se Chan, I feel like I am going to die.
- Seriously. - My goodness.
- Seriously. - Give us a sign.
My goodness.
- Give us a sign. - I am so scared.
(They are ready to go.)
Get ready.
- In 1, 2. - In 1, 2.
(Get ready.)
- 3. - 3.
(Shoot.)
(They are shot into the air.)
(The shock pushes the camera down to his face.)
(It gets a close look at Jae Seok's face.)
(They use their head voices.)
(He is using his face incredibly well.)
My goodness.
(The sight is enough to send chills down their spines.)
(I am sorry, but I love you.)
(It's never-ending.)
(Please save us.)
(Are they scared...)
(or excited?)
(Perhaps it's both.)
Please get us down.
Jae Seok, look far ahead.
- You do that. - Look far ahead.
Look far ahead.
(With much shouting, the 2nd round of Truth Game ends.)
(Next week)
(Things become more intense.)
(Scary penalties await them.)
(It's more thrilling.)
(Indonesia Manual Wooden Cable Car)
(Is there another penalty?)
(Running Man gives back to its viewers with a live broadcast.)
(Next Sunday at 4:50pm)