(A winter night before Christmas)
(The members of Running Man arrive at a mysterious place on a van.)
(However, )
(why are they wearing blindfolds?)
Why are we wearing blindfolds?
Why are we wearing them? Where could we be going?
I'm curious too. Did they prepare something for us?
When they blindfold us, they usually take us to prison or something.
- Prison? - We're not headed to a good place.
They don't usually blindfold us from the start.
It must be a surprise.
- Where are we going? - Is it like the last supper?
(At that time, the bus stops in the middle of the darkness.)
- Will we gather and play games? - I guess we have arrived.
- You'll get off one by one. - Are all of us getting off?
- Why are we exiting one by one? - But we can't see.
I hope it's something good.
(The members are being isolated.)
Thank you.
I can't see at all.
My gosh, it's freezing.
- Seriously. I can't see anything. - Watch out.
There's a tree.
Isn't this a Christmas Special? Wait. What is it?
What just happened to my voice? I think we're inside a building.
Do we go up?
We keep going up.
(They enter a school.)
I feel dizzy because I keep going up.
(With their eyes covered, the members go up one by one.)
- Do I walk forward? - Yes.
I am scared.
Se Chan, will you throw up again?
(He remembers what happened at Nevis Swing.)
What is this?
(They enter a narrow place.)
We're going into a small space.
(They enter a narrow place at the end of the staircase.)
Where are we?
What is this?
Is this an attic?
Where are we going?
(They enter an attic-like place.)
- Is that you, Haha? - Yes, it's me.
Come here carefully.
Where are you, So Min?
Everyone,
please remove your blindfold at the count of three.
(Please remove your blindfold at the count of three.)
Perhaps you will make us shed tears.
- Is this a guerrilla concert? - Okay, everyone...
(Is this a guerrilla concert to celebrate Christmas?)
(If not...)
Please remove your blindfold.
(Is this a Christmas nightmare?)
Do we take it off?
(What awaits them?)
(It's a Christmas feast.)
I was right.
(It's for the members who worked hard for a year.)
- Look at this. - What is this?
- I said it might be a feast. - What is this?
This is incredible.
(There are presents under the twinkling tree.)
(Welcome to Running Man's Christmas Party.)
- Are you serious? - I was right.
- How did you know from the smell? - What is this?
(What a surprise!)
- I am touched. - What has gotten into the crew?
Are you serious?
Can we eat this?
To celebrate Christmas,
- we prepared a Christmas miracle. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Is it tasty?
- I want to eat that one. - Who knew this day would come?
Everyone, merry Christmas.
(Everyone, merry Christmas.)
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
Christmas is...
just another day in December.
(Christmas is a just the 25th of December.)
He is ruining the mood as soon as the party started.
- I should eat quickly and go. - I should eat quickly and go.
Gosh, what a killjoy!
This is why I didn't want to come to this party.
- For goodness' sake. - It's tasty.
I love Chuseok and Christmas.
Why do you like them?
I like the festive atmosphere.
(I like the festive atmosphere.)
(Christmas puts lights on the street and love on the face.)
I like the festive atmosphere.
- You don't go out. You stay home. - You got me.
(You know that I am a homebody.)
You stay home.
- Still, they play movies. - Special movies for the holiday.
We get to see Macaulay Culkin.
- "Home Alone". - "Home Alone".
He is a mischief-maker.
Macaulay Culkin is...
an alcoholic now.
- He must be Kwang Soo's age. - That's right.
This feels strange.
What's wrong?
(He suddenly coughs.)
What's the matter?
- What's wrong? - He has a cold.
You know,
Jong Kook takes care of his body the most.
He is the sickest in winter.
(He is the preacher of health.)
- His body is like glass. - Why does he even work out?
I know that it's winter when Jong Kook catches a cold.
He doesn't turn on the air conditioner in the summer...
in order to avoid getting sick.
What are those presents? Do we get those presents?
When do we get them?
I want one. I want a drone.
I want a video game console.
If I win a drone,
I will always fly it above me.
You should take the head deodorizer.
(You don't need a drone.)
(It's a present that targets Seok Jin and So Min, )
(who suffer due to their smelly heads.)
I was so surprised.
It's what I smelled, right?
- I was so surprised. - It's what I smelled, right?
(Perfume spray that eliminates the head odor is ready.)
- Seriously. - It's for Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin's head... - It smells like flesh.
His head smells rotten.
- You are done eating, right? - Yes.
This is tasty.
(The merry feast ends.)
What?
The chefs are dressed up as Santas.
Merry Christmas.
(Merry Christmas!)
- These are presents. - What is this?
We brought objects with Christmas-related memories.
(What are the presents?)
- Memories. - They asked us to bring them.
(The objects with Christmas-related memories)
- We... - What is this?
These objects are related to Christmas.
(What is this object?)
Kwang Soo,
- for goodness' sake. - Kwang Soo.
For goodness' sake.
- You... - Why?
(The silhouette is similar to Dan Bi, )
(Kwang Soo's object of memory and soulmate.)
He always brings stuffed animals!
- You brought a giraffe again. - It's not a giraffe.
It has to be a giraffe.
- It has to be a giraffe. - It's not a giraffe.
There is no way it's anything else.
- It really isn't a giraffe. - It will be revealed soon.
- For goodness' sake. - I think...
To celebrate Christmas,
we prepared a Christmas miracle.
A Christmas miracle sounds cool.
Each member brought...
an object that contains Christmas-related memories.
- Yes. - Yes.
When one member reveals the memory,
other members will judge it by excellent, fair, and poor signs.
It will decide the present.
The members' judgment...
will activate a Christmas miracle...
and transform your memory into a present.
I need a coffee machine.
If we rate each other well,
we can take the good presents.
- Let's rate each other well. - In that case,
- I want a pillow. - Okay.
I want a video game console.
- I want an electric scooter. - I want a tablet computer.
Remember that it's Christmas.
I want an electric scooter.
An eye massager sounds nice.
- So Min, do you want to go first? - Shall we do that?
It was hard.
Since you told me to bring a Christmas-related memory,
I went over my old letters.
Letters are interesting.
- So Min has a lot of those. - She has a lot of those.
I am jealous of her.
I am the type of person who throws away old letters.
This is a Christmas card I received...
from a friend who goes back 20 years.
This is a pop-up card I made.
Watch carefully.
- Ta-da. - How did you make that?
Did you make that?
(It's a Christmas card So Min made when she was young.)
- Did you make that? - Yes.
I made it in fifth grade.
- I can't believe she still has it. - It's fascinating.
It dates back 20 years.
- You kept a card from a friend. - Yes.
May I read it?
She did my homework a lot in middle school.
She must have put a lot of effort into this card.
- It's handmade. - Yes.
Let's read it.
"To So Min. Hello, So Min. I am Na Rae."
"Winter break and Christmas are fast approaching."
"Have a fruitful winter break and a merry Christmas."
"Receive a lot of presents from Santa."
- What is this? - E 10,000.
It was popular to write "Stop" this way.
- E 10,000. - It sounds like "Stop".
(I will stop here.)
It was popular back then.
If you make an error, you crossed it out and write, "Under construction".
That's right. "Under construction".
- Really? - Yes.
- Did you do that? - Yes.
You cherish your memories.
This is a pop-up card I made.
When did you make it?
I made it in 1997.
It was right before the IMF Crisis.
- 1997. - "Mom, it's my."
"It's me."
You still made spelling mistakes at this age?
"Mom, it's my."
"I am your trustworthy and lovely daughter."
"Pat me on the head when you see this card, okay?"
"Merry Christmas."
So Min has a cute side.
The date is December 19th, 1997.
December 19th.
It would be really scary...
if So Min made it yesterday.
(If that's the case...)
- Kwang Soo. - Listen.
- It's a possibility. - Stop it.
What would be scarier is this.
So Min still doesn't know how to spell.
- You're right. - That's really scary.
That would be scary.
It's a card with many twists.
(The truth is beyond them.)
It's time to judge it.
Take a look at the pop-up card.
(This deserves "Excellent".)
- I made up my mind. - Everyone grabbed "Excellent".
It's time to give her a score.
(Thanks to the pop-up card, most of them reach for "Excellent".)
In 1, 2, 3.
(What's the value of So Min's Christmas memory?)
(Excellent)
Merry Christmas!
(This is a miracle.)
This is amazing!
We couldn't help it.
So Min, if you choose a present from the Excellent pile,
we will put a sticker on it.
Does she get a present right away?
Right away?
I want a coffee machine.
- Okay. - A coffee machine.
The coffee machine is mine.
That's why he gave her "Fair".
(He really wants the coffee machine.)
Seok Jin is scary.
He did it to take the coffee machine.
The coffee machine is mine.
(I swear I will take it from her.)
It warms my heart.
Let's take a look at what Seok Jin brought.
To be honest,
I have been married for 18 years.
Since we moved nine times,
we don't have anything like this.
I was really flustered...
that I didn't have any objects of memories...
such as cards or gifts.
- Things like this. - Seok Jin told me this...
over the phone the day before yesterday.
"Which object should I bring?"
"I don't have anything either." "What will you do?"
"I will make something up."
(I have no other choice.)
- Stop lying. - It's not like that.
- It's not like that. - Why did you put on an act?
It's not like that.
Listen. After I told him that,
I thought for a while and remembered something.
Since it's a secret...
my wife and I share, I wasn't sure if I should reveal it.
He will reveal a family secret.
I wasn't sure if I should reveal it.
However, I have no other choice. There is nothing else.
In relation to Christmas,
my wife and I have a secret.
What is it?
- You will reveal it. - Yes.
Yes. It's true.
(It's funny to him.)
- What is going on? - There he goes again.
There he goes again.
I will tell you.
I am embarrassed...
to talk about this.
What is it? He is acting strange.
People wash each other's feet...
- to wash away the past. - Yes.
We thought we'd go even further...
and do this for each other.
- Was it waxing? - No.
(Was it waxing?)
(No!)
- What was it then? - Hey.
What does a foot bath have to do with waxing?
Is this considered beautiful?
He seemed shy.
No, that wasn't it.
We scrubbed each other's feet.
(He takes out a foot exfoliator.)
(They burst into a laughter.)
(Seok Jin's Christmas memento is a foot exfoliator.)
Is that all you could think of?
There's something here. I think it's dead skin.
- Here. - No, there are not.
I couldn't bring the old one, so I brought a brand new one.
By the way, is it true?
It's true.
Let's listen to his story. Tell us about it.
How can you not trust me?
It was Christmas, and we...
I am sorry, but can we call her right now?
(He can't believe Seok Jin.)
She's unwell right now.
Come on, Seok Jin.
- Don't go that far. - Come on.
Her body temperature was 38°C, so I told her to go see a doctor.
- 38°C? - Yes. It went up that high.
Actually, when you wash a foot...
Once I got really emotional.
Her feet used to be really pretty.
I was washing her feet.
And her skin was rough.
(He realized that her skin had become rough.)
I wondered what happened. Did she have a corn?
It turned out...
(He becomes emotional.)
What is it?
Why does he take the glasses off when there are no glasses on them?
It turned out she...
He was faking it.
(He's embarrassed.)
It turned out she's been going to markets barefoot.
(What?)
- You're a liar. - Barefoot?
Your wife did that?
- Is she like Lee Eun Mi? - Wait.
Is she the Barefoot Diva too?
She has calluses because she does Latin dance.
(Jae Seok knows the real reason.)
It's because she doesn't wear socks.
She does Latin dance.
- Of course she likes samba. - I know.
Her skin was so rough.
Looking at it, I cried...
(Her rough skin made him very emotional.)
my heart out.
Did she really go to markets barefoot?
- Wait. - It doesn't make sense.
- That's scary, you know? - That's horrifying.
Take her to a doctor.
(The thought of his wife going shopping barefoot is scary.)
Perhaps she had her reasons for going shopping barefoot.
And there's another one.
(He reveals the second memento.)
It's a letter.
It's a letter of apology.
That's...
- It's a letter of apology. - When did you write it?
I didn't write it. My child wrote it.
My child did.
Did you bring whatever you could find?
Perhaps you just woke him up...
Perhaps you woke up him yesterday and made him write it.
- Wait. - Is it related to Christmas?
Of course it is.
- He wrote it when he was little. - Can I see it?
- Can I see it? - I can't reveal the content.
(He can't reveal the content of the letter.)
- What? - What are you doing?
- Let's see it. - Why did you bring it then?
- You should read it alone. - Wait.
Don't read it out loud. Read it alone.
It contains something personal.
Right. But there's a carnation here.
I think this was for Parents' Day.
(It wasn't for Christmas.)
- Wait. - This was for Parents' Day.
No. Wait.
- Wait. - Give it to me.
- It's... - That's not it.
This must've been the only paper he had.
It is related to Christmas.
- Can I read it then? - Yes.
"Mom and Dad."
"Mom, I sometimes talk back to you, but I won't do that now."
"I will be polite from now on."
"And if I am born again, I want to be born as your son again."
- "I love you." - Right.
This was written on May 2.
(It's right before the Parents' Day.)
- Hey. - It's written right here.
- Why does he lie so much? - Stop it.
- It says "May 2" here. - I folded it.
Why would you fold this part?
Merry Christmas.
Wait.
My family looks at this on Christmas.
1, 2, 3.
(Seok Jin gets "poor".)
Okay. I won't forget this.
(I will get my revenge.)
You won a portable cell phone power bank.
- Let's check Ji Hyo's. It's big. - You see,
Santa used to be very important to me.
Until I was in Grade Four, I believed in Santa.
- It lasted long. - I brought a doll...
I really wanted to get from Santa...
- It's a plastic doll. - when I was little.
- I brought a plastic doll. - It's lovely.
Didn't Santa give it to you?
- I have it. - I love it.
I was waiting for Santa with so much excitement.
I wanted this so badly.
(She really wanted this doll.)
(Little Ji Hyo waited all night long for Santa.)
The next-door neighbor...
Next-door neighbor?
I saw him leaving this outside my house.
That really hurt me.
And at that moment I realized that there is no Santa.
I brought this as a reminder of that memory.
This is my memento.
- You remembered it. - You believed in Santa...
- until Grade Four. - It's...
the story about how she learned the truth.
- Santa... - It's not bad.
Until when did you believe in Santa?
I learned the truth a little early.
- But I used it. - I did too.
I prayed out loud.
- I prayed for what I want. - Right.
I said out loud what I want.
Actually,
I used it until I entered middle school.
What?
- Middle school? - It's because...
Isn't that too much?
Isn't that too old?
He's the type of person who would go to a women's...
bath house pretending he's innocent. Isn't he?
- No. No. - Until when did you do it?
Until when did you go to public bath houses with your mom?
I don't remember it clearly.
Perhaps he was a high school freshman.
What are you saying?
Come on.
- Don't be ridiculous. - High school freshman.
That's...
High school freshman.
My goodness.
- He would've pretended to be naive. - "Hello."
Right. Right.
That's horrible.
It's Ji Hyo's turn. 1, 2, 3.
"Fair". It's "Fair".
(Ji Hyo's Christmas memory gets "fair".)
Thank you.
I want the calf massager.
Jong Kook is next.
- It's Jong Kook's turn. - It's Jong Kook's turn.
Okay. My family doesn't care about Christmas.
- He goes to the gym. He does. - His family, you mean?
Every year, I work out on Christmas.
I spend it alone.
10 years ago, I took my mom to the US,
- and we spent Christmas there. - I see.
I took her to Disneyland.
- That must've been lovely. - Right?
I saw this pretty thing at the entrance of Disneyland.
My mom wanted to buy it too.
So we bought one.
- Is it an egg? - Yes, it is an egg.
By the look of it,
- it doesn't look that appealing. - It doesn't, does it?
You don't want to buy it now.
- It's cute. - We didn't want it at first.
Look.
- It's creepy. - It's adorable.
(There's a baby doll inside an egg.)
It's cute.
It's a baby.
How can a baby come out of an egg? Is he Hyeokgeose of Silla?
It's Hyeokgeose of Las Vegas.
Is it James Hyeokgeose?
(Jong Kook's Christmas memento is born from an egg.)
There's a baby inside the egg.
It's a little creepy.
- It's... - It's scary.
(It's strange.)
Why would you shove him inside that small space?
Touch him. It's really nice.
- It's cute. - It's really cute.
I feel like he's going to open his eyes.
People on social media are trying to...
get Ji Hyo and Jong Kook to date.
There was even an article that we're getting married.
There was an article.
- It's been a year. - It shocked us too.
It shocked us too.
Are we getting married?
(They're asking other people about their future.)
I bet my entire fortune that they're not dating.
(That's how certain he is.)
Can you take his fortune and split up?
That's a good idea.
He doesn't have a lot of assets anyway.
When that happens, his wife will have to go shopping barefoot.
She will...
Right.
- It will actually be true. - You're right.
- Yes. - Yes.
(I will scrub your feet tonight, honey.)
- 1, 2, 3. - It's really nice.
I love this.
3 "excellent", 3 "fair", and 3 poor" makes it "fair".
Thank you.
Why is it "fair"?
- If Kwang Soo gave you... - He should've raised "excellent".
It's a shame.
It's all right. It's not like he's ever helped me...
with anything in my life.
I didn't expect anything.
Why didn't you...
- give him "excellent"? - I don't care.
So Min gave him "poor". Why blame me?
He doesn't care about So Min.
- Did you give him "poor"? - Did you give me "poor"?
Why did you do that?
I want to hear your explanation. Why did you give me "poor"?
It didn't touch me.
(She didn't care about the baby doll.)
It didn't touch you?
(He's upset.)
I think she's a psychopath.
Come on.
Everyone is different.
- There are good gifts. - There are.
- There's Korean beef set. - What should I get?
- Korean beef set is good. - Korean beef set is good.
Korean beef set is amazing.
- Share it with your mom. - I will. I love it.
Next is Haha.
I thought hard about what to bring.
What Christmas memories do I have?
If I was a single man,
I would go to a club and have a good time.
Since I got married and got my own family,
I realized that you are supposed to...
spend your Christmas with your family.
Family is important.
- What is it? - This is...
- You brought a lot of things. - He's got a lot of things.
This is all pieces that Dream drew himself.
Really?
He drew all of these pictures.
I was touched by it.
My mom keeps...
all the things I made or received when I was young.
I want to be like that too.
Last year,
he made...
- Did Dream make it? - a Christmas tree.
- It's cute. - Did Dream make it?
Yes, he just colored it.
His name is written on it.
As soon as I saw it...
(As soon as I saw it...)
What's wrong?
(He's about to cry.)
(His eldest son Dream is his valuable treasure.)
(He made a Christmas tree with his tiny hands.)
I was so happy to be with my family.
We made a Christmas tree together...
- and spent the day laughing. - That sounds nice.
I thought of my family...
and remembered our Christmas together.
It was so much fun last year.
- This is... - What is it?
My father...
loves "Edelweiss" very much.
- It's from "The Sound of Music". - Edelweiss.
(His father's "Edelweiss".)
My father picked a real edelweiss.
- Is it real? - Yes.
- Is that it? - He picked it...
- Wait. - in 1973.
He gave it to me in 2011.
- It's very old. - I wanted...
to have the one that he framed.
- It's interesting. - He gave it to me...
as a Christmas present.
Is it from Liechtenstein?
It was when he was in Germany.
- "An edelweiss for my son". - Yes.
- He made it again. - "2011".
For the three generations...
from my father, me to my son,
we put it next to the tree.
We put the tree that Dream made next to it.
This is how we spend our Christmas.
(His family is ready for Christmas in 2017.)
(Starting with Haha's father...)
(to Haha's son)
(These are memorable treasures to Haha's family.)
- Do you have more? - There's one more.
- Do you have more? - It's unforgettable.
- What is it? - It's the best Christmas gift.
Running Man.
(The best Running Man present)
- I give it the lowest score. - Gosh.
(It deserves the lowest score.)
- Come on. - I give the lowest score.
- Please. - I give the lowest score.
- Seriously. - I'm being sincere.
- The others were good. - I'm being sincere.
- You were doing well. - I'm being sincere.
I liked Dream's tree.
Okay, give him your score in the count of three.
- Three. - Thank you.
"Excellent".
(Haha scores Excellent.)
- I'll give you "Excellent". - Thank you.
- He deserves it. - Thank you.
(Haha wins a game player.)
Next up is Se Chan.
- Here's mine. - Let's listen.
Last Christmas Eve on December 24,
I was on my way to a club with my friends.
I coughed quite loudly.
When I coughed loudly,
my lower back got cramped.
- That could happen. - Yes.
- That's possible. - I hurt my lower back.
On Christmas Eve last year,
they gave me this to protect my back.
It's unforgettable.
Everyone who had lower back surgery has it.
Listen. I talked with Se Chan...
on the phone.
I remember that we talked like Jae Seok and Seok Jin.
- How? - What did we say?
"What will you bring, Se Chan?"
"I can't find anything."
"I have to make something up."
- Is this it? - I couldn't find anything to bring.
No matter how much I searched, I found nothing.
In 1, 2, 3.
- This is a little... - I'm sorry.
- It's thoughtless. - Unfortunately, this is poor.
(Se Chan scores Poor.)
- Yes. - It wasn't impressive.
I'll take the head odor remover.
(He chooses a head odor remover.)
Next up is Kwang Soo. If he brought the giraffe,
- He will immediately get a "Poor". - Let's ignore him.
If it's the giraffe, let's pass him.
(Did he bring Dan Bi again as his item?)
For me,
I don't remember...
being happy and joyous on Christmas.
I was always lonely.
(He always felt lonely.)
Whenever I felt lonely...
What are these legs?
- What are they? - Look at these.
- Take a look. - I knew it.
- Take a look first. - It's obvious.
- Take a look first. - I knew it.
- That's Dan Bi again. - No.
This is what stayed by my side.
Dan Bi?
It's Rudolph Dol Bi.
(It's Rudolph Dol Bi.)
- What? - It's Dol Bi.
(It's Dol Bi instead of Dan Bi.)
It's Dol Bi.
Is he Rudolph?
- This is Rudolph? - Yes.
It fell off.
That's Rudolph?
Are you kidding?
- Are you kidding? - Do you think we're dumb?
- Are you kidding, Kwang Soo? - It's Rudolph.
Dol Bi and Dan Bi look similar.
They're different.
Are you saying that this isn't the same giraffe?
Right. It's Dol Bi.
Is Dan Bi at home?
Yes.
(He tries to play it off.)
Isn't it Dan Bi?
No.
- Take it off. - Hey!
Don't do that to Dol Bi's nose.
Isn't this fake?
What are you doing?
- It's Dan Bi. - Long time no see.
- It's Dan Bi. - It's definitely Dan Bi.
- Get out. - Get out, Kwang Soo.
- Wait. - He deserves no score.
- I have one more. - No way.
- Really? - I have more.
- It's over if you're lying. - I have one more.
What So Min brought last time...
- made me think a lot. - That's great.
(So Min brought a napkin that she used when she broke up.)
It's from my heart. Everyone here knows what happened...
during Entertainment Awards last year.
(Kwang Soo's speech after receiving the Grand Prize)
I was about to cry.
Then...
Do you have something?
(Is it an item that relates to that moving moment?)
I used this tissue to wipe off my tears.
(He used the tissue during the award ceremony.)
(You're such a crook.)
Wait, it's too wet.
- I'm serious. - Forget it.
- What? - One.
- Wait, why? - In 1, 2, 3.
- How can it be so wet? - Come on.
- He gets a "Poor". - It wiped off my tears.
- That's nonsense. - Why did you copy mine?
Her tears count,
- but are mine nasal discharge? - Kwang Soo.
- I'll take a box of sweet potatoes. - Okay.
Everyone.
My story is another tearjerker.
I see.
My friend invited me.
- To a party? - To his house.
I spent the Christmas with my friends.
He also invited girls in his neighborhood.
- Goodness. - Pardon me?
(It's a heart fluttering moment.)
I wanted to impress them.
Did you pull another trick?
No, I didn't.
Wearing a golden ring...
seemed cool at that time.
However, I didn't have one.
It looks like a golden ring, doesn't it?
- What is it? - Is it a coin?
I didn't have it then, but I asked someone.
When you clean a brass ring with toothpaste,
it looks like it's 14K gold.
It looks like gold.
It really does.
- That's interesting. - Is it brass?
When I saw that...
my friend had the ring, I borrowed it from him.
It looked like I was wearing a golden ring.
- You wanted to look impressive? - Yes.
I had it on for two hours.
After a while,
black dirt got stuck on my finger.
It was due to moisture.
(I know what it is.)
- I know. - I had no idea.
I had no idea.
Black dirt kept getting stuck,
so I kept wiping it off with saliva.
- That's funny. - Gosh.
Seriously.
Let me tell you.
You called me that day.
He asked if I had one, and I said no.
I asked him if he had one, and he said, "Of course I don't."
To be honest...
That's what he said.
I remembered what happened.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Jae Seok gets Poor.)
Who gave him "Fair"?
- So Min? - Hey.
Are you saying that his is better than mine?
Are you saying that's better than my memory with my mother?
Gosh, thank you, So Min.
- Your story was so sad. - Right?
You're my enemy from now on.
He wanted to wipe off the trace of his poverty.
That's right.
That's ridiculous.
It's what happened when he tried to seduce women.
(Poverty, my foot. He was trying to seduce women.)
- Jong Kook. - It's not a trace of poverty.
How could you say that?
- What do you mean? - You can't say that.
If you can't afford it, you shouldn't pretend.
- You're so rude. - Goodness.
Goodness.
It doesn't deserve a "Fair".
I'll take the clementines.
A box of clementines?
It deserves at least a "Fair".
(Jae Seok wins a box of clementines.)
- Goodness. - Gosh.
My sincerity was rejected.
Sincerity?
I should have made up a story...
instead of telling an honest one.
- I brought something very precious. - Gosh.
- Me too. - How do we get the presents?
(Suddenly)
- What's going on? - What?
- What happened? - What is it?
They're stealing the presents.
- Don't do that. - No.
Don't do it.
Gosh, what's going on?
(The light comes back on.)
(However, the light is red.)
(What kind of party is this?)
The presents that you received disappeared.
(The presents that you received disappeared.)
(Their Christmas presents disappeared.)
Did one of us take it?
- Is it one of us? - Really?
- No way. - Did someone take it?
- How dare you, punks? - No way.
Kwang Soo, did you take them again?
It wasn't me.
You're at Horror School with a story of ghosts.
(Welcome to Horror School.)
(It's Horror School with a story of ghosts.)
(It's Running Horror School, )
(a secret shelter for dissatisfied ghosts.)
Come on.
This isn't appropriate for year-end festivities.
- Don't bring us ghosts. - Seriously.
It's Christmas.
Why are there ghosts again?
There are ghosts among the members.
Among us?
(There are ghost or ghosts...)
(here to ruin Christmas.)
There are ghosts among the members.
Among us?
(There are ghost or ghosts...)
(here to ruin Christmas.)
If one person survives...
and stands on the platform that only humans can...
when a rooster crows at dawn, that person wins.
They take all the gifts.
- Only one person? - My game console.
That means the ghost has to become human to take the gifts.
There are two ways for a ghost to become human.
They can either eliminate a human...
or get their revenge.
They can then be reborn as human.
(There are two ways to be reborn as human.)
- How do you get your revenge? - What's that?
Every time you win a mission,
you can find out the identity of the member of your choice,
so please try your best.
(They don't know how many ghosts there are.)
(Who are they?)
This mission is...
Frightening Box.
It's this again.
- It's been a while. - It's something frightening.
Find a box with the R flag on it inside the school,
- and check the mission. - I can't go.
Put a blindfold on with a camera attached to it.
Put your head inside the box, and reveal the question.
If the other members can answer the question on the monitor, you win.
You'll win a hint.
This is a group mission.
(2 people will find the box, and 6 will solve the question.)
All right.
Who would like to go?
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors. - All right.
(Nobody wants to look for the box.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors.
No, ready or not...
You lose then.
(You want to do it again?)
(Everybody went, but he didn't.)
- No. Why? - You lose.
- You didn't go. - Exactly.
(He eliminates himself.)
Rock...
You said it yourself.
We got one person. We need another one.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They're picking another person to join Seok Jin.)
(Jong Kook and Haha lose.)
Okay. Is it you and me?
- That's fine. - There's Seok Jin too.
We have 1 person already, so 1 of you are going.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Who's going to be Seok Jin's partner?)
(It's Haha.)
- My gosh. - Oh, dear.
This is bad.
(It's a pair of cowards.)
- They're cowards. - This will be better.
They'll react better.
- It's the two cowards. - Right.
- They should go. - I'm reassured.
I should have played in the beginning.
That's why he lost.
The person who doesn't play loses.
(They start looking for the Frightening Box.)
Are they going down?
My neck is stiff.
This is driving me nuts.
(They must search 1st to the 3rd floor and find the R flag.)
- I don't think I can do this. - Goodness.
Nevis!
(Give me some power, Nevis Swing.)
Gosh, this is insane.
I can't do this.
Let's see how this works out.
(They can hear Haha and Seok Jin from the 4th floor.)
Since...
(That was unexpected.)
Since this round is a group mission, you must share the pain.
Every time they scream,
you'll get penalties of different strengths.
What penalties are you talking about?
(Every time those 2 get scared, )
(the 6 of them will have to share the pain.)
Those two scream a lot.
Of course, they will.
(They'll scream so much.)
(Will Haha and Seok Jin be brave and succeed?)
Your eyes are glazed over.
(Haha's already frightened.)
They don't look right.
Where do we go?
(They enter after 10 minutes.)
I don't like this song.
Why this music?
Where do we go?
What do we do?
Where do we go? Will you tell us?
Is there a mission?
(What?)
There's somebody there.
- This is driving me nuts. - Goodness.
- Gosh. - This is insane.
Do you want to run?
The mission might be here.
(They gather up the courage to enter the first classroom.)
(Come, spirits.)
(Are you here?)
You scared me. This is insane.
I can't go.
How can we go? Are they crazy?
I'm so sorry. I can't do this.
- For goodness' sake. - What's that?
What?
(There's a girl coming.)
- She's coming down. - My gosh.
(Wherever they go, there are ghosts.)
- She's coming down. - She is.
- She's coming down. - She's coming down.
- Don't come. - Darn it.
- Haha. - Darn it.
- Gosh. - Gosh, she's coming down.
I won't do this.
- Mission incomplete. - She's coming down.
Mission incomplete.
This is insane.
This is totally insane.
I can't do this!
I can't do this at all.
I won't.
I'm not joking. I can't do this.
- I can't even get past this. - Goodness.
We can't even look.
(They're scared already.)
Call the producer, and say we can't do this.
(They were screaming so much.)
- I can't. - What's that?
They screamed,
so you get a penalty.
What's that?
(What will they have to do to share the pain?)
What is it?
Fans? It's cold.
Are you crazy?
It's cold.
(Level 1: Fans)
It's so cold.
No way.
- Are these real fans? - It's cold already.
Fans in this weather?
I can see my breath.
There are more fans.
The wind...
It's okay.
- I can see my breath. - It's so cold.
- It's so cold. - I can see my breath.
It's more than minus 10°C outside.
Why did we make those two go?
(It's 1 fan per person.)
Next time they scream, there will be water guns.
- What? - Now?
(Water guns are the next penalty.)
(Fans and water guns?)
Water guns?
Didn't the water freeze?
What's wrong with her?
Hey, go back up. It's okay.
- Go home. It's late. - Go back up.
- My gosh. - This is driving me nuts.
This is insane.
- Goodness. - What?
(Screaming)
Why did I not play...
rock-paper-scissors and lose?
Why did I not play? Why did I do that?
- My gosh. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Hold on.
- They're all people, right? - They won't kill us.
They're all people.
- How are we supposed to do this? - We have our cameramen too.
Right. Let's go.
Don't come down.
- Don't push me, Seok Jin. - I won't.
Can you turn the music off?
Close your ears. It's less scary...
- without the music. - That's what is driving me nuts.
I can't open the door.
(Creaking)
(There's a security guard in his office.)
It's the security guard.
Salute.
(It's a good place to hide something.)
Is he a person or a doll?
Sir.
Sir?
(They're terrified.)
I'm not doing this.
(They return to the starting point because of the security guard.)
- My gosh. - Goodness.
I can't do this.
I hate myself too.
I'm not being helpful to the team.
I want to be recognized in the awards ceremony,
but I can't do this.
This is a fail.
(He always congratulates other people during the awards ceremony.)
(I wanted to have the spotlight this year.)
I can't do this.
(Stay tuned for Haha's 2018.)
Goodness.
My gosh.
(The water guns are loaded because Haha screamed.)
It's cold.
(They have launched.)
- It's cold. - Tell them not to scream.
Gosh, this is insane.
How long is it going to take them to go inside the room?
- Seok Jin. - We have to do this.
They're all people.
- We have to do this. - Go.
- What? Why? - We have to do this.
I'm mad.
They keep doing this because I always get scared.
If we don't get scared, they won't do this.
Sir.
(It sounds like fireworks.)
(Screaming)
Hold on.
(Are those poppers?)
I'm so mad.
- My gosh. - Again.
That doesn't count.
That's how he talks.
It's cold.
My head is cold.
It's so cold.
(Shivering)
Can we just...
face the fans toward one person who loses rock-paper-scissors?
- Don't rotate it. - Just one person.
- It's for 1 person. - Fix them on 1 person.
- It's for one person. - You can't rotate the fans.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Ji Hyo wins. - Only she won.
(Ji Hyo wins by herself.)
Okay, the two of us.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook are exempted next.)
- Okay. - No, it's the three of you.
(Jae Seok, So Min, and Se Chan remain now.)
Hey, you must win.
- I'll feel the fans too. - All right.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok wins.)
- My gosh. - So Min, you have to win.
- Which one should I play? - This is... Goodness.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Scissors.
- Rock... - Hold on.
(The loser will feel the biting cold.)
(6 fans at minus 10°C)
It's minus 10°C outside.
(Which one will get to monopolize the fans and the water guns?)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min gets the penalty.)
Okay!
(Is it me? I'm so dead.)
We should switch every minute.
- Let's do that. - I like that.
- Hey, So Min. - They work hard for penalties.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan want to share the warmth of the holidays.)
My gosh, they are the nicest.
- They are both the kindest. - Seriously.
- They are full of love. - They can't be more affectionate.
Kwang Soo, you must turn it a bit.
Goodness, I feel so grateful.
Hey, this is like that place when you go...
Hey, So Min. You look like you're in a music video.
So Min, it's like a music video.
(Her attitude changes. My gosh, did I look pretty?)
She's enjoying this too.
- Here it comes. - So Min, here's the camera.
- The jib camera is filming her. - The jib camera.
The cameraman is filming her.
(She targets the advertisers' hearts with the biting cold.)
(However, the guys are frozen at heart.)
- I love how windy this is. - She likes it too much.
(The fans last long.)
(These advanced fans have an exceptional mobility.)
(Running Motor Fans)
I bet she'll come down with a cold now.
- Let's do it again. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay. - The loser stays in the middle.
- My gosh. - Okay. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Goodness. - It's so cold in this seat.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- You didn't play that, right? - Gosh.
Okay. It's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok, the unlucky one, loses.)
We didn't set you up.
- This is so amazing. - We didn't set this up.
Seriously?
(He feels the piercing cold as soon as he sits down.)
Hey, it's freezing.
(Everyone else isn't that cold.)
- How does it feel? - My minute hasn't passed yet?
- What are you talking about? - Not even close.
- It just started. - It's not over yet.
Only three seconds passed.
- Wait. - What is it?
(Plopping down)
Why are you sitting over there?
If they happen to scream...
I see how it is.
(That looks fun. Then should I join her?)
- She's doing it. - Was it done on purpose?
- She looks like a sniper. - Hey.
- Are you doing that on purpose? - Don't fire that at me.
(Is Kwang Soo joining them too?)
Are you doing that on purpose?
Hey, that's not cool.
- What do you mean? - You can't do that.
- You can't do that. - Why not?
- You can't. - That's too much.
- You went too far. - Seriously?
- That's not a water gun. - He's not reading the room.
He's drinking it.
I feel like I'm going to hit you.
Is it the same place?
(This time, it's the art classroom.)
I can't do this.
Let's just go now.
What is it? What do you want?
(Bellowing)
What do you want?
(The bust falls all of a sudden.)
(I have a feeling it must be in here.)
- Okay, okay. - That's not a real person.
(It must be somewhere here.)
- We'll be fine. - What do you want?
- We'll be okay. - The hint must be in here.
(Their hunches tell them it must be in the art classroom.)
- Wait. What is that? - What is it?
(Screaming in fear)
(Screeching)
Hey.
- Seok Jin. - Hold on.
- You totally squashed me. - I'm sorry.
(What are we doing?)
- I'm so sorry. Are you okay? Gosh. - Seriously.
- Unbelievable. - Are you serious? Darn you.
- That scared the wits out of me. - Goodness. I can't believe it.
Hey, you!
This is driving me crazy.
(As they scream, the water guns are fired.)
What are you doing?
It's freezing.
(Gosh, it's so cold.)
What are you doing?
(I should fire my water gun.)
(What just happened? What is this?)
(They betray even at this moment and target So Min.)
(We must get rid of any potential danger from the start.)
Gosh, So Min.
Ji Hyo, why did you shoot at my ears?
But why are we going after each other?
It's so cold.
- I'm freezing. It's really cold. - It's freezing in here.
It's really cold.
(The penalty is put to shame.)
- We are in trouble. - I'm so cold.
- I'm freezing. - Why must we attack each other?
So Min, put that down.
(The staff had no part in this.)
I told you to put it down. My gosh.
Are they going to take three days to find the box?
Until when should we wait?
This must be it.
This is it.
- This is the place. - Haha.
- Haha. - Yes, I'm here. Yes.
Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine. - I'm about to pass out.
- We were so worried about you. - Yes, we were.
- This is the mission. - He's more brave now.
"The time limit is three minutes."
"Put on the blindfold where the cameras are installed."
"Shine a light inside the frightening box."
"When six members accomplish the mission, it's a success."
Here I go. This is the real deal now.
Okay. Team Nevis Swing, you can do it!
Get ready.
- Good luck. Try to figure it out. - Start.
- Get ready. - Good luck. Try to figure it out.
(The mission begins.)
Put your head deeper.
- He's outside. - We must figure out what it is.
- No, no. - Is that it?
(The point of view from Haha's camera)
What do you see?
- He didn't start yet, right? - My gosh, what is that?
- What is that? - Who is he?
(Is that a ghost?)
- What is that? - Are you serious?
- That startled me! - Goodness!
They must've gone mad!
(The mission is...)
(answer the question on the ghost's face.)
Something is written on it.
- It's a person. - It's a person?
- Goodness! - Look at his face!
- No! - What was that?
(He throws a fit.)
They must've gone mad.
- What was it? - What was that?
- They must be out of their minds. - What?
- Something is written on it. - I just hear something exploding.
(He is delusional.)
- Face the front side. - Haha, shine the light inside.
(We'll only reveal it to you.)
Come on. Face the front already. Hurry.
(The question on the ghost's face is...)
(Where is Santa Claus' hometown?)
Haha, get in there.
I'm going in now. It's really happening now.
- "Santa Claus..." - "Santa..."
Move a bit to your right.
Lower the camera a bit.
(However, he's rigid.)
- Hold on. Lower it. - Haha, lower the camera.
- Lower it. - Move it down.
"Santa Claus..."
(His body is shaking.)
It's asking about the hometown.
"Where is Santa Claus' hometown?"
(He finally read the question.)
(If they answer the question, they accomplish the mission.)
(I don't know the answer, but please get it right!)
"Where is Santa Claus' hometown that he lives in?"
Finland.
(Finland)
- You accomplished your mission. - Gosh, Finland.
What a relief.
- He lives in Finland. - We got it right.
- We answered it correctly. - There's a Santa Village there.
What did you say?
- Okay! - Great job! We got it right.
- Finland was the right answer? - Take off your blindfold now.
- We're done now. My goodness. - I was so manly!
- Manly? - You're a real man.
- You accomplished your mission. - Right.
We'll tell you the member's identity of your choice.
You're at Horror School where it's full of ghost stories.
There may be one or more ghosts among you.
- One of us should get the hint. - If you say that...
(We went through some rough patches.)
If you say that, we'd be disappointed.
- Earlier... - We had a hard time here too.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
- Okay! - I haven't won anything for ages.
(So Min and Se Chan will get the hint.)
I've never won at rock-paper-scissors.
(They can find out the identity of the member they'd like to know.)
(The identity of the member Se Chan wants to find out is...)
So Min.
(It's So Min.)
(Is So Min a ghost or a human?)
The identity of So Min...
(The identity of So Min...)
is a ghost.
(She's a ghost.)
(So Min is...)
(a ghost.)
(He's shocked to find out So Min is a ghost.)
Name a member whose identity you want to find out.
(It's So Min's turn next.)
Jae Seok.
(So Min asks about Jae Seok.)
The identity of Jae Seok...
(The identity of Jae Seok...)
is a ghost.
(Jae Seok is also a ghost!)
(Jae Seok, you are a ghost too.)
(The identities of the ghosts unravel.)
(Then who are the humans among them?)
The final mission to put an end to the Nightmare of Christmas Race...
is Tag with the Ghosts.
(The final mission is Tag with the Ghosts)
I seriously want to end this race.
- We'll play tag? - With ghosts?
Hints about the members' identities are scattered throughout the school.
Put the name of the member whose identity you want to find out,
and then you can find out their identity.
There's a hint box.
After discovering their identities,
the last member who gets on the platform...
as a human before the rooster crows at dawn will win the race.
When you are not the only remaining human standing on the platform...
We must eliminate whoever is remaining.
(You must eliminate other members until only 1 human remains.)
Ghosts can find out who the humans are...
and switch each other's identities.
Humans can eliminate only humans,
but if a ghost eliminates another ghost,
the ghost, who removes the tag, will be eliminated.
My gosh. We can't eliminate just anyone.
Moreover, there are vengeful spirits who threaten the ghosts' existence.
Vengeful spirits can be resurrected only when they eliminate ghosts.
(Vengeful spirits must eliminate ghosts to resurrect themselves.)
When vengeful spirits eliminate humans, they will be eliminated.
(They cannot eliminate humans.)
There are vengeful spirits, humans,
- and ghosts. - They'll be eliminated.
Then we will head to where the race will be held today.
(Vengeful spirits can attack ghosts, but they cannot attack humans.)
- Do it here? - Yes.
What's your identity?
I'm a ghost.
Jae Seok.
- This is how to let your grudge go. - What is this?
(Ghosts can be humans after letting go of their grudges.)
"You died from lack of blood circulation from skinny jeans..."
What is this nonsense now?
"You're a ghost due to lack of blood circulation from skinny jeans."
"Three pairs of loose pants are hidden all over the school."
"Find them, put them on, let your grudge go, and become a human."
As soon as I become a human, I can go to the platform?
Yes, as long as you're the only human.
If you manage to survive...
and go up to the platform, you will be the winner.
(He will win if he's the only human to survive.)
- If I am the only human? - Yes.
- Here's your mission. - Okay.
- So Min. - Yes?
You died because you were wrongfully accused...
of having smelly scalp.
Make a member...
smell your scalp...
and say, "It smells good."
Once you hear that, you will reincarnate as a human.
Dear viewers, it's not true.
My scalp doesn't smell that bad.
They were exaggerating when they said that.
Seok Jin's scalp smelled like rotten bread.
Seok Jin won't tell me the truth if I ask, would he?
He never trusted me.
I have no idea who the human is.
(You win only if you are the only human when a rooster crows at dawn.)
Let's begin the race.
The countdown starts now.
Five.
Four.
Three.
- Two. - I'll go inside the music room.
One. The race starts.
(The race starts.)
I need to get out of this place.
I need to get out of this place fast.
(Someone plays an organ in the classroom.)
Why is she playing an organ alone?
(Do re mi fa so la ti)
(Let's find the hint box fast and get out of this place.)
It's really scary.
I am sorry.
I can't remember what comes after this.
What?
What can't you remember?
I can't remember what comes after this.
What comes after this?
What was it?
(Do!)
(His heart nearly stops.)
I wondered why she stopped at ti.
(So Min the Ghost is looking for the hint.)
(She finds 2 girls who are communicating with a spirit.)
Tell me.
Didn't you see the hint?
Please.
Are you here?
(The spirit writes "O".)
Is the person here beautiful?
(Is the person here beautiful?)
(The ghost says, "No".)
Am I not pretty?
You asked if I am beautiful, didn't you?
Please tell me I am beautiful.
I am really not beautiful.
(She couldn't care less about the hint.)
It's not here.
The hint is not here.
(Our spirit doesn't lie.)
I'm so scared.
(Haha is searching the nurse's office.)
Maybe something horrible will pop out.
Is someone in there?
Raise the camera.
Raise the camera and see if there's anyone.
(I feel like someone might be behind.)
(Someone screams.)
(I knew it.)
(Let's find the hint.)
(Screaming)
(Did you think it was over?)
(The unexpected attack...)
(knocks him out.)
(Laughing)
Just kill me now.
I want to get eliminated.
I can't do it.
I can't even speak.
(I don't care about the race.)
No way.
Why did they turn on the red lights?
What's that? My gosh.
(What is that?)
I think the hint box is there.
(The hint box must be over there.)
Isn't that the box?
(Who are you?)
I can't do this.
I won't get the box.
(Avoid scary things at all cost.)
(Screaming)
I can't do this.
(I will look for the hint next time.)
So this is how it's going to go today.
(Screaming)
- Hello. - What was that?
That surprised me.
(Despite the fear, he walks towards the box.)
(Hide well, I can see your hair)
(Who are you there?)
(That scared me.)
I found the box.
That's not the box.
(What does he mean this is not the box?)
What do you mean this is not the box?
Is there really another box?
What's this?
Where are you?
Are you here?
What is she looking for?
(Why is she playing hide-and-seek in the school at this hour?)
Where are you?
What are you looking for?
(Is something in here?)
Where are you?
I can't find you.
Here I am!
(Here I am!)
(Screaming)
(Why would you come out of there?)
(Why can't you find me?)
(I can't walk anymore.)
That scared me.
I can't do this anymore.
I want to quit. I can't do this.
I give up.
Okay.
I am hurt. I can't do this.
(He got scared, dizzy, and annoyed. He wants to quit.)
I'm dizzy.
There must be a box there.
Can you...
- I was here before. - Hide well
I was here before.
I know how this works.
I know the situation here.
Hide well, I can see your hair.
(She's got the hint box.)
(He saw the box, but he moves in the opposite direction.)
My gosh.
(Take it if you dare.)
She's got the box.
Hide well, I can see your hair.
Please give it to me. It's my third try.
This is crazy.
(I can't go near her because she might pop out.)
(But he's a great strategist. He comes up with his first tactic.)
(Laughing)
(He blocks her way, so she can't pop out.)
(Then he carefully tries to steal the box.)
(Will he finally be able to get the hint box on the fourth try?)
(I see it, I block it, and I get it.)
I got it.
Find the hint box, and put the name of a person.
Then you will find out that person's identity.
(He can use the hint box to find a member's identity.)
Is Jae Seok a ghost?
(He asks if Jae Seok is a ghost.)
(He sighs.)
(Jae Seok is a ghost.)
(Jae Seok the Ghost is patrolling the security office.)
What is that?
(What's that?)
I found it.
(He finds the pants.)
(He has never worn pants that weren't tight.)
(Putting it on is tough enough.)
My clothes are too thick.
Please help me, Kwon Ryeol.
My goodness.
Do you need help putting on your pants?
Aren't we on the same team?
Are you...
I hear rumors that...
- you have a second job. - No.
I heard you have a second job.
(Kwon Ryeol makes many mistakes.)
Gosh.
Are there any other pants?
(He clears 1 out of 3.)
You win one.
- I got one, right? - Yes.
I can't keep them on. Others will recognize them.
You can take them off.
(What?)
Why did you tell me to put them on?
(Are there any other pants?)
Is there another pair?
What's this?
"Security Daily Log"?
(There are 3 security daily logs with R stickers.)
What's this?
(He opens 2015 security daily log.)
"They come back on the same day every year."
"Some are pathetic, and some are funny-looking."
"Why do they come back?"
(Is it about the ghosts who return every year?)
"Will they come back this year?"
(Will they come back in 2017?)
(Will they come back this year?)
(Haha follows a suspicious security guard ghost.)
Why do the ghosts have name tags?
(In the past, once you take off...)
(the ghosts' name tags, )
(you find important hints behind them.)
Will I be eliminated once I take off his name tag?
(What will happen...)
(once he takes off his name tag?)
What's this?
(December 24, 2016)
"They're back again."
"Eight ghosts that we thought were made up by students."
"Eight ghosts"?
(If there are 8 ghosts on December 24th...)
Today is the 24th.
We're eight members.
(If all members came back this day every year...)
(What's the secret behind the security guard's name tag?)
Will I be eliminated once I take off his name tag?
(Human)
What was that about?
(Is the security guard human?)
We're eight members.
Are all of us ghosts?
(Are all 8 Running Man members ghosts?)
(At a peaceful school, )
(8 ghosts started a story of ghosts.)
(As a matter of fact, )
(all the members were ghosts.)
(Jae Seok thought the student playing the piano was a ghost.)
(However, she's an ordinary student preparing to major in music.)
(When Jae Seok pressed the piano key, )
(she was shocked and ran out.)
(In the infirmary where Haha was looking for hints, )
(the ones who were lying down were students.)
(Due to Haha's movements, )
(rumors about infirmary ghosts spread widely.)
(To the classroom where students were calling ghosts, )
(Ghost So Min entered.)
(I thought someone was calling for me.)
(8 ghosts who return every Christmas Eve)
(They were the Running Man members.)
(A bus arrives at the school before the opening.)
(There was no one on the bus.)
One ghost became human.
There's one more human being.
(By taking off the name tag, Haha becomes human.)
That's amazing.
I'm surprised.
(He's shocked.)
Are we ghosts?
(All members are ghosts, )
(and one of them became human.)
(By keeping his identity a secret, )
(Haha is determined to remain human.)
Are you human?
Who are you?
(He speaks in a low voice.)
Someone became a human.
Who could it be?
Who's the vengeful spirit, and who's human?
What are you?
What?
I'm a ghost.
You need to get over your grudge.
(Haha seems suspicious.)
Where's mine?
(Jong Kook looks for his mission tool.)
(He enters the music classroom.)
She must be cold.
Gosh, the student looks scary.
(Yes, I found fingernail polish.)
(He makes his nails pretty and colorful.)
I should leave so that she can stop playing the piano.
(He uses 1 out of 5 colors.)
(Goodbye)
(She's embarrassed by how thoughtful he is.)
Hide-and-seek.
(He searches the hide-and-seek room.)
(Someone stares at Jong Kook.)
(While he's busy looking for hints...)
There are so many places to hide.
(While he's busy looking for hints, )
(a mysterious being approaches Jong Kook.)
What?
(Tearing)
Ghost Jong Kook is eliminated.
(Did Jong Kook get eliminated?)
(That means a vengeful spirit became active.)
There's a vengeful spirit.
There's a vengeful spirit among you who's dangerous for ghosts.
(Vengeful spirits become human by eliminating 2 ghosts.)
Was he a vengeful spirit?
Who's a vengeful spirit who eliminated Jong Kook?
How can we eliminate the vengeful spirits?
We wait until they become human.
Until they become human?
He turns human once he eliminates one more.
(One more ghost must be sacrificed.)
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
"You died in your sleep."
"You're the ghost of the sleeping classroom."
"When one of the members kisses..."
"the back of your hand, you're reborn as human."
A kiss on the back of my hand?
Can I put my hand on someone's lips?
(She must get a kiss on the back of her hand.)
(Before she's eliminated by a vengeful spirit, )
(she must clear the mission and become human.)
Look, Seok Jin.
I don't want to.
(He's suspicious.)
I know that it's your mission.
(It's obviously a mission.)
It's obviously a mission.
(Was that too obvious?)
Gosh.
Why do you keep one hand bare?
(Everyone, I'm about to start a secret mission.)
Why don't you ask me?
Haha, please do it once.
- What? Hold on. - Please do me a favor.
- What did you say? - Do me a favor.
(Come on, aren't we friends?)
Have I ever been so desperate?
- Wait a little. - Gosh.
(The members get more curious...)
(about humans and vengeful spirits.)
You startled me.
(Jae Seok crosses paths with Haha.)
Are you a ghost?
Yes, I am.
(Are you sure you're a ghost?)
(10 minutes ago)
Goodness.
It's Haha.
(After finding a hint box, )
(Jae Seok asks Haha's identity.)
(Haha is human.)
(Don't lie to me.)
Stop it.
You're human, aren't you?
(I'll take off your name tag.)
- You're human, aren't you? - No.
- You are. - I'm not.
- You're human. - I'm not.
Aren't you?
(Jae Seok becomes human...)
(as Haha turns back into a ghost.)
I worked so hard to become human.
A ghost...
should remain as a ghost.
How dare you try to become human alone?
Get lost. Wait, am I human now?
You became human while he became a ghost.
(He walks around to celebrate becoming human.)
(What are you doing, Kwang Soo and So Min?)
(We are...)
(doing...)
(Ripping)
Human Yu Jae Seok is out.
(He just became human and is out?)
What?
He was a ghost but became human. He's out now.
Jae Seok was human?
- How is Jae Seok out? - Where's So Min?
- Was it the two of you? - Yes.
Then it's either of these.
- Kwang Soo got him out, - I got Jae Seok out?
Or So Min did. It's either of those.
(Only humans can eliminate humans, so it's one of them.)
- Where is she? - Down there. So Min is there.
One of them is human.
- It's more likely Kwang Soo did it. - That's right.
Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, and So Min were together.
- 1 of these 2 are human then. - That's right.
- It's right. - True.
There is a vengeful spirit here too.
- Of course. - There has to be.
Hold on.
(Who's the vengeful spirit that eliminated Jong Kook?)
If the spirit gets another ghost out...
- They'll become human. - They become human.
If there are no ghosts left, they can't become human.
- That's right. - That's right.
One of us must be feeling impatient.
(If there are no ghosts left, the spirit can't become human.)
(Before all ghosts turn into humans, they have to eliminate a ghost.)
How did they become human?
- What are you? - I'm a ghost.
- You're not human yet. - Not yet.
- Didn't you do a mission yet? - No.
Do you have to eat?
- I have to eat. - I stole your food. Are you out?
I'm not, but I failed. I have to eat again.
(He has to eat in secret, but he couldn't do it yet.)
There are no lunch boxes. I have to find it.
- There was one over there. - Where?
- Over there. - Let's check it out.
(Ripping)
(Se Chan rips Seok Jin's name tag.)
(What happened?)
"You're a vengeful spirit who died namelessly..."
"because people didn't recognize your existence."
- Why do you keep staring at me? - You're going that far?
(It was his mission to eliminate Jong Kook.)
(He got 2 ghosts out, so he's reborn as human.)
Human.
Humans can get other humans out.
(He got 2 ghosts out, so he's reborn as human.)
Hold on so...
At this rate,
I can escalate this into a war.
If one person survives and stands on the platform...
that only humans can when a rooster crows at dawn, that person wins.
What's going on?
(Ji Hyo bumps into Kwang Soo and So Min.)
What's going on with you two?
Are you human?
(He's being creepy.)
- Kwang Soo, wait. - Kwang Soo.
(She appeared out of nowhere and did her mission.)
What was that?
- What was that? - What was that?
(I remember that.)
I got it.
She's human now.
Let's check.
Oh, dear.
(Let me see your name tag.)
Hey.
Goodness.
(Ripping)
(I'm sorry, but I love you.)
(Earlier with Jae Seok, )
(So Min got him out with a surprise move.)
Jae Seok is out.
(So Min is human who completed her mission early.)
What are you?
Human Song Ji Hyo is out.
If the security guard was human,
I can get other humans out...
and become human again.
(Would he become human if he eliminates a student?)
(He approaches a student...)
(and rips her name tag.)
(Human)
(Haha is human now.)
I was right.
- Se Chan. - Yes, Haha.
- Listen to me. - Okay.
This is war.
Look. They're talking.
- We're all humans. - Right. There's none left.
Se Chan is human too.
If you say you're human, they'll get you out right away.
(They form an alliance.)
Those two.
They'll get you out.
We have to work together.
- Did they form an alliance? - Yes.
(Kwang Soo hit my head earlier.)
(That must have been his mission.)
(He must be done with his mission then.)
(You should donate your name tag.)
Come. We have to work together. Let's work together.
We have to work together. Trust me.
Trust me. I'm serious.
(Se Chan and Haha are a team.)
Think carefully.
(Kwang Soo and So Min are another team.)
- It's the four of us left. - Right.
There are only humans left. Why are you hesitating?
Exactly.
(They have to go head-to-head now.)
Come on.
(She backs off.)
You can't be out.
(There are two guys on the other side.)
(We're all humans.)
I'll hold them. You rip the name tag.
(This is their joint plan.)
That's the only way.
That's cunning. He's going to rip mine later.
What are you talking about?
- He's going to get me out. - What are you talking about?
Whom am I to trust right now?
If one person goes on the platform, this is over.
- I know. - It'll be over.
You're going to get me out and go on the platform.
- It's so obvious. - That doesn't make sense.
(I can't trust you.)
Do you have a good idea?
(Haha and Se Chan's best strategy is...)
If So Min gets eliminated by Kwang Soo...
(It's best if we make them fight.)
We have to think carefully.
Will we do this together...
We have to. There are two of them.
It has to be 2 on 2.
One of them can betray the other.
I'll betray you.
(Se Chan...)
(removes Haha's name tag.)
I'll betray you.
(Their alliance is broken first.)
I'm going to do this by myself.
How dare you?
(Haha is out.)
Human Haha is out.
Se Chan got him out.
(There's Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and So Min left.)
(At that moment)
The rooster crowed.
One human can go on the platform in the schoolyard.
(There's the platform to decide who will win.)
(They head to the platform.)
Go.
(It's Se Chan versus Kwang Soo and So Min.)
(You have to get other humans out and stand on the platform.)
(It's the showdown.)
- Rip his name tag, So Min. - Hurry.
If I help them, they'll rip my name tag.
(If I get Se Chan out, Kwang Soo will rip my name tag.)
Hurry, So Min.
(So Min stops hesitating and joins him.)
(Se Chan is outnumbered.)
Why, So Min? Let's do this together.
(He sways So Min...)
(and rips her name tag.)
What happened?
(She can't help but laugh.)
(Se Chan versus Kwang Soo)
(If I get Kwang Soo out, )
(I win.)
(Grabbing)
(Ripping)
(As soon as he gets his name tag ripped, )
(Kwang Soo runs to the platform.)
Kwang Soo...
wins.
Is he a ghost?
(What?)
(Ghost)
(The whole thing was a part of Kwang Soo's plan.)
"You're a ghost who died from getting backstabbed."
"Find toy hammers hidden inside the school,"
"and hit 4 Running Man members' heads..."
"to be reborn as human."
There's no reason for humans to eliminate ghosts,
and ghosts are out if they eliminate other ghosts,
so I'll do the mission slowly.
I'll find the toy hammer...
and hit three members.
I'll hit the last one later.
(I'll finish my mission late.)
(He hit Se Chan's head but still stayed as a ghost.)
(In front of the members, )
(he pretended to be human.)
(You're human.)
(He tricked Se Chan, and his plan worked.)
(He tricked me.)
(He became human and stood on the platform at the end.)
Kwang Soo, you won, so you get a box of sweet potatoes...
and another gift you want from the pile.
I pick coffee maker.
(He picks a coffeemaker.)
Thank you.
(His hands are full.)
(He's envious.)
Viewers, Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas. - Have a merry Christmas.
(Have a merry Christmas!)
(Next week)
(The idol group that represents the nation, Sechs Kies)
(The rising star in variety shows, Lee Elijah)
(The number 1 healthy beauty, Soyou)
(It's winter training for variety shows.)
(However, )
(a snowstorm suddenly hits them.)
(Welcome to the winter kingdom.)
(Something is strange about this winter kingdom.)
(Their bodies become paralyzed.)
(The competition for survival in the winter kingdom starts.)
(Their only chance of survival lies in finding the flame.)
(If you want to live, find the flame.)
(Where is the flame? Give it to me!)
(Without the flame, everyone will become ice zombies.)
(Who is destined to survive in the ruthless winter kingdom?)
Why did you touch my chest?
(Winter Kingdom Survival)