(The 5th Member's Week, "What Is Wrong with Him?")
I am Kim Sang Joong Ha from What Is Wrong with Him?
It's been five weeks since the Member's Week had started.
This week's host is Running Man's child,
Haha.
(Haha's office in Hapjeong-dong)
The host of this week's episode is you, Haha.
If there's anything you wanted or wished to do,
please tell us honestly.
(Haha, the host of the 5th Member's Week)
What shall I do? What do I do?
Should we play basketball?
Or should we play baseball? I don't think we should do sports.
Should we do something with music?
But I'm not confident in music.
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
Or should I bully the members?
How about going to Dokdo? We can build a ship and go.
Shall we do a live show?
Should we do something that offers prize money?
Or we can just fight?
There are so many things I would like to try,
but I can't include all that in one episode. It's so hard.
What am I going to do?
(The 5th Member's Week hits a wall.)
But you see,
during the interview with Haha,
we were able to discover something strange about him.
Do I look bad? Should I put on some makeup?
Should I put on a mask or not?
It's cold, right?
Shall I drink hot coffee?
This is iced coffee.
As I think about it, I want to do a lot of things.
I don't know what I should do.
I'm going crazy.
What should I do?
(Laughing)
(Here he goes again.)
(Screaming)
My head hurts!
It seems like Haha has a difficult time...
when he has to decide on something.
But you see,
why can't he decide on his own?
We should meet his acquaintances to see if he struggles...
to decide on something in his daily life.
I think he contemplates a lot...
even when he eats.
He has a hard time choosing which one to buy. He can't decide.
It takes a long time for him to decide.
He asks me...
what he should do. He asks me this quite a lot.
I find that side of him very irritating.
When I gave him his outfit and even though...
the socks were the same design, he contemplated between two pairs.
He said that one of the pairs looked more loose than the other one.
So I ended up helping him choose.
In that sense, it's a bit frustrating.
He irritates me a lot.
He should make his decisions quickly.
According to the interviews,
his inability to decide seems to be more serious than we thought.
In order to help him,
we decided to put him under extreme situations to decide.
We had to face the result...
of his profound decisions.
(The result of Haha's decision)
Why don't we look at these...
thrilling situations together?
(The whole world has turned into a snow-white, winter palace.)
- This week is Haha's week. - Haha's the host.
(What will the members face here?)
The host of the fifth Member's Week...
is Haha.
- Right. - What will he do?
- He will do something childish. - Right? I think so, too.
- I thought last week was his week. - So did I.
- Right. - I didn't imagine it'd be Gary's.
This episode is for Haha who is always at a crossroad...
between two important choices and struggles to decide.
- You're right. - He thinks too much.
- He can't decide at all. - I agree.
He seriously struggles to decide.
So we have prepared a race named,
I've Made My Decision.
What is that?
- What? - Are we being taken again?
- This is happening again? - We're being dragged again?
(Please come with us.)
- Stop this. - They're getting tired of it, too.
- What are you doing? - This is driving me crazy.
Why do you always do this?
The blindfolds are always changing every week though.
(To where are they forcefully being taken?)
Why is this blindfold so tight?
I can't see anything.
(How will this place be relevant to Haha?)
Where are we going?
(What are you up to, Haha?)
I think Haha will do something hard.
(They arrive.)
We've already arrived? What is this?
- What is that crane-looking object? - Wait.
What is it?
What is that?
(What is the view unfolded before the members' eyes?)
- What? It's for bungee jumping. - Isn't this bungee jumping?
Hey!
(Welcome to a high-altitude drop point.)
Haha's gone mad.
(We will provide you with fresh, wintry air.)
(This will introduce you to a luxurious sky view.)
Are we going to bungee jump in this cold wind?
(This 63m tall, bungee jumping platform is the highest in Korea.)
What is this?
- We won't bungee jump, right? - No way.
- This isn't possible. - What on earth is this?
(Please enter quickly.)
- No way. This can't be right. - What's wrong with him?
(He doesn't mean we should jump here, right?)
- It's bungee jumping. Haha's mad. - It's bungee jumping.
- Hey! - Jae Seok. It's for bungee jumping.
(He has already lost his senses.)
- Wait. Jae Seok! - Hey.
I can't do this.
(I want to go home.)
How can we do bungee jumping in the midst of winter?
(The elevator welcomes them.)
(You've come in one piece, but I won't let that happen when you go.)
This isn't acceptable. He really must be out of his mind.
This can't be happening.
- It's too cold to bungee jump. - I can't do this.
- We can't do this. - He must have lost his senses.
(Haha, what are you up to?)
Why are we going there?
(They are unable to ask or discuss. They are forced to get on.)
Should I sit here?
My gosh.
I'm going insane.
(He hasn't even gone up, but he's already feeling dizzy.)
Gosh, this is total insanity.
I mean...
I really hate high places.
(I'm only sitting down, but it's enough to make me cry.)
(Here comes the customers.)
Do we really have to go up? It's quite high.
(Let's meet again alive.)
- It's going up. - My gosh.
(Goodness)
Stop it.
Don't go up too high.
(The lift is about to break through the atmosphere.)
I'm about to lose it.
(Why do I have to undergo this hardship?)
(Haha, what have we done so wrong to deserve this?)
This is really scary. Let's stop here.
My whole body is going numb.
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook are 40m above the ground.)
Stop going up. It's seriously scaring me.
It's really windy.
(The wind is teasing this coward.)
(I can't get up since it's too frightening.)
I'm not kidding here. I'm serious.
I can't look outside.
Stop it please.
(What is their fate as they dangle from the atmosphere?)
How can we go bungee jumping in this cold weather? Come on.
What is this?
(What is it that Kwang Soo and Seok Jin will face?)
I can't do this.
I can't handle this.
I won't do it. I'm going to the bathroom.
- Where is Haha? - Wait.
(We will boycott this episode as a whole.)
(What's causing them to make a fuss already?)
- Are you serious? - I really can't do this.
I won't be able to handle this.
(It's a slingshot ride. It's a new kind of fearless ride.)
(With one shot, it'll send you to another universe.)
What is this? What's happening?
(Welcome to 50m above the ground.)
- Are we doing this right away? - Hey! Be quiet!
My gosh. Come on.
Look, they installed cameras. They are planning to film this.
(The moment you depart is precious.)
- Come on. - Hold on.
I won't get on it.
(Run for your life.)
(There's a fugitive who refuses to get on the ride.)
(The mission to capture Kwang Soo has been put into action.)
(Running)
Hey!
(Since you've stepped on the premises, you can't leave.)
My gosh.
(I caught you, Kwang Soo.)
- I seriously can't handle this. - Let me go.
Let go of me!
Come out, Haha.
Please report them to the police!
(I am innocent.)
This is driving me crazy.
Let go!
(How is 50m possible?)
(I want to go home.)
Let me go!
(What are you giving me this hardship?)
Can I take it off?
(What is it that awaits Ji Hyo?)
What is that?
Is that a snake?
(What is that bizarre creature?)
(It's an ominous feeling.)
What is this?
What is that?
(She's shocked.)
(Flinching)
I hate this so much!
(What is the mysterious creature that's put in front of her eyes?)
(Welcome. Would you like to touch me?)
Please, I can't do things like this.
(Ji Hyo's Achilles' heel is anything involving insects.)
Has Haha lost his mind?
What's going on? I hate it.
It's so annoying.
(Ji Hyo, who hates bugs, is trapped by insects.)
I want to go home.
(The worst possible scenarios are about to happen.)
(What will happen to the members?)
(Haha, please save me.)
Hello, where are the other members?
The main member of the fifth Member's Week is you.
Please take a look at this.
(Haha receives a mysterious mobile phone.)
(What could be inside the phone?)
- Haha! - What's going on with Seok Jin?
- What's going on? - Seriously.
(He hears Seok Jin's desperate voice.)
What's going on?
What is this?
- Haha! - What's going on with Seok Jin?
You know me. I'm in a desperate situation.
Haha, I can't get on this ride.
- Please, I beg you. - What is it?
I'm like your brother.
Please, I consider you as my older brother.
What's going on?
What is this?
- Haha. - It's Kwang Soo.
- I wonder why he's making a fuss. - I can't ride it!
I'm staying calm because I trust you.
I wasn't going to say this,
but Seok Jin has said bad things about your family.
- What? - When we aren't filming,
- I'll tell you later. - Okay.
It's Jae Seok.
I don't know what's going on,
- but I can't bungee jump... - Jae Seok...
in the middle of winter.
- He really hates it. - Please, Haha.
- Please save me, Haha! - How can I save him?
What's going on?
Haha, you know me.
I hate it more than bungee jumping.
- What? - Please save me.
He has to eat ramyeon and cake.
- Haha. - What's wrong?
- It's terrible. - What's wrong, Ji Hyo?
There are so many centipedes...
that are about this big.
- Please save me. I beg you. - Ji Hyo.
- Please do me a favor. - What's wrong?
She's about to cry.
What on earth is going on?
As you always have a difficult time making...
important decisions, we prepared this for you.
Here's the race that the production team prepared.
It's called Haha's Choice, I've Made My Decision.
(I've Made My Decision?)
What happens to the members depends on you.
As time passes, the members will suffer more.
You must decide the order of whom you will save.
This morning, I couldn't decide between hot and iced coffee.
In the end, I drank Job's tears tea.
I almost lost my mind this morning.
I've made my decision.
My goodness, this is too hard.
Usually, I like to...
follow the majority rule.
I'm a pacifist so I like peace.
One of the hardest things is...
having to choose a dish when there's a lot on the menu.
I get a panic attack when I have to choose an ice cream flavor.
I should have come up with an idea.
I hate having to make decisions.
(It's almost time to decide.)
(Will he save Jae Seok or Jong Kook?)
He has to make a good decision.
I have to make a decision.
Please call the police.
This is driving me crazy.
(Will it be Seok Jin or Kwang Soo?)
(Or will it be Ji Hyo who's afraid of insects?)
Oh, my goodness.
I can't decide.
(Whom will he choose? That's the question.)
Gosh, what is that?
(Haha arrives at Decision World.)
(His decision will determine the others' fates.)
My goodness.
What is that? Is that for bungee jumping?
That's just crazy.
Why are the members placed in such extreme situations?
How can anyone jump from there?
It's impossible.
How is this possible?
(How will he decide their fates?)
(What happens to those at 63m above ground depends on Haha.)
Jae Seok!
Jong Kook!
What? Was that Haha's voice?
Hey, Jong Kook.
- Haha! - What's happening?
(Haha's voice from below comforts them.)
- Jae Seok. - Haha.
- I didn't know what was going on. - Haha is here.
- Haha. - Please save me.
Please save me.
- Please save me. - What's going on?
Save me.
Haha, please save me.
- Gosh. - Haha.
- If they fall off, - Please.
They'll fall in the water.
I'm so scared!
What do I do?
Here's your first decision to make.
Starting now,
within five minutes, you must decide...
one member to save.
(Decide only 1 between 2 members?)
The member who isn't chosen will be punished immediately.
- Gosh. - Why?
- Jae Seok is afraid of heights. - Haha.
- Please save me. - If he isn't chosen,
he'll jump off from 63m above ground.
My goodness.
- Haha. - Healthy Jong Kook...
- It's over 10,000 calories. - will eat...
high-calorie foods before coming down.
If I eat all of it, I'll die today.
If you exceed the time limit,
both members will be punished.
- Please decide within five minutes. - Let me come down!
How can I decide?
(Whom will Haha choose?)
Jong Kook!
- What? - It's just high-calorie foods!
- How can I eat all this? - Jong Kook.
- I have to eat all of it. - I thought you had to bungee jump.
- I have to eat all the food. - Come on.
- Jong Kook, that's nothing. - I have to eat them all.
All you have to do is eat.
- My goodness. - All you have to do is jump.
What did you say?
- The jump won't take long. - It's the middle of winter.
- All you have to do is jump. - Gosh.
- This will stay in my body. - Just eat and use the toilet.
- I have to exercise a lot. - Haha!
- What are they saying? - Yours is much easier.
- Jae Seok! - I'm serious.
What?
How do you feel today?
I feel terrible!
Jae Seok is in his best condition!
- Are you feeling well? - I feel terrible.
He wants to bungee jump for the first time.
Haha.
Jong Kook will have a fit if he eats all the food.
If he gets angry, I'll get beaten up instead!
I had a big breakfast this morning.
I can't eat all of this. It's too hard.
(Haha can't decide.)
My goodness, what should I do?
I think the ramyeon is over 10,000 calories!
Can you believe what Jong Kook is saying?
- Do you love me? - It's perfect for bungee jumping.
- Haha. - I said, do you love me?
I love you, Haha.
Make the decision now.
- Haha. - I can't decide.
Do you want to see me dead?
All you have to do is jump.
It's over after you jump.
How could you even say that?
- Just jump. - Bungee jumping is scary.
Jump and enjoy the cool weather.
Jong Kook, you can eat that.
No, I can't!
I have to eat all of it.
It's ramyeon and pizza.
Gosh, I know how much he hates it.
(To Jong Kook, fast food is the worst food in the world.)
Do you know how much oil is added to jjajangmyeon?
(Despite what others said, he was determined to stay healthy.)
- I know how much he hates it. - There are chips.
Jae Seok.
Please save me.
You have 30 seconds.
Jae Seok, just...
- Please let me go down. - You've bungee jumped before.
(Will it be Jae Seok?)
You've bungee jumped before.
I like the ground. Please.
Haha, please save me.
(Please, I'm a total coward.)
(Jae Seok was seen as a coward due to his fear of heights.)
It's too high.
I'm so nervous.
(Trembling)
(He loses his mind when he's somewhere high.)
I know Jae Seok also hates it. My goodness.
- What about Jong Kook? - You have 15 seconds.
I have 15 seconds left!
What about the consequences?
I have to make a decision.
(It's time to decide.)
Please, Haha.
Don't make me bungee jump.
No, I can't eat it.
I know Jae Seok hates bungee jumping.
- All Jong Kook has to do is eat. - Please.
Sometimes, he wanted to eat junk food.
- Please. - It's just a jump.
- People like bungee jumping. - Please.
I've made my decision.
(Jong Kook, the strongest, always protected Haha.)
(Jae Seok, the funniest, always cared for Haha.)
- Please. - I don't know.
- What should I do? - Please.
(On the other hand, both embarrassed him, too.)
(However, which of them does he like more?)
He changed.
I'll save...
(Whom will Haha choose?)
Yu Jae Seok.
(Haha chooses Jae Seok.)
You just have to jump.
No!
(Jae Seok descends, and Jong Kook rises towards high-calorie foods.)
(Say hello to high-calorie foods.)
- No! - Thank you. Thank you!
(I survived.)
No.
(This can't be happening.)
- No! - Thank you, Producer.
- Call Haha. - Thank you, Cameraman.
Thank you, Sir. Thank you.
Haha saved me.
(Haha saved my life.)
I know that Jae Seok has fear of heights...
and Jong Kook once told me that he wanted to eat ramyeon.
I remember him telling me.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
What am I to do?
- I'm sorry, Jong Kook! - You are a dead man now!
- I won't forgive you! - I didn't mean to.
You are dead!
Have a nice meal!
- I am going to hit you! - Jong Kook.
Why do I have to go up so high to eat?
Gosh.
- Enjoy it. You wanted it! - You are dead!
Thank you, Haha.
Oh, my. I'm alive.
Jae Seok, I know how it feels like!
It's too high up here.
Why do we have to go up so high?
What am I to do with these?
(High-calorie foods)
It's been years since I had ramyeon.
Haha must have gone crazy.
- Haha, thank you. - Jae Seok.
- I'm safe now. - Jae Seok.
- You saved my life. - I know how much you hate it.
I hate bungee jumping.
I hate it too.
Do you know what Jong Kook said?
He said I can simply jump, whereas he can't eat those food.
How could he say that?
They are having a dramatic reunion down there.
They seem happy.
(Are you guys happy now?)
What am I to do?
Jong Kook will probably thank us.
He wanted to eat ramyeon but didn't have an excuse.
But it's like poison to Jong Kook.
It's over.
Jong Kook is furious.
How can you say that?
- What? - How can you say that?
I saved your life.
- I saved your life. - What life?
(What did I do wrong?)
What? Why?
You chose me. So?
Can you please take this off me?
I'm so angry.
(Thanks to Haha, I get to eat hamburgers.)
Haha.
(Munching)
(What's this salty and sugary flavor?)
(Chocolate cake, the highest-calorie food here, is next.)
(Is this what people call, "cake"?)
I can't cut it.
(He is eating as if he were chewing on rubber.)
Haha, it's over. Let's go.
- You are heartless. - Why?
- How can you change like that? - What?
- It's over. - Don't you feel sorry for him?
I told you already.
How often do you eat ramyeon?
- I eat it 200 days a year. - See?
I eat it at least twice a week.
Eating ramyeon once is not so bad.
Jong Kook!
That's enough.
I'm sorry, Jong Kook!
Why are you sorry? Let's go.
I'm sorry!
Let's go.
Enjoy your meal!
Jong Kook, enjoy your meal!
Haha must have gone crazy.
(Taking one bite after another, he's having an inner conflict.)
(Along with the amount of calories he consumes, his anger rises.)
(He's eating chocolate as if he were chewing on plastic.)
(He's eating them one by one.)
Ramyeon's next.
(Next up is ramyeon.)
Gosh.
(I did miss ramyeon sometimes...)
(but I never thought I'd eat it today.)
Haha.
(Jong Kook finally eats ramyeon.)
I'm going to hit him hard.
He will regret his choice.
I trusted you.
(That was my fault.)
See you soon.
(I'll have to burn some calories off by dealing with you later.)
Jong Kook!
- Hey. - I'm sorry!
Forget it.
Jong Kook, send me some kind of signal that you are okay!
- It's over. - 7012!
- Be quiet. - We're one. Let's last forever.
Haha, I love you.
This one is hard, too.
- Haha. - What am I to do?
Hello.
I love you, Haha.
- I can even bow down to you. - Haha.
- Oh, my. - I can bow down to you.
- It will be a pleasure. - Can I ask you a favor?
Please let me kneel down.
- It's comparatively easier here. - Why is it easier?
As I told you before, you have to choose...
a member to save within five minutes.
(Even if he wants to send them both away, he has to choose one to save.)
I'll tell you one thing.
That was really charming.
Seok Jin's Member's Week is over.
Mine isn't.
- I... - You don't know what I'll do.
Come to think of it,
I have my Member's Week left.
- Think carefully. - I have, for Running Man...
Think carefully. Look at me.
- I brought my wife. - Haha.
Are you threatening me?
Do you want to ride this naked next week?
Wake up.
Come here and take this off.
- I'll give you five seconds. - He really means it.
- I'll give you five seconds. - You've got to send him off.
- It's too much. - Are you threatening me like this?
Do you want to ride this naked next week?
If that happens,
I'll use my Member's Week to make him ride it naked.
- Jae Seok. - I like that.
- What are you doing? - That's a good idea.
- He's being cheeky. - He learned all the bad things...
- from the other members. - I didn't mean it.
Tell me a good memory you had with me. Be concise.
Haha, during the seven years of Running Man,
I can never forget the day...
- we fought in the mud. - It was incredible.
- That day... - It was incredible.
It was incredible.
(Do you remember the feeling of adrenaline flowing that day?)
It's incredible.
(Some say it felt like Jung Woo Sung and Lee Jung Jae fighting.)
It was incredible.
I know what you mean.
- It was incredible. - You remember, right?
- However, looking back, - Haha.
- I've spent a lot of time... - Haha.
With Kwang Soo.
(They share the DNA of betrayal.)
(They have a strong friendship amidst suspicion and resentment.)
I love you both so much. You know that.
I love you, too.
Raise your hand if you want to volunteer for me.
- I can. - Okay.
- For you... - Okay.
- It has been decided. - Wait!
(Why do you say okay?)
It has been decided.
- Wait, no. - Thank you, Kwang Soo.
Haha, please.
- Don't do this to me. - Thank you, Kwang Soo.
For further reference,
it's a ride for two.
If you decide on the member, his cameraman has to ride it with him.
Yoo Seok.
- Yoo Seok. - Yoo Seok.
Yoon Sang, you told me that you have diarrhea.
Yoo Seok, say something.
- Yoo Seok told me he wants to try. - Really?
Don't lie.
- They are professional liars. - Or Haha...
Me, me, me.
- Haha. - Yoo Seok is calling you.
- What is he doing? - I visited your restaurant...
- three times a week when it opened. - That's right.
That's right.
- That's right. - Look at Yoon Sang.
- That's right. - Yoon Sang has to go now.
You never showed up.
- Yoon Sang. - What is this?
He always went home staggering.
- Yoo Seok. - I remember.
- I remember. - It's decided then.
- It's decided. - Okay, I've decided.
- Wait. - Kwang Soo doesn't have memories.
He went to the restaurant...
Why didn't you go?
I choose Seok Jin.
(Haha chooses to save Seok Jin.)
That's right.
Really?
- Really? - You helped a lot.
I had a hard time then.
- I went there a lot, too. - I know.
My voice is hoarse.
- I know but Yoo Seok helped a lot. - Really?
Yoo Seok.
Blame Yoon Sang.
Well done!
- It's because of Yoon Sang. - Why didn't you go?
- I'm sorry, Kwang Soo. - Do I really have to ride this?
(Am I riding this because I ate less pork entrails?)
- I actually texted your wife. - What did you say?
I asked her to persuade you.
I texted her because of you.
(However, Byul checked the text two hours later.)
Why didn't you eat pork entrails? Why didn't you visit the restaurant?
I don't like pork entrails.
But why...
Why don't you like pork entrails?
- I'm sorry Kwang Soo. I love you. - I'm sorry, too.
You understand, right?
I still have Member's Week left.
- I'm really sorry. - I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
Yoon Sang. I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
Let's start!
- Please save me. - The cameraman looks more scared.
- What? Why aren't we going? - What's happening?
(Kwang Soo and Yoon Sang shoot up to the sky.)
(It's a vertical takeoff towards space.)
(The gravity is pulling down their faces.)
(Surprised)
(Lee Kwang Soo and Choi Yoon Sang aboard. Apollo 7012 takes off.)
(Are you listening, Earth?)
(Do you copy? Is anyone there?)
(I, Lee Kwang Soo, )
(finally became Prince Universe from Asia Prince.)
(The history of the universe has been rewritten.)
(Shrieking)
(Screaming)
(It looks like his face is weighed down by 10 times the gravity.)
(He drools.)
(They really don't look charming.)
Look at Yoon Sang.
(He spits out gibberish.)
(He loses his speaking ability due to zero gravity.)
(Earth is much better than space.)
(They reach stable orbit.)
It looks doable.
(Welcome back to Earth.)
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
Wasn't it fun, Yoon Sang?
I thought only the ball would fly off.
(They pretend to have enjoyed it.)
Wasn't it better than you thought?
(Kwang Soo's Week will feature dark scenarios.)
Good job, Kwang Soo.
Let's go.
(They move to the third location.)
It's freezing.
Jong Kook.
You look good together as a team.
- It looks great. - Did you enjoy the food?
What a team.
What did I do?
Jong Kook. Kwang Soo.
- What did I do? - What's this?
What's this?
(Jae Seok spots grasshoppers.)
Save me, Jae Seok.
- Isn't this an anaconda? - Save me, Jae Seok.
Isn't this what Byung Man eats?
They must have brought it from the jungle.
Isn't this an anaconda or something?
- It looks like a dragon. - What are they?
What am I supposed to do?
This is driving me crazy.
All right. Jong Kook and Kwang Soo,
put your heads in the punishment box.
Put your heads in the punishment box.
(Put our heads in the punishment box?)
(Why do we...)
(have to...)
(do this again?)
- Why would we do that? - You want us to put our heads in?
(It's all your fault, Haha.)
Is this a punishment?
It already upsets me that I didn't get chosen.
It's your third decision time.
There's Ji Hyo or Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
Within five minutes,
you must choose which member to save.
What? From them?
You can choose Ji Hyo or Jong Kook and Kwang Soo.
You must make up your mind.
I'll be abandoning her twice.
(What did I do so wrong?)
The member that doesn't get picked with receive punishment.
Ji Hyo has to put her hand in the insect box.
(She has to touch the insects in the box.)
(Ji Hyo is scared of insects.)
Every time a minute passes, the box will get closer to her.
The member that doesn't get chosen...
will receive the punishment in the punishment box.
(It's hard to gauge how much fear they'll be in.)
(There's also a fear of the unknown.)
- Save me, Haha. - You're supposed...
to do this at the end. Why would you do this from the start?
Isn't this too much?
Haha.
- You have five minutes. - Haha.
- It's decision time. - This is driving me crazy.
Is Ji Hyo supposed to touch that?
Haha, it's me.
- I don't know what to do. - For goodness' sake.
It just moved. What now?
(They get louder.)
Why are you coming closer? Hold on.
(With every minute passing, the insects get closer to Ji Hyo.)
- I don't know what to do. - Isn't this too much?
This is too much.
Haha.
I'm going to keep it inside forever.
(Are you going to betray us twice?)
(They are about to crawl out.)
How am I supposed to save you?
(He can't make her touch the insects because she's frightened of them.)
What am I supposed to do?
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo have been hurt already.)
- You have one minute left. - This is driving me crazy.
- My gosh. - Haha.
Haha. I love you.
- I'm being serious. - Don't do this.
(She loves him out of fear.)
It's already over between us.
You used to like me in the beginning.
- We had a love triangle. - Come on, I...
(Don't you remember, Haha?)
You're just pretty.
(You said I was the prettiest girl in the world.)
(You used to take good care of me.)
I didn't like you.
- Come on, Haha. - You have 10 seconds.
- Save me this once. - This is driving me crazy.
- What am I supposed to do? - Haha.
- Kwang Soo, tell me it's okay. - I'll be...
- good to you all my life! - Four, three,
- two, one. - Kwang Soo.
What's your decision, Haha?
(Haha runs out of time.)
(Would he be a gentleman and save Ji Hyo from the insects?)
(Or...)
I won't let this one go.
(Would he save the two members whom he betrayed already?)
Please, Haha.
- Haha. - Haha.
I'll save Ji Hyo.
(That must have been a difficult decision.)
How was Ji Hyo supposed to put her hand in?
Haha!
I'm sorry, Jong Kook. I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
(Collapsing)
Ji Hyo.
Where are you going?
(Her legs give out.)
What's wrong with you?
Stop it, Ji Hyo.
You're saved.
(The punishment box opens.)
What did I do to you?
- Watch, Haha. - Why am I doing this?
My goodness. Haha.
(We have to live.)
I'm sorry.
(Rest of them are on their way.)
I remember the old times.
- I have to decide for myself. - Really?
Why are you so indecisive? Just do it.
It's hard for me.
You are...
so indecisive. How are you supposed to survive in this world?
Exactly.
I...
bought land on the day I checked it out.
Seok Jin is too rash.
Hey.
If I was a bad guy, I would have made Seok Jin homeless.
Hey. When I retire,
I'm going to backstab you first.
He gets defrauded easily.
I don't anymore.
You won't have to decide again, right? What do you think?
- I think it continues. - I think it's for the entire day.
My gosh. Do I have to flatter you all day?
That's not nice, Seok Jin.
It doesn't suit my personality.
It suits you perfectly, Seok Jin.
You're the best at it.
- I'm usually quiet. - You're Flatter Jee.
(Flatter Jee, flatter, flatter)
Flatter Jee, flatter, flatter.
(This is his third nickname.)
It's your song.
You should talk back to him.
I think he's funny.
(He just thinks it's funny.)
Flatter Jee, Flatter Jee.
(Dancing)
(The chosen ones are on their way to a restaurant.)
What did I ever do wrong?
How long do I have to be in here for?
It's over.
(He pops his head out.)
What did I do to you?
(He gets a makeover.)
(His lips are intensely red and his mustache is alluring.)
(Jong Kook is next.)
You need professionals for this.
(He also gets a makeover.)
(They're shocked by each other's faces.)
This is too...
I take it back. Can I be in a different team?
- I accept my mistakes. - Hey.
- Can I be in a different team? - Come on.
(This is too beautiful to be aired on television.)
What am I supposed to say to this?
Wait. You actually have a theme to your makeup.
(What theme?)
What are you supposed to be?
(Jong Kook's makeup looks futuristic.)
What am I supposed to say about this?
He has a theme to his makeup. What about me?
- He looks disgusting. - What did you say?
How am I supposed to have this on all day?
Can you take off his hairpin? It's really scary.
(Is he a clown or an entertaining beggar?)
You must be either one of them.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo's revenge starts now.)
(The survivors are at a Korean restaurant nearby.)
Thank you, Haha.
- Come in. - This is amazing.
(It's a feast.)
- This is amazing. - I'm so hungry.
Isn't this fried smelt?
(The table is filled with delicious dishes.)
This is such a great plan.
(What would Haha have to decide in front of the food?)
- Haha. - Haha.
I have a question, Sir. The two left behind.
Would they not come here?
- They won't come. - Really?
Do I have to decide from this group?
(Laughing)
That little Haha...
(Are you happily eating warm food?)
I see.
(We understand, Haha.)
I'm speechless.
(Laughing)
That was a big mistake.
You have to be good.
In front of you is...
a table full of food...
or a triangle gimbap and a yogurt drink.
If Haha chooses to eat the food from the table,
the rest of the members must share the gimbap...
- and the yogurt drink. - Sorry?
If Haha chooses to eat the gimbap and the drink,
the rest will have good food.
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
- That doesn't make any sense. - You're not making any sense.
- Who would choose otherwise? - Do you think he'll be different?
Why would he choose this over the good food?
- Don't you trust me? - He loves to eat.
What would you like to choose, Haha?
This is making me so sad.
- I was going to consider. - What is your justification?
I'll give you five minutes. If you can't choose...
If you eat the gimbap and we eat the good food...
- That would be nice. - I would be touched.
- Me, too. - Wouldn't Haha's public image...
- look great? - You could've been nicer.
- You can't yell... - What are you doing?
- Stop it. - Get back.
- He's being too bossy. - Get back.
- This is too much. - I'm bossy?
(Do you want to eat gimbap?)
I was actually thinking...
how it would look if we did it that way.
If that was your plan, do that.
- I'm so disappointed. - Okay.
Please face the wall.
I'm not sure where I'll sit but...
If you sit here, I might cry.
We'll be so touched if you sit here.
(Will he have the meal to himself or try to look like a nice person?)
- Seven, six... - Do you remember our trip?
That's right. Haha.
(Do you remember our happy trip?)
(The meat tasted better because they were together.)
(They could laugh more because they were together.)
(We were so happy then.)
Turn back on three.
One, two, three.
(Even the nicest meal wouldn't taste so good if you ate it alone.)
(Where is Haha sitting after hesitation?)
(He's enjoying the meal himself.)
I knew it.
I knew he'd do that.
This is what I was talking about.
Hey.
This is what I meant, Ji Hyo.
I was going to have the gimbap.
- Don't blame me. Blame Jae Seok. - That's absurd.
- You're lying. - I mean it.
Hold on. Is that your choice?
Haha can...
eat with 1 of the 3.
- Really? - Haha.
(They change their attitude right away.)
Haha.
- Haha. - Look at me.
- Hey. - I can eat really well.
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
You should have told us earlier.
- Haha. - Let go of me.
- Haha. - Haha.
I'm so sick of you guys.
- Haha. - I'm so tired of you.
- Haha, cheer up - I can't live without Haha.
- I can't live without Haha - I'm sick of you guys.
- I'm so tired. - Haha.
You're our only hope.
You're...
the real hero.
(Haha, you're our only hope. You're the real hero.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I think Ji Hyo can have the gimbap.
Do you know me?
(Excuse me?)
- Are you my attorney? - That's not it.
Don't touch me.
- Send Ji Hyo to the gimbap. - You're unbelievable.
If you'd like to...
volunteer...
to have the gimbap, please raise your hand.
All right, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok volunteered.)
- Wait. - Sit here.
- Hear me out. - Just sit there.
- Wait. - Sit.
Sit here.
Gosh.
You have 10 seconds.
10,
- You're unbelievable. - nine,
I didn't want to say this but...
my mom hit me...
with a triangular ruler when I was a kid.
He's lying.
Any triangular objects frighten me.
(He has a phobia for triangles.)
All right.
- Seok Jin... - He's...
He doesn't even deserve this.
(Munching)
Hey, you shouldn't eat it all. You're supposed to share it.
(He doesn't care.)
- Did you eat it? - Yes.
He ate it all.
You're supposed to share it.
(I didn't know.)
He grabbed it.
We don't know who'll be sharing it with you.
The one who doesn't get chosen won't have any lunch.
(There will be no lunch for one.)
What's your choice, Haha?
I'll put a piece of fried smelt in the mouth of the person I choose.
Close your eyes.
(Please come to my mouth.)
- Keep your eyes closed. - Keep them closed.
(Their lunch depends on Haha.)
(Jae Seok approaches.)
One, two, three.
(Who has the fried smelt?)
(Enjoy the finger.)
(You brats.)
Hey, come here.
- You don't have anything. - How dare you make fun of me?
- That was funny. - Enjoy your lunch.
(It's finally lunch time.)
Let's eat.
Do we have to do this?
The potatoes are so chubby.
(Are you happy?)
Is that potato jeon?
It's so hard to decide what to start with.
It's so painful.
But you seem to be making decisions with no problems.
- It's too difficult. - That's absurd.
You're so annoying.
You're being absurd. What's so difficult?
(Here, you see only dried fish hanging.)
(The losers arrive at an unknown place.)
Where are we going now?
A special lunch is prepared for you.
- A special lunch? - Are we going to eat?
(We at least get food.)
Aren't we going to a restaurant?
(Ice)
(At the end of the mysterious mountain path, )
(they end up having lunch outside.)
(There are two cold lunchboxes and frozen water bottles.)
Why are there bottles of ice?
Is the water frozen?
(It froze in a second.)
(In the cold lunchboxes...)
- Are we at war? - Is there a war?
- Are we at war? - Are we refugees?
Is this how Member's Week works? My turn hasn't come yet.
Are we at war or something?
(Let's eat anyway.)
It tastes good.
(Wait. It tastes like...)
(Surprised)
(Did someone dip the potatoes in honey?)
Why is it so sweet?
It's really sweet.
Is it because we look like beggars?
(Their costumes perk up their appetites.)
- This is the best potato I've had. - Me, too.
It's my first.
(These potatoes are lovely.)
Is it minus 17°C today?
It's the coldest day this winter.
It'll be the coldest day this winter.
The whole country is frozen.
Haha is crazy.
How dare he do this to us?
(We won't forgive you.)
(It's such a beautiful, winter scene covered with snow.)
(The frozen river and the stiff cliff create a beautiful harmony.)
- This is not okay. - The wind comes through the shoes.
Seok Jin, that's same for everyone.
The wind comes through. These are summer shoes.
(On this cold day...)
What's that?
- What's that? - What's that?
Why did you come up with an idea like this?
(There's a game board on the ice and a backboard on the handrail.)
- Haha. - Yes?
- A video clip has arrived. - A video clip?
Why did you come up with an idea like this?
Haha.
You'll regret your choice.
(How dare you discard us?)
(He looks scary.)
Did they eat there?
Haha.
Is this all that we mean to you?
We'll show you what revenge is.
(The video contains a warning about revenge.)
Everyone,
- you're going to bungee jump. - We'll make you all feel this cold.
Run within five minutes.
See what consequences your choice will bring.
Be prepared.
Run!
We're going to get you.
(The choice has brought consequences.)
- Run within five minutes? - What are we supposed to do?
They just got a little makeup.
- What are we supposed to do? - What did we do so wrong?
This is too much.
Here are the rules.
Haha needs to complete the final mission...
before the losers rip off your name tag to avoid the penalty.
What am I supposed to do?
Haha's final mission is...
putting the ball into the basket five times with your eyes covered.
(He needs to shoot 5 hoops blindfolded.)
Put the ball into the basket five times with your eyes covered.
(He has to put the ball into the basket five times blindfolded.)
The other members should stall the beggars...
- by fighting against them. - All right.
If Haha fails,
all of you will receive the final penalty.
(The remaining 3 have to share the penalty.)
(Are we receiving penalty, too?)
(Today's final penalty)
(Bungee jumping from 63m high)
Let me explain how it works.
You're going to play "Rock-Paper-Scissors",
"Speedy Eating",
- and "Icy Slap-Match". - "Icy Slap-Match"?
Each person will play one game.
- To stall them? - Yes, you should hold them back.
Haha is going to...
try to put the ball into the basket over there on the ice.
We'll make sure you succeed.
- My goodness. - Try it.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
- Don't worry. - Please go to your positions.
- With my eyes covered? - Yes.
We can do this.
- One, two, three. Let's go. - One, two, three. Let's go.
Let's avoid the penalty.
(The death match starts.)
(Careful)
It's so cold.
I'll practice a little.
(He'll fight alone on the ice.)
(Will he manage?)
(He's the Michael Jordan of Running Man.)
(I play basketball with my heart, not my height.)
(This slippery ice can't stop me.)
(Bouncing)
(He misses the hoop.)
Can I make five shots?
I should shoot it like this.
(That was not even close.)
(He keeps missing the hoop with his eyes open.)
(The ball rolls away.)
I'm sorry.
(Will he be penalized?)
We're on a frozen river.
This is a frozen river.
This is unbelievable.
The river is completely frozen.
(Ji Hyo will play "Icy Slap-Match".)
Gosh, we're standing on a frozen river.
(Will she also play well on ice?)
My goodness, this is crazy.
(How about a Popsicle?)
(Mixing the hot and the cold is key.)
Gosh, it's cold.
I'll play rock. If it's paper,
I'll play scissors.
(He has to go over the rules first.)
(Which team will win?)
(They put on black gloves. They have thick red lipstick on.)
(You won't find such gangsters anywhere.)
What do we have to do?
(They're Kwang Soo and Jong Kook.)
One of my socks is wet, so I took it off.
(Kwang Soo isn't wearing a sock.)
How can they treat me like this?
Please save us.
What's going on? Where should we go?
(While suppressing their anger, they enter the kingdom of ice.)
(They're finally here.)
What happened to your face?
It's nice to be in nature.
Come on. It wasn't my fault.
I'm innocent.
Please, Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook's anger rises.)
- Seok Jin. - You look cute.
Here are the rules.
The first match to protect Haha is called...
"Rock-Paper-Scissors".
You must win three consecutive rounds...
You must win three consecutive rounds to pass.
Three consecutive rounds?
- I tell you what I'll play. - Okay.
- You can win, Kwang Soo. - Let's play.
- Let's go, Haha. - Let's go.
Good luck, Haha.
Please put on the blindfold.
(Haha's performance will determine everything.)
I have no sense of direction at all.
Make it in the hoop five times. Get ready, set, go.
(Protecting Haha starts.)
(Haha shoots his first ball.)
(He misses.)
You missed.
Did I miss it?
(When will he do it 5 times?)
- I'll play rock. - Rock?
- I'll play paper. - Okay.
(Do you remember, Kwang Soo?)
(Their "Rock-Paper-Scissors" was very competitive.)
(Seok Jin is the king of rock-paper-scissors.)
- I'll play rock. - Rock?
- I'll play paper. - Okay.
(Will Kwang Soo defeat the legendary player Seok Jin?)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
(Seok Jin got weak.)
- We have two more rounds. - Let's go.
What will you play?
- I'll play rock. - Me, too.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(What's the result?)
- I'll play rock. - Me, too.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins again.)
- You won. - What will you play?
- What will you play? - I'll play scissors.
- Scissors? - It's the last.
Just win this round.
(Will they defeat Seok Jin and pass through?)
(The fate of Haha's team depends on Seok Jin's performance.)
(Buy us more time, Seok Jin.)
(What's the result of "Rock-Paper-Scissors"?)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Amazingly, Kwang Soo wins again.)
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo win 3 consecutive rounds.)
Ji Hyo should have played it instead.
Oh, no.
No, Seok Jin.
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo win. Please go to the next game.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo take off.)
I'm so annoyed.
(They run angrily to the next game.)
Please.
(He shoots the ball and misses.)
My goodness.
(He focuses.)
- You made it. - Did I?
(Haha scores one.)
Did I make it?
- You made it. - Did I?
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo approach Jae Seok.)
They look hilarious.
It serves you right, Jong Kook.
I'll take revenge on you.
- It serves you right. - Jae Seok.
Here are the rules.
The second match to protect Haha is called...
"Speedy Eating".
(The game is called "Speedy Eating".)
It's called "Speedy Eating".
(The first to finish eating wins.)
(They have to eat ice cream and sweet potatoes at minus 17°C.)
- Okay. - The first to whistle...
- Okay. - The first to whistle after...
eating sweet potatoes and ice cream wins.
(They're fighting for food.)
- Come on. - You eat this.
They must be hungry.
Wait a minute.
My teeth will hurt.
I'll eat the sweet potatoes.
- Get ready. - Get ready.
Get ready, set, go.
("Speedy Eating" starts.)
My goodness.
(They eat ice cream in the freezing cold.)
Kwang Soo.
(Their tongues get stuck to the ice cream.)
(Their mouths freeze.)
(Their mouths are filled with hot sweet potatoes.)
You can do it.
(Haha only scored one.)
(Haha is running out of time.)
(His nervousness makes him fail.)
Oh, no.
(When will he make 4 more?)
I can do it. I'm Michael Jordan.
(He imagines himself to be Michael Jordan.)
(Michael Jordan made successful free throws with his eyes closed.)
(Please give strength to Haha.)
Feel the wind.
(We hope he makes it in the hoop.)
(Will he make it through the hoop despite the strong wind?)
I'll make it. I love you.
Welcome to Running Man.
"I've shot the ball 10 million times."
(Here he goes.)
- You made it. - Okay.
(He scored 2.)
Let's do it again.
(Meanwhile)
We can do it.
(They experience two extreme temperatures.)
(Kwang Soo enjoys the ice cream.)
Do you want to switch?
No, I know you want to eat ice cream because you're thirsty.
Kwang Soo, scold him.
What are you doing?
- What? - Let me go.
I'm so thirsty.
- My throat is so dry. - Drink some water.
- Give them water. - Where is it?
(Here's some snow.)
What is that?
- Here's some water for you. - That's snow.
Stop.
(Kwang Soo whistles.)
- Kwang Soo made it. - Okay.
Hurry up.
(Once Jong Kook finishes eating, they move on to the next.)
Gosh, I'm cold.
(Who will finish eating first?)
- He did it. - He made it.
(Jong Kook whistles.)
- Okay. - Jong Kook and Kwang Soo win.
(They move to the next game.)
We only have two games left.
(They head to Ji Hyo.)
Haha, keep trying.
My goodness.
(Haha scored twice so far.)
- You made it. - Okay, this is good.
I'm coming to get you, Haha.
They're coming.
Hurry up.
(They're coming after Haha's name tag.)
(Haha misses.)
Hurry.
Haha, you must hurry up.
- You must make it. - Keep trying, Haha.
Please.
(He scored 4 so far.)
Here's the last one.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(She must buy Haha time.)
Let's win.
(Jong Kook starts the game.)
(4 years ago, he was amazing at playing slap.)
(He won without breaking a sweat.)
(Here he goes again.)
It didn't flip.
(He fails.)
Hurry, Ji Hyo.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
The slap will flip when you hit it right in the center.
(Ji Hyo even received a special lesson from her father.)
(Is it like this?)
You shouldn't do that.
Okay.
(He claps.)
- Is this mine? - Yes, hurry up.
The paper might tear.
(Ji Hyo is ready to show what she learned.)
(She'll show the power of education.)
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo must play until they win.)
(She fails to flip it.)
- It's hard because it's slippery. - It doesn't flip easily.
You can do it!
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo are getting closer to Haha.)
Did I make it?
(He shot from a good angle but failed.)
(Just one more)
It bounced off.
What?
This is driving me crazy.
Hurry up.
(It's Jong Kook's turn again.)
(I'll flip it this time.)
Hey.
(He ruins his team's chances.)
I'm sorry.
(It's the ice.)
Hurry up.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn again.)
Let's go, Ji Hyo.
This won't flip.
(She fails.)
Hurry.
(They have to rely on Haha's shooting ability.)
Fail.
(Is it Haha's shooting ability...)
(or Jong Kook's fingertips?)
(If Jong Kook manages to flip, Haha's name tag will be in reach.)
It flipped.
- It flipped. - I did it.
(He's successful.)
- I sacrificed myself. - I did it.
- I did it. - It worked.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo clear all the missions.)
Hey, Haha.
(There's only Haha's name tag left.)
- You're done. - Haha.
(I can hear him approaching.)
- Hurry. - This is cold.
(We're coming for you.)
- Hurry and get it in! - Haha.
It didn't go in. Use more force.
I'm scared.
(He just needs to get one in.)
(Here it goes.)
(It's Haha's last shot.)
(Is it in or out?)
Fail.
(He fails again.)
Can I rip his name tag?
I ripped it.
(Jong Kook and Kwang Soo take the win.)
Why couldn't you get that in?
- You're done. - How many did you get?
You're done.
(You humiliated us.)
- You're done. - My goodness.
- This is totally frozen. - You're done.
(Haha's mission fails.)
Haha, you have failed the ultimate mission.
- You have failed... - What goes around comes around.
- You did well. - What goes around comes around.
Haha and the three members you rescued...
will all receive punishment.
Yes!
We'll go back to the bungee-jumping location.
My goodness.
(They will go bungee jumping.)
We'll head to our last location.
- Don't joke around. - Will they all be doing it?
(Let's go for bungee jumping.)
(Location of the punishment)
(It was filled with Jae Seok's cries before.)
The fifth Member's Week,
Haha's I've Made My Decision race.
There's only one decision left.
He has to choose again?
It's rather...
he'll live or not. That is the question.
If Haha chooses to take the punishment himself,
the rest of the members will be exempted.
(If Haha takes the punishment, the others will be exempted.)
If Haha decides not to take the punishment,
the three of you will be punished.
If you cannot decide within five minutes,
- all four of you... - Yes.
Will have to bungee jump.
(Will Haha live...)
(or will the other 3 live?)
How are we all supposed to bungee jump?
You can try it.
(This is complicating.)
- My goodness. - Come here for a second.
(This is the cruelest decision of the day.)
The thing that scares me the most...
is that Haha is not making eye contact.
It means he already made up his mind.
(I didn't know my decisions would affect me this way.)
(Their fates are entirely upon Haha.)
What would you do?
You can't do this.
- If it was me, - I'm not sure.
I would take the punishment.
- If it was me. - Haha, if it was me,
- I would do that. - But you are different.
We have our own way of living, right?
- Exactly. - Of course.
Did you put your ear muffs on so that you don't have to listen?
(He ignores Seok Jin.)
What would you do, Jae Seok,
if you had to make this decision?
You must choose.
I have no choice.
- Jae Seok will jump. - He will.
- That's what I would do. - To be honest...
- You can do what you think. - He wouldn't have been happy.
Don't think too much, Haha.
It's all right. This is a variety show.
- Don't worry, Haha. - You look scary right now.
(Do you think you won't worry?)
(Get away from me. I want to be alone.)
What am I supposed to do? How do I jump?
I can't do this for my life. How am I supposed to jump?
He's never done bungee jumping before.
Try it, Haha.
He failed to do it on "Infinite Challenge".
(Why are they doing this to me?)
(All I did today was make decisions.)
(His indecisiveness should have gotten better by now.)
(He didn't expect he'd have to do this.)
(Can I cry?)
What do I do?
What should I do?
10...
(Haha has tried bungee jumping before but was never successful.)
- Nine, eight, - What now?
- seven, six, - This is too cruel.
- five... - five...
(Make a decision for us, Haha.)
- two... - two...
(He's desperate.)
- One. - What is your decision?
(He looks determined.)
What is your decision?
(Will he die or live by himself?)
We'll all jump.
(We'll all jump.)
- What did he say? - He wants all of us to jump.
(It'll be a good memory.)
Let's do it together.
Hey. Don't do that.
From his face, I thought he was going to jump by himself.
- But I knew. - I thought he was going to jump.
- I knew. I saw it coming. - What was that face for?
Why did you have a determined look?
- Even Seok Jin... - I can't jump by myself.
- Bungee jumping is hard. - I was...
just joking. I just...
(He can't seem to talk.)
I can't say it.
(You can put yourself at ease and just save us.)
The sun's going down.
(The sun can't wait no longer.)
I should've chosen a blind date.
(Blind dates are difficult too.)
(It's time to make a decision.)
(Every Member's Week up to now had a happy ending.)
(Everybody suffered in the freezing cold during Haha's Week.)
(End our suffering, Haha.)
(This is all because I'm too indecisive.)
I'll jump by myself.
(He finally decides to jump by himself.)
Really?
(He's about to tear up.)
Are you crying?
(I usually don't cry but I'm right now.)
What's wrong?
- He's getting teary-eyed - Is he crying?
- It's okay. - Haha.
(He can't talk.)
Are you crying?
(Are you really crying over bungee jumping?)
- Are you really crying? - He's actually crying.
(Haven't you seen someone cry?)
Haha.
He doesn't have to cry.
- Be quiet. - He's never done it before.
- Don't say that. - Excuse me.
I have a fear of heights but he's worse.
(Smile so that your tears won't fall.)
I really can't do this.
I'm sorry. I can't.
(Haha chose the impossible for the members.)
(Would he get down safely?)
Do we have to end a variety show...
this sad?
We feel bad.
Haha.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
(They're all together in spirit.)
- I'm sorry. - Thank you. I'm more thankful.
- Thank you. - I can feel your heart.
You're doing it for us.
Thank you.
(Thanks for your decision, Haha.)
It's cold.
(Haha gets on the elevator by himself.)
- Please put on the equipment. - Yes.
(As soon as he gets on, the elevator speeds up.)
What should I do?
He puts the equipment on first.
(They cheer him on.)
He has the rope fastened.
- I'm scared looking at the rope. - How is he going to do it?
The rope scares me too.
(Bouncing)
(Even the smallest wind makes the elevator shake.)
(He must endure it on his own.)
(He never even dreamed of being this high.)
(He chose to jump from 63m for the members.)
This is killing me. What do I do now?
He's going all the way up.
All the way there?
- My goodness. - The elevator went all the way.
(He ascends very quickly.)
I can hear him yelling.
- What now? - It's too high.
- I can't watch. - Let's go, Haha.
Don't say that.
I want to say something for him.
(His eyes are shut.)
(He keeps repeating himself.)
(He didn't know his indecisiveness would lead him here.)
(He keeps climbing higher...)
(and higher.)
(He finally stops at 63m.)
This is driving me crazy.
(He puts a safety harness on.)
(He's both desperate and fearful.)
(The final punishment is held at 63m above ground.)
- You can do it, Haha. - I love you!
- I can relate. - I love you.
Thank you, Haha.
- I was there, too. - He's standing, right?
Oh, gosh.
I'm dying up here.
I can't even root for him. I know that feeling.
He gets scared easily.
Please stand in front of the door.
You will jump after 10 seconds.
(Only 10 seconds remain until the jump.)
Haha, please untie it.
After 10 seconds, you will jump.
- My gosh. - You can get ready now.
I don't think I can do this.
I can't even look at it.
(I have to stand here, relying on a single string.)
(He's teary.)
You will jump after 10 seconds.
(It's time to face his extreme fear.)
Ten.
- Hold on. - Nine.
- I can't do this. - Eight.
- Wait. - Seven.
- No way. - Six.
Five.
- Four. - No, I can't do this.
Three.
Gosh. I wouldn't be able to do it.
You can do it, Haha!
- You can do it, Haha! - He can't even talk to someone.
Two.
(There are 2 seconds left before the jump.)
One.
(1 second before the jump)
(It's time to jump.)
Before you jump,
(Before you jump...)
Wait.
(His legs give way.)
(What? Why? What's happening now?)
Do you see that door over there?
Can you open the door?
(Why did you ask me to open the door 1 second before the jump?)
(What is behind this door?)
What is this?
(What is waiting for Haha behind the door?)
(It's a diaper-shaped cake and an unidentified video.)
(He plays it not knowing what's happening.)
Haha, were you surprised?
We know you have an extreme fear of heights.
- It must've been hard. - It must have been difficult...
for you to come up here.
(Hold on. What is this?)
It's absolutely for you.
We are not doing this to avenge ourselves on you.
It's to congratulate you about your second child.
We made this in order to celebrate for So Wool, your second child.
(It's to celebrate for So Wool, his second child.)
(So this is a surprise party?)
The most important thing is that I hope there is a twist.
There has to be a twist.
(Haha dreamed of a week with a twist.)
(That's why we've prepared this.)
Jong Kook and Kwang Soo. You were informed you came to avenge Haha,
but you've been assigned with a task to help with Haha's party.
- You brought the gift, right? - We have to throw him a party?
- A surprise party? - Yes.
(This is why they told us to prepare a gift.)
- We are supposed to avenge him. - Right.
- But it's not it. - It's not it.
- It's not? - We must do a surprise event.
- I have to lose? - When you do your mission...
I will play rock, paper, and scissors respectively.
(They managed to persuade him.)
(Of course, they won consecutively.)
That's it, right?
(Haha, are you watching?)
- You have to lose, too. - Of course.
(They convinced him to eat slowly.)
(They quickly passed through the second gateway.)
Please lose. We have to throw a surprise party.
We are throwing him a surprise party.
(They convinced Ji Hyo in "Icy Slap-Match".)
(Their fake revenge was successful.)
(They easily removed Haha's name tag.)
(They managed to escort him to the platform.)
(It's a story only Haha wasn't aware of.)
Overcome this fear.
I hope you will become a cool father.
(The elevator slowly starts to come down.)
What is this?
(He's relieved and grateful.)
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations, Go Eun.
- Congratulations. - I'm so jealous.
- Congratulations. - I hope the child is healthy.
I hope your family will be happy and So Wool will grow up to be bright.
- So Wool. - I love you, Haha.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
So Wool, be healthy.
So Wool, be brave.
(We'll see you soon, So Wool.)
This must have surprised you a lot.
(He got comfort and a present in a moment of an extreme situation.)
(He's about to cry. Tears are filling in.)
I could've jumped.
Gosh.
(He lets out a laughter as he feels embarrassed.)
(I'm sorry I can't make decisions.)
Why don't you go and meet the members?
(Thank you.)
(The mission of Haha's week is over.)
Thank you.
- Haha. - Haha!
- Haha. - Haha, come here quickly.
- Haha. - Congratulations, Haha.
(Were you surprised?)
(Stop teasing me. If you keep at it, I will feel more embarrassed.)
- Where are you going? - Are you embarrassed?
- Come back. - Are you embarrassed?
- Gosh. - Are you embarrassed?
What would have happened if you told us to jump?
I was only joking.
- This is embarrassing. Thank you. - Did you cry?
- We even bought presents. - Thank you.
This is the present from us. That is from the staff.
- Here they are. - Thank you.
- Eat this at home. - Please do.
The members have prepared gifts for Haha...
and his second child who will be born soon.
- It's So Wool. - Right. So Wool.
- For So Wool. - Yes.
Why don't we give him a round of applause?
(Congratulations on the birth of his new family member.)
We bought it last night...
- at a department store. - Really? Thank you.
Goodness.
I had no idea you prepared a surprise event like this.
I think all of us should stay together forever.
(He's crazy about the members.)
We are the one.
- Thank you so much. - Our pleasure.
I hope we can grow old together.
- It's touching. - I hope we can smile along the way.
- I hope so, too. - Thank you.
- Anyway, Haha... - Thank you.
- Haha. - We also thank you.
- I hope So Wool will be healthy. - This is embarrassing.
- I hope she grows up healthy. - She will grow up to be happy.
Go Eun, it's a difficult time for you since you are almost due.
Hang in there a bit more. Let's deliver the baby safely.
I love you, So Wool and I hope you will be born healthy.
I love you, my family.
I love you too, Go Eun.
(We will always root for Haha's decision.)
- It's so touching. - My goodness.
This is Running Man's Member's Week.
(It's the 6th week.)
(Ji Hyo, Jong Kook)
(Seok Jin, Gary)
(Then Haha)
(Who are the 6th and 7th hosts?)
(It's a special gift from the staff for the members who worked hard.)
(It will be revealed on next Sunday.)