(Parental guidance is advised for viewers under the age of 12.)
(One summer day after the rain in Yangju, Gyeonggi Province)
(It's a clear, summer day which fills the heart with excitement.)
The family special came to an end.
- That's right. - That's right.
So Min, the outfit you are wearing today...
is very elegant. Why is that?
I want to be feminine today.
(I want to be feminine today.)
(She suddenly shows her feminine side.)
(Does she have a change of heart?)
- Don't be ridiculous. - She heard about the guests.
She heard about the guests.
Don't tell the members who the guests will be ahead of time.
Whenever we have actors as guests,
the members act strangely.
Ji Hyo did that in her 1st and 2nd years.
- That's right. - She is dressed the same as usual.
You bet.
There is nothing left to show after seven years.
There is nothing I want to show.
She wore pot scrubbers instead of socks.
Hey,
- these socks are in style. - She wore pot scrubbers.
These socks are in style. For goodness' sake.
- Aren't these pot scrubbers? - My goodness.
(She sure is a member with 7 years of experience.)
- You are right. - Who drew Kwang Soo's...
- future portrait? - It's not my future portrait.
It's not my future portrait.
- Really? - His hair makes him look different.
If he pushes his hair back, he will look the same.
(It's his current portrait.)
No, I won't.
- He has a wide forehead. - That's not true.
(Jong Kook is right.)
- Are you sure about that? - It's okay.
- Stay still. Let's take a look. - It's okay.
(It's his current portrait.)
My goodness.
(Slapping)
Don't pull my hair back so far.
- Where does your forehead end? - Anyone would look bad that way.
Don't be ridiculous.
- It's okay. - Only you look bad that way.
His forehead goes on forever.
- He has a wide forehead. - Seriously.
All right.
Among Find Trilogy of Running Man,
the first episode will be joined...
by two special guests.
(Today is the D-day of the 1st episode of Find Trilogy.)
- Here they come. - They're here.
(Who are the guests who made So Min feminine?)
(Their silhouettes alone captivate women's hearts.)
Park Seo Joon and Kang Ha Neul.
(Park Seo Joon and Kang Ha Neul)
Welcome.
(The popular star, Park Seo Joon. The kindhearted man, Kang Ha Neul)
Kang Ha Neul.
- "Fight for My Way". - Hello.
Hello. Hello.
- Have you been well? - Come closer.
- Hello. - They are the stars...
Running Man discovered.
Running Man didn't discover them.
So Min is embarrassed.
(What is wrong with her?)
- Stop it. - You can stand next to them.
Why are you acting so shy?
- So Min. - Hello.
Please scoot over.
(She barely says, "Hello.")
(The guests turn So Min into a timid girl.)
What's wrong, So Min?
- I... - What's wrong with you?
Have you worked with them before?
- No. - No?
She is being ridiculous.
- She is being ridiculous. - She is pretending to be shy.
Don't force a romantic atmosphere. They don't want it.
Stick a spoon on your face.
Come on, Magnet Lady.
(Where is the magnet?)
I don't know why I feel so hot. I don't know. It's too hot today.
Stick this to your face.
(He turns her into the magnet.)
- Why is she acting this way? - For goodness' sake.
- Why do I feel so hot? - She is the magnet.
This is my first time seeing male guests on Running Man.
What about Hang Ho?
(He was on the show last week.)
Hang Ho and Geun Sik were here. What is wrong with her?
Did you forget about them already?
I don't remember.
- She doesn't remember. - I don't remember.
(The special guests make her forget about last week's guests.)
The two guests are...
Park Seo Joon and Kang Ha Neul.
- It's nice to meet you. - Thank you.
They are cool.
Kang Ha Neul means "strong sky".
My goodness.
Strong sky. S.S.
S.S.
"Fight for My Way", Park Seo Joon.
"Fight for My Way".
Let's shorten the title and call it...
- Three MY. - Three MY?
Three MY?
They are the stars who captivate women's hearts.
Women fall for them.
They are incredible stars.
The nation fell for Seo Joon.
My goodness.
(He is currently the most popular star.)
- What about Ha Neul? - Don't do that.
You are joining the military soon, right?
- Yes, I am. - I see. Good luck.
(He joins the military in September.)
Why would you talk about...
- the military so soon? - It's a fact.
- Everyone was avoiding the subject. - It's fact.
- I will be back. - It's cool that he is going.
- You are so annoying. - It's cool that he is going.
- Work diligently before you go. - "Work diligently before you go."
The movie they star in...
will be premiering soon.
- The movie is on everyone's lips. - Is it on everyone's lips?
(It's unknown to Jae Seok.)
(We haven't heard anything. Are there rumors?)
Did you have to ask me in detail?
(Flustered)
- What rumor? - I mean...
I said it based on what we've talked about so far.
It's good to hear.
They say the movie is full of impressive and exciting scenes.
- It must've been great... - He's looking for...
a new master now that Joong Ki is getting married.
Am I some kind of a dog? Why would I look for a master?
- Do you want to hire him? - What?
Seo Joon, try him.
- He's a good servant. - Goodness.
- Don't mind him. - He's pretty loyal too.
- They're my close friends. - Goodness.
Feel free to use him as your servant. It's okay.
Today's race is the first part of Summer Vacation Special.
It's called, Find the Boss.
- "Find the Boss"? - All right.
(Summer Vacation Special, Find the Boss)
Today, you'll be divided into Team Police and Team Boss.
Seo Joon and Ha Neul are in Team Police to catch the boss.
They're the police.
(The two guests will run to catch the boss.)
The Running Man members are in Team Boss.
Among them, there are 1 boss, 6 villains,
and an undercover officer who will help Team Police.
(The undercover officer will support Team Police in secret.)
- Really? - "Undercover officer"?
Team Police will win if they find and arrest the boss.
The team will be awarded with 1,000 dollars.
- 1,000 dollars? - Yes.
(Successfully arrest the boss to receive 1,000 dollars.)
Team Boss will win if they find the briefcase which has money in it...
and succeed to escape.
They'll also win if Team Police arrests the undercover officer.
If Team Police arrests them...
(It's crucial for Team Police to guess who the others are correctly.)
(All right, I'll make sure to find them.)
Excuse me.
(Hello, I'm Kwang Soo, the undercover officer.)
- Is it you? - It's you?
- He's the undercover officer. - It's obvious.
(There's me too.)
(I'm Mapo Sheriff Haha, and I'm the undercover officer.)
- Goodness. - What was that?
(Let's get to it, my police friends.)
- He wants your attention. - It's me.
Okay, I see.
Why would she...
What's wrong with you?
(Who is the real undercover officer?)
- What is this? - Hello.
(1 hour before the guests' arrival)
- Hello. - It's so humid.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I know. What are these? - What are these?
- I can see what's inside slightly. - I guess there's something today.
Please choose a box among the boxes in front of you.
- Okay. - I choose this one.
- Goodness. - I'll choose what's in front of me.
- Okay. - I'll take what's left.
Number one.
(What is inside the boxes?)
I have a bad feeling about 2 and 4.
I've always chosen something disadvantageous.
(They finish choosing their boxes.)
Please show us the cards inside your boxes.
- Do we open it? - Yes.
(What's written in their cards will be their identities.)
- I'm a villain. - I'm a villain.
(Jong Kook is a villain.)
(Ji Hyo is a villain.)
I'm a villain.
- What? He's the police. - Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo is the police.
He got something again.
(Kwang Soo is the undercover officer.)
- Is this a penalty? - Kwang Soo is the police.
He's the police.
There will be a boss who will lead Team Boss.
(Among them is the boss, the police's main target.)
It's me.
- No? - Isn't it me?
- What are you saying? - Isn't it me?
- It's me. - My goodness.
- No? - Why do you keep doing this?
Team Police including Kwang Soo...
will win if they arrest the boss.
Team Boss will win if they escape with their boss and money...
or make Team Police arrest...
Kwang Soo who is the undercover officer.
Make Team Police arrest...
It's not undercover though.
(This isn't undercover.)
Didn't you just say undercover officer?
Why don't you treat me like everyone else?
Treat me like you do to everyone else.
You have to pick your boss now.
- Okay. - Didn't you hear me?
Since you're the police, please leave the room.
- Get out. - Get out.
- Get out. - Right now!
- To where? - Get out.
- Get out. - Get out.
- Get out. - Excuse me.
- What are you saying? - Get out.
Get out already.
- Come on. - Get out.
Get out.
- I pray for your soul. - What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
I think it'll be over soon.
- Get out. - Get out!
- I mean... - Kwang Soo...
- Go far away! - Am I on the other side?
- Right. - Kwang Soo...
- You're the protagonist today. - Go over to that side.
- Bye. - This is...
Am I really the protagonist of today's race?
- Hey! - I don't understand...
- Go! - Go away!
What? Okay.
(Miserable)
They're being too mean.
(He gets driven out to a further location.)
Go in this room and don't come out.
I can't come out of this room?
Go in already.
Why would an undercover officer get locked up?
Why would you lock me up?
I want a role that I can feel proud of.
(He's the undercover officer, yet he looks so miserable.)
All right. The boss will play a crucial role in today's race.
Your boss for today is...
(It's that person?)
- Who? - What?
It can't be!
(Who is today's boss that will lead the 7 Running Man villains?)
Simply put, the two guests...
and the undercover officer within Team Boss are one team.
Rest of them are all villains.
(7 Running Man members except for Kwang Soo are Team Boss.)
(The boss needs to hide their identity...)
(while Kwang Soo needs to reveal his.)
It could end right away, right?
You need to be very careful.
(Team Police, be careful.)
(He's being way too suspicious.)
- You know it's not him, right? - Don't trust him.
Let's stop talking.
(Trust me. I'm on your side.)
(How will the suspicious Kwang Soo's fate turn out to be?)
Come on. Don't do this.
Go sit next to Ha Neul.
Then push me harder.
Change seats with her, will you?
Push me harder.
Otherwise, I can't go there by myself.
Is this what you want?
She kept texting me. She was very persistent.
What's wrong with So Min?
I'm so surprised.
I asked her when the cameras weren't on.
I asked if it was Ha Neul or Seo Joon, and she said,
"Ha Neul is going to serve the military soon."
(She's after Seo Joon then.)
What are you thinking all by yourself?
She keeps struggling...
to choose between you two.
(She picked Seo Joon.)
- It's driving me crazy. - Date him until he joins the army.
Look how she applied lip gloss on her lips.
What's up with you?
(Shy)
So Hyun is well-known in SBS for not being hygienic.
She washed up today.
(The guests made her wash up.)
I can't believe this.
I'm sorry, but is that makeup on your face?
(She's a bodyguard.)
(Even a bodyguard put her makeup on today.)
- What? - Are you serious?
- Yes. - She applied makeup on her face.
I mean, we're close friends.
- I've never seen her smile before. - I mean...
- She's very unusual today. - Goodness.
She usually doesn't show any face expressions.
She usually never smiles.
- She's different today. - She's smiling.
Let's move on to the first mission where you can earn hints.
It's called, Show Me Your Charm.
(Find the Boss, Show Me Your Charm)
There are your talents and names written on those two roulettes.
You'll spin each roulette.
The selected person will show off their corresponding talent.
The staff judges give them marks, and the scores will be recorded.
Anyone can challenge others.
The person with the highest score in each area will be given a hint.
- A person who places first. - I see.
Team Police will be given a hint about the boss.
Team Boss will be given a hint about the money bag.
- Good. - Goodness.
Let's do well.
(My police friends, let's do this.)
(Is he the undercover officer?)
Don't try to get their attention.
Don't mind him.
Don't mind him at all.
Why do you keep doing this?
(When everyone is relaxed, someone is feeling very anxious.)
(Guys, they're all villains.)
Tell us honestly.
Do you have anyone in mind who you think is the undercover officer?
- Go with your first impression. - Right.
I first thought...
Ms. Jeon might be the one.
Ms. Jeon?
Why?
Call me So Min.
(Ha Neul, you can call me So Min.)
(It's okay.)
(What was that just now, So Min?)
Did you forget you're older than him?
My goodness, she's incredible.
- What are you doing? - What was that?
- It's how we used to flirt. - Goodness.
- Gosh. - She's scary.
So Min didn't say it normally either.
"Call me So Min."
(She sounded full of cuteness.)
Call me So Min.
(Ha Neul was flustered by her flirting.)
- What do you think you're doing? - I can't believe this.
Who do you think is the undercover officer, Seo Joon?
I think...
(Seo Joon, please.)
- I think it's Jong Kook. - You guessed right.
- That's how you feel now. - That makes me upset.
(The police are guessing wrong when he's right here.)
They were suspicious of me all the time,
and they're ignoring me completely today.
I think he's really upset.
There's nothing to be upset about.
Because I'm the undercover officer.
(He's frustrated.)
They're going for another person, and it's making me frustrated.
If you're the one, I'm the undercover officer too.
- You? - Yes.
If you're an undercover officer, then I am too.
Judging by the way you talk, you must be the boss.
(Why do you have to say it like that?)
That's right.
- It says so on your shirt. - That's me.
Quiet ones are likely to be undercover officers.
(It's definitely not Kwang Soo.)
Gosh, your face expression.
You look so serious.
(He successfully confuses Team Police.)
All right. Seo Joon and Ha Neul will spin the roulettes first.
- Okay. - All right.
- Ha Neul, please go ahead. - Me?
- Should I spin the one with names? - Yes, you should spin that first.
I have never spun a roulette before.
- I can just spin it, can't I? - Of course.
He's so cute.
All right. I will spin it.
(The staff members laugh.)
I will spin it.
- Okay. - Wait a second.
- Hold on, everyone. - Spin it.
Why is this funny?
Why did you laugh?
- What was funny about his line? - Is that so important now?
What was funny about that?
- So Hyun, why are you blushing? - I've never seen her like that.
- What is happening? - She likes him that much?
You didn't even laugh when my pants were taken off.
(He's feeling bitter.)
(The crew didn't laugh like this when his underwear was exposed.)
After all I've done...
I heard the crew staff watching that clip when they were editing.
- He's such a nice guy. - I haven't spun it yet.
- I'll spin this. - Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
I'm curious which one will be picked.
- I bet he's not really curious. - "Which one will it be?"
What has Ha Neul picked?
(The first chance for Team Police to guess who the undercover officer is)
- Is it dancing? - Is it showing charms?
- Is it the charm? - Is it dancing?
- It's dancing. - I see. It's dancing.
- It's dancing. - Will it be a dance battle?
(The 1st round: Show Me Your Charm)
It's dancing.
- Play us the music. - Play a song for us.
- You know when people rap, - If you put on a good song...
- people rap in a cypher. - That's true.
- We should dance just like that. - Okay.
We will play the music, and you will evaluate right away.
We will keep playing songs.
If no one is dancing to a song, we will move on to the next song.
Please put on a song for us.
Let's go!
(Feeling the water)
(Wait. This isn't the song.)
- I already danced. - You don't know this song.
This song doesn't suit my taste in music.
Haha, that's great.
Let's keep going. Someone should dance. So Min?
- She's moving forward. - She's dancing.
- Look at her. - What's wrong with you?
Why is she being like that?
(What's wrong with you?)
- What's wrong with you? - What's the matter with her?
(She dances with her skirt.)
(The male judges are not even slightly affected.)
(Hey, cold-heated judges. So Min is on the move.)
(Ji Hyo is startled.)
What's the matter with her?
(She approaches them in a sexy and confident manner.)
(She begins dancing right before their eyes.)
What is wrong with her?
(She shows no reactions.)
(Hold on. What? What was that?)
(Her 1st attempt fails, and she targets Jae Seok's cameraman next.)
(Flapping)
(Please just go.)
(She desperately flaps for him, but it doesn't work at all.)
(He doesn't respond at all.)
(She finishes with sexy gestures.)
All right. That was So Min.
In 1, 2, 3. Evaluate her dance.
(So Min receives 10 points.)
(I'm satisfied with my score.)
So Min earned 10 points.
(Her dance earned 10 points?)
(Ji Hyo, feeling confident, moves forward.)
- Ji Hyo is dancing. - It's Ji Hyo.
(She gives off a relaxed vibe as she's been on the show for 7 years.)
Her socks look like the dish sponge made of steel.
She's dancing with those socks.
What's going on with Ji Hyo?
(Exposing)
(She sensually gets her groove on.)
(Ji Hyo, the queen, has descended. Everyone is going crazy for her.)
(The panelists are starting to show some interest.)
(You thought I was only sensual?)
(I can do some cute dance moves too.)
(Ji Hyo, you are a good dancer.)
This is...
Ji Hyo, that's right. Great!
(She even demonstrates some adorable footwork with the socks.)
That was a good one.
That was excellent. She danced well.
It was great.
Ji Hyo. Look at your score.
(Oh, my! My score is really high!)
- Well done. - She did very well.
- She got a lot of points. - Gosh.
- All right. - She's a good dancer.
(The fourth song is played.)
This song.
I like this song. My dance moves go perfectly with the song.
(The uplifting beat makes them move.)
(Should I dance too?)
Kwang Soo, you're going to dance?
- Haha, you should dance. - Kwang Soo, you're going to dance?
Kwang Soo!
(They've seen it before and don't have any expectations.)
(He reveals his back.)
(And now, he's dancing only with his bottoms.)
- So Hyun gave him a look. - I don't know where to look.
(The guys find Kwang Soo's move interesting.)
- Hey, that's good. - So Hyun.
(However)
(The ladies show no interest in his dance at all.)
They will evaluate now.
In 1, 2, 3. Show us the score.
Look. He got negative five points.
(Someone in the panel gave Kwang Soo...)
(negative 5 points?)
(Kwang Soo gets negative 3 points.)
His final score is negative three points.
His score is negative three points.
We're going to continue.
(The fifth song is played.)
All right. Ha Neul, do you like this song?
- Ha Neul. - What do you think?
- Go and dance! - That's all right. Come.
(Ha Neul, you should dance.)
(With Ha Neul's dance, the real dance competition begins now.)
Let's go!
(Ha Neul shows off unexpected dance skills.)
(The path he walks on is covered with a red carpet.)
(I just saved Ha Neul in my heart.)
(We're going to keep him in our hearts forever.)
(Ha Neul is the best!)
(I'm happy that I decided to join Running Man's crew.)
(Wiping)
(This wipe-the-floor dance move is new.)
(She can't keep her composure.)
(His dance move is appealing to the ladies.)
(I came here to catch the boss, but I ended up wiping the floor.)
(I'm the king of this floor.)
I can't dance.
What is his score?
(Ha Neul says he can't dance. What score did he get?)
(He gets 350 points from someone.)
- What are you doing? - No way.
(Do you think that makes sense?)
- This is ridiculous. - Is this how you're going to play?
- Goodness. I can't believe it. - By the way,
the bodyguard gave Ha Neul the highest score she could give.
She gave him 5 points.
That was the highest score she could give.
The final score is 363 points.
He got 363 points, but I got negative 3 points?
(Ha Neul's score is 363 points, and Kwang Soo's is negative 5 points.)
(The difference is 368 points.)
But the thing is that even the bodyguard...
gave Ha Neul the highest score she could give him.
Thank you.
The first round goes to Ha Neul.
(The winner, Ha Neul, acquires a hint.)
All right.
I want expression.
- It's power. - Power.
It's about power.
- Jong Kook has the upper hand. - He's at an advantage.
(Let me properly show you my charm.)
(Which one of them will get to show off their power?)
- He's so handsome. - He's right here.
Seo Joon just picked himself. It's him.
(This is an era where everyone promotes themselves.)
(The last member who defeats Seo Joon will receive the hint.)
- Who is that? - You should've practiced first.
Seo Joon spun the roulette and chose himself.
Since all of you said that you were undercover officers,
- you will let him win, won't you? - That's right. Wait, no.
The undercover officer should let him win.
Ha Neul, you are sharp.
He is indeed.
This time, you will play Leg Wrestling to show your charm.
(The 2nd round: Leg Wrestling)
(I will teach you a lesson with this game.)
I think Se Chan will win.
The undercover officer will...
- tire us out in this round. - Se Chan will win.
(I have to help Team Police win this round.)
Get ready.
- Set. - Go easy on me.
- I can just make them split, right? - Right.
(We are both villains. Let's go easy on each other.)
Start.
(In pain)
(I won't go easy on you.)
It's over.
(The game ended in less than a second.)
I won't let you off, Haha.
Next challenger, come forward.
Whoever is next, come.
- Se Chan is good. - Who's next?
(I will beat everyone and get the hint for the money bag.)
- He's that powerful? - Seok Jin.
- He's no joke. - Come here.
He's really strong.
Start.
(Screaming)
(Se Chan shows off his manly side.)
- I'm not lying. - Who's next?
I'm telling the truth.
- Who are you? - I'm serious.
- I wasn't trying to be funny. - What is this?
Seok Jin, you didn't try to be funny, did you?
- He's really strong. - Goodness, Se Chan.
- Gosh. - Look at you, Se Chan.
- You're that strong? - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, you should go next.
Through this game,
I will show you that I am the undercover officer.
Get ready. Start.
(Screaming)
(You have to do better than that, undercover officer.)
Stop. That's enough.
Se Chan is really strong.
- It wasn't even close. - Se Chan is...
- Se Chan is the strongest. - Kwang Soo.
Who's next?
Who's next? Jong Kook.
Se Chan. Hey.
Goodness, Se Chan.
Look at Jong Kook.
(His legs are as thick as a mammoth's.)
You're going to try to widen the gap first?
Or do you want to go first?
- He must be tired by now. - Get ready.
- That's true. - Set.
If you want this game to be fair...
(Punching)
(The undercover officer makes the game more fair.)
I should punch them. I did it to make the game fair.
- It's only fair. Se Chan is tired. - Good job.
- Se Chan used up a lot of energy. - Kwang Soo.
- Hold on. - That hurt.
He used up a lot of his energy.
- He caught me off guard. - I was trying to make this fair.
- It should be a fair game. - Okay.
- You're amazing. - Hey, Kwang Soo.
("A fair society is not far away from us." Lee Kwang Soo)
- Get ready. - That was amazing.
Set.
Goodness. Wait. Hold on, Jong Kook.
(Wait. We didn't even start yet.)
You're hurting me. Give me a second.
- We didn't start yet. - Okay, fine.
Start.
(As soon as it begins, he starts laughing.)
- Jong Kook wins. - It's over.
(As expected, Se Chan's unexpected charm stops here.)
- Ha Neul, you should try it. - Did you see that?
Ha Neul's lower body is strong too.
- By the way, Team Police... - Goodness, Jong Kook.
You're the undercover officer, aren't you?
(I have a feeling Jong Kook is the undercover officer.)
Are you the undercover officer?
Well... Later...
- The undercover officer... - Seo Joon...
- Seo Joon and I are the police. - Yes.
(If Jong Kook is an officer, he'll try to help the police.)
Wait.
I'm scared.
It hurts.
It really hurts.
Strong Sky, don't be like that.
- All right. - Ha Neul, you have strong legs.
All right.
Eliminate him as soon as the game starts.
- Take it easy. - All right.
Start.
Ha Neul is holding out.
He's strong.
(Surprised)
- You're strong. - He's strong.
(Both are determined to win.)
(Who will win the hint?)
(I'm the passionate police, Kang Ha Neul.)
(Screaming)
(You can see how much pain he is in.)
Wait.
- Good job. - Good job.
Good job.
(You can go now.)
Good job, Ha Neul.
- Ha Neul. - It's not because you're weak.
Jong Kook won, right?
(It's hard to be the police.)
It hurts.
- Is it my turn now? - It is.
Let's give him a big hand.
(Will Seo Joon be able to beat Jong Kook?)
Jong Kook is impossible to beat.
(Will he be able to win the hint about the boss?)
How am I supposed to beat Jong Kook?
(The police have to win.)
(But it's the wrong match.)
Ready.
One more time. Here you go.
Gosh.
I mean,
it's to be fair.
It's to be fair.
You need to lose a bit of energy.
Jong Kook.
Is this okay?
Can he do that?
- Why isn't anyone stopping him? - This is the finals.
- This is the finals. - He hit me three times.
He hit me three times.
Three times.
- Three times is okay. - Didn't you see that?
Three times is okay.
Calm down.
(It feels like the police have just won.)
- Ready. - Goodness.
Ready.
- I don't know what to do. - Seo Joon works out a lot too.
(The king has become weak. I'll show you a miracle.)
(His body has been trained through action scenes.)
(When it comes to strength, I'm confident.)
Warm up your body.
His legs feel strong.
(Will the police miraculously win?)
- Start. - Nice.
(His legs spread.)
(His legs are forced to spread.)
(Jong Kook is amazing.)
This is Jong Kook.
I'm sorry.
Jong Kook is the power boss.
(Jong Kook is the power boss.)
This was pointless.
Expression would be the best.
(Show Me Your Charm)
- What is "expression"? - What is "expression"?
- Expression... - Cuteness...
- Cuteness. - It's cuteness.
Cuteness.
- Cuteness? - So Min is going to win.
- It's Haha. - Please.
- Haha. - Haha.
(Haha has to go first.)
I hate it.
This is hard.
But you're good at it.
Haha used to be very good at it.
- But now... - He has kids now.
He has become shy.
- But you have no choice. - I have no choice.
Don't worry. You don't have to win.
You don't have to win.
(Shy)
Is he supposed to just start?
Like this?
(Just here?)
Aren't you going to give me an example?
No.
Is he just supposed to act cute?
Just like this?
- Yes. - Without any help?
That would be a problem.
(That would be a problem.)
(Shocked)
(Cute)
I can't do this if you don't give me any lines.
(Doesn't he just look stupid?)
- The score... - 1, 2, 3.
Don't be like that.
I'm disappointed.
- He won three points. - I'll fart if I'm upset.
(What is he saying?)
- Excuse me, I'm very curious... - Don't do this to me.
why you gave him three points.
Why did you give him three points?
- Why did you do that? - Otherwise, he wouldn't go away.
- He was trying. - He was trying.
Thank you.
Ji Hyo, you should try.
- There you go. - You look cute.
You look cute now.
- You look very cute. - You look cute.
Here it comes.
Let's go.
(She's ready to be cute.)
- You're doing great. - Should we give her a situation?
Someone is leaving,
and you want to stop him.
- Right. - Her boyfriend is leaving her.
That's right. Ji Hyo.
You think you could give him your everything.
I'm leaving.
(It's time for Ji Hyo to be cute.)
Here it comes.
Honey, don't go.
(Honey, don't go.)
Isn't that a gangster?
Isn't that the movie "Friend"?
"I've had enough."
- All right. - Wait.
- You want to try again? - You know, I love you
Gosh.
(Giving up)
(For the tough Ji Hyo, this is a difficult mission.)
1, 2, 3.
What?
50 points?
Thank you.
You know, I love you
He gave her 50 points.
He has finally revealed his taste.
He's blushing.
He likes Ji Hyo.
Gosh, this is so hard.
- Jong Kook. - If Jong Kook does it,
- It'll be awesome. - it'll have an impact.
Can you give me a situation?
Well...
Let's say you're at a gym.
(It's his home ground.)
Someone is drinking a protein shake.
- He wants a sip. - Someone is doing something wrong.
I want to correct her.
A girl is doing an exercise incorrectly.
Let's do that.
(Thinking)
(I can do this.)
(To win the hint,)
(he has to win the most points.)
(Sulking)
(Don't do that.)
The floor just vibrated.
(His footsteps are shaking the place.)
What is this?
What's that?
You shouldn't do that.
(You shouldn't do that.)
- What? - What is with him?
(What is wrong with him?)
Are you crazy?
(Too cute)
He's crazy.
(Scared)
You're crazy.
(He gets kicked.)
Wake up.
- Are you crazy? - What?
- I'm cute, aren't I? - Pull yourself together.
(Sulking)
It was so scary.
- It was really scary. - How was it?
You'll get minus points.
- Minus 20 points. - Minus 20 points.
What?
2 of them gave him 4 points.
Gosh.
- That was crazy. - I did an amazing job.
You were very cute.
(I'm being generous.)
So Min...
So Min is good at it.
Let's say So Min is late.
Something happened to her family, so she's late.
Let's start. Seo Joon, say something.
What time is it? Why are you so late?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm late.
(Shocked)
I'm sorry.
(What is this?)
- Forgive me. - Look at Seo Joon.
- Seo Joon is still angry. - Please forgive me.
Next boyfriend.
(Next boyfriend)
(It's not just because she's late.)
All right. So Min.
This is how you broke up with Seo Joon.
He couldn't accept it.
You broke up with him.
And then you got a new boyfriend.
All right. This time,
Ha Neul is late.
Both of them are cute.
What should I do?
Start.
I'm sorry. My bus was late.
The subway was late too.
It's okay, Ha Neul.
Ha Neul, it's okay.
This is not a kindergarten.
(This is not a kindergarten.)
You're supposed to be cute.
So Min, speak clearly.
- Speak clearly. - Speak clearly.
- Stop mumbling. - You're doing it wrong.
- You're a grown-up. - She's a four-year-old.
You're not a kid. Try again.
Gosh.
But some people speak that way.
- You're right. - You're right.
Start.
My bus was late, and my subway was late too.
- Okay. - So...
- So... - Okay.
That's why I'm late. I'm sorry.
Is she a baby?
It's okay. Ha Neul.
I love you.
(Ha Neul, I love you.)
- I love you more. - I love you.
(The studio is full of love.)
I love you more.
What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - What?
- I mean... - Are you jealous?
- Why would she say she loves him? - Are you jealous?
They're not supposed to say they love each other.
- Are you jealous? - They're supposed to be cute.
- They're not in love. - What is this?
What are you doing?
He's jealous. It's strange.
It's strange.
Let's see So Min's score.
Please show us.
15 points.
So Min tried so hard, but So Hyun gave her only one point.
That's mean.
You're also mean.
Let's find out Ha Neul's score.
- I bet it's high. - 1, 2, 3.
(What is Ha Neul's score?)
My goodness.
His total score is 85.
(Thank you for being generous.)
By the way,
- the bodyguard gave him... - Thank you.
- five points. - It's the highest score.
She gave him the highest score.
(The highest she could give was 5 points.)
(You were very cute, Ha Neul.)
She couldn't give 40 points like the others,
but she gave him her perfect score.
- Thank you. - Next up is Seo Joon.
Seo Joon is good.
I'll do it in front of the judges.
Please go ahead.
Which judge?
I'll do it for So Hyun.
My goodness.
So Hyun, it's game over.
(She's overwhelmed by gratitude.)
So Hyun.
(Park Seo Joon comes toward her.)
You'll be happy from now on.
(We've never seen such a big smile on her face.)
I'm jealous.
Goodness.
- Stay focused, So Hyun. - She's blushing.
You're a judge. You're still working.
She's blushing.
Start.
(Her heart flutters just by looking at him.)
Look at him in the eyes.
So Hyun.
When other members give you a hard time,
I feel very bad.
(Laughing)
(So Hyun is knocked out.)
(She doesn't feel bad at all.)
That's it. It's game over.
(That's it for today's shoot.)
(What's wrong with him?)
- Keep going. - Keep going.
Why are you over there?
Leave me alone. He's so cute.
May I do it again to another judge?
Of course.
He's getting greedy.
So Min, sit down.
(Seo Joon attempts to act cute in front of the bodyguard.)
Her highest score is five points.
- Will he break the record? - Will he earn more than five?
(The charismatic judge always remained objective.)
(Go ahead, and give it a try.)
He's kneeling.
(He kneels in front of her. Will he win her heart?)
If you don't give me a high score,
I'll be sad.
(If you don't give me a high score, I'll be sad.)
(She tries not to smile.)
(He ends with a cute sound.)
(Yoon Jung is also knocked out.)
She also fell for him.
She fell.
(She gives him 50 points.)
It's 50 points.
She gave him 50 points.
She gave you 50 points.
(It's a celebration.)
- Let's see. - It worked.
1, 2, 3.
Goodness.
(The scores become much higher.)
His total score is 621.
(Seo Joon has the highest score.)
(He wants to try as well.)
(Frightened)
(She reacts as if he's a harmful insect.)
(They get rid of him.)
- You're under arrest. - Stop it.
I'm an undercover officer.
- I'm an undercover officer. - You're under arrest.
Don't worry.
We'll put him in prison.
What do you mean?
What did I do wrong?
I feel sad too.
(I feel sad too.)
(He has feelings too.)
I feel very sad.
(Don't be biased.)
Goodness.
Kwang Soo is sad too.
(Kwang Soo's cuteness fails.)
We'll give you a hint.
- You may not share it with others. - Really?
- Do you keep it to yourself? - We can't share it?
Team Police gets a hint about Team Boss.
Team Boss gets a hint about the location of the money bag.
(The hint about the money bag is 70. What does the number mean?)
(He hopes that the police will trust him soon.)
We don't know since we're just starting.
- That's right. - Let's move to the next location.
Let's go.
(Let's get another hint from the next game.)
It may be simpler than we think.
(Team Police reads their two hints.)
"The boss uses his or her real name."
Real name?
- Kwang Soo is his real name. - Right.
Doesn't it only exclude Haha?
It excludes Haha.
It's also Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo isn't her real name. - That's right.
(Haha and Ji Hyo are excluded.)
We can exclude Haha and Ji Hyo.
- That's right. - Right.
- They could probably be one of us. - Right, right.
What's next?
(What's the second hint?)
"The boss has appeared in movies."
- Who could it be? - How about Se Chan?
I don't think he appeared in movies.
What if he did?
We'll be in trouble.
(It's that simple.)
He might be in movies that we don't know about.
Who's the undercover officer?
Isn't it Haha?
- That's what I think. - He gave signals.
It was excessive.
Here's what I think.
Others may feel unsettled if I say this.
I think the boss is...
(The most important identity, the boss, is...)
Kwang Soo.
- I think so too. - Really?
(They think the boss is the undercover officer, Kwang Soo.)
During the first mission,
when I said that I was the undercover officer,
Jae Seok said that he was also the undercover officer.
Out of the blue,
Kwang Soo mentioned something about being the boss.
- Really? - He said one of us was the boss.
He brought it up at an awkward timing.
(Kwang Soo must be the boss.)
Let's go.
I'll win today no matter what.
(Will they find the real boss?)
(It's a swimming pool in Yangju, Gyeonggi Province,)
(that awaits the villains and the police.)
This mission is a team competition.
A team competition?
It's called Find the Three.
- "Find the Three"? - Yes.
One member from each team who gives...
3 correct answers within 5 seconds wins.
It's a five-second quiz competition.
Two members from each team participate.
One sits in a chair while the other answers the questions.
If Team Police wins,
The member in the chair is thrown into the water.
He or she will be sent to Team Police.
When there are five members on each team,
both teams will move to the next location.
(5 Team Police members ride the same car.)
That's how the teams are divided.
- I see. - This is important.
- We should be strategic. - That's right.
We should take those whom we think are the undercover officer.
- True. - That's right.
(It's me, Ha Neul and Seo Joon.)
- That's right. - It'll be advantageous.
(I'm the undercover officer.)
(He looks around.)
(I'm the real police.)
(Is it really Haha?)
Haha and Kwang Soo, stop sending them signals.
- They keep sending signals. - Stop it.
What are you doing?
They'll recognize the truth.
- Jae Seok. - Stop it.
- They'll recognize the truth. - Stop.
(You know who it is.)
That's right.
Haha, sit in the chair.
- I'll sit first. - Ha Neul.
- I'll go first. - I will.
(It's Ha Neul versus Kwang Soo.)
Ha Neul is up. Both of you have to sit at some point.
(To recruit Haha, Ha Neul must win.)
Last time when I was on Running Man,
I was traumatized by quizzes with a time limit of few seconds.
- It's difficult. - It is.
The colors of a secondary rainbow are reversed.
Say the rainbow colors in reverse within three seconds.
- Wait. - 3, 2...
- One. - Violet, indigo...
(He fails.)
Violet, indigo, blue, green, yellow, orange, and red.
(He falls off.)
(He has a painful memory of humiliation.)
The answer has to make sense.
It has to make some sense.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Who are three female celebrities you've dated?
Jun Ji Hyun.
Jung Yu Mi and...
- Gosh, I'm sorry. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo wins with his smart question.)
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
(Splash)
(The losing team member falls into the water automatically.)
(That must feel refreshing.)
You get thrown immediately.
(It's rather humiliating.)
Are you okay?
Isn't it cold?
(Haha stays with Team Boss.)
Come to the front, Seo Joon.
- Have a seat. - Please sit.
Get ready.
- Do I question him first? - 3 answers in 5 seconds.
(Recruiting Ji Hyo is advantageous to Team Police.)
Ask him a hard question.
Who are the women who've visited your home?
(He names three random women.)
What did you say?
(What has Kwang Soo done?)
(Who is she?)
May I do it again?
What did you say?
(He was blinded by his desire to win.)
- May I do it again? - Are you okay?
(Names of 3 female celebrities whom he's dated)
(He names three women out of anger.)
(He gave the same, exact names.)
(Pretend that you didn't hear me.)
What's wrong with him?
- Come on. - He lost his mind.
(Kwang Soo gives up, and Team Police recruits Ji Hyo.)
She's recruited.
She'll join your team,
- so I did a good job. - They recruited Ji Hyo.
(Team Police doesn't know that Ji Hyo is a villain.)
(I wanted to recruit her.)
- I wanted to recruit her. - Trust me.
- That's true. - Do you want to try, So Min?
Well...
(I need to get recruited as well.)
It's this team's turn to answer.
- Is it? - Yes.
- It's So Min's turn. - So Min, try.
- Me? - Try.
- Our magnetic girl. - Okay.
- Our hero. - Our magnetic girl.
Show him.
All right.
Seo Joon will sit there.
- I'm the police. - You're not.
Try.
(Ji Hyo tells him what to ask.)
- Try. - All right.
Start.
Give me three reasons why you like me.
(Give me 3 reasons why you like me.)
(Tell me why you like me in 5 seconds.)
I just like you. Everything. Everything.
- What's that? - That's not okay.
This is not truth or dare.
- That's not okay. - This is not truth or dare.
(Reality hits.)
What is she doing?
Is she shooting a drama?
(I'm sorry.)
(I have somewhere to go.)
- Where are you going? - Where are you going?
She's crazy.
You said I could say anything.
Still...
(They'll play the game one more time.)
"I just like you. Everything. Everything?"
All right. Ha Neul will attack again.
I can't look him in the face.
I can't look him in the eye.
You're so girly.
Here we go.
Tell me three of Kwang Soo's strengths.
(That's an easy one.)
He's tall, handsome, and cool.
That was so hard.
(He's tall, handsome, and cool.)
(She had to lie for the game.)
She just said whatever.
(Look at you.)
Kwang Soo is happy.
Why do you look so happy?
He's so ugly.
I'll start.
Give me three reasons why you don't like me.
(That can't be too hard to answer.)
(Laughing)
You're so pretty that I feel uncomfortable.
And...
Gosh.
Is it that hard?
I can't believe him.
You just don't want me, do you?
(Kwang Soo can't transfer to Team Police.)
Hey!
You can't win like this.
- I'm the police! - Go back to your place.
This is so frustrating.
- I'm sorry. - I mean it.
- Goodness. - I'm the undercover officer!
Pull yourself together!
I'm sorry!
(Seo Joon goes into the water, and Kwang Soo stays on Team Boss.)
- Why are you sorry? - Why?
(Seo Joon gets to play in the water thanks to Running Man.)
It's better for me to do it.
Everyone stays.
- Seok Jin, why don't you try? - Me?
- Okay. - Seok Jin, try.
- Seok Jin. - Okay.
Here we go.
- Let's do this. - Here we go.
Who want to try?
This is crazy.
(Team Police has to pick a person to recruit.)
(Approaching)
(Team Police should...)
(Why is Haha doing that?)
Jae Seok.
Stop it, Haha.
We're a team.
It's me.
I'm staying quiet on purpose.
- I mean it. - Seriously...
He said he was being quiet.
- My goodness. - I can't say three things.
Okay.
Give me three reasons why you don't like Ha Neul.
He's handsome, pretty, and kind.
- Then why do you not like him? - I just don't like him.
Ji Hyo is so good at this game.
Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin looks so flustered. - Ji Hyo is so good at this game.
It's too obvious.
Give me three reasons why your marriage life is great.
She is a good cook, wakes up late, and goes out often.
- She goes out often? - Where?
Are they good things?
- She's busy? - Are they good things?
(Seok Jin spoke on behalf of all married men.)
What are you doing?
He just said whatever.
I don't understand the game.
He doesn't understand the game.
What are your three charms?
I'm pretty, kind, and sexy.
Amazing.
(I'm pretty, kind, and sexy.)
- She's so good. - You're so shameless.
She's so calm.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
What are three lies you tell your wife?
"I'll be home early."
"The shooting is over."
There are so many.
- "I love you." - "The shooting is over."
(There are too many to choose from.)
- Am I going into the water? - Yes.
(Jae Seok is transferred to Team Police.)
We've already lost two.
You look so ugly right now.
- Don't fix your hair. - Okay.
It's perfect now.
It's perfect.
Ji Hyo is too good.
(What will happen to the undercover officer, Kwang Soo?)
- Okay. - Seo Joon.
- If So Min... - With So Min.
So Min, try again.
- Just confess your feelings. - Let's do it.
It's So Min's lucky day today.
(So Min can't look at Seo Joon.)
Who will win?
So Min.
I don't understand why you're doing this.
- I don't understand. - We're so confused.
- She can't help it. - Which do you like better?
It's 100 percent Seo Joon.
Which do you like better?
(Seo Joon can come off cold, but he is kind to me.)
(Ha Neul always smiles to me.)
(What am I supposed to do?)
I don't understand why she's torn between the two.
Neither do I.
(The police and the villain are not meant to be together.)
She's so happy.
I understand her.
- I understand her. - So Min.
Kwang Soo must understand her.
All right. Let's go.
(The fifth round starts.)
Tell me three guys you've kissed recently.
- Say it. - Say it.
(Tell me 3 guys you've kissed recently.)
(She can say whatever names in 5 seconds.)
- Say it. - Say it.
(Flustered)
I'll say people I like. Ahn Jae Hong, Won Bin...
Why?
My goodness.
You could have just said whatever names.
- You could have said our names. - Don't try to be girly.
You're a magnetic girl.
Pull yourself together.
You could have said just any names.
Why did you do that?
(Seok Jin is transferred to Team Police.)
We've played Find the Three.
Ji Hyo, Jae Seok, and Seok Jin have been...
transferred to Team Police.
Kwang Soo, Se Chan, Jong Kook, and So Min are...
Team Boss.
- Let's move to another place. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They move to their next destination.)
Ha Neul.
(It's me.)
This is so frustrating.
(Haha can't stop pretending to be the police.)
- Are you the police? - Yes.
You'll see.
- You'll see. - I'll show you.
You should trust me, not him.
I can't lie.
Just watch me. I'll show you.
- Watch me. - I'll show you.
- I'll show you. - Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, I'm sorry, but please be quiet.
(Please let the police talk.)
You shouldn't do this.
Give me a chance.
- Give me a chance. - Ha Neul.
Watch me.
(Will Kwang Soo win their trust?)
Seo Joon, have you found any hints?
Yes, I have.
By the way,
except us two,
the others don't know who the boss is, right?
- Do you know who it is? - I don't because I'm undercover.
Can you...
Can you guess who the undercover police is?
Seo Joon, Ha Neul.
I can't believe you guys.
You think too much.
(Tapping)
(It's me.)
- Are you the police? - Yes.
Were you sending them signals?
Gosh, you're so sly.
- You're next to them, so... - I mean...
I'm telling them because I am the police.
Seok Jin, when did you find out you were the undercover officer?
- When did I find out? - Yes.
(Hesitating)
(What is this awkward hesitation?)
I'll tell you precisely.
Right before the water game.
- Right before the water game? - Yes.
Right before the water game?
They told us in the beginning.
That's right. I forgot.
After all those water splashes...
- Water splashes? - You didn't get splashed.
I got splashed with water.
He might be acting.
No. I'm not good at that.
I'm so curious how it'll end.
You don't have to be. I'll be with you.
- Hey. - That sounded so fake.
Gosh, Seo Joon, I can't believe you.
It sounded fake?
(Who will the police trust in the final race?)
(Kwang Soo is surrounded by villains.)
Mr. Lee, let's go.
Don't do that in front of Jong Kook and Haha.
I'm doing this because they are here.
I don't want to keep talking.
Please speak on behalf of me.
Don't look back. Keep your eyes to the front.
(Se Chan mimics Jong Kook.)
Stop pretending.
He didn't tell you to speak so rudely.
- You didn't? - It's okay.
You can speak rudely when you speak on behalf of me.
- Gosh. - What?
No, I was talking to So Min.
- What? - You should...
stop making things too obvious.
It's too obvious.
- What are you doing? - We're on different teams.
We're being careful.
Just because you're the police,
do you think you can be so stuck-up?
- Kwang Soo. - Is that what Jong Kook thinks?
Hold on to the steering wheel. Look straight. We'll talk.
Use both hands. Don't take them off.
Right. Don't mess around.
(So Min pitches in.)
(What are you saying?)
- That's what Jong Kook said. - That was out of nowhere.
That's what Jong Kook is thinking.
How do you know what he's thinking all of a sudden?
They know exactly what I'm thinking.
You're not just a villain in the fairytales.
You're a thug.
(You're a thug.)
Jong Kook is?
- Then our boss is... - It's Seok Jin.
Is it advantageous for Seok Jin to be on the other team?
Then our boss is...
- It's Seok Jin. - Is it advantageous for him?
(Did you just say...)
(Seok Jin was the boss?)
No, we're done if he gets caught.
- We can't tell him. - We're done.
- He doesn't know. - We can't tell him.
(He doesn't know who the boss is.)
(I get it. Seok Jin is the boss.)
We're in trouble.
(Nodding)
What? Here.
That was real.
(Kwang Soo is certain Seok Jin is the boss now.)
(Did the villains make a mistake, or was it intentional?)
- Oh, dear. - Oh, dear.
What's this?
I think the chef...
boiled this for hours.
- This is unbelievable. - He softened it.
Look at the marinated crab.
(Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo passed the restaurant mission.)
This rib melts in my mouth.
(Only they get to eat.)
(He forgets about the sorrow of being an undercover officer.)
Let me have some side dishes.
Don't ask.
(The rest of them get rice, seaweed, and soy sauce marinated crab.)
(He's sick of eating seaweed.)
This crab is insane.
(He stands up.)
Water.
I'm so hungry.
It's been a while.
(It's been a while.)
Please let me pay my respects.
- Oh, dear. - Oh, dear.
(May you live long and be happy.)
Oh, dear.
I was eating,
and realized that it's been a while since I've paid my respects to you.
Give him that.
(He's thankful.)
(It's not a lot.)
Keep it.
(He gives him a seaweed.)
Please keep it.
We can't give you much.
(There's an anti-bribery act, so we can't give you much.)
(I'm happy I didn't try anything.)
- Do you want some of this? - There are seven vegetables.
- Wait, can I have some? - Okay.
- Can I whisper to you? - Whisper?
- I heard that. - Hold on.
- I heard that. - He...
(Kwang Soo is in shock.)
He called me a dog.
You're mistaken.
I wouldn't say that.
He's very dear to me. That's not possible.
You heard it wrong.
- You... - I heard it wrong, right?
I can't believe him.
(I need to get some food.)
Then if you can lick your nose, I'll give you a piece of meat.
- Really? - Just one?
Yes, I'll give you a piece.
- I can do it. - Try it.
(She sticks her tongue out.)
It has to touch here.
(She tries diligently.)
(He finds it funny.)
You're touching the top of your upper lip.
- Kwang Soo. - It has to touch the tip.
Please give me one.
Your tongue has to touch the tip of your nose.
(Kwang Soo, please give me one.)
(He's a silly policeman.)
It has to touch the tip.
(He looks like a dork.)
(He succumbs to reality.)
He was hesitating.
Let's see, Ha Neul.
- Hello. Thank you. - Oh, dear.
- Please try it. - Can I have a rice cake?
One rice cake? I can do that.
- One rice cake? - That one's good.
The fish...
- Hello. - We're friends.
I'm Jang Moon Bok.
It's me, it's me
- You can't do that. - It's me, it's me
(Moon Bok is back with seaweed on his hair.)
- It's me, it's me - I'll give you some.
(The rib belongs to me.)
- I'll give you a piece. - He deserves it.
I'm Jang Moon Bok.
(What's Haha working on now?)
(What is it?)
Everybody, whom do I look like?
- Kim Bo Sung. - Whom do I look like?
- Loyalty. - Loyalty.
Is it Park Sang Min?
No.
(It's neither Kim Bo Sung...)
(nor Park Sang Min.)
Then?
(Haha is impersonating...)
I'm Wolverine.
Really?
(Haha is impersonating Wolverine?)
(Running Man: The Wolverine)
(That was an unexpected transformation.)
Haha.
Look.
(Viewers are impressed by his enthusiasm for the rib.)
He's a genius.
(He deserves two pieces of meat for that.)
- Haha. - That was amazing.
He's a gem.
He's a genius.
Three of you won earlier, so here are your hints.
- Yes. - Yes.
I got no hints today.
- I'm envious. - Me too.
If you're a villain, you'll get a hint about the money bag.
If you're an undercover officer, you'll get one about the boss.
(The boss' name has the letter "S" in it.)
I don't need this hint,
but it does confirm my suspicions.
If you have any idea, you'll know. Never mind.
I think he's the boss.
(The final race remains.)
(What will happen to the villains and the undercover officer?)
We don't have any other way.
- We have to frame Kwang Soo. - Okay.
That's our only way.
- Ha Neul... - We can frame him,
- but don't make it too obvious. - Right.
We're lucky because Ha Neul and Seo Joon...
- have no idea. - They have no clue.
They're not even thinking about that person,
so they might try to eliminate that person first.
That won't do.
It'll end too early.
I'm kind of worried about people in the other car.
(The villains in the other car have a job to do.)
All right. We're going.
Villains, are you all here?
Yes, we're all here.
- There's police too. - I might be a villain...
or the police.
You two are very sharp.
- I agree. - The situation in this car...
is very dramatic.
We think the undercover officer, the boss, and the villain are here.
(They think all of them are here.)
(They get goosebumps.)
However, we should keep our mouths shut.
That might be better for us.
We're just observing your talking.
I see.
We don't have to talk much. You can feel it in the atmosphere.
You'll know. It's a strange feeling.
- We're all villains. - Kwang Soo.
(Why did he call Kwang Soo?)
I need to drive.
(Please be quiet.)
Okay, Seo Joon.
You won't do well if you do this.
(He's going crazy.)
You won't do well.
Seo Joon, that was funny.
(They all have fun except for Kwang Soo.)
He has to drive.
I see.
Do you remember way back?
(Way back when?)
(Remember what?)
We...
graduated...
from the police academy together.
(That was a good time.)
We were insane.
We threw eggs and flour at each other.
(What a great memory.)
My goodness.
Kang Ha Neul from class 103.
(Kwang Soo can't just watch.)
Yes, sir. What class are you?
I'm from class 98.
There was a scandal within class 98.
A confidential document...
Do you remember that?
- I do. - Me too.
- It was class 98. - I remember.
You all remember.
It was class 98 for sure.
The policewomen...
(She joins the conversation.)
(Even So Min knows about the incident.)
She's so funny.
We heard the rumor as well.
- Are you a policewoman? - Yes. It's very famous.
You know how we have two hints?
- Right. - They're very factual.
They're extremely factual.
- So I think we got it. - Please don't share them yet.
- Right. - We can't share them now.
- We can kind of infer. - Don't share.
- Make sure you don't share. - All right.
Do you remember that time?
(It's a different story.)
- In the dormitory, - That one.
Detective Park wanted to skip,
so we went outside!
We had...
- sausages that time. - We got caught.
Don't say that on television!
I know.
(Are they the alumni of a police academy?)
I remember that time.
We asked for sausages.
(He's happy to see his colleague.)
(Don't you realize that I'm the one?)
It's the final mission.
It's called Find the Boss.
(The final mission is Find the Boss.)
Mobile phones with R stickers are hidden in this place.
Team Boss will get hints regarding the money bag.
Team Police will get hints regarding the undercover officer.
Undercover officer?
During the race, two police officers excluding the undercover officer...
may tear off the name tags of Team Boss' members.
When the boss is eliminated, Team Police wins.
They also win an award of 1,000 dollars.
If they eliminate the undercover officer,
Team Police loses.
When the undercover officer is eliminated...
or the villains find the money bag and escapes with the boss...
(The villains must escape with the boss.)
Team Boss wins.
Undercover officer?
(Shouldn't the police stick together?)
Stop it, Kwang Soo.
- Stop it. - You startled me.
(Who is this gangling man in yellow?)
Gosh, you startled me.
- My body brought me here. - You startled me.
You frightened Seo Joon.
Why are you being so greedy?
- I did what my body told me to do. - You really scared me.
Kwang Soo is hopeless.
(He wants to stay away from him.)
(Sighing out of frustration)
When Team Police tears off a villain's name tag,
they earn a hint about the boss.
(Every villain's name tag gives a hint about the boss.)
(They must eliminate many villains to identify the boss.)
Go to your places, and start the race.
- Are we on different floors? - Yes.
- Really? - Let's go.
See you in the lobby.
We need to get the hints first.
On our way?
(What will be the final result?)
(They get ready for the final race.)
- What? - What should we do?
(Two policemen and Haha take the elevator.)
Who do you think the boss is?
For now,
leave Kwang Soo alone until the last.
That's better.
I'm sure that it's Kwang Soo.
(He's suspicious of him.)
(Kwang Soo is the strongest candidate.)
He's a fool.
This is frustrating.
Everyone seems to suspect that I'm the boss.
Why would I act like this if I'm not the undercover officer?
I know everything, and they don't need hints.
All they have to do is believe me.
What's so difficult about that?
(Is it that difficult?)
Is it difficult to believe me?
(He shouldn't have lied so much in the past.)
(Undercover officer)
Does it say, "undercover officer"?
I'll show that justice prevails.
All police officers in Korea, stay strong.
Justice prevails.
Let's go.
(What will happen to Kwang Soo?)
We must make them eliminate Kwang Soo and end the game, okay?
I'll run as fast as possible if I see Ha Neul or Seo Joon.
First, I must find the hints.
(Her goal is to escape with the boss.)
I should stay with someone...
who's big and strong.
My goodness.
(It's best to escape alone with the boss.)
Goodness.
(Team Police wins once they catch the boss.)
I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous.
(They can't eliminate the undercover officer.)
(Who is the real boss?)
(3 police officers versus 7 villains)
The race will start now.
- It's being announced. - Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
- One. Let's go. - Start.
(The final race starts.)
I should search from here.
(Finding hints is the priority.)
I should search in there.
(Team Boss and Team Police get different hints.)
It's over once I see them.
(His priority is to see the police.)
I don't need to find hints.
Have you seen a phone?
(Have you seen a phone with an R sticker?)
Is it here?
Why did you give me that look?
(She has a hair roller in her hair.)
I'm embarrassed by my hair.
It's okay.
Your hair will be edited on air.
Soon,
Seo Joon and Ha Neul will be walking about.
I hope you'll stay quieter.
Why did you remove the hair roller when I mentioned Seo Joon?
- Please go. - I will.
I'm leaving.
They also treat me like dirt.
(Jae Seok searches the Running Man office.)
Why did they make it difficult to find it?
(He finds a phone.)
I found it.
- Let me look. - Be quiet.
- Let me look. - No.
(Seok Jin joins.)
(Call R man, and identify yourself to get a hint.)
(He calls immediately.)
This is R man.
I'm a villain.
The hint is 8065.
What does that mean?
(What is 8065?)
(How does it relate to the money bag?)
My goodness.
What could 8065 mean?
(On the other hand)
(Seo Joon hums while searching.)
Where's the phone? What's this?
(Seo Joon also finds a phone.)
Wait.
"To get a hint,"
"call R man and identify yourself."
This is Police Park Seo Joon.
(Give me a hint.)
The undercover officer doesn't live with his parents.
Is that all?
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo live with their parents.)
Okay.
(Ji Hyo finds out about 8065.)
Does it work on the phone?
(Could this number be...)
Is it a word?
(Does it utilize the phone keyboard?)
This could make up a word.
(She compares it to the phone keyboard.)
We can eliminate either Jong Kook or Ji Hyo.
They're Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
(Where are you, Jong Kook and Ji Hyo?)
(What? There's Ji Hyo.)
- Are you going to eliminate me? - What?
- We found you. - Can you give me more time?
- What's going on? - What are you doing?
I found a hint. Why are you approaching me?
- It's okay. - Hey.
- We won't eliminate you. - Listen.
What's the hint?
- Where did you find it? - Will you eliminate me?
I could be the undercover officer.
The undercover officer doesn't live with his parents.
(That means Ji Hyo is a villain.)
Wait a minute.
- Come on. - Tell us later.
- Goodness. - We're sorry.
We're sorry, Ji Hyo.
We're sorry.
- Come on. - Thank you.
Ji Hyo is out.
Ji Hyo is eliminated.
I'm a big fan of yours.
Get lost.
- Get lost, you two. - Thank you.
- Darn it. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - I was about to do something.
I said, get lost.
Here's a hint about the boss.
The boss isn't lucky.
(The boss isn't lucky.)
He's not lucky?
(The boss isn't lucky?)
- I see. - Is that the hint?
- That means it's Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo.
(The boss is Kwang Soo.)
- When we eliminate him is the key. - Right.
- Let's look for the undercover one. - You're right.
We'll leave him last.
There are other unlucky members.
It's Kwang Soo.
(They're convinced.)
(You're right. I'm unlucky.)
Have you seen Ha Neul and Seo Joon?
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Let's stay together.
For what?
What would I do with a villain?
Let me tell you this.
I am...
May I tell this to him?
(It's top secret information.)
I am...
(Actually, I am...)
I'm the head of the police.
(I'm the head of the police.)
(Laughing)
(What do you take me for?)
What's wrong?
Sometimes, you treat me like a complete fool.
- I don't like it. - Kwang Soo, I'm serious.
- You're the head of the police? - You're the undercover officer.
Do you want to be handcuffed?
Come on, follow me. Seriously.
Stop talking nonsense. I don't like it at all.
Saying that you're the head of the police isn't convincing.
(They search for Jong Kook.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(There you are, Jong Kook.)
- Did you get any hints? - Yes.
What have you found?
We're watching you all.
How far are you? How many hints?
- We have many. - You do?
- We know whom to eliminate. - You do?
- You do? - Yes.
(I see. Am I in that list?)
- I see. - That's it.
- You have an idea. - Yes.
- You know whom to eliminate. - We have an idea.
I see. It's hot today.
- Please take some time off. - Please.
Would you like to take a break?
Sure. It's quite a hot day.
It's hot.
- All right. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - All right.
(They thank him,)
(and eliminate him.)
- Oh, dear. - You figured it out.
You have a good idea.
- We got him. - I wasted my time.
You got me.
- He's a villain. - Right.
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook are out.
Here's a hint about the boss. It's a male.
- Did you see Seo Joon and Ha Neul? - I haven't.
- Where did they go? - Hey.
Why are you looking for them?
I'm a policeman.
- You're not. - You...
- Rip my name tag. - Let me ask you a question.
I'm an officer that can't rip name tags.
You can't rip them?
Rip mine.
- Gosh. - Rip it.
Line up. Rip all of ours.
- I can't rip them. - If you're a cop, rip it.
I can't because I'm an undercover officer.
- Let's talk on our own. - Let's talk.
Our hints...
Am I...
the ugly duckling?
Where did they go?
Boss, why are you following us?
- Boss, why do you keep following? - Why are you following us?
You'll get caught by the police. Hide.
- Hide, boss. - Hey, boss. Hide.
No. Come on.
What's this?
It's for you. Open it when you're alone.
Kwang Soo, go to the corner.
Trust me, Kwang Soo.
What's this?
(What did Se Chan give him?)
(You're stupid.)
(What? Stupid?)
I have to end this. This won't do.
(I'll show you what I've got.)
(Meanwhile, the 13th floor is quiet.)
(He's on full alert.)
That startled me.
(Villain Yu is looking for additional hints.)
(He finds another hint.)
I'm a villain.
Your hint is "70H".
"70H"?
(That's...)
(It's "70H 8065".)
It's a license plate.
(All the hints point to a parking lot.)
(He has to find "70H 8065" at the parking lot.)
(He looks around.)
Turn the light off.
(He finds the car.)
(Clicking)
Turn it off.
There's no key.
Do I have to find a key?
My goodness.
Gosh.
I found the car though.
Se Chan? No, I think...
- I don't think so. - Haha...
- seems like an undercover officer. - I think so too.
He's the most likely from all the guys.
Haha wanted to meet at the lobby, right?
Ha Neul.
(Haha is at the lobby.)
Seo Joon?
(Where did they go?)
(What's this?)
(He finds a phone.)
(He hides, and tries to contact the R man.)
I'm Villain Haha.
Yes.
Your hint is "70H".
- "70H"? - Yes.
That's a 7, 0, and H?
It's a license plate.
I got so many hints today. That's not usual.
That's so fascinating.
It's such a delightful feeling.
I have to go to the first floor.
It's so hot.
(The police are on the 1st floor.)
There's nobody here.
I hope I can get another hint.
(So Min is coming down,)
(and the police are on the 1st floor.)
The boss is a guy.
They'll trust me.
(That was the hint from earlier.)
Hello.
(She has no fear.)
(It's So Min.)
- Did you find something? - What's going on?
- There's nothing. I was looking. - There's nothing?
- Have you eliminated anyone? - Help us then.
How? What should I do?
Please join us...
- I just saw... - It's Kwang Soo.
It's Kwang Soo.
Who is that? Seo Joon.
Listen to me.
Wait, listen to me.
You don't think it's me, right? Listen to me.
(Ripping)
- That's right. - Hey.
(Why did Ha Neul rip So Min's name tag?)
What is she?
She's a villain. We got her.
Go there.
(5 minutes ago)
- There's one. - There is?
I got it.
The undercover officer is a male.
A male. "The undercover officer is a male."
- Yes. - I thought it was So Min.
- It's not. - That's right.
(So Min is not the undercover officer.)
(They knew it wasn't So Min.)
That was unexpected.
What is she?
She's a villain. We got her.
She's a villain.
We're good.
If they rip Kwang Soo, it's over.
(She is sad.)
The boss...
is Seok Jin. It's Seok Jin.
Did you find any hints?
- I didn't need to. - Why not?
I'm the undercover officer.
Villain So Min is out, so here's a hint about the boss.
(I'll prove my identity with this hint about the boss.)
The boss is a coward.
(The boss is a coward.)
It's not me.
(He's a coward?)
- What kind of a hint is that? - What was that?
- "The boss is..." - It's not me.
- "a coward." - Seok Jin is the boss.
I'm certain. It's Seok Jin.
- Trust me. - I didn't look for any hints.
- Seo Joon, this is urgent. - All day, I was looking for you.
You won't bump into us. You don't have many chances.
Jae Seok found something.
- Where's the bag? - He found something.
Here.
- Not that bag. - The money bag?
How do I know?
Look at my eyes.
I'm the undercover officer. If you get me out, this is over.
- You think I'm the boss? - I swear.
Why do you think it's me?
Why should I give you information about the boss?
- Why did I do that? - Kwang Soo.
Look, I'll even let you rip my name tag.
- All day, - I'm an undercover officer.
I've been criticized by both sides.
Let's go together. I'll help you. I can help you.
- Let's go. - Hey.
You can't let him go. He'll run away.
Let's go up. Seok Jin is upstairs.
Kwang Soo, don't go by yourself.
- Where are you going? - Excuse me.
- Excuse me. - Press the button. We have no time.
- Don't move your hand. - Let's go up.
Watch him.
Don't treat me like a criminal. I'm not that kind of a person.
Let's separate and rip everybody's name tags.
It's awesome if you get Seok Jin.
Should I stay with Kwang Soo, or do you want to?
I can go around and then we can switch.
Don't make it sound like you're watching me. I'm a cop too.
Is there a lock?
Why do you need a lock?
- We're a team. - I know.
Isn't there a jail here?
Why would a cop be jailed?
(I'm the undercover officer, guys.)
(This is the jail on the 1st floor.)
I was coming this way,
then Ha Neul followed me.
My heart fluttered.
(So Min was on her way to the jail after she got eliminated.)
(He went after her.)
(Ha Neul made her heart flutter.)
I didn't want to show him, but he grabbed my wrists,
and flipped them over. My heart fluttered again.
It's nothing.
(He stole her heart with his strong grip.)
So Min falls in love easily.
She's the second one. She's like Kwang Soo.
She's the female Kwang Soo. She seems like one.
(So Min is silly like Kwang Soo, and falls in love easily too.)
- Then you can... - We have no time.
watch him.
Seok Jin is hiding because he doesn't want to be out.
- You haven't seen him today, right? - No.
I saw him on the upper floors. I think it was the 13th floor.
- 14th floor? - If you see him, rip his name tag.
- There's no time. - I'll do the 14th floor.
- Jae Seok is on the 4th floor. - Good luck.
(If Kwang Soo is right, they have to find Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin.
- Jae Seok. - Yes.
- Did you find anything? - Well...
- The police are too close. - Right?
- You know, right? Be careful. - I know.
- Hold on. - I have to be careful.
- I know where the car is. - Okay.
- I do too. - Which floor are you on?
This is the 13th floor, right? I am on the 13th floor.
Be careful.
I know. I'm hiding.
I need to find the car key.
Find it quickly, and call me.
Okay.
(Why is Jae Seok sharing information with Seok Jin?)
He told me to be careful.
Jae Seok cares about me. He told me to hide.
(Jae Seok cares about me. He told me to hide.)
I will leave with the last one standing.
(What does he mean?)
I wouldn't mind if more people get eliminated.
(Is he planning to leave...)
(with the last one standing?)
Your boss of the day is...
Seok Jin.
(It's hard to believe but true.)
No way!
- Are you sure about it? - Look forward to a difficult day.
10 minutes into the game, he will go,
"Do you know who I am?"
(He wasn't reliable.)
(The villains called Seok Jin the boss in the car.)
(It was a big accident.)
The boss doesn't go into the war zone.
The boss sits behind the desk,
and reaps the benefits.
(Villains, hurry up, and find the car key.)
I think this is the editing room for Running Man.
(He must find the car key before the boss gets apprehended.)
Maybe it's here.
(Rummaging)
(He finds a phone.)
I am a villain. Where is the car key?
The hint is 18th floor.
Okay.
It must be on the 18th floor.
(Team Boss' goal is to find the car key on the 18th floor.)
Let's find them. I won't run away.
Okay.
We found the car. We just need to find the car key.
(Team Boss arrives on the 18th floor.)
(Where is it?)
What is it?
(Did Jae Seok find it?)
- It was here. - Where?
Here.
(He finds an R box in the refrigerator...)
(and a car key inside it.)
- What is this key? - I found it.
- What is this key? - It's a car key.
- Why do we need a car key? - Where is Seok Jin?
- Why do we need a car key? - We need to go.
- Where are we going? - We need to run away.
- Where are we going? - Come on.
- Jae Seok, where are you? - Seok Jin.
- Yes? - Which floor are you on?
I am on the 13th floor. Did you find the key?
- Yes. - Okay, I am on the 13th floor.
He found it. Okay.
It will be game over once we take it to the car.
(If the boss and a villain get into the car, Team Boss wins.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
I told you not to go off on your own.
(It's the 2nd warning.)
Wait a minute. I am the undercover officer.
I am the undercover officer.
You are a coward.
(What is this coward saying?)
(The boss and a villain are about to have a rendezvous.)
(Talking noisily)
(They see Seok Jin.)
(They run at full speed.)
Seo Joon! Seo Joon! It's Seok Jin.
It's Seok Jin!
What are you doing?
- Rip off his name tag. - Rip off his name tag.
- Why are you holding me? - Rip off his name tag.
Come on.
Rip off his name tag. Come on.
- Rip off his name tag. - Rip off his name tag.
Listen to me.
- Rip off his name tag. - Don't be that way.
My goodness.
- It's over if you get Seok Jin. - It's over if you get Kwang Soo.
(They talk at the same time.)
I spent the entire day telling you this.
- I found out that he was it... - It's over if you get Kwang Soo.
- over four hours ago. - Seo Joon.
It's over if you get Kwang Soo. Rip off his name tag.
- Give me a second. - Okay.
Okay. Think about it.
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok is at the car waiting for the boss.)
Hurry up and come. Please hurry up and come.
There is the money bag.
Please.
(Se Chan is on standby at the lobby.)
(They ready themselves, and wait for the boss.)
For goodness' sake.
(My goodness.)
(The boss doesn't come.)
What is going on?
Something must have happened.
Why?
(There is no reason for him to be this late.)
Did you hear that?
The game is almost over.
You need to rip off his name tag. Rip off his name tag, Seo Joon.
Seo Joon, rip off his name tag. Listen to me.
- I am the undercover officer. - Seo Joon.
- Seo Joon. - I told you that before.
- Listen to me. - I am the undercover officer.
- Seo Joon. - Okay.
(What is his decision?)
- I found out that he was it... - Okay.
- over four hours ago. - This is crazy.
(He is confident.)
(He becomes a bit nervous.)
(Seok Jin seems to be nervous.)
You are so brazen.
You know what he is like, right?
Jae Seok is calling.
(What? Is Jae Seok calling?)
Why did he call? Hi.
(Be quiet.)
(Jae Seok calls at the crucial moment.)
(Can Kwang Soo prove his identity with this phone call?)
Hey, boss.
(Boss?)
(Jae Seok's pranking him.)
Boss.
- Seo Joon. - Boss.
Hey, boss.
(Everything is clear now.)
I told you that I don't lie.
Seo Joon.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you calling me the boss? I am the undercover officer!
Okay.
- What did he say? - He hung up right away.
Okay. You might misunderstand.
- Rip off his name tag. - Jae Seok planned this.
- Jae Seok planned this. - Seo Joon, rip off his name tag.
- I mean... - Finish him.
- Wait a minute. Seo Joon. - Finish him.
- Finish him. - It's over if you rip mine off!
- Listen to me. - Finish him.
- Hurry up. - It's over if you rip mine.
- It's over if you do. - Rip off his name tag.
- No, please! - Hurry up!
(Don't let the villain get the better of you.)
- Be quiet, you coward! - I'm not!
(He rips it.)
(Undercover officer)
(Kwang Soo was the undercover officer?)
(Team Police loses because of a single mistake.)
We won!
That was incredible.
(Devastated)
I got played. What was that phone call?
How would I know?
What was that phone call?
I spent the entire day...
resolving misunderstandings.
That's the only thing I did today since the moment I woke up.
I tried to deliver the truth.
- The entire day... - I couldn't help it...
because you act too much on a regular basis.
People always say...
(He swears at Seo Joon.)
(You don't understand how I feel.)
- Jae Seok. - Kwang Soo is out.
The undercover officer, Kwang Soo, is out.
Okay.
I see that Seo Joon and Ha Neul didn't trust him.
(Thinking that Kwang Soo may be with the two cops,)
(Jae Seok decided to make him look suspicious.)
(Acting)
(Distrust led to the path of self-destruction.)
(Jae Seok's plan was a big success.)
Kwang Soo is out. Kwang Soo is out.
- What? - The undercover officer...
(The undercover officer, Kwang Soo, is out?)
(Does that mean Kwang Soo was the undercover officer?)
(I was just a liar.)
Haha, do you remember way back?
Haha. Don't you remember way back when?
We graduated from the police academy together!
You are the one who said that!
You are the one who mentioned the police academy!
- I am sorry. - Let me rip off your name tag.
Let me rip off your name tag.
Why did you say that?
You were not the boss.
You were no one of importance.
You were just a villain!
You were just a villain.
(I can't believe a lowly con man got me.)
I am sorry.
(With Ha Neul's tears, the race ends.)
Thus, Team Boss wins.
(Team Boss wins with a dramatic comeback.)
- Boss. - Boss.
Boss.
- Good work, everyone. - Jae Seok.
You did an amazing job.
The only thing I did today since the moment I woke up...
was resolve misunderstandings.
I told everyone that I was the undercover officer.
That's the only thing I said today.
Thus, the seven members except for Kwang Soo will share...
the prize money of 1,000 dollars.
I told you to trust me.
The password is 6375. Please open the briefcase.
(What can we do with 1,000 dollars?)
- Is there money inside? - What is it?
Come on.
(Donation)
- That's good. - That's good.
- That's good. - Kwang Soo.
It brings a smile to my face. I am so happy.
We will donate 1,000 dollars under the 7 members' names.
(The money goes to Hope TV SBS.)
- Thank you so much. See you again. - Thank you for your hard work.
- Return safely. - Return safely.
(We thank Ha Neul and Seo Joon for working hard as the police.)
(The 2nd Summer Special of Running Man)
(Do you spot the bad girl...)
(behind the girl?)
(Gazes)
(Facial expressions)
(Way of speaking)
(Find the bad girl...)
(who swallowed the girl's everything.)
(Part 2 of Find Trilogy, Find the Bad Girl)