(It's the first Sunday of 2017, the Year of the Chicken.)
(A special ceremony for the new year is prepared.)
(2017 Running Man Kickoff)
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
- It's Hwan. - Nice to meet you.
- It's Hwan. - Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year. - Hello.
- Hello. - It's a kickoff.
- Please stand in a line. - Okay.
We will now begin...
- Running Man kickoff of 2017. - All right.
It's a new year. Please tell the viewers...
about your New Year's resolutions.
- Okay. - You go first, Haha.
(Haha will speak first.)
For the New Year...
(Stuttering)
I will round this year off.
(He's getting laughed at since the start of the year.)
I will try my best and stay healthy.
(Please become a grown up this year, Haha.)
- You can go next, Seok Jin. - Okay.
Staying healthy is the best.
I got a checkup last year.
- Really? - How did it go?
They said I screamed a lot when I was doing endoscopy under sedation.
I became a baby all of a sudden and said,
"Please..."
(He became a baby.)
- My wife was... - That's so scary.
- very embarrassed. - You sounded so scary.
I think you were possessed.
(50-year-old baby ghost)
- It was a baby ghost. - That could be possible.
My wife was very embarrassed.
My priority is also staying healthy.
I will keep staying healthy...
and continue to be a health preacher.
How exactly are you going to be a health preacher?
Staying healthy doesn't make you a health preacher.
I wish a day would come...
when Jong Kook turns 80...
and appear on "How is that Possible"...
with his bulky body.
- I think I could do that. - Right?
- You would be shirtless. - I can see that happening.
You could show off your back muscles.
(The secret behind 80-year-old Jong Kook's body)
"Let's find out how Jong Kook manages to stay fit."
You could do this to your daughter-in-law.
(The grandpa uses his daughter-in-law to play basketball.)
He's so full of energy.
I could do that.
What a way to celebrate your 80th birthday.
I'll make sure that happens.
If I want to see that, I'd have to stay alive.
- Right. - Please stay alive for long.
I'll do that.
Kwang Soo?
For this year, I wish everyone happiness...
including my family and the viewers.
Personally, I hope Jong Kook gets married.
- That was random. - What?
I wanted to cheer you up.
(May Jong Kook get married in 2017.)
I wish many good things happen not to just us,
- but to all the viewers. - Of course.
- I wish them happiness. - I do, too.
We'll try really hard...
to make you laugh.
Everyone, Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
To celebrate a new year,
we'll announce the launch of Running Man's new project.
Oh, my goodness.
(What is that?)
What is that?
2017 Running Man Project.
- Member's Week. - Member's Week.
(Member's Week?)
It's Running Man's New Year project for 2017.
It's Member's Week.
A project has been prepared for your seven years of hard work.
Each week, members of Running Man...
will each choose an item of their liking and go on a race.
Seok Jin.
This is amazing.
(This is amazing.)
Can we team up?
Please tell us if there are specific items you prefer.
There was a project Seok Jin and I were seriously working on.
- What is it? - If we can do whatever we want,
we'd like to do that project.
- You can do whatever you want. - Really?
I can't talk about it.
- We two have the main roles. - Don't talk about it.
- We're the leading roles. - We'll destroy everyone.
- You'll destroy everyone? - Watch your mouth.
Get ready to get imprisoned.
Should I get my water gun ready?
(Jae Seok threatens them.)
Do you want me to spray you?
(Should I wake Jae Seok Bond up from his sleep?)
You're all done for once I ready my water gun.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
I wish we could all go on a trip together.
- Without cameras. - Without cameras?
How are we supposed to record it then?
Think before you speak.
You asked me what I wanted to do.
We'll get to go on a trip. Don't worry about that.
- I really wish for that to happen. - All right.
- A real trip? - We could record it ourselves.
I wish I could personally train all of you.
(Do you want to get personally trained by Jong Kook?)
It'll be called "Jong Kook's Intense Training".
Why do you keep trying to give us a hard time?
- Did we do wrong by you? - What did we do so wrong?
I won't go easy on you.
Member's Week will start next week.
- Really? - For such reason,
we'll choose the first runner...
to start off the first race.
The winner of the race will get an R Ball.
- It's the R Ball again. - It's been quite a long time.
It'll be a lot of pressure to be the first runner.
There are benefits for the first runner.
The winner will be given water bombs to clarify the body and soul.
(Water bombs for clarifying body and soul)
(The ice bath will refresh you to the bones.)
There will be a purifying bath.
(How is that a benefit?)
You call that purifying? It's a penalty.
(They're frozen up already.)
The first runner will choose...
the next runner of the following week.
(Member's Week will continue until all members get selected.)
- Will it be like a relay? - You could do that.
With a big project coming up,
it's important to get yourself checked out.
We'll get moving...
to have our fortunes told.
- Shall we do that? - Yes.
- Let's get moving. - Let's go.
(Announcement of Running Man's 2017 Project)
(Running Man Checkup: New Year Fortune Telling)
(It'll be a time to take a peak at Running Man's fortune.)
This mission is called The Fortune Race.
We will tell your fortune of this year.
The person with the best fortune told...
will get to decide on which game we'll play first.
Fortuneteller Park Sung Joon will help us today.
(Fortuneteller Park Sung Joon will read Running Man's fortune.)
He's the fortuneteller from last year.
- Hello. - Hello.
He's got quite a sharp tongue.
(You should stay still for 2016.)
(Park Sung Joon started 2016 off by making spiteful remarks.)
(He gave everyone a mental breakdown by giving them pieces of advice.)
He'll read each of your fortunes.
- Should I go first? - You should go first.
Seok Jin is very curious right now.
Please listen to him this year.
- I should. - Last year,
- you didn't listen to him. - He told you not to do anything.
He argued with him.
(Seok Jin was full of hopes and dreams for 2016.)
(It'll be better if you just stay still.)
(Seok Jin was told to stay still.)
Last year, I told you to stay still.
- For this year... - This is important.
(Can I move around this year?)
You should stay still again.
(He should stay still again.)
(It's been 2 consecutive years.)
Really? What did you say?
He has to stay still again?
(Is he a statue?)
Living isn't living for him.
Seok Jin has to stay still again?
Shouldn't I at least do something?
It's a windy season so if you decide to do something,
you should keep your head down and lay down flat.
(Keep your head down and lay down flat.)
How much longer does he have to crawl?
- That's what you need to do. - I need to keep my head down?
After 3 or 4 years, you will finally get lucky.
I'll be 60 by then.
(He'll be a grandpa by then.)
That's true.
- You won't get lucky until 2020. - 2020?
Don't you think you'll have a grandson by then?
- He has to stay still until 2020? - This is driving me crazy.
This feels a lot like last year.
Your keyword of this year is...
"No Investing".
(Seok Jin's keyword for this year is "No Investing".)
(I have to stay still and can't even invest my money?)
Mr. Park. What if...
he has already invested some money? Should he retrieve the investment?
When did you invest your money?
I started investing seriously since last year.
- Since last year? - Yes.
You shouldn't put more money in.
(He recommends freezing his account.)
I recommend you retrieve your investment...
- as soon as possible. - It's funny because he's serious.
(Is there anything I can do?)
I don't know if he's speaking from the bottom of his heart but...
We go see fortunetellers in the beginning of a new year...
- to get hope. - That's right.
That didn't sound hopeful at all.
I've done this before. They usually give you at least one good news.
There's nothing good about what he's saying.
Seok Jin, you should go back to your seat now.
(Looks like I'll be unlucky this year again.)
Please stay still, Seok Jin.
(Don't invest your money and lay down flat.)
Seok Jin, stay still.
Haha was born as land.
- I get that a lot. - He's a rich land.
It's a big and rich tract of land.
That's good.
There's even water. It has a good environment.
However, there aren't any trees to plant there.
That means you want to harvest, but you don't have...
any crops to plant.
I don't know why that is. I'm not getting any results.
One good thing about you...
is that your children are your hope.
- Dream. - That's very good news.
- That's good news. - Only your children...
can make you feel stable.
Really?
He used to be such a brat.
He's become a changed man after he got married and had a child.
(He is no longer a brat thanks to Dream.)
(Kicking)
(If it wasn't for Dream, he would be much worse now.)
I'm sorry. I got carried away.
You should have many children.
The more children you give birth to, the better.
- I see. - Really?
In terms of your fortune,
there is no powerful, determining force.
(It's good to have many children, but there is no powerful force.)
What does that mean?
What does it mean?
He wants to have more children, but his situation doesn't allow it.
(He is flustered.)
How can you see that?
- Gosh. - I'm being serious.
It surprises me these days.
It's too difficult.
Gosh, is that so?
- Despite all that, - How did he know?
the more children you have, the better it is.
Your keyword for the year 2017 is...
"Keep Your Head Down with Seok Jin".
That's the best thing to do this year.
- Let's not do anything together. - That's your fortune this year.
- Haha's is the same as Seok Jin's. - Stay down on your stomach.
It wasn't so bad.
(He's disappointed by his fortune reading.)
(Haha's hopes are his children.)
(Stay low with Seok Jin.)
Jong Kook, your fortune...
for this year is that you'll be stronger in maintaining your life.
Your greed for money and women...
(He gets extremely greedy about money and romance.)
Is that finally happening?
Wait a minute.
Jong Kook, remember the rich woman whom you mentioned?
- Remember the rich woman? - What?
You said she was rich.
Have you lost your mind? Whom are you talking about?
He must know someone who's wealthy.
- He's been busy with his finances. - I'm really interested...
because I want to meet a good woman these days.
In terms of your romantic life,
stop analyzing.
- Gosh, please stop analyzing. - Seriously.
- You can't analyze women. - Right.
You need to open up your heart more.
Jong Kook, this is your keyword for this year.
"The Time to Make New Changes".
Changes in your life could be good for you...
if you follow through.
Whom should I follow?
- You're great with Ji Hyo. - Really?
- Ji Hyo is good in many ways. - That's true.
I might be getting ahead of myself,
but it'd be best if Ji Hyo and Jong Kook got married.
- What are you talking about? - Let's have them get married.
What are you talking about?
- She's the rich woman. - Ji Hyo is...
really rich.
- What's wrong with Ji Hyo? - She bought me a fan before.
Why can't it be her?
- She's like family. - She'd be perfect.
Ji Hyo, think about it.
You never know how life will turn out.
The score of your match with Ji Hyo is 85 to 90 out of 100.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook make a 90-point couple.)
- 90 points? - Is that good?
You should live together.
- Do you mean me and Ji Hyo? - She showed her interest.
Okay, thank you.
Gary would be disappointed if he hears this.
Sir, please take a look at it one more time!
Sir, please!
- That's big news. - They get 90 points?
("The Time to Make New Changes")
(He may get lucky financially and romantically.)
Ji Hyo, based on your fortune,
you were born as a thirsty tree in the summer.
The summer is hot and lacks water.
That's why you always seem thirsty for something.
Jong Kook is your great source of water.
(They're a perfect match.)
- There you go. - Does Jong Kook represent water?
You're a good match as he waters a thirsty tree like you.
This year...
is when you get your hands on money.
(She's surprised.)
Suddenly, she stretched out her arms.
She did.
(She feels more confident.)
In terms of your romantic life,
you've had strange and lowly men around you.
(She's had strange and lowly men around her.)
Don't say it that way.
- Do you mean us? - Is that us?
- We're not lowly men. - That sounds funny.
They're the closest men around me.
- That was funny. - Are we lowly?
Did you hear that, Gary?
Gary is one of them.
As those unnecessary men get out of your life,
the time for you to meet a good partner...
is this year.
That makes me feel sad.
Your weakness in your romantic life is that...
you have high standards for men.
- Really? - No, she doesn't.
You have high standards.
However, even if you choose someone based on your standards,
it's likely that he's strange.
(She has the worst judgment when it comes to men.)
In other words, only she thinks that she has high standards.
It's okay as long as she's happy.
You choose men based on your own standards,
but it's hard for others to accept him.
You may have high standards, but you have bad judgment.
That's why you may find an unusual man.
That's why she's working with us.
(Lower your standards and make better judgments.)
- It's like us who aren't so smart. - Right.
- I bet Kwang Soo is lucky. - Last year,
- Kwang Soo's fortune was the best. - Is that so?
(Both Kwang Soo and Jong Kook had good fortunes in 2016.)
(Kwang Soo was selected as the luckiest in 2016.)
Kwang Soo was the luckiest.
Kwang Soo, you're already accomplished,
but your willingness and desire to grow are excessive.
- Right now? - You want to do better.
You're almost 2m tall, Kwang Soo.
Do you want to be 3m tall?
That's not it.
That's why you always feel frustrated.
- Frustrated? - Yes.
- You're lonely. - Right.
- You feel inadequate. - That's correct.
- And... - He can't sleep alone.
your personality is...
What are you talking about?
(Has he lost his mind?)
(Stop talking nonsense on the first day of the new year.)
(Laughing)
You have many thoughts.
- Kwang Soo thinks a lot. - Many thoughts are on your mind.
You also daydream a lot, too.
Does he daydream?
Your fortune regarding romance this year...
is that you desperately want to find a woman, but there aren't any.
(There's no woman available to him.)
Could you read the fortune again?
- That's the worst. - Why?
Why isn't there any?
He desperately wants to find one, but there isn't any.
Kwang Soo, you and I are quite similar.
Since you feel lonely very often,
you fall in love easily.
- That's right. - That's true.
- You fall in love at first sight. - That's right.
He's an easy guy.
What are you talking about?
- Don't you think so? - That was too rude.
What's wrong?
He's easy because he falls in love easily.
How could he say that?
- You fall in love easily. - What does that supposed to mean?
Don't misunderstand me.
You fall in love easily.
What do you mean?
I meant that you're a man who falls in love easily.
- That still sounds rude. - I'm an easy guy?
(Kwang Soo is ready to argue.)
Kwang Soo, don't misunderstand.
I just said he falls in love easily.
- I'm sorry about that. - Many thoughts are on your mind.
Since you aren't good at expressing yourself,
the thoughts only stay in your head.
The other person wasn't even thinking about it,
but you think you're in a relationship.
Is that how it is?
That's right.
You're amazing, Sir.
- That's completely true. - It's true.
He gets into relationships and breaks up all by himself.
I broke up with about 30 people this year.
- He threw a birthday party alone. - You're full of imaginations.
You imagine as if you're dating someone.
You feel impatient, and you consider yourself as her boyfriend already.
In other words,
you're full of desire and passion,
but your plans don't usually come to fruition.
However,
when you meet Jong Kook, the story changes.
A tree should be rooted in the ground, but when you meet him,
the ground gets muddy.
- Muddy? - You can't establish roots.
- Does it turn into poop water? - It becomes muddy.
Muddy?
Don't they usually meet...
- each other often? - They hang out together the most.
- Does it become muddy? - They hang out the most.
- They meet each other often. - He said it becomes muddy.
The tree can't photosynthesize because there's no sun.
If it can't root in the ground, it can only float.
I've never heard something bad like this.
His fortune is similar to mine.
I suggest...
to distance yourself from Jong Kook.
The person you're good to work with is Jae Seok.
Really?
When you meet him, it's not only good for him,
but it's also good for you.
Keep close to Jae Seok and distance yourself from Jong Kook.
Kwang Soo, you can live in one of the rooms at my house.
I have an extra room.
We heard the same thing last year.
- That's right. - Right.
(Do what matters the most.)
(Avoid Jong Kook and stay close to Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok, you're a giving person...
- and have people's support. - I do?
You may seem friendly but...
you distance yourself from others except close friends and family.
- That's right. - That's why...
I don't have that many close friends.
- That's why you don't have hobbies. - Right.
There's not much going on in your life.
- That's true. - I feel bad for him.
- All I do is... - I feel bad for Jae Seok.
hang out with my close friends. I don't do much else.
- I'd like to tell you something. - What is it?
This is your keyword this year.
- This is your keyword. - I'm curious.
"Be Devoted to Your Wife".
("Be Devoted to Your Wife")
You should have a second child.
That's my wish.
Your wife can also be a daughter to you.
She wants to receive a lot of unconditional love.
That's something you can work on.
I'd like to travel more with her,
but I didn't have the chance yet.
My plan is to travel more this year.
You should be more devoted to your wife this year.
- I plan to do that. - Take care of her like a daughter.
- You need to focus more on her. - Okay.
There's one thing you should be careful about.
Your fortune says that you may have a health problem this year.
Let's start training from tomorrow.
You lose more energy when you meet Haha.
(Haha sucks the energy out of people.)
- Why is it always him? - He sucks everyone's energy.
- I'm already tired. - What is wrong with him?
My goodness.
You don't know why, but he'll drain your energy out.
- That's the chemistry. - There's no reason?
What about my chemistry with Seok Jin?
When you meet Seok Jin, he reminds you of money.
- He reminds me of money? - He does...
and he provokes the ambition for you...
to be more active in the society.
- That's right. - Seok Jin...
He gives me a lot of suggestions.
- That's right. - It's right.
I want to own an organic bakery with Jae Seok.
He keeps on offering the idea to me.
- He mentioned it several times. - Jae Seok will bake.
But you don't go well with bakeries.
- What suits him, then? - What suits me?
- What suits him? - He wants to open a business.
- What suits him? - Tell us.
What is it?
- What should he do? - How...
- Would nothing work out for him? - What am I supposed to do?
Seok Jin is patient...
- Should he wait? - What about charity work?
What about charity work?
(He's forced to do charity work.)
- That's right. - You should do some good deeds.
You should.
This is funny.
Thank you. He was right...
- about everyone. - He was close.
Let's give the fortuneteller a round of applause for joining us.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thanks so much.
He was so funny. He made me laugh.
My feet are numb.
Did your feet fall asleep?
- My feet are numb. - Are you okay?
(He's about to fall.)
(Slipping)
(He can't get up by himself.)
- What's the matter with him? - What's going on?
(Gathering)
You should take care of yourself.
You should take care of yourself first.
Don't worry about me.
- What's going on? - He has to lie down.
- He has to lie down. - Lie down.
What's the matter with him?
What's going on?
- Sir. - His feet are numb.
You should join me at the gym tomorrow.
Don't do anything this year.
You should stay at home.
You should lie down at home.
- Don't do anything. - Are you all right?
You told me not to do anything. You shouldn't either.
(Limping)
Sorry.
He was so funny.
That was today's best moment.
- That was the best moment. - He's so funny.
We had the fortuneteller interpret our 2017.
I'll reveal who have the best fortune for the new year...
- out of the Running Man members. - You have the order?
- I'll reveal 6th place. - It's 6th place?
- It's the last. - All right. It goes to...
(Who has the worst fortune for Year of the Chicken?)
(I hope it's not me.)
It's Seok Jin.
- I'm not surprised. - That was anti-climactic.
- I'm not surprised either. - That was predictable.
(It follows the fortuneteller's predictions.)
Haha is in fifth place.
(Haha in 5th place)
It hasn't changed from last year.
That's right.
In fourth place is Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo is in fourth place? - She is.
In third place...
is Jong Kook.
- It's the same as last year. - Is it him and me?
It's similar from last year.
We have 1st and 2nd places remaining.
First place goes to...
(Who will have the best luck for Year of the Chicken?)
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is the man of Year of the Chicken.)
Congratulations.
It was the same for last year.
- It was. - It's the same.
With everything combined,
- Kwang Soo scores first place. - That's great.
That's right. He's still young.
- He has a bright future. - The first game of 2017...
is called "When the Chicken Lays".
"When the Chicken Lays"?
Kwang Soo have the best fortune...
so you can pick the order that each person will go.
There's a chicken toy that lays eggs but you don't know when.
You can press the button three times at a maximum.
If the chicken lays eggs during your turn,
- you're eliminated. - They're eliminated.
- It's easy, right? - All right.
The last person to stay alive will get 50 R Balls.
- That many? - You can give them to others...
but you must keep one at least.
- That's good. - It's bad to have them, right?
- That's right. - It's no good.
We might get the water bucket.
Kwang Soo, please designate the order.
I'll have everybody move up one and I'll go to the end.
- Really? - You're going last?
I need to distance myself from Jong Kook and get close to Jae Seok.
- That's fine. - He's doing as the fortune says.
- Let's listen to the fortune. - All right.
- I'll go first. - You're first?
- Kwang Soo is first. - Am I last place?
That punk.
- Do you see the egg? - Where does it come out from?
You need to press the egg three times.
- It's three maximum, right? - Right.
(If he gets unlucky, he might get the water bucket.)
(Who would be the first unlucky one of the new year?)
That was one.
- That's two. - Hey.
- It's totally luck. - Totally?
(Should I do another click or not?)
It clicks. Stop. Yes.
- All right, Kwang Soo. - Yes.
(Kwang Soo gets the first egg.)
- You're first to be eliminated. - Look what happens.
(His bad luck continues in the new year.)
- He's unlucky. - He still is.
- You need to stay by me. - This is weird.
- Our luck shows here. - He didn't pick properly.
- This is interesting. - It is.
That's what unlucky ones are like.
- Kwang Soo is eliminated. - It's unpleasant to see the egg.
It rolled out. It made me mad.
I agree it looks unpleasant.
- We'll start again with Jae Seok. - We'll start again.
Press it hard. That's one.
(He passes it on after one click.)
No way.
(Here's the egg.)
How can I believe this?
(What's going on?)
- How can I believe this? - You've been eliminated.
Look at the egg.
I don't understand. I only pressed it once.
Seok Jin is eliminated as well.
You guys are so unlucky.
Let's start again with Ji Hyo.
- Once. - Twice,
and three. Aren't you scared?
- Haha is next. - She must be at ease.
Once, twice.
(Would Haha choose to go again?)
(I don't know.)
- Here's the egg. - Oh, dear.
(Oh my goodness!)
- You're eliminated. - Why were you being greedy?
You shouldn't have done it.
- What's wrong with you? - You didn't have to press it.
You could have stopped at two.
Why did you do that? This kid.
- You should have stopped. - That was unfortunate.
We have three people left.
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo and Jae Seok are left.)
Once.
- Ji Hyo. - All once?
Ji Hyo.
(Here's the egg.)
(I miss my luck.)
- Ji Hyo is eliminated. - It lays eggs every time.
It comes out near the end.
- We have two people left. - It could have been you.
- Who will take... - It's love and hatred relationship.
- 50 R Balls? - We'll see.
- My gosh. - Whoever wins...
- will get 50 R Balls. - It's 50 R Balls.
Go ahead.
(We meet again.)
(Who will be the first winner of the new year?)
Jong Kook goes first.
Once.
(Clicking)
Just once?
- Don't hesitate. - Go again.
(He hesitates.)
- Go again. It's okay. - Go.
(Here you go.)
Something spilled from your mouth. You must be nervous.
Who will be the last one standing?
(Is this how you want to do it?)
(Please lay the egg.)
(Their fates can change at any moment.)
Who will it be?
(Clicking)
(Will he go or stop? That is the question.)
(What will Jong Kook do?)
Don't hesitate.
(He goes again.)
(Jae Seok feels the pressure.)
I bet my entire savings on Jong Kook's win.
(Here's the egg.)
(Sorrow)
(Joy)
Congratulations. Jong Kook is in first place.
It's not anything new.
- Why does it never work out for me? - It's not anything new.
Jong Kook will be awarded with 50 R Balls.
It's not anything new.
Why does it not work?
You can distribute the R Balls.
It's obviously not good to have a lot of them.
However, you must keep one at least.
- You can't distribute everything. - I'll keep one.
You can distribute the rest.
Should we play another game with 10 R Balls?
- Let's go. - Should we give it to one person?
- Should we? Let's do a hand flip... - All right.
- Okay. - and whoever faces the wrong way...
- will take the R Balls. - Bring your hands to the middle.
It'll be the person who faces the wrong side.
- Do it. - Isn't Jong Kook doing it too?
- He's not. - Why would I?
- Kwang Soo. - No, I'm sorry.
I was just asking.
Thank you.
(Lee Kwang Soo)
- The loser... - That wasn't funny, right?
That was all right.
- Thank you. I appreciate it. - That was all right?
- That was all right? - Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
What should our next game be?
- Let's pull on people's sideburns. - That's a good idea.
That's a good idea. What do you think about the game, Kwang Soo?
I think it's great.
Should we do this?
- Let's go on our knees. - Go on your knees.
Let's do one at a time.
- Let's see. - Why are you playing?
There's no one else on this side.
- Keep going. - Don't you want to move there?
No, no.
- All right. - Why are you playing?
I'll actually move to that side.
- Are you moving here? - Yes.
- I'll come here. - What about Haha?
Move one space down.
You just have to pull with your right hand.
- Ready. - Anyone who screams first.
Whoever screams first will receive R Balls.
I don't think we should try hard.
- We don't have to. - Right.
Get ready.
(The game starts.)
Start.
(He throws a punch.)
(He lost his rationality due to strong pain.)
(Jong Kook could have peeled off his skin.)
- My gosh. - What?
(I only touched your sideburns. What's wrong?)
Jong Kook, Seok Jin screamed first.
- That's right. - Did he?
Start.
(Seok Jin screams.)
- Did he scream first? - Yes, he did.
- No, I didn't. It didn't hurt. - He did.
You did scream first, Seok Jin.
- I wasn't supposed to scream? - No, you weren't.
I have 20 left.
- Shall we half them, 15 each? - Shall we?
We will split them and each group will have 15.
- How can you split 20, you dummy? - One will have 15 and the other 5.
- He just called you dumb. - We can do 15 each.
- Let's give him 5. - Let's do 15 and 5.
(I should have held my tongue.)
- He called you dumb. - I was talking to Jae Seok.
(I will give you more R Balls for your courageous advice.)
- Thank you. - Seok Jin, you have a lot.
- You have four? - Prepare an extra basket for him.
(For 2017 Kickoff, New Year's fortune is first on the list.)
(This is the number of R Balls each member has.)
This is amazing.
- Please come in. - My gosh... This is...
The second stop on today's race is...
"Find Your Soulmate" which will be revealed through tarot cards.
You can discover who will be helpful to you in 2017.
You will find out about partners who will bring good luck to you.
You can consult the result...
when you choose your partner for the game.
Let me bring in an expert in this field.
Lee Yoon Jung will be the reader for today.
- Welcome. - Hello.
- She filmed with us before. - Right, it was last year.
(A reader, Lee Yoon Jung)
(She is a tarot master and a former president of a tarot society.)
Who should have the reading first?
- Seok Jin should. - Should I go first?
He gets really excited about this kind of stuff.
- It's true. I'm always curious. - He has a hard time waiting for it.
I see.
- You must've made a lot of money. - Should we sit?
I guess we can sit down.
Stop talking nonsense.
It's just to break the ice at first.
We need to get along.
I think he is more interested in finding out about his...
- personal business than his mate. - Right, he is.
- I will start. - Here I go.
(He will pick the first tarot card.)
(He has the reputation of being unlucky.)
Think about organic bakery.
One,
two...
I'm sorry, Seok Jin. Can you not throw the cards?
The viewers might assume you are playing poker.
I'm sorry. She's sitting a bit far from me.
- Please place the cards gently. - My apologies.
- I think this person goes well. - Really?
- Is everyone good for me? - This person may try...
to control you the way he or she wants.
- This must be Jae Seok. - This must be Jae Seok.
- He will be good for you. - He will?
He always nags me.
- Jae Seok. - Gosh, he's such a nagger.
Sometimes, I think he's older than me.
- He is your best partner. - He is?
I know Seok Jin really well. I am certain he's not interested in this.
Seok Jin, don't you want to pick cards for this year?
Can you read my fortune for this year?
- Be honest with him. - Please.
It is different from Korean fortune reading since it's from overseas.
This originated from the West.
People tell me that I look very western.
Where?
- My facial features are western. - Your facial features?
(He gingerly chooses his cards.)
- He's careful. - Yes, he is.
You saw it, right? His attitude is very different.
- He's picking them with two hands. - Exactly.
(The universe is on my side.)
This is good.
However, the only thing is that when you start something,
you don't finish strong.
(It doesn't end on a good note.)
(His fortune reading doesn't end on a good note.)
- She's being honest. - I am fine.
- This is scary. I have goosebumps. - So is it good or bad?
It's okay to maintain and keep what you have, but it's
- risky to start something new. - She's on point.
The reading matches completely.
So you are saying it's better if I just don't do anything. Right?
Or you can do something that will be quick.
- Something quick? - Right.
Nothing too permanent?
Do something that will be temporary.
You can do something like a street stall.
You can call it "Seok Jin's Street Stall".
(Seok Jin's Tarot Reading Stall?)
Is there any specific business you want to start?
- There is. - Well, I run a business.
- He wants to expand. - I see. You want to expand?
(What is Seok Jin's fortune regarding his business?)
You shouldn't expand.
(I shouldn't, right?)
It doesn't matter if it's from the East or the West.
- The whole world is stopping him. - The universe...
- The universe wants him to stop. - The whole world is stopping him.
(This is Seok Jin's compatibility with the members.)
Next up is Haha.
(Haha, a father of one child, is next.)
(Cards have been spread.)
Please choose three cards.
Your compatibility with this person...
At first, it may seem great, but as it heads to the end,
- it's a bit ambiguous. - Why?
- They don't end well. - When you actually play games...
with this person, the result isn't that great.
You are right.
Who is that?
(Who is the member he didn't accomplish much with?)
- It's Jae Seok. - My goodness.
- When we partnered up, - That applies to me, too.
- You're right. - we never won anything.
That's right. When I work with Haha...
It's either you betray me or I do.
He betrayed me a lot.
Jae Seok, you betrayed me a lot, too.
- You came to my house on Christmas. - Stay quiet. Stop lying.
You left me at a gas station and ran off.
(That was so long ago.)
- That happened ages ago. - Jae Seok.
- It's when the show just started. - Right. Jong Kook...
- Right, he was with me. - My goodness.
However, in terms of personal compatibility, it is very good.
- I see. - We aren't good professionally.
- We shouldn't play games together. - Right.
Now about the second person...
(How compatible is Haha with the second member?)
I think it's all or nothing with this person.
And I will pick on from the middle.
Here we go.
This is a bit disappointing.
- Didn't I pick this card before? - You are disappointed again, Haha.
- How can I pick the same one? - That's why...
- Maybe something's wrong with you. - With this person...
- You're the trouble. - Something's wrong with you.
The result leaves something to be desired.
But it's only professionally, right? We are good personally, right?
No, even personal compatibility isn't good.
Who is it? Is it me?
- No, it's Kwang Soo. - It's me?
We aren't compatible personally?
- This is weird. - It can't be.
- They're good together. - Something has to be changed.
(There needs to be a change.)
(He picks the cards for the third time.)
Why do I keep picking this card?
(A card keeps following Haha.)
I think you ought to shuffle the cards better.
- You're not doing it well. - Don't blame it on her.
Do you know how to shuffle properly?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
She's not a poker player.
- This can't be right. - Haha.
I chose this card five times in a row.
- You picked it. - You are the one picking it.
- How can this be possible? - Then don't pick that one.
I'm going crazy. Why is this following me?
She isn't a gambler.
(As Haha wished, she shuffles the cards better.)
- He didn't get a compatible member. - That's right.
- You should shuffle a bit more. - Should I?
Then you can be a dealer and try to shuffle.
How can he?
- That's a bit much. - Why should he shuffle?
(He cultivates his own fortune.)
These cards are hard to shuffle.
I haven't seen anyone trying to shuffle the cards like a dealer.
It's my first time, too.
- Shuffling doesn't matter. - It was too disappointing.
(How will this one work?)
It's up to the person who picks the cards.
Jong Kook said...
- He has no future. - This person is better than others.
- It's not perfect... - But it's better than others.
Out of the bunch, this person is better.
Haha, let's try to get along.
Why is it him?
(Seok Jin is most compatible with Haha.)
It was Seok Jin.
She told me that my compatibility with you isn't that bad, either.
Haha and Seok Jin will partner up.
- It's a match. - It is.
(This is Haha's compatibility with the members.)
(Next is Jong Kook, the luckiest member of all.)
- We will start. - I will think about this person.
(How compatible is he with the first member he thought about?)
It was so hard to pick.
- This person will be challenging. - Seriously?
- Is that me? - You must lead this person.
- Is that so? I didn't expect much. - Yes.
It's Seok Jin.
- I didn't expect much. - Was that me?
(He's the only challenging one.)
This is a good result for both of you.
All right.
We are...
(Whispering.)
Of course.
Haha told me that fates are to be cultivated independently.
(Fortunes can be changed.)
Was that a consolation?
- This is too funny. - Let's cultivate ours.
He was so cute when he whispered.
- So this person isn't good for me? - Yes.
(How compatible is Jong Kook with the second member?)
- It's good this time. - Really?
You can be friends with this person and will be at ease.
Out of 100 percent, it's about 80.
- This is good. - Is it Ji Hyo?
- It's Ji Hyo. - Me?
This is amazing.
Really.
(How compatible is he with the third member?)
- It's you. - You may face troubles.
You and this person will constantly fight and struggle.
- It will be difficult. - How can you be so on point?
- It's about 40 percent. - She's accurate.
You are generous.
- She sure is generous. - Seriously.
She is...
I figured it would be more like three percent.
- I didn't expect a lot. - That's a generous score.
- About the last person... - One more person to go.
- Who's left? - Haha.
It's Haha.
(How compatible are Haha and Jong Kook?)
I don't have to be careful when it's about Haha.
We are like brothers.
(He picks three cards randomly.)
(From their time on "X-Man", they spent a decade together.)
(They showed off the best compatibility.)
He chose three cards at once.
The cards tell me you aren't.
- Shouldn't you be more careful? - I mean...
Okay.
(What's the score of the tarot read that put friendship in jeopardy?)
- I'm sorry. - Be more cautious.
What's the score?
- It's zero. - Zero?
You can get a zero?
He didn't do it with caution. He should've drawn more carefully.
- He'll go again. - You make your own fortune.
Be more cautious.
I feel bad for her because you got a zero.
(We can have a fresh start, Haha.)
(This is Jong Kook's compatibility with the members.)
- It's Ji Hyo's turn. - Let's see how she does.
(Ji Hyo is the luckiest member.)
I feel like Ji Hyo will get lucky even with this.
- It's me. - No, it's me.
There's nothing but disappointment with this person.
(There will only be disappointment.)
Nothing but disappointment.
It says there's no way of making it work with this person.
I don't think this person is the right partner for you.
I also feel like that with Seok Jin.
They've never been good partners.
- They've never been a good team. - I feel the same way.
Why is everything related to Seok Jin sad?
- It's breaking my heart. - Gosh, I'm upset.
(It's heartbreaking but true.)
He said I make my own fortune.
(You make your own fortune.)
- I can't believe this. - Me, neither.
(What's Kwang Soo's compatibility with the other members?)
He didn't forget to iron his coat, did he?
(Gosh)
I have to focus right now.
He kind of looks like Gong Yoo when filming "Goblin".
(Gong Yoo?)
(I look like him?)
(Do you mean the handsome Goblin?)
(Do I look like Goblin?)
Oh, it was just a hallucination.
I realized it was a hallucination when he turned around.
(Be aware of replicas.)
- It was a hallucination. - A hallucination?
I was mistaken.
- How can someone even say that? - It was a hallucination.
I realized when you turned your head around.
- You saw a hallucination. - I did.
It was just a hallucination.
This person will feel like a good partner,
but later on, you'll feel suffocated.
I'll feel suffocated?
Is it me?
Does it say so on the cards?
- He'll feel suffocated. - I got goose bumps.
This is great.
I got goose bumps when she said I'll feel suffocated.
- He'll feel suffocated. - Disappointment and suffocation.
It'll be hard on you.
But I'm so good to you.
But I still feel suffocated.
Being good to him suffocates him.
(Jong Kook makes Kwang Soo feel suffocated.)
(It's the unlucky Jae Seok.)
(What is compatibility with the other members?)
You can't focus on each other.
If you decide to work together,
your concentration will be dispersed.
- But it won't be of disadvantage. - I see.
You'll have to gradually build up the relationship.
Is it Seok Jin or Haha?
I was thinking of Jong Kook.
- Me? - You have to build it up.
I have to build up the relationship.
The results weren't bad...
- when I teamed up with Jong Kook. - That's true.
What score would you give it?
- About 70. - That's pretty high.
- That's high. - It's 70 and 40.
It's 110 in total then.
- That's way too high. - This doesn't make sense.
- Why was it so high? - You must have a crush on me.
You wish.
- I guess so. - Were you secretly in love with me?
- I guess I liked you more. - I guess so.
- You scored 70. - That's way too high.
- My score was 40. - Really?
Is it better to get a lower score in this game?
(Jae Seok has a crush on Jong Kook.)
(Running Man's level of affection)
You can now partner up...
according to the partnership level.
I'll team up with Seok Jin.
- I have Haha. - That'll be for the best.
- We'll have each other. - Let's do this, Seok Jin.
We're the remaining three.
I scored 100 with Kwang Soo. The score with Ji Hyo isn't too bad.
I have Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo.
- You can team up with Jong Kook. - I have Jong Kook, too.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo will be a team.
Let's do this.
- Let's show them what we've got. - Let's do this.
- Let's see if we can overcome fate. - Let's go.
- We have to overcome it. - That's right.
All right. This game is called "Press and Hide".
(Press and Hide)
The teams will take turns being the tagger.
After you ring the bell, you have to catch the others.
You can get them out just by touching them.
- You will play here in this room. - Okay.
The two people will ring the bell and come back inside.
(Is this what the game was about?)
You should've explained the game before we could draw.
(This is also your fate.)
What difference did it make?
(We're ready to begin the game.)
- Let's catch them all. - Okay.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are the taggers for Round One.)
Your pants are too big. You should get them tailored.
This is how you wear these.
- Kwang Soo. - The game didn't even start yet.
I'll go to the cleaner's and tighten them for you.
- You're supposed to wear these big. - Really?
Do we go together to ring the bell?
Or can one person do it?
We can gather here and make a run for it later.
You should be gathered over there.
But it'll be over if they come at us from both directions.
- No. - We'll start once we verify it.
Should we ring the bell?
(I'll do it.)
(You can count on me.)
(Why is Seok Jin so confident?)
(What is Seok Jin's strategy that makes him so confident?)
Press it.
(Let's go, Seok Jin.)
(I'm so nervous.)
(Everyone is ready to play Press and Hide.)
- It started. - Let's go.
(Ringing)
Let's go, Kwang Soo.
(Press and Hide has been started.)
Let's go, Kwang Soo. Let's go.
(What kind of bad strategy is this?)
Gosh.
- Seok Jin is out. - They caught me. Why weren't you...
Seok Jin is out.
They caught me. Why weren't you...
(Caught you.)
Ji Hyo is over here.
(Let's get Ji Hyo.)
(Kwang Soo joins the chase.)
Song Ji Hyo!
- Song Ji Hyo! - I touched you.
Ji Hyo is out.
I touched you!
(Is something there?)
Did you touch someone?
- No. - Where are they?
(There was something here.)
I touched Haha!
He was hiding there?
- Where's Jong Kook? - He's not here.
- There's only one left. - Jong Kook's the only one left.
- Kim Jong Kook. - We only have to catch Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, you have to hold out for long.
(Jong Kook is hiding.)
- Kim Jong Kook! - Where did he go?
Where did you go, Jong Kook?
He hid very well.
(The whereabouts of a muscular man)
(A muscular man has gone missing.)
You have to hold them out.
He hid so well.
They're never going to find him.
Tell the cameramen to shoot him.
(Kwang Soo is on a chase for a missing man.)
He's not here.
- He's over here! - Where is he?
(Did they finally find Jong Kook?)
Gosh, that scared me. What is that?
I got really scared.
- What is that? - I thought his head was floating.
- Find Jong Kook. - His head was floating in the air.
(He thought something horrible happened.)
Where did he go?
- He hid so well. - Where is he hiding?
Jong Kook sure is good.
(Where on earth is he?)
(He's gone missing in the small studio.)
How are we...
Where is he hiding?
He vanished.
- Is he hanging from the ceiling? - Over here!
- He's over here! - Where is he?
Where is he hiding?
(Detective Yu wandered around for a long time.)
- Is he hanging from the ceiling? - Over here!
- He's over here! - Where is he?
- Why are you filming me? - He's over here.
- I found him. - What are you doing right now?
- How did you find him? - You can't be filming me.
- That was amazing. - It really was.
- We didn't know until now. - We really didn't know.
They were never going to find me.
(Seok Jin and Haha are the taggers for Round Two.)
Let's show them that we're different.
With your power and my speed.
Don't you think I can fit in there?
- How are you going to fit in there? - You don't think I can?
- You can't fit in there. - Let me try.
(What kind of a plan is this?)
Even Mr. Barrel wouldn't be able to fit here.
I think I can fit in here.
- In here? - Don't you think so?
It'll be easy.
They caught me so easily. Why did he look aside while running?
There's no reason for him to look there.
The fact that he looked over here is absurd.
People would usually just run past it.
- What's Jae Seok doing? - What are you doing?
(What a bad timing.)
- What? - Why would you open the door?
Why would you open our door?
You won't have time for that. The game starts at the bell.
(Jae Seok's plan has failed.)
- I'll run and... - What are you trying to do?
I'll run and...
This is good.
The eggs keep coming out of there.
(He's planning on getting vacuum sealed as the bell goes off.)
- This won't be easy. - This game is not about being fast.
This is about finding them. It's not about being fast.
- Don't you think so? - We have to find them quickly.
We have to be really quick.
(What will Jae Seok's power and Haha's speed bring?)
(Ji Hyo will be the one pressing the bell this time.)
(The game will start any time now.)
(The fast team will distribute 50R.)
We have to do it very fast.
(The doorbell rings.)
We were too busy talking.
(The game has begun.)
Hey.
- That's not the way. - Where did you go?
(Is anyone next to the door?)
Where did he go?
(Before getting vacuum sealed...)
- Here he is. - Catch him.
(Seok Jin spots Jong Kook.)
(Seok Jin runs very fast.)
He's over here. Attack him on the other side, Haha.
- Hey. - Where is he?
(Why can't she catch him?)
Wait, I'm getting close.
(She isn't close to catching him.)
There's Jae Seok.
(Haha succeeds in spotting Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok is completely trapped.)
I touched you.
How did you get in so quickly?
(On the other hand...)
This is frustrating.
(Seok Jin struggles...)
I can't catch her.
(Seok Jin struggles to catch Ji Hyo.)
Haha.
Why can't you catch her?
(He's running out of breath.)
(She giggles.)
(Are they playing tag or simply going in circles?)
Ji Hyo!
(Haha joins.)
(Haha starts running to catch Ji Hyo.)
- I got you. - Where's Jong Kook?
- Who did it? - Jae Seok is out.
Ji Hyo is also out.
- Only two members remain. - I tried my best.
There you are. I touched you.
- There you are. I touched you. - He touched you.
We only have one member left.
Jong Kook.
(Only Jong Kook remains.)
Jong Kook, keep hiding.
Hide well, Jong Kook.
- We're quite quick. - Keep hiding.
He was behind the curtain.
Actually, we didn't have to hide.
We just needed Jong Kook to hide.
Isn't it impossible to find him?
He disappeared.
The time keeps ticking.
- Where is he? - Take a break. We can't find him.
Where is he hiding?
He's the biggest one, but where is he?
Where could he be? I saw him at the beginning.
Is he hanging from the ceiling?
- Isn't this team running last? - No, we aren't.
(Where could Jong Kook be in this small studio?)
Where is he?
He disappeared.
Where did he go?
Seok Jin keeps repeating himself.
He's stating the obvious.
- Did you check there? - Is he here?
- Is he there? - I found him!
- Where? - He's over here.
Seok Jin.
Seok Jin. Corner him.
(They finally found their long lost brother.)
Let's corner him. He's going that way.
Gosh.
(Shy Jong Kook finally appears.)
- Where is he? - Catch him. He's over there.
I touched you.
We finally caught him.
(Jong Kook is out.)
Where was he hiding?
- When did he go there? - He was hiding over here.
I definitely saw him around here.
This is great.
(Round Two of "Press and Hide" ends.)
We're doing well.
You played an important role.
Shall we go in quickly?
Let's catch whoever we see first.
Let's divide the area.
- You can take this side. - Me?
- I'll take this side. - I'll take the other side.
Kwang Soo might be in disguise this time.
The doorbell sounds funny.
- He's too fast. - No, I'm not.
He's not too fast.
(He's very nervous.)
Coincidentally, we're on the same team.
They're done for.
("Press and Hide" starts.)
(Run away, they're coming.)
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook take off to catch the others.)
(Seok Jin is found as soon as the game starts.)
(He runs away with all his might, but he's not strong enough.)
Seok Jin is out.
(Seok Jin is out.)
(Where is everyone?)
There he is.
(He gets punched.)
(Kwang Soo is also out.)
- I just caught Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo is out.
- This is so embarrassing. - Did you catch him?
Who else is there?
- Haha? - There's Jae Seok and Haha.
You're doing well.
(Ji Hyo climbs up to look far.)
It couldn't have been easy to run and hide so quickly.
(He's dying to catch them.)
- He's good at hiding. - He hid himself well.
People are getting better at hiding after trying it a few times.
(They're as good as ninjas.)
- Jong Kook, did you check there? - Where?
- Where? - It's where staff members are.
Over here? Let me see.
Get out.
(He found him.)
- Isn't he over there? - You're embarrassing me.
Jae Seok is out.
- I have to find Haha. - Only Haha remains.
- I must find Haha. - He hid himself well.
- You did quite well though. - Didn't I?
- You have a good chance to win. - Haha can't go up high.
- Where is Haha hiding? - Where is he?
What if he keeps hiding until the shooting ends?
(Haha is excellent at hiding.)
I haven't seen him.
He might not come out until the award ceremony.
He might be at a dangerous place.
I haven't seen him. Where did he go?
(Did Haha become part of an object?)
I don't think he went this way.
- What if he went home? - Did he run and hide?
I haven't seen Haha, either.
- He's not here. - He isn't.
Why am I looking for him?
I was just curious.
(She peeks behind.)
Did you check on this side, Ji Hyo?
(Did he rise up to the ceiling or go down to the ground?)
He did something with his clothes.
Buy time.
(Try to find where Haha is.)
(We'll play it one more time.)
(Haha is here.)
(He pretends to be with the sound crew.)
I'm sure hiding places are limited.
- Do you mean Haha? - Yes.
(Ji Hyo comes back to the studio.)
(She looks around the sound crew.)
- Where did he go? - Did you check this side?
No, I didn't.
- Did you check this side? - No, I didn't.
Where did he go?
(Haha is at risk.)
(She approaches very close to where he is.)
I can't find him at all.
It's slowly getting scary.
(Jae Seok spots Haha.)
In the beginning...
Why aren't you filming him? You filmed me when I was hiding.
You should film him by now.
- That's right. - Film him like how you filmed me.
(He's being filmed.)
Really? You're filming him?
I can't see anyone filming him, though.
Where on earth is he?
Where are people filming him?
(Others start to spot Haha.)
- Where are people filming him? - He won.
He's in complete disguise.
I found him.
Where are people filming him?
You won't find him.
Where did Haha go?
I can see that he's being filmed, Jong Kook.
- Is someone filming him? - Time is ticking.
- He's in complete disguise. - I see where he is.
Jong Kook is very upset.
(I'll take care of you now.)
(Run for your life.)
(Ji Hyo touches him.)
- He was standing there. - That was great.
(Haha is out.)
Here are the results of "Press and Hide".
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo took 4 minutes 30 seconds.
- We took a long time. - They're running last.
Haha and Seok Jin took 2 minutes 55 seconds.
We don't know who's winning yet.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo...
(What about Jae Seok and Kwang Soo?)
Three minutes?
They took 1 minute 41 seconds.
(They're the winners.)
- Therefore, - Did they win?
we'll give 50 R Balls to Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.
Thank you.
Gosh, thank you.
- Let's share one by one. - Okay.
Each can take 10 balls.
Take out your basket.
(Try taking 10 balls.)
- That's too many. - We should hurry.
- I have a lot. - Okay.
Be careful, Kwang Soo. Take them to the others.
There's no rule. They give out however many they want.
It's like shopping at a market on the street.
We have a lot of love.
Here are some for Seok Jin.
What are you doing?
You don't have to give me many.
You already gave me a lot.
- That's good enough. - It's more even now.
(These are the numbers of R Balls each member has.)
(Running Man's New Year's fortune)
(Running Man's physical checkup)
- What's this? - Please come in.
Welcome.
- What's going on here? - Please come in.
There's a lot to listen today.
Seok Jin didn't hear anything good today.
- It's driving me crazy. - Now that it's the new year...
I even thought about changing my career.
Seok Jin is under a lot of stress.
This is the second part of Running Man's New Year.
For the new year, you can't ever emphasize enough about...
- health. - Health is the most important.
We'd like to take responsibility of your health.
Isn't iridodiagnosis accurate?
Isn't iridodiagnosis accurate? I've gotten one before.
- Really? - The diagnosis is so accurate.
I have the result attached on my fridge.
- Is it accurate? - Yes.
We'll rank you by your state of health.
Won't Jong Kook rank first?
It may be different from what you see.
We can't be sure about our health.
We'll invite him right away.
- Please welcome Dr. Park Sung Il. - Welcome!
(He has spared time today for the Running Man members.)
He's here to examine our health.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Park Sung Il, Korean medicine doctor)
We've never done this before.
I'm nervous about it.
- Me, too. - Iridodiagnosis can...
figure out your strengths and weaknesses.
It tells you how healthy you are.
It can predict your past diseases as well as diseases that you may face.
- Diseases we might have? - It's possible to predict them.
- Can we try? - Of course.
I never knew such a thing existed.
- I'm so curious. - You already took the photo...
- of your iris. It will be good... - I see.
if I can explain while we see them together.
- It will be good if you listen... - The iris looks so exhausted.
The iris looks so exhausted. Whose is it?
Why don't you guess whose it is?
I'm not sure.
- It's Ji Hyo's. - I think it's Ji Hyo's.
- It looks like a lady's eye. - It doesn't look good.
- I don't know whose it is, but... - Ji Hyo has a lot of eye lashes.
The color looks a bit murky.
(If it's murky...)
- This has to be Seok Jin's. - It's Seok Jin's.
(The murky eye is Seok Jin's eye.)
- Is it mine? - Yes.
- It's too murky. - Seok Jin.
- It sure is murky. - It is Seok Jin's.
When you look at his eyes, sometimes they look a bit hazy.
As you see, the surface of his iris...
isn't smooth like marble.
Right? What do you see in the upper part of his iris?
(The upper part of his iris is especially hazy.)
- It's gray. - It's not clear.
Couldn't it because I am a bit westernized?
Your brain has already started to age.
(Getting into the point right away)
(Has he gotten old already?)
- No way. - This can't be true.
- My brain? - Yes.
- How's your memory lately? - My gosh.
- My memory? - He can't distinguish faces.
Your memory will start to deteriorate.
This part shows your stomach condition.
Do you see how there's a tear here?
It shows your stomach condition isn't well.
Not long ago, I started...
- taking pills for my stomach. - You said your stomach was...
Can you tell him at least one good news? Please.
Just one.
- Fortune reading didn't go well. - Please.
I am about to pass out.
You can be careful in the future.
(Seok Jin's physical condition)
(New Year's advice is to improve eating habits and exercise muscles.)
- Next up is Jae Seok's eye. - It's mine?
I like this kind of people.
The reason is...
I usually say that people with this kind of eyes have a sexy brain.
- A sexy brain? - He has a sexy brain?
- It means he is smart... - He must have dirty thoughts.
(He's the man who only thinks of dirty thoughts.)
His brain is filled with adult videos.
Let's look at his left eye.
His stomach isn't good.
- It isn't? - He can't digest well.
You need to be careful of what you eat and your environment.
- I see. - Live in a good environment.
A good environment? I will eat some delicious food.
Please understand if I eat delicious food alone.
- Alone? - We can eat it together.
- You should think about us, too. - Okay, okay.
- Let's eat together. - Of course.
Can we look at his right eye one more time?
- The right eye? - The upper part is gray, too.
This is actually a shadow.
(He's firm.)
(Mine is aging process and his is shadow?)
This can't be right.
- How can it be... - He said that's a shadow.
(They accuse him of favoring Jae Seok.)
- Are you sure it's a shadow? - Let's look at mine.
- Can we look at mine again? - Here you go.
Look. This isn't a shadow.
How are they different? His eye is grayer.
- Yours is certainly gray. - This is crazy.
(Seok Jin's eye is hazy while Jae Seok's eye is clear.)
It's a shadow of his eyelid.
It's a shadow of his eyelid?
(Jae Seok's physical condition)
(New Year's advice is to enjoy working in a good environment.)
Guess whose eye this is.
This eye looks healthy.
- It's smooth as marble. - It's smooth. It's Ji Hyo's.
It means this person is full of energy. Energy is like a fire.
- This person has a fire inside. - It's Jong Kook.
To whom does it belong?
- This person is too energetic. - It has to be one of them.
This person won't die even if he or she doesn't eat for 10 days.
It's Jong Kook.
This person recovers quickly even after a surgery.
- I do recover fast. - Isn't he a cyborg?
It's Jong Kook's eye.
(It's Jong Kook's iris.)
You are lucky to have parents like yours.
You're born to be healthy. It's thanks to your parents.
Men with this kind of healthy condition was considered to be...
the best in times of war...
during the 16th and 17th centuries.
(He must have been preferred in war times.)
He should have been born during the Roman Era.
If we were in war,
- we would all be killed by him. - Right.
- We'd all be dead. - That's right.
(Even his iris is manly.)
(Jong Kook's physical condition)
(New Year's advice is to exercise as much as he did last year.)
- Let's look at the next eye. - Shall we?
This is Haha's.
You should notice...
that the upper part is brown,
but the lower part is brighter.
That's right.
- Isn't it? - It is.
This is related to his spine and bones.
(How did he know?)
Next, urogenital organs will start to weaken.
The same thing showed up in his fortune reading.
That's why...
(He's in shock.)
- You need to make children quickly. - He has no time.
He won't be able to later.
(You can also predict that from my iris?)
You should try to strengthen your lower body and your waist.
- You should walk a lot. - Walk?
Go for a walk by yourself.
I can see some gray parts in the bottom. Why is that?
This is because...
you often drink a lot.
- He does drink a lot. - Why is...
Why do you say mine shows aging process...
and his is caused by drinking?
(You need to accept the reality, Seok Jin.)
- He's really hurt. - There's a slight difference.
- I'm disappointed. - Don't be.
- He's telling you what he sees. - Everyone's eyes are gray.
Let me continue.
On the left, I can see that you have a hole in your lung.
You have a hole in your lung.
(He's surprised.)
There's a chance you may get lung cancer.
His lung isn't in a good condition in fact.
- You must stop smoking completely. - You should go to the hospital.
(He is shocked.)
You really should quit smoking.
Then everyone else can smoke?
No one should smoke.
(He's frustrated.)
Please just don't do anything.
Don't smoke or do anything.
(You should've stayed quiet.)
Just keep quiet.
(Haha's physical condition)
(New Year's advice is to stay away from cold food and exercise.)
- Who's next? - Shall we see the next one?
- It's pretty. - What a clear eye. It's Ji Hyo's.
- It has to be a lady's eye. - It's mine.
(Unlike previous eyes, it is clear and pure.)
Her eyes are pretty just like her face.
It's Ji Hyo's eye.
But don't you see...
some parts are cracked?
- That's true. - There are.
Her stomach is weak.
It's because she's stressed out and it affects her stomach.
Because there are a lot of parts cracked,
you should avoid stress and spicy or salty food.
There are small holes on the edge.
Your immune system for throat and lymph nodes are weak.
- I get sore throat often. - She does.
Your immune system is weak.
- This is amazing. - Your throat is weak.
- You can find out everything. - So...
the best medicine for you is...
Since you are very active,
sleeping is the best medicine.
That's why I sleep a lot.
- She does. - She really sleeps a lot.
She sleeps when she's tired. So you shouldn't wake her up.
After you sleep, you don't feel the need to eat.
- She sleeps without eating. - She doesn't eat.
It's better for her to sleep well instead of...
eating and not sleeping.
There was a reason.
- That's right. - Sleep is good for Ji Hyo.
Her body is trying to get what's most needed.
- Take care of your lymph nodes. - I will.
(Ji Hyo's physical condition)
(New Year's advice is to sleep well.)
- Next is the last eye. - It's Kwang Soo's.
- His eye is... - What is this?
- It's too gray. - I'm wearing contact lenses.
- It's because of the lenses. - My gosh.
- I can see he drinks a lot. - It's because of the lenses.
Isn't this an eye of fish?
(It does look similar.)
How could you say that?
(He's angry.)
What's the black thing at the bottom?
Does it have to do with his heart?
It's like a dot.
- It relates to his liver. - His liver isn't good.
You can't eat junk food.
- This is amazing. - When you see the iris,
you have sensitive intestines. That's why you don't gain weight.
You have weak intestines.
Your lung, respiratory system, and intestines are weak.
You have hormone imbalance in your brain.
My condition is just terrible.
You need to work on your muscles and you must do cardio exercises.
Is that it for me? Is there anything good about me?
Please find one.
You are worse than me.
(Something good?)
(Like my waist or my lower body?)
Let's give a round of applause to the doctor.
(I am not done yet.)
- Thank you. - This was interesting.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you, Doctor. - Thank you.
(All I remember is the eye of fish.)
(Kwang Soo's physical condition)
(New Year's advice is to cut back junk food and improve muscles.)
- Thank you. - This was amazing.
It's quite convincing.
- It's so interesting. - The iris...
We will reveal the ranks...
of your iris conditions.
- Not this again. - We've graded the results.
Whoever is ranked last...
will receive herbal medicine...
and a chance to distribute R Balls.
- It's good to be ranked last. - Whoever is last can...
It's to comfort that person.
Who knew I would be competing with Seok Jin?
I will announce the first place.
- It's the best. - The first place...
(Who will get the first place and have a healthy start?)
(Even his DNA is capable.)
(Is it the manliest member, Jong Kook?)
(Even his brain is intelligent.)
(Is it Jae Seok, a man of talents that the 21st century seeks for?)
The first place...
goes to Kim Jong Kook.
(Everyone expected him to take the first place.)
- I'm jealous. - Congratulations.
- It's as expected. - I will try to be healthier.
- The second place goes to... - Jae Seok?
It goes to Yu Jae Seok.
- Thank you. - These two exercise the most.
The ranking is proportionate to the exercises we do.
- I will announce the third place. - It's Ji Hyo.
It's Song Ji Hyo.
(She's satisfied with the result.)
- My goodness. - Now we have...
It's us three.
- Now we will... - We all drink a lot.
We will announce the fourth place. It goes to...
(The first nominee is Seok Jin whose brain started to age.)
(The second nominee is Haha whose manhood is at risk.)
(The third nominee is Kwang Soo whose body is undergoing a crisis.)
We will announce the fourth place. It goes to...
(Who's in 4th place among these 3?)
- It's Haha. - It's me?
(It's Haha.)
- For real? - This is nonsense.
- Congratulations. You're fourth. - It's me?
I'm the youngest in Running Man.
You're in fourth place.
I'm okay with losing to you.
- You're right above me. - He's 20 years older than me.
It's because I've been drinking a lot these days.
You've been drinking too much.
He'd call me out and make me drink. He doesn't drink himself.
Who'll score the last place on their physical checkup?
- Let me reveal 6th place. - It's 6th place.
Please.
(He can't embarrass himself as the youngest member.)
(He already has the worst fortune.)
Sixth place goes to...
(Who has the worst results for their physical checkup?)
Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin has the worst luck, tarot read, and health.)
Are you okay? Don't cry.
I'm sick of being last place.
- I'm relieved. - I'm sick of being last place.
- Seok Jin will get 50 R Balls... - That's good.
- That's not good. - It is.
Please give him some herbal medicine.
- He's not healthy. - Isn't that sophora root tea?
It's a type of tonic.
It invigorates and improves blood circulation.
Really? It's good for him.
- Seok Jin will distribute these. - I'll take one.
- I'll take one. - Seok Jin will hand them out.
- I really like you. - Thank you.
You don't have to give me so many.
And...
- I feel sorry for Haha. - Have pity on me.
- You pity me, right? - I do.
- We've been hurt. - Ji Hyo.
- Excuse me. - I like you a lot.
We've been hurt a lot.
- We've been hurt a lot, Seok Jin. - I like you a lot.
(Jong Kook will take it all.)
For you...
Here you go.
(Ripping)
Is this allowed?
I'm envious of you.
(That concludes the checkup. There's only one category left.)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo have the most R Balls and Haha has the least.)
(Running Man's new year physical checkup)
(Running Man's new year verification of competence)
Here's the last category.
It's time to verify your competences.
It's "R Ball Name Tag Elimination".
It's Name Tag Elimination?
You'll be assigned a target by lottery.
Whenever you remove a person,
the number of R Balls reduces by half.
You also get a chance for revival.
There are three boxes that contain Revival Cards.
(Targets have been assigned and the game starts.)
I have no chance.
Who has me?
We don't know who has who. I can't just pick on people.
- You must trust me. - Okay, let's go.
Jae Seok.
Who do you have?
(Kwang Soo picked Jong Kook. The three of them face each other.)
You scared me.
If you're going to help me, you have to be all-in.
(Kwang Soo pretended that his target is Jae Seok.)
(Jong Kook got fooled.)
(Kwang Soo backstabs him.)
Was it me?
(That's the 1st backstabbing of 2017.)
He's very mad right now.
Leave, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo didn't realize what tragedy lied ahead of him.)
(Jong Kook awakens.)
(Kwang Soo's betrayal...)
(makes Jong Kook mad.)
- What's going on? - Rip his name tag.
(I'll eradicate the root of treachery.)
(This is the start of Jong Kook's name tag hunting.)
Don't do this.
(Jong Kook shows what he's capable of.)
(He's invincible in 2017 yet again.)
You're done.
(He goes from 20 R Balls to 1.)
(This is how risky betrayals are.)
(Outdoor parking lot at SBS Headquarters)
2017 Running Man,
it's time for the bath.
Please place your R Balls inside this lottery wheel.
- Let's start with Haha. - I have 10.
You only have 10?
- Haha, it's behind you. - My goodness.
Place your R Balls inside the lottery wheel.
(Haha has 10 R Balls.)
(Seok Jin has 26 R Balls.)
This is making me nervous.
I have less than before.
Jong Kook, not only should you wish that you don't get picked,
but you better also wish that I don't get picked.
Let's say Jong Kook put 21 R Balls in the wheel.
- Shake it well. - I did.
This is insane.
I'll close the opening.
Please.
(This is the final R Ball count.)
(Running Man members await their fates.)
Let me reiterate.
The person that gets picked by lottery...
will get the water bucket.
They'll become the first runner for Member's Week.
As the first runner,
they can pick the next runner.
Whoever is picked will also get the water bucket.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- The draw... - Please.
- The draw starts now. - Please.
(The draw starts.)
- Please. - Please.
(There are about 80 R Balls with 6 names on them.)
- Take your time, Hwan. - Please.
(Nobody can predict the result.)
The first person that will take the water bucket...
(The first person that will take the water bucket...)
- Please. - Please, Hwan.
- Please, Hwan. - Please.
(The decision can't be taken back.)
Please.
(Who will get the water bucket...)
(and be the first runner of the Member's Week?)
- Please. - Don't let it be me.
(Who will get the honor?)
Please.
- Please. - He has it.
He has it.
- He has it. - He has it.
Please. I can't see.
Please, please. I can't see.
Please. It can't be Kwang Soo.
(What would the result be?)
All right. The first runner...
- for the Member's Week... - No!
(First runner for the Member's Week)
(Who does it go to?)
It's Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo gets picked.)
(Oh my goodness!)
It's Ji Hyo.
(Splashing)
(That was a powerful one.)
- Are you okay, Ji Hyo? - Ji Hyo.
(It's holy water that contains the spirit of Year of the Chicken.)
(I hope everybody is happy this year.)
(Ji Hyo is the first runner for the Member's Week.)
- Ji Hyo. - Are you okay, Ji Hyo?
You almost fainted.
- Are you okay, Ji Hyo? - Think about...
- who ripped your name tag. - Ji Hyo is the first runner.
- That was strong. - Do I get to pick now?
You get to pick the second person.
- Really? - Are you all right?
- Yes, I'm okay. - Whisper in my ear.
- You are okay, right? - Miss Ji Hyo.
- Miss Ji Hyo. - Today...
- Ji Hyo. - Today...
- No, Ji Hyo. - Do you think it was me?
- Are you all right, Ji Hyo? - Get back to your spots.
- All right. - Go back.
(Let's see.)
- Ji Hyo, - Yes?
you can whisper one's name in my ear.
(Would she punish Jong Kook for being ruthless...)
(or punish somebody else that she prefers?)
- I let you rip my name tag. - Seriously...
(His loyalty grows all of a sudden.)
Please do me a favor.
- Miss Ji Hyo. - I love you, Ji Hyo.
- You're beautiful. You're so sexy. - Let's pick Kwang Soo.
Just think about what happened today.
- That doesn't matter. - Do you want to talk it over?
- I'll talk it over with you. - I'm serious.
The second runner...
for the Member's Week...
- Is it me? - Why are you looking at me?
Is it me?
Why is he looking in this direction?
(Ji Hyo is unpredictable. Who did she pick?)
It's Jong Kook.
(She picked Jong Kook.)
(Let's go, Ji Hyo.)
(Splashing)
(Jong Kook is the second runner for the Member's Week.)
Are you all right?
Aren't you cold?
(They all look after Jong Kook in case he gets mad.)
- Are you all right? - Are you okay?
Why did these two get picked?
This is what I told Hwan. Things have happened already,
- so let's take the water bucket. - Let's start fresh.
- That's what I told him. - Excellent.
- Let's take the water bucket. - That's what she said.
- Let's start fresh. - Next year,
- let's have good things happen. - That's right.
That makes sense.
- Ji Hyo. - I wish you the best.
- Ji Hyo. - Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - Be quiet.
- You're all in this together. - We're not.
Don't say that.
That's not true.
You're all in this together.
- Are you in this too? - That's not true.
Are you in it too?
You too?
What are you talking about?
That's not true, Jong Kook.
- Is it you? You punk. - Hey.
- Come here. Punish him. - You punks.
- Where's Cheol Min? - Take the water bucket.
The members have agreed...
- You punks. - to punish the staff members.
Let's take the water buckets...
- and start fresh next year. - Let's start fresh.
We apologize again, viewers. We'll work harder.
- We'll run harder. - Thank you.
Let's pour the water buckets.
- In 1, 2, 3. - They need to experience it.
(The volume of water increased.)
(We're sorry for not able to protect you, Running Man members.)
(We'll treat you better.)
(They didn't realize how strong the water force was.)
Thank you for joining us today, Hwan.
(We thank Hwan for being the host for the kickoff.)
We'll renew our determinations...
and work with the staff to run even farther.
- Viewers, Happy New Year! - Happy New Year!
(Viewers, Happy New Year.)
(Member's Week is finally getting started.)
(Ji Hyo will be coming to you for next week's Member's Week.)