(The 2017 Running Man's Second Global Project)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(The global viewers recommend A Place for 1 Percent.)
(You can have a unique experience of seeing rare animals.)
(The global viewers recommend destinations only they know about.)
(A member with 3 I Go Stickers will go to A Place for 1 Percent.)
(Thus started Global Project Part 2.)
(Haha and So Min received a Sticker during the first race.)
(Seok Jin received a Sticker during the second race.)
Six!
(Haha received a Sticker again during the third race.)
(Last week, the thieves caught the sheriff and won.)
(The thieves gave 1 Sticker each to Seok Jin and So Min.)
It's a three-cornered fight.
(Among Haha, So Min, and Seok Jin, who will win a trip?)
(A hot summer day at Sangam SBS Prism Tower)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
(Limping)
(Wait a minute.)
(Why is he wearing slippers?)
Jong Kook got a gout attack.
Jong Kook is suffering...
from a gout attack.
I knew it would happen.
I asked the doctor,
"Why does it happen to me?"
It's because you consume too much protein.
- I know that, but... - It's the chicken breast.
You need to eat less chicken breast.
Wait a minute, does that mean we have an opportunity today?
- What kind of an opportunity? - Today is the day.
Today is the day we strike back.
You got an opportunity in eight years.
While he wore slippers because of his swollen feet,
Jong Kook's upper body is very much alive.
He is still strong.
His upper body is fine.
Jong Kook is still strong.
He will follow you in a handstand.
The strength my legs can't contain...
all went to my upper body.
My upper body is angry.
Let me summarize.
Jong Kook wont' be able to chase you down.
However, he will end you if you come at him.
Understood?
- That's scarier. - Keep that in mind.
- That's scarier. - That's scarier.
So Min, you have news.
She will finally move to Yongsan.
Please keep it quiet.
She bought an apartment.
Please don't do this.
- Let's have a housewarming party. - I won't reveal where I live.
She recently filmed a commercial.
She used her income from it as seed money...
to buy an apartment of her dreams.
80 percent of it is a loan.
Still, So Min has dreamed...
of moving out of her parents’ place.
She managed to do that four months after joining the show.
That's incredible.
She showed me a risk upon arrival.
- You mean list, not risk. - A list.
- A list. - He embarrasses me.
- The brothers are the same. - He embarrasses me.
- A list. - My goodness.
He shocked me.
You have a risk.
She showed me a list of items she needs.
She wants a gift from everyone.
- Everyone should give her a gift. - That's right.
- That's right. - Also,
we should congratulate Se Chan.
He got to spend time with Na Eun.
That's right.
- It was a short-lived love. - Did something happen?
(He was Na Eun's butler during the first Couple Race.)
(Na Eun found a place in Se Chan's heart from the start.)
(I was happy to be your butler.)
Na Eun appeared in his dream.
- Did she appear in your dream? - Yes, she did.
- What did she say? - I don't remember,
but I led her and took her to places.
Did you want to do that in your dream?
- You... - I keep thinking about her.
- Never mind. - What is it?
(What did Kwang Soo want to say?)
- What is it? - I had the same experience.
- He had the same experience. - He had the same experience.
- It happens when I fall in love. - She appears in your dream.
- Let's talk later. - Did you have a similar dream?
The dream made me lose my hair.
If it goes on,
- you will lose your hair. - Do you become stressed out?
- Yes. - You feel like you are dating.
Haha is quite used to the experience.
I am envious.
In any case,
you will soon see...
who will go on a trip.
(They will have the winner of A Place for 1 Percent today.)
- Today is the day. - What should I do?
(Seok Jin, Haha, and So Min are at a high risk.)
It will be decided today.
(They will go on a trip if they receive another Sticker.)
Bye, So Min.
Don't you want to go on a trip?
I won't go alone.
That's right. I need to be on your good side.
As you have guessed,
we will have a final mission to decide who receives a penalty.
Okay.
(The final mission to decide who receives the penalty)
Currently, Seok Jin, Haha, and So Min...
have two I Go Stickers each and are most likely to be chosen.
Before we have the final mission,
we will go over...
the six finalists of A Place for 1 Percent.
Okay.
(The 6 finalists of A Place for 1 Percent)
I am nervous.
Kim Cho Rong's recommendation, Catacombs of Paris.
(Catacombs of Paris)
(The mysterious underground ossuaries in the heart of Paris)
(The 300km-long underground tunnel is filled with human bones.)
Unlike her cute name,
Cho Rong recommended us a scary travel destination.
Abril's recommendation, Copper Canyon of Mexico.
My goodness.
I can't go there.
(It's a frightening collaboration between a canyon and a cliff.)
(With the zipline across the canyon, face your fear of heights.)
Hong Se Hee's recommendation, Giant Canyon Swing in the US.
- I remember that one. - It will give you a heart attack.
- I can't ride it. - It will give you a heart attack.
(A swing on the 400m-high cliff goes up to the sky.)
(It's a legendary swing even the architect only rode once.)
Park Ji Ni's recommendation, Crater of Diamonds State Park.
Let's go there.
- I would go there. - I would go there.
I wouldn't mind going to Crater of Diamonds State Park.
- It would be a nice trip. - I would go there.
(If you find a diamond, it will be yours.)
(The land of opportunity is open to anyone...)
(who pays 7 dollars for its entrance fee.)
Another candidate is Hammocking in Indonesia...
which Bi Kyung has suggested.
Are you talking about taking a nap in a hammock placed on a cliff?
- That sounds risky. - That's too dangerous.
(A hammock is placed in between the two mountaintops.)
(They'll enjoy a thrilling nap in the air 2078m above the sea level.)
(Clouds will be their blankets. It's both romantic and thrilling.)
- Who recommended it again? - Goo Bi Kyung.
You better watch your back.
(Join us, Bi Kyung.)
The last candidate is...
the manual wooden cable car in Indonesia...
which has been recommended by Syifa.
(The waves are menacing as if they'll swallow everything.)
(They'll have to move above the waves alone on the cable car.)
(Today, the members to go on the dangerous trip will be decided.)
All right, so today's final mission is called...
I Go, Stop Race.
(The final mission is called I Go, Stop Race.)
Seok Jin, Haha, and So Min currently have...
two I Go Stickers each.
They'll be Dud Man...
to determine the result of today's race.
(These three members are the Dud Men to determine today's race.)
(The name sounds suspicious enough. What will be their mission?)
All right, please wear this badge.
- Dud Men gets to wear something. - They get something.
I guess they'll be our team leaders.
Do we have to win their favors from now on?
(Are they the team leaders for today or the members to go on the trip?)
Still...
Still, at least 1 of us 3 may not go on the trip.
- You're right. - At least one of us.
I hope it'll be two among us.
- You never know. - Gosh, that stings!
(I'm sorry. I didn't do it on purpose.)
You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
- Hey! - Goodness.
How many times has it been?
Seok Jin is aware of it, but he still lets Jae Seok do it.
He was waiting for it.
He was waiting for you to prick him.
He was aware of it.
(It's a must to see their teasing each other now.)
Some of our viewers wait to see me tease him.
I've succeeded to tease him today as well!
(He clears his self mission to tease Seok Jin for today.)
Today,
you will go through the race in two teams.
At the end of the race,
the team with fewer Dud Men will win.
(The team with fewer Dud Men will win today's race.)
After each mission, the winning team will get to have a chance...
to change one of your team members.
If you choose to switch members,
each team'll play the roulette that has members' names written on it.
You'll pick one member to change by playing it.
Or you may choose not to change members.
This is going to be fun.
So 1 of 3 will go for certain.
If there's 2 Dud Men in 1 team, they'll have to go on the trip?
(Dud Men in the losing team will go on the trip.)
Today's missions will be fierce.
Two Dud Men in the losing team will be given a I Go Sticker each.
- Dud Men will... - There's no need for us to do hard.
choose whom to go on the trip with...
- Within their team? - within their team.
- That's scary. - Within their team.
- They'll take Dud Men out. - This is incredible.
- Kwang Soo... - This is bad.
It's a chance for Kwang Soo to survive though.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
I'll put all my effort.
(He's been penalized for 7 years, but not today.)
If you win today's race, you won't go on the trip for certain.
- Right. - You're right.
Okay, I'll be really serious today.
(Will his dream to be exempted from the penalty come true?)
Before the race, you'll be divided into two teams by this mission.
It's called Up and Down.
- What is it about? - I'm serious today.
- This? - Serious.
(What is it about?)
All the members will either sit down or stand up...
with the count of three.
As soon as there are four members who are standing up,
the mission will come to an end.
- I'll say, "Up and Down, 1, 2, 3." - Okay.
Up and Down.
(It's the most important part of the race.)
One.
Two.
(The fewer Dud Men are in your team, the better it will be.)
Three.
(How will these 3 Dud Men be divided in teams?)
Up and Down, 1, 2, 3.
(Seok Jin stands up while Haha and So Min stay seated.)
Thank goodness.
- We're a team! Wait. - Gosh, I'm going crazy.
- Are we a team? - I'm the only Dud Man here.
- We have the unluckiest members. - Hold on.
- Let's win. - Let go!
- Let me go! - I can't go on the trip!
I can already see who'll go on the trip with Seok Jin.
I'm confident in this team.
- I can do this. - All right.
Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, So Min, and Haha...
will be in Team Black with two Dud Men.
Seok Jin, Jae Seok, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo...
will be in Team White with one Dud Man.
If the race ends as it is,
- Team Black'll all go on the trip. - The game ended at once.
- Right. - That's right.
Let's keep things as it is.
- Let's keep things this way. - Great.
- Let's do that. - Really.
- Don't betray us. - It's all right.
- Let's do that. - Let's not change members.
It can't stay this way until the end.
- It's not possible. - It can't be.
You'll be given a chance to switch members once every mission.
We never know yet.
- We never know. - This is amusing.
(Until when will these two teams remain the same?)
I have a feeling...
that my team will try to send me away if we win.
It's you for certain.
- The four of us are like family. - Just keep this in mind.
We'll win if the four of us stay in this team.
- Then... - Seok Jin, you have to know this.
You may stay the same all you want,
but if we send one of our Dud Men in the end, you'll be doomed.
It'll be you.
Just get your gout treated already.
I hope you'll recover soon.
- I'm just saying it. - Focus on your treatment.
I have a point though.
- This is frustrating. - Goodness.
Look at the color of our outfits.
We're in the same team.
It's white.
- Seok Jin. - It's an angelic color.
We're unlucky, but we'll show them.
Let's show them what we can do.
Am I supposed to trust you guys?
Goodness.
You never know what they're thinking inside their outfits.
You can't see through their thoughts.
Now that he can't use his legs freely, he's talking so freely.
He's using his mouth instead.
He has abs on his tongue.
- Come on. - He has abs on his tongue.
(Jong Kook has trained his tongue through exercising squats.)
I'm serious.
He holds a dumbbell with his tongue.
That's how he gained the abs on his tongue.
He even does tongue sit-ups. He exercises his tongue.
You're all aware that your team members are very important.
Now, you'll play a game to win a Chance Card.
- Okay. - This Chance Card...
- Do you think it'll be yours? - Goodness.
- I may look forward to having it. - Do you think it'll be yours?
This Chance Card will allow you...
to spin the roulette again if you have to switch your member...
with a Dud Man or you're not satisfied with the result.
We must win this.
- It's a must. - We must win this card.
This Chance Card is huge...
because if Team White wins it, they can send Seok Jin over...
to the other team.
- Really? - Right.
- Then it's not great. - It's good for our team.
Will you not choose to stay?
- It's good for our team. - We gets to spin again with it.
Seok Jin seems to want to try that thing.
What was it, the swing?
What I meant is that I can't ride it.
I'll have terrible motion sickness if I ride that.
Does it mean you can go to the charnel house?
- I can. - He can't.
It'll be a huge mess if he does something wrong.
- I'm okay with it. - It'll be his charnel house.
- We have to avoid it. - It might be his charnel house.
It might be his last place.
So he can't go there.
Well, it can be done at a right timing.
He might find his place to rest in.
(What are they talking about when he still has many days left?)
"It can be done at a right timing."
When he went to Japan...
Take it easy.
- We're a team. - Goodness.
(Long live Seok Jin!)
You'll start the game to win the Chance Card.
You'll play Jae Seok's Game that's trendy nowadays.
(Jae Seok's Game)
(It's a success if they answer randomly...)
(for 3 consecutive times to the producer's questions.)
(It's become even more amusing ever since its name got chanced.)
All right. Starting from So Min.
(3 members from each team will play the 1st round.)
- So Min, you need to focus. - Ji Hyo.
- Focus. - This game is so hard.
- Hey, this... - Ready,
set, go.
What do you like to do the most recently?
Thank you for visiting us.
What's the word you often say?
Jung Chul Min.
(That's the producer's name.)
(Why would you say his name often?)
- That makes sense. - Why?
Do you say his name often to win him over?
- So Min. - She must like him.
- That's not it. - She likes him.
Don't be so sly trying to win him over.
Why are you looking at her so dearly?
You're mistaken.
I know you have a girlfriend.
They might argue over this later.
It's Ji Hyo's turn now.
- You can do it! - Be confident.
- Ready. - Don't try to think.
Set, go.
- How will you be after 10 years? - 6 times 5 is 15.
- What do you want to be afterlife? - 6 times 3 is 18.
What's your favorite math formula?
(Oh, dear.)
(Ji Hyo fails.)
That was witty.
- He improvised it. - He didn't follow the script.
(He's so meticulous!)
- He didn't follow the script. - He put down the script.
This game keeps being upgraded.
(When she answered in calculations, he improvised to change questions.)
He put down the script and improvised his question.
That was so cool.
That was cool. I admit it.
- Haha, we only have you. - That was great.
- Okay, I'll do my best. - You can do this.
- Ready. - Let's go.
Set, go.
- How'll you name your third child? - 6 times 4 is 24.
(Wrong)
- Why? - That makes sense.
(Didn't you say you'd name your third child "6 times 4 is 24"?)
It's my baby's name!
- I know. - What...
- Hey, 24. - It's my...
- It makes sense. - Why would I name...
Why would I name my baby "6 times 4 is 24"?
6 times 4 is 24!
- Come to your senses! - 6 times 4 is 24!
It doesn't make sense at all!
- That sounds cool. - It's unfair.
- Let this one slide, seriously. - All right.
I'll give you another chance then.
Ready,
set, go.
What comes in your mind if you see Jae Seok?
1 plus 1 equals 2.
What do you wish to give your mother-in-law as a gift?
- Gift... - Gift voucher?
(Gift vouchers are the best gift for your mother-in-law!)
- Gift voucher. - I'll present you this time.
I'll make sure to give it to you this time.
Gift voucher!
The producer asked about his family.
(Haha fails to answer randomly to his family-related questions.)
- Gift voucher! - I'll give it to you.
I love you!
(Team Black fails to succeed in the 1st round.)
- Okay. - Let's go.
- One of us should succeed. - One of us.
Just one of us.
We'll decide.
(If Team White wins, they'll win the Chance Card.)
6 times 4 is 24. All right.
- Se Chan. - Yes.
(Se Chan's turn)
- Stay cool. - Ready, set, go.
What does Son Na Eun remind you of?
Son Na Eun.
(Na Eun reminds him of her.)
(All I can think of is you.)
- Nice. - What?
I love it.
Na Eun...
Is she all you can think of?
(I don't mind losing a game as long as I have memories of you.)
My head is full of her.
It's full of Na Eun.
All right. It's Kwang Soo's turn.
- Okay. - Ready, set, go.
What do you call your girlfriend?
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
- Hold on. - Why are you so sorry?
(Were you looking for your girlfriend in the labyrinth?)
(Why are you so sorry?)
I call my girlfriend that?
It's not even Korean.
My third child is called 6 times 4 is 24.
- What about Thank You? - I love you, I'm Sorry.
- Is it Thank You? - That'd be weird.
It sounds good.
It's not even Korean.
I'm Sorry?
- If Jae Seok fails, - It's Jae Seok's turn.
- Look how I do it. - Team White will...
Jae Seok.
- You've never succeeded. - Of course.
- You've never succeeded, right? - No.
- Succeed today. - Today, I'll succeed.
(Jae Seok is determined to succeed today.)
- This is our last chance. - All right.
Ready, set, go.
What did you say when you proposed?
Well... Toad.
(Toad)
(Will you be my toad?)
I was going to say, "toad".
This is not okay.
- Did you say, "toad", to her? - Gosh.
- Did you say that? - This is too much.
"Toad" is a bit too...
I can't believe this.
- It's too difficult. - Then...
I'll give you another chance. I won't ask about your family.
- Don't ask about our family. - Don't ask about our family.
I have answers in mind.
Ready, set, go.
What do you want to eat to stay healthy in the summer?
(Well...)
Why do you make that sound?
(Why do you keep making that sound?)
- Why do you make that sound? - What?
Didn't I succeed?
Why do you keep making that sound?
(He can't stop making that sound.)
- My goodness. - You failed.
Let's play fair.
- Let's play another game. - Let's play another game.
Why don't we play the multiplication game?
Should we play a game where you have to say the wrong answer?
- Okay. Let's do that. - Ji Hyo is on the other team.
She said, "6 times 5 equals 15."
(The problematic player, Ji Hyo, is on the other team.)
(Ji Hyo once answered, "6 times 5 equals 15.")
Let's go. Let's start from Team Black.
Just say the last digit wrong.
The rules are simple.
You have to say only the last digit wrong.
If you don't say the answer right away, it doesn't count.
So Min will play first,
- and Haha will play last. - Okay.
- Here we go. - Here we go.
- Let's play the multiplication game - Let's play the multiplication game
- 6 times 3? - 30.
Fail.
(She fails.)
- Fail. - Hey.
6 times 3 equals 24.
You just have to finish one round.
Let's finish one round.
- All right. - Who should start?
Seok Jin will play first.
If we succeed, we'll win.
(This is the last chance to win the Chance Card.)
(Will Team White win?)
- Let's play the multiplication game - Let's play the multiplication game
- 8 times 8? - 62.
- 6 times 4? - 21.
- 7 times 5? - 38.
2 times 9?
(Team White will win if Jae Seok succeeds.)
15.
- 7 times 5? - 38.
- 2 times 9? - 15.
(Team White wins.)
- We did it! - Team White wins.
- We weren't slow. - We weren't.
- I was determined. - Good job.
We were so desperate.
After spinning the roulette wheel,
if you don't like the result, you can spin it one more time.
I did my best in the game,
but I can't benefit from it.
You did a great job.
Where are we?
We're outdoors.
There are dice.
- There are dice. - There are dice.
(What mission will they be given?)
- Do you see the dice? - Yes.
You'll have lunch soon.
Before that, you'll carry out the first mission.
(They can change their team members.)
- I like it. - Okay.
Are we already saying goodbye?
- Don't think too much. - We won't.
If we stay this way, we'll win.
The mission is called, "Dice Go, Stop".
You'll take turns in throwing the dice.
The team with the sum of the dice...
closest to 10 will win.
After throwing the dice,
decide if you want the other team to continue or stop.
If the sum exceeds 10, you'll lose.
That sounds fun.
(They have to carefully decide if they'll stop the other team.)
(It's the perfect chance to send Dud Men to the other team.)
Please decide who will play first.
Who should play first?
It might be better to play first.
Let's play rock–paper–scissors.
- Should we do that? - Yes.
- Rock–paper–scissors. - Rock–paper–scissors.
Don't sound so angry.
- Are you angry? - No.
Why did he get angry while saying, "rock–paper–scissors"?
Rock–paper–scissors.
(Are you pulling my leg?)
I'm thinking.
(Jong Kook is already angry.)
- I mean... - Why do you need to think?
- Why do you need to think? - I have to.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Rock–paper–scissors. - Rock–paper–scissors.
Rock–paper–scissors. Okay.
Hey.
Ji Hyo, you go first.
They have so many lucky members.
A four is a good one.
Good luck.
- They have so many lucky members. - A four is a good one.
- A four is good. - It's good.
Ji Hyo, get a four.
Ji Hyo, throw the dice.
(Please get a 4.)
(If she gets a 4,)
(it'll be a good start.)
A four.
(She got a 4.)
It's a four. You're crazy.
- Amazing. - You're crazy.
What is with her?
Please decide between Go and Stop.
- Go. - Go, definitely.
My goodness.
- You're unbelievable. - You're amazing.
We can do this.
- They're so lucky. - It's okay.
- Don't feel burdened. - A four is good.
(They loved a 4.)
(Then I will...)
Nice, it's a six.
Why is it nice?
- It's not? - Why is it nice?
(Isn't a bigger number better?)
(With a 5 or 6 in the next round, they'll lose.)
- I like big numbers. - Why is it nice?
- We might lose. - Why are you so oblivious?
I'm sorry.
You were the only happy one here.
You two should stay out of the game.
(Me too?)
- Why? - You're so bad.
- Get a 6 and win. - I need a 6.
Here we go.
Let's do this.
Let's go.
(Confident)
Wait. Hey!
- It ended up on his foot. - It doesn't count.
- Give it to me. - Why did you do that?
It doesn't count.
Why doesn't it count?
Let me explain.
(I won't explain in detail.)
Let me tell you.
In every game...
(Jong Kook answers the question in an aggressive way.)
Wait, why are you guys just watching?
Why are you just watching?
- I'm so relieved. - We're just like you.
Fine.
(Who could stop him?)
Every game has this rule.
My goodness.
(They got a 3.)
Go or Stop?
- What is our sum? - It's seven.
It's a bit risky.
- We have get either 1, 2, or 3. - You have a 50-percent chance.
You have a 50-percent chance.
It's a 50-percent chance.
- Can you give us 10 seconds? - Okay.
I'll just listen to you.
(What will Ji Hyo choose?)
Stop.
(Stop by all means.)
(Settle at 7.)
(Don't take risks.)
We would...
We would choose Go.
Let's just stop.
- We have the next round too. - You're right.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
If you get a three...
Kiss the dice.
(They kiss the dice.)
That was a bad idea.
If you get a six...
I don't believe I'll get a six.
(I don't believe I'll get a six.)
We just have to avoid a six.
(I'll finish the game.)
(It's a 6.)
It exceeds 10. We win!
(I didn't believe I'd see a 6.)
I told you.
(Happy, sad)
Why did you get the dice dirty?
- What? - What?
- What did you just say? - Our lips are dirty?
- Our lips are not dirty. - What are you talking about?
- How can you say that? - Let's continue.
(Team Black wins.)
Please. For the last time.
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo, So Min. Please.
- I won't do it again. - Hey.
Apologize to the viewers.
You were so indecent. You really were.
- You can't do that. - That's right, Kwang Soo.
- Shame on you. - Hold on.
I am only as honest as you are.
(I am only as honest as you are.)
- How could you? - I learned this from you.
Then slap me once.
(Slapping)
(He slaps Jae Seok without hesitating.)
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
We won't do that again.
(It's delightful.)
Well done.
- We won't try to break rules again. - Kids are watching our show.
- We won't try to break rules again. - That's right.
We mustn't do this.
- We won't do it again. - We won't do it again.
(As they respect the rules...)
Team Black wins.
It's a variety show after all. It must be exciting anyway.
Ji Hyo.
- This is great. - It was a fun game.
- Team Black can change a member. - We have to switch someone.
- We have to. - I agree.
- I wish Haha would go. - Either So Min or I…
- has to go. - We'll deal with this.
- That's how we can survive. - Will you change or not?
- We will switch no matter what. - We have to try.
Who is going to spin the roulette?
- The opposing team should spin it. - All right.
We want either Ji Hyo or Jong Kook.
(Team White wants either Ji Hyo or Jong Kook.)
We want to change So Min.
- No, it's Haha. - It's So Min.
Haha.
In 1, 2,
- Three. Here we go. - Here it is!
Please be So Min.
(If it's Jong Kook or Ji Hyo, Team White has a better chance.)
(If it's So Min or Haha, it will be favorable for Team Black.)
- Please, please. - Be So Min.
Please be So Min.
- Ji Hyo! - It's Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is chosen.)
- It's Jong Kook. - Jong Kook!
(Breaking News: Jong Kook Is Transferred to Team White.)
- Come here. - I have to make sure I stay.
(We are doomed.)
- We are doomed. - I have to make sure I stay.
I just have to stay in this team.
- The chosen one is the unluckiest. - Jong Kook.
I have to make sure I stay in this team. That's all.
(Welcome, Jong Kook who is not a Dud Man.)
- Jae Seok. - Why were you so mean before?
- I don't know. - Jong Kook.
I don't know who will be picked.
- Good work. - Well done.
- Well done. - Great work.
- It was fun. - It was great.
If Seok Jin is chosen, it will be awesome.
- That's right. - It will be amazing.
(He plans to put all the Dud Men into Team Black.)
- If it's Seok Jin, it'll be great. - No way.
(Shaking his head)
The member who is picked now is the unluckiest.
It can't be me. I don't want to go.
I really don't want to go.
Get ready.
- Please! - If it's Seok Jin, it'll be great.
We need either Kwang Soo or Se Chan.
- No, it has to be Seok Jin. - If it's Seok Jin, it's perfect.
No way. It won't be me. It can't be.
Please be Seok Jin.
- Please be Seok Jin. - No.
It can't be him.
- Seok Jin should be picked. - No, it won't be me.
It has to be Seok Jin. Please.
(Who is the unlucky member that will...)
(join Team Black?)
- Be Seok Jin. - No.
- No way. - Please be Seok Jin.
- It's Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo!
(Kwang Soo is picked.)
- Be Seok Jin. - No.
- It's Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo, come quickly!
- Why were you so mean before? - Kwang Soo, hurry.
Don't ever bring in the roulette again.
Okay!
- Don't bring it in again. Please. - He's unbeatable.
Some can't do the multiplication, but I'm not good at the roulette.
Please give them the team uniforms. They'll change now.
(It's time to change uniforms.)
He can't be saved.
Look at him. He looks great in black.
Let's get it.
- We have to change here? - Team White,
you had a chance to spin the roulette one more time,
but you decided that you won't use it now, right?
(You won't use it?)
Hold on! The roulette!
- What is he talking about? - We'll spin it again!
- We'll use it. - No.
- Give me that. - I used it. Hold on.
- No. - I already used it.
- I just used it! - Okay.
- I used it. - Disregard this.
- Hey, look. - It was in my pocket!
Give me that. Give it back.
- Hold on. - He's...
- We'll use it later. - You are one strange guy.
Why would we use it now?
- It's for the team! - Look at you, weirdo.
This is for Team White. Why did you take it?
You are a member of Team Black. Why did you do that?
What a funny guy.
(Don't push it. I'm already mad as it is.)
Since this belongs to Team White, use it at a crucial moment.
How can a moment be more crucial than now?
What color is your shirt?
It's black.
It's black, but...
- Come to your spot. - That was close.
No one really thought about that.
Now, you will go inside and have your meal.
Let's go in.
(Since some switched teams,)
(you can give us a meal without playing a game, right?)
For members who will travel to the place for one percent,
we prepared a meal with three kinds of duck dishes to invigorate.
- This is great. - Okay.
It looks really tasty.
It does. Gosh, look at the roasted duck.
- There are dice over there again. - Yes, there are.
There are dice again.
(Is there another mission in the restaurant?)
You will play the game, Dice Go, Stop, which you played earlier.
- Only the winning team... - I'm in!
- can eat. - Okay.
(Only the winning team of Dice Go, Stop can have the meal.)
It's the game our team is the most confident at!
Let's go.
- Please throw a 6. - Be 6.
- It's 2. - 2 is great.
(Lucky Ji Hyo throws a 2.)
This is all luck.
- It's 5. - It's great.
Throw a two.
- She threw a two! - What?
(The total score is 4.)
- When I throw it, I'll get a five. - I know.
I'm sure I'll throw a five.
Look at this. It will be a five.
(If Jong Kook throws a 5, the game is over.)
(Will he be able...)
(to throw a 5 as he predicted?)
- Yes! - Did you see that?
(He really threw a 5!)
- I can't believe it. - It really happened.
(Team White gets the meal as they score 10 points.)
- It really happened. - No way.
- Haha, can this be possible? - I told you so.
Seriously?
Can I sit in front of the soup?
- Yes, please. - I'll sit here. You can sit there.
- Okay. Let's sit and eat. - Goodness, look at this.
Let us enjoy our meal.
(Should we, Team White, enjoy the victors' meal by ourselves?)
Goodness, we have some leftover duck.
(Since he feels sad to enjoy this amazing meal alone...)
Kwang Soo, you know that...
duck dishes are healthy summer food...
that energize us, right?
These dishes have unsaturated fat.
- It's good for people on a diet. - That's right.
Those are healthy fats.
- Ducks are great for our bodies. - It's really healthy.
Ducks are full of protein,
but what's more is that this fat is healthy.
Even the skin tastes awesome.
The skin is the tastiest.
Goodness.
I want to give this wrap to someone.
Me.
(Give it to me.)
- It's refreshing. - So Min.
(I can't just give it to you.)
Show us your skills with the magnet.
Can the lid of the rice bowl stick on your face?
- This one? - Yes.
- If you can do, I'll give you this. - I haven't done it with this.
If I can do this, will you really give it to me?
(She hasn't put the lid of the rice bowl on her face,)
(but since I'm the magnet, everything sticks onto my body.)
(Let me see.)
(It sticks.)
Stay as you are. I'll feed it to you.
- No way. - Gosh.
(It's the skill of the magnet.)
Let me have one too.
- I did it too. - You are amazing.
- Give me a wrap too. - Kwang Soo, you are late.
(Kwang Soo becomes the magnet too.)
(When people are desperate, things go their way.)
Please. Let me do this once.
(It's a miracle!)
- Give me a wrap too. - Kwang Soo, you are late.
- I did it too! - Please.
Give me the meat too!
I did it too.
I can do this too. It worked.
Kwang Soo, you were late.
(Show us something else.)
- Kwang Soo, do something else. - Kwang Soo.
Please give me a chance.
- Hey, this is... - Please give me a chance.
(He shows his greatest skill.)
- If that works, I'll give you one. - Please.
I did it. I can do this too.
Let me have just one wrap, please.
- Please. - Kwang Soo.
(He gives advice.)
I can give you food if you stick the dried laver on your teeth.
- If you do it, we'll give you food. - But...
whoever puts the dried laver on their sideburns is the worst.
I won't give that person the food.
(He's the worst.)
What is it? He put it on his sideburns?
(I didn't know you were doing that.)
You can't do that.
What do I have to do next?
(How do I look? He distinguishes himself from others.)
(Impersonate a dummy)
(If you do well, I'll think about it.)
Say, "Kwang Soo isn't here."
You have to do exactly he did.
I'm starting to have second thoughts.
Why are you having second thoughts?
Hey, I even put it here.
- That's great. - Hey, just do it.
- Great. - Nice.
(She shows off her skills.)
(Floundering)
Hey, stop it.
Hey, stop it. That's enough!
(Why are you doing that? Just ask them to give you food!)
Stop it.
(Do you not have self-respect? It's only duck.)
(Impersonating a dummy)
Kwang Soo isn't here.
(He doesn't have even the slightest self-respect.)
(He swaps his self-respect for a piece of duck.)
Kwang Soo succeeded.
(Delicious)
The myeongyi wrap is really good. It's the tastiest.
- It's really tasty. - By the way,
don't put the dried laver under your eyes like the baseball players.
(Sighing)
Hey, Se Chan, stop being so mean. Haha is older than you.
- Let's eat. - He's a father of two children.
Do you think he wants to do that?
I'm sorry.
(I'm a respected father at home.)
- Did we eat it all? - Hey, then...
- If you think... - His son watches Running Man now.
How can we work if we think about those things?
We ought to do our job when we are at work.
(I have to eat that duck.)
(He becomes G-Dragon.)
Wow, fantastic baby
That's great. Haha, I like that.
(Satisfied)
(G-Dragon, are you watching?)
- I'm Mamamoo. - You didn't like it?
Give me a wrap.
(I even danced for you.)
If he can't eat it even after this...
(Poor Dad)
(Son, it's hard to make a living.)
I even danced twice.
- You are too cruel. - Others have to agree.
- Before you danced, - No way.
what Kwang Soo did left a stronger impression.
- You can sing for us too. - That's right.
(My heart is reminded of you)
(My heart is reminded of the duck.)
That was pretty funny.
That's right. Give me a bite.
I liked it.
Here is a duck leg.
Here you go.
Enjoy.
Why are you eating it?
So Min, wait a minute.
She is crazy.
Why are you eating it?
(Justice wins.)
(He confiscates the duck.)
That was incredible.
She had it past her molars.
How did you take out food past her molars?
That was incredible.
(He studies the opponent and puts the food in his mouth.)
His fingers came down to my uvula.
(His fingers came down to my uvula.)
I thought I had missed something.
Was that your uvula?
I thought it was meat.
I pulled it because I thought it was meat.
(They now move for the next mission.)
(This mission will chase away the heat.)
What is that?
- What is that? - Will they make us dive?
(What is that?)
(There are tall diving platforms...)
(and frightening flying chairs.)
(The oasis of celebrities in variety shows)
- Aren't those flying chairs? - Those are flying chairs.
My goodness.
The season of flying chairs has begun.
- I haven't used it before. - This is a disaster.
- Haven't you used it before? - No, this will be my first time.
(Fascinated)
I have used it recently.
What?
So Min!
It's a frog.
(It's good to see you, my friend.)
Why is the pool so deep?
It's nice.
(She doesn't pay attention to the flying chairs.)
(She is cheerful.)
Please stand in the center.
- Okay. - I hate this.
- For goodness' sake. - This is fascinating.
(It makes me realize that I joined Running Man.)
This mission is...
Jukebox Go Stop.
What is that?
Listen to the song that is playing on the jukebox.
If you know the title, come out to the front and say it.
If your answer is wrong, wind will blow on your face...
and a chance to answer will be given to the next person.
While the person who got the title right sings the song,
other members will quickly sit on the flying chairs.
Then they will hold a beach ball and play rock, paper, scissors.
The beach ball can be passed down only if they play the same hand.
When the person who was singing...
yells "Stop" and raises the flag,
the person with the ball will fly backwards.
(When the person who was singing yells "Stop",)
(the person with the ball will fly backwards.)
If you sing for a long time, the ball will continue to move.
That's right. You can sing for a long time.
The winning team will get a chance to change a team member.
(The winning team will get a chance to change a team member.)
The first problem is a K-Pop song from the past.
- That's great. - A K-Pop song from the past.
- That's great. - I love K-Pop songs from the past.
I love K-Pop songs from the past.
(We can't win against those middle-aged men.)
The first problem, a K-Pop song from the past.
Music, please.
(The music begins to play.)
This is...
(What is this strange intro?)
Is it by Chakra?
(Moving)
- Do you know this song? - I have the answer.
(He slowly moves as if something is pulling him.)
(You are younger than me.)
(Is Se Chan unexpectedly well-versed in old songs?)
- Tell us the answer. - Between the sky and the earth
(Confident)
-You need to tell us the artist... - The artist?
and the title of the song.
- Was there a rule like that? - I told you earlier.
That's right.
(Jae Seok figures out the answer.)
Was there a rule like that?
Ahn Seong Il?
I have the answer.
Dosi Brothers.
(Confident)
"The Fairy and the Woodcutter".
(Is the answer Dosi Brother's "The Fairy and the Woodcutter"?)
(The answer is "The Fairy and the Woodcutter"...)
(by the former member of Dosi Brothers, Kim Chang Nam.)
Dosi Brothers.
(He didn't get the artist right.)
"The Fairy and the Woodcutter".
- "The Fairy and the Woodcutter". - I have the answer.
- It's right. - I have the answer.
(He gets a gust of wind in Jae Seok's place.)
Dosi Brothers' "The Woodcutter and the Fairy".
(Incorrect)
It's "The Fairy and the Woodcutter".
I have the answer.
The Fairy and the Kids'...
"The Woodcutter, You, and Me".
("The Woodcutter, You, and Me")
What was that?
(The title is too sentimental for a woodcutter.)
Dosi Brothers.
"The Fairy and the Woodcutter".
- And? - "The Fairy and the Woodcutter".
"The Fairy's Woodcutter".
Dosi Brothers.
It's "The Fairy and the Woodcutter".
"The Fairy and the Woodcutter" is correct.
A member of Dosi Brothers...
(The producer gives them a hint.)
- It must be a solo song. - I have the answer.
(It looks like he will get it right.)
Kim Chang Nam and Dosi Brothers.
I have the answer.
Kim Chang Nam's "The Fairy and the Woodcutter".
(Seok Jin's answer is correct.)
- Our team got it right. - Sit down.
Do we need to sit down?
- Sit down. - Do we need to sit down, too?
We need to sit down as well.
(What will become of Pass the Bomb?)
Fools.
I won't get thrown into the pool.
How do we play?
(Dancing)
Please enjoy it.
(They begin to pass the bomb.)
Rock, paper, scissors.
(The ball can be passed down if they play the same hand.)
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Your teammates are at the end.
(He doesn't hear anything.)
Rock, paper, scissors. Rock, paper, scissors.
(They begin to feel nervous.)
Rock, paper, scissors.
You have five seconds left.
(He announces he will yell "Stop" 5 seconds later.)
(They rush their movements in nervousness.)
(When Seok Jin yells "Stop",)
(someone will get plunged into the pool.)
(Who will be the first member?)
Rock, paper, scissors. Rock, paper, scissors.
Five.
- Five. - Rock, paper, scissors.
4, 3.
(The countdown makes Team Black flustered.)
Two.
(The countdown has 2 seconds left to go.)
One.
(Who will be holding the bomb?)
(They tied with 1 second remaining.)
One.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Stop.
(Stop.)
Haha. In 1, 2...
In 1, 2, 3.
It's too intense.
(Shocked and scared)
Haha. In 1, 2, 3.
(The upgraded flying chair of 2017)
(The height, degree, and comfort of the flight are the best.)
It's too intense.
(The first customer is satisfied.)
(This is no joke.)
He flew so high.
He flew very high.
It's not dangerous since the water is deep.
- That was intense. - It will be the end of you.
(The customer's review)
All right.
That was incredible.
I had a lot of thoughts up there.
It took forever to come down.
This problem...
is an OST of the past.
We have an advantage.
That's my specialty. I know a lot of OSTs.
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, and So Min would know a lot too.
You don't need to get the artist this time.
Name which drama or movie it was in.
I don't know the OSTs for movies.
I need to beat the person next to me to pass down the ball.
That's right. You need to beat the person.
Music, please.
(The music for the second problem begins to play.)
- I have the answer. - I have the answer.
(Everyone knows the answer.)
- Se Chan. - He grabbed the microphone.
Get in the line. Se Chan will answer first.
- This is... - Get in the line.
Get in the line.
The answer is "Piano".
- That's it. - It's incorrect.
- It's correct. - It's correct.
- It's correct. - It's "Piano".
The answer is "Piano".
I am sure it's correct.
- It's the correct answer. - The answer is "Piano".
"Piano".
Don't we need to name the artist?
("Piano" is an SBS drama...)
(that had a viewer rating of 40 percent.)
(The drama made stars like Go Soo, Zo In Sung, and Kim Ha Neul.)
Let's try not to receive the penalty.
- Let's do a good job. - We didn't answer the problem.
We can do this.
(Everyone is scared.)
I will enjoy singing. Let's get it on. Okay.
Let's go.
(He is in good cheer.)
(The members in the back play rock, paper, scissors of death.)
- Rock, paper, scissors. - This is great.
I bet he will stop after the first verse.
(Se Chan begins to sing.)
(Absorbed)
He is good.
(Se Chan has no intention of yelling "Stop".)
(They waste time.)
(Hurry up and pass the ball.)
(Taking their time)
(Slow)
(The sadness brings tears to my eyes)
Here I go.
(They were taking time, but their bodies react to "Here I go".)
(Don't call me a coward)
(I love Se Chan.)
(Towards the end of the chorus,)
(they begin to worry.)
(Hurried)
(They are nervous as if it's a real bomb.)
(Please let me win.)
(The bomb is close to exploding.)
He is good.
(It's a fight with time.)
(The sky... Here I go.)
(Se Chan shouts, "Here I go.")
(Jae Seok still has the ball.)
(The moment you look away)
Stop!
(He yells stop.)
(Who has the ball?)
(They both stop.)
(Haha gets selected for two consecutive times.)
It's Haha.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Welcome, customer.)
(This is the standard posture for the flying chair.)
(With eyes open wide,)
(he flaps his feeble arms.)
(This is the standard way to fall in the water.)
That was so close.
- It was so close. - Was it?
- I almost got thrown in. - He yelled stop as you passed it.
That was amazing.
- I won many times. - It's scary.
I defeated Jae Seok many times.
- He kept winning. - If I had won...
one more round.
(He wins once.)
(Twice)
(3 times)
(4 and 5 times)
(Se Chan yells stop after they play 5 rounds.)
- If I had won one more round... - That was close.
Next category is...
old Korean pop songs.
- This is great. - Old Korean pop songs.
- Old Korean pop songs? - Here we go.
Please play the music.
Why are you competing against me?
Deux.
Is it correct?
Isn't it correct?
Come back here.
May I answer it?
- Go ahead. - May I answer it?
Yes.
(Will he answer correctly again after the first measure?)
It's "Two of Us" by Chae Yeon.
(Is he being arrogant or is he correct?)
What's the answer?
(He's incorrect.)
The answer is "I Don't Know" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
Uhm Jung Hwa?
Wait a minute.
- What are you doing? - "Festival" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
The answer is "Betrayal of the Rose" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
- That's wrong. - "I Don't Know" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
- That's wrong. - "Poison" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
The answer is "Betrayal of the Rose" by Uhm Jung Hwa.
It's not a song by Uhm Jung Hwa.
- Let's go again. - We were fooled.
Play music.
I know this song.
(It sounds familiar.)
I know the answer.
"You're So Sexy".
- I know the answer. - It's Korean pop.
It's "Wa" by Lee Jung Hyun.
- That's wrong. - That's not it.
Come back.
- I know the answer. - That's the one.
- It's something else. - Doesn't it go like this?
It's by Chae Jung An.
- I was going to say that. - Chae Jung An's...
What is it?
(People start to wonder.)
It's Chae Jung An's...
Come on, you know the song.
- It's Chae Jung An's... - Didn't it play yesterday?
I know the answer.
It's "Two of Us Alone" by Chae Jung An.
You sounded so cheesy.
Chae Jung An?
Isn't it correct?
Keep listening to the song.
I have no idea.
I thought it was Chae Jung An.
It's by Chae Jung An, but I don't remember the song title.
Gosh.
I know this.
- Gosh. - I know this.
The song goes like this.
You must know it.
It's by Chae Yeon.
- Chae Yeon? - Chae Yeon?
(Isn't that right?)
It's by Chae Yeon.
- That's wrong. - Isn't it by Chae Yeon?
It's by Lee Jung Hyun.
I was attracted by your quivering look
Don't try to avoid me
It's called "Half".
That's correct.
(Jae Seok answers correctly.)
(He finally answers "Half" by Lee Jung Hyun.)
My goodness.
- We said all possible answers. - Goodness.
(Released in her 3rd album, it represents techno music.)
(Though it wasn't her main song, it swept all music charts.)
I almost didn't make it.
Please play the music.
("Half" by Lee Jung Hyun)
(I was attracted by your look)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They're very serious.)
(Singing with his harsh voice, he dances along.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(While everyone else is nervous, he finishes the first verse.)
(If he yells stop, Jong Kook will be selected.)
(Please say stop.)
I'll sing a little more.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Shall I stop here or continue?
(I want to continue, but shall I stop here?)
I'm wondering.
(It's nerve-racking.)
Goodness, what should I do?
(Don't come to me.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(He keeps singing.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Don't insist upon me
I only loved you
(It's coming up soon.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Come on.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(He yells out stop.)
- Stop. - Wait a minute.
- Stop. - Wait.
- Stop. - I'll go after I take a breath.
- Is it So Min? - Yes.
- Did So Min get selected? - In 1, 2, 3.
(Welcome.)
(Is this your first time on the flying chair?)
(She falls forward as she dives.)
So Min, you fell on your face.
What happened?
Why did you fall on your face?
(Why did you fall forward?)
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
- I'm sorry. - I was so nervous.
I can't be on Running Man anymore.
It's okay, So Min.
Mom, take out the deposit on the house.
- No. - If you want to...
buy a house,
you have to work more.
- If you want to buy a house, - Go in the water once more.
you have to fall in the water more.
It's only for today.
Mom, I'm sorry. I'll buy you delicious food instead.
So Min, you have to persevere.
The next category is old Korean pop songs again.
Let's try to win.
(Team White wins if they win one more round.)
(Will Team Black turn the tables?)
Play music.
It's the sound of a boat horn.
I want to sing at least once.
I don't know the song.
- I have no idea. - Me neither.
All techno songs from early 2000s start like this.
What's the answer?
Is it "999"?
("Galaxy Express 999")
- What did you say? - "999".
It's "Genuine" by Koyote.
- That's wrong. - We should listen farther.
- We do. - Play music.
I know this song.
They all start like this.
Right.
(Hesitant)
- What is it? - You lost your chance.
(He seems to recognize it.)
That's right.
I don't remember the song title.
Who knows the answer?
I know.
(Seok Jin knows many old Korean pop songs.)
(If he answers correctly, Team Black will be defeated.)
I know the answer.
It's "Seoul" by Lee Yong.
(Incorrect)
What are you talking about?
Seok Jin.
Will you keep losing our chance?
What you're doing is pointless.
Will you keep saying nonsense?
How could he say Lee Yong?
Continue playing music.
I know this song.
What you want is
It's a song by Chae Jung An.
Are you serious?
You must love her song,
- but it's not her song. - I'm sure it's Chae Jung An.
It wasn't her song last time.
I don't remember the title.
It's by Chae Jung An.
(What was it?)
It's Chae Jung An's...
What is it?
Song titles were short at this time.
- It goes like this. - Right.
Continue the music.
It's definitely by Chae Jung An.
- It's by Chae Jung An. - I can't remember the title.
It goes like this.
- I have no idea. - It goes like this.
How does it go?
What's the title?
All we need to know is the title.
I told you that it's by Chae Jung An.
It really is.
(His body remembers the song.)
That's right.
- The lyrics are correct. - Wait.
- I know the answer. - Even if you do it
(He barges in.)
What's the answer?
"Gratitude" by Chae Jung An.
(How can that be the title of a techno song?)
"Ula Ula Ulaleyo" by Chae Jung An.
That will cause us trouble.
I made a guess.
(Everyone remembers the song.)
(They remember the lyrics.)
I know the answer.
- Is this it? - What is it?
(The song has a special refrain.)
(If song titles from early 2000s were short...)
"Ula" by Chae Jung An.
- Come on. - Isn't it?
You'll hear the title in the second verse.
The second verse starts soon. Play music.
Pupa?
(The second verse starts soon.)
Here it is.
(The song title is included in the lyrics of the 2nd verse.)
(The lyrics will determine the winner.)
(It's time to dance.)
- Dance time - Dance time
(The 2nd verse starts.)
(Love opened my eyes)
I know the answer.
- The answer is... - "Love" by Chae Jung An.
- "Love" by Chae Jung An. - That's not it.
She said love.
Play music.
I know the answer.
What?
- "Farewell" by Chae Jung An. - "Farewell".
That's wrong.
Everyone goes one by one.
- I know the answer. - Take a guess.
- "Regrets" by Chae Jung An. - Step back.
Step back.
Let's step back.
We started here.
You'll hear it right away. Cue the music.
(They have to move fast.)
(Heartless)
I'll answer!
(I'll answer!)
"Heartless" by Chae Jung An.
(Correct)
"Heartless"!
We need to pull ourselves together.
You know this, right?
("Heartless" is Chae Jung An's debut song.)
(The lyrics and performance have been loved for a long time.)
It was "Heartless".
Cue the music.
(Heartless)
(Seok Jin dances to the techno music.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - I hope this will be the last time.
Please end this pain.
It's so painful!
Rock-paper-scissors.
(It's also painful for the staff who has to listen to Seok Jin sing.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
I'll stop as soon as the second verse starts.
(The 2nd verse starts.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They're desperate.)
It's coming soon.
We're almost there.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Who will be penalized this time?)
- Yes! - Let's go.
Stop!
(Ji Hyo)
(Ji Hyo falls into the trap.)
1, 2, 3.
(Ji Hyo enters the water.)
(Her movements look cool.)
(Team White wins by a score of 4 to 0.)
Are you okay?
- Team White wins. - Yes!
The songs were so old.
You should have played new songs.
The result is out.
Team White can spin the roulette wheel twice.
We can choose not to change the members too, right?
- Yes. - You have a Chance Card.
You have a Chance Card.
You're going to spin the wheel until I'm gone, right?
Guys.
Did you realize it now?
- I mean... - Choose Stay.
I mean...
You might be sent too. You should know that.
You should use your chance.
Let's spin the wheel.
- Let's go! - Come on.
Hey, I have a 25-percent share.
We'll spin the wheel first.
Let's see.
- Kim... - Kim, Ji...
I'll be sent with a 50-percent chance.
If So Min or I get chosen,
it'll be amazing.
It'll be fantastic.
(The roulette wheel is spinning.)
- Is it spinning? - Yes.
It's to decide who will come here, right?
Please.
(It's the last chance to change the team members.)
(Who will move to Team White?)
- Kwang Soo. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo moves to Team White.)
It's Kwang Soo.
(They now just have to send Seok Jin away.)
If Seok Jin is sent away, it'll be perfect.
That's the plan.
We'll spin the wheel.
It'll be amazing if Seok Jin gets chosen.
Why am I here?
If Seok Jin gets chosen, the game will be over.
(If Seok Jin gets chosen, Team Black will have 3 Dud Men.)
- The game will be over. - Please.
It'll be over.
(Who will be sent to Team Black from Team White?)
I mean...
It'll be over.
(Jae Seok gets chosen.)
Jae Seok!
- You go. - Let's do it one more time.
- We'll use the Chance Card. - Are you using it?
We have to use it now.
- It'll become useless later. - We have to use it now.
- We have to use it now. - I have a 25-percent share.
Se Chan and I have 50-percent share combined.
We have a 50-percent share.
- We'll use the card. - I'm in too.
- We'll use it. - I have a 25-percent share too.
- Survive, Jae Seok. - Let's do it.
- The next slot is Seok Jin. - I hope Jae Seok will be chosen.
(If Seok Jin gets chosen, Team White will have no Dud Man.)
- Please. - I hope Jae Seok will be chosen.
Please.
- Survive, Jae Seok. - Let's do it.
(They won another chance by using the Chance Card.)
(If Seok Jin gets chosen, Team White will have no Dud Man.)
(What will happen to the two teams?)
Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin is sent away.)
- Be quiet. - Was Seok Jin chosen?
(The non-Dud Men achieved independence.)
(Fussing)
It's Seok Jin.
(I tried so hard to win.)
It's perfect.
There's another round, right?
I can't believe this.
- There's another round, right? - Yes.
My goodness.
- It's perfect. - It's perfect.
I can't believe this.
- How can this happen? - It's perfect.
- It's perfect. - What about me?
What am I doing here?
- Poor Ji Hyo. - What about me?
- Save me. - Poor Ji Hyo.
Change your clothes and move to the next place.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Will miracles continue to happen to Team White?)
Are we playing a name-tag game?
We play name-tag games whenever we're here.
We always play it here.
Our team has an advantage.
We look so weak.
(All three Dud Men are on Team Black.)
Before I introduce the final mission,
Team Black will put on red caps.
(Team Black will wear red caps.)
- Team White will put on blue caps. - Thank you.
What are we going to do?
- Are we doing something with them? - What are these?
(Why are we putting on caps?)
In the final mission,
you can reverse the situation.
It's Life-changing Name Tag Elimination.
Name Tag Elimination?
(Life-Changing Name Tag Elimination)
(Life-Changing Name Tag Elimination?)
Is it Name Tag Elimination?
With these members?
(Team Black is at a disadvantage.)
The game will last 30 minutes.
If you rip someone's name tag off, you'll switch places.
(If you rip someone's name tag off, you'll switch places.)
The team with fewer Dud Men at the end of the game...
will win.
- Then... - Hold on.
We'll have to run away from them.
(Team White has to run away from Team Black.)
(Team Black will try to rip off Team White's name tags.)
(The game will change their lives.)
Member changes will be announced in real time.
Please keep an eye on the situation.
(Team Blue versus Team Red)
(This final race will...)
(determine who will be sent to the Place for 1 Percent.)
Then we'll have to wait until the last minute.
(Then we'll have to wait until the last minute.)
That sounds so easy.
He's the king of games.
Can you do that if you want to?
He can do it.
If I want to rip a name tag off, I can do it.
I can start when there is five minutes left.
(He'll start when there is 5 minutes left.)
Okay.
- He could do that. - Okay?
I'll just look around.
I'm jealous.
Please move to your starting points.
Let the Life-changing Name Tag Elimination begin.
- Gosh. - Let's go.
We'll have to hold out.
- Gosh. - Let's not waste our energy.
We don't know what will happen.
What will happen?
- You have to think. - Let's say...
they get the name tags of two of us.
The team with two Dud Men...
- will lose, right? - Yes.
If we lose two, it'll be over.
We can't rip off their name tags yet.
If we do that, we have to go to that team.
(Team Blue has to run away from the other team for now.)
We have to think carefully.
One of us has to...
- go to that team. - For us to have a chance.
One of us will survive.
- Only one of us will survive. - That's right.
Or we'll all lose.
(They aim to reverse the situation.)
We can do this. Let's meet here.
- 1, 2, 3. - Let's do this.
- Let's meet here. - Okay.
We sound so discouraged.
(How will this race end?)
It's because I have a lot on my mind.
See you later.
(How will this race end?)
(They're at their starting points.)
In the beginning,
should I run away from them?
(Keeping your name tag doesn't guarantee anything.)
(It's important to watch the situation.)
I'll just have to try.
If you think about it,
it might not be a bad idea to do nothing.
They'll do their best to get our name tags.
Anyway...
(Thinking)
If I think only about myself,
I should be the only Dud Man on the team.
It's not a competition between teams.
It's not.
- It's between individuals. - It's me against the others.
It's between individuals.
Who is talking to me?
(It's me.)
- I'm alone here. - Your heart is talking to you.
Is it my heart?
It's your heart. It's a competition between individuals.
Okay.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
I won't go after you. I don't want to.
- I don't want to compete with you. - Haha.
Just give Se Chan to me.
I'll switch with Se Chan.
Okay? Give Se Chan to me.
- Listen to me. - Hold him.
Haha.
Otherwise, I'll bring my members and attack you.
- Fine. - Just give me Se Chan.
- Fine. - I...
- never lie on the first deal. - Okay.
I'll hold out for the next 25 minutes.
All right.
I look forward to your cooperation.
We don't know how things will turn out.
This is so complicated.
This is driving me crazy.
I guess you really don't want to go.
No.
I really don't want to go, Jae Seok.
- Earlier... - I have a heavy heart.
Go.
I'll go if I have to.
He kept on talking about it.
(I'm going to survive on my own.)
Jong Kook.
- Can you rip off my name tag? - Yours?
- You can come and rip off mine. - Jong Kook.
So Min.
Will you let me?
You can try.
(Come get it if you're feeling confident.)
What should I do?
(It might not be a good idea to rip off people's name tags.)
Let's get the race started.
10.
(There are only 30 minutes.)
Nine.
Let's hold out.
(As soon as your name tag comes off, your team changes.)
This requires a lot of thinking.
- Eight. - This is war.
- Seven. - I am afraid of heights.
(The team with more Dud Men will be penalized.)
My goodness.
Six.
Gosh, I don't want to go.
- Five. - I'm scared.
- Four. - It's starting.
Three.
Two.
Race starts now.
I have to go meet people.
(The final race starts.)
(Seok Jin, Haha, and So Min are Dud Men.)
Hold on.
(Jae Seok is on the run.)
I have to run away for now.
There he is.
(Seok Jin finds Jae Seok.)
He's coming. It's Seok Jin.
I never thought I'd be running away from Seok Jin.
I need to run away from him.
(He gets chased by the weakest member.)
Hey, Jae Seok.
(He must stay in Team Blue right now.)
- What? - Come here.
- I can't get your name tag anyway. - What?
You know that.
So Seok Jin,
let's think about this.
- Then... - All right.
Can you help me get Kwang Soo's name tag?
There's no point in doing that right now.
- You know what I mean? - You can help me get Kwang Soo.
If Kwang Soo leaves my team,
we'll get another Dud Man.
You won't.
They won't go.
They won't go unless they're stupid.
They'll try to get me.
Think about it.
(It's all so complicated,)
(so let's rip off the name tag first.)
(Give me your name tag.)
Wait.
(As soon as your name tag comes off, you switch teams.)
- Wait. - I'm sorry.
I don't even know now.
I don't want the penalty.
(Jae Seok keeps on defending himself.)
I can't go, Jae Seok.
Please.
Don't do this.
- Help me get Kwang Soo's name tag. - Okay.
(He gives up very fast.)
(Or not?)
(Give me your name tag.)
- I'll help you get Kwang Soo. - Will you?
(That was a lie.)
That little...
(Jae Seok gets out of the situation by running away.)
(It's so easy to fool Seok Jin.)
I have to go this way anyway.
(He tries to keep his pride.)
(You got lucky, Jae Seok.)
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is here.)
I have no choice but to run away.
Let's hold out.
I must hold out.
Kwang Soo.
Jong Kook.
Come here.
It's 30 minutes.
Here comes So Min.
(So Min comes by.)
(They run away from Team Red.)
What is she thinking?
Why are you running away?
You startled me.
(Ji Hyo was waiting on the 2nd floor.)
(So Min lures them,)
(and Ji Hyo will attack.)
(Ji Hyo and So Min are on their way.)
Jong Kook.
I'm sorry.
(Ji Hyo is after Jong Kook.)
I'm sorry. Run, Jong Kook.
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
(So Min is after Kwang Soo.)
Catch him.
(Haha is in the front.)
(So Min is in the back.)
(Can you give me your name tag, Kwang Soo?)
What are you doing? Run.
Run.
Catch him.
(Dashing)
(Haha is after Kwang Soo now. So Min changes her target.)
Guys. Why are you doing this to me?
- Let's do this together, Kwang Soo. - Do what together?
- Let's catch Se Chan. - Do what together?
What are you saying?
Let's catch Se Chan.
- We have to get Jong Kook. - What?
- We have to get him. - We can't.
- Wait. - Let go first.
- Let's talk. - What are you planning to do?
- Let's talk. - Why me?
- We won't do anything. - Go somewhere else first.
Go somewhere else. Why are you doing this to me?
- Fine. We'll go somewhere else. - Good. Come back.
Let go.
(Let's talk first, Jong Kook.)
- My hair. - Here.
- Hey, why are you doing this? - Let's talk.
What are you thinking? Tell me what you're thinking.
Help us get one person. Please save So Min and me.
- Please, Jong Kook. - Who do you want?
If either of us go to your room...
What if we get a Dud Man on our team then?
You have to stop that from happening.
(She's so square.)
- What? - You have to stop it.
So we can't...
let people know that we're allies.
Stay far away and once you catch your target,
I'll go...
and pretend like I'm helping. But I'll catch them for you.
- Okay. Really? - Yes.
- You have to help us. - Okay.
- Don't touch me then. - Okay.
As soon as you touch me,
I'll destroy you.
- Gosh. - He's really strong.
Hey, did you just realise that?
- Hey. - The lights won't go out.
- Hurry up. - What were you planning on doing?
My goodness.
I have no choice.
- We just got started. - I know.
I have no choice, Kwang Soo.
You should rip mine off.
You can rip my name tag off.
What are you talking about?
Rip it off.
Here it is. Rip it right off.
- Please. - Kwang Soo.
You can rip mine off.
I have to survive.
Rip it off. Go ahead.
Good job.
Here it is.
- I have to survive. - Rip it off.
- Try harder. - No.
Just hold onto it. I'll do the rest.
- Please. - Save me.
Please, Kwang Soo.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
(Ripping)
(Haha and Kwang Soo switch teams.)
I'm really sorry, Kwang Soo.
- I'm sorry. - Okay. Let's see how this ends.
Fine.
(Kwang Soo is on Team Red, and Haha is on Team Blue.)
Haha from Team Red and Kwang Soo from Team Blue...
have switched teams.
(Haha is on Team Blue now?)
Haha switched?
From the three of us...
One has to switch teams to make it a tight race.
Only one person will survive.
- 1 out of 3 will survive. - That's right.
Or we'll all die.
(As of right now, only Haha will be the only Dud Man to survive.)
(I'm saved.)
He ripped it off.
We just have to rip off Haha's now.
Let's join hands.
(How long can he be in Team Blue for?)
Kwang Soo is behind you.
(Kwang Soo is behind me?)
He's after me already.
(I won't leave you alone.)
(If Kwang Soo gets me, I'll end up on the team full of Dud Men.)
That was close.
(He sprints away.)
(I just need one guy in a blue cap.)
He's coming.
(I got one.)
(Ripping)
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan switch teams.)
Why is it a dead-end here?
This is where I got mine ripped off too.
(Kwang Soo is safe for now.)
I'll get going.
Se Chan from Team Blue...
got his name tag ripped off by Kwang Soo from Team Red.
Okay.
(Team Blue doesn't have more Dud Men, so it's still safe.)
Hello.
Excuse me. Come in.
(Let's hide in the waiting room.)
I'm not here. Please help me.
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry.
I'm good. Sit down.
It's okay.
I can't go.
(He hopes the teams don't change.)
I did everything I can. I'm going to stay here for 25 minutes.
So Min from Team Red...
ripped off the name tag of Team Blue's Jong Kook.
- Their teams have switched. - She's coming to Team Blue then.
My gosh. Why would she do that? Is she stupid?
(Team Blue is tainted now.)
(They must flee to Team Red now.)
- So Min is on this team? - Yes.
Goodness.
My gosh.
(Team Blue has more Dud Men now.)
I have to switch over.
I have to switch.
(3 minutes ago in a confrontational situation)
Let's get Jong Kook. Come here.
- What are you going to do? - No, no.
- Hey. - Think first.
There's no point in ripping his name tag off.
- We should switch caps. - Really?
Hey.
(We need a Dud Man to go over to Team Blue.)
- Hey. - What do we do with the caps?
Just let So Min rip his name tag off.
- What do we do with the caps? - Let her do it.
(Jong Kook, send So Min to your team.)
(It doesn't matter for Jong Kook if he gets switched.)
(Would Jong Kook and So Min switch according to Seok Jin's plan?)
Never mind.
Come here.
(They get started.)
Rip it off.
- So Min, rip it off. - Rip it off.
(Would this lame plan work?)
(Ripping)
(So Min rips Jong Kook's name tag off.)
(Seok Jin's plan worked.)
- All right. - I'm sorry.
- It's okay. - Jong Kook.
- You know, right? - Of course.
He's so smart. I just had to look at him.
(What? What happened?)
I'll stay here. I'll hide.
- Okay. We're one. - I'll stay here.
- We have to run. - Their teams have...
switched.
He's so good.
- We're fine. - This is good.
Yes.
What?
What happened? Seok Jin.
That was so mean of you.
What?
- You tricked me. - That's how the world works.
- That's how it works. - Seok Jin.
- How can you do this to me? - What? What are you going to do?
I won't do anything. Why did you lie to me?
I didn't.
(He can hear Kwang Soo gasping...)
(and coming after him.)
(Kwang Soo's target is Seok Jin.)
Why are you after me? You shouldn't rip mine off.
(Please)
(It's time to switch over to Team Red.)
Why would you rip mine off? It doesn't matter.
Why would you rip mine off?
I don't even know.
I don't know.
Why would you rip mine off?
I'm leaving.
Can you help me?
Kwang Soo from Team Blue...
ripped off the name tag of Team Red's Seok Jin.
Their teams have switched.
This is the worst place to be.
(This is the worst place to be.)
My gosh. It's the opposite now.
- Jong Kook. - Do we have no Dud Man at all?
- We don't. - Rip it off. There's Kwang Soo.
(They can't just sit and watch now.)
(Seok Jin's target is Kwang Soo.)
Hey.
(They quarrel.)
So Min, get it.
No, So Min.
(This is for you.)
(Ripping)
(Kwang Soo is back to Team Blue after 1 minute.)
Run.
What's going on? This is confusing.
(So Min and Kwang Soo switch.)
So...
(He's coming.)
(Somebody is coming.)
Wait. He's too fast.
Let's talk.
Hey.
Let's talk. Hold on.
Hold on.
Let's talk, Kwang Soo.
Sit down. Let's talk.
Kwang Soo, why are you trying to get me?
Think about it. What if you rip off mine,
and then I rip Haha's name tag off?
Then I'll rip yours off again.
You have to be smart.
(Kwang Soo doesn't budge.)
- Kwang Soo, become stupid again. - What?
(What?)
(All of a sudden?)
What are you talking about?
- Do you think I'm dumb? - Yes.
(Ripping)
(Se Chan becomes Kwang Soo's victim.)
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan switch.)
I'm sorry.
I'll remember this.
(He has a chance if he holds out for a little bit longer.)
Wait. What color are you?
Wait. That's not it.
Hold on.
Hold on. Jae Seok, listen to me.
Be quiet.
(It's survival of the fittest. Kwang Soo is the weak one here.)
Kwang Soo.
There are 10 minutes left.
(10 minutes until the race ends)
- Where's Ji Hyo? - These two have reasons to get you.
I'm sorry.
(Here are the blue guys.)
Do it.
- Kwang Soo. - Don't.
(It looks like Team Blue is getting attacked.)
Right now...
Rip it off.
You like ripping them off. Go ahead.
Rip it off. It's your specialty.
You rip these off more often than you eat chicken breasts. Do it.
Rip it off. Do it!
- Come on. - She's so strong.
Wait.
(He rips it off and puts it back on.)
(Turning)
(Was that not good enough?)
What are you doing?
- There are 10 minutes left. - There's still time.
- Wait five more minutes. - I'm going to rip it off and hide.
- Come on. - Mine got ripped eight times today.
Let's rest now and do it later.
Please do it for us.
(Goodness)
(The tiger is on top of the food chain.)
No, Jong Kook.
- I won't rip yours off. - Do it later.
I wasn't even thinking of getting you.
Do it later.
What did I say? Let's do it later.
Jong Kook.
I'll go to him. I'll ask him to protect me.
I'll ask him.
There she is.
(I have to stay here to survive.)
(Seok Jin's only target is So Min.)
There she is. Catch her.
- Come here, So Min. - Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - I have something to say.
You.
(She lies down.)
I have nothing to say.
- Seok Jin. - This is awkward.
I'll give it to you if you win in rock, paper, scissors.
(She makes a proposal.)
If you lose, let me go.
I can't let you go.
Let me go.
You have to win three times in a row then.
How am I supposed to do that?
(What's that about?)
That's what you did to Kwang Soo.
I'm doing what you did.
- He had to win three times. - Jae Seok on Team Red...
(There's an announcement.)
- Jae Seok on Team Red... - What?
ripped off Haha's name tag from Team Blue. Their teams have switched.
(Team Red has 2 Dud Men now.)
(Team Red is tainted again. They must switch over to Team Blue.)
What does that mean?
(The table has been turned.)
(Ripping)
(Kwang Soo gets his taken off instantly.)
Come here.
Run!
(You'll die once you get caught.)
What's going on? Come on.
Why are you doing this?
Hey, why is she doing this? Don't do this to me.
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo!
(She snatched his name tag...)
(and ripped it off.)
- What did it say? - Haha...
(It's reversed now.)
What happened?
(Oh, right. That's what happened.)
What just happened?
- I should have switched with him. - What now?
What happened?
(Dud Man Haha is on Team Red now, so Team Blue is the safe zone.)
I should have switched with him. That was close.
(Blue Dud Man runs away,)
(and Red Dud Man chases him.)
I'm tired.
(Who will be the one Dud Man that will remain in the safe zone?)
- So Min is coming. - What?
Come. She saw us.
(It's best to avoid Team Red.)
I'm tired.
Five minutes remaining.
(Let me hide here.)
Right now,
I turned on my phone camera. I lost my cameraman.
I was running away and lost him.
I was being chased by So Min.
I'm hiding right now. There are only three minutes left.
Please cheer me on.
(Will Seok Jin be safe for the remaining time?)
(Ready or not, here I come.)
(So Min approaches him.)
(Please go. His mouth is getting dry.)
(She gets near him.)
He went out that way.
(She fails to spot him.)
He went out this way.
You have five minutes remaining.
Who's on our team?
- It's going to change near the end. - You have Seok Jin.
Seok Jin will get his ripped off.
It's likely So Min will be the one to do that.
Let's go to her.
Let's sit and watch first.
- Goodness. - So Min...
I think there will be chaos when we have two minutes left.
(It's almost the end of the race.)
Right now,
it's Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Seok Jin, and me, right?
(Is this the right time?)
What's wrong with you guys? You have to look at the big picture.
(He was talking about a "big picture" all this time.)
Kwang Soo, Se Chan, Haha, and So Min.
(He checks who are on the other team.)
They're all vicious.
(What is Jae Seok's big picture?)
(A month and a half ago in Japan)
(Dangerous Tourist Attractions Project ended that day.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo were exempt from any penalty.)
(With the start of a new project,)
(Jae Seok's big picture started.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo)
(I'll send those two.)
(In order to send Jong Kook and Ji Hyo abroad,)
(one of Team Red's Dud Men has to go over to Team Blue.)
You have one minute before the race is over.
Goodness.
(He only has one minute left. What will be his decision?)
(Hello, So Min.)
(What's going on now?)
(He chases after her.)
(To achieve his big goal,)
You must see the bigger picture.
(a small sacrifice is necessary.)
Come on, Jae Seok.
You have 10 seconds.
- Hurry up. - 10.
Seok Jin isn't here.
- Look for Ji Hyo. - I must find Ji Hyo.
(Team Blue must survive for 10 seconds.)
(Team Red tries to turn the tables.)
(Everything depends on the last 10 seconds.)
- Hurry. - Goodness.
- One. - The race is over.
Time is up.
(Life-changing race is over.)
The race is over.
(If the team members stayed the same...)
(The fate of two teams depend on So Min and Jae Seok.)
(If he takes off So Min's name tag, Team Blue will be punished.)
(Did Jae Seok rip off So Min's name tag?)
- The race is over. - Where's So Min?
Where were you hiding?
- I was in the makeup room. - Were you hiding?
I couldn't find you.
Where were you?
(What's the color of So Min's cap?)
(It's red.)
(A few seconds before the time is up)
(Jae Seok chases after her to change their caps.)
I must catch her.
The race is over.
(The race finished before he could switch the caps.)
(The only Dud Man on Team Blue succeeds.)
It's me. I'm the hero today.
Goodness.
(Haha, So Min, and Seok Jin are Dud Men.)
The race was exactly for 30 minutes.
- I thought so. - As you can see,
there are two Dud Men on Team Red.
The winning team is Team Blue.
(Team Blue wins.)
- I knew it. - Seriously.
These two members are impressive.
They're always exempted from being punished.
I wanted to go.
They're good after all.
I really wanted to go.
It's not over yet.
It's not?
(It's not over yet?)
We have two Dud Men.
(There are two Dud Men on Team Red.)
You'll be sent to two different places of our choice.
(Haha and So Min will choose where they go.)
("People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent")
It's called Catacombs of Paris.
(Catacombs of Paris, France)
(Giant Canyon Swing, United States)
(Copper Canyon Ziprider, Mexico)
(Manual Wooden Cable Car, Indonesia)
(Hammocking, Java, Indonesia)
(Crater of Diamonds State Park, United States)
(Where will they go out of these 6 places?)
Haha.
- I'll spin it. - Please go first.
(Haha is very nervous.)
Where do you want to go?
I want to go here.
Diamonds State Park?
I think this is the worst.
(The worst is Copper Canyon.)
This is the worst.
(The best and the worst are next to each other.)
Let's go for the diamond.
(He spins for Crater of Diamonds State Park.)
(Where will...)
(the pointer stop after Haha spins it?)
Please.
(Please help me.)
(He has 1 out of 6 chance to get Diamonds State Park.)
It's Crater of Diamonds State Park.
(It's Crater of Diamonds State Park.)
(It keeps moving.)
It's Giant Canyon Swing.
(He's selected for Giant Canyon Swing.)
What's that?
(It's the legendary swing.)
(This is Giant Canyon Swing.)
Haha can't even ride the Vikings.
Giant Canyon Swing?
I was hoping he wouldn't get it.
- I don't know anymore. - I think...
- I don't know either. - he should do what he wants.
I bet I'll get something dangerous.
- Give it a try. - Go ahead.
(Spinning)
Where do you want to go?
I want to go to Diamonds Park.
Where do you not want to go?
I don't want anything scary.
(So Min wants to go to Crater of Diamonds State Park.)
(Will her wish come true?)
Manual Wooden Cable Car?
(Laughing)
It's manual.
Manual Wooden Cable Car?
(She gets selected for Manual Wooden Cable Car.)
It's Manual Wooden Cable Car.
I think this is the end.
I'm leaving Running Man today.
Even if you leave, you must go there first.
I can't go there. How can I?
(You must fight against the current.)
(Manual Wooden Cable Car, Indonesia.)
It's time to choose a partner.
Get ready.
(They will go with the Dud Man whom they select.)
You'll be fine.
I picked it first.
I want this one.
I want it too.
- Let me have it. - Here they go again.
They're going to make a fuss again.
Shall I just do it?
- I don't know. - Never mind.
No, I choose that one.
I already picked it.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors. Okay.
(It's difficult to let go, but they finish picking their partners.)
Now,
show us the names in the count of three.
One.
Two.
(Which partner did they pick?)
Three.
(Their partners are revealed.)
(Kwang Soo picks So Min.)
It'll be noisy when we go together.
(Kwang Soo and So Min are sent to Wooden Cable Car.)
(Haha and Se Chan are sent to Giant Canyon Swing.)
There will be romance that nobody cares about.
We'll see it again.
Nobody will care.
Those who will be punished on...
People's Recommendation Project...
are Haha, Se Chan, So Min, and Kwang Soo.
We need more than one month to request visas for our shoot.
We'll leave as soon as we're ready.
Are we going with the viewer who recommended the place?
We'll send the viewers gifts.
- They won't go with you. - Why?
They should go with them.
Shouldn't we go with them?
If they're not coming, tell us their IDs.
- Please. - Give us their IP address.
Give us their IP address.
(Running Man is always on the viewers' side.)
(7th anniversary of Running Man)
(Special people are coming.)
(Their family is here.)
(What are his drinking habits?)
(He becomes a mess.)
(They're more vicious than Running Man members.)
(He's not good at anything.)
(They're funnier than them.)
(Cho Sae Ho)
(Kim Soo Yong)
(Son Na Eun)
(Tae Hang Ho)
(Real family members are coming.)
(Compared to Running Man,)
(their family members run faster.)
(Running Man)
(Running Man and their family)
(Their infinite charms can't be seen anywhere else.)
(I'm not sure why I'm here.)
(Family is Here)