Previously on Running Man...
(Last week, the Running Man
members won the resting place.)
(However, )
(it's not over.)
You have to bring all the things
you wrote in the wish list.
(The mission is to decorate
the resting place.)
(There is only one rule.)
(Self-sufficiency)
(The members call their friends...)
(without mercy.)
(There are endless donations from
top stars we can only dream of.)
Is In Sung here?
(The strange, self-sufficient mission...)
(is unpredictable.)
This is unbelievable.
(And the secret behind the roulette
that decides their destiny)
(The strange, self-sufficient mission
is breathtakingly exciting.)
(Running Man starts now.)
Come in.
- This is our resting place.
- It's a real resting place.
- This is our home. For all of us.
- Now that the furniture is gone...
(They moved in last week.)
- It looks smaller unlike before.
- It has heating too.
Welcome to Running Man's new resting place.
- Yes.
- No, wait.
We should be the ones to
welcome you to our house.
- We can kick you out. It's ours.
- It's our home.
On the empty floor plan of this house,
write down your wish list...
including things you want
and things you need.
(Write down your wish list as you wish.)
- Claw crane.
- Gosh.
- Machines too?
- Like the ones in arcades.
- Whatever we want?
- I want claw cranes too.
I used to want them when I was young.
(Today's mission is to fill
in the empty floor plan.)
- Really?
- I see.
First, we need a television
in the living room.
- Yes.
- We need to monitor the show.
- We need a television.
- Yes, right there.
- TV.
- Next to the other one.
- How about two claw cranes here?
- We don't need them.
- Why do you need them?
- It's fun.
- Claw cranes come here.
- Claw cranes are supposed to be...
- connected to the manufacturer.
- No, we can buy one separately.
- Really?
- It's in Yeongdeungpo.
Sunbed.
- Okay.
- Is it for tanning?
This one is probably Kwang
Soo with a long waist.
- Kwang Soo!
- No, it's not me.
- It looks like your waist.
- But it has short legs.
It's not me.
- How would you know?
- A bed in the bedroom.
- We should get 2 mattresses.
- Okay, 2 mattresses.
- Let's make this a playroom.
- With disco balls.
- Disco balls?
- Mirror balls.
- I like disco balls.
- Disco balls.
- We also need mattresses.
- Cover the floor with the mattress.
- Put them on the floor.
All right. We can sleep anywhere
if the mattress covers the floor.
- I like it.
- And a basketball stand.
- I like it too.
- Let's hang it from the ceiling.
- Let's put a dart board here.
- I like it.
- I like it too.
- Next to the basketball stand?
- All right.
- Next to the basketball stand.
Maybe we could put chairs and
barbecue grills instead of sunbeds.
We could have parasols, too.
- Let's get one.
- It's better.
- A parasol and chairs.
- All right.
- We could sit there to talk.
- That's enough.
- Chair.
- A rug.
- We need a sofa here.
- A zebra-patterned rug.
- All right.
- You should do everything.
- Haha.
- I learned the tricks.
Don't we need a bidet?
- Are we really getting claw cranes?
- I need a bidet.
- We need a bidet.
- Don't put a bidet here.
- Why?
- They put cameras in here.
- Come on.
I don't care about having cameras,
but they need to be blurred.
- Let's put a model figure here.
- Don't.
- Don't. That's what you want.
- Here?
Why do you erase it? Please.
Can't you just stand there?
Why?
I need to shoot Running Man.
He should be in the Avatar costume.
You should stand there.
(Avatar figure, 190cm, for free)
It takes three hours for me
to get dressed as an Avatar.
- You could stay there every day.
- Can I put a full-length mirror?
You can.
I need to see myself when I shower.
- Why would you take a shower?
- It needs to be over 190cm.
It's a waste of money.
- Put a small one.
- Then we need hair dryers, too.
- See? We need hair dryers, too.
- Hair dryers.
- We also need shampoo and rinse.
- We need towels.
- And washing machine for towels.
(Everyone criticizes intensely.)
- How much is the mirror?
- Haha.
- Take it out.
- The two wishes I made were erased.
- Stop it.
- We have a mirror.
- Kwang Soo.
- Why would we need a bigger mirror?
Who wrote down zebra-patterned rug?
It was me. Wait.
- Who wrote that down?
- You can't get away with this.
- This is unnecessary.
- Why?
- Why would you need the design?
- Then what have I done today?
Get out. Get out.
- This is my house.
- Get out.
My house contract is over soon.
- Are you finished?
- Yes.
Now, you have to bring...
the items you wrote down.
(Where can we get...)
(all of these?)
- Bring them?
- Give us 20,000 dollars.
- Without money?
(How do we get them without any money?)
Where would I get a bidet?
Do we need the sunbed?
- No.
(They wrote down so much without thinking.)
- Good thing we erased the zebra.
- It is. I wasn't thinking straight.
Today's mission is...
Decorate Your Place.
If you fail to bring everything,
- there will be an annoying penalty.
- Annoying penalty?
- What would it be?
- We probably need to come here.
We will decide the number of
people getting the penalty...
according to the number
of things you missed out.
To save more people, - Yes.
Bring as much as you can.
There is a chance card...
for each product you bring.
It's important you get them fast.
We can't divide the teams
according to the area...
because we don't know
where we could get them.
- It will be hard to get a sofa.
- Sofa.
I could ask my dad.
- All right.
- I could call him.
He likes to be on television too.
He doesn't like to be on television.
He smiles when the camera focuses on him.
- He is very smiley.
- Your dad...
You could get a sofa, a rug,
and a table from the company.
- In the Running Man office...
- That's right.
- They have these things.
- They do.
- I will get the mattress.
- All right.
- And the parasol.
I can get the parasol
from my stylist's office.
- Okay then.
- Then our first destination...
- will be the Running Man office.
- It's not clean.
- We'll bring what we can.
- Okay.
- Okay. We'll go now.
- I think we could find a rug.
- Let's go.
(Decorate Your Place starts now.)
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin heads to SBS.)
We need to get a lot of things.
Is it okay to take things from SBS?
- It won't matter, right?
- Where do you shoot Running Man?
- SBS.
- Where does the show broadcast?
- That's why we're going to SBS.
- It's very persuasive.
- It's okay.
We're here. Okay.
Let's go.
(They look like sons coming
home to take Mom's food.)
- They might have everything.
- They might.
- It's always SBS.
- Yes, it's SBS.
- It's here.
- Where?
- Gigantic claw crane.
- You're right.
- Can't we take it home?
(They find a gigantic one.)
It looks fun.
Hey,
where are you going?
(He finds an actor.)
Hello.
(It's Son Hyun Joo who appeared
in Running Man twice.)
- Where are you going?
- I had a radio broadcast.
A radio?
When will you come out
on Running Man again?
Let's run now.
(He's ready to go.)
(Hyun Joo is always full of drive.)
- Goodbye.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Bye.
- We could have asked for something.
- I know.
Can't we take the
television from the lobby?
- You can't.
- How many are they?
There are five televisions here.
This is a treasure chest.
Don't tell us off for taking everything.
We might get everything from here.
(They are emptying the
Running Man office first.)
Can you open the door
with the entrance card?
- Where is the Running Man team?
- It's here.
- Look at this.
- It's a treasure chest.
- It's unbelievable.
It looks like a stationery store.
- It was a great choice coming here.
- I know.
You are unbelievable. I didn't know.
Here are the Running Balls.
(It's a paradise.)
There is a stapler and a stamp.
- They have everything.
- It's a stationery store.
- What is this?
- It's almost like...
"Daiso".
You didn't know, right?
I didn't know this existed. Look at this.
- This is...
- Look at the thing outside the box.
I knew about the other things,
but why would they need fertilizers?
(Fertilizers are necessary for games!)
This is too much.
- Fertilizers?
- Why would they have that?
- This is unbelievable.
- It is.
I thought I saw a
basketball stand somewhere.
(Where is the basketball
stand and the dart board?)
Wait, I think they would have a dart board.
They don't have them.
The things we need aren't here.
(They have fertilizers,
but not game utilities.)
(It's here somewhere.)
- Where is the basketball stand?
- Hey.
- What?
- Isn't this a basketball stand?
(Seok Jin has a good feeling about this.)
- Gosh.
- It is, right?
Wait.
We got a basketball stand.
(It looks somewhat strange.)
We have a basketball stand.
(It's really small, but it
is a basketball stand!)
- Basketball stand.
- We got it.
- Let's tell the others.
- We should.
You found a basketball stand.
- You can spin the roulette.
- What is this?
(What is this roulette for?)
With the roulette, you can earn from
one dollar to an infinite check.
We will give you the amount
selected by this roulette.
- They'll even give us 100 dollars.
- This is amazing.
- This is what we need.
- This is incredible.
It says "100 dollars" and "1 dollar".
- What is this "infinite check"?
- When you get an infinite check,
we will give you an item
you want free of charge.
- Yes!
- This is splendid!
Great job. This is a way
to do your job right.
To spin this... Wait. Are
you going to spin this?
- Let me practice once.
- Why are you spinning this?
- Let me try this.
- Both of us should try once.
(Jae Seok tests out the roulette
to evaluate his condition.)
(He wins a dollar which is
the lowest amount of money.)
How could you get a dollar?
He has to be the unluckiest guy.
He got a dollar.
- My hands are doomed.
- You should stay out of this.
I'm relieved this was a practice round.
- You're practicing too, right?
- Yes.
(Seok Jin also tests out the roulette.)
I will get a better amount than you.
(He's not so lucky either. He wins
a dollar just like Jae Seok.)
It's a dollar.
(They are the unluckiest.)
Hey, then...
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- The loser will spin it.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok gets to spin it.)
Let go of my hand.
(He's nervous to let Jae Seok spin.)
You can't get a dollar.
You have to win more than a dollar.
I'd rather have a passer-by
spin this for us.
Let's put this on here and spin.
Challenge!
Watch me. I'll win an infinite check.
Winning 100 dollars will be enough.
(A saying goes, if one's desperate,
things will go one's way.)
(Will Jae Seok be able
to pull off a miracle?)
(There's no such miracle.
He wins a dollar.)
A dollar!
(No way.)
(He's consistent.)
- How can you win only a dollar?
- Here is your dollar.
(His unlucky hands go at it again!)
I can't believe this.
Your hands are so unlucky.
- I can't believe you won a dollar.
- My goodness.
(Meanwhile, where are other members?)
(If they continue on this road,
they'll arrive at Itaewon.)
If we pass by Itaewon, we
can meet Hong Suk Chun!
Hong Suk Chun. Right. I met yesterday.
He tends to be quite generous.
Hello?
- Suk Chun.
- What?
Were you sleeping?
No. I'm in Itaewon.
Suk Chun. We are filming Running Man.
You know how you are known to
be an angel without wings.
- That's why Haha and I...
- Come here then.
- You're generous.
- You're our giving tree!
We plan to visit you, the
wingless angel of Itaewon.
We are wondering if there
are things we could get.
- Suk Chun.
- I'm glad to have you visit me.
- Then we'll head to your place.
- All right.
- See you soon.
- Okay!
We are in Itaewon!
- It's nice to come on a sunny day.
- Right. On a sunny day,
you can't just pass by Itaewon
without visiting this area.
An outdoor table?
(This is a place where they
can't hold in their freedom.)
(Jong Kook, the movie actor)
- You're good.
- Hey.
(They act silly out of excitement.)
See? This isn't weird.
No one is staring at us.
Right? When we do this, - I feel free.
No one considers our behavior strange.
They're taking photos.
(Their eyes meet with a citizen
inside the restaurant.)
(Out of nowhere, they start dancing.)
Look at this. Don't they look so free?
- Freedom in Itaewon.
- "Freedom in Itaewon."
Itaewon is a place of freedom.
- It's a place of freedom.
- Yes, it is.
We are the world.
(They arrive at Suk Chun's place.)
Hello. Is Suk Chun here?
I see. He's in the bathroom.
This is a nice, calm place.
- I see a mirror ball.
- I see it too.
(As soon as they step in,
they spot a mirror ball.)
How could he have thought of
putting a mirror ball here?
How nice.
(There might be a lot of things
we could get from here.)
(He welcomes Suk Chun zealously.)
Hong Suk Chun!
- Stop it.
- Hong Suk Chun!
(Suk Chun looks great even after
he comes back from the bathroom.)
- Our generous angel, Hong Suk Chun!
- I knew it.
- We were passing by...
- and thought of you.
- Why did you come to Itaewon?
Look at your outfit. It's as
if you knew we were coming.
- No.
- He's always prepared.
- He always dresses up nicely.
- I always look presentable.
- My gosh.
- You're amazing.
Suk Chun. We are in a hurry.
- Why are you in a hurry?
- We got a resting place.
This is a list of furniture we need.
Take a look at this and see if there
is any furniture you can donate.
If there is,
we can do its worth by working for you.
We have the basketball stand.
- We need a mirror ball...
- You need to get a mirror ball?
- Yes.
- It's good if we have it.
- I can see a mirror ball.
- I happened to spot a mirror ball.
(There is a mirror ball in a
perfect place for them to take.)
(You want to take my mirror ball?)
- I'm not trying to pressure you.
- No.
- We didn't mean that.
- You don't have to give it to us.
- We were just mentioning it.
- There's no need to give it to us.
- You happened to have it.
- There are smaller ones.
We'll have to get it from somewhere else.
Are you here to steal from me?
- No, we are not here to steal.
- That's not it.
You can ask us to do something for
you in exchange for these things.
- You will?
- We'll do something.
- We'll do it for you.
- Really?
Then both of you will...
Come on, Suk Chun.
What? Hold on.
- You two overestimated yourselves.
- We are?
I only said,
- "Then both of you will..."
- What were you going to say?
- I was going to ask you to clean.
- To clean? I see.
- I'm sorry.
- What were you thinking?
- That was the funny part.
You two are unbelievable.
- We're sorry.
- I'm not like that.
We can definitely clean for you.
Besides, you're the last
person I'd think about.
(He speaks bluntly to Haha.)
I know your wife.
All right. Then do you want a desk?
- Or do you want a mirror ball?
- Okay.
- I mean...
- I'd like to give you everything.
I just got goosebumps. When
you starred on our show,
- we were on the same team.
- Were we?
- I think we were. Yes, we were.
- We were on the same team.
(Running Man, Episode 206)
(Their teamwork was fantastic
and they won the race.)
- Yes, we were.
- Suk Chun.
We were a team.
- Right. We were family.
Then give us a sofa.
(We are family, aren't we?)
(Family members share everything.)
Oh, right. It turns out that...
- I have a sofa I'm not using.
- Really?
Don't you have a lot of refrigerators?
(You own a lot of restaurants.)
(Can't you give your
family a refrigerator?)
Hold on.
Family is...
Family is such a burden!
(They obtain a microwave
and a mirror ball.)
I can't even swear at you guys.
(Nothing is free in life.
It's time for them to work.)
- We are very thankful.
- A microwave and a mirror ball.
- How many dirty dishes do we have?
- Give me the dishes.
- You can give everything to him.
- Please give them to me.
- He's going to wash them.
- Of course.
- He'll clean them nicely.
- I like doing dishes.
- Bring them.
- I like cleaning dishes.
Give him anything that has
to be washed and cleaned.
(He starts washing dishes.)
- Look at this.
- What is it?
- It's still greasy.
- Really?
- Do it again!
- Are you certain?
It can't be.
- You'd better wash them well.
- My goodness.
(Sloppy)
You don't seem to be
good at washing dishes.
You only used those hands of yours
to lift weights. They're sloppy.
You need to be thorough with every dish.
(My boss seems to be strict.
I will work hard.)
I hire part-timers for their looks.
Look at you.
You are definitely in charge of cleaning.
(It was really Haha.)
Oh, my.
- He's a part-timer.
- Right, I am.
I really thought you were
a part-timer at first.
- You're Haha.
- Yes, I am.
(He smiles like an angle since
he's in front of a customer.)
By the way, both of you are good-looking.
I will give you something.
It's on the house.
You have no right to do that.
Don't you know how much you earn?
(Where did that angel go?)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Taking photos with
customers is their duty.)
- You are one lucky lady.
- You're right.
- Thank you.
- I'm a fan.
Suk Chun.
- Gosh.
- By the way,
- this is a bit dirty.
- It doesn't matter.
- Clean it before using it.
- This is a used microwave.
Where would we have gotten this?
Here is the mirror ball.
- I have memories with this.
- I see.
- Use it well.
- Of course.
- We appreciate it.
- Thank you. We'll use it well.
- It's only possible in Running Man.
- I can't thank you enough.
- Suk Chun should spin this.
- Me?
- Don't worry.
- I'm not very good at this.
- I don't get lucky.
- That's fine.
What am I going to do?
You never know. This isn't for you.
- You can spin it twice.
- Really?
- Spin it from here.
- All right.
Hold this.
- Don't practice.
- Let me practice.
- You can spin it twice. Do it.
- Win an infinite check.
- Do it now?
- Do it.
You are our generous angel.
The universe will help you.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Give it a good spin.
(Right, I am an angel.)
(Suk Chun. You always share. You
were busy taking care of us, right?)
(The universe won't turn its back
on you and your good deeds.)
(He wins a dollar!)
- I said I shouldn't do it.
- That's all right.
- I said I should practice.
- Don't worry.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- It's okay.
- You'll get lucky now.
- This is all right.
- Win us 100 dollars.
- Let's win 100 dollars.
- It's on the roulette?
- Yes, it is.
- Spin it.
- Here it goes.
(He's hesitant.)
(We're grateful for the items, but
we hope we can thank you even more.)
(What will generous Suk Chun
win at his second try?)
(He wins a dollar again.)
(He's a man who only wins a dollar.)
How could he get a dollar again?
How can he win a dollar twice in a row?
He could have won 10 dollars.
(I'm sorry.)
Goodness.
Two dollars are nothing.
I told you I'm unlucky.
You're right.
(Where's Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo?)
- Can we accept things?
- Yes.
- Whom are you calling?
- I'm calling my brother.
- Sung Moon is...
- Is he at home?
We can ask favors from him, right?
- Right, he's your family.
- However,
he usually doesn't answer my calls.
- I'll call him.
- Wait.
Let me call him first.
Where are you?
- I'm at home.
- That's good.
- I'm recording Running Man.
- Hello, this is Kwang Soo.
- Hello, Kwang Soo.
- Your voice suddenly changed.
- We're coming to the house.
- Is it close to here?
Do you know the table I use
when I read my scripts?
(Actresses have a special
table for reading scripts.)
Which one?
"Which one?"
- He doesn't know.
- Go and wash your face.
- Bring the table outside.
- Why?
- Wash your face for now.
- Okay.
- Let's go to the house.
- To Sung Moon?
(They head to Ji Hyo's house.)
(They arrive to meet her brother.)
It'd be perfect if we can take that chair.
Gosh, those would be perfect.
(It's a nice table and chair set.)
- I'll call Sung Moon.
- I want to steal them.
- I have an urge to steal.
- No way.
- I want to run away with it.
- I'm regular here.
(He has a sudden urge.)
- Sung Moon is coming.
- Is he here already?
What's wrong with him?
(He delivers a table for reading scripts.)
He looks embarrassing.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
Does he know he's on camera?
Come to senses, Sung Moon.
- Isn't that good?
- The table looks good.
Have you been well? Thank you.
Did you just get up?
- This is a great table.
- It's a table.
Let's use it.
This is good enough.
Do you usually use this table?
No, Ji Hyo uses it when she drinks beer.
Ji Hyo uses it when she drinks beer.
She said something different on the phone.
- She said it's for reading scripts.
- I read scripts at this table.
- That's once in 10 times.
- She uses it once out of 10 times.
Mostly, she uses it for drinking
beer before going to bed.
You can't simply take this table.
You must do a favor of
the person who owns it.
- I own this table.
- Don't say that.
- The table is Sung Moon's.
- Right.
It's Sung Moon's. Is
there anything you want?
(He whispers.)
(Are you sure that's what you want?)
Sung Moon wants to hit Ji Hyo.
He wants to hit Ji Hyo.
She always hits him, but he
never gets to hit her back.
He'd like to hit her lightly with care.
- Okay.
- Okay?
(You won't hit me hard, will you?)
(That was a lie.)
- In 3, 2, 1.
- Look at his pose.
(He gets into a position to hit her.)
- Sung Moon.
- What?
You look like you're ready
to kick a soccer ball.
- I thought you were Ronaldo.
- Okay.
In 3, 2, 1.
(He's ready to take revenge.)
(He kicks hard.)
(She feels extreme pain.)
Where did he go?
(Love is deep between siblings.)
It really hurts.
(Punching)
Your brother kicked you.
I don't deserve this.
You encouraged him.
- That really hurt.
- Thank you anyway.
Thank you.
(They obtain a table.)
When you obtain an item,
you may spin the roulette.
Here's the roulette.
- Don't do it. Here, Sung Moon.
- Sung Moon should do it.
I'm unlucky like you.
- Try it, Sung Moon.
- Try it.
You have good energy.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Will Sung Moon get lucky?)
(It's one dollar.)
(How dare you after kicking your sister?)
(I'm sorry.)
(They obtain a table and a dollar.)
- See you.
- Bye, Sung Moon.
Thank you. Bye.
Let's make another call.
(What's the next item?)
Lee Dong Wook isn't answering.
(Is it who I think he is?)
(Lee Dong Wook, the best-looking man
in afterlife, is a popular actor.)
Lee Dong Wook isn't answering.
- Hello?
- Where are you?
- I'm at a film shoot.
- When will you finish?
I'll finish around 9pm.
Listen to me carefully.
- Listen carefully?
- Bidet...
- Bidet?
- And a mirror ball.
A mirror ball.
(She recites the list of items.)
(What is she talking about?)
- Claw crane.
- Parasol.
Barbecue grill.
Are you teaching me Korean now?
No, that's not it.
- Among these items...
- Should I repeat after you?
- No.
- No, we're sorry.
Is there an item you can
give me as you don't use it?
- Claw crane.
- Do you have a claw crane?
(That's a difficult item to find.)
- What?
- Do you have a claw crane?
Do you mean something I have?
- What are you doing?
- Are you joking?
We have to obtain these items.
How can I give it to you?
Tell me. I'll take it from your house.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry, Dong Wook.
(Hey, you jerks.)
I'm sorry. It's because we're in a hurry.
- Dong Wook.
- We're really in a hurry.
I really enjoyed your drama.
It came out of nowhere.
We should hang up.
- Okay.
- What's going on?
I'm sorry.
- If you think of something,
- We should hang up.
Please call me.
Are you hanging up because
you don't need me?
- That's not why.
- Hey.
- Call me if you think of something.
- We'll call you again.
Call me if you have an item.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, Dong Wook.
- Have a good day.
- Bye.
I'll call Park Jung Min.
- Is he nearby?
- He's moving.
- Is he moving?
- He's moving two days later.
- That sounds good.
- Jung Min is moving two days later.
(Give us things you don't need.)
- Hello.
- Where are you?
- I'm in Samcheong-dong.
- Do you have a mirror ball?
- Why would I have it?
- You don't have it?
- I have things at home.
- When will you go back home?
I'm going home at night.
I'll come to you. Let's talk in person.
You can come, but I can only...
- take a 10-minute break.
- Of course I know.
- Let's go.
(They head to Samcheong-dong
for possible items.)
- Is this the place?
- Yes.
(We're here for your donations.)
He and I look similar.
He looks similar to Seok Jin.
- He really does.
- The door is open.
Okay.
- How do we open it?
- I don't know.
The door is open.
Hello.
(Jo Woo Jong)
- Hello, congratulations.
- Is this the apartment?
(He's getting married on March.)
Congratulations. When is your wedding?
- It's on the 16th.
- I see.
Are you getting along at work?
He told me to stay at home,
- so I'm at home every day.
- That's good.
- Come on. You work a lot.
- By the way,
- you're getting married suddenly.
- Right.
Are you here to interview me?
- No, I'm not.
- Weren't you a reporter?
- Right.
- I was too.
We were reporters on
"Entertainment Weekly".
- That's true.
- I worked there too.
All of us are former reporters
on "Entertainment Weekly".
- That's right.
- We're coworkers.
- We were on that show.
- I was a reporter...
on "Entertainment Weekly", and I got fired.
- He was a reporter at that time.
- Right.
- Soon after, I got fired.
- I remember.
You were fired next.
- Woo Jong was...
- I was a reporter,
- but then I got fired.
- Were you?
Woo Jong seems to get fired
often from TV shows.
(Woo Jong had forgotten his past.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
That's what I noticed.
Thank you, Woo Jong.
- For what?
- I'm just thankful.
- Seriously.
- I haven't done anything.
Shall we take a look at your house?
Let's see.
(They start to take a look at the house.)
Wait a minute.
- I'm not married yet. I need them.
- Don't worry. I know.
You'll be next week.
- Let me take a look.
- I need it for cooking.
We won't take it. We can't.
- May I get a drink?
- This isn't new.
- Do you have food?
- I bought a used fridge.
I bought it for 600 dollars.
Is it a used fridge?
- This is great.
- It works well.
Even if it works well,
it's still a used fridge.
A new fridge might be better
since you're getting married.
I have a question. I've been living here,
so using an old fridge doesn't matter.
- My wife may feel differently.
- She'd like a new one.
- Right.
- You know that sofa?
- Your wife might want a new one.
- She keeps talking about it.
- Of course.
- This is why.
- She may want new furniture.
- Come here. My goodness.
- It may be okay for you.
- Is it true?
- Are you trying to take it?
- No.
- Listen to me carefully.
- Listen.
You should sit here.
I thought Seok Jin was Woo Jong.
It doesn't matter where we sit.
- It's hard to differentiate.
- It's confusing.
- You have to look carefully.
Your wife may feel this way.
- It's her one and only marriage.
- Look.
- Not because she doesn't like it.
- It's not because it's old.
It's you and her apartment.
These things are yours.
To decorate it as a new apartment,
you should get rid of the used ones.
It's fun to fill the house
with more furniture.
That's true, but the bride
might not think so.
That's right.
- Woo Jong.
- Yes.
Are we taking that television?
Pardon? That's the only television I have.
- I know.
- You're planning...
to get a new one, right?
It's a nice television. It's too nice.
It's even nicer than mine.
Are you going to... Right now... I see.
- We are.
- I have around 10 days until...
- my wedding. I like watching TV.
- I see.
- Is there anything else you want?
- We...
There's nothing else.
(He doesn't sound happy.)
(We really like your TV, Woo Jong.)
- No, it's okay.
- Is that the only thing you want?
- That's not it.
- Do you have a gas burner?
- Do you have it, by any chance?
- A gas burner?
I do.
I have it.
- I don't even use it.
- That's it!
(They finally agree.)
It worked out.
- I have it.
- That's good.
- I was planning to give it away.
- That's perfect.
- I have it.
- That's great.
I'm happy that he's giving it up so easily.
People have it at home,
but they hardly use it.
Same goes for me. I have
one, but I don't use it.
You only use it when you go camping.
That's right.
- Woo Jong.
- I didn't know what to do with it.
- It's nice.
- Woo Jong.
You hardly used it.
Do you need anything else?
- Do you need rugs?
- We do.
- Do you have it?
- Of course, I do.
(I have rugs.)
- I don't use them. I have them.
- That's great.
You only wrote down what I don't need.
That's amazing. How can you have rugs?
- You don't use it?
- I have so many.
This?
- We only need one.
- I have...
- so many.
- This is awesome.
This is awesome.
- Keep the rest. This is enough.
- I have more.
- These rugs.
- Woo Jong's house...
- is great.
- We got a lot.
If you need something, you
have to visit newlyweds.
- Yes.
- You're right.
Do you need anything from them, Woo Jong?
Do I need anything? Would
they grant anything?
Tell us.
- Me?
- What if Running Man members...
Then... - create a video message for you?
- We can do that.
- That's too easy.
- A video message?
- I'm sorry to say this,
That's too easy.
But he's a celebrity as well.
What is he saying?
- It'll help.
- He thinks he's so important.
It'll only help if you're a non-celebrity.
- It doesn't help me.
- He's a celebrity himself.
- Tell me if you need it.
- Are you really doing that?
Sorry?
- I need a humidifier.
- That's perfect.
- We can get it for him.
- Let's do that.
- It's not too much, right?
- No way.
That's great.
- That's not difficult.
- We'll get you a humidifier...
to put in your couple's room.
It'll be filled with love.
- Thank you.
- You have gained your items.
- Do we spin it again?
- My gosh.
- Let me spin it this time.
- All right.
He got a dollar last time.
- Let me try it.
- Go ahead.
I hope we get 100 dollars.
(Is he lucky or unlucky?)
Look at that.
- You should do it.
- I'm good at things like this.
- Should I do it?
- You do it.
- You have to say, "Go."
- Say it.
- Go.
(Spinning)
(How good is he when it really counts?)
A dollar?
(It's only a dollar.)
(He was doing well before.)
(He feels guilty now.)
I'm sorry.
Take your dollar. I'm sorry.
I landed on 100 dollars before.
I don't know what happened
to the 99 dollars.
He gave you another item, so
we'll give you one more chance.
- One more chance?
- Okay.
- It's our last chance.
- I'll do it.
Go.
(He needs every luck he can afford.)
I hope it's the infinite check.
(He spins it with all the
luck he can afford.)
Infinite check.
(They need a big one this time.)
(It lands on 100 dollars.)
You did it!
(It's the miracle of the unlucky one.)
(That was the 1st time in 7 years.)
- It's 100 dollars.
- Good job.
See?
(I'm happy you got 100 dollars.)
- 100 dollars? Really?
- They really give it to you?
That's awesome. They give
it to you right away.
(They earned 2 items plus 100 dollars.)
(The unlucky ones are doing well today.)
- Is that yours now?
- This is amazing.
- We're leaving.
- See you.
See you, Woo Jong.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
(They get going after
meeting the new groom.)
I think we're hitting most of it.
We're lucky there are
people getting married.
- Good thing we went to his house.
- Exactly.
We have 100 dollars,
so let's tell the members that
we'll get the television.
- That's right.
- We can even buy games.
- Do you think we can?
- No,
we have to go see it first.
- We can get a small one.
- We can get a 27-inch.
That's right.
- There it is. It says "Recycling".
- Where?
- Okay.
- Here it is.
It's going to be fun.
- This is amazing.
- Look at that.
- They sell those.
- They should have parasols as well.
- They should.
- They have refrigerators too.
(It looks like they have everything.)
The price is the problem.
I don't think they'll be expensive.
- Hello.
- Hello, sir.
- Oh, dear.
- Can we browse?
- Sure.
There are so many interesting things.
- Look at the fridge.
- It's 40 dollars.
(They were here for a TV, but
they look at something else.)
- It's 170 dollars.
- It's expensive.
(The fridge is expensive.)
- This one's nice.
- How much is it?
It's 530 dollars.
(They look at all the fridges.)
We can't get one.
Are there any small ones?
There must be 50-dollar ones.
We need half that size.
What about this?
This is 100 dollars.
- This is 100?
- It is.
(They want a fridge more
than a television.)
This one's perfect.
Is there something smaller
than this that's 50 dollars?
What's the cheapest television you have?
- Let's look at this one.
- It's expensive. It's 230 dollars.
- This is 50 dollars.
- It is.
It works well.
(It looks decent.)
(If we get this television, we
only have 50 dollars left.)
(Do we have to give up on the fridge then?)
Should we call them?
It's more expensive than we thought.
(Is it the TV or the fridge?)
- They might not pick up.
- The television works well.
- Hello?
Do you want a fridge or a TV?
Television? That's awesome.
We can take care of the fridge.
You think so? All right.
Bye.
It's 100 dollars, so should we get it?
- Should we get that?
- What if we get this?
- Should we get this?
- The fridge?
You're debating...
because the television is 50
dollars and the fridge...
- is 100, right?
- Yes.
What if...
we bet 50 dollars...
and play a game of roulette?
(A game of roulette?)
- Let's do it.
- How do you play it?
We spin the roulette...
and whoever gets the larger amount wins.
Let's do it.
If you lose, we take 50 dollars from you.
- We know.
- We can buy the television then.
If we win, we can get both.
Are you going to play or not?
I used all the luck I
had on the 100 dollars.
I'll do it.
Don't do it.
Let's do it.
- Okay.
- Let's do it.
- I'll do it. Do I go first?
- Okay.
Say, "Go." Don't make excuses.
- Go.
(The director goes first.)
(I hope it's a small amount.)
(What number would he land on?)
10 dollars.
(He gets 10 dollars.)
This is bad.
(They need something bigger
than 10 dollars to win.)
Go.
(Jae Seok goes after.)
(Hopefully, he has some luck left.)
(Would he kill 2 birds with 1 stone?)
(He lands on one dollar.)
I said I was going to do it.
- Give me the money.
- Come on.
(They lose 50 dollars.)
- It makes me laugh.
- Give it to me.
- My gosh.
- One dollar.
What's wrong with us? We're so unlucky.
What now? We need to get the fridge.
Let's bet this as well.
(Let's bet everything on this.)
Do it.
(Let's bet 50 more dollars
and spin it again.)
- There you go.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
- Let's do it.
We have nothing more.
But let me go first. Let me do it.
Go.
(What would Seok Jin land on?)
(One dollar)
(Shoot)
- You get nothing if you lose.
- Okay.
- How's this possible?
- What's wrong with us?
I don't understand.
(What would the director land on?)
(He gets 10 dollars again.)
You're a gambler.
- You're good at this.
- Is this how you bought a house?
- Hold on.
- I swear you did.
How's this possible? I don't understand.
Gambling robs you of your fortune.
You should never...
bet your luck on something so trivial.
We got a dollar again. How's that possible?
You see...
(What just happened?)
- We'll be back.
- Sorry?
(They're quiet.)
I'm sorry. We wanted to get them.
- Why did you agree on this?
- We didn't know he gambles.
- Why did you agree to play this?
- He's a gambler.
(He is doomed by the roulette.)
- What a letdown.
- You agreed too.
- Call them.
- This is driving me nuts.
- What a letdown.
- My gosh.
- This is driving me nuts.
- What a letdown.
(They can't explain the feeling.)
We worked so hard for that money.
What now?
This is driving me nuts.
(What are we supposed to tell the others?)
- What now?
- This is driving me insane.
(Let's not do this ever again.)
I'm ashamed of myself.
Do you want to bet the gas burner?
- Don't do that.
- What are you trying to do?
- He's a gambler.
- We're on television right now.
Why do you keep asking us to bet things?
(We barely made up our minds.)
Let's do it.
(Their firm and determined
response is "Go.")
We can get a television.
We want the television.
How much would you give us
if we bet on the gas burner?
We'll bet 50 dollars.
50 dollars?
- Okay.
- Let's do it.
Are you going to do it?
- Don't do it.
- You can do it.
You keep losing.
Do rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
- I won. You can go first.
- Go first.
- I'm going to watch you.
- What's wrong with it?
(The director goes first.)
One dollar.
(Would he get 10 dollars
this time as well?)
That's right!
(He gets a dollar this time.)
(We have a chance.)
We can get the television.
(We win if we get 10 dollars or more.)
(If they win, they accomplish
a part of their goal.)
(If they lose, they'll get Woo
Jong's gas burner taken away.)
(What will be the result
of this last round?)
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin
win with 10 dollars.)
(They get 50 dollars.)
That's it.
- Bring it.
- Give us 50 dollars.
Thank you.
(After an intense match,
they get a television.)
- Take care. Thank you.
- Which one's our car?
- Is this it?
- This is it.
(At least they won't be humiliated.)
- I'll call Ji Min.
- Sure.
- Don't come.
- Ji Min.
- Why not? We're already here.
Can you come down?
- There she is.
- Where?
Ji Min.
Drive safe.
- Come down.
- Come on.
Come down, Ji Min.
(Kim Ji Min, Korea's most
beautiful comedienne)
(She lets them in on a surprise visit.)
She has a puppy.
Your house is so nice.
Look at her house.
(Her puppy welcomes them.)
You're so cute.
You're so clean.
- I'm clean.
- It smells like a lady's house.
Look at the wine.
(Her house is clean and pretty.)
You've lit a candle.
- I need to wipe off...
- We feel bad.
- Can you wipe off the dust?
- Sure, I'll do it.
I feel bad now.
What are you doing?
- He's trying to look cute.
- I'm not.
- He's acting like he's warmhearted.
- I'm not. I love puppies.
Stop lying. I've never
seen you with a puppy.
I feel bad looking around your house.
This is so cool.
Do you sit here by yourself and play games?
- No, I don't.
- Don't you play games?
- I read books here.
- You read?
Of course.
You have two refrigerators.
How are you going to take that?
- We can't take it.
- Your vacuum.
You can't take it. It's broken.
- Wait a minute.
- It just broke.
It just broke?
Look. This...
You can't take this.
- No, I'm not taking it.
- You have so many awards.
- You can't take this.
- I'm not taking this.
There's nothing. Get out.
(There's nothing she doesn't use.)
- You want us to get out?
- Get out.
Don't say that.
- Take the printer.
- Who's that? Is that you?
- You used to be so pretty.
- Do you want it?
- It'll make you feel better.
- It's okay.
- It's fine. I'll give it to you.
- It's okay. We're fine.
- It'll make you feel better.
- Hang it up on the wall.
- You used to be so pretty.
- Of course.
- Let's see.
- Right?
- You're right.
- You were so charming.
- I'll give you all of them to take.
It's okay.
We can't take anything.
- I do have something I don't need.
- What is it?
- You have something?
- Give us everything you don't need.
It's too out of style, so I stored it away.
- Let's see.
- It's a chair.
Ji Hyo doesn't have to sit on the floor.
- What do you think?
- It's a chair with a back.
Try sitting on it.
- It's nice.
- It's not bad.
- It's so comfortable.
- It's nice.
Since you're giving this chair to us...
- The puppy...
- Are you going to ask for a favor?
Can you walk him for the first time?
I brought him outside before,
- He doesn't move?
- But he doesn't move.
- Really?
- He never walked outside before.
- Should we go?
- You want us to walk him?
- Okay, we can do that.
- It'll be great if he walks.
(They decide to walk the dog.)
- Jong Kook, that's a good spot.
- It's sunny.
- Neu Kkim.
- Neu Kkim. We know how it feels.
- We know how it feels.
- Neu Kkim.
We know how to walk.
Let's go this way. Come.
(This is how you walk.)
Good job.
Come here, Neu Kkim. Catch me.
You're fast.
(He's as excited as the puppy.)
(Neu Kkim did well, so
that wasn't difficult.)
- Good job.
- He runs well.
- Give us the roulette.
- There you go.
- You can spin it.
- Go ahead, Ji Min.
This is how you do it. Do I spin it?
- Do I spin it?
- Spin it this way.
(She doesn't hesitate.)
You're too careless.
(Spinning)
Infinite check!
(It's an infinite check.)
You're insane.
(That's amazing.)
- You're insane.
- What's going on?
It's an infinite check.
- This is real.
- How is this possible?
We got an infinite check.
Can you get anything you want?
- We can get a fridge.
- Really?
- We're getting a fridge.
- Thank you, Ji Min.
I didn't know you were so lucky.
Why are they all glaring at me?
- We're getting a fridge.
- Really?
Isn't this a miracle?
We have no time. It's 6:30pm.
Let's hurry.
Ha Nan.
(Jong Kook visits his stylist.)
Come here.
- It's so heavy.
- I have that too.
- Up there.
- What's that?
She has it.
- Okay.
- You have a parasol.
You put this together.
This is a parasol.
- It's a perfect table.
- That's right.
It's a parasol.
(They earn 10 out of 16 items.)
- There it is. We're here.
- Where?
He's doing an interview right now.
- Hello.
Let's eat first.
Don't go.
He's being interviewed.
- Interviewed?
- He is.
He's a celebrity.
Jung Min's sitting in the middle,
- and there are people around him.
- Really?
There's only one left.
We talked to your dad about the sofa.
- Let's ask him.
- Should we?
- Hello?
- Hello.
Have you thought about a wish?
- What was that?
- A wish.
(They want to know his wish.)
(Three hour earlier, they
were coming up with plans.)
Are there any sofas you don't use at work?
- Sofas we don't use?
- Yes.
- It doesn't have to be nice.
- I'll have to look.
- Can you have a look?
- All right.
Have you thought about a wish?
(What is his wish in
exchange for the sofa?)
Song Joong Ki and Jo In Sung's autographs.
That's great. That's perfect.
Why would you ask me for that?
Is that what your employees want?
You just need Song Joong Ki and...
- Jo In Sung's autographs, right?
- Your son is Lee Kwang Soo.
- Tell them not to upset me.
- I see.
We'll get the autographs and
send the pictures to you.
Sure.
- I have my own signature too.
- Stop it.
Yours is not important.
Hurry. Call Joong Ki and In Sung.
Hurry up and call Joong Ki and In Sung.
(He's embarrassed to ask.)
That's the only way we can get the sofa.
I know it's not difficult.
(Jung Min gets them food while they wait.)
- Hi, In Sung.
- Aren't you working?
- I'm filming right now.
- Okay.
Can I...
- Hello?
- Hi.
I'm not buying.
Don't do that.
- In Sung.
- Yes.
I need your autograph.
You can leave the parcel
in front of my house.
What are you talking about?
- Thank you.
- In Sung.
You can leave it at the real estate office.
I'm not leaving anything.
That's not why I called.
I need your autograph.
I don't have an autograph anymore.
What do you mean? How's that possible?
- I only shake hands these days.
- In Sung.
- Don't lie.
- I don't have one anymore.
- I'm eating. Call back later.
- Are you eating?
- Yes.
- I'll call you back.
Sure.
(I'll be nice because we need the sofa.)
(What are you guys doing?)
Hello.
- Long time no see.
- How are you?
- Excuse us.
- Thank you for the food, Jung Min.
- We ate before we saw you.
(Actor Park Jung Min, the
rising star of Chungmuro)
- You're moving, right?
- Yes.
- You're moving in two days, right?
What are you throwing away?
- I'm throwing out my bidet.
- And then?
Here are the list of items we need.
- We're already getting the sofa.
- These are what we need.
What's this?
- Numbers.
- Numbers we need.
Is there a fridge you don't use?
- Are you going to take it?
- Who doesn't use one?
- That's not what I meant.
- Everybody uses it.
- Do you have a claw crane?
- Claw crane?
- You don't own a claw crane?
- I don't.
- Darts? Don't you play games?
- No.
What do you do?
I have a bidet.
- Only the bidet?
- Yes.
- Can't you take it from my house?
- Then...
I know it's a lot to ask.
If he gives us his passcode,
we'll go to his house.
- We'll go there.
- We'll take his bidet and leave.
- Okay.
- We'll assemble it.
We need to do you a favor.
- Right.
- We'll grant you a wish.
May I advertise a movie?
- Of course.
- It can be anything you want.
- Isn't it okay for 30 seconds?
- Can you advertise it?
- Me?
- Yes.
(Asian Prince Kwang Soo
speaks about a movie.)
I won't tell you the movie's title.
The lead actors are Park
Jung Min and Ryu Hyun Kyung.
(It'll be a big hit.)
It sounds fun.
You can find it when you search
these actors on the Internet.
It's an incredible movie.
- When will it be released?
- On March 9.
- It's March 9.
- It makes you cry and laugh.
My goodness. How can I describe it?
You haven't seen it.
Don't say that. I was too
busy to go to the premiere.
Please watch the movie because it's fun.
You won't be disappointed. I
put my everything on the line.
(They advertise the movie in 30 seconds.)
Thank you.
It's much farther than I thought.
Let's call Joong Ki.
- Hello?
- Hey.
(Welcome back, Joong Ki.)
- Hi.
- We're shooting Running Man.
- Joong Ki, this is Ji Hyo.
- We have to...
- Hi, Ji Hyo.
- Get a sofa...
from my father, but I
need to grant him a wish.
His wish was to get your autograph.
- I don't know how it happened.
- Joong Ki.
- That's what's going on.
- We're in a hurry.
I'd like to get your autograph.
Are you far away?
Yes, I have to go to Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do.
We're coming to your office.
(We'll go anywhere for your autograph.)
I need your autograph.
Why does he wish to get my
autograph and not yours?
- How would I know?
- Are you okay?
- Of course, he isn't.
- That's his wish, okay?
I have no choice.
Can you give us your autograph?
We need to get it.
My manager may have it.
Does he? See you later.
- Good luck, Ji Hyo.
- Thank you.
Let's go to Gangnam.
In Sung isn't answering.
(The remaining time is 1
hour and 40 minutes.)
(Where is Jong Kook and Haha going?)
- What's up?
- Tae Hyun.
(Who is he calling?)
- What?
- What are you doing?
- I'm at home.
- Tae Hyun.
Tae Hyun.
(He's calling someone named Tae Hyun.)
(Is he the man on "One Night Two Days"?)
- I'm at home.
- Tae Hyun.
I have a favor to ask.
We're shooting Running Man.
- Running Man?
- I know I shouldn't do this.
(He tries to cast him on Running Man.)
It's okay if it's only my voice.
Right, it could be only your voice...
- on Running Man.
- Is this a quiz?
It's nothing like that.
(How will he ask him to visit his house?)
May I see you for a minute?
We can blur your face out.
(He makes a difficult request.)
Could you appear on the show?
We'll blur your face out.
I'll come to your house.
Could you...
I don't have many friends with children,
but you do. Do you have
a mattress for babies?
Do you want a baby mattress?
Yes, may I get one from you?
Could we get a few, please?
- You want a few pieces?
- Yes.
- Just a few pieces.
- Do you know what it's like?
- Please give us a few pieces.
- I can't detach the pieces.
- May I get a piece?
- It's not detachable.
Then give me the whole thing.
(Jong Kook doesn't give up.)
- Come on.
- Why do you need it?
On Running Man,
- we're trying to decorate...
- Don't tell him so much.
Anyway...
- Tae Hyun.
- Yes?
Come to our resting place
and spend a night.
We'll rent it out.
You may rent our resting place.
You can come and spend a night.
Anyway, - Call me when you arrive.
We're coming to your house.
- Gosh, he's easygoing.
- Yes, he is.
(They finally meet him.)
Let's ring the door.
- Is this the doorbell?
- Yes.
(What kind of a situation is this?)
(He still can't believe it.)
The gate is open. Excuse us.
- Excuse us.
- Is this the place?
Wait, is this the place?
(Today, they're meeting him
as a friend, not a rival.)
- Hello.
- My goodness.
(5-year-old Cha Soo Jin)
- Hello.
- Where's your dad?
(Actor Cha Tae Hyun)
Where's your dad?
(Mask Tae Hyun appears.)
(He hasn't been on SBS
on Sunday in a while.)
(He appears in a shocking manner.)
The production team and I know each other.
Blurring my face is more work for them.
Is that why you're wearing it?
I'm also wearing "One
Night Two Days" jacket.
- Really?
- Yes, look.
I see.
My daughter is laughing too.
- Hello.
- This is hilarious.
His daughter is excited.
She's so cute.
Did you say, a resting place?
Wait a minute.
- What is it?
- Do you have a dartboard?
- Tae Hyun.
- Do you have a dartboard for kids?
- I don't.
- He doesn't.
- I'm sorry for bothering you.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Are you giving it to us?
- We need them.
- Tae Hyun.
You'll need it.
- What's this?
- Why are you wearing a mask?
- It's better this way.
- Are you going to sign it?
Here's what's incredible.
Tae Hyun is wearing a mask.
3 TV broadcasting stations became 1.
Tae Hyun signed here.
I'm impressed. You're so open-minded.
Isn't she so cute?
Come here.
(He's moved.)
- Isn't she cute?
- She's the youngest.
(He supports the harmony of variety shows.)
(It's a historic moment as Korean
variety shows come together.)
(It's a festival of weekend
variety shows becoming one.)
You're so cute.
He doesn't need a microphone.
- You're so cute.
- We should let him go.
We're almost done.
- Next week...
- Could you sign here?
- Sign here?
- Sign your autograph.
(He signs the baby mattress.)
Goodness.
"King of Mask Singer",
"One Night Two Days", and
"Running Man" became one.
That's impressive.
- Right.
- Variety shows are one.
Thank you.
Tae Hyun is wearing a mask.
(We are the world.)
- Thank you, Tae Hyun.
- Thank you so much.
- It's good to see you.
- Gosh.
I wanted to try that.
Thank you so much.
- See you later.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
- Excuse us.
We won't need to blur your face out.
- Don't do it.
- Goodness.
- Don't blur it. Soo Jin.
- It's up to our imaginations.
- Say goodbye.
- He's leaving.
- See you.
- Say, "Happy New Lunar Year".
She doesn't have to wear a mask.
She doesn't.
Just change her name to Jin Soo.
She was on "One Night Two Days" last week.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
We'll grant a wish.
- We have to do something.
- We have to give back...
- by doing something you want.
- How about this?
Soo Jin, is there something you want?
- Do you want to eat anything?
- Ice cream.
- Ice cream?
- You'll catch a cold.
What type of ice cream?
- I want vanilla.
- Vanilla ice cream?
Go outside.
- There's a market nearby.
- I know.
- You should go.
- I'll go.
What else would you like?
I'll buy it for you.
- Do you want chocolate?
- Ice cream for my siblings.
She wants ice cream for her siblings too.
- Do you want enough for everyone?
- She's nice.
How about something everyone can share?
(They buy ice cream as a thank you.)
- Okay.
- Look at her hand.
We should spin the roulette.
Why don't Tae Hyun spin it?
- How do I do it?
- Tae Hyun should spin it.
I'll show you.
- You should spin it.
- Soo Jin.
- Spin this roulette.
- That's a good idea.
- Soo Jin.
- I'll hold it for you.
- Come here.
- Could you hold it?
Hold it and spin it like this.
- Spin it like this.
- Can you do it?
- Try it.
- Practice spinning.
- Spin it harder.
- Do it harder.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- This is how you do it.
- We got it!
- In 1, 2, 3.
- This is how you do it.
- We got it.
- We got 100 dollars.
- That was only practice.
You must say, "Go."
The staff is always against us.
Regardless of the broadcast
network, they're always against us.
Soo Jin, spin it one more time.
Soo Jin, spin it again.
- Soo Jin, spin it again.
- Do it one more time.
Spin it one more time. Spin it hard.
- Spin it hard.
- That's right.
You're good at spinning.
- It's an infinite check.
- That's insane.
You're good at spinning.
(Soo Jin gets the infinite check.)
That's insane.
That's right.
(They get another infinite check.)
(It's another shocking result.)
We got another infinite check.
- My goodness.
- It's infinite check.
- This is crazy.
- It was 100 dollars before.
(The harmony of variety shows
brings about a miracle.)
I get lucky on Running Man.
I should be on Running Man.
This is unbelievable.
- I belong on this show.
- Goodness.
- This is incredible.
- We got an infinite check.
- We can't change it.
- No, we can't.
They should have stopped at 100 dollars.
- It's incredible.
- Goodness.
Okay, we got it.
We're so lucky today.
- Barbecue grill.
- What do we do?
We have so many things.
- I'll go get ice cream.
- Go on.
This is amazing.
(Haha runs to the convenience
store for Soo Jin.)
This and...
(What will she like?)
This. How much would this be?
Thank you. Goodbye.
Okay.
(Excited)
I'm appearing for too long.
I'm doing too much.
You should get ready to leave that show.
There's nothing to cut out.
My face is appearing too much.
You're wearing a mask.
It's someone else that
appears on the other show.
- Exactly.
- Don't worry.
- It's okay.
- He's working hard.
- Here.
- Did you get it?
It's a mix between
strawberry and chocolate.
- All right.
- It's totally worth it.
It's here.
- Say thank you.
- Thank you.
- I'm more thankful.
- I seriously am.
- Enjoy.
- Bye.
- Thank you. Bye.
He's my friend.
Thank you so much.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Go, Running Man!
- Go!
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- All right.
(Their hands are full.)
My goodness.
We'll get going.
(Tiger Mask sees them
off from the balcony.)
We're leaving. Bye.
Thank you so much.
That was amazing.
I feel so rich.
- Let's go.
- How can this be possible?
I'm especially happy because
the baby picked it.
Right? The baby picked an infinite check.
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo are
at Jo In Sung's agency.)
Hello.
(Why is Lee Kwang Soo here?)
Do you have In Sung's autograph?
(Why is Kwang Soo asking for that?)
I'm sorry. You must be surprised.
Hello. Do you have In Sung's...
Thank you.
(In Sung left his autograph
for his good friend.)
We're here. It's on the sixth floor.
We need to go up to the office.
Is this it?
Is this his autograph?
He left this.
(Kwang Soo looks like a fanboy.)
I need his autograph.
- Hello.
- Hi, Bo Gum.
("Hi, Bo Gum?")
What are you doing?
(Park Bo Gum is here.)
(The most sought-after actor, Park Bo Gum)
I see. You were here.
Are you having a meeting? I see.
Bo Gum, do you have an
extra fridge at home?
You don't, right? You're
not moving, are you?
No. Do you need a fridge?
- Do you have one?
- No.
Can I have your autograph?
- Me?
- Do you want mine?
- I do.
- Okay.
Bo Gum wants my autograph.
I'll give him one.
- On your name tag?
- Yes.
I'm so honored.
- Like this?
- Yes.
(It's an honor.)
- Thank you.
- All right.
I'll treasure it.
- Bo Gum.
- This is so precious.
- Oh, it sticks.
- I don't do this often.
I don't sign my name tag often.
Thank you.
Can you give me your autograph?
- Should I write the date?
- Sure.
(Kwang Soo got Bo Gum's autograph.)
- Thank you.
- No problem.
- I'll get going.
Thank you.
(They even give Kwang Soo drinks.)
Thank you, Bo Gum. You
didn't have to do this.
- Thank you.
- I hope you'll win.
I feel great.
(He has good friends.)
I have Joong Ki and Bo Gum's autographs.
(He won a sofa.)
Let's go to Gangnam.
Is there a place that sells
dartboards around Jung Min's place?
Can you think of any places?
Dartboards are...
easy to find at stationery stores.
Is there a stationery store around there?
Hello. Do you have a spanner?
- Do you have a spanner?
- Is this okay?
It's perfect.
- We'll return it soon.
- We'll return it.
Thank you.
- Done.
- Hold on.
Just a second.
I'll take a look.
I'll take a look in his bathroom.
How is it?
(Flushing)
Just a second.
(It must be dirty.)
- Don't do anything.
- It's just...
Give me just a second. This is not okay.
(Water splashing)
Is he cleaning the bathroom?
Are you cleaning?
I was going to clean the
bathroom if it's dirty,
but it was very clean.
The bathroom is here.
Let's...
(How do we separate it?)
Kwang Soo, move.
How do we do it?
Hold this and step aside.
(I'm a bidet expert today.)
How do we do it?
Hold this.
(Can you do this?)
How do you separate a bidet?
(Ji Hyo starts to separate the bidet.)
How do you know how to do this?
What are you doing?
I need to turn off the water.
- Is it separated?
- Yes.
- Hold it.
- What's going on?
She just separated the bidet.
- Hold it.
- Look at this.
(Now, she can even separate a bidet?)
(Thanks to Ji Hyo, they acquired a bidet.)
Are there dartboards?
Let's buy them.
(They're rummaging through
someone else's stuff.)
We separated the bidet.
- Can you help me when I move?
- Hey.
When I move... Right.
- Here I go.
- Start.
(It's time to spin the roulette wheel.)
Do it.
Go!
(There's only 10 minutes left.)
(They need some money to get
dartboards and a claw crane.)
(100 dollars)
100 dollars!
(It's a miracle.)
We won 100 dollars!
Let's buy dartboards first.
Where can we buy them?
Excuse me, is there a
stationery store around here?
- Can we walk there? Thank you.
- Are we walking?
Yes, it's right around the corner.
Let's hurry.
What if they don't have dartboards?
They must have them.
We don't have much time.
Hi, where's the stationery store?
You'll see a pole.
- Is it there?
- Yes.
What if they don't have them?
Then we're doomed.
- Where is it?
- It's there!
- Where?
(They find a stationery store.)
It's big. Let's go in.
- They must have them.
- They have a lot of toys.
- Excuse me, do you have dartboards?
- Do you have dartboards?
- Yes, we do.
- Where are they?
- Over there.
- Let me see.
It'll be okay.
(If there are dartboards,
they can just buy them.)
There it is.
Here. How much is it?
It's 17 dollars. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
We can do this.
(They acquire a dartboard.)
You got a dartboard.
Spin the roulette wheel.
This is our last chance.
If we don't get an infinite
check, we're doomed.
- We need an infinite check.
- Let's do this.
Let's do it together.
1, 2, 3.
- 1, 2, 3.
(Will a miracle happen?)
This is our last chance.
If we don't get an infinite
check, we're doomed.
(Please move one more slot.)
If we don't get an infinite
check, we're doomed.
(No way)
You won one dollar.
Why do we keep getting one dollar?
- It's...
- Too bad.
We didn't get any infinite checks.
It's just one slot before.
(They failed to acquire a claw crane.)
Let's just go, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is unlucky today too.)
It needed to move just one more slot.
(Everything except a claw
crane has been acquired.)
You have brought all the items.
Among the things you listed,
you failed to get a claw crane.
One person will be penalized.
- It's too harsh.
- But...
(But?)
You have a last minute chance.
- You have a last minute chance.
- Really?
You can save everyone
from being penalized...
- and acquire the last item.
- Now, you're talking.
You have a chance to do that.
- Can you open the bathroom door?
- Okay.
(What is the last chance?)
It's "Dirty Golfing".
"Dirty Golfing"?
You sit on the toilet...
and get the ball in the hole.
- Sitting on the toilet?
- Only one person gets to try.
You're given only one chance.
It's going to be hard.
(Their fate depends on one try.)
- Here.
- You have to sit.
You have to sit.
But the floor isn't even.
Where's the hole?
It's here.
- It's not impossible.
- Try it.
Practice.
It should go this way.
It has nothing to do with
your golfing skills.
(The floor is slanted.)
(In addition...)
(to the narrow, slated floor...)
It should go this way.
My legs are numb.
You have to put up with it.
I have to squat.
My legs are going numb.
- Why is this here?
- This side is better...
(Dripping)
- Come out.
- What are you doing?
He turned on the water all of a sudden.
- Come out now.
- You're unbelievable.
- My goodness.
- Why did you turn on the water?
- He's not helping.
- Seriously.
I served with someone like
him in the army. I swear.
I can't believe this.
- Get out.
- It's not easy.
- My socks got wet.
- You're a troublemaker.
- Jae Seok should try.
- It's not easy.
- How can we get a hole-in-one?
- It will go over.
I see. This doesn't come out of its place.
It's a matter of luck anyway.
Gosh. This is...
This is not an easy thing to do.
- It won't go in, right?
- It's hard.
(He focuses the best he can.)
(It goes in.)
- He did it.
- Jong Kook.
(He gets it in, practicing it only twice?)
- You should do it, Jong Kook.
- You have to do it, Jong Kook.
(It has to be Jong Kook
who will try this game.)
- You should do it.
- Let's do it right away.
- You must do it.
- Challenge!
- Let's do it now.
- We're going to do it now.
- Say "Challenge" to start.
- Wait.
- Challenge!
- Hold on.
(Jong Kook tries.)
(Everything depends on his putting.)
(Please just do what you just did.)
(He hits it.)
(Will Jong Kook be able to succeed?)
(It goes in.)
(It's a miracle. What a perfect shot!)
(Jong Kook succeeds at "Dirty Golfing".)
- This is incredible.
- Amazing!
- He's the best.
- This is splendid.
(Thanks to his perfect shot, they
are exempted from the punishment.)
This is crazy. How could
it have possibly gone in?
(It's a celebratory shot.)
- You are unbelievable.
- This is beyond my imagination.
- You are amazing.
- Right.
You successfully
accomplished the race today.
No. It's more than that. This is...
- a complete success!
- A complete success!
(Congratulations!)
You even successfully
accomplished the bonus mission.
- How about the claw machine?
- We will give you the claw machine.
- Anyway, we succeeded!
- We succeeded!
(We thank those who appeared on the
show despite their busy schedule.)
(The night deepens at the resting
place of Running Man members.)
(Spring has returned with...)
(Jeon So Min, )
(Lee Se Young, )
(Park Jin Joo, )
(Um Ji, )
(Kang Han Na, )
(and Choi Tae Joon.)
(These lovely ladies
show unexpected charms.)
(It's a spring race of the couples.)
(They will visit Running Man next week.)