(Last week on Running Man)
(People's Recommendation Project: Place for 1 Percent)
(It was decided that Haha and Se Chan will ride Nevis Swing.)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo, exempted from the penalty, joined them.)
You are to accompany them to New Zealand.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are to experience the Cage of Death.)
You'll travel for your penalty.
(As So Min and Seok Jin joined them, their penalty trips began.)
(Are there suspicious Chance Cards for this trip?)
(They chose 3 cards which can be either helpful or disadvantageous.)
(They can only check their cards when they accomplish missions.)
(They can also decline to use the cards.)
- We can refuse to use them? - We don't have to use them.
(And thus began their Swallowtail Butterfly Tour.)
(Two teams headed to Darwin and Queenstown.)
(Both teams arrived in Australia and New Zealand.)
(Team New Zealand successfully accomplished their first mission.)
(They decided to choose 1 card between 2 cards.)
(All of us won't complain about the penalty.)
(Everyone on Team New Zealand won a chance to ride Nevis Swing.)
(Team Australia also successfully accomplished their first mission.)
(They chose a card that gave another member to join their penalty.)
(Seok Jin, the slippery fellow of Jamwon-dong, is chosen.)
(They finally reached the ultimate place for Cage of Death.)
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin will enter the cage together,)
(and Kwang Soo will enter the cage all by himself.)
(Will they be able to overcome their fear and complete the penalty?)
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok's cage is descending toward Axel.)
Is there water coming in?
The water's coming in now.
(They start to feel scared as their feet start getting cold.)
They're going in.
They're in the water.
I can't believe this.
(So Min and Kwang Soo are also shocked by what they see.)
They're really inside.
They're really close.
That's a real crocodile.
- The crocodile's moving. - It's a real crocodile.
It's a real, living crocodile. This is crazy.
Oh, no. Jae Seok is scared.
They went into the water.
- Where? - It's right here. Here.
Gosh, I'm scared!
(The crocodile starts batting the cage at the sight of them.)
- My gosh. It startled me. - What's going on? It's moving.
- It's moving! - It's coming.
- It's moving. - I saw it too.
My gosh, look. It came down.
It came down after spotting them.
My gosh.
(The ruthless crocodile, Axel, is right in front of the cage.)
It's right in front of us.
I saw it!
(I'm the predator around here!)
(Bellowing in fear)
It's huge!
(Crunching)
(Frozen)
- It's so big. - My gosh!
Look at its teeth, Kwang Soo!
Look at its teeth!
(The broken tooth is a testament of its strong jaw movements.)
- My goodness. - Oh, dear!
- It's as big as a house. - Seriously.
It's gigantic!
(Escaping this cold cage is impossible.)
(Startled)
(They're lucky they didn't pass out in the water.)
- Stay still. - My goodness.
It looked at me.
(Axel even tries to eat up the pole used in feeding.)
(It scares the life out of them.)
- It's heading that way. - It's on the move.
(The furious-looking jaw threatens Jae Seok and Seok Jin.)
(He can't refrain himself from screaming even in the water.)
(Their countenance grows pale in a matter of few minutes.)
- It must be angry. - I think it's furious.
It must be livid.
(We will repent if we upset you.)
(It continues to hover around them.)
It's here. The crocodile is close.
It's there.
(I'm begging you. Please get away from us.)
It's going under them.
It just bit.
(I'll just go down to rest quietly.)
(Did you fall for that?)
(It intimidates them as it bats the cage.)
(Shaking)
(Will Jae Seok and Seok Jin be able to complete their penalty?)
(Snapping)
My goodness.
(It's getting riled up by the scent of humans in the off-peak season.)
(Is Seok Jin losing his mind?)
Don't go near it. Don't.
- Don't get close. - Why?
It's angry. It's livid.
It bumped into the cage.
Did you hear it breathing?
Did you see it snapping?
(Is she writing an emergency message?)
(Crocodile, let's go.)
Did you write "Crocodile, let's go"?
Why would you cheer for the crocodile?
You should cheer for the members, not the crocodile.
It's simply going about its day.
(So Min inspires Kwang Soo to write something as well.)
I wrote something as well.
"Cinnamon flavor"?
(Cinnamon flavor and vanilla flavor)
- Seok Jin is cinnamon flavor, - Cinnamon flavor.
- and Jae Seok is vanilla flavor. - Jae Seok is vanilla flavor.
Is Jae Seok 46 years old?
(Seok Jin is 52 years old, and Jae Seok is 46 years old.)
(She even provides the year of manufacture.)
Can you read this?
(Put it down this instant.)
It feels strange.
This is really scary.
It's so big.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin's penalty ends here.
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok's Cage of Death penalty ends.)
Kwang Soo, please go get ready.
(Is it my turn?)
(Kwang Soo is an A plus. Look forward to it.)
(I am not Korean beef.)
The container shook when the crocodile struck it.
(The warriors finally step on land.)
It was scary.
The way it snapped its jaw was very scary.
It's really huge.
- It's really big, right? - Its size is no joke.
- Seok Jin. - Did it look big from the outside?
- It's really big. - It was no joke.
- Does it look big from the outside? - Yes.
- Also, - It's huge.
when the crocodile struck the container,
- it shook. - It left a mark.
It left a mark on the container.
- It left a mark. - It left a mark with its teeth.
You should go inside now.
- This is nice. - You should go inside alone.
- It was... - The cameraman won't go, right?
You will go alone.
Please give me back my glasses.
(I don't have Cameraman Yoon Sang by my side today.)
By the way, the pool Kwang Soo will enter...
has the biggest crocodile that's 5.5m long and weighs 790kg.
It's Lee Byung Hun among crocodiles.
- That's right. - "Inside Men".
(That's the crocodile I will see.)
(Its lack of front legs shows that it had a wild life.)
(Chopper measures 5.5m and weighs 790kg.)
(Kwang Soo, are you here by yourself?)
"The name says it all."
Chopper.
5.5m...
- It looks bigger in the water. - I think it does.
It's three times longer than me.
(Chopper is the king of crocodiles and is bigger than most cars.)
(Kwang Soo finally enters Cage of Death by himself.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Be careful. - Say your last words.
- Say your last words. - It looks dangerous.
Don't say that.
- Say a few words. - Don't say that.
Give me the PIN number of your bank account.
Why would I give you the PIN number of my bank account?
- This is your last chance. - Is it good?
- It's good. - Is it good?
Your money could be lost.
(Be quiet.)
(So Min teases Kwang Soo when he is feeling faint.)
Why would you ask him that?
This could be his last moment.
Kwang Soo.
Why didn't she get picked for this penalty?
(It's fun to watch them.)
- For goodness' sake. - She is so annoying.
(He enters the cage by himself.)
I am really entering the cage by myself.
What is this?
(What is this?)
Where did it go wrong?
I am in a cage by myself.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Hi, Kwang Soo.
- Go away. - Good luck.
Okay, okay.
Where did it go wrong? Where did it go wrong?
I will watch you from below.
(Chopper is waiting somewhere in the pool.)
Where is it? Where is it?
- We will remove the ladder. - Okay.
(The ladder is removed.)
- Don't wet your pants. - I won't.
(He is alone now.)
What is this on the bottom?
There is something.
The bottom is made of a net. That startled me.
Gosh, it's going down. Okay.
It's like going into a pool.
It's like going into a tub.
I'm just soaking half of my body.
She is closing the entrance.
Thank you.
I will be next door to see Chopper.
Yes. Chopper.
(Good luck.)
- See you. - See you.
My goodness.
(The cage begins to move.)
Okay. Okay.
It's like a merry-go-round.
My goodness.
(He pours out words when he is nervous.)
This is crazy.
The bottom is made out of a net.
Is this secure?
It opens.
(He is nervous.)
This is crazy.
I mean...
(Kwang Soo's lonely words fill the cage.)
It opens. It shouldn't open.
All right. Okay.
I can do this. I can.
There isn't a problem. Okay.
(Mumbling)
My goodness.
Okay. Let's go.
(The cage moves toward Chopper's pool.)
Okay.
(In the pool...)
(is Chopper.)
It's big.
- It's really big. - It's big.
(It's really big.)
It's huge.
It's the ferocious one.
(Welcome, Kwang Soo.)
My goodness.
(Chopper is beneath his feet.)
My goodness, it's big.
It's big.
It's too big. The cage is going too near.
No.
Too near!
(He uses his English skills.)
(A close look at a crocodile that measures 5.5m and weighs 790kg)
It's too big.
What was that?
(Splashing)
Okay.
(The cage enters the pool, and the water comes up.)
It's going down.
My goodness.
Chopper. Okay.
(He moves backward.)
Okay.
(He can only say "My goodness" and "What should I do?")
What should I do?
(There is Chopper right before the cage.)
It's right in front of me.
Chopper has a lot of scars.
He must have had a hard life.
I am just going to look at you...
inside this cage.
My goodness.
It's your toy.
(Chopper's favorite toy enters the pool.)
It's too big.
(It doesn't change upon second look.)
(Biting)
Okay.
(Chopper welcomes the yellow ball with enthusiasm.)
(Look at the way it bites.)
It bit the ball.
- Okay, okay, okay. - It's angry.
- My goodness. - How scary!
All right. Here it goes.
Okay.
It bit the ball. Okay.
My goodness.
It's too close.
(After warming up with a ball, Chopper moves toward Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo is wearing a yellow top. - Kwang Soo is wearing a yellow top.
My goodness.
Both the ball and Kwang Soo are yellow.
(Kwang Soo's top is the same color as Chopper's favorite toy.)
His top is the same color as the ball.
After the ball agitates the crocodile...
Well,
it's a coincidence...
that Kwang Soo wore a yellow top.
It's a coincidence.
My goodness.
(To Chopper, Kwang Soo is a bigger ball.)
It bit the ball. Okay. My goodness.
It's too close.
You live up to your name.
Good job, Chopper.
(Biting)
(Flailing)
My goodness.
(That big, yellow ball looks fun.)
I am only standing next to it.
He has...
(The big, yellow ball trembles in fear.)
He has no reason to dislike me.
He has no reason to mind me.
It's too close. It's too close.
(Against Kwang Soo's wish, the cage moves towards Chopper.)
The cage shouldn't go further.
Chopper will get agitated.
Chopper might get agitated.
The cage might touch him.
He might look me in the eyes.
Wait, Chopper is looking in this direction.
(They are close enough to have eye contact.)
He is looking in this direction.
My goodness.
This is...
(This is interesting.)
Where is he going?
(Snapping)
(This is how strong Chopper is.)
(The sound of its teeth sends chills down his spine.)
He is too close.
Gosh, you came so close.
(Chopper circles Kwang Soo like he is on a hunt.)
My goodness. I can't do this.
My goodness.
(Chopper circles Kwang Soo like he is on a hunt.)
My goodness. You are coming in this direction.
(Is it good? Is it a yellow ball?)
(It circles Kwang Soo for a while.)
(Snapping)
(Even from the outside, they feel the power of Chopper's bite.)
It's climbing the cage.
My goodness.
(Chopper lives up to his name as he continues to chop.)
(Calm down, Chopper.)
(Flailing)
He's startled.
It makes you do that with your feet.
It makes you do that.
If feels as if the cage is not there.
It's scary.
- You don't see the cage. - It's scary.
It feels as if you are floating in the water.
(Chopper bites at the cage again.)
The cage got a scratch.
What happened? Gosh.
(Chopper keeps biting at the cage.)
(It has calmed down.)
(It's hovering around the cage.)
What is it doing?
It would have been dangerous without that cage.
(It puts its head close to the cage.)
- It's showing its face. - It moves so fast.
- It's very active. - Gosh.
- Look at that. - Chopper is smiling.
I think he likes him.
(Chopper was trying to attract Kwang Soo's attention.)
The zookeeper thinks you should try to kiss him.
(Kiss?)
(Those who get along with Chopper can kiss him.)
The zookeeper has never seen anyone...
Chopper liked so much.
She thinks...
Kwang Soo should try kissing him.
Kwang Soo is too scared. He's avoiding Chopper.
(Kwang Soo is trying to kiss Chopper, but he's scared.)
- Is he going to kiss him for real? - No.
He can't do that.
- I see. - You mean inside the cage?
- Through the cage? - Yes.
That wasn't our plan.
Kissing is too...
(Kwang Soo, bite the bullet, and kiss me.)
It's too close.
Kiss him.
(Kiss the crocodile.)
This is your chance.
Chopper is doing everything he can...
to save Kwang Soo's part.
(Give me a kiss.)
(I can't kiss him!)
The cage is broken.
(Scared, Kwang Soo steps back.)
This is your chance. Kiss him.
(Do it now.)
Way to go.
Kiss him.
- They're kissing. - He's close.
(Chopper sticks his mouth out.)
(Will Kwang Soo stick his mouth out too?)
(Chopper is so close.)
(His smile intimidates Kwang Soo.)
It's too close.
(Their mouths get close.)
(Kwang Soo and Chopper kiss.)
It's so close.
(They kissed.)
Like in "Free Willy",
- he's communicating... - Communication with a crocodile.
with a crocodile. The boy has grown up.
(Romance with a crocodile)
He's communicating with a crocodile.
Was "Free Willy" about...
- A dolphin in a zoo... - A turtle?
- What? - A dolphin?
(That was close.)
(The crocodile boy comes back.)
- He's here. - Kwang Soo.
It was scary, wasn't it?
- It's huge. - It's big, right?
Chopper seemed to like you.
- Yes. - He didn't want to leave you.
He stayed nearby the whole time.
After you left, it went away.
(I love you, Kwang Soo.)
Anyway,
you've completed the Cage of Death penalty in Australia.
(Cage of Death is completed.)
- Good work. - Let's go now.
- We did it. - Congratulations.
You're the only one who didn't get penalized.
- The penalty is completed. - Yes.
It's time to decide what to do with the remaining Chance Cards.
It's important.
- Are there more? - Yes.
There are two more.
("We will do..." and "We won't go...")
Yesterday, we picked a positive one...
- "We won't go..." - We picked "We will go..."
We picked "We will go..." and one more got penalized.
- Wouldn't "We won't go..." be good? - I think I know.
What?
"We will do..." must be...
"We will do it one more time."
Probably.
- You're probably right. - It makes sense.
"We won't go..."
- "get penalized again." - "Get penalized again."
(We won't get penalized again.)
What if it's, "We won't go home?"
- No way. - It wouldn't make sense.
- You've made a choice. - Yes.
You can choose not to use it too.
- Well... - We'll use it.
We should. "We will go..." was a bad one.
- Exactly. - This one must be a good one.
If we don't use it, the whole things is pointless.
- You want to use it? - Yes.
I don't want to use it.
Please open it.
- So Min. - There are two lines.
- Yesterday, we picked a positive... - Exactly.
Both of them might be bad.
(Their last choice made Seok Jin get penalized.)
Yesterday, we picked a positive one,
- Exactly. - and it turned out to be a bad one.
It was a bad one.
Both of them might be bad.
"Another..."
(Another penalty)
(We won't go receive another penalty?)
Okay!
- "Another penalty..." - "Another penalty..."
- There's another line. - "We won't go..."
"receive another penalty."
(What is the other line?)
There's another line.
- Let's see. - "Another penalty..."
"We won't go home..."
(We won't go home before we receive another penalty.)
"Before we receive..."
- He's crazy. - Are you kidding us?
(Our producer is crazy.)
- Are you kidding us? - What is this?
- What are you doing? - We just celebrated.
What are you doing?
- All of them are bad, aren't they? - Hold on.
- Tell us the truth. - What is this?
You picked the worst one.
- How can we be sure it's true? - What are you doing?
If the other team had picked it, they would have tried Nevis Bungee.
What?
(Nevis Bungee is bungee jumping off a cliff.)
Let me tell you what penalty you'll receive.
This time, there's no cage.
You'll get to see wild crocodiles close up.
It's wild crocodile experience.
(Wild crocodile experience)
He's crazy.
(Wild crocodiles?)
- Wild crocodiles? - You're crazy.
You're crazy.
- Will you stop... - You're overzealous.
if someone gets hurt?
You could have chosen not to use the card.
It was your choice.
It was either "We will go..." or "We won't go..."
We chose a negative one today.
- It should have been a good one. - Yes.
- You said there was a good one. - It was your choice.
The other team took more.
They were the ones you won.
I mean... Listen.
- How could you say that? - Gosh.
- You're evil. - He's crazy.
We won't go home before we do it?
I have to go home.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
If none of you show...
the same thing as I show, you can go home.
(They'll play rock-paper-scissors.)
- That doesn't make sense. - That doesn't make sense.
- Wait. It can be possible. - It can be.
Why do you take his side?
We could all show the same thing.
Do you want to try?
You win if none of you show the same thing as I show.
- Okay. - Don't give a signal.
- So Min. - It was so obvious.
(So Min is bad at doing something secretly.)
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- Rock... - Rock...
(They might have to see wild crocodiles.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Wild crocodile experience.
(Will they escape their bad luck?)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(All of them show scissors.)
- Gosh. - Unbelievable.
- I can't believe it. - It's impossible.
Let's go.
We already saw the crocodiles.
(They have to see wild crocodiles.)
(Meanwhile, in New Zealand,)
(D-Day is here, and it's a beautiful weather.)
Beautiful weather.
It's perfect for Nevis Swing.
Look at that.
Even the weather is nice.
It's New Zealand.
We'll have to go on Nevis Swing.
(They have no choice.)
(The sky is so clear.)
I was hoping for heavy rain.
Haha didn't get any sleep.
I did.
- He had a nightmare. - Really?
He was solving problems.
He was on a quiz show.
And he couldn't solve anything.
(He couldn't solve any problems on a quiz show.)
It's no surprise, is it?
It's not a nightmare.
(It's just like in reality.)
It's...
Man.
Is this the LA weather or the New Zealand weather?
It's the LA weather plus the New Zealand weather.
- What's that? - What?
- What's that? - What's that?
We should have breakfast.
It's good for your health.
- Really? - Try it.
- What's this? - What?
- "Diet water jelly"? - "Diet water jelly"?
It helps lose weight,
but it's also a nice breakfast.
You often skip breakfast.
I don't.
- You guys skip it. - Right.
Drink this every morning.
- Hey. - It's good.
If you drink it,
- you'll be full. - I'm full.
It's a nice start of the day.
All right. As I said yesterday,
you can win a Chance Card by completing a mission.
It's a swing dance mission.
(Swing dance in Queenstown)
(The mission for the last Chance Card begins.)
(They have to attract 30 people within the given time.)
(They do their best to attract the audience.)
(They use all the skills they have.)
(The mission is accomplished.)
Thank you.
- Guys. - Yes.
You'll choose a Chance Card.
There are two left.
One is very good,
and the other is very bad.
("We will receive..." and "We won't receive...")
Okay. "We will receive..." would be better.
- Should we start with this one? - This is it.
No.
We choose this one.
- Have you decided? - Yes.
Would you like to use the card?
- Yes. - Yes.
Take a look at the Chance Card.
(They worked hard to win the last Chance Card.)
- "One of the penalized..." - What is it?
(One of the penalized will not...)
(What will happen to one of us?)
Please, just this once.
(It could be an exemption from Nevis Swing.)
Just this once.
(What does it say below?)
What?
"One will not be penalized."
(One of them will not be penalized.)
"One will not be penalized." Thank you.
- Thank you. I was voted. - What?
(One of them is exempt from Nevis Swing.)
That's amazing.
Seriously. Please save me once, Ji Hyo.
We don't know whom it will be.
It could be me.
(He makes a shocking comment.)
That's true, but everyone else is brave.
- No. - Gosh.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do that.
Let's do it up here.
Right.
- This is how Running Man works. - Yes.
- That's right. - You have to earn it.
- Okay. - Let's go.
This is how Running Man works.
- Can we decide up there? - Yes.
The member to be exempted...
(They head to Nevis Swing.)
What do I do?
It feels real now, Haha.
(Sighing)
We're ascending far.
(40-minute drive from Queenstown)
40 minutes of hiking is very high from the ground.
- Right. - This is 40 minutes of driving.
We're going up to the peak.
This is confusing because...
the view around us is beautiful.
When you think about riding the swing?
When I think about that, I'm angry and scared.
(Thinking of the destination makes him furious.)
(Haha has 17 years of experience in entertainment.)
(This is his fatal weakness in entertainment.)
(He's the biggest coward.)
(When he goes somewhere risky,)
(half of his comments can't be aired.)
(He hasn't gotten over...)
(his fear for extreme rides.)
(It's the most difficult moment of his 17 years in this industry.)
Nevis Swing sounds fun, doesn't it?
(He teases Haha.)
Imagine hanging in the air.
- Walk in the air. - He's a penalty destroyer.
Imagine sitting while hanging in the air.
There's a view of a cliff in front of you.
You're hanging in the air, and the seat is unsteady.
The seat keeps moving.
You never know when you'll fall. Three.
- 2, 1. - 2, 1.
Do you know what I mean?
My goodness.
Do you know the feeling?
- Stop it. - You fall suddenly.
Stop it, Jong Kook.
You hear the wind while you fall.
Stop it!
(Stop it, darn it.)
Are you making sound effects?
It's like the IMAX theater.
(Is this a nightmare with sound effects?)
I can imagine it.
(He's wearing 3-D glasses.)
It's terrible.
I'm breaking out in a cold sweat.
I can't breathe.
Then you should yawn.
(He expresses his concern for him.)
Then your brain gets some oxygen.
(What kind of advice is that?)
Try yawning.
(He encourages him.)
Start.
Come on and yawn. Go.
(Yawning)
Breathe oxygen into your brain. Go.
(Will this help him a little?)
Look at the trees. Aren't they amazing?
(He breathes in during the ride.)
Haha is so funny.
- Are we here? - Where is it?
- We're almost there. - Really?
- I don't see the swing. - We have to go up higher.
We'll ascend in another vehicle.
It's an off-road vehicle.
It's an SUV, Haha's favorite.
- We'll go up in a 4WD. - Yes.
(He makes an engine sound.)
(Stop it, you punk.)
Se Chan might get hit today.
He's my partner, Ji Hyo.
I'll take care of him.
(Otherwise, he might cry.)
- Gosh, we're really going. - Goodness.
Let's go.
I was so nervous in the van.
Give him something to calm down.
(The staff members give him medicine to calm him down.)
Gosh, look at that.
What? Seriously.
(Haha remains silent.)
Fully enjoy the taste.
Breathe in at the same time.
(Enjoy the taste while breathing in.)
Make yourself yawn like this.
Stop it.
Get away.
You're on my team, Haha.
We're here for you.
Look at the dandelion seeds.
- Look at him. - Jong Kook is here too.
He came here to play.
(Standing among dandelion seeds in the air,)
(Jong Kook enjoys the beautiful nature.)
(Look at the sky, Haha.)
(The way to Nevis Swing is beautiful.)
(He's so happy.)
(If only I were a good fighter...)
(He gulps down water.)
(After waiting for 5 minutes...)
The car is here. Let's go.
Let's hurry and finish the shoot.
Let's get it.
(Laughing)
You make me feel reassured...
- Let's go. - a little.
- Let's go. - Let's go now.
He's passionate.
(They head to Nevis Swing.)
(The off-road vehicle moves unsteadily.)
The ride feels great.
It's so unsteady.
(They start to feel it.)
It's how it feels whenever we head to a scary ride.
Goodness.
- Yes! - Yes, man!
(Jong Kook shoots a travel show by himself.)
Remember to breathe, Haha.
- Yawn. - You should yawn.
(Sighing)
It helps you.
Remember that brain lacks in your oxygen.
(Yawning can help.)
Keep yawning.
Did you say, "brain lacks in your oxygen"?
You mean the brain lacks oxygen.
He was too nervous.
Are you nervous?
- Are you nervous? - He must be.
- I'm scared too. - That's why he keeps repeating.
He said, "brain lacks in your oxygen."
- Goodness. - I'm scared too, Haha.
Stop showing me how scared you are.
Okay.
- I'll use a Chance Card. - This is great.
Once we climb up the road, you'll find Nevis Swing.
Which road?
The road over there.
(The road gets rougher.)
It vibrates a lot.
Goodness.
It looks scary on your left side. Don't look.
(It's the edge of a cliff on the left.)
- Don't look, Haha. - It's really scary.
If you fall...
Be quiet.
Keep breathing.
(Let's stay calm.)
That must be it.
(He screams in shock.)
That's incredible.
(Incredible)
Look, Haha.
That's it.
(What did they see?)
(Welcome to Nevis Swing.)
(It's the biggest and the worst swing in the world.)
(Highest speed of 125km per hour, 160m in height, 300m in trajectory)
(It's the marvelous Nevis Swing.)
Haha.
(He's speechless.)
I saw it, Haha.
- This must be it. - It's incredible.
My goodness.
My gosh.
Keep breathing.
(He's lost for words.)
Yawn.
(He keeps suggesting him to yawn.)
Don't cover your face. You can't inhale properly.
Do this as you inhale.
This is insane.
Your hand is sweaty.
(What's going on with you?)
- His hand is sweaty. - I'm sorry.
Give him some medicine.
(He needs to calm down.)
- Can you give me some? - He can't do it.
He can't ride the swing now. Otherwise, he'll die.
(Nevis Swing looks more frightening in real life.)
I have to go to the restroom.
Excuse me, where's the toilet?
(He goes directly to the restroom.)
- Here it is. - Is that it?
Even the restroom sign looks scary.
- Look at the sign. - It's a man falling.
He's falling.
I'm going in.
(They go into the restroom.)
I don't think I can go on the ride.
It's okay, Haha.
- Can you do it? - You startled me.
(Se Chan comforts Haha.)
What's going on?
Se Chan is throwing up.
(He laughs at Se Chan who's throwing up.)
Se Chan.
(Vomiting)
(He kept suggesting to yawn.)
(His nose gets runny.)
I suddenly felt nauseous. Haha?
Goodness.
(He takes some medicine.)
(I'm usually not a coward.)
What are you eating, Se Chan?
I'm eating some candy.
You should yawn.
Yawn.
(Yawning)
I'm being serious.
(He pretends not to be a coward.)
What's going on with me?
I definitely practiced breathing, right?
Acting brave doesn't fit you.
(Now, they know.)
Why did you message me...
to say that you can do it?
(Se Chan sent him a video to encourage him.)
Haha, you can do it.
You're the hero in our hearts.
Haha.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
- Leader of Mapo. - Leader of Mapo.
(You can do it, Haha.)
(How dare you tease me?)
What will you do?
We came all the way here.
(Ji Hyo appears with a camera.)
What is that?
(His eyes are already red.)
- Ji Hyo. - You startled me.
Inside the building,
there's a surveillance camera.
I took a look, and it looks really scary.
(Even Ji Hyo, who doesn't get scared easily, feels nervous.)
He's enjoying the trip alone again. My gosh, there he goes again.
(Jong Kook's "Backpack Travels")
I think the scenery here is very beautiful.
I don't even want to look at him.
My gosh. He's trying to show off his English.
You should just live here.
I'm from the United Kingdom.
- Really? - So...
- "Really"? Unbelievable. - Hey.
Hey, Hothead. Come here. Hey.
- Don't call him. Don't do that. - Should I stop?
- He's not here to meet people. - Yes, that's right.
Give me a minute.
- Don't worry. Don't. - Okay.
I shouldn't worry.
(Haha ventures out to stop this international blind date.)
I drove away like crazy.
I had such a great time.
- These two guys are... - Hi.
- really scared. - I'm Paris.
- You're Paris? - Yes.
(He's about to deliver his punch line after the introduction.)
It's nice to meet you.
Where's the toilet?
(I need to pee.)
(He's blunt and isn't shy at all.)
Show him the toilet, please.
- Thank you. - What's going on with Haha?
(After Haha visits the toilet for the fourth time,)
(they are fully ready to ride Nevis Swing.)
(Meanwhile, in Australia...)
- Where are we now? - I see eagles.
- Is this another... - Where are we?
- What are we doing here? - They are eagles.
- Aren't they eagles? - They are hawks.
- They are hawks. - Seriously? They're hawks?
This feels different.
- Where on earth are we now? - Where are we?
That's a river. It's a river.
My gosh, this place...
I guess we're going by boat.
What are we doing?
Hey, hey, everyone.
- Hi. - Hi.
- This is the thing, right? - Yes?
- Yes. - Are you the crocodile's food?
- What? - What did he say?
He asked if we were the feed for the crocodile.
(They are terrified.)
No.
- Are we the crocodile's food? - Yes.
- No, we are not. - You look tasty.
- No. - No.
(He's joking.)
My name is Tony. Welcome to Crocodylus Park.
You guys are here to help me feed some crocodiles today.
- We didn't hear... - Yes.
We are going to feed the crocodiles?
(It's news to him.)
You won't be in a cage this time. You'll ride the boat...
to meet the wild crocodiles in person.
- What did you say? - It's such a special place.
(Welcome to the tour of wild crocodiles.)
- When did we say we'll feed them? - They haven't eaten anything, no?
(There are basks of crocodiles that are desperate for their meals.)
- It's here. It's here! - Where?
(Looking vicious)
However, one of you must personally feed the crocodiles.
When the crocodile jumps to eat its food,
the other members will try to take a selfie with the crocodile.
- He's talking gibberish. - Look at this guy.
- You are one nasty producer. - Everyone's face must be visible.
(Faces of 4 members including the crocodile's must be in the photo.)
Right now,
this mission is harder than the penalty we just faced...
- over the last three weeks. - Hold on a second.
One of us has to feed the crocodile.
- When we feed the crocodile... - We must do it when it jumps.
He wants them to explain because he's planning to do this mission.
Seok Jin, get out of here.
You're on their side. Get away from us.
- Just trust me. - This is unbelievable.
He's such a traitor.
It's going to be a great clip. I can't wait to try this.
We already tried this ourselves.
Our staff tried to take a selfie...
- when it jumped. - Does it actually jump?
Wait. That's why...
one of the staff members is missing.
(This just got a whole lot scarier.)
(Why are there less staff members?)
- What you're saying is terrifying. - I don't see one of them.
I don't see the staff member.
As long as you don't stick your head or hands,
- they say it's safe. - Who doesn't know that?
If you follow the instructions well, it will be a great experience.
The crocodiles don't jump into the boat?
Can crocodiles come inside?
If you come with me, we'll feed them and make them jump,
and you guys would have to collect the crocodiles' eggs...
- from the nest. - Okay. Goodness.
(His response is late.)
What he said had nothing to do with your question.
They are talking about two different things.
They can't communicate with each other.
- When we try, will they jump? - "Try".
- Yes. - They'll jump?
Do they jump into the boat?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I'll be in the boat too.
And then, we'll head over there.
- They will jump into the boat. - In that case,
we should turn off the engine.
They are talking about two different things.
What are you saying?
(He's frustrated.)
(I'll smile and pretend I got it.)
- Okay. - Okay. Let's go.
My goodness, this isn't what I was expecting.
- This isn't right. - I don't know if they'll jump.
- Hi. - So we're going to feed them.
(They walk into the creepy-looking place.)
This is crazy.
(A tang of fishy smell permeates.)
So Min, this is no joke.
I already...
- smell the spoiled meat they like. - I do too.
- I can smell it too. - It smells like trout.
- My gosh, this is... - I smell the fermented fish.
It's a perfect environment for them.
Look at the color of the water.
(The swamp has a deep green color.)
- It matches the crocodiles' colors. - Exactly.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
How many crocodiles live in the swamp?
40 females and 8 male crocodiles live here.
- They are real crocodiles. - If we fall, we're done for.
If we fall into the water, it's over.
This has a different vibe from the cage.
- This is for Discovery Channel. - Precisely.
- Hey, this is... - It's interesting.
National Geographic would cover something like this.
It's something I'd see in movies.
Didn't Tarzan fight against a crocodile in somewhere like this?
Do you know who Tarzan is?
- This is cool. - It is.
I feel special.
(He feels like he's an explorer.)
Like a giraffe?
Drop it.
At a place like this, impalas are the first ones to die.
(Seok Jin, the impala, is crocodiles' primary prey.)
- They can die while drinking water. - I'm going to run away.
I'm going to run away.
- You applied cologne, didn't you? - Pardon?
The smell of cologne in the jungle is...
signaling the animals to attack you.
Wait. There's a crocodile in the back.
- Where? - A crocodile is in the back.
- Gosh, you startled me. - It's a crocodile.
- A crocodile is in the back. - Where?
(A huge crocodile shows up.)
- It's a real crocodile. - There's one, indeed.
- I didn't know it could be so big. - It's a crocodile.
- The trees make it hard to spot. - There is a crocodile here.
- It's protective coloration. - Yes, it is.
That's not a rock. It's a crocodile, right?
It's a crocodile.
I do feel like I'm in Africa.
- Sorry? - It does feel like that.
This does feel like we're in a jungle.
- There's one over there too. - Where?
Up there?
- There's one. - That one is huge.
- I don't know if it's real or not. - The left one is massive.
It's moving.
- It is moving. - It's going.
I wouldn't know if it's a crocodile or a tree if it doesn't move.
- It looks just like a tree. - Seriously.
- It looks identical. - There's another one next to it.
- You'll be done if you sit on it, - There are a lot.
- mistaking it for a tree. - You bet.
Seok Jin, you shouldn't spray cologne before coming here.
- We're in a jungle. - Who would sit on that?
- Do you think I'm stupid? - I mean...
- There are other places to sit on. - Seok Jin.
You're good as dead if you sit on it after wearing cologne.
- I mean it, Seok Jin. - Who would sit on the crocodile?
- Are there crocodiles underwater? - Yes.
- There are crocodiles at the front. - Where? I can't see.
- They are under the water. - I see the crocodiles.
It's floating on the water.
- I can only see its nose. - Its head is sticking out.
- Don't stick out your head. - It's a crocodile.
Everyone, we'll pull over on the right...
- so you can collect the eggs. - What?
- What? - We're going to collect the eggs?
- Right here? - Yes.
- It's looking at us. - What are you talking about?
- There's a crocodile over there. - There's a crocodile.
What are you getting at?
We're going to get off here?
The zookeeper is going to make sure you are safe.
But the crocodile is staring at us.
I see one over there too.
- There's another one there. - There are tons here.
- How will the zookeeper help us? - There's one more.
There's one more over there.
Here's another one.
They are scattered all over the place.
Only two of you will go and collect the eggs.
- Will the parents let us take them? - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The winners will stay in the boat, right?
Let's set the rules first.
- The winners will stay here. - Exactly.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are here.
(They're the ultimate unlucky pair.)
(Eggs must be collected for them to hatch safely.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Wild crocodiles will be observing the process from somewhere.)
(Which 2 members will get to observe them up close?)
Rock-paper-scissors
(What a surprise! Jae Seok and Kwang Soo win!)
(So Min and Seok Jin will collect the eggs.)
You two may go and collect the eggs now.
(Seok Jin and So Min will enter the nest of crocodiles.)
Promise me that you won't leave me.
Don't worry about that.
They're taking the poles with them.
(He's shocked.)
It must be dangerous here.
The captain must think it's dangerous.
He brought a pole with him.
But the thing is that collecting their eggs...
- is such... - The captain...
- It's a once-in-a-lifetime chance. - Exactly.
- Actually, I want to try this. - So do I.
I will go into Cage of Death.
(I'll rather go into Cage of Death.)
I will let other members try this since they want to do it.
I really want to try this.
- Then do you want to come with me? - Sorry?
- Seok Jin has to go. - Come with us.
Only two of us must try it.
- How about you 2 go for it? - 2 of you must go now.
Seok Jin, we need to film this,
so pretend it doesn't hurt if the crocodile bites you.
- Hey. - Scream when you see...
- the crocodile. - It'll definitely hurt.
Hold on.
- We'll go when it's safe. - When it's safe?
- It must be dangerous over there. - I think so too.
I think things are tense and dangerous.
Everyone here are flustered.
Something must've come. It must've shown up.
- What is it? - They're hitting it.
Look at that. Right now, they are...
- My gosh. - Did you see that?
You want us to go there?
I don't think So Min can cross.
- Is it okay? - Okay.
- Is it safe there? - Up there.
Around the nest. Come this way.
Thank you.
Okay.
Truth be told, I was scared.
Jae Seok, they are real crocodiles.
They are real.
- Hey. - It's no match for haunted houses.
- There's no shelter. - Jae Seok.
- Labyrinth of Fear is make-believe, - My gosh, this is insane.
but this is real.
They are real wild crocodiles.
(This is at another level. This is the real jungle.)
Be careful. Watch out.
Be careful. It's going to start now.
- What am I going to do? - So Min, crocodiles live here.
- I'm serious. - Quiet. They might come.
Okay. I'll be quiet.
- Don't talk too loudly. - There are no crocodiles?
- Hey, be careful. - Yes.
(This is an entirely different kind of experience.)
The eggs won't be deep in the forest, right?
(Can they safely collect the eggs?)
Okay, you guys. This is the nest.
Right here. You will stay here.
The eggs are here?
(The eggs are below So Min and Seok Jin's feet.)
- Right here? - Yes.
The eggs are underneath this?
(This is the nest where the crocodile eggs are kept.)
(The cameraman climbs down to film.)
- The crocodiles are here. - Hey, hey.
(Hey, no! You can't go down there.)
Be careful.
- It's dangerous. - Don't go there.
Don't go near the water.
- There must be crocodiles. - Don't go near the water.
(The crocodiles might attack you.)
Gosh.
Is this...
They're guarding the whole place.
- To prevent any danger. - Yes, just in case.
(They're guarding around the nest.)
They're guarding the place.
This is a wild environment.
If you see here,
they're very delicate.
(Crocodiles laid eggs in the bush.)
(Crocodile eggs)
(There are so many.)
- Are there eggs? - Yes.
- There are so many. - Are they hatched?
- No. - Really?
There are so many.
He's checking the eggs.
He's making sure the eggs will hatch.
(At a low temperature, a female is born.)
He's taking a temperature.
It's 31.5°C.
(At a high temperature, a male is born.)
- Is it good? - It's 31°C.
It's 31°C.
You don't get to see this often.
- When will we get to see it again? - We got to see crocodile eggs.
They're not very big.
- No bigger than chicken eggs. - Right.
Maybe a bit bigger. They're as big as duck eggs.
How did they lay eggs here?
Did they cover up the eggs afterwards?
It's very important that we mark on top of the eggs.
(They draw a line on each egg.)
We mark them all.
What does he mean?
He's drawing on the eggs.
(Why is he doing that?)
- Make sure it doesn't roll. - Okay.
Okay.
It has to stay this way.
They make marks to make sure the eggs don't roll.
I see.
- Interesting. - Very gentle.
Do you want to try?
- There are so many. - There are so many eggs.
They laid a lot of eggs.
There are so many.
(A crocodile lays 15 to 30 eggs at a time.)
They're going to hatch the eggs in a safer environment, right?
Yes.
(They're trying to hatch the eggs safely.)
It's big.
Like this.
It's quite heavy.
(It's heavy.)
You have to be careful.
It's so interesting.
- Is it cold? - It feels like a ping-pong ball.
- No. - I think it'll feel warm.
It really feels like a ping-pong ball.
- It's like a ping-pong ball. - It's like plastic.
Is it smooth?
They said it felt like a ping-pong ball.
You're being sensitive.
- I was just asking. - They said...
it was like plastic.
- We're good. Are you all right? - They're coming back.
- Crocodiles are coming. - They're coming back.
(Crocodiles are approaching.)
Are the parents coming?
If you don't go near the nest, it'll be all right.
They're keeping them out by tapping on their heads.
- Really? - The parents are coming.
Hurry up, please.
I feel a bit bad.
You don't have to. We're trying to...
Last few. We're almost there.
They're making sure...
the eggs hatch safely.
- It's for their safety. - But the parents don't know it.
- They don't. - No.
But the babies will be released back here, right?
- What if they don't recognize them? - Hold on.
- Hey. - This doesn't seem right.
You say that because you don't have your own babies yet.
They will recognize them. What are you saying?
The babies will look like them. They can recognize their babies.
(Are you sure?)
I don't think everything will fit in there.
(They cover the eggs with grass.)
- Okay. Oh, like that. - You cover them up.
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
- When will we get to do this again? - I'm getting scared.
This is such a rare experience.
Exactly.
Engrave this moment to your eyes and heart.
You were so happy when you won the rock-paper-scissors.
- Who? - You were so happy.
We were being generous.
- You're dealing with lives. - Seriously.
We gave up on this opportunity...
so you can experience it.
As if. You were so happy.
- It's the last egg. - Okay.
(They handle the last egg carefully.)
(They're done collecting the eggs.)
- My goodness. - They're so precious.
The eggs will hatch...
in the laboratory.
Artificially.
After that, they'll release the babies back here.
After hatching them safely,
- when they... - With these hands.
can survive on their own.
These hands contributed to...
the preservation of crocodiles.
(These hands contributed to the preservation of crocodiles.)
Do you have your own show or something?
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
You always seem to be shooting something on your own.
What's with you?
(She shot a show on her own in front of the crocodile cage.)
(They're onto her.)
Are you shooting a show on your own?
(Did you all see it?)
Who are you talking to?
She talks to herself a lot.
My goodness.
(So Min's show continues.)
It looks...
It looks like a place...
- from a movie. - It looks like maesaengi soup.
- What? - Maesaengi?
- There's a crocodile. - It's a big one.
(A crocodile appeared.)
You see only the head.
- It's a crocodile. - We're in the wild.
(A crocodile is looking at their boat.)
How do they jump?
You can feed them whenever you want.
Let me know when you're ready.
Decide who is going to feed them.
It's been decided that So Min will do it.
(5 minutes before departure)
So Min should do it.
I'll do it.
Be careful. It might eat you.
Who's going to do it?
So Min.
(They all say So Min should do it.)
Breathe.
Gosh, you're unbelievable.
- There's no need to waste time. - Breathe before you answer.
It'd time to feed the crocodiles.
The zookeeper will demonstrate first.
- It's meat. - It's steak.
Are you hungry?
It looks very fresh.
(Prepare food crocodiles like.)
As we go up here,
you'll see Popper.
Put the food out like this.
(Put the food out as if you are fishing.)
It looks like he's fishing.
Watch.
(Attract the crocodile's attention by bouncing the food off the water.)
And then...
Popper, come on.
- Popper? - Popper.
- Popper. - Pop.
(It's called Popper.)
- Popper. - It pops up.
Like popcorn.
- Gosh. - Come on, Popper.
- It's here. - Where?
(Give me my food.)
(It pops up just like its name.)
(I can't do that.)
(It snatches the meat.)
She ate it.
(They see it for the first time.)
(Fascinating)
(They break into applause.)
Now, you guys have to do it.
- Okay. - Do you want to go first?
She'll try.
- Okay. - So Min.
Seriously...
- Do a good job. - When will you get to do it again?
- You should be honored. - Can you take a picture?
- That's ribs. - Give it to me.
I'm scared. They'll eat it?
- There's one. - There's one.
- Look at that. - Over there.
(They found a crocodile.)
- Let's get ready. - Let's get ready.
(Both So Min...)
(and the other members are nervous.)
Come on.
Are you taking a selfie?
- No. - Yummy.
We all have to be in the picture.
- All of us? - Yes.
- Yes. - Come on.
- We all have to be in it. - It's not a selfie?
- Where did it go? - Hey.
Are you ready?
- Yes. - It's there.
(Will they succeed in feeding the crocodile?)
Her name is Cinderella.
- Cinderella. - Cinderella.
(She suddenly feels familiar.)
(Will she come close?)
- Cinderella. - I can't see her.
- It's in the water. - It's coming here.
(It suddenly disappeared.)
Dip it.
(Bubbles)
It's coming.
- It's there. - I see bubbles.
(She's approaching.)
- Cinderella. - It's going away.
Inside there is Casanova.
- Casanova? - Casanova?
(A crocodile called Casanova?)
It's called Casanova.
That one is Casanova. It's funny.
Casanova!
My phone number is...
(Call me, will you?)
(Casanova is So Min's type.)
Why would you tell him your phone number?
I was born in 1986.
How old are you?
- Come on. - Deeper.
- Yummy. - It's like rowing.
(Yummy)
It's delicious.
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
- Is this a children's show? - Kids come if you do this.
(Yummy. Come on.)
Won't they?
If I was a kid, I'd never come.
I'd never come.
Come on, crocodile.
We're going to give them a big one.
Look at the color.
- It's a lot of meat. - It's a lot.
It's a family set.
- Come. - That one is called Sunshine.
Come.
- It's coming. - Dip the meat.
Dip it.
- Where is it? - Over there.
It's coming. Crocodile.
Come on, Sunshine. Let's go.
- It's coming. - Sunshine.
- Sunshine. - Sunshine.
- Sunshine, come on. - It's coming.
(They have to feed her and take a picture.)
(Look)
(Can we take the picture now?)
- Is it here? - No.
No. The meat dropped.
(Only the rope is left.)
(The meat dropped.)
- Give us more meat. - Give us more meat.
Let's use this.
Move over. I'm coming.
Dropping the meat might not be a bad thing.
It came off.
(He keeps moving in vain.)
Is it here?
It feels like I'm washing the meat.
When will you get to eat something like this?
- Sunshine. - Sunshine.
- When will you... - Sunshine.
They must be resting.
The meat became white.
We washed it too much.
All the blood got removed.
(Calling for the crocodile)
(Crying like a rooster)
What kind of sound is that?
They might run away.
Are they coming?
So this was our penalty.
(The sound of labor)
This was the penalty.
The sun is about to set.
It's about to set.
I'm the one who lost.
Use this. Let it go.
(They try to lure another crocodile.)
Don't put out your hand.
- My hand? - There's one over here.
- Here's one. - Is it coming?
(They badly want to succeed.)
- Stay still. - It's coming.
- It's coming. Please. - It's yummy.
- Jae Seok isn't in the frame. - Prepare the camera.
- Prepare the camera. - Jae Seok.
- It's coming. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Come this way, Jae Seok.
- I'm so scared. - I'll do it.
Wait, I'll do it.
Excuse me. Can you take our picture?
Please?
- Come in the frame. - Here it is.
- It's yummy. - He's not in the frame.
- It's yummy. - Goodness.
(Even when a crocodile approaches,)
- Take a photo now. - Do it.
(they can't take a photo.)
It's yummy.
- Take a photo now. - Take it.
Take a photo.
- Hurry and take a photo. - No.
Take a photo now.
- Goodness. - The crocodile left.
Move one of the rods away.
Where did it go?
There's a bigger one. Do you see it?
- What's that? - It's a bigger crocodile.
(Did a bigger crocodile appear?)
- It's bigger. - Be careful.
- What's going on? - Goodness.
They found out that we have food.
Come this way.
- Get ready. - Wait.
- Do it slowly. - Come in the frame.
Do it slowly.
You have to be in the frame, Jae Seok.
- I'm too scared to do it. - Come on.
(They're startled by the crocodile's gesture.)
(The red teeth look gruesome.)
My goodness.
- Gosh. - The meat fell off.
- Goodness. - You got it.
- Get in the frame. - Oh, no.
- Gosh. - The meat fell off.
You have to be in the photo.
- Seok Jin. - Let's take a photo.
(Let's take a photo.)
- It's here. - Seok Jin.
Come in the frame.
- Come in the frame. - Kwang Soo.
The crocodile is ready to jump.
Turn around, Jae Seok.
I have to keep watching.
(Either he took a selfie alone,)
(or he took one without any crocodile.)
Kwang Soo.
Did you see the red teeth?
- Pardon me. - We're doomed.
- We're doomed. Take it out. - Wait.
- What's going on? - Take it out.
- Wait. - Did I get it on camera?
- Let's calm down. - Relax.
(He holds the stick with a camera.)
It's hiding.
It went back in the water.
(The camera gets stuck in the tree.)
We're doomed. We have to take it out.
Goodness.
(What they filmed today got lost.)
(What should we do now?)
I'm sorry. It got stuck in the tree.
Was it filmed?
(Everyone looks at the water.)
- Is that it? - Yes.
We can take it out.
Thankfully, it's standing up.
(Jae Seok is quite flustered.)
Did we lose everything?
All we have to do is take it out.
Can you take it out?
(It's a moment of risk.)
(An assistant boat comes to rescue.)
- Okay, grab it. - Goodness.
(Please save our camera.)
It's over here.
(All staff members hope that the camera will be saved.)
Okay.
(He successfully takes out the camera.)
He got it.
(Jae Seok is relieved about the camera.)
It's still stuck in the tree.
Thank goodness.
- There we go. - What a relief.
I'm so relieved.
I'd be exasperated if we lost what we shot.
- You'd feel bad. - Did you see...
Chul Min yell at me in anger?
(We're doomed.)
(We have to take it out.)
(We have to take out the camera!)
I'm sorry. We almost lost what we shot.
When Chul Min said that we were in trouble,
he said it while looking at you.
- I'm sorry, Chul Min. - He did that.
While holding the camera,
I didn't want to damage the tree.
So many things happened.
Things can get wild in nature.
Thank you, thank you very much.
- Yes. - You're welcome.
We should have succeeded.
All we needed was a photo.
We had a chance,
but Jae Seok dropped the camera.
(Jae Seok is the troublemaker.)
Why do you cause trouble?
- He's such a troublemaker. - Seriously.
- Jae Seok. - He's a troublemaker.
Gosh, Jae Seok.
I'm sorry, So Min.
- You're as bad as me. - I'm sorry.
It's the last one.
- Isn't it the last one? - It's fine.
- They might come. - We used most of the bait.
Isn't it fun?
(Kwang Soo puts on bait.)
(What happened?)
- In reality... - Did it fall?
- Did it fall? - The meat fell in.
There are troublemakers everywhere.
He was the one who dropped it,
but I can't say anything in English.
Gosh.
- He's a troublemaker. - You're a troublemaker.
(He shows his anger with facial expressions.)
- Okay. - Go get it.
- Okay. - Okay.
Be careful.
The meat turned white.
(They keep fishing.)
Are there three?
(A crocodile pops up.)
- Bring the camera. - Hold it up.
- Hold the camera higher. - Hold it up.
(They're determined to go home.)
Higher.
- Get the camera. - Do it.
- Let's do it. - It's as if...
It's coming.
- It's as if the fish is jumping. - It's coming.
(They're feeling lucky.)
It's coming. Come on.
(What happened?)
What have you done?
- It's as if the fish is jumping. - It's coming.
(He lets the crocodile take the bait.)
- Goodness. - I'm sorry.
- You're such a troublemaker. - Stop it.
I'll do it better.
- It's here. - Goodness, Jae Seok.
It's eating the meat.
- Take a photo now. - Take it.
Take a photo.
- Take it. - Get in the shot.
Get in the shot.
We got a photo.
You're such a troublemaker.
What's wrong with you today?
He won't come because he's full.
- He ate and left. - No way.
We finally had a chance after three hours.
- Goodness. - I'm sorry.
- You're such a troublemaker. - Stop it.
I'll do it better.
- It's here. - Goodness, Jae Seok.
It's eating the meat.
- Take a photo now. - Take it.
Take a photo.
- Take it. - Get in the shot.
Get in the shot.
We got a photo.
You're such a troublemaker.
What's wrong with you today?
He won't come because he's full.
- He ate and left. - No way.
We finally had a chance after three hours.
The crocodile is in the photo.
- Is it? - Yes.
It looks clear.
(They take a photo with the crocodile.)
The crocodile looks clear.
- We got the photo. - This is amazing.
- It has meat in the mouth. - Approved.
(They successfully take a photo with a crocodile.)
Okay.
Goodness.
Why did you drop it?
All three of you are cursing at me at once.
You're such a terrible troublemaker.
- Seriously. - Goodness.
My throat became sore from screaming so much.
Gosh.
You have one last Chance Card.
- Aren't we done? - I hope it's a good one.
- What do you want to do? - Let's not take it.
You may check what it is after rejecting it.
- We reject it. - How about...
What do you think, So Min?
I want to reject it.
- How about you? - I want to take it.
- How about you? - I prefer to rest after this.
It's 2 to 1.
- How about you? - I want to reject it.
- It's 3 to 1. - I'll reject it.
- We'll reject it. - You decided to reject it.
- Yes. - Take a look.
(They reject the Chance Card.)
There has to be something good.
(What was written on the Chance Card?)
What is it?
"You may go to..."
I'll take it.
Take a look first.
(You may go to a restaurant of your choice.)
A restaurant?
This isn't right.
Goodness.
(He punches everyone.)
(I said that we should take it.)
(He can't control his anger.)
I'll buy it for you.
Let's go.
(Their mission is over.)
I'll treat you.
(Team New Zealand stands in front of the swing.)
- Let's take a look. - I can't do it.
Let's check it out.
What's that bridge for?
We have to cross the bridge to get there.
Is that it?
That's why it's like the Golden Gate Bridge.
This is...
(It's a bridge over a cliff.)
(A bridge over a cliff)
(It's the only route to the Nevis Swing.)
(If you want the swing, you must cross the bridge.)
My gosh. Look below.
I can't even cross that.
There's bungee jumping next to it.
Oh, dear.
There's bungee jumping.
(Haha and Se Chan start gagging again.)
(Jong Kook is taking a selfie.)
How are we supposed to cross this?
(Looking at it makes him sigh.)
Nevis.
Do we go this way?
(He pops in.)
No, there are holes.
(Are you guys scared? I'm excited.)
(I'm excited too.)
It's moving.
(Once you cross the scary bridge,)
(it's the Nevis Swing.)
(Before they start, they must be trained for safety.)
- What's this? - Fill out this one.
You have to fill it out.
- Is this a memorandum of some sort? - You have to fill it out.
First name.
It's Dong Hoon. My surname is Ha.
It's Ha Dong Hoon?
- Okay. - Please, please. Help me.
- Killing me softly. - He just threw up.
(They're registered.)
You four?
- These two are going. - Are you guys going together?
- Together, yes. My crew. - You're going to be fine.
My hero.
All right. So what's your name?
Your name.
(He's silent.)
Haha.
- This one? - Yes.
(He's funny.)
- Take your hat off. - Your hat.
Make sure there's nothing in your pockets.
He's going to weigh you.
(Once you're registered, they weigh you.)
They're going to weigh me?
(My weight?)
Take your hat off.
Are you going to film this?
(She's hesitant.)
With clothes on, you're much heavier than expected.
Don't worry. You have clothes on.
Your clothes must be very heavy.
- Step on. - My gosh.
Are you going to film this?
Step on. Stay still.
(She steps on the scale.)
Oh, my goodness.
He's not allowed to say that.
- He's not allowed to say. - I think it's a secret.
I have my clothes on.
Okay.
(They get safety training and put equipment on.)
How do you say, "Please make it tight"?
Can you make it tighter?
(He tries his best to tighten the safety belt.)
If it's a little bit loose, that's okay.
There's a chance game, right? Why am I nervous?
These guys here,
they have to sit down but upside down.
Okay.
You guys are doing upside down?
You guys are doing upside down, yes?
- What? - Upside down?
- Do you want to go upside down? - Upside down?
No way.
I want to stay upright.
He says no.
- I want to stay upright. - It's not upside down.
(He almost said yes.)
- Strong? - Yes.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are relaxed.)
(He's laughing, and she's dancing.)
Okay, guys. Are you ready?
- Yes. - Ready.
Time to go.
- Go? - Yes.
Challenge yourselves.
- Okay. - Challenge yourselves.
- Okay. - Yes.
(He roots for them in Korean.)
Don't worry. No problem.
(I hope you don't change your mind.)
(The safety training is done. They are off to the Nevis Swing.)
Let's get it.
You can do it.
I don't think I can do it. I think I have to give up.
(They can't even look at it.)
My goodness. Hold on.
(He's shocked.)
Look at that.
(Jong Kook steps on.)
- My gosh. - I can't go.
(Wait for us, Jong Kook.)
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
You can't go.
Haha can't cross.
- Hurry. - Look forward.
(On top of a tall cliff...)
It's so long.
(On top of a tall cliff, the bridge hangs.)
This is driving me crazy.
I can't do this, Ji Hyo. What should I do?
What do I do?
Don't look down.
He's incredible.
He's insane.
(They watch Jong Kook go...)
(and gather up the courage to start.)
Here we go.
Byul.
What do I do?
This is driving me crazy.
Look forward. Look far.
(They're cautious.)
Don't look down.
I'm serious.
My gosh.
Bring your legs to the sides.
- There's a gap in the middle. - This is unbelievable.
(Jong Kook is filming everything.)
(They only look straight ahead.)
- This is insane. - It's shaking.
Bring your legs to the sides.
There's a gap in the middle.
(When does this bridge end?)
Why are we even here?
Don't shake it, Jong Kook.
Don't shake it.
Oh, my goodness.
(Jong Kook arrives first and looks down.)
My gosh. This...
(They're almost here.)
My foot is about to go numb.
I'm focusing too much strength in my toes.
This is like a scene from "Silmido".
I looked down.
(They finally reach the end.)
(Isn't that enough for a penalty?)
Mission complete.
(My legs are giving out already.)
It's high.
(It's time to use the exemption card.)
You startled me.
(Burping)
Burping is a type of breathing.
It's a type of breathing. Good job.
Good job, Haha.
What did I do wrong?
I'm sorry if I did anything wrong.
This is really scary.
Everybody, since you successfully completed the swing dance...
(They got a chance card from completing a mission.)
- You have a chance card. - Right.
(They completed the swing dance, so they got an exemption chance.)
(One person won't be penalized.)
Who will be exempted?
If you pick the exemption card,
you can use it, give it up,
or not use it.
Okay.
- This is unbelievable. - Haha...
is crying right now.
- He's really crying. - This is unbelievable.
(I cry sometimes in front of the swing.)
This is unbelievable.
Please pick. One at a time.
(Out of 4 cards, only 1 is an exemption card.)
(Who is going to be that one person?)
I'll take this.
Please take it.
Please show me in three.
Do you want this?
Who wants to switch?
(He's easily influenced.)
No, it's okay.
Look at his face.
Ready.
One,
two...
(Who will be exempted?)
Three.
(Jong Kook is exempted.)
(He's the least scared of them all.)
I'll live as your slave all my life.
(Collapsing)
For the rest of my life,
I'll live as your dog.
Don't do this.
Please, Jong Kook.
After we got here,
I don't think I can do it.
I can't do it after seeing that.
This is brutal.
Since he picked the exemption card...
Please, Jong Kook.
I'm serious.
Look at me, Jong Kook.
- It's me, Jong Kook. - What?
It's me.
It's me, Ha Dong Hoon.
- All right. - Give it to him.
Since "X-Man", right?
When you conquered...
all three music awards,
who was next to you?
I was there.
(It was me, Ha Dong Hoon.)
(Do you remember the days?)
(We used to sweep "X-Man" as a team.)
(It's been 13 years,)
(and we are still a team.)
This is heartbreaking.
Please become Dream and So Wool's godfather.
This looks really scary.
- You should try that. - Haha,
hold this.
(Grabbing)
Haha.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Se Chan.
(Were you scared, Haha?)
Thank you very much.
What is your decision, Jong Kook?
One,
- two, - Thank you.
three.
(Ripping)
(He hesitates...)
(and rips the exemption card.)
What was that?
(This is not a paused screen.)
What was that, Jong Kook?
Let's do it together.
We came this far.
(Let's go on it together.)
(Punching)
- Do you think this is funny? - Wait.
Do you find this funny?
He's really mad.
(Give it back.)
No.
No!
This can't be happening.
(It's a puzzle.)
I'm sorry. I'm not pretending.
This is for real. I'm serious.
Sir,
please take this.
(I put it together. Isn't this good enough?)
- Haha. - I'll do anything.
This doesn't say the right word.
This won't work.
(It's missing a piece.)
- This won't work. - Please.
Please help me.
- Haha. - What do I do?
It's not the right word, so it doesn't count.
(Punching)
(You're just like Jong Kook.)
(They all get to go on Nevis Swing.)
Let's go.
Let's get it. Come on.
This feels like a dream.
I'm going on this? Me?
Me? I'm going on this?
(He's going mad.)
You need to breathe.
Breathe.
(He's enraged.)
I need to imagine.
Dream, you are down there.
So Wool is down there as well.
There's a war, so I have to save you.
Aliens have invaded.
I'm coming to save you.
(He hypnotizes himself.)
Daddy is coming to save you.
This looks so scary.
Okay, let's do this.
Let's go.
(Will the two cowards be fine?)
(The reality is in front of him.)
We're going to walk straight.
- What? How? - Yes?
- What did she say? - Come on.
- Come on. - You're going to be strong.
No, I'm going to die.
He said he's dying.
(They lost all motivation in front of the cliff.)
From now on?
- You go first. - No.
We'll go together.
Come on.
- How? We're going to die. - What do I do?
You can move it back.
You got to stand all the way up.
(She's too kind.)
It's fine, okay?
(Why are you doing this to me?)
Can you tell her to hold me?
All right.
I need you to come up here so that I can keep you nice and safe.
(It's difficult just to get on the swing.)
- Okay. - Lie down.
Hands down.
(They put safety equipment on at the end of the cliff.)
Hold on. Is this okay?
I think it's tangled.
Be careful.
Dream. So Wool.
Please make it tight.
- Tight. - Strong.
Please.
Tight.
- When you sit down... - Me too.
When you sit down, I'll tighten it up.
We're going to get a double-check.
- Double-check. - Double-check. Triple-check.
- Hold on. - Hold on.
(Once they check, it's time to jump.)
Be careful, sir.
(They check the equipment for the cowards.)
All ready, team.
How are we supposed to sit?
Hold on.
- Hold on. - How do we position ourselves?
- Keep looking up. - How do you say it in English?
My hands are shaking. Wait.
Oh, my goodness. My legs aren't touching the ground.
(They're in mid-air.)
- What's this? - Dream.
- A little bit more. - Hold on.
So Wool.
(What are we doing?)
Hey, hey! Hey.
Hey...
(Cursing)
(This is a real situation.)
(They're at the descending point.)
Hold on.
(They're 160m high. The cliff is under them.)
I'm doing this for you, Dream.
I love you, Byul.
I love you. I love you, Se Chan.
- In three... - I love you, Haha. Hold on.
Two.
Two,
- one. - Please.
- Two, - Hold on.
(They descend.)
(Groaning)
(They form a parabola as they go down.)
(It's the fiery swing.)
Oh, my goodness.
(She's terrified.)
Oh, my goodness. Where are they?
- Where are they? - Oh, my goodness.
(Their faces are distorted.)
It's the cliff!
The cliff!
(They run into the cliff.)
It's the cliff.
(The swing moves back before they hit it.)
Dream and So Wool.
Se Chan. Byul. Running Man. My fans.
Wait. Look up. Don't look down.
My hands are numb. Look up.
(The swing is done now.)
Look at the water.
This is insane.
My hands are numb.
Se Chan, I can't help you.
They couldn't even scream.
They couldn't even...
(They finally speak.)
This is beautiful.
Look down.
Breathe.
Breathe now.
(Breathe in.)
Do it.
Mom.
You know what?
I've done many things in my life,
but there's nothing as scary as this.
(It felt like it was never going to end, but they're done now.)
- Se Chan. - Near the beginning...
I'm still not myself.
- I was so scared. - This is going to drive me nuts.
Running Man... I don't like you.
This is the penalty of your life, Haha.
This looks more scary. Look.
(It's not easy coming back up.)
- They look so shabby. - Oh, my goodness.
Look at them from the back. They look so shabby.
Hey, hey. My legs.
My hands are numb as well.
Are we going up?
Yes, we are almost there. Don't look.
What was that?
(Their shoulders look weak after what they've gone through.)
- It's windy. - Hey.
I hate this sound.
- Hurry. Speed it up. - Hurry. Pass.
- Speed it up. - Quick. Hurry up.
- Don't look. - Please.
"Speed it up."
(They want to speed it up.)
(This extreme sport makes you speak English.)
Please.
- Hurry. Speed it up. - Really.
All done.
(They hold their heads up until the end.)
Going down is not the end.
(Are we finally done?)
My legs.
(Hitting)
(My legs)
Wave at the camera.
- Good. - Good job.
(We're finally standing on something.)
Sorry. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, my brother. - Jong Kook.
- Okay. - That wasn't good?
No, that wasn't.
That wasn't it.
Okay, give me that.
- Okay. - Jong Kook.
My hands went numb.
(They've earned Jong Kook's respect.)
I give you my respect.
(The first team successfully finishes their mission.)
(It's time to get ready for the second team.)
- Sorry. - Sorry.
(They return in glory.)
Wow, fantastic.
(He sounds excited.)
Encore.
(They're so cool.)
(Everybody on land knows how great we are.)
Nevis Swing.
Nevis.
- Swing. - I say, "Nevis", you say, "Swing".
- Swing. - Swing.
Good job.
Where is the restroom?
Why were you falling for so long?
- It's not a swing. It just drops. - It's just... This is just...
(It's beyond your imagination.)
This is really...
The water...
approaches you.
Stop lying. You had your eyes closed.
- You closed your eyes. - I opened them in the middle.
I couldn't even scream.
We didn't hear you scream.
You make this sound.
(You can't even breathe.)
(He expressed himself with his face.)
My goodness.
(Now that I think about it,)
(we're pretty great.)
Come here.
Let's pick something.
We have to show off.
Wait. Excuse me.
Is this free size?
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook can pick a different color.
- No, they can't pick one. - They can't.
They didn't go on the swing.
But we're here. We have to get one too.
- You didn't go on it. - That's mean.
This shirt is only for people who went on it.
We, Nevis swingers, wear hoodies.
It's only for those who went on it.
Do you want sunglasses as well?
Let's get everything with the swing on it.
- Top and bottom. - What should we do?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Let's perform our ritual first.)
(Nevis swingers do the swing dance after going on the swing.)
(Did you see that, rookies?)
- Nevis. - Swing.
(Look forward to how Jong Kook and Ji Hyo do it.)
Let's do it.
Nevis.
- Nevis. - Swing.
(If you want to be cool, follow the Nevis swingers.)
(Be like us.)
We're back again.
I'm so envious of how relaxed he is.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo get ready to descend.)
Both of them have such calm faces.
How are they so different?
They are incredible.
Ji Hyo, I love you. Jong Kook, I love you.
Don't worry. Even I did it.
It's comforting, right?
(Nodding)
In middle...
In the middle...
As you come up,
you should yawn a few times.
You will want to yawn.
You will want to yawn. Make sure you yawn.
It looks like Jong Kook is a bit nervous.
It's impossible not to be nervous.
I am really nervous.
- You are nervous, right? - Yes. I am scared.
(They become nervous when they face the swing.)
I am trembling once again.
(I am trembling once again now that I am here.)
- Are you okay? - What?
- Are you okay with being here? - I can do this.
- Like a man... - Don't do that.
Like a man, I will watch them go.
You will get yourself killed. Come here.
(Come on.)
Take your words back.
I take my words back.
I don't want you to die.
(Come here, Se Chan.)
I became scared again. This is driving me crazy.
- Do you have a lip balm? - Come here.
- Be quiet. - It's okay.
- Let's hold each other tight. - Let's hold each other tight.
- That's right. - Hold on tight.
Watching others do it makes me scared too.
- All right. - All right.
- Are you guys ready? - Yes.
All right. All right.
There they go.
All right. Come on in.
Haha, come here.
(They finally face the cliff.)
My goodness.
- My goodness. - Come all the way up.
You got this.
Turn around back towards me.
- Are you guys all right? - All right.
Keep going backwards.
(They even turn around.)
- Backwards? - Are they riding it backwards?
Are you riding it backwards?
(What is going on?)
They are crazy.
(Are they riding it backwards?)
There.
(Laughing)
(Why is he laughing?)
Haha, come here.
Do you guys realize what you are doing...
is the most extreme way?
- Yes, I heard. - Cool.
(It's the most extreme way of riding the swing.)
- My goodness. - Good luck.
(Have a safe trip.)
Oh, my goodness.
All right. Take a step back.
Are they really going to do this?
Sit back.
(I hope they will be okay.)
- All right. - I hope you find it a good one.
All right.
- Behind? Okay. - We are all set.
- All right. Take a seat. Get comfy. - Sit.
(The fearless duo is ready for the drop.)
Take a seat. Get comfy.
- Sit. Just sit. - Yes. Just sit.
(The 1st stage is letting the swing support your weight.)
- My palms are sweating. - Are you ready?
All right. Okay.
(The 1st stage is letting the swing support your weight.)
Are you ready? I want to explain how to get upside down.
What's going to happen is, I want to raise you up higher.
When you are out there, you are going to lean back.
Your legs are going to come around the outside of the straps.
Around. Then lock the position.
- Our legs. Okay. - Yes.
- Your legs. Go wide. - Okay.
You can come up that way.
- Are you guys ready? - All right.
(After the explanation, only the drop remains.)
They are so brave.
Well, go upside down.
- Upside down? - Yes.
- Right now? - Yes.
- Okay. - How will you do that?
(Go upside down.)
- Right now? - Yes.
(Do they need to lie down in the air?)
- Inside? - What are they doing?
Then the other leg.
- It doesn't work for me. - Inside?
Look at them.
- Like this? - I can't watch.
- This is crazy. - Look at them.
(The 1st stage is leaning back in the air.)
- This is crazy. - Link your feet to the swing.
- Why would you do that? - Ji Hyo, link your feet.
- Like this? Is this okay? - Did I do it right?
- This foot? - No, it's the other way.
Push and turn just like that.
Okay.
- What are they doing? - Like this.
All right. Now, let's go.
- This is crazy. - Jong Kook, this is really scary.
Here they go.
(Laughing)
- He is laughing. - Are you guys ready?
Yes, we are ready.
(Are you guys ready?)
Yes.
(They face the worst fear in the most extreme position.)
(The countdown starts.)
- Three. - Okay.
Two.
One.
(Get ready...)
(and shoot.)
One.
(This isn't a work of computer graphics.)
(His jaw drops.)
Did we do that?
Oh, my goodness.
(Hanging upside down, they swing down the cliff.)
My goodness.
(It's time to swing back.)
We're falling for way too long.
(Laughing)
(It's more fun to ride the swing upside down.)
This is unbelievable. This is unbelievable.
- Respect! - Big respect!
Big respect!
Hero! My hero!
I bet blood will rush to their heads.
How do I say that in English?
Haha, how do I say that in English?
Blood puke.
Puke?
(I am right.)
(Their faces are red...)
This is hilarious.
(because blood rushed to their heads.)
(That's why this is the most extreme position.)
I feel dizzy.
Did they tell us to sit on our way up?
Did they?
- Shall we try sitting up? - Shall we?
Let's go.
(Struggling)
Jong Kook, this is much better.
Gosh, I felt like I was dying.
- We're going up. - It's beautiful down there.
This is incredible.
(They now notice the beautiful scenery below them.)
I can see the scenery now.
I couldn't see it earlier since blood was rushing to my face.
How was it? Was it good?
- It was incredible. - It was incredible.
Jong Kook, the first drop was really scary, right?
When we fell upside down...
(He laughs until the end.)
I could only laugh.
He is laughing. He is laughing again.
What's so funny about that?
Aren't you scared now?
- Why is he laughing? - Did you yawn?
- We are fine. - We are fine now. At the bottom,
we couldn't open our eyes because blood rushed to our heads.
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
You are truly the ace.
- They can do anything. - You put me to shame.
You are the ace, and I'm the Nevis.
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook's extreme ride is a success.)
Good job.
(We have so much respect for you.)
(With Jong Kook and Ji Hyo completing the penalty...)
It's indescribable, right?
Thank you.
(All 4 members of Team New Zealand clear the mission.)
Ji Hyo, you are incredible.
It was unbelievable.
You will get the hoodie now.
- Haha. - Hoodie!
- I will get the hoodie now. - Yes.
This is touching.
People's Recommendation Project, A Place for 1 Percent.
The Nevis Swing penalty is completed.
(The Nevis Swing penalty is completed.)
Finally!
We are finally done with it.
- Number 26. - Number 27.
Number 30.
31.
- Nevis... - Nevis...
- Swing! - Swing!
(The Global Penalty Tour, the end)
Same Money, Different Dreams Race.
(Same Money, Different Dreams?)
(Everyone is given a suitcase that is filled with money.)
(Decide whether to empty the suitcase...)
(or fill the suitcase.)
(Emptying saves the team, and filling saves an individual.)
(The money-related dilemma is endless.)
(In this race,)
(everything is about money...)
(and for money.)
(Decide between the victory of an individual...)
(and the victory of the team.)
(What lies at the end of this dilemma?)
(Same Money, Different Dreams Race)