It's Running Man Member's Week.
(The sixth member is...)
(Yu Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok's week offers more than any other member's week.)
(Kim Yong Man, Kim Won Hee, Lee Chun Hee, Heo Kyeong Hwan, KCM)
(Jae Seok's strong friends have come to teach the members a lesson.)
Don't tense up.
(This is a very large scale battle.)
(It's an Olympics with fun, sports, songs, and talks.)
(However,)
(if you aim for the throne, watch your back.)
(There is a secret hidden inside.)
(What is the secret surrounding Jae Seok?)
(The entertainment industry is focusing on this big event of 2017.)
(It's a special day with special guests.)
What is this?
It's Yu Jae Seok's Member's Week.
You are here as his friends.
(These five friends will help him.)
We are the people that have some connections to him.
What are you saying?
(Don't pretend like you didn't know.)
- I'm just saying. - They...
called the obvious people.
- What is he trying to do? - I was explaining just in case.
- You are still being mean. - I know.
I think Jae Seok was thinking about...
how he could match us with the Running Man members.
There's no one other than KCM who can challenge Jong Kook.
I know Chun Hee will be in charge of Kwang Soo.
- That's right. - Yes.
I am always in charge of Kwang Soo or Seok Jin.
How about you?
I'll take care of Seok Jin.
(Leave Seok Jin to me.)
I'll take care of him.
He is quite strong, though.
- He is? For him, his legs... - That's true.
I do have strong legs because I play soccer.
- I was going to say they are weak. - Really?
- I did play a lot of soccer. - But you miss a lot.
(These members were invited by this man.)
(Jae Seok is the main member today.)
What's over there?
(He enters first as the main MC.)
Lee Seul started the job in her early 20s.
As Jae Seok wished, there will be an entertaining sports game...
between Team Running Man and Team Friends today.
The winner will get to receive the prize he promised.
However...
However, there is a hidden rule...
that Jae Seok doesn't know about.
(Is there a secret on Jae Seok's Sports Day?)
I mentioned that the winner gets the prize...
he promised for each round.
- Right. - So there are prizes?
In each prize, there will be hidden hints.
They are about the location of the last prize which is a treasure.
The team that finds the treasure first wins.
Are we a team?
Yes. However, if you are clumsy...
and Jae Seok finds the hints and the treasure first,
he gets to win alone.
(It's important to get as many hints as possible without his knowing.)
The scale is different for Jae Seok's Week.
- I knew it. - It's Jangchung Gymnasium.
It's my Member's Week today.
I realized that...
we had too many touching...
- and teary episodes. - Why not?
- I really liked it. - There were...
too many episodes like that.
So I told the staff that I wanted my episode...
- To be fun? - to be fun.
- I wanted to spend a happy day. - Okay.
That's why I decided to buy the prizes...
with my own money.
- Really? - There is one for each round.
- I bought them with my own money. - Really?
- Yes. - Really?
I brought my friends that could be matches with...
- each of the Running Man members. - Really? I like that.
Please welcome, Team Friends!
Who is that?
- It's Yong Man. - What is he doing here?
It's Yong Man.
(It's the Fantastic Five, armed with wit and experience.)
- It's Chun Hee. - And KCM.
It's KCM.
Oh my!
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Thank you for coming.
- Hello. It's been a long time. - KCM is here.
- Hello. - Hello.
Put this away.
- KCM, it's been a long time. - Hello.
It's been a long time.
(Here are the five friends.)
They rented a gymnasium.
It's incredible.
It's the unforgettable two-shot from...
"Mystic TV: Surprise."
(They used to emcee together.)
I was in that program as well.
- For 6 weeks. - For 6 weeks.
- "Surprise". - It's incredible.
- "Come to Play". - "Come to Play".
- There is "Jagiya", too. - Okay.
- "Jagiya". - "Jagiya".
The show is still broadcasting until now...
but there was a little problem.
There was.
- It just happened. - He's not coming back.
- He isn't. - No.
Let me introduce them one by one.
The rival of Seok Jin is...
- Kim Yong Man. - Thank you.
Hello.
- It's been a long time. - It's been a long time.
It's been a long time.
- I laughed when I was cast. - Why?
I knew I'm not a match for Jong Kook...
but I thought I could be a match for Kwang Soo or Haha.
Why did it have to be him?
- It was like that before. - He's quite strong.
After doing Running Man, he was given a new lease on life.
- I know. - What are you talking about?
How would you know?
- He was. - How would you know?
Yong Man is used to being an MC in a studio.
I have returned after a long break.
I had doubts about Running Man at first, but I came because...
they told me we were shooting under a roof.
We are shooting under a roof.
- And it's a huge roof. - At least, there's a roof.
It's almost like we're outdoors.
The most important factor for him is not how much he gets paid.
- It's the existence of a roof. - Is it the roof?
It's whether or not there is a roof.
Yong Man will be...
the leader of Team Friends.
Who do you think is the weakest in your team?
It's Chun Hee, of course.
He seems like the weakest.
- He has that aura. - Totally.
He's confident because he has a lot of experience.
- He does. - I saw the episodes and he's weak.
He doesn't do anything.
He did seem uncertain about his past battles with Kwang Soo.
He admits to losing. But...
- he's grinding his teeth today. - In "Family Outing",
- there was a famous incident... - Right.
where he washed radish with soap.
(November 2, 2008, Episode 20 from "Family Outing")
(What is this?)
(Is it soap?)
Chun Hee!
(Puzzled)
- Really? - It was my first day on the show.
- That can happen. - With soap?
As you know well enough,
the next contestant will be in rivalry with...
Song Ji Hyo.
It's Kim Won Hee.
- Kim Won Hee. - It's Won Hee!
- Look at her. - Kim Won Hee.
(The queen of variety shows declares war.)
- Look at her. - Look.
- You can't lose. - Look at her.
It's just as expected.
She's the first generation of female entertainers.
She opened up a new world.
- She's like Lee Seong Gye. - Lee Seong Gye?
- The first king of Joseon Dynasty. - Stop teasing her.
Kyung Hwan is...
- watching out for a chance. - He's really small.
I chose the wrong place. They are too tall for me.
I am hidden by them.
It's driving me crazy.
This was supposed to be...
a team game.
But you all try to stand out.
We have to survive.
There is no team work.
- This could be the last chance. - We're all under pressure.
And they say things as to...
stand out.
- Let's control ourselves. - Let us.
- Do you mean it? - Yes, I do.
- Go. - Go.
- Go Team Friends. - Go Team Friends.
- It's really old-fashioned. - It's really old-fashioned.
We didn't even do that on "X-Man".
- Who made that? - We did that decades ago.
I only helped Chun Hee make the slogan.
- All right. First, Kyung Hwan, - What's our slogan?
when you are in rivalry with Haha...
- Please listen to me. - Okay.
- We're making our slogan. - We don't want to.
- Let's make one. - Why?
He's envying our slogan.
- Yes. - Seok Jin always makes one.
- He'll make one today. - One important fact is...
that Seok Jin is not the leader of this team unlike Yong Man is.
Why not?
- Jong Kook is the leader. - Why?
There's hierarchy here.
- We respect him because he's old. - You're not the leader here.
It's not well-balanced then. The balance has tipped.
You should change places.
The balance is tipped.
- Here... - Age doesn't play a role.
It's best to clear any confusion.
No. You are not the leader.
- No, you are not. - We should clarify it first.
- You are such a great host. - Goodness.
The time has finally come.
- Goodness. - It's been a while.
I thought about who could be a suitable match for Jong Kook.
- There was only one person, KCM. - It's KCM.
(KCM, who has a sweet voice, visits a variety show after a long time.)
I thought KCM had a cast on his arm.
Isn't that a cast?
It's an arm warmer, a leading fashion accessory.
- Why did you put it on? - Long time ago,
when he was actively starring on TV shows,
he wore arm warmers with sleeveless shirts.
I haven't seen it outside of billiard parlors.
This is my first time seeing it outside.
I have prepared something to compete against Jong Kook.
- What is it? - What have you prepared?
(They're matching arm warmers.)
- Let's wear them together. - Let's not. I don't wear them.
- I have prepared them for you. - I don't want to wear them.
- You should try them on. - Stop it.
- Take off your parka. - He can wear them over.
- What's happening? - Wear them over the parka.
- I've prepared them for him. - Where's the sleeveless shirt?
- Why do I have to wear them? - He even sewed them.
- I made them in a hurry. - It's driving me crazy.
You made holes here.
(They look stylish and warm.)
You look scary.
- You two should stand together. - What is this?
My goodness.
(These arm warmers will make you a professional billiard player.)
KCM, can't you imitate Jong Kook when he sings?
- Of course, I can. - You can, right?
- Can you sing a bit? - I was the first to imitate him,
but a lot of people started imitating.
- Can you sing for a bit? - I am so curious.
Sing, "One Man".
There is one man
- I think his pitch is off. - He's out of tune.
Can you sing?
Show us the original.
There is
- One man - He's trying to sound different.
- He sang it differently. - No, I didn't.
That's low even for you.
- You should've matched his singing. - I didn't sing it differently.
- I mean KCM... - There is one man
- That's it. - He sounds exactly like Jong Kook.
Who loves you very much
- It sounds exactly like the CD. - You think so?
- Is that the right pitch? - He doesn't sound like me.
Try again.
- There is one man - There he goes again.
(Even before listening, she criticizes him.)
- Exactly. - What are you talking about?
He's the original singer.
- KCM should match his singing. - Why do I have to match him?
- KCM was supposed to imitate him. - He did a fine job.
Why don't we start now? Why don't we start with an applause?
(The match begins.)
The first round is a battle of rivalry.
We have prepared a triathlon for...
- men of strength. - Men of strength?
Who do you think suits the description?
- They are Jong Kook and KCM. - It must be Jong Kook.
(It's a battle of power. It's Jong Kook against KCM.)
- Are you going to be okay? - We get to see this at last.
Look at his body. He has a good build.
- They're bringing in something. - Goodness.
- It's arm-wrestling. - They're really going to play it?
He must be good at arm-wrestling.
- I can't predict who will win. - Me, neither.
(It's a chance to scare off the other team.)
(Jong Kook is a true man of strength and a symbol of power.)
(He's an exceptional arm-wrestler who won against 52 people in a row.)
(KCM is the only match among the celebrities to compete against him.)
(He will knock him out with unusual power and exercise capability.)
(Who will be the victor of the first battle?)
I am really curious to find out the result.
- They are really going to do it. - This is amazing.
- Show him. - The pride of athletes is at stake.
This will be quite a match.
Both of you are known to work out a lot.
You two are considered to be really strong.
Why don't you sing your songs...
in order to vanquish your opponents?
You can sing the highlight of your songs.
Jong Kook, go first.
There is one man
Who loves you very much
- You love me? - All right.
It's your turn.
- Should I say I love you again? - They sound the same.
- Should I wait a bit more? - I haven't heard it for so long.
Can you sing one more song? Sing one more.
A day passes by, a month passes by
(Somehow, they are getting a bit too emotional.)
Both of their songs are so sentimental.
- They have similar voices. - It feels weird to sing right now.
This was supposed to distract your opponent.
Why don't you grab the stick? Get ready.
- Please move to my side. - Goodness. He's strong.
(They can feel each other's power just by holding each other's hand.)
Get ready. Please move to the side.
- I am so curious. - Shouldn't someone grab the table?
- They are so serious. - Let me hold the table.
- Ready. - Goodness, KCM.
- It will be just one round. - You'll play only one game.
- Their pride is at stake. - This is...
- It will light up. - It's quite a rare scene to watch.
- Yes, it is a rare scene. - This is my first time seeing it.
- KCM, show him what you've got. - Get ready.
(Who will take the first win?)
(Will it be KCM with arm warmers that will increase his offense?)
(Or will it be Jong Kook who has a great defense?)
(It's a battle of their pride as they work out at the gym zealously.)
(Start!)
(From the start, they go hard at each other.)
(He clenches his teeth.)
This is...
(At that moment, the momentum of the game seems to change.)
(To whose side will the arms go down?)
This is..
(Pulling)
This is...
(Jong Kook is shocked.)
(Will KCM be able to win?)
- KCM has won. KCM won. - It's over.
(KCM, the father of arm warmers, wins.)
(The score is 0 to 1.)
- Are you okay? - Jong Kook is strong, too.
(It's been years since he lost in a strength battle.)
- This can't be right. - This can't be happening.
- I can't believe this. - This must be a dream.
He's really strong.
(What will be the second battle?)
- We'll start the next battle. - It's thigh wrestling.
- Jong Kook's thighs are amazing. - This won't be easy.
- It's easier if he... - Here we go again.
Sit closer.
- This is nice. - This won't be the same.
(Jong Kook's thighs are like steel.)
(He overpowered Kim Dong Hyun, an MMA fighter.)
(He even had a neck and neck battle with Choi Shin Soo.)
(It's the ultimate pride of muscular athletes, iron-like thighs.)
- Goodness. - He's so strong.
It's easier to split the legs.
Should I play defense first?
You can play defense first.
(It won't be easy this time.)
Please check the time.
- Ready. - The camera...
(Jong Kook will play defense and KCM will play offense.)
Offense is harder.
(Thigh wrestling starts!)
Hold the chairs.
- Goodness. - Check the time.
(If he holds KCM's legs together for 15 seconds, he wins.)
- They have 10 seconds left. - Are you timing it?
- For KCM to compete with him... - They have 10 seconds?
- Only 10 seconds left. -10 seconds?
(If KCM splits Jong Kook's legs in 15 seconds, he wins.)
For KCM to compete with him is amazing.
(They are amazed at KCM and respect him at the same time.)
10 seconds left.
(They won't give in.)
This is impossible.
(Jong Kook finally meets a suitable match today.)
Time's up.
- Look at his face. It's so red. - Good job.
- You have a runny nose. - All you have to do is hold out.
- My legs are about to fall off. - You just have to withstand him.
How was it?
I felt like I was going against a rock.
Your legs are not fixed, are they?
We will switch positions now. KCM will play defense.
This is so challenging.
- It will be another 15 seconds. - It will last for 15 seconds.
- Get ready. - He has to play defense now?
I bet they worked out more than all of us combined.
- That's true. - They do work out a lot.
Ready. Jong Kook.
- Playing offense is harder. - It is.
It will be tied if KCM wins, right?
Yes, it will be even. Get ready.
You can do it.
(Thigh wrestling starts!)
- Hold them together. - There you go.
(They're using up all their energy.)
- This is it. - Keep your thighs together.
- It's almost over. - You can do it.
(It's a strong offense against a tight defense.)
(It's a battle of a spear against a shield. Who will win?)
(Their legs tremble.)
(KCM's legs are slowly splitting.)
- Keep them together. - It's almost done.
(He tries with all his might.)
(Who are these scary people?)
(Jong Kook wants to separate KCM's legs while KCM resists.)
(As they go through several battles, their battles get more intense.)
(KCM's lower body strength is gone along with his upper body strength.)
- Good job. - Well done.
(His mouth drops open.)
- He won, right? He spread more. - Who won?
- It was a close match. - As a judge,
- Jong Kook did separate them more. - He did win, right?
Goodness.
Give a round of applause for them.
(What will be their next battle?)
- Goodness, he's strong. - That was crazy.
- It's the last battle. - I see.
This battle will decide who wins overall, right?
- If you wind it up, it will hurt. - Yes, it will.
This is the game that made Jae Seok stand up.
(This miraculous, leg-wrestling game made Jae Seok stand up.)
(Jong Kook's opponent for today is the powerful KCM.)
- It will be hard. - Get ready.
This is the last battle.
I've never seen Jong Kook this nervous.
- It's been ages. - He's not an easy opponent.
You weren't this nervous before.
Ready.
You can do it.
(Leg wrestling starts!)
(From the start, he clenches his teeth.)
Goodness.
(KCM manages to withstand Jong Kook's power.)
- You should hold the rope again. - Yes, I should.
(They pause the game for a moment.)
Goodness, they tested each other's power.
Give them a round of applause.
This is amazing.
How can this be?
(We are very serious.)
It's as if I'm watching a bullfight in Cheongdo.
(He feels the atmosphere of Cheongdo in Jangchung Gymnasium.)
You shouldn't spread your legs like that.
How can you compare them to bulls? They are not animals.
Their power struggle reminded me of the fight.
They are really strong.
(They resume the match.)
(Their pride as athletes is at stake on this last battle.)
I think the rope might snap.
They are in the air.
(To which team will the victory of the first round go?)
(The rope is dangerously tight.)
(Slipping)
(This is intense.)
This won't settle.
- This won't work. - They'll hurt themselves.
This won't work. Let's do something else.
(It's a tie since they're at similar levels.)
(The result is 1 win, 1 loss, and 1 tie.)
(Team Running Man: 1, Team Friends: 1)
(Next game is "5-Second Quiz".)
All right. It's Haha and Kyung Hwan's turns.
"5-Second Quiz".
("5-Second Quiz")
If you're unable to answer my question in five seconds,
I'll cut one of the wires.
There are colors designated to you.
If that wire is cut,
the balloon filled with flour will pop above your head.
Please inflate the balloons.
(The balloons are inflated.)
I'm scared of balloons.
(It sounds scary.)
(Can't we just do something physical?)
Can you stop it?
(The others are scared as well.)
(They get farther away from the balloons.)
(All of Jae Seok's friends are cowards.)
That's fine. You're good there.
Don't worry.
Please stop.
- It's about to pop. - Please stop.
- Is that sound effect? - No, it's not.
Are you ready?
- Let's start with Haha. - Okay.
- Go ahead. - You're dead.
You must answer in five seconds.
Running Man is 7012.
Let's go!
- All right. - What was that?
(We are embarrassed for you.)
- Let's get started. - I don't feel good about this.
What was your first impression of me?
(I have to answer this question in 5 seconds?)
- You were handsome, ugly, and nice. - In 4, 3...
and 2. All right. What was your first impression of me?
In 5, 4,
You had wrinkles. You were losing weight.
You had tidy hair.
- I said all of them. - He did.
- I didn't say how many. - The wrinkles around your eyes.
(Kyung Hwan is safe.)
I didn't say how many.
- Why are you take his side? - I'm not taking his side.
- It's obvious you are. - I'm not.
Do you choose us or them?
- Let me say this again. - Have you forgotten 7012?
- I didn't say how many. - You said we were one.
Let's continue. Here's the next question.
(He gets anxious.)
- You're taking his side. - What is it?
Does he get you chicken breast?
(Kyung Hwan has a chicken breast brand.)
(Jae Seok is under fire for getting chicken breast from Kyung Hwan.)
- I don't. - I was wondering which one you ate.
- You're mistaken. - I see how it is.
(You can't be biased.)
Name five positive qualities about me.
- In 5, 4, - You talk fast,
- you're handsome, and tall. - 3, 2,
- On top of that... - Time's up!
My goodness.
Why did you change your position?
- You should have just said it. - It's Haha's turn.
Let's go. Name five positive qualities about me.
- You're ugly, more ugly, very ugly, - In 5, 4, 3,
- really ugly, and extremely ugly. - 2...
(Haha thinks Jae Seok is just ugly.)
(He bombards Jae Seok with bitter facts.)
(Haha is safe.)
That's good.
(He knows Jae Seok well.)
Please choose a color.
Jae Seok is a grasshopper so I choose green.
All right!
(Haha chooses the green wire.)
Green, it is.
(Will Kyung Hwan be showered in flour?)
You're not changing your mind, right?
No.
(There's a 20-percent probability. Will this be the end?)
Will Kyung Hwan be eliminated on the first try?
1, 2...
(They're tied right now. Which team will take the win?)
(Cutting)
I think that's it.
(Kyung Hwan survives.)
(He could have won.)
- He survived. - This is so nerve-racking.
(The game continues until the balloon pops.)
That was close.
Haha, what are three things you don't want to hear from me?
"You're boring, you're ugly, get lost."
(Haha replies.)
(Did I say that?)
"Get lost" was good.
(Haha passes.)
Haha has the upper hand in this game.
- Exactly. - He doesn't usually think.
Kyung Hwan can do this as well. Don't worry.
Kyung Hwan, don't think too much.
What are three things you hear a lot from me?
- 5, 4, - He doesn't see him a lot.
"Kyung Hwan, Heo Kyung Hwan, you punk, where are you?"
(Kyung Hwan passes.)
"What are you doing?"
(He can almost hear Jae Seok.)
I...
- Was that three? - Whenever I meet Kyung Hwan,
- I say that. - "Heo Kyung Hwan".
- You punk. - "You punk".
Those are the things...
- I say to him all the time. - Why do you keep...
taking his side?
- You must be on their team. - What's wrong with you?
It's true. I say that all the time.
It's like I bumped into you in the hallway.
- Next. - This is difficult.
Five things you think you're better than me in.
I'm handsome, my family is better off, and my wife is prettier.
Four...
(He's more handsome and better off. He has a more beautiful wife, too.)
(He has no logic behind his answers.)
- Hold on. - That was incredible.
I don't know about the last one.
(I'm sorry, my honey.)
(My wife is the best.)
He's saying whatever.
(Everybody starts talking.)
- Okay, I'll give you that. - All right.
I'm not approving his answer but we'll just move on.
- Byul is pretty. - Let's just do three.
- Do you know what he just said? - What did he say?
"Byul is pretty."
(Jae Seok receives an unexpected, second blow.)
- She's pretty. - He thinks she's pretty.
(My friends are too involved in the game.)
(Haha is just happy.)
- Byul is pretty. - Next.
Kyung Hwan.
Three things you think you're better than me in.
I'm shorter but more handsome, I'm shorter but more awesome,
I'm shorter but faster, and I'm shorter but stronger.
(He's shorter but better in many ways.)
You asked for 3 things but he said 4.
- You can choose them. - Only answer three from now on.
Good job, Kyung Hwan.
Three times you didn't want to see me.
- Now, yesterday, and 2 days ago. - 5...
Correct!
(These are facts, too.)
Correct.
- Correct. - That was the best.
(Haha passes easily.)
He knows Jae Seok too well.
He has experience. He's good at this.
It's your turn, Kyung Hwan.
Five things you want to change about me.
- 5, 4... - Talking about work during dinner,
talking about work after work is over,
(I win.)
This won't work.
- Fail. - Why is that a fail?
How do I beat Haha?
Should I choose red?
Sure.
Running man is passion! The color of passion is red!
- 7012! - Red?
(They're so cheesy.)
(Kyung Hwan is in danger again.)
Is red correct?
(Would Team Friends lose or get another chance?)
(Cutting)
He cut it.
(The team that wins round 1 will get a prize and a hint.)
(Popping)
(Haha wins.)
Haha wins.
Do your move and shake it off.
(There's flour everywhere.)
(He's mad at Haha.)
(Team Running Man: 2, Team Friends: 1)
(Ji Hyo and Won Hee are up next.)
(Entering)
(She looks very spiritual.)
It suits you well.
Did you get involved in a new religion?
(She's here to experience the flour baptism.)
- Sister. - She looks like a nun.
It looks nice on both of you.
(The gymnasium is turned into a sacred place.)
- She looks exotic. - Somebody from Dubai.
She looks like a rich lady from Dubai.
Won Hee used to be so pretty.
All right. Ji Hyo is ready.
- You saw the previous game, right? - Yes.
We'll get started right away then.
Name five negative qualities about me.
- 5, 4, - You talk a lot, you glare at me,
- He wears glasses. - you wear glasses,
your lips protrude, and your eyes are small.
Okay.
Don't be so honest.
(It sounded like the truth.)
Do I glare at you?
She was looking at you straight in the eye.
All right. Name five negative qualities about me.
- Negative qualities? - Name five. Start.
You only wear tight pants, your nose is round,
- 3, 2, - you change your glasses too often,
your lips protrude, and your teeth are ugly.
(These are her truthful answers.)
You got two from his mouth. Good job.
(Jae Seok's worst qualities come from his mouth.)
You were close.
(Won Hee passes.)
The other team complained.
Let's move on.
Three things I say a lot.
- 5, 4, 3, - "Be quiet, get lost,"
- 2, - "you're too loud, go away,"
"go."
(Ji Hyo passes.)
She said, "Go."
Three times when you think...
I look pitiful. Go. Five,
- When you get wedgies, - four,
(When he gets wedgies.)
when you argue with your wife...
- and ask me to talk. - Time's up.
Time's up. You fail.
You're trying to be honest. Just make it up.
- Ji Hyo. - You have to make it up.
All right.
(Ji Hyo gets to choose a color.)
- Blue. - Blue, it is.
- I think she's right. - I think she is.
Hold on.
(Will Won Hee get another chance?)
(Or will Ji Hyo continue Running Man's winning streak?)
(Cutting)
(The wire has been cut.)
- Hold on. - The balloon is blue.
(Popping)
(Ji Hyo wins in one try.)
Ji Hyo wins.
(Team Running Man: 3, Team Friends: 1)
(Seok Jin and Yong Man are next.)
Seok Jin and Yong Man...
will face each other in a one-legged fight.
You haven't played this against each other, right?
- We haven't. - We've never played it.
I haven't seen it, either.
We don't play physical games.
We hardly exercised together.
Exactly. I go to the gym...
that Yong Man recommended.
I didn't know he'd get so addicted to it.
I go frequently but Yong Man stopped after three times.
I looked around the gym and it wasn't my style.
I felt like smelling the place...
gave me enough energy...
so I just smelled around and headed for the sauna.
That's where I go.
Are you ready?
- Yes. - It's Seok Jin and Yong Man.
- Okay. - All right.
- We've never done this before. - Let's go!
I wonder how this will turn out.
These two never had...
- physical contact with each other. - Never.
They only talked.
This is their first time.
I wanted to face him physically today.
- I've known him for 30 years. - Get ready.
Let's get started with the one-legged fight.
- You can do it. - Ready.
Seok Jin played a lot of games.
- Seok Jin! - All right.
You have a weird form.
(They look for a chance to attack.)
(Bumping)
(Yong Man attacks first.)
(Striking)
Are you all right?
- Isn't this what we do? - That's right.
(He continues to attack.)
- Yong Man is good at this. - He is.
- Be careful. - He's really good at this.
(This is an unexpected side of him.)
He's really good at this.
- Seok Jin. - Be careful.
Yong Man is unexpectedly...
- You're tired already. - For 30 years...
(Attacking)
- Why are they so slow? - You're breathing heavily.
(Yong Man's breathing heavily.)
Should we take a break?
That sounds like a good idea.
- Put our legs down in three. - Sure.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- No, I won't put it down. - Me, neither.
- Let's just take a break. - Shall we?
This is your chance.
What was that?
(Groaning)
(Collapsing)
What was that?
Why did you collapse?
What did you do?
I tried to attack.
- Come back. - That was embarrassing.
That was a humiliating loss.
- I feel bad. - You bowed in their direction.
I didn't know you'd collapse so easily.
Nobody gets thrown to the ground in a one-legged fight.
(Yong Man, I didn't know you were this strong.)
(Team Running Man: 3, Team Friends: 2)
(Kwang Soo and Chun Hee will play "Pole Wrestling".)
"Pole Wrestling"...
will be played by Kwang Soo and Chun Hee.
This is Kwang Soo's game.
Kwang Soo is strong, too.
I haven't heard that before.
Me, neither.
- That was discouraging. - Is he strong?
- Yes. - Chun Hee surfed for a long time.
He has real muscles.
He's a surfer.
You can do it.
- Ready. - Let's go.
Get set, go.
All right.
(They both climb at once.)
(The two giraffes reach the top.)
(They don't hesitate.)
Push him down. Attack.
- Good job. - He's winning.
- Tickle him. - He's winning.
- Kwang Soo. - What's wrong, Chun Hee?
What's with that face?
Don't make that face.
You're supposed to use your feet.
- Use your feet, Chun Hee. - Don't make that face.
Do something. Come on.
Ouch! Hold on!
(He feels pain.)
Hold on. I said, hold on.
(He doesn't know what to do.)
(This is your chance, Chun Hee.)
Spin him around.
(Spinning)
(Is Kwang Soo out?)
Good job.
(Did you think I was going to let go?)
- Good job. - You have the advantage.
- Let's go, Chun Hee. - Spin him around.
- All right. - Good job.
Kwang Soo and Chun Hee.
(If Chun Hee loses, his team loses.)
- You have to attack now. - This is looking good.
- You have to attack now. - Attack.
- Come closer. - I can't.
I can't come closer.
- Don't get closer. - He's coming.
- We have to win, Chun Hee. - You can do it!
- Let's go. - We can't lose.
(Grabbing)
All right. Good job.
- Chun Hee. - You're fierce.
You're fierce. Don't let go.
He's winning.
Good job. Keep going.
(Kwang Soo hangs on with his hands.)
(Chun Hee looks for a chance to make a tie.)
(Who will touch the ground first?)
(Good bye, Kwang Soo.)
(Chun Hee is the better giraffe.)
Chun Hee wins!
(Team Running Man: 3, Team Friends: 3)
Round one was a tie.
- What about the vitamins? - It was a tie.
It'll be added on to the prize for the next round.
(Prizes and hint for round 1 will be added to the next round.)
- That sounds good. - Prizes for the next round doubles.
It will double.
- It doubles. - Let's get started with round two.
(We'll win the next round.)
Thanks to you, we tied.
Round two involves eating.
(Lunch is a bonus.)
- I didn't have breakfast. - You didn't?
I love sausage stew.
(They have everything from sausage stew to bulgogi.)
It's braised spicy chicken.
That looks so good.
- There's octopus as well. - Where?
- There it is. - This is hot pot bulgogi.
(What game will they play?)
We can't just let you eat.
We'll do a chatting battle. It's time to talk.
We have Seok Jin.
He's the chatty king.
There's chicken as well. I want Seok Jin to have some.
Why?
- Just because. - Excuse me.
Let's arm wrestle.
Look at that.
Anyway, we have the vitamins from round one...
- and the prize from round two. - What is it?
It's accumulated.
Prize for round two is a set of Korean beef.
It's Korean beef.
(Prize for round two is a set of Korean beef.)
It's for the winner to take.
(On top of that, the winning team gets 2 hints on the treasure.)
(However, Jae Seok doesn't know that.)
You don't have to talk about me.
Let's talk comfortably.
I'll reward you with a dish on the spot.
You probably have many stories to share.
We have a friend named Yoon Gi Won.
He bought his first car.
We're all fellow comedians.
It wasn't a good car.
- It was an old car. - He bought an old car.
We were all staring at it.
We were supposed to meet in Apgujeong-dong.
When it got dark, his car lightened up when he drove.
When he stopped, the light turned off.
- Isn't that a good car? - I was wondering what it was.
This was 20 years ago.
It was like neon lights.
The light turned on and went away when he stopped.
I thought it was incredible. I went to have a look.
He rolled down his window.
(What was the secret behind the technology?)
The seat belt was broken...
so the metal buckle was screeching the ground.
(The spark was from the metal buckle.)
- This is a true story. - It was gone.
- There was a spark? - This is a true story.
It was gone.
(Gi Won decided not to have a seat belt.)
When he drove, the spark came on...
- and when he stopped, it went away. - It's true.
- The light would come on? - That's right.
When he drove faster, the light was more intense.
It's true. Good job, Yong Man.
Here's hot pot bulgogi.
- That is your reward. - That was great teamwork.
I'll talk about my car and manager in the same story.
It's not about my current manager. My previous manager...
would always be sleeping when I returned from work.
So I gave him an advice. I told him not to sleep...
and read a book to make better use of his time.
I told him a few times so he said he won't fall asleep again.
One day after "Gag Concert", I opened the car door...
and he sprang up from his seat.
I asked if he was sleeping and he said no.
I told him to drive. He used a water bottle as the gear stick.
His water bottle was always on the side. He grabbed it.
- He didn't even look. - Good one.
(Here's braised short ribs for you.)
Let's do something.
That was good.
So...
(If they win another point, Team Friends will win this round.)
It's a true story.
Lee Hoon's manager...
His manager gets nervous easily.
He's been on television quite a few times.
He's a funny guy.
He was nervous about his job.
One time, Hoon had a few drinks.
He's a manly guy so he sat next to the driver's seat.
He said, "Let's go." The manager was backing up and grabbed his head.
(He grabbed Hoon's head.)
(My gosh)
He was nervous.
That was good teamwork.
Good job, Seok Jin.
That was good teamwork with Seok Jin.
- He was backing up. - That was good teamwork.
- He was too nervous. - That was funny.
- I just remembered something. - Here he goes.
- Here he goes. - This is true.
Don't say that.
- You're a bad person. - You're the chatty king.
- I'm not the chatty king. - But you are.
Fine.
- Don't make fun of me. - What? It's true.
Let's keep it natural. Why would you say that?
- He can beat Yong Man. - I'm not trying to beat him.
Why would I try to beat him? I'm happy my friend is here.
- It's a story about a thug boss. - I like this.
He had this tattoo across his chest.
During a fierce fight,
he was stabbed in the stomach.
(They start to get bored.)
He was transferred to the operation room.
(Isn't it working?)
- To the operation room. - Wait.
- Hear me out. - They look uncertain.
- That's why he can't talk. - Hear me out.
Yong Man.
- Show some response. - They're just sneering.
Show some response.
I can't look him in the eye.
- He's acting like the leader. - Wait.
No one here is saying anything.
- Right? - We're just relaxed.
- Hear me out. - Calm down.
Sit down.
He's sent to the operating room.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
He's admitted to the operating room.
I'm telling a short version.
The doctor asks him,
"Do you have a wish?"
Is he skipping everything in between?
He's about to have surgery.
"Please..."
(They're all hoping Seok Jin will make them laugh.)
(What favor did the boss ask the doctor before the surgery?)
"Please connect the tattoos correctly."
(The boss asked the doctor to connect the tattoos properly.)
Give up now!
(Haha explodes.)
- Give up! - Wasn't it funny?
(Aren't you holding back your laughter?)
Tell him he doesn't have to do this just because he's the leader.
You don't have to do this.
He's feeling so burdened.
Seok Jin is usually not like this.
It's your fault.
Sit down.
It's time to listen to them.
All right.
We have sausage stew left. You can have it.
We have sausage stew left.
Jokes need context.
I'll talk about army lives.
It's about my friend.
(He'll talk about army lives.)
He got a subordinate...
who's a martial-arts champion.
One night, they were on patrol.
He was getting bored, so he talked to his subordinate.
"Hey, come here."
"Ghosts appear around here from time to time."
"Some were so shocked that they had to be discharged."
"You should be careful, too." He tried to scare him.
What he wanted to do was startle the martial-arts champion.
"So..."
"Oh, it's there!" The champion was startled...
and punched his superior.
He had a double nosebleed.
That's funny.
That was so predictable.
- He pulled it off. - So...
- The punching part was funny. - Punch.
Anyway...
In the second round,
Team Friends wins.
(Team Friends wins.)
As promised, you can take the vitamins...
and Korean beef.
Each should get one.
Don't worry. There are two more rounds left.
Sure.
In the silver box...
(The first hint is a paper ship.)
This is the hint.
- Where? - Be careful.
(You like my gifts, right?)
(They must have found a hint.)
Can we take a look?
- No. - Can we take a look?
- Just see it from a distance. - Show us.
Look.
(They find the second hint in the beef, too.)
Wait.
- There are many gifts left. - Are they good ones?
- Are they better than the first? - Of course.
We've already won two gifts.
I feel so confident.
The vitamins are working.
- They are. - They woke me up.
The gifts in the third round are even better.
Better than beef?
- What would it be? - Do you have the beef with you?
- Yes. - It's ours.
Let's discuss how to divide it.
Each can take his or her favorite part.
Let's talk when we get off.
(Will Team Friends find the treasure before Team Running Man does?)
We don't have much time.
We have two hints.
Each vitamin box had a paper boat.
- That's right. - Do we have to take it out?
- No. It's just a paper ship. - What was the other one?
What was in the beef box?
There's no text, right?
The second hint is very simple, too.
- What is it? - It's this.
- A grasshopper? - It must mean...
Jae Seok knows something.
- This is it. - Is that it?
- A grasshopper and a ship? - This was in the beef box.
Is the paper ship a hint?
- There are ships. - There are ships.
There are four ships.
It has something to do with Jae Seok.
- I think we're right. - I think it's about his stomach.
Something must be in his stomach.
Hair?
The treasure's in his hair?
What is this?
(They need to find the treasure.)
It's time for the third round.
It's simple. It's a match between the teams.
If your song gets more than 90 points, you'll get 5 minutes.
If your song gets between 80 and 90 points, you'll get 3 minutes.
We get 5 or 3 minutes?
I'll tell you what to do during the given time.
Behind you are 30 vans.
While the tagging team is...
staying here,
the other team will hide themselves in the vans.
(It's a hide-and-seek inside the vans.)
(Find the best spots to hide yourselves in the vans.)
("Hide-and-Seek")
There are so many vans.
(They'll hide in the vans while the tagging team sings.)
(The tagging team will be given either 3 or 5 minutes to find them.)
We'll sing first.
- Do you want to sing first? - Yes.
All right. While we're singing,
- Team Friends will hide themselves. - We'll hide.
Start as soon as the song begins.
Pick a long song.
Ready.
Start.
("Unconditionally")
Here we go.
(They're getting ready to sing.)
Who wants to sing?
What should we do?
- Okay. - Let's go.
Let me see.
Where should we hide?
Psychologically...
- In the middle? - The middle?
How can we not get caught?
Let's find vans with dark windows.
(Which vans have dark windows?)
Should I hide in the trunk? They might open it.
The trunk?
Should I hide here?
(Won Hee and KCM will hide in the trunk.)
I wish I had a smaller body.
Please cover me up.
If they find you, drive them away.
Cover me up.
(KCM will divert their attention.)
(Won Hee hides under a blanket.)
Stay there. It's perfect.
Should I lower my body?
No. It looks perfect.
Find vans with dark windows.
Should we hide ourselves behind the drivers?
Here. Can we hide here?
You can stay here.
Just make yourself comfortable.
I should pretend that I'm a driver.
(Yong Man and Chun Hee pretend to be drivers.)
- Come here. - In the front...
Wait. I'll sit first.
Sit in front of me.
(Yong Man sits the driver on his lap.)
Like this.
(They can even hear each other breathe.)
(Honking)
(His stomach pushes the horn.)
What's this?
Why are they honking?
(They won't be able to find us.)
Stop honking.
It'll be impossible to find me.
The song is almost over.
Be careful.
Why is the song so long?
(To get the hint, they have to hide in the right spots.)
Why is it already over?
This jacket will trick them.
(Kyung Hwan plans to distract them with his jacket.)
(There's a 10-percent chance that they'll be caught.)
(Team Running Man's performance is almost over.)
(They sing the last line.)
What's our score?
(They need a high score to win more time.)
Please.
Is it 98?
(A new, singing king is born.)
100 points.
(They get 100 points.)
What should we do?
- We have five minutes. - What are we supposed to do?
We have five minutes.
Start.
- Has it already started? - How do I do this?
(The search begins.)
(We're coming to get you.)
Stop him from moving.
(They start the search at once.)
Open the doors!
In the front...
(Some of them start from the front.)
- There's no one here, right? - Can they be in the trunk?
Can they be in the trunk?
I didn't look in the trunk.
There's no one.
(Kwang Soo is near them.)
(Ji Hyo focuses on opening the doors.)
- They're not here, right? - Seok Jin.
I'll open the doors. You look.
- I'll open the doors. - There are only 30 vans.
- Seok Jin. - Look in the trunks.
We should check the trunks.
(Yong Man and Chun Hee are in danger.)
Look into the vans I opened. What are you doing?
Look into the vans you opened?
- I've been opening the doors! - Okay.
(Will they be caught?)
We should look in the trunks, too.
(Seok Jin fails to spot them.)
It'll be impossible to find me.
- Where are they? - They're nowhere.
They're nowhere.
Do you think you can search for them with me on your back?
Do you think I can't?
Do you think you can?
Let's go.
(Moving)
My goodness.
Jong Kook.
(It's my week. Why do I have to go through this?)
- My goodness. - The doors are open.
Did they already look?
- This is not how you do it. - Yes, it is.
This is not how you do it.
It's supposed to be easy for me.
This is too exhausting.
We need to find them.
Don't exercise using me.
Don't train your legs using me.
(Exercising)
- This is impossible. - It's impossible.
(2 minutes remain and they haven't found anyone.)
Why is there no one?
Where are they?
There's no one.
(They have to win a hint this time.)
I thought someone was here.
There's no one.
We looked everywhere.
Where are they?
Why is it so hard?
They just have to open all the cars.
I think I hear someone.
I'll act. I'll open the door to lure them.
If they find you, leave the van screaming.
(Will the bait strategy work?)
They just have to open all the cars.
(KCM tries to escape.)
Gosh.
(Catch me if you can.)
(The bait is here.)
(He's running away to distract them.)
He shouldn't run away.
You can't run away.
(He's caught.)
(KCM lets them arrest him while saving Won Hee.)
(Thank you, Mr. Bait.)
What should I do?
You can't run away.
(They start looking for the others.)
(Kyung Hwan hears someone.)
You can't run away.
Is someone here?
I found one.
I found Kyung Hwan.
(That was close.)
I found him.
(They approach Chun Hee.)
They're nowhere.
Can they be in the trunks?
(Frozen)
I didn't look in the trunks.
You're out.
Gosh.
- Chun Hee is out. - What is this?
(Team Running Man found 3.)
- Chun Hee was here. - How did you know?
It was easy.
Yong Man is completely invisible.
It'll be impossible to find me.
Where's Won Hee?
She's nowhere.
(Someone must be around here.)
(Ji Hyo is right in front of Yong Man.)
I didn't look in the trunks.
(He might get caught.)
(Ji Hyo is near Yong Man.)
(Yong Man is sitting in the front seat.)
(Yong Man is in danger. Will he get caught?)
(Let me search your van.)
I found Yong Man.
- Gosh. - I found him.
(Ji Hyo found Yong Man with her gut feeling.)
- I found him. - Where was he?
(How did she find him?)
There's only five seconds left.
(He could have held out a few more seconds.)
It's unbelievable.
Ji Hyo is amazing.
(The search is over.)
We haven't found Won Hee.
Where's she?
(Here I am.)
(Team Running Man missed Won Hee.)
(Team Running Man found everyone except Won Hee.)
- Let's sing something easy. - It'll bring us together.
As we're Team Friends, let's sing "My Friend".
("My Friend" by Insooni)
- It has rap. - Let's do it.
(Team Friends are singing "My Friend".)
Do something.
The song started.
The door won't open.
What should I do? There's nowhere to hide.
I think it'll show.
Kwang Soo, what are you going to do?
Can I hide behind your legs?
- Here? - Yes.
I think it'll be hard.
(Struggling)
What should I do?
(He gave up right away.)
The song is almost over.
(The song is almost over. They need to hide soon.)
(What's their score?)
It's 90...
We got 100 points.
(Their performance of friendship got 100 points.)
(They won 5 minutes.)
We don't have much time.
I'm sorry, but I don't think I can run.
(The search begins.)
Push it.
(They have to find everyone to win.)
- There. - Hurry.
- Start from here. - From here?
Go through them one by one.
Turn on the light.
(Searching)
There's one. I found one right away.
It's Ji Hyo.
(She runs away.)
You're out.
(Ji Hyo got caught after 30 seconds.)
I was caught by you.
I got caught while looking at Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook was sending a signal to Ji Hyo.)
He's there.
(I found him.)
(He's caught.)
I'm caught, right?
Am I caught?
(Jong Kook got caught after a minute, too.)
- I'm caught. - I see.
(I feel something.)
Who's this?
- Who is this? - It's Seok Jin.
- I found Seok Jin. - I didn't know you'd find me.
I found Seok Jin.
(Someone's here.)
(What is this weird-looking creature?)
(Laughing)
What is this?
(It's Kwang Soo.)
You're unbelievable.
What is this?
(He made himself more conspicuous.)
- How did you know it was me? - Gosh.
- How did you know? - How would I not know?
I covered my head.
How did you know?
- What is this? - I thought no one would know.
It didn't work.
(Kwang Soo got caught with 1 minute left.)
- That was close. - Gosh.
(Haha is the only hope now.)
Haha is playing a trick.
Excuse me.
Look closely behind the drivers.
Is he not here?
(If they find Haha, they'll win the hint.)
(Let's find Haha and win the hint.)
That's strange.
(They're approaching Haha.)
This is strange.
Are they here?
(He has to hold out just a little bit longer.)
Look closely. Check the front seat.
Is he not there?
How can he be nowhere?
This is impossible.
(Yong Man approaches Haha with 10 seconds left.)
Are there only 10 seconds left?
Excuse me.
(Let me search your van.)
(Gosh)
(Will he get caught or not?)
All right.
(Yong Man moves away.)
- Are there only 10 seconds left? - Only 10 seconds?
(That was close.)
(There are 5 seconds left.)
Did you find him?
(Where are you?)
Time's up.
They haven't found Haha.
Haha is great at hiding.
Where is he?
That was incredible.
(Haha was hiding under the passenger seat.)
Thank you.
(Haha saved his team members' faces.)
This is unbelievable.
(Team Friends found everyone except Haha.)
We have no choice.
We'll have to have a singing competition.
- We're tied again. - Both teams got 100 points earlier.
I'm sorry to say this, but I looked down on them at first.
- We shouldn't. - But you're amazing.
(Did you just judge us?)
You guys are clumsier than we expected.
(You guys are clumsy.)
Pick a member of the other team who should sing.
- Would that be okay? - Then...
- We choose Won Hee. - I think we'll win.
Won Hee will sing on behalf of Team Friends. Who do you choose?
- We choose Ji Hyo. - You choose Ji Hyo.
She's making that face again.
Won Hee and Ji Hyo's scores will...
determine the result of the third round.
- All right. - Are songs with high notes better?
If you sing loud, you'll probably get a high score.
That's why we got a high score earlier.
- Try "Tears". - How does it go?
(This song is known for extremely high notes.)
- Won Hee's going to sing "Tears". - Go to the center.
(She drinks water before singing.)
Please make some room.
(This singing competition will determine the result.)
It's for your team.
- Your team's destiny depends on it. - Go for it.
("Tears" by So Chan Whee)
- All right. - Here we go.
(Let me introduce you to tonight's singer, Kim Won Hee.)
(Walking)
(She sets the mood by walking sexily.)
Go, Won Hee!
(I have a good feeling.)
- Let's go. - You can do it.
(Give me the beat.)
Here we go.
(Everyone's having fun.)
(Enjoying)
(How will she start the first line?)
Nothing!
- Nothing... Nothing has happened - Oh, no.
(She stuttered.)
(It wasn't a good start.)
(She's calm again.)
(She's fully focused.)
(She's following the camera skilfully.)
(Her awesome stage presence is exciting the audience.)
Waiting for me
(Amazing vibration skills)
(That sounded very heartfelt.)
- Just hate me instead - Good.
- Hate! - Hate me!
(Her voice is surprisingly addictive.)
- Don't show! - Good!
(The high notes are coming.)
(Here we go.)
Here we go.
(Are you ready for the climax?)
- Here we go. - Let's go!
Don't say
I'm a cruel woman
(She pulled off the high notes.)
(The middle-aged man is having fun.)
It's for your sake
(He's feeling the groove.)
Let's go.
Don't forget my love
You're in my heart
(Perfect shouting)
It won't take long
(It is a passionate performance.)
Until your sadness goes away
(Kim Won Hee forever!)
(She's exhausted.)
- What's the score? - What's the score?
- No. - Let's see.
(The queen of singing is born.)
(Thank goodness.)
You did it. It's a decent score.
- It was higher than I expected. - Ji Hyo, you can do this.
- A score of 82 is very high. - Be prepared.
I think I burst a capillary.
(Shouting without proper instruction might cause high blood pressure.)
It's okay, Won Hee.
Everything was good except for the score.
- Ji Hyo can sing very well. - Really?
- I heard Ji Hyo is a good singer. - Will it be a close match?
- All right. - I will sing "Mr. Chu".
- "Mr. Chu". - That's nice.
It's a song by Apink.
- You can do this. - Dance, Ji Hyo.
- How will she sing? - You are cool.
All right.
You look young.
- You look young. - Here I go.
- That's good. - Her voice is steady.
- We will lose. - Song Ji Hyo!
Even when I pinch my cheeks 2 and 3 times
- Song Ji Hyo! - Song Ji Hyo!
It's like dreaming, dreaming
My goodness.
(Here comes the highlight of cuteness.)
- Let's go. - In 1, 2, 3.
Mr. Chu, kiss on your lips
(Ji Hyo's unexpected charm brings everyone together.)
- Come to me secretly - Come to me secretly
(Middle-aged men suddenly join in.)
- My goodness. - She is doing a good job.
You are my one and only Mr. Chu
We don't know what her score will be.
- I think she did well. - Please let it be 83.
The winning team will be decided.
This is nerve-wracking.
(Which team will win and receive a hint on treasure?)
- The winning team will be decided. - This is nerve-wracking.
(You sang well.)
It's a bad score.
(The final score is 82 to 75.)
(Team Friends receives a prize and a hint on treasure.)
It's better to sing a song with high notes.
You did a good job.
- High notes have an advantage. - It was fun.
You are lacking in many ways.
Even I didn't sing like you.
- She did a good job. - Won Hee was smart.
As promised, I will give you a prize of Round Three.
(The prize of Round Three goes to Team Friends as well.)
- We lost again. - They are good.
- Here is the prize I prepared. - It's inside a silver box.
I am so jealous.
It can't be helped.
I am excited.
- Here is the prize I prepared. - It's inside a silver box.
- It's a tablet PC. - I knew it.
- Congratulations. - It's yours, Won Hee.
Thank you.
- All right. - Is a tablet PC inside?
- Can I open it? - No way.
I shouldn't open it now. Thank you.
- Round Four starts now. - The prize will be a laptop.
- Jae Seok is cool. - Maybe there are two inside.
There is only one.
Will Round Four take place here?
(Haha picked something up.)
(He steals the hint.)
- Stay quiet. - All right.
They dropped the hint...
while dancing.
- Really? - Is that a hint?
Really?
What does it say?
It's green grasshopper.
- Really? - Yes.
- What does it mean? - What is it?
It's incredible that we got this hint.
(During the singing competition five minutes ago)
(Grasshopper was dangling from his pocket.)
(It fell right away.)
(What's the new hint Team Friends received?)
What is this?
- Wait a minute. - This is incredible.
- Inside the ship... - A washing machine?
must be a washing machine or laundry.
- It could be laundry. - Laundry.
I don't think it's a ship.
- You don't think it's a ship. - I think...
it means Jae Seok's stomach.
- Jae Seok's stomach. - That's right.
Listen, everyone.
Team Running Man isn't doing so well in games.
We will win for certain this time.
The last round is "Telepathy with Jae Seok".
- Telepathy. - I don't know the questions.
The team with the same answer as mine will win.
(The team with the same answer as Jae Seok's answer will win.)
- We are confident. - There is only one question.
- This is nerve-wracking. - There is only one question.
- All right. - Here is the question.
When Jae Seok takes a shower,
which body part does he wash first?
(When Jae Seok takes a shower, which body part does he wash first?)
Which body part does he wash first?
(Where does Jae Seok wash first?)
- Wait a minute. - We can't write it.
We can't write it.
- What do you mean? - Can we write it?
- How precise do we need to be? - My goodness.
- He washes vigorously. - Like crazy.
(That's embarrassing.)
- I need to keep the answer clean. - It will air after all.
I will be straightforward with my answer.
- I will be straightforward. - Ji Hyo is speechless.
We know the answer.
- Ji Hyo is speechless. - We have known him for seven years.
- We know. - It has to be the right answer.
Yong Man has taken a bath with Jae Seok.
Didn't you take a bath with him often?
- It has been many years. - That's right.
It has been a while since we went to a sauna.
- It has been over 10 years. - It has been 10 years.
At the count of three, lift up the answer.
In 1, 2, and 3.
(Face, head)
What did they write?
- Face? - We wrote, "Face".
We wrote, "Head".
- I have seen Jae Seok wash it. - We mean the entire head.
What's the answer? Jae Seok, lift up your answer.
In 1, 2, and 3.
(What could Jae Seok's answer be?)
(Which body part does he wash first in a shower?)
- In 1, 2, and 3. - Face.
(Face)
Face.
(Jae Seok's most precious body part is face.)
- It was face. - We are right!
(What about head?)
You should count "Head" as the right answer.
- I wash my face and head together. - I often take a shower with him.
Jae Seok washes his face and head together.
Answers from both teams are correct.
- It's the right decision. - My goodness.
To be honest,
this isn't the right answer.
- Here is the right answer. - His hand moves south.
He does this.
He gently wets it.
- My goodness. - Then he washes his hair.
(Running Man cheers for your shower.)
Let's move on to the last question.
Here is the question. Which one...
is Jae Seok more confident about?
Face or personality?
- Is there body? - This is too easy.
- Everyone can shout out the answer. - There is no doubt.
The entire nation will be able to get it right.
- It's his thought that matters. - Is that right?
- He might think the same. - Will he write honestly?
He has conscience, right?
- I think so. - Let's leave it to his conscience.
I trust him to have conscience.
- He might lie to be funny. - This is hard.
He might choose the other one.
I think it's personality.
- This can't be right. - Not his face.
He won't choose this one if he has conscience.
Please answer conscientiously.
I hope Jae Seok will answer with his hand over his heart.
- Me, too. - I trust him to have conscience.
Raise your answers at the count of three.
- In 1, 2, and 3. - I hope he isn't shameless.
This must be what he wrote.
(Personality)
(Face)
(Personality versus face)
- His answer can't be face. - Jae Seok.
Raise your answer at the count of three.
I say this with a hand over my heart.
When I look back on my life,
this is the logical choice between the two.
(Will Jae Seok's choice be his unique face?)
(Will it be his considerate personality?)
(What did Jae Seok choose as his lethal charm?)
If he has conscience...
- What is his answer? - Show us.
(What did Jae Seok choose?)
- In 1, 2, and 3. - It has to be his answer.
He didn't lift it up right away.
(Jae Seok chose face.)
(Jae Seok has a nice face.)
- In 1, 2, and 3. - Face.
- My goodness. - Yes!
(Team Running Man's answer is correct.)
- You are the absolute worst. - It's not personality.
- You are shameless. - It's not personality.
- How could you do that? - You are the national MC.
- It's not personality. - You are the national MC.
- It's not personality. - You succeeded because of it.
- You face didn't make you famous. - I think it's face.
- You are shameless. - My face.
- It's my face. - You have problems.
You chose face. You know me well.
I am annoyed even though we got it right.
Even Team Running Man are annoyed.
- It's frustrating. - I don't care.
If I must choose between the two, it's face.
You have no conscience.
- My goodness. - I can't believe him.
Team Friends won prizes up to Round Three.
- The prize of Round Four... - A small car.
- goes to Team Running Man. - A small car?
(Team Running Man took a win. What will be the prize?)
(The prize of Round One was a set of vitamin supplements.)
(The prize of Round Two was a set of Korean beef.)
(The prize of Round Three was a tablet PC.)
(What will be the prize of Round Four?)
(For goodness' sake!)
(He throws it on the floor.)
- What is it? - Are you out of your mind?
It's my signed name tag.
It's Jae Seok's name tag.
(The prize of Round Four is Jae Seok's signed name tag.)
- Are you out of your mind? - Are you serious?
- It suits the theme of the day. - Gosh...
(What's the last hint?)
You are supposed to have a nice personality.
(All the hints for the treasure have been distributed.)
- Let me see your navel. - Why do you want to see my navel?
(He is flustered.)
Paper ship.
(The hints from Round One and Two were paper ship and grasshopper.)
(The hint from Round Three was a care label for clothes.)
(Clothes, ship, grasshopper)
- What are you talking about? - You shouldn't have done that.
- What are you doing? - Come over here.
There is something.
- Wait a minute. - Let go.
- Get out of the way. - What is happening?
- What are you doing? - Microphone.
What about the microphone?
(A hint for the treasure is somewhere on his clothes.)
What are you keeping from me?
What is going on?
He took it away.
(They thoroughly search his body.)
What are you doing to me?
(Screaming)
- Where is it? - Take off his pants.
Won Hee, how can you say that to your friend?
(He gets goosebumps.)
- Take them off. - No!
(In the midst of public's roaring attention,)
(his clothes are taken off.)
(They take off his clothes rather forcefully.)
It's here.
- What is happening? - Hey. It's in here.
- Take it. - Hurry.
Hey. That's mine.
(He has finally gotten wind of it.)
(It's a tight tug of war.)
- It's inside the clothes. - It's ours.
(What is it that you need at a moment like this?)
(It's speed!)
(Jong Kook gets Jae Seok's clothes.)
(Run away with his clothes!)
Jong Kook. Get in the car.
Get in the car and lock it.
Run. We have to run. Hurry.
Close the door. Close it!
Lock the door.
- Lock the door. - I did.
(Jong Kook manages to get inside the car.)
"Yu Jae Seok".
(What is the hint for the treasure hidden inside Jae Seok's clothes?)
(Yu Jae Seok's cameraman)
(Does Kwon Ryeol have the treasure?)
(Ripping)
(He hides the hint first.)
Did you find it?
(When Team Friends surrounds Jong Kook,)
(Kwang Soo runs at his full speed to Kwon Ryeol.)
(Kwon Ryeol, give me the treasure.)
(What is happening now?)
What is it?
(Other members start to gather around him.)
What is it? What do you know?
- Help me. - Come on.
She's bluffing. Go. Hurry.
Hurry. They already took it.
You are pretending, right? You don't have it, right?
Goodness.
Okay!
It's over!
Ji Hyo! We found it.
Ji Hyo found it!
(Team Running Man acquires the treasure.)
What is this?
(He's still confused.)
Jae Seok's cameraman had the treasure.
- What's going on? - You must be cold. Wear this.
- Put this on. Thank you. - How could you...
Are you telling me now that I should put this on?
- You must be cold. - Are you okay?
Don't drop hints like this.
- Why would you lose hints? - I lost this before.
I lost this hint before.
I looked for this for so long.
Running Man, Member's Week.
It was Jae Seok's week.
How can you call it's my week?
(He's about to cry.)
- My gosh. - His clothes are all ripped.
You did what you wanted. You even have a nice outfit.
- I am so jealous. - Didn't you have fun?
- That's right. - You pretended to be generous...
and gave us presents.
Now that I think about it, you are right.
Everyone all gathered around you at the end. You are a powerful man.
(Even a film star can't get that much attention.)
- You're right. - Everyone clustered around you.
Everyone.
- You had fun, right? - Yes, we did.
I haven't filmed anything like this before.
As I told you before...
Although I didn't know about the twist at the end,
my week with the people I love has delightfully finished.
I'd like to thank the five of you who joined us today.
- Thank you. - Next week will be Kwang Soo's.
(Please look forward to Kwang Soo's week.)
It's the Member's Week of Running Man.
(The 7th host)
(The last host is Lee Kwang Soo.)
Hello, members of Running Man!
I will give you a mission.
Until the midnight,
think about a trip we can take at night for me.
Then, come to the place where we film our opening segment.
(However)
Don't wear any makeup.
Don't do your hair.
Don't bring your manager or your stylist.
Running Man members, don't forget to come at 12am.
Viewers, my week will be...
I will bet everything I have and make sure...
I will absolutely make sure...
that I succeed this time.
Thank you!
(The last Member's Week will visit you.)
(Running Man)