(Running Pictures Production)
(Real Criminal Variety, City of Crime)
(October, 2017, Ilsan, Gyeonggi Province)
(The head of Mungdol Gang, CEO Mung)
(Mungdol Gang's Underboss, Dol So Min)
(We rule Ilsan.)
(This is a cafe that is managed by Mungdol Gang.)
Let's go and collect money.
I heard this cafe serves delicious coffee.
Hey, hey.
- You can't run a cafe without us. - I hear the business is going well.
(Pay your street tax.)
Let's see how tasty their coffee is.
You can't run a cafe without us.
Where is the owner? Hey, where is the owner?
(She is the owner of the cafe who agreed to the shoot.)
Are you the owner?
You can't run a cafe without us.
The owner of this cafe looks feisty.
(Maybe we should stop, So Min.)
She looks aggressive.
The owner of the cafe seems to be older than us.
(The owner of the cafe bursts out laughing.)
(It's my turn.)
I hear the business is going well.
- Talk to her. - Okay.
You can't run a cafe without us.
I am sorry.
- Please give me iced Americano. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Order one for me, too.
- Please give me 2 iced Americano. - 2, 2.
- Give us two. - I don't have any money.
Let's go.
I didn't bring money.
All right, President Kim.
- I didn't bring money. - That's not how you should work.
My goodness.
(Get out of my way.)
(Who are these men?)
(Running Man Police Department Violent Crimes Unit 1, Ma Jong Kook)
For goodness' sake.
(Violent Crimes Unit 1, Cunning Yang and Ha Ro Ro)
You are right.
Where are they?
Wait until we catch them. Where are they?
- Let's go. - Yes, sir.
- Say hello to him. - I can't believe you.
- He is a man who looks out for us. - I see. A detective on our side.
I told you to lay low.
- You did. - Why won't you listen?
Why are you creating so much noise?
- Who are you? - "Who are you?"
Who are you?
Can't you tell? I am a police officer.
Police officer, my foot! You drew that mustache.
- Ha Ro Ro. - Who are you?
Say something.
I can't.
- Why not? - I am scared.
- What do you mean? - I'd like to move teams.
What happened to your face?
I popped a pimple.
- Did you pop a pimple? - Yes.
Do you have folliculitis? Do you have face mites?
- I couldn't pop it all the way. - Really?
It's too painful.
Why do you keep causing trouble?
What is wrong with you?
- For goodness' sake. - Who do you think you are?
- Who do you think you are? - You didn't watch "The Outlaws".
No, I didn't.
- You didn't watch it. - No, I didn't.
You should have watched it.
- Who do you think you are? - Hello.
- I guess you watched it. - Yes.
All right.
Give us three cups of coffee.
Pay for the coffee.
May I pay with my watch?
Pay with your watch.
- Pay with your watch. - She didn't watch the movie.
- Take off your watch. - She didn't watch the movie.
Let's wait for the coffee.
Why are you so intimidated? Say something.
- Ha Ro Ro. - Hey.
I am sorry, but bring us the coffee when it comes out.
Bring us coffee when it comes out.
How dare you order me around?
- She didn't watch the movie. - You folliculitis!
She didn't watch "The Outlaws".
How dare you order me around?
I don't have to act according to my character, right?
(He pulls out his gun in a childish way.)
- Come on, Ha Ro Ro. - You didn't watch the movie.
- Shoot me! - Don't be ridiculous.
This is getting out of hand.
You can't treat her like this. Shoot me instead.
This is upsetting. We gave you so much money.
- I understand that but... - Don't be ridiculous.
- You are doing well. - This is upsetting.
- You are doing well. - This is "The Outlaws".
- You can't treat her like this. - Come on.
Don't confuse it with another movie.
- You are doing well. - Impressive!
- For goodness' sake. - This is "The Outlaws".
Impressive!
- You are confusing the movie. - We are not in Busan.
This isn't "Nameless Gangster: Rules of Time".
We are in Yanbian. Get it right.
I doubt the production crew will use more of this bit.
- Bring us coffee. - Bring us coffee.
Folliculitis!
"Folliculitis"?
(A bigger crisis heads their way.)
That's right.
For goodness' sake.
(It looks like...)
This is nice.
It seems like they will make a grand entrance.
(Where are the remaining three?)
Where are they?
(Where are the weaklings?)
What? What?
Who is that?
- What? What? - It's exactly like the movie.
(They back away.)
What are you filming?
(The representative gang for the unlucky, Yuchen Gang)
Did you come alone?
(Head of Yuchen Gang, Yu Chen)
All right.
(Yuchen Gang's Underboss, Wi Kwang Rak)
(Just another member of Yuchen Gang, Nose Tae)
(Are you watching this, the police and Mungdol Gang?)
Did you come alone?
(Kwon Ryul)
Do you have company?
- Did you eat? - Not yet.
Then why are you so fat?
(They are known to attack with facts.)
Did you come alone?
It's exactly like the movie.
No way.
(Their costumes are high-quality.)
- They look really scary. - Did you come alone?
It must have been hard to get made up.
Isn't he Hwang Jung Min?
- This is "The Wailing". - "The Wailing".
This is "The Wailing".
Please act like Young Gu.
(He looks like Young Gu.)
I am sorry,
but he is Lim Ha Ryong.
He looks like Lim Ha Ryong.
- He looks like Lim Ha Ryong. - He does.
- He looks like Lim Ha Ryong. - Seriously.
"I am too old for this."
- "I am too old for this." - My goodness.
Kwang Soo looks exactly like the character in the movie.
Kwang Soo's makeup took forever.
It must have been hard to get that makeup done.
Let's not make any comment on it.
- Why not? - "Why not?"
- Make fun of me. - Let's leave him be.
It took an hour and a half.
He is Krillin.
- Do you think it's summer? - What?
Are you a physical education teacher?
Let's give a powerful performance.
- Do you know who we are? - What?
Do you know who we are?
Who are you?
The fight is on.
What did you say?
- Who are you? - He looks strong.
For goodness' sake.
Who are you?
(Pushing)
(He falls backwards.)
What do you think you are doing?
Nose Tae.
A staff member shouldn't interfere.
Go away.
Come on.
(Young Gu doesn't understand the situation.)
- He looks exactly like Young Gu. - Don't touch him.
What is this?
Do you want to get slapped?
- Please stop. - Seok Jin,
- your performance is too much. - Please stop.
You have never been in a comedy skit, right?
He has never been in a comedy skit.
I haven't been in a lot of them.
What kind of a dialect is that?
For goodness' sake.
- What kind of a dialect is that? - He just sounds cute.
- Do you know who I am? - I haven't been in a lot of them.
The race, City of Crime,
is not about getting a penalty, but about winning prize money.
(City of Crime)
It's in a long time.
- It's about prize money? - I see.
The winning gang in each mission...
will be given working capital to their digital moneybox.
Only one member of the gang with the most amount of capital...
will engross the money in the end.
- Only one? - So only one will take the money.
- It's an individual game. - That's right.
Each gang will have a boss as well.
Your bosses will be among the three guests who will join us later.
- We have guests? - We have guests.
- Three guests. - Is that right?
I didn't know.
I hope we don't have any female guests today.
Please.
- Please. - I hope.
- I hope they're male guests. - Who are they?
- What? - This song's from "The Godfather".
- "The Godfather". - Maybe it's Lim Ha Ryong.
- Really? - "The Godfather".
(Who's the first guest to come out along with this music?)
- Gosh. - Noh Sa Yeon.
Sa Yeon.
- Sa Yeon. - Hi.
- Are you here alone? - Yes.
- Gosh. - Hi, Sa Yeon.
- Hello. - Hi.
Sa Yeon.
(The godmother intimidates the members as soon as she joins.)
- Hello. - Ms. Tuna.
(Oh, right.)
She had a bad experience during her last appearance.
(Sa Yeon came out on the Princess Special in July 15, 2012.)
(Her butler, Kwang Soo, was too weak to serve her right.)
It looks like you're fishing her out of a net.
(She was as energetic as a tuna.)
You think she's a tuna or something?
(And so became her nickname, Ms. Tuna.)
- Your outfit today... - Mackerel.
reminds me of a mackerel.
It's blue like a mackerel.
- Let's call her Ms. Mackerel today. - Goodness.
- Blue mackerel. - Mackerel.
- She's our guest for today. - It goes perfect for the special.
- Sa Yeon, you're... - Kwang Soo?
- Well... - She burst out laughing.
- I'm losing my confidence. - Enjoy.
- Feel free to laugh at him. - I feel so timid and shy.
Sa Yeon is here with us as our first boss today.
- Welcome, Sa Yeon. - Thank you.
- Let's bring in our next boss. - Okay.
(Who's the second boss?)
- What's this? - Is this "Wonder Woman"?
It's "Superman".
(The next boss comes out with the song from "The Smurfs".)
Goodness, it's Ha Yeon Soo.
(She's the smile captain, Ha Yeon Soo.)
- Hello. - Goodness.
- It's you, Yeon Soo. - Hello.
- Hello. - Long time no see.
- Hello. - It's so good to see you.
- Hello. - Hi.
(He's flustered to see Yeon Soo.)
- She's like a doll. - How...
- She hasn't changed a bit. - Kwang Soo...
What should he do?
How have you been, Yeon Soo?
(Stepping away)
- Goodness. - How have you been?
(I've changed a lot, haven't I?)
- Kwang Soo. - My goodness.
- I missed you. - Wear this.
That'll make it weirder.
- Wear this. - What should he do?
Her face is so small.
- It's so small. - It's unbelievable.
If you want to get along with me, you better stand 1m ahead.
Okay.
Now, they look the same size.
- Let me see. - Does it seem all right?
Your face is still a bit bigger.
(Sa Yeon's face is still bigger.)
- What? - Step back a little more.
- There you go. - It's done.
- It's done. - This will do it.
- Good. - Goodness.
Yeon Soo's so cruel. She really stands in the front.
I'm so glad to have her with us.
All right. Let's see who's our third boss.
- We have one more? - Kwang Soo...
Please come on out.
(Who's their third boss?)
- What? - What?
Is it Kang Daniel?
It must be Wanna One.
(Wanna One's "Pick Me" gets played.)
(They mentioned his name many times, but he hasn't come out yet.)
(Is it the trendy idol group Wanna One's Kang Daniel?)
(You've waited for so long.)
What's this?
(They had false hope.)
Why are you here again?
(Call him Cho Daniel.)
He should've at least changed the opening song.
He comes out too often.
(Sae Ho, you aren't the one we've waited for.)
Goodbye.
- Goodness, Sae Ho. - Do I get in the car?
- Yes. - In this car?
I'm sorry, but this isn't my car.
Really? Don't worry. He'll give you a ride.
Please go home.
- Bye. - Sorry.
- I won't see you off. - You've gotten a makeover.
- Yes. - Bye.
- Good job for today. - He got the wrong schedule.
- Bye. - He gave us a big impact though.
- That was short but thick. - I'd just go home if I were him.
- It's not good for him either. - Good job.
It hasn't been long since he last appeared.
- And the song was the same. - We're fed up with it.
Right.
(It should be okay to go again now.)
- He comes too often. - I know.
- He's here again. - He came out not long ago.
The driver... What?
Try it.
(The crew members give him another chance to dance.)
There he goes again.
Sae Ho's dance is always entertaining.
(Let me show you how I dance.)
(Let's dance together, Sae Ho.)
Let's dance together.
I'm doing this for your sake.
- Please welcome, Sae Ho. - Hello.
- Sae Ho never lets us down. - Come this way.
- He never lets us down. - Hello.
Sae Ho is with us as our guest for today.
- He's not talking. - Is he a streetlamp or what?
- Goodness. - He's so reserved today.
- Kwang Soo. - You know, Kareem Abdul-Jabbar?
- What are you talking about? - Abdul-Jabbar.
- He looks like him. - Goodness.
No, he looks like Squidward from "Spongebob Squarepants".
What do you mean?
(Kwang Soo just looks funny.)
All right, let's bring in...
- our next guest. - We have another guest?
- What? - There's one more?
Please come out.
What?
Will it be Nam Chang Hee?
Nam Chang Hee?
Right, it's about time he joined us.
Who is it?
(Their eyes open wide.)
(Who's the fourth guest?)
(He's Wanna One's Kang Daniel.)
(Daniel is really here!)
- Really? - Goodness.
- He's here. - Goodness.
- Daniel! - Goodness.
- Daniel. - Hi.
Daniel.
(The trendy star is finally on Running Man.)
- Hello. - It's really Kang Daniel.
(He's the real star among the ladies.)
Daniel.
- Daniel. - He's so handsome.
- He's cute. - Goodness.
- Daniel. - Gosh.
- Gosh. - Come to the middle.
- I'm sorry, - Daniel.
- but why are you blushing? - I was so surprised.
So many people are gathered here.
- They aren't usually like this. - They're hurting my feelings.
This is upsetting. I mean, we're well aware that they like Daniel.
- It's all right. - Of course.
But when we do our opening, they usually...
- I know, they pick their noses. - You're right.
Some of them look very unfamiliar.
Daniel is here with us.
- Daniel! - They're going crazy here.
- They usually don't say much. - Right.
Daniel!
(All of a sudden)
It's over.
She has her eyes on him, so you have no chance.
- Give in. - Goodness.
You can't go near him.
Anyway, I should mention this.
This year is Sa Yeon's 40th-year anniversary since her debut.
- Really? - 40th-year anniversary.
She debuted when I was two years old.
I'm planning to hold a dinner show at the end of this year...
to celebrate my debut anniversary.
- Congratulations. - Dinner show.
Does that mean you'll cook dinner yourself?
Yes, I'll cook myself.
- That's new. - Goodness.
- I bet the dishes will be amazing. - This is...
You'll eat, and the audience will give a round of applause for that.
- Goodness. - That's not it.
The show will be about eating.
"You can do it! Finish one more bowl."
Goodness.
That's not it. She's planning to hold her own talk show.
- To celebrate her anniversary. - Congratulations.
She's our big senior in this field. She's admirable.
- Right. - I hope...
- Hold on. - What?
Will you keep being like this today, Kwang Soo?
- Just wear this. - He doesn't talk at all.
- He should regain his confidence. - That makeover's too much.
He lost a lot of confidence ever since Yeon Soo came out.
- You should've told me before. - Goodness.
- Kwang Soo... - I didn't know.
Be confident.
He lost confidence because of Yeon Soo.
- I really didn't know. - He'd be like that all day long.
Yeon Soo is his type.
- She is. - Someone cute and small.
Yeon Soo gave me this look as if she was looking at an insect.
Kwang Soo likes girls who are like Yeon Soo.
I remember when Yeon Soo came out last time, she played...
- that game with Jong Kook. - I remember it too.
The kiss.
The video clip is still on the internet.
That video is still all over the internet.
So many people watched it too.
What? Oh, that's the one.
- Gosh, this. - I mean...
- Check this out. - Stop it.
- When she came out... - It was the first time.
Look at Jong Kook's gums.
- It's disgusting. - I tried not to touch her lips.
Look. Let me clarify things for you.
This is when he played the game with Yeon Soo.
This is when he played the game with Sa Yeon.
Goodness.
- I knew it. - Goodness.
- Why you little... - Calm down.
- You're mistaken. - You're unbelievable.
He really didn't want to touch her lips.
What scares me the most is not Jong Kook...
but that Sa Yeon's smiling there.
(Sa Yeon's smiling in this picture.)
Goodness. I'm serious.
(Haha indeed has amazing observation skills.)
(Sa Yeon's experienced enough to keep her smile in any situation.)
All right, let's talk briefly about you, Sae Ho.
There's one question for you.
"You join us once every month, so why is that?"
(Why do you keep coming out?)
- It's a question. - Oh, is that right?
- It says in the script here. - It's real.
- It's real. - I'm telling you.
- It's really written on the script. - Why?
- Why would I lie? - Gosh.
- I don't make up stories. - Okay.
Let me tell you this again.
The crew members did ask me to come out.
I asked you the other time as well, but who cast you?
The scriptwriter named Eun Kyung. There she is.
- Eun Kyung? - Yes.
- That's how it happened. - Eun Kyung gave me a call.
She said, "You're available on Monday, right?"
- She was certain. - She wasn't asking.
- Wait. - She knew.
- She didn't ask if you were free? - No, she didn't.
She said as if she was certain I was free on Monday.
- "Wait." - When I was about to check,
she said, "Tanhyeon by 10:40am," and hung up.
- "Tanhyeon by 10:40am." - She said that because...
- she had a gut feeling that he was. - Right. So...
I told her that I might not...
- Here's the next question. - Okay.
"What is the reason the crew invites you often?"
- This is your next question. - I wasn't finished.
We don't have time.
- We're moving on to Daniel. - We need to interview Daniel.
(Sae Ho gives up his air time for viewers who are waiting for Daniel.)
We all know that.
- We are moving on. - Okay. We're moving like a train.
- Answer questions on your website. - Should we move on or not?
- All right. I will. - Say what you want to say there.
All right. Here's our next guest,
Kang Daniel!
(This is the interview everyone has been waiting for.)
This is Korea, Daniel's motherland!
All right. Daniel...
- is the most sought-after star. - Indeed.
Don't you feel the popularity you have garnered these days?
- They support me for my effort. - Exactly.
Jong Kook, as a former idol singer who has been in the industry...
- longer than he has... - Right. I was once an idol.
- He's a living history. - Must he be careful of anything?
- He must be careful of women. - Jong Kook.
- Right. - That's so true.
- How could you say that? - He must be careful of them now.
- I mean it. - Goodness.
Sa Yeon, what do you think? You've been a singer for a long time too.
Moo Song wasn't careful of women, so he ended up with her.
(He makes a remark out of the blue.)
(Unintentionally, she becomes the living sermon of his advice.)
- I said it because we're close. - Hey.
- Moo Song really wants to see you. - No, no.
He said he would like to treat you to a meal.
My apologies.
- At Daniel's age... - We are close friends.
- We really are close friends. - He...
- They really are. - Right now, he's so innocent.
Just like we talked about earlier,
- Daniel is incredibly popular. - I agree.
- He's on commercials and shows. - Thank you.
I bet you don't get to sleep a lot these days.
- He's the 1st choice for everyone. - I sleep about 2 or 3 hours.
- You only sleep that little? - Yes.
- Poor you. - How many hours did you sleep?
- I slept for about 12 hours. - 12 hours?
- That's a bit alarming. - I did sleep for 12 hours.
- That's not healthy. - Seok Jin.
People might think you're sleeping forever.
I took a nap yesterday and woke up today.
Then that can't be considered napping.
- You slept too much. - Seok Jin.
- You should visit the clinic. - That's enough.
- I took a nap, but it was morning. - That happens to people.
- But it's too much. Go to a clinic. - Some do sleep that much.
- Get yourself checked out. - Well,
- I should save up when I can. - Hey, let's listen to Daniel.
(Everyone, be quiet!)
(Every viewer wanted to say the same.)
- Anyway, his smile is so pretty. - Right.
- It is very pretty. - All right, Daniel.
- I want to see him dance. - Dance?
- Daniel's dancing? - The move with the thigh.
- I really want to see it. - Daniel, please do the dance.
(Daniel dances for the show.)
- He's an excellent dancer. - This is great.
(He was acting shy, but his attitude suddenly changes.)
(His dance moves are fancy as he's the center of Wanna One.)
(Jaw-dropping)
(Everyone including the crew pays him the utmost attention.)
(You pierce into my heart like my destiny)
(Open your heart to me)
(The body wave opens the hearts of the female viewers.)
(Their hearts are racing.)
- Do the move with the thigh! - Do the thigh move!
(Stroking)
(Daniel, do whatever you want to do!)
Stop it. Don't!
Hey, the kids are watching. Stop.
- Why are you so red? - Stop it.
- Leave me alone. - No, don't do it!
- Come on, Se Chan. - Stop it.
- Stop scratching your thigh. - Gosh, it's so frustrating.
- You stopped me from dancing. - He was great.
Thank you.
Hey, we...
When it got hectic,
- Sa Yeon came quietly and hugged... - She hugged him?
(Approaching)
(Sa Yeon abruptly approached and hugged him.)
(Goodness, did you see that?)
I saw it.
She is very affectionate towards her junior singers.
- I'm his entertainment senior. - I understand.
- He's so cute. He just started. - That's right.
- I wanted him to be a good singer. - Thank you.
(Ji Hyo, look at me.)
So Min keeps imitating Daniel's dance.
- What did she do? - Come here, and show them.
- So Min, do your thing. - What is it?
So Min, why don't you dance to the song?
- You should give that a try. - Right. Give it a go.
- This is nice. - I didn't mean to.
(This is So Min's cover dance as Daniel demonstrates for her.)
(What a surprise! She can pull off a decent body wave.)
Come on!
- Give us a break! - So Min.
Hey, you didn't have to go that far!
- She always causes trouble. - So Min.
- So Min. - I...
- I'll keep her with me. - Yes, please.
- Jae Seok. Kwang Soo is ready too. - Really? That's awesome.
- Kwang Soo, you should try. - Kwang Soo.
Since you're wearing the jacket, you can pull it off.
- He'd look cool with the dance. - Try it.
Kwang Soo has the longest thighs than anyone here.
- I'll take this seriously then. - Kwang Soo, go all out for it.
- When will you ride the spaceship? - The spaceship?
He looks like the skinny version of Don Spike.
He truly does.
With the sunglasses, he does look like Don Spike.
- His thighs are not muscular. - It will take long as they're long.
Here it comes.
(Kwang Soo begins dancing.)
Kwang Daniel!
(Yeon Soo, you're watching, right?)
That's disgusting.
- I told you they were long. - They are long.
His legs are so long.
(A bad output of long legs)
(Open it)
Jae Seok, what are you doing?
(Hwang Jung Min of "The Wailing" drives evil spirits of his dance.)
(This is the purgatory of dance.)
I can't stand this.
Goodness, that's it.
I'm so honored.
(Their initiations are over. Which guest will take over the gangs?)
- There are three gangs right now. - Okay.
We will start Fight to Become the Boss, My Boss is in First Place now.
(Fight to Become the Boss, My Boss is in First Place)
You will hear the keywords of the boss candidates' best weapon.
If you think you can beat the candidates, you can challenge them.
Through the matches, whoever wins the last match will become the boss.
(Whoever wins the match will become the boss.)
Sae Ho will reveal his best weapon.
- What is yours? - He's good at many things.
Will he be dancing?
- Dance? - It's dancing.
He's so shameless.
He's the best dancer when Daniel is here?
- He can't win with dancing. - There's a hole.
Even the tags are problematic like the owner.
- Why is that? - He's taking up too much time.
- Sae Ho, just forget it. - Hold this.
- "The Best Dancer". - "The Best Dancer".
- Will you be okay with this? - This is a stupid move.
You can't follow through.
Daniel joined her today.
- No, Sae Ho isn't a good dancer. - I...
I don't know which song they will play for me.
He's 1 of the 5 best dancers among comedians.
- That's true. He's a good dancer. - I didn't expect that.
- I'm 1 of the 5 best dancers? - Yes.
- He didn't know. - Shall I start now?
- He's 1 of the 5 dancers. - He didn't know.
Since he said we could play any song,
- we prepared random songs. - Sure.
All right. Let's watch his dance.
Sae Ho, you can do it.
I wonder what kind of music they will play.
Goodness.
(Oh, gosh. What is this?)
- See? He can dance to every song. - He wasn't flustered.
He can practically dance to every song.
That was a nice turn.
- Goodness. - That was great.
- That suits him. - He's adorable!
- The dance suits him. - He's so cute.
(Unbelievable. He can actually pull this off.)
(He imitates a monkey.)
That's it. You must come back.
- There you go. - What is that elephant move?
(Dancing like an elephant)
(Tooting)
You all saw that, right?
- You saw what he did, didn't you? - He really is a good dancer.
- That was so cool. - Goodness.
- The song surprised me. - That was groovy.
- Who's next? Yeon Soo? - Yeon Soo should go next.
- Yeon Soo. - I can't.
- Yeon Soo might be an underdog. - That's right.
- I'm so curious. - That suits you well.
- You can win with your cuteness. - Yes, I'm a bit hot.
- Play the song. - What should I do?
- Here it is! - Let's go!
(Her eyes undergo a sudden change.)
(A monkey climbs up the tree)
- That's great. - Great.
(Tossing her hair)
(She's engrossed in dancing.)
Nice!
(Yes! This is my chance.)
(A giant octopus appeals his charms to her.)
(Doing her best)
Monkey, monkey magic, monkey magic
(She doesn't lose focus despite the distraction.)
All right. Both of you...
- You were so good. - That was excellent.
She lost herself in her dance.
- That was great. - I liked that.
- Really? You did? - Yes, I did like it.
- You did well. - All right.
The rest of you will decide who the winner is.
- Next up is... - Yes, go, Ma Jong Kook!
It's not that...
- Jong Kook. - Goodness.
He's warming up.
(Feeling shy)
It's the shark song.
(His muscles do the wave.)
(Feeling narcissistic)
Please switch the song.
- My kid loves this song. - Let's change the song.
(The theme song of "National Singing Contest")
- What is this? - It's "National Singing Contest".
Hey, this is...
(He wriggles his body again.)
Do a cute dance move.
(Officer, you can't do that here.)
- But... - Why am I feeling hot?
don't you think he has guns all over his body?
I have a gun here.
- He does. - He has guns in his biceps.
I'm going to take out my guns.
All right, everyone.
- Let's see Daniel's moves. - Let's go, Daniel.
He's one of the strongest boss candidates.
(Daniel enters the stage.)
Here we go.
(Oh, my.)
(Are you watching?)
He's so well prepared.
Amazing.
(His sense of rhythm is incredible.)
Please change the music.
(He finishes off relaxedly.)
(Second song)
You can do this.
(He's getting into the rhythm.)
(This is not good.)
- He is really good. - He's so cute.
How can you do this?
(I'm the king of dance.)
He's amazing.
Oh, my.
- This is embarrassing. - You did an amazing job.
Even his freestyle dance is amazing.
This is embarrassing.
- His freestyle dance is so nice. - I'm so embarrassed.
- It was fantastic. - You're cruel.
- No. - Amazing job.
Daniel wins.
Thank you.
I accept the result.
- I respect the result. - Then...
Daniel can choose which team he wants to join.
We're...
- Are you here alone? - Okay.
You'll have to dress similarly to the other team members.
- Really? - You have to.
Okay.
Daniel can have my hairstyle.
- My wig... - Daniel can wear my wig.
- This jacket is too warm. - It's so hot.
(I'll donate my jacket.)
This is much better.
I didn't know what the weather would be like in Korea.
(Nose Tae thought it'd be hot in Korea.)
He's good.
(What is he doing?)
It's not hot in Yanbian.
- That's a Gangwon dialect. - That's a Gyeongsang dialect.
Where are you from?
Due to global warming...
Global warming is getting serious.
- Daniel. - Yes.
- Please choose a team. - You can dress like a detective.
- It'll look cool. - We're Mungdol Gang.
Mungdol Gang.
- Mungdol Gang. - You're?
Team Police.
(A real man should join Team Police.)
- Which team do you choose? - Well...
(All teams want Daniel. Where will he go?)
Mungdol Gang.
Really?
(Daniel chooses Mungdol Gang.)
- That's clever. - All right.
Whose turn is it now?
- It's Yeon Soo's turn. - Yeon Soo.
(It's Yeon Soo's turn.)
- Let's take a look. - What is she good at?
Being cute?
- Smile? - Smile?
I have a nice smile.
(Best Smiler)
Among us,
the only ones who have a chance are...
So Min and Ji Hyo.
- I have a nice smile too. - Show us.
(I have a nice smile.)
(His smile could...)
(literally kill a person.)
- You see... - Oh, I recognize that smile.
He does this all the time.
When did I do that?
- Like this. - I never do that.
You do this.
(He looks the same in every picture.)
I don't do that.
It doesn't look like that.
No, no.
It'd be hard to decide...
which smile looks the best.
How are you going to judge?
You'll be flicked in the forehead while smiling.
(They'll be flicked in the forehead.)
After the flick,
you have to keep a smile for five seconds.
We can't flick Yeon Soo in the forehead.
(They have to keep a smile for 5 seconds.)
- Kwang Soo doesn't care. - No.
- He's fair to everyone. - It's just a game.
Of course.
It's going to hurt.
Definitely.
- I'll start. - Keep a smile.
That's going to hurt.
You have to keep this smile.
- Yeon Soo. - I'm scared.
You're already frowning.
(You're already moving.)
His hand is so big. It's scary.
Then you'll fail.
- Yeon Soo. - Yes?
- Are you ready? - Can't I just give up?
(I suddenly want to give up.)
- You can't. - It was your idea.
Wait.
(He's having a hard time managing his anger.)
Why are you so angry?
- What are you doing? - Why are you angry?
Are you drunk?
What's with you?
It was your idea.
Please smile.
(Take a deep breath...)
(and smile.)
(She's so pretty.)
I'll start.
(Kwang Soo gets ready.)
(Flicking)
(I have to keep a smile.)
Isn't this just how she usually looks?
- This is just how her face looks. - She looks like this all the time.
(Poker face)
She's good.
- It hurts. - Does it hurt?
Yes.
(She kept a smile for 5 seconds.)
- So Min. - She'll pull it off.
(The first contestant is So Min.)
Seriously.
Put on a smile.
Show us.
Cameras, please...
Yeon Soo, can you come over here?
- Please smile. - Keep it for five seconds.
- Yeon Soo. - Please come here.
You're in the way.
I thought she was a viewer.
- Please stand here. - She wants to see.
Show us your smile.
- Like this? - Like this?
You look pretty.
That looks nice.
You're doing great.
With your hands covering your face.
(She decides on her smile.)
(Flicking)
(Her smile is gone.)
Wait.
Hold on.
That fast?
You fail.
- So Min failed. - I was smiling.
So Min failed.
- So Min. - You should try too.
- So Min failed. - You should try too.
You should try.
- You should. - Try, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo gives it a try.)
Please smile.
That looks good.
There you go.
That disgusting smile again.
(Prince of Asia's smile)
- Please face the camera. - It won't hurt.
(So Min will flick him in the forehead.)
It won't hurt.
(Punching)
(You come here.)
(An eye for an eye.)
- You're crazy. - So Min.
Kwang Soo failed.
He failed.
She punched me.
His forehead is red.
(He was punched.)
It's red.
(Kwang Soo fails.)
- No one has done this before. - Kwang Soo failed.
(He's no longer the Prince of Asia.)
Now...
(The next contestant is...)
(Is it me?)
It's not your turn yet. You don't have to get ready.
(It isn't?)
He wants a close-up shot.
It's not my turn yet?
He's been...
(He's been getting ready for a close-up shot.)
- Then... - Why doesn't Sae Ho try?
- I'm okay. - Give it a try.
Well...
Can't I choose not to?
Eun Kyung and your manager have agreed on this.
They have?
Se Chan will flick him in the forehead.
All right.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Please put on a smile.
- Like this? - Yes.
(Se Chan is the strongest one.)
Here we go.
(Flicking)
(He gets teary-eyed.)
(His eyes are crying.)
What is this?
He looks a bit different.
(Sae Ho fails.)
He failed.
Daniel should try.
- Okay. - Daniel should try.
Okay.
Se Chan should flick him.
- Se Chan is strong. - Will you be okay?
- I'll try. - Are you sure?
- Will I be okay? - I'll try.
- Will I be okay? - Don't worry. It's just a game.
- Are you sure? - Of course.
- Of course. - You're a professional.
- Sure. - Daniel,
please show us your smile.
- Show us a few. - Show us your favorite ones.
1, 2, 3.
(Cute)
- He's so cute. - He's so cute.
(Their hearts flutter.)
A bigger smile, please.
(Winking)
That looks great. Please keep that one.
Wink. I love that.
(Everyone is in love.)
Here we go.
Se Chan is strong.
(Flick)
Hey.
(Crying)
You're...
I'm sorry. It was just a game!
It was just a game!
It's just a game!
Attack him!
(Daniel fails.)
- You're the star of the night - No!
(He closed both eyes.)
(Are you okay?)
Yeon Soo kept a smile.
She's the boss.
(Yeon Soo becomes a boss.)
Please choose a team.
(She has to choose a team.)
Are you here alone?
(She has to dress like the other team members.)
Will I have to dress like that?
- Yes. - It's embarrassing at first,
but you get used to it. It's quite comfortable.
I saw the other wig back there. It's a Chinese queue.
- No. - What?
It isn't.
- It isn't. - What are you talking about?
You wear it the other way around.
It's a Chinese queue.
Are you choosing us?
- Are you? - Yes!
(Yeon Soo chooses Team Police.)
- Is it Sa Yeon's turn now? - Yes.
Sa Yeon's specialty is...
- Strength? - Her specialty is strength.
She's really strong.
She's incredible.
She suppressed Seok Jin with force earlier today.
I touched her arms,
and they were hard like Jong Kook's.
(Her arms were hard like Jong Kook's.)
- She's really strong. - She is.
(Sa Yeon has extraordinary arm strength.)
(No one can beat her in Wrist Wrestling.)
We'll play Wrist Wrestling.
(Wrist Wrestling is her specialty.)
Wrist Wrestling.
(Bring it on.)
If your feet get off the ground,
you'll lose.
If Sa Yeon defeats all female members, she remains first place.
(She remains 1st place if she defeats the females.)
(Round 1 is Sa Yeon versus So Min.)
- Push her to the side. - To the side.
Do I push her to the side?
You can't throw her around back and forth.
(Be gentle with her.)
- I'll try to win. - Okay.
Get ready.
Start.
(Sa Yeon and So Min start.)
Sa Yeon doesn't budge at all.
(She attacks her with all her might.)
(She stands firmly.)
She's so strong.
Goodness.
(She easily pushes So Min off to the side.)
Hold on.
People don't usually fly off.
They don't usually fly off while playing Wrist Wrestling.
She seems like a 100-year-old zelkova tree.
(She's not human.)
How can you say that she's 100 years old?
She has strong roots.
Regular wrestling is better.
She's described as a 100-year-old zelkova tree.
She's deeply rooted.
Next up is Yeon Soo.
- You can do it. - Let's go.
(Round 2 is Sa Yeon versus Yeon Soo.)
Let's go.
What if I lose within one second?
You never know.
It's hard to tell.
All you need is technique.
- She's very determined. - Start.
(Sa Yeon and Yeon Soo start.)
That's good.
Start.
- How is she not budging? - She puts weight on one side.
That's right.
- She puts weight on one side. - Right.
She knows how to play it.
Yeon Soo knows how to play it.
(Does she know how to play it? I don't think so.)
Goodness.
(She falls flat on the floor.)
Yeon Soo.
Are your feet nailed to the ground?
(Could that be her secret?)
She doesn't move at all.
- I know. - You're invincible.
She doesn't budge.
She's like a 100-year-old zelkova tree.
(Her weight is impressive.)
Next is Ji Hyo.
Let's go, Ji Hyo.
- By the way... - It's hard to defeat Sa Yeon.
Ji Hyo is strong and tough.
Once, she grabbed my arm.
My knees went weak. I apologized to her.
Sa Yeon is able to play with her ring on.
(She even has her ring on.)
She has her ring on.
(It represents how confident she is.)
- You should take it off. - Most people...
take off their diamond rings before playing.
Sa Yeon is different.
It's rare to see diamonds on variety shows.
Get ready, set, go.
- Isn't Ji Hyo different? - Isn't she?
- Isn't it different this time? - What's going on?
(Once she defeats Ji Hyo, Sa Yeon will be in 1st place.)
(It won't be so easy, Sa Yeon.)
(As expected, Ji Hyo falls on the mat.)
I really respect you.
- Respect, respect. - Goodness.
She pushed everyone as far as 30cm.
(Seok Jin steps in.)
Seriously.
(Are you that strong, Sa Yeon?)
They fell over here.
(Nose Tae is curious about Sa Yeon's strength.)
- What's going on? - Come here.
Come here.
- Jong Kook, why don't you... - Yes?
- play against Seok Jin? - Come here.
(Come here, Seok Jin.)
- That won't work. - Come over here.
(He has no business with Jong Kook.)
Come on, Seok Jin.
You're already here, so let's play.
I can't play against him.
- All right. - Wait, come this way.
- Okay. - We should start here.
Seok Jin is serious.
(Why is he so serious?)
Start.
(Jong Kook and Nose Tae start.)
(As soon as they start, Seok Jin loses.)
You go.
- Kwang Soo, you're up next. - No.
Nose Tae, step out. Kwang Soo, it's your turn.
- Play. - Take revenge, Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is strong.
Start.
Pull him inward. Gosh.
Darn it.
(He falls as soon as they start.)
- He fell. Come out. - Bring it on.
Jae Seok.
(Please take revenge on him.)
- Are you alone? - Jae Seok.
- What's your name? - You're strong, aren't you?
Start.
(Jong Kook thrusts him.)
How did you fall that way?
(How did he end up on the opposite side?)
- Gosh. - How can you fall to that side?
- That was pathetic. - Jae Seok is embarrassed.
He practically flew off.
Jong Kook, this is impossible.
Okay.
- All right. - You lost already.
You lost already.
- That won't be aired. - You fell here.
- You lost already. - It won't be aired.
(We don't remove interesting bits.)
- Start with taking off the jacket. - Don't start again.
- I was... - Here I am.
(Shall we start again?)
- This is impossible. - Right.
- This is good. - Are you alone?
What's your name?
Gosh, you're strong.
(He will show the strength of his gang.)
- You're strong. - Be careful, Jae Seok.
He'll fall forward. See?
- Come here. - Didn't it happen before?
I'm sorry. I started too early.
(He goes back.)
Seriously.
(He pretends like nothing happened.)
Hey.
- "Are you alone?" - Are you alone?
- Yes. - What's your name?
Is he Doctor Strange?
Doctor Strange?
(Jae Seok keeps turning back the time for Wrist Wrestling.)
- Here. - It repeats infinitely.
- Stop it. - Wait.
If you don't stop, you will die, Jae Seok.
He reminds me of my great-aunt.
(He looks like his great-aunt from the back.)
He looks very similar to my great-aunt.
I feel so bad. Please stop, Jae Seok.
His great-aunt?
- Please stop, Jae Seok. - That was great.
(He fails to take revenge.)
It doesn't work.
(Sae Ho volunteers.)
Sae Ho.
Sae Ho is going next. Let me tell you beforehand.
He comes from a family of strong men.
(Everyone probably didn't know.)
What?
Sae Ho's family became rich because...
they won oxen from wrestling.
(His family won oxen.)
- Is that so? - They won oxen from wrestling.
He comes from a family of strong men.
- I see. - Yes.
- Yes. - My family?
- Yes. - Really?
- Listen, Sae Ho. - If you bring up oxen,
my father will get flustered.
(The topic of oxen makes his father flustered.)
My father was very flustered after watching Running Man.
He said, "Are we a family of strong men?"
- "What do you say to other people?" - Stop it.
- Go to the center. - He has a good sense of balance.
This game isn't about strength.
- It requires technique. - Right.
(He's determined to change the reputation of his family.)
Sae Ho will do well.
- Get ready, set, go. - Let's go.
(Will he defeat Jong Kook?)
(They're neck and neck.)
He's hanging on.
(Sae Ho holds out quite well.)
(I'll show you the strength of my family.)
(He falls.)
What's the point of having a strong family?
(He fails to prove the strength of his family.)
He's incredible.
Daniel, give it a try.
- Right, Daniel is strong. - He looks great.
- Daniel, try it. - It's an experience.
(He decides to try Wrist Wrestling.)
I can't do this to Daniel.
Jong Kook.
(You should be gentle with him.)
Start.
(He plays gentle.)
Goodness.
(He fails to control his strength.)
- Are you okay? - Try it again.
- Attack him. - Are you okay, Daniel?
I can't do it.
You should let him resist for five seconds.
That's interesting.
(I'm sorry. Please understand me.)
As a result, Sa Yeon is first place.
(She gets to choose her gang.)
- I'm sorry, but that's my jacket. - Is that so?
I need a jacket too.
I can't wear it. It's too hot.
It's incredibly thick.
(What kind of jacket is this?)
It keeps in a lot of heat.
(It must be very hot.)
There are buttons...
- in the front. - Be careful.
(Bosses and their teams)
Teams are determined now.
Daniel brought three types of weapons.
He has three?
The team to win...
the most weapons will receive 200 dollars.
- 200 dollars? - That's great.
Yes.
What did you bring, Daniel?
As a new member, I worked hard to prepare them.
- It's Sweet Words in a Dialect. - Sae Ho can play Spinning in Place.
- What's Four Leg Run? - This is difficult.
It's hard.
How do we play Sweet Words in a Dialect?
You say sweet words while speaking...
in a dialect.
- Women like them. - We must come up with words.
- Okay. - How about this?
Starting with Sae Ho, let's play 1 by 1.
- Okay. - Say them to Yeon Soo.
I'll say them to Yeon Soo.
Without any bias,
- speak whatever is on your mind. - Okay.
Start.
(A man in a leather jacket walks with a macho gait.)
(What sweet words will he say to Yeon Soo?)
(He fails already.)
You should walk slowly.
- Walk slowly. - The way you walked...
The way you walked...
I'm about to speak in Gyeongsang dialect.
However, when you walk...
- you should be gentler. - I'm from Gumi.
(He fails again.)
That's the wrong way to say it.
- That's not it. - Okay.
- Try it, Se Chan. To Yeon Soo. - To Yeon Soo?
- Can I do it with Yeon Soo? - Sure.
I'll play a sharp guy.
- I'll play a sharp guy. - All right.
(I'll steal Yeon Soo's heart.)
Hey.
(Hey)
(He starts off with "Hey.")
(Will it win Yeon Soo's heart?)
What a pretty face.
Hey.
(What a pretty face.)
What?
What's wrong?
I mean...
- What's wrong? - That doesn't work.
Why?
You failed.
It was rude of you.
Next up is...
I lived...
in Changwon for a while.
Haha.
- I'll say it to Ji Hyo. - Okay.
Will you be okay?
Yes.
Cue.
Ji Hyo.
Eat this.
I picked it up on the street.
(Eat this. I picked it up on the street.)
You can react, Ji Hyo.
- Is it for me? - Yes.
Eat it. I picked it up on the street.
(Have it. I picked it up on the street.)
You jerk, did you really pick it up?
(You jerk, did you really pick it up?)
(How did you know?)
- You picked the wrong one. - You picked the wrong one.
You picked the wrong one.
You really picked it up on the street?
- What did you throw at him? - What was it?
- What did you throw? - Did you see that?
I'm sorry.
He gave her something he really picked up on the street.
- Next up is Kwang Soo. - Yes.
- To whom? - Yeon Soo?
He should do it with So Min.
That sounds good.
It might be hard to escape her.
She won't let you go.
Kwang Soo, take off your jacket. Look cool.
- You look much better now. - Right?
He looks different.
Nice.
That shirt is so distracting.
You look great.
Let's do this. Cue.
(Striding)
(What will he say?)
You're cute.
(You're cute, So Min.)
What's with you?
You know, I'm...
You know?
Say something.
What are you doing?
Were we strangers?
(Puzzled)
(It's a line from the movie, "Nameless Gangster".)
(So Min even copied the gestures.)
"I went to the sauna with him."
You know?
Your... I mean...
Did I do something wrong?
I just said she was cute.
What's with her?
You did a great job.
Next up is Jong Kook.
- Okay. - To whom?
- Yeon Soo? - He's from Hapcheon.
He's good at speaking dialects.
Really?
Let's say we're watching TV at home.
You're a couple, and you're at home?
- Are you married? - Are you married?
- They're newly-weds. - They're married.
They almost kissed during that Yellow Radish Game.
Cue.
Watch anything you like.
Okay. What should we watch?
(What sweet words will Jong Kook say?)
I'll just watch you.
(Cheesy)
(Everyone is revolting.)
Jong Kook.
That was nice.
(So Min likes it.)
What?
What's wrong?
Jong Kook is disgusting.
- Gosh. - You're disgusting.
- You've changed a lot. - What?
Gosh, please stop.
That's enough.
Daniel, please show us.
- I have an idea. - You do?
- Improvise. - I'll do it with Sa Yeon.
(I'll do it with Sa Yeon.)
Daniel and I?
(Thrilled)
Okay.
Here we go.
- Ms. Noh. - Yes?
(Ms. Noh.)
(What will the variety show novice say?)
Can I call you Sa Yeon for today?
(Can I call you Sa Yeon?)
(Daniel's dialect makes their hearts skip a beat.)
- That's... - Good job.
Why are you guys so excited?
It's...
- my lucky day! - Sa Yeon.
Can I call you Mom from now on?
(Can I call you Mom?)
Why would you do that?
You already have a mom.
(Sa Yeon suddenly has another son.)
Mom.
Buy me some winter clothes.
How long do I have to wear this jacket?
I don't have a son like you.
(I don't have a son like you.)
- What dialect is that? - What dialect is that?
- What's that? - What's that?
(What dialect is that?)
What's that?
I loved what you said.
Daniel is...
Can't I give it a try?
- Yeon Soo. - I want to try role-play.
Sure.
- With Jong Kook. - With me?
(What's going on between these two?)
Today...
Look at Jong Kook's clothes.
- Look how he's dressed. - Goodness.
I've been watching.
Why do you two keep doing things together?
In reality, Kwang Soo is more interested in her.
You don't know what will happen once I take off this wig.
(You don't know what will happen.)
Please say, "Yeon Soo, I'll get going."
Yeon Soo, I'll get going.
(The second role-play starts.)
- Right now? - Yes.
Yeon Soo, I'll get going.
- Okay. Bye. - Bye.
Jong Kook!
(Jong Kook!)
(Yeon Soo runs to Jong Kook. What's going to happen?)
(Hugging)
What are they doing?
(She hugs him from the back.)
- What are you doing? - Yeon Soo is...
What are you doing?
Seriously, what is this?
I love this game.
This is great. She wins.
- I win. - She wins.
She wins.
- What are you talking about? - She wins.
Jong Kook.
(Let me try.)
- Let me try too. Jong Kook. - What are you doing?
- Jong Kook. - Stop it.
- Jong Kook. - What's with you?
(They look like they're having fun.)
- What's with you? - Go away!
Oh, my. Are you angry?
Mom, buy me jeans.
(He's here again.)
- Mom. - Buy me clothes.
Mom, I want matching clothes like yours.
Matching clothes.
He's a childish son.
(Every family has one.)
I want to take English classes.
Oh, my.
Seok Jin is very unhappy right now.
- Yeon Soo doesn't even look at him. - I mean...
- I can try with Seok Jin. - Sure.
(I can try with Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin is happy.
I guess she hates me.
(He thinks Yeon Soo hates him.)
Okay.
How many have you prepared?
Here we go.
(You don't know what will happen when I take off this wig.)
We're at an aquarium.
- We're looking at tropical fish. - Tropical fish?
There's an octopus.
(There's an octopus at the aquarium.)
Be quiet.
It's my turn soon. Be quiet.
It's a blowfish.
(You're an octopus.)
An octopus?
(He starts to swim around.)
What is this?
What did I do wrong?
Seok Jin, are you happy to be with me here?
(The role-play starts.)
Of course.
Give me a kiss.
(Give me a kiss.)
(A kiss?)
(This is too much.)
Those idiots are going overboard.
(The octopus passing by is at a loss for words.)
(The octopus said the correct answer.)
- Good job. - Did you hear me?
I was in the aquarium. How could you hear me?
(The octopus wrapped it up nicely.)
That was very nice. Kwang Soo.
So Min, do you want to try?
Which one?
- The kiss? - What?
I mean...
What kiss?
- I mean the role-play. - Role-play?
- No kissing? - No.
Sae Ho, do you want to try?
- Okay. - Okay.
Just improvise. You never know what So Min will say.
Why do you keep showing up?
- Sae Ho. - Get off of me.
What's with you?
- Stop it. - Sae Ho.
Why are you taking off my clothes?
Wait.
- What is going on? - Why are you taking off my clothes?
What is going on?
What is she doing?
What's happening?
What are you doing?
He came home.
- What's happening? - There's a scene...
like this in "The Outlaws", but can she do that?
There's a scene like this in "The Outlaws".
(It's not that scene.)
My husband came home.
- I'm your husband? - Yes.
You should have told me.
I thought you just randomly showed up.
What are you doing, So Min?
(I'll open the door first.)
It's over.
(The role-play is over.)
- It's over? - What were you doing?
I was opening the door.
- It's over. - Okay.
(I wanted to start over.)
This is awkward.
(After So Min took his jacket off, he feels awkward.)
She took off your clothes.
(The game ends in a tie.)
The next game is Spinning in Place.
- It's... - Sae Ho is good at it.
No one can beat him.
(Sae Ho is invincible when it comes to Spinning in Place.)
(During the Family Outing Special last July,)
(Sae Ho showed unrivaled talent during Spinning in Place.)
(He touched Jae Seok's nose after spinning 20 times in place.)
(He's the king of Spinning in Place.)
It makes you very dizzy.
- Right? - Yes.
- Have you spun 20 times? - Start.
(Spinning)
(He spins extremely fast.)
- 4, 5. - He wins if he does it.
(He's much faster than Sae Ho.)
He's the winner if he wins this game.
- He's faster than Sae Ho. - 6, 7, 8.
- Can he do it? - He spins well.
- He's so fast. - He's young after all.
He deserves an applause after spinning.
It's enough to make you dizzy.
18, 19, 20.
Here he goes.
(He spins 20 times very quickly.)
(He succeeds if he walks straight to Kwang Soo's nose.)
(He stumbles.)
(This is the wrong direction.)
He's flustered.
What's wrong?
I'm over here.
- Why did you grab me? - I'm here.
- Daniel is just like us. - I was surprised.
(Why is this his strongest weapon?)
- He's human. - Are you okay?
- Are you okay? - I wanted to show you something.
It's good to see him work hard.
(It's okay even if he's clumsy.)
The last one is Four Leg Run.
Three members will volunteer and play.
One from each team should volunteer.
(Including Daniel, one member from each team plays.)
- Let's go, Daniel. - Let's go.
Let's go, Se Chan.
(Daniel, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan play.)
All right.
(Kang Daniel, Lee Kwang Soo, Yang Se Chan)
Now...
- Look at Kwang Soo. - Do you know the type?
Gosh, look at him.
He looks scary.
Daniel, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan will play.
I'm nervous after...
watching Daniel play Spinning in Place.
He isn't good at it.
- He doesn't seem good. - I know.
He seems athletic though.
He's ambitious.
Be careful, Daniel.
If you're hurt, I'm hurt too.
(I'll do better this time.)
Get ready.
(Will ambitious Daniel win this time?)
Set.
(Four Leg Run starts.)
Here they come.
Why is there a ribbon?
(Kwang Soo charges forward.)
(He trips.)
What's this?
(While Kwang Soo falls,)
(Se Chan moves forward.)
(Much faster than Se Chan, Daniel takes the lead.)
Daniel is good.
(Where is he headed?)
Daniel isn't doing well. What is he doing?
(He moves forward without looking.)
What is he doing?
Daniel, watch out.
- I'm sorry. - What's wrong with him?
(He crashes with the cameras.)
I couldn't see the front.
(He's flustered.)
- You came in first. - I'm sorry.
Where did you go?
I couldn't see ahead.
(Daniel's clumsiness is confirmed.)
- I'm sorry. - Gosh, Daniel.
(He had to stop due to a crash.)
(Daniel is accepted as the winner as he arrived first.)
I think Daniel determined...
his personality on variety shows.
- I didn't expect it. - This is great.
I thought he was a rhinoceros.
(Daniel kept moving forward.)
- That's not it. - Why did you drag it?
I tripped.
I pulled up my pants to run faster.
Running Man took away all the hair on my body.
(He realizes the truth.)
(He recalls being waxed.)
I didn't realize it for two days.
(It was a painful experience.)
I'd forgotten about it.
(Thanks to Running Man, he's smooth all over.)
We aren't quite sure,
but Daniel places first anyway.
Thank you.
(Daniel wins Four Leg Run.)
Mungdol Gang, the winner of Four Leg Run,
will receive 200 dollars.
(Mungdol Gang wins 200 dollars.)
After you change into the outfits that your bosses have chosen,
we'll start the race.
(After they get changed, the race officially starts.)
As you might be hungry, we'll go to a restaurant.
- That's great. - We're going to eat.
The bosses will receive...
1,000 dollars.
I see.
(1,000 dollars is given to the boss of each gang.)
Aren't you our boss?
- Boss. - 1,000 dollars?
As I told you before,
1,000 dollars will be given as a prize.
It will be given to one member in reality.
- In reality? - Yes.
Really?
Mungdol Gang has earned 200 dollars as of now.
- It's a total of 1,200 dollars. - That's a lot.
- Sae Ho. - Awesome.
Are you the chauffeur...
for the man and the two ladies?
I haven't determined my character yet.
Is that so?
Are you Piggy Mom?
I can play any type of character.
(Look for Piggy Mom at the entrance.)
Each gang has a boss.
The boss has the authority...
to distribute the capital to the gang members.
That's awesome.
Does the boss distribute it however he wants?
Let me tell you about...
Boss' Unfair Deal.
The boss may equally distribute...
the capital of 1,000 dollars to the gang members.
He may distribute 250 dollars each.
- Or? - Or...
he may distribute it unfairly...
however he likes.
Gang members can't find out how much capital is distributed.
- However, the gang members... - We can't find out.
get one chance to revolt and find out...
how much capital they're given before the final race.
Revolt?
If you suspect the boss to be unfair,
you may use the Revolution Card.
You may find out how much you received.
It's better to distribute fairly.
If you find out that the boss distributed fairly,
then it was wrong to revolt.
I see.
All distributed capital will return to the boss.
(All distributed capital returns to the boss.)
That's great.
If the boss distributed unfairly, the revolt is successful.
The boss' capital is divided equally to the members.
After a while...
- The boss can act suspiciously. - Right.
There are many who love to revolt.
I'll use it now.
Can we use it now?
You have to do it in secret.
(He revolts instinctively.)
(How will the bosses distribute?)
In your standing order,
Yeon Soo will decide first.
(Yeon Soo starts to distribute.)
(The boss gets everything if someone revolts when distributed fairly.)
Let's see.
(Members get the capital when distributed unfairly.)
To Kwang Soo...
To Seok Jin...
(How did the bosses distribute the capital?)
- Let's go. - Here we go.
Let's go.
(They head to the restaurant.)
- Our boss is competitive, right? - Yes, she's strong.
She's also ambitious.
She's not the type to do something ordinary.
- That's right. - Never.
I bet she didn't give herself 250 dollars.
That's possible.
It doesn't matter.
You can be suspicious and use the Revolution Card.
(If you're confident...)
- Do you want all the money? - I'm okay.
Yes, I'll take all.
- Please use the card. - We won't suspect you.
Let's be friends.
We're so great.
- We trust Yeon Soo. - Seriously.
We trust you completely.
We turn right.
(On the other hand...)
That's good.
We're turning right.
(Piggy Mom is driving.)
It may be too early to bring it up,
but did you distribute the capital evenly?
- 300 dollars each. - Right?
- Can we trust you? - Yes.
I distributed 300 dollars each.
Did you give 250 dollars each?
- For gangs, - That's right.
loyalty and trust are important.
Of course.
(Are they telling the truth?)
There's a lake.
It's bulgogi.
(They arrive at the restaurant.)
There's seasoned raw beef and pajeon.
Please sit with your team.
(Yuchen Gang sit down quickly.)
He's the manager of the restaurant.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Welcome. It's nice to meet you.
- Hello. - Over here.
Bring some more meat.
- Please sit down. - Thank you.
He fits perfectly.
(He works hard to keep the customers satisfied.)
(It's time to enjoy the food.)
We should eat well.
- Give me your plate, Seok Jin. - Okay.
(Sa Yeon takes care of the younger members.)
Thank you. That's a lot of meat.
If you only look at these four,
Sa Yeon seems like a charity worker.
She's someone who helps...
the poor.
She's full of love.
She washes and feeds them.
(She shares food with love and kindness.)
I agree.
- She serves us too. - I can't help but agree.
I agree as well.
(She raised them with love.)
Did you enjoy the meal?
- Yes. - Yes.
Before we move on to the next round,
does anyone want to use the Revolution Card?
(Does anyone want to use the Revolution Card?)
We trust each other, right?
Our boss tells us we should never do that.
Why would you revolt?
We have no reason to.
- So... - Trust us.
we will...
(Sa Yeon is a kind boss.)
(Considering her character...)
We will use the Revolution Card.
- You are unbelievable. - We will use the Revolution Card.
- Why would you use it? - I have my reasons.
- Who wants to use it? - Listen.
- I have my reasons. - You are unbelievable.
Already?
She fed you, tucked you in, and bathed you. Have you no shame?
(It's fun to witness betrayal.)
Do you want to check how much I gave you?
Then you have to pay me back.
(Then you have to pay me back.)
Really?
- Then you won't have any money. - That's right.
Are you really going to use it, Kwang Soo?
- Do you want to check? - Let's discuss once more.
In 1, 2, 3.
- We will use it. - We will use it.
(They are ungrateful.)
I will announce how the capital of Yuchen Gang was distributed.
Out of 1,000 dollars, Sa Yeon has...
(How much money does she have out of 1,000 dollars?)
- 940 dollars. - Okay!
(Sa Yeon took 940 dollars.)
(She gets caught on her unfair distribution.)
- I knew it. - Did we receive 20 dollars each?
(Distributing capital before leaving for the restaurant)
(30 dollars for Kwang Soo)
(20 dollars for Seok Jin)
(10 dollars for Jae Seok)
- Did you give us 20 dollars each? - 20 dollars?
(She gave herself 940 dollars.)
(I am the best at spotting betrayal.)
- Did you give us 20 dollars each? - 20 dollars?
- 20 dollars. - 20 out of 1,000 dollars?
Rich people are worse.
I didn't know you would be like this.
Don't say that. I didn't know you would be like this.
- Why do you say that? - Why is she upset at us?
- I knew it. - She acted all nice before.
- My goodness. - Now, I will have...
- 920 dollars. - I will have 920 dollars.
320 dollars.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin wins.)
- I won. - Step back.
I will have 910 dollars.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Kwang Soo wins this time.)
Then I get the money, right?
Is that how it works?
(Doesn't the winner get the money?)
Didn't I win?
He won.
Seok Jin got eliminated because he won.
- Between you and me, who won? - I did.
Then you are eliminated.
- I won. - Why was I eliminated?
- Wait a minute. - I won, didn't I?
You are so stupid, Kwang Soo.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
- I won. - Okay.
I won.
(Yu Chen is the winner.)
I can't believe they agreed to play another round.
How could they accept that?
How were they persuaded?
What is wrong with them? Is it the effect of makeup?
Did the makeup make them that way?
Let's move on to the next game.
All right.
With this mission, you can win the prize money of 400 dollars.
(You can win the prize money of 400 dollars.)
- Okay! - Let's do this.
We need to get the prize money.
This is the psychological quiz, I Heard It Through the Grapevine.
(I Heard It Through the Grapevine)
- I Heard It Through the Grapevine. - I Heard It Through the Grapevine.
How does it work?
The two people in the front row will participate from each team.
One team will be the offensive team and present a problem.
The other two teams will solve it as the defensive teams.
The offensive team will pick someone who is likely to answer incorrectly.
If that person answers incorrectly, he or she will be eliminated...
and replaced with another member of the team.
If both members are likely to answer correctly,
shout out, "You all know, right?"
(Shout out, "You all know, right?")
It involves guessing.
We need to guess whether the others answered correctly or not.
You can either write down the correct answer...
or write down the incorrect answer on purpose.
When the two members are eliminated,
- that team is out. - Okay.
(When the 2 members are eliminated, that team is out.)
(Team Police carefully chooses 1 out of 8 problems.)
Okay.
I didn't like the other one. Let's take a look.
This is a long problem. It's a long one.
- It's really difficult. - Okay!
You chose well.
Good job.
No one will know the answer.
- Shall I read it out loud? - Yes.
- It's very difficult. - I will read the problem out loud.
"During the Joseon Dynasty, men gave women..."
"a part of his body as a symbol of love."
They gave something?
(What could it be?)
"In a satirical novel, 'Baebijang-Jeon',"
"Jeong Bi Jang gives this to a kisaeng named A Rang."
- "What is this?" - They gave something?
(Do they know the answer?)
(Do they plan to write down the incorrect answer?)
(Thinking)
- Ji Hyo, you don't know, right? - Ji Hyo, you don't know, right?
(Ji Hyo, you don't know, right?)
(Surprised)
She was thinking so hard.
I am 100-percent sure.
- I know the answer. - Okay.
Ji Hyo is acting. My goodness.
I am serious.
- Okay. - I am serious.
We can pick Ji Hyo.
Look at Kwang Soo.
Could you read the question again?
Daniel doesn't know the answer.
He keeps looking around.
Did you write down the answer?
- It has to be right. - Did you write down the answer?
Kwang Soo, my goodness.
(Does Kwang Soo have the correct answer?)
You are impressive.
- You don't disappoint. - There weren't a lot of options.
- You don't disappoint. - Seok Jin.
- Did you finish? - Yes.
You can't change the answer now.
Let's see the answer.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Tooth)
- My goodness. - Tooth?
Why?
Jae Seok.
Did men give women their teeth?
- Didn't Ji Hyo write for a while? - Yes, she did.
(They remember that she wrote for a while.)
- Neither one of them knew. - They didn't know the answer.
(It seems like neither one of them knew.)
- I saw how Daniel acted. - I...
(He is similar to Ji Hyo.)
I read the book.
- I read the book. - What's the title of the book?
A satirical novel, "Jaebijang-Jeon".
- You didn't know the answer, right? - Of course, I did.
Let's ask Seok Jin.
I came to know about it thanks to my wife.
What about your wife?
- She told me... - He came up with a story.
I am telling you the truth.
When my child lost a tooth,
- she told me to give it to her. - Really?
Then she told me about a custom... Why are you laughing?
(They can't help but burst out laughing.)
My stomach hurts from laughing. Did she want to keep the tooth?
- I mean... - How childish!
- You are too much. - How childish!
Let's go. Let's pick one of them.
- Okay. - Pick between these two.
Why don't you shoot us?
I am serious. Go to them.
Whom shall we pick? Ji Hyo or Daniel?
(They need to decide on the target.)
Spare Daniel.
(Daniel, you don't know, right?)
Daniel, you don't know, right?
Should I show my answer?
Maybe he got it right.
(If his answer is right, Team Police loses.)
- I would be amazed if he did. - Maybe he got it right.
I'd be amazed.
(What is Daniel's answer?)
(Hair)
(Incorrect)
Hair.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Hair. - It hurts.
Why did you hit me?
So Min, why did you hit Sae Ho?
I was in pain.
You should have endured it. Why did you take it out on me?
I am sorry.
Kwang Soo wrote down something different.
- I thought... - Toenail.
I thought hair was too obvious.
Tyrannosaurus' claw.
Read the question.
This is easy.
"Complete the titles of the three SBS dramas in order."
"Secret Blank, Wife's Blank, and My Girlfriend Is Blank."
- My goodness, this is hard. - Oh, my.
Everyone knows the answer,
but some of them will answer incorrectly on purpose.
It's a psychological warfare.
(Most of them know the answer.)
(Shall I get it right or wrong?)
What is it?
- Do you think it's hard? - So Min says it is.
I bet everyone knows the answer.
This is what Sa Yeon said to me.
"Is it 'My Girlfriend Is Sam Soon'?"
(Is it "My Girlfriend Is Sam Soon"?)
(You are confusing it with "My Lovely Sam Soon".)
That's "My Lovely Sam Soon".
Respect, respect.
Sa Yeon, what do you think the titles are?
"Secret Garden", "Wife's Outing",
"My Girlfriend Is Sam Soon".
(Please love SBS dramas.)
- Respect, respect. - Big respect, big respect.
- Superman! - You are the hero of variety shows.
Superman, Superman!
You finished writing down the answer, right?
Show us the answer.
- "Secret Garden". - It is a nine-tailed fox.
That's the hard one.
I bet people wrote down the wrong answer on purpose.
They are like that.
- Yeon Soo would know. - Yes.
She is in dramas.
She would be interested in dramas.
There is the possibility of her answering incorrectly on purpose.
- On purpose? - Yes.
Since she hadn't been on the show for a while,
she would have shown off her knowledge to look cool.
She would have shown off her knowledge to look cool.
(Laughing)
- Don't you agree? - My goodness.
- I bet she didn't know the answer. - I swear she wrote,
"My Girlfriend Is a Girl from Gumi".
"A Girl from Gumi".
(A slight change makes the title funny.)
She wrote, "My Girlfriend Is a Girl from Gumi".
I am sure of it. That's why I strongly recommend...
- that you choose Yeon Soo. - That's right.
I don't think she wrote down the answer.
Yeon Soo.
Pick Yeon Soo.
No, no.
Yeon Soo, when I say the first part, say the second part.
- "Temptation..." - "Of Wife".
- "Secret..." - "Garden".
- "My Girlfriend is..." - "A Gumiho".
- "Temptation..." - "Of Wife".
What are you doing?
(She already knows the answers.)
He just wanted to talk to her.
- You're good. - He wanted to make eye contact.
He wanted to talk to her.
Team Yeon Soo. We have to hit them.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Yeon Soo doesn't know? - Okay.
(Did Yeon Soo write down the wrong answer?)
She might have gotten it wrong on purpose.
She has to know.
In 1, 2, 3.
Oh Yeon Soo.
It's Ha Yeon Soo.
(Oh Yeon Soo)
What is wrong with you?
Oh Yeon Soo?
What's wrong with you?
Can somebody take his wig off?
Hold on.
Is he trying to get more camera time?
I'd be so disappointed.
I'm sorry.
My bad.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Yeon Soo, you don't know, right? - Yeon Soo, you don't know, right?
(Did Yeon Soo write down the wrong answer on purpose?)
(Cheering)
(Haha and Se Chan cheered. Did she write down the correct answer?)
I'm suspicious.
What is it?
(Garden, Temptation, Gumihong)
(She wrote "Gumihong" to get it wrong.)
- "Gumihong"? - "Garden", "Temptation"...
- "Gumihong". - "Gumihong".
That hurts so much.
(Their head hurts, and they lost their chance to win 400 dollars.)
That was too easy, so I got it wrong on purpose.
Seok Jin, that was good.
- You did well. - Sa Yeon guessed it for us.
- Good job. - An alien?
You did it on purpose, right?
- We knew. - I got it wrong on purpose.
"Gardan"?
"Secret Gardan", "My Wife is Studying Abroad",
"My Girlfriend is an Alien".
I like "My Wife is Studying Abroad".
(He wants his wife to go somewhere.)
I like it.
- I really like that team. - He's crazy.
"My Wife is Studying Abroad".
I like that too.
Please go to South America.
(Please stay until you get a doctoral degree.)
This is too easy.
This is the same.
(Is this question really easy too?)
It must be easy.
"Yeon Soo's nickname is Squirtle. What kind of animal is it?"
What?
Really?
You even have a picture of it.
That was so kind of you.
Would we say that's an octopus?
- You underestimated us. - Is that what you wrote?
I'm just saying.
We know.
(Is Yuchen Gang going with Plan 1?)
(Okay, they're ready.)
Are you ready?
Do you really don't know?
(Come on, Sa Yeon.)
What do you mean?
You can't say it.
(He wrote down the wrong answer.)
- This is our strategy. - It is?
- What are you doing, Sa Yeon? - It's our strategy?
- We'll go again. - We're sorry.
We have an internal enemy. I don't know what to do.
She doesn't say it,
but if you write the wrong thing...
(She's not satisfied.)
Please look elsewhere. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Her face it like...
My gosh.
Ji Hyo, let me tell you this.
We wrote down the correct answer,
so please don't bother us.
I'm serious.
We wrote down the correct answer too.
We did.
There's no reason for us to get it wrong.
What did you write, Seok Jin?
Me?
I wrote "terrapin".
(What?)
Is that what you wrote?
That's what I wrote.
- You're not making sense. - Why not?
We said...
- we know the answer. - What are you going to do?
What's our plan? Share it with us.
What's our plan? Did we get it right or wrong?
(Either they didn't talk it out, or he thought it was a terrapin.)
Are we going to get it right or wrong?
- I... - What's our decision?
I actually don't remember what I wrote.
Kwang Soo, did you write the correct answer?
Did you write the wrong answer or the correct one?
You said you wrote the correct answer.
Choose one. You said you wrote the correct answer.
It's better to go back and forth.
Just do that.
- What did you write? - You can't ask now.
You can't ask now.
- He can, Sa Yeon. - He can?
(What's the whole point of this game then?)
- What did she say? - He can?
She's like,
"You can't ask now."
- This is the time to ask. - Is that it?
It is.
Let's get started. Let's go that way.
- Towards us? - Yes.
We'll do this. "You all know, right?"
(Yuchen Gang, You all know, right?)
"You all know, right?"
One...
(The answer is obviously "turtle". They can get it wrong on purpose.)
Two...
(They probably wrote the correct answer.)
Three.
Turtle?
(He wrote "frog".)
(Kwang Soo got it wrong, so they didn't know it.)
(Mungdol Gang is out since 2 people got eliminated.)
- What did you write? - That was so close.
It's between us now.
(It's Yuchen Gang versus Police Department.)
"When people draw, they use 4B pencils".
- "What does B stand for?" - Okay.
(Isn't this it?)
Don't look. They're looking.
So Min saw everything.
(She's flustered.)
They're out.
It doesn't matter?
Is this...
a dream?
(Thanks for making us laugh every round.)
I'll show you the answer.
(What does B stand for?)
(Black)
I got it right.
How did I get it right?
- He got it right. - He's amazing.
- He got it right. - How did I get this right?
(As soon as he heard the question...)
Is it black?
Hold on.
- He got it right. - He said it was black,
but Ji Hyo was like, "That doesn't make sense."
(It does make sense.)
I told him that. "Does that even make sense?"
Jae Seok, did you know the answer?
(Did Jae Seok know the answer?)
- Me? - Yes.
I did.
Did you used to draw?
I didn't but this is basic knowledge.
Is this basic knowledge?
Of course.
Does Ji Hyo have no basic knowledge?
No, to me I mean.
Kwang Soo, you didn't know, right?
I thought it was...
- What did you think it was? - You didn't know.
- You were writing down something. - You were very busy.
(You were scribbling something down.)
I wrote down "belly hair".
I'm being honest.
- That's what I wrote. - You did?
But I was going to go to an art school.
He was planning to go to an art school.
Did you really write "belly hair"?
- No, I knew. - He did write that though.
- I did really write it. - He was joking.
- After he saw it... - I knew it, but...
- Why are you getting scolded? - I mean...
He wrote the wrong answer.
This is a movie.
- This is a scene from a movie. - Right. Detective, sir.
- Hold on. - Hold on.
We're just trying to figure it out.
We're sorry. He thought he was a detective.
We're not filming "The Outlaws".
Boss,
let's do the Room of Truth.
(By that, do you mean...)
Shall we?
- Byung Sik. - Yes, sir.
Let's go to the Room of Truth.
(Once you're in it, you have to tell the truth.)
(This is it.)
- Should we? - Hey.
Let's go to the Room of Truth.
- Who? Me? - The Room of Truth.
Did you write down "belly hair" or not?
(He's speechless.)
- It fits you well. - Come on.
- Did you write it or not? - What?
Did you write down "black",
or did you not change it?
- I don't remember. - Okay.
(Tell us the truth.)
(I remember now.)
Do you remember?
- Wait. - What are you doing?
It split into half.
- What was that? - The Room of Truth.
What was that?
- How's this the Room of Truth? - Didn't you watch the movie?
The Room of Truth.
We'll announce it now.
- Let's go. - Go, Haha.
- Do we get hit? - Yes.
(They decide to attack Yuchen Gang.)
(He said this is basic knowledge.)
(If he wanted to go into arts, this is a piece of cake.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - I'm not scared.
- Kwang Soo, you don't know, right? - Kwang Soo, you don't know, right?
(If he wrote "black", Yuchen Gang wings.)
- Should I show it? - Yes.
(He was so confident. Did he write "black"?)
(He wrote "bright".)
"Bright"? What?
- Okay. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Police Department is tied with Yuchen Gang.)
That was so strong.
I wrote "bright" too.
- He told me to write his. - Yes, "bright".
He said it was the correct answer.
This is the last question.
This will be the last question.
These two teams are tied.
(It's the final round between these two teams.)
- Do we attack? - Yes.
- Please come forward. - Last one.
We picked a good question.
"In Estonia, when you raise cattle,"
"you must pay a certain tax".
"What is this?"
(Estonia? Cattle? Tax?)
(They look clueless. What could be the answer?)
Just say anything.
(We're done already.)
Foot smell tax?
Sae Ho said it was Lee Moon Sae.
- I'll always stay with - I know the answer.
Yuchen Gang
He's so funny.
I won't leave you
(They love this question.)
Good job.
(Daniel is cute.)
- It's so fun watching this. - Right?
(They're having a discussion.)
You need a lot of water to raise cattle.
They poop a lot,
- so it pollutes the environment. - Pollution tax.
Wait. Look. I think it's...
air pollution. Their gas...
- That's what I mean. - That's it. So...
(Tax on cattle's gas? What is the correct answer?)
Here's the answer.
It's hard.
(What is the tax on raising cattle?)
(Flatulence tax)
- I was right. - "Flatulence tax"?
What?
(It looks like they got it right.)
(They look suspicious.)
(There must be somebody who got it wrong.)
- Se Chan. - Yes.
Did you get it right?
Yes, I did.
- Did you write "flatulence tax"? - Yes.
Did you spell it correctly?
I'm bad in spelling, so I got it wrong.
- Oh, we can ask like this. - We can.
You didn't know how to spell it?
We've been doing this for 1.5 hours.
- We're done now. - We are?
- Yes. - This is the last question.
You should ask Jong Kook.
(She finally understands the rules and participates.)
Jong Kook, did you spell it right?
- I wrote something else. - See?
(I wrote something else.)
- He's so honest. - Jong Kook...
(What game are you playing, Sa Yeon?)
- He might be lying. - Right.
- Really? - He might be lying.
(Jong Kook looks truthful.)
He looks truthful.
- I'm sure about Se Chan. - He got it wrong?
I'm pretty certain about Se Chan.
He couldn't smile properly.
(What did Se Chan write?)
Se Chan. In 1, 2, 3.
- You don't know, right? - You don't know, right?
(What did Se Chan write?)
If we win, we get 400 dollars, right?
(This is the last round. Who will take 400 dollars?)
- Se Chan, you don't know, right? - You don't know, right?
(Pollution tax)
(He's wrong.)
(Police Department is out.)
Pollution tax?
- What did you write? - That was difficult.
- Pollution tax. - Pollution tax?
So the winning team is...
Sa Yeon's team.
(Yuchen Gang wins.)
- Our team is the best. - Good job.
Flatulence?
The winning team's boss is Sa Yeon,
so she'll take the money.
You can divide it up in any way you like.
You have already used the Revolution Card.
(That means...)
She can keep it all.
That's good. I'll keep it all.
You can.
(Yuchen Gang's day was filled with betrayals.)
This is your last chance to use the Revolution Card.
- What is Daniel's team going to do? - I got the answer.
How much time can you give us?
- I'll give you 10 seconds. - What?
- 10 seconds? - That's a lot of time.
Hasn't it passed already? Hold on. What do we do?
(They're confused. They only have one chance.)
This is too cruel.
- No. - Try it.
Use it, Sae Ho.
- Sae Ho. - Sae Ho, use it.
Just go for it.
- Please decide. - Sae Ho,
I can...
This is the last chance. I'm scared of this card. Take it.
You can...
either take it out or zip it up.
- It's up to me? - Yes.
I'll use it.
(It's up to me? I'll use it.)
(She uses the Revolution Card without hesitating.)
She doesn't hesitate like a tiger moth.
It's a revolt.
You used the Revolution Card.
I'll tell you the amount in Daniel's digital moneybox.
Out of 1,200 dollars...
(Everyone trusted Boss Kang.)
I don't think our boss will lie.
I trust Boss Kang.
I think he'll be clean and fair.
I'll be fair.
The amount Daniel has...
(Did Boss Kang...)
(divide 1,200 dollars...)
(equally amongst his team members?)
(Next week)
(There's no mercy.)
(The real war begins now.)
Are you by yourself?
- Hold on. - I think we are first place.
(What would be the result of this battle...)
(of becoming number 1?)
This is brutal.
(That was scary.)
(And)
(Fall reminds them of the old times.)
(So Min's diary)
(From Jeon So Min)
(This is my friend, Dan Bi.)
(Dan Bi...)
(is a hostage?)
(He got his memory stolen.)
(This is not your memory.)
(If you don't find the memory thief, somebody's memory is in danger.)
(The culprit is one of them.)
(They look for the despicable memory thief.)
(Mysterious Autumn Trip)