(Fall visits Running Man.)
(What is the race of the day that will unfold at a hanok cafe?)
- Hello. - Hello.
Due to the result of Half and Half Tour Race,
it was decided that Kwang Soo will go to the Cage of Death.
That's right.
(Kwang Soo, the expert of penalties...)
(gave a grand finale to the 3rd Global Project.)
(He will receive all 3 penalties of Global Project.)
(This time, he will swim with crocodiles in a cage.)
(Choose a member who will go with you.)
(Let's go with me, Kwang Soo.)
(Give me another week to decide.)
(Kwang Soo postponed choosing a member who will go with him.)
We prepared your last chance to avoid getting chosen,
Half and Half Tour Pass Race.
(It's to decide Kwang Soo's partner.)
(It's their last chance to avoid getting chosen.)
A member who acquires Half and Half Tour Pass...
will be exempted from Kwang Soo's choice.
- Really? - Okay.
The members who fail to acquire Half and Half Tour Pass...
will become the candidates Kwang Soo can choose from.
He could be a cool man and go by himself.
(There is no reason to do this.)
I will keep every word you say in mind.
I haven't made my choice yet.
Some people say that, but I disagree.
- I almost misunderstood. - That's right.
Please do me a favor.
(He makes a sudden request.)
Take me with you.
You should go with Jong Kook.
- Take the person who wants to go. - That's right.
If the glass breaks and the crocodiles attack,
I will protect you.
You are scarier than the crocodiles.
(Crocodiles, please stop Jong Kook.)
- Seriously. - You stress me out.
He can rip the jaw of a crocodile.
I can rip it. Give me a chance.
Here is a thing about the cowards.
A coward can only depend on another coward.
- Then the other one can sympathize. - A brave person won't help.
Of course.
I would rather go with my father than with Jong Kook.
(I would rather go with my father than with Jong Kook.)
- Is your father a coward? - My father and I will go...
- into the glass cage. - Is your father a coward?
It's rare for a son to reveal that his father is a coward.
- That's incredible. - He exposed his father.
That's how desperate I am.
- I want to go too, Kwang Soo. - Ji Hyo.
This gives me the creeps.
Why do you say that? I only said...
- I want to go. - This gives me the creeps.
You know it's terribly boring to team up with them.
- That's right. - They are good at everything.
Then I will sit inside the cage without anything to do.
"Look at those crocodiles!"
(It's Cage of Death even without the crocodiles.)
Since Kwang Soo is worried,
we've two guests who will help him with Half and Half Tour Pass Race.
- Half and Half Tour Pass Race. - Are there guests?
You should go with the guests.
(Who are the guests of the day?)
Bo Mi and Sung Rok.
- It's Bo Mi. - It's Bo Mi.
(They are a treat to her eyes.)
- My goodness. - It's Bo Mi.
- Hello, it has been a while. - Bo Mi.
She is like a family since she visits very often.
She is like a family.
Sung Rok and Bo Mi are here.
(They are here to aid Kwang Soo in choosing his partner.)
He's almost tall as you.
- Bo Mi. - Yes?
- Hello. - Have you been well?
Bo Mi, there used to be romance between us.
- That's right. - When was there such a thing?
(Do you remember the last time you were on Running Man?)
(In a bus number 362,)
(they had a match of holding hands.)
(Bo Mi, this is just a game.)
(Grinning)
(Like a rain shower in summer,)
(strange romance formed between Kwang Soo and Bo Mi.)
(It has been a while. How have you been?)
He told me that he will buy me a present from Japan.
(That's right.)
- Really? - Yes.
- Did he contact you afterwards? - He is shameless.
He video calls me when he is drunk.
(There is another thing.)
What?
What are you talking about? I didn't do that.
- Kwang Soo. - I didn't do that.
Don't speak nonsense. What are you talking about?
- Don't do that. - You really need to stop.
Did you try to flirt with her?
Bo Mi, it's a problem he has. Please understand.
He is ridiculous.
It wasn't like that. I think of her as a little sister.
Then why would you video call her?
I called with my own phone.
That's true. He's right about that.
- After the shoot last time... - Isn't it awkward to meet here?
I didn't know she would revisit so soon.
(He resents the production crew.)
- Hey. - I didn't know.
You shouldn't have video called her.
Bo Mi, you should let him know if you aren't interested.
- Make it clear. - I already made it clear.
(Bo Mi is firm.)
Really? What did you say to him?
- She already made it clear. - What did you say to him?
- Let me tell you honestly. - Okay.
I wasn't making a move on Bo Mi, but she suddenly rejected me.
I am serious. I am being honest.
- Did she suddenly reject you? - I thought she was a good friend.
I kept in touch with her since I thought of her as a friend.
- Okay. - Then texted me one night,
"You are making me uncomfortable."
I was so surprised.
- She was getting ahead of herself. - I was so surprised.
- It's not like that. - Did you get ahead of yourself?
I bet Kwang Soo thought, "I haven't even started yet."
I texted her, "Bo Mi, I wasn't making a move on you."
"I am glad." That's how the conversation ended.
Sung Rok, I am sorry that this is "Kwang Soo's Love Game".
I am sorry.
I shouldn't have come.
- Don't say that. - I am sorry.
- Your time will come. - I had to tell this story.
- Will it come? - He looks like a sad dog.
- Why would you say that? - One of the Kakao friends.
His facial expression is similar to that of a character.
Sung Rok, you are in a musical.
He is a musical actor.
I heard it's a musical that is based on "Sandglass".
- Yes. - He plays Choi Min Soo's role.
"I thought doing this would let me have you."
(Everyone remembers Choi Min Soo from "Sandglass".)
(Sung Rok has a role of Park Tae Soo in the newest production.)
He has a similar face.
- That's right. - He is very tall.
How tall are you?
I am 189cm tall.
Despite the similar height, he seems different from Kwang Soo.
- How tall are you? - The proportions matter.
- I hate it when tall people visit. - Kwang Soo has a long face.
- That's right. - Kwang Soo has a long face.
Sung Rok's shoulders are broad too.
- He has nice hips too. - He must work out.
We have two guests today.
Before we go over the rules,
we will show you a video we prepared.
(A video?)
Is there another video?
They prepared a lot of videos.
Is it a video on a hint?
(A few days ago in SBS, Mok-dong)
- What? - What's this?
Plus one to be penalized in Australia.
- Is that you again? - Again?
What's the big deal about taking one more person?
It's time...
to make a decision.
I don't know whom I'll take.
Didn't you want to go with Jae Seok?
Shouldn't you take Jong Kook?
Is that a writer?
Everyone is a strong candidate.
For example,
Ji Hyo hasn't been penalized yet.
I don't remember the last time that she was.
I don't think she was for seven years.
What about So Min?
The reason why I'm here is So Min.
If So Min didn't distract me that day,
there wouldn't have been a problem.
So Min was penalized not so long ago. What about Haha?
Haha and Se Chan will go to New Zealand.
It'd be perfect if they stop in Australia on the way back.
- I agree. - That's perfect.
That sounds good.
(Who keeps giving Kwang Soo advice?)
It's not easy to decide.
Today...
No matter what,
I'll follow what the assistants say.
(I'll follow what the assistants say.)
- Assistants? - Assistants?
They must be the assistants.
- Really? - No.
I don't think so.
Are they the assistants?
As you saw on the video,
there are assistants amongst you who will help Kwang Soo decide.
(There are assistants amongst the 10 members.)
As you saw on the video...
(Unidentified assistants who help Kwang Soo decide)
(While hiding their identity,)
(the assistants will help Kwang Soo decide.)
That's why So Min has been quiet.
(That's why So Min has been quiet.)
Stop it, Haha.
- Why is it always me? - She was with Kwang Soo.
- Right. - It's neither Bo Mi nor Sung Rok?
- I don't think so. - Listen.
You get a video clip hint when you clear a mission.
The member who arrests the assistants before the end...
of the race will be exempted from being penalized.
Is that so?
Are we exempted if we arrest the assistants?
If you arrest them, you win an exemption pass.
If all members fail to arrest the assistants,
Kwang Soo and the assistants win.
Kwang Soo may choose two members...
- to take to Australia. - Two members?
- Will 3 of us go? - 2 members?
- Why 2? - Will 3 members go?
(Kwang Soo and assistants versus the rest)
I feel much better.
Do the assistants know who they are?
Right.
All answers are in the video clips available if you clear the missions.
(Video clips contain hints.)
- They're in the video clips. - I'm not it.
Please get changed, and we'll start the race.
Let's go.
- Let's go. - We have no hints yet.
- I don't think it's Seok Jin. - It's not me.
He isn't ready to take such a big role.
(Who are Kwang Soo's assistants today?)
Here's the first mission for which you can win a hint.
It's called Bell Hide and Seek: Kwang Soo, Let's Play.
(Bell Hide and Seek: Kwang Soo, Let's Play)
Is it Bell Hide and Seek?
It's been a long time.
The time limit is five minutes. As the seeker, Kwang Soo may...
eliminate other members by touching them.
The time limit is five minutes.
As the seeker, Kwang Soo may eliminate...
other members by touching them.
Kwang Soo won't look for Bo Mi today.
(Kwang Soo won't look for Bo Mi today.)
Why not?
- Why? - He can call her on video.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean by video call?
- You can call her. - Wait.
You probably feel awkward, so I'll stand in between.
- What? - Stop it, Jae Seok.
- Don't you feel awkward? - What are you talking about?
- Are you okay? - I don't feel awkward.
- She said, "I don't feel awkward." - Is that so?
(Will their romance start again today?)
The other members will put on a bell and hide.
Stay hidden during the time limit...
or run away before being eliminated.
(If you touch the stuffed crocodile on the coffee table, you survive.)
If you touch the stuffed crocodile on the coffee table, you survive.
- Stuffed crocodile? - Crocodile?
If Kwang Soo sees someone...
and touches the crocodile after shouting the member's name,
then the member is eliminated.
- If he says the name? - I see.
Once he sees someone?
Do I have to touch it by hand?
May I kick it?
- Isn't that touching? - Yes.
May I defend myself by punching?
(May I defend myself by punching?)
You'd be eliminated by him.
His chin would touch your fist.
- By the way... - I don't care.
- He doesn't care. - I don't.
If I touch someone with a weapon, is that considered touching?
- No. - No?
(That's so funny.)
Since we haven't seen Bo Mi in a while,
let's see her kick.
Shall we?
(Let's see Bo Mi's kick.)
- Her kick? - That's so random.
I had forgotten about it, but I remembered her kick.
(8 years of training make her fierce.)
(According to Seok Jin and Jae Seok,)
(their bruise lasted for a week.)
I had forgotten about it, but I remembered her kick.
- Remember the kick? - All of a sudden?
- Come out, Kwang Soo. - It was sudden.
- Kwang Soo. - Me?
Kick Kwang Soo's leg.
- Come out, Kwang Soo. - That's right.
- Me? - Kick Kwang Soo's leg.
Me?
Let's see it.
You don't need to stretch, Bo Mi.
Why is it me?
Brace yourself. She's strong.
- You might get injured. - He's weak.
If Kwang Soo doesn't fall or make a sound...
once he gets kicked, we'll give you...
30 more seconds to seek.
- 30 seconds? - Really?
- This is worth it. - Okay.
(He'll be given 30 more seconds during Hide and Seek.)
(If he endures the pain,)
(he may stop others from getting the video clip hint.)
(She kicks him hard.)
(My goodness)
(He falls down.)
(Bo Mi's kick impresses everyone.)
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
I thought a giraffe fell down...
- in the savanna. - I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
(He looks like a falling giraffe in the savanna.)
- Seriously. - My goodness.
- Bo Mi. - I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Kwang Soo.
Will it be transferred on screen?
- I don't think so. - Seriously.
- Sung Rok... - He looked like...
- laughed at him. - a falling skyscraper.
- Really? - He laughed.
Did you?
He laughed at him.
I saw him.
Be honest.
Do you think that Kwang Soo exaggerated?
Tell us honestly.
- He's definitely an entertainer. - I know.
That's what I thought.
It's true that Kwang Soo...
- He exaggerated. - exaggerated.
If Sung Rok endures the pain, he may put on 1 bell instead of 2.
Okay.
It's beyond what you imagine.
(Bo Mi kicks hard.)
(However, Kwang Soo did exaggerate.)
(Sung Rok's pride is on the line.)
(Screaming)
(His reaction is dramatic.)
(He crawls.)
He looked like a paulownia tree...
My goodness.
He broke into two.
She kicks really hard.
Kwang Soo wasn't acting.
Seriously.
- I'm sorry. - How was it?
Sung Rok.
How hard was it?
- Wait. - He's stumbling. Are you okay?
Wait. My muscles are tense.
She kicked me before. The bruise lasted a week.
- Are you okay? - I'm so sorry.
Let's get started now.
By the way,
has she kicked Jong Kook before?
It's not fun for me.
My goodness.
What do you mean?
It's not fun when he doesn't want to do it.
It's fun when he wants to do it.
- It's not fun. - Hurry up.
Don't live that way.
Why wouldn't it be fun?
- Come on. - Try it.
- It may be funny. - Listen.
- It's not fun. - Let's do this.
- It won't hurt me. - Se Chan, Jong Kook...
and I.
- Include Haha. - Right.
- One of us gets kicked. - Okay.
- Don't exclude Seok Jin. - Jae Seok.
- Seok Jin... - Why would you include us?
She kicked me very hard last time.
We must be included to make Jong Kook participate.
(Make Jong Kook get picked.)
Stop that.
- What am I doing? - Stop it.
Is it five of us?
Let's draw straws to pick one person.
Here are five straws.
There's one dud.
This is what Sung Rok told me.
"It was real."
We don't act.
- You weren't acting. - You became pale.
- You're sweating too. - It's real.
It really hurts.
Don't look at the straws.
Don't look.
- The rest of you can see it. - One.
- It really hurts. - 1, 2, 3.
(Who will be the unlucky one?)
Let's see.
(Haha gets picked.)
- Now, - She shows no reaction.
fold the paper.
Decide if you'll exchange.
I will keep mine.
- Wait a minute. - I'll keep mine.
- Let's exchange. - I won't.
I won't change mine.
- Let's exchange. - No.
Come on.
- Let's exchange. - Okay.
(Haha exchanges his unlucky draw with Seok Jin.)
- Wait a minute. - Did they exchange?
- Why? - I don't know.
- I won't exchange. - Let's exchange.
Who wants to exchange?
For now...
(Singing)
My goodness.
(Will you exchange with mine?)
- What's going on? - It's not me.
This is what everyone does.
- Everyone does this. - It isn't me.
- When Seok Jin offers his straw... - Seok Jin.
(He freezes.)
Is it me?
(They couldn't hide their reaction.)
It's because...
Seriously?
- You're not going to switch, right? - No.
If it's me, I'm...
- 1, 2... - 1.
(Peeking)
Then...
(I see.)
1, 2...
It's just a simple kick. You'll get it...
- like Kwang Soo and Sung Rok. - Right.
- 1, 2, 3. - Wait. We'll switch.
- What? - We'll switch.
What? What is it?
- Let's switch. - Did you see letters?
No, no. I didn't read it yet.
- Should I switch mine with his? - You should give that a try.
I swear. I saw Seok Jin taking a peek.
I did too!
I can bet my entire savings.
(Common action taken by liars being caught in action)
No, I didn't see it!
- I saw him reading it. - It's not me.
- I'll bet my entire savings. - Wait.
- No. - I saw him.
- Why me? She kicked me last time. - Go. I didn't get it, did I?
- Why did I switch mine with you? - It was you, Haha.
- It was supposed to be me. - Let's not do this.
Let's hurry. Let's get it over with and move on. We don't have time.
- You should get the kick too! - Get the kick, and move on.
Get the kick, and put it behind us.
- He wants to get rid of Seok Jin. - Get the kick, and move on.
- Hurry. - As we talked about before,
- he'll get it, and be gone. - We already wasted too much time.
- I'm fine. I can endure the kick. - Watch your hands.
- Face forward. - My thighs can handle her kick.
Let's get rid of him. Let's put him away.
- Goodness. - Put him somewhere else.
(He got the kick and was removed.)
(Even before his pain goes away, he was dragged out.)
- I'm really sorry. - This will do it.
- Let's film. - That's good.
- Let's continue shooting. - Let's start.
- Seok Jin. - Let's film.
- Can we really leave him here? - That's fine, Bo Mi.
He's all right.
It hurts so much! It seriously hurts!
- We respect you. - Respect!
All right.
Only the members who survive in the game will be given the video.
If the tagger eliminates everyone,
- the video won't be given to you. - Really?
- Kwang Soo will enter the house. - Okay.
One of the members outside has to ring the bell.
(1 member must press the bell.)
The member must say, "Let's play, Kwang Soo", ring the bell and hide.
So you may choose the member among yourselves.
The one who will ring the bell is Seok Jin.
(The member is already predestined.)
- Seok Jin will press it. - You're trying to get me.
(He was kicked and dragged out.)
(He will run faster and differently from the others.)
All right. We'll tie the bells on you now.
Kwang Soo, please go inside the house.
(Members put on the bells, and Kwang Soo goes inside the house.)
(This is the stuffed crocodile members and Kwang Soo must touch.)
This is the stuffed crocodile.
Haha took a peek.
I should keep the assistants alive to avert any suspicion.
(I should keep the assistants alive to avert any suspicion.)
The rest of you may hide with your own cameras.
How far can I go?
But isn't this space too small?
(They must make good use of the cafe and the sculptures.)
(Ji Hyo will ring the bell.)
Gosh, I'm horrible at hiding.
Hey, Jae Seok, no. This is my spot.
- Jae Seok. - I was heading there.
This is my strategy.
(This is a popular place among cunning members.)
(It's the space behind the rock which is close to the house.)
Hey, you have to run away well too.
(Jong Kook enters the kitchen of the cafe.)
I can lie down. Is there a blanket or something?
(Behind the refrigerator seems nice, but I need more.)
(He's patient, and puts effort even into the game.)
(Hide well, Jong Kook. Otherwise, your muscles will be spotted.)
(Haha hides behind the house which is an innovative strategy.)
No one will find me here.
You should hide there and film me.
(This genius of hide and seek even commands the cameraman.)
(Jingling)
I guess someone's here.
Darn. You are here.
- Do you want to come? - Are you going to take that space?
- We can hear the sound from there. - We should get out then.
(Haha and Seok Jin hide behind the house together.)
(Where should I hide?)
Stay here. No, you should stay here.
Let me. Let me just stay here for a while.
(As a new, cunning member, she hides among the crew's equipment.)
(Go back to work, please.)
No, stay there. Please you can stay.
(This is perfect. I'm satisfied.)
It's perfect.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you. I love you, all.
(I'll be the audio equipment for 5 minutes.)
10 seconds before the race starts!
(The hint video is at stake on the 1st round of the game.)
(They must touch the crocodile first or not get caught for 5 minutes.)
(If he finds members and touches the crocodile, they're eliminated.)
2, 1.
Kwang Soo, let's play!
- 1, 2, 3, 4... - Kwang Soo, let's play!
(The tagger must count to 10 and start looking for them.)
9, 10.
(The 1st round of Kwang Soo, Let's Play starts.)
(Ji Hyo hides behind the rock swiftly.)
- Hey. - Hold on.
(As soon as she hides, Kwang Soo ventures out.)
(Where did you all hide?)
How can she hide so quickly?
(Bo Mi is hiding behind the stairs.)
The space is so small.
(You did a good job of hiding in this limited space.)
(Please don't come here.)
(He enters the cafe which radiates a suspicious vibe.)
(Sung Rok is hiding right in the center of the cafe.)
(If things go wrong, he might get caught.)
(Rattling)
(Oh, no!)
(I heard a sound from somewhere around here.)
(This is the place Seok Jin and Haha are hiding.)
(The tagger has gotten close. When he turns, they're caught.)
(Feeling nervous)
(Meanwhile, this guy was about to get caught by Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo is occupied searching the back.)
(This is my chance!)
(Sung Rok, let me go with you!)
(Bo Mi who was hiding behind the staircase is running.)
(And Ji Hyo and Se Chan who were behind the rock are running.)
Hurry up, and run.
(This is the chance to touch it without the tagger present.)
(No! My crocodile!)
(Four of them enter the house in order.)
Move aside.
(Sung Rok, Bo Mi, Se Chan, and Ji Hyo get to watch the hint video.)
Hey, you idiot.
Four of them touched it?
- Goodness. - I...
- I mean, Kwang Soo... - Four of them got it?
Bo Mi, you are so fast.
Darn. I'm so bad at this.
I am bad at this.
(Members who are still hiding)
Where did they hide? They can't possibly hide here.
I can hear the bells. The bells.
(Seok Jin observed how the four members succeeded.)
(Kwang Soo is far from the house, and this is my chance!)
(Seok Jin, the oldie, makes a run for it.)
(In an instant...)
(What just happened?)
(Why is he running so fiercely?)
(Laughing)
(Skipping)
Seok Jin is eliminated!
(Seok Jin gets eliminated easily.)
I saw that coming, Seok Jin.
He was walking, not running.
I felt so bad when I touched the crocodile.
(His slow run broke Kwang Soo's heart.)
I can't find them no matter how thoroughly I look.
(Members who are still hiding)
(He arrives in front of the sound team where So Min is hiding.)
(Something is fishy here.)
(So Min disguised herself as the equipment.)
(Excuse me. Hold on.)
(Ringing)
(I must get out of here now.)
He's not here? Where is he?
(So Min can't see what's in front of her well.)
What? What is this?
You're out.
- So Min, you're eliminated. - Kwang Soo, I...
I literally tapped you like 30 times.
You should know when you've been eliminated.
Until when you are going to hide?
I thought for sure that it was a guy, but it was So Min.
(So Min is eliminated despite her embarrassing efforts.)
- 10 seconds before the race ends. - I'm doomed.
- 10, 9... - Wait.
(Did they fly to the sky or go into the ground?)
(All he can see are the crew and the empty field.)
(Let's hold out for 5 more seconds.)
(Where on earth is everyone else?)
- 2, 1. - Hold on a second.
(Kwang Soo, Let's Play is over.)
- Please be over. - One!
Great! I did it.
- Where did they hide? They're good. - All right.
Bell Hide and Seek has ended. Show yourselves!
(He sticks his head out.)
(You didn't know this, did you?)
- What? Seriously? - You didn't find me here, did you?
How could a person fit there?
- Kwang Soo. - I mean...
What were you doing?
How could I find you here?
Why not?
I thought it was a pile of garbage.
Did you only find one member?
I found So Min and Seok Jin.
- Goodness. - Oh, my.
My legs went numb.
(He's enjoying the victory too.)
Goodness. I have pins and needles in my legs.
- Ji Hyo, where were you? - Where did you hide?
I was in the kitchen.
- I was in the kitchen whole time. - Let me see.
- I even checked the drawers. - Hey.
- Goodness. - Why would you check the drawers?
This time, Kwang Soo must find members who will hide...
inside the house and eliminate them within five minutes.
(The same rules apply. He must find members hiding inside the house.)
This time, I need some clues from the assistants.
We have to find out who the assistants are among us.
So there are the assistants.
Are you the assistant? Are you going to make a noise?
No, I'm not.
- Are you the assistant? - Will you shout?
- No. - The female assistant might be her.
Sung Rok is suspicious too.
Sung Rok looks like he's the assistant.
Very much.
- I can tell by his face. - What? Gosh.
(Will they be able to get a clue regarding who the assistants are?)
It's 10 seconds before the race starts.
5, 4...
(They must stay in hiding for 5 minutes...)
(or touch the crocodile before Kwang Soo does.)
- 2. - 2.
- Open it when he enters. - One.
(If he finds a member and touch them or the crocodile, they are out.)
(Ringing)
(Jae Seok begins his plan as soon as he hears the doorbell.)
Let me go out first.
(While Kwang Soo tries to enter the house,)
(he plans to run outside and touch the crocodile.)
Let me go out first.
Hold on.
Jae Seok is eliminated.
(He gets eliminated only after 2 seconds.)
- Gosh, I thought it was a ghost. - Oh, dear.
- Gosh. - You startled me.
- Goodness. - I mean, why...
- What are you doing? - Seok Jin is behind me.
Seok Jin is behind me.
(Jae Seok tries to drag Seok Jin down with him.)
(Thank you for the nice information.)
I should go inside the room.
- Hey. - Seok Jin, you're out.
- I should go inside the room. - Hey.
(Seok Jin gets eliminated thanks to Jae Seok.)
- You can touch me to eliminate me? - What?
- Hey. - What?
- Isn't this too much? - Hold on.
(Why is he running when he's already out?)
(Jong Kook quietly watches them from next door.)
(Kwang Soo checks the windows first after eliminating the two.)
Who's that?
I think someone got caught. Oh, dear.
Goodness.
(While Kwang Soo is busy checking the room next door...)
(Now is the time!)
Wait a second.
(He climbs over the window and runs straight to the crocodile.)
(He touches down with an incredible speed.)
It's scary.
(This is Jong Kook.)
(Is he a human being or a spring?)
Is he out?
I was going to touch him first.
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
(He's checking on Haha's window.)
Gosh.
(The ace watches for a chance and runs with leisure.)
Kwang Soo.
When did you come out?
(Sung Rok succeeds as well.)
You're really bad at this.
(While Kwang Soo enters the house,)
(Haha tries to climb over the window swiftly.)
Haha's coming outside.
- Haha's slow. - You're out.
(Haha fails to succeed.)
(Bo Mi was hiding behind the sofa.)
(She comes out through the back door.)
- Oh, no! - Bo Mi.
(Bo Mi succeeds.)
- Bo Mi's good. - Where were you?
Can you hide outside?
(There are only So Min and Se Chan left.)
(He's determined to catch them.)
(So Min plans to escape from the house like Jong Kook did.)
(Let's fly like a butterfly and run away from Kwang Soo.)
(Will So Min's plan succeed?)
It won't open.
What?
(What's going on?)
Is this how you open it?
I need to get out of here, but it won't open.
It won't open.
(She can't even open the window.)
(He heard a loud bell sound in this room.)
(He walks straight to the pillar.)
So Min, you're really bad at hiding.
(So Min, you're really bad at hiding.)
- You're terrible at this game. - I mean...
- The window won't open. - You're bad at this.
This window won't open.
- You opened it in a wrong way. - That's why I couldn't...
(She wanted to escape like the Catwoman.)
You have a minute left.
(There's only Se Chan left in hiding.)
(Where are you, Se Chan?)
(Seok Jin suddenly enters the house.)
Se Chan, come out.
(Se Chan, come out.)
Se Chan, now is the time.
(Seok Jin tells him to come out.)
Se Chan, come out now.
(Seok Jin tells him to come out when Kwang Soo is around.)
- What? - Se Chan.
Seok Jin is helping Kwang Soo catch Se Chan.
(He could've gotten eliminated if he came out.)
(What's going on outside?)
He's really cunning.
How could he... Can he be so obvious in helping Kwang Soo?
- What's that? - He's cunning.
I only tried to help Se Chan.
You're terrible at being the assistant.
I know it's you.
(Flustered)
By the way, why aren't the assistants doing their job?
Haha, why aren't you doing anything?
You just did your job.
You talked with Kwang Soo a while ago too.
- You taught him where we were. - You should do your job.
I asked you what you were doing and you got flustered.
(The second round of Kwang Soo, Let's Play ends.)
- Please come outside. - Goodness.
How could you not find Se Chan?
- He's nowhere to be found. - He's not in here.
(Where did Se Chan hide?)
I searched everywhere.
- He's in there? - Here.
- Really? - My goodness.
I didn't even know these doors can open.
I almost got caught.
- You're amazing. - I told you to come out.
I knew Kwang Soo was around.
Right. You heard him, right?
- Yes, I heard. - I even saw him do it.
You really shouldn't do that.
You made it so obvious.
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
He really wasn't around.
Se Chan heard him say things to Kwang Soo.
No, we shouldn't assume.
When we look at it in a broader way, he's too weak to be the assistant.
You're exactly right.
Look at it as a whole.
- Hey. - Gosh.
I never said I'm the assistant.
- He's too weak... - I never said that.
He's too weak to be the assistant.
Can I change my assistants?
(Can I change my assistants?)
You're making it sound like I'm the assistant.
All right, I'll give the video hint to Haha and Sung Rok...
since they placed first in each round.
Please step forward.
- Okay. - Oh, you'll show us with that.
I'm 100 percent sure either one of them is the assistant.
- Gosh. - They'll watch the hint now.
I'm 100 percent sure.
(He's calling us the assistant.)
He says the assistant is either me or Sung Rok.
- I'm sure. - He's sure of it.
And he's the assistant himself.
We'll watch it now.
(They watch the first video hint.)
I'm very much worried.
To be honest, I'm not lucky in basically every game.
I have no luck in spinning roulettes.
I have no luck in playing Dreadful Pirate either.
That's why I'm worried I might be unlucky this time as well.
I'm pretty much the same as you.
Shall we go exorcise or something?
What should we do? I have no luck either.
Now that I think about it, it's most likely that we won't succeed.
What are you talking about?
We must succeed no matter what.
Here's something positive.
A lot of the members aren't that lucky either.
A lot of them.
Let's get this done. Thank you in advance.
(We aren't lucky, but we can do this.)
It's for certain.
I'm so curious.
- You know who they are? - They can't share the hint, right?
- They can't share it with others. - The first hint is big.
Gosh, what should I do, Chul Min?
Shall we do this again?
(It's too certain.)
Did the hint say his nose is big?
- Tell me. - I won't say anything.
I'm free next week.
(Is Seok Jin really the assistant?)
(Or is Kwang Soo only pretending?)
I'm free all week as well.
(They're narrowing down the assistant candidates.)
- It's cool and nice in here. - This won't do.
Goodness.
- Sit down. - Let's sit down.
What's wrong, Bo Mi?
Oh, I'm just hungry.
- Gosh, I thought you were sick. - No, I'm not.
I'm really hungry too.
Are you hungry?
- Yes. - Very much.
It's lunchtime now.
We've prepared a menu for your lunch.
- Really? - Please make orders.
I'm sure they won't give us food for free.
There it is.
- Here comes the menu. - It's Chinese cuisine.
- Gosh. - Shrimp fried rice.
- I want shrimp fried rice. - I'll take what I want to have.
Here. Let me hold this for you.
- Will we have to play some game? - Jjajangmyeon.
- I'm having what I want to have. - I'll have jjajangmyeon.
- I'll have jjamppong. - There's ulmyeon too.
- They all sound delicious. - It's either jjamppong or jjajang.
- Gosh. - Can I take seafood jjamppong?
I don't eat seafood.
I'll take japchae.
- I'll take seafood jjajangmyeon. - Let's share.
- Respect, respect. - Respect.
Then I'll take japchae rice.
I'll take ganjjajang.
Then I'll take seafood jjajang.
I'll take plain jjajang.
- I'll take plain jjajangmyeon too. - I'll have ganjjajang.
Both of you chose plain jjajang.
(It's just a coincidence.)
Come on.
- I always take plain jjajang. - Stop it.
- That's what I always have. - Ulmyeon?
- Seafood jaengban jjamppong. - Seafood jjamppong.
- Seafood jjamppong? - Seafood jjamppong?
- Seafood jaengban jjamppong. - Seafood jaengban jjamppong.
(They joke around with the dish names.)
Okay.
You know, we're being like the typical middle-aged men now.
- Gosh, it's so annoying to hear. - Too much like them.
It's so annoying to hear.
- Are you saying that we sound old? - No, we are just old.
Seafood Jjamppong.
(They're in their 40s and 50s.)
- Jjajangmyeon. - No.
Do any of you want to change your dish?
- No. - No.
- Never. - Never.
Let's just do it.
Such teamwork.
- Respect, respect, big respect. - Respect, respect, big respect.
Superman, Superman...
- Superman? - Superman?
That's mine.
Go with Wonder Woman.
Wonder, Wonder Woman.
(Laughing)
Seok Jin seems to want to join.
I shouldn't do it.
He can't speak fast.
Assistant, assistant, assistant.
- Respect, respect... - Stop it.
Gosh.
- That's you. - You got caught in the first round.
- Assistant, assistant, assistant... - You got caught in the first round.
You got caught right in the beginning.
(I'm not an assistant.)
- Assistant, assistant... - That's hilarious.
(Are we just getting the food we ordered?)
(They're waiting for their lunch.)
The order has been made.
While waiting for your food,
you'll play a game where the winner can watch...
- another hint video. - What's the game?
There are so many videos.
The game is dedicated to our hopeless romantic, Kwang Soo.
It's based on a survey of singles in their 20s and 30s.
Temperature of Love Questionnaire.
(Temperature of Love Questionnaire)
The survey consisted of popular questions on dating.
(They have to guess which option was chosen by the majority.)
That sounds fun.
It's a team competition.
It's Kwang Soo versus...
teams of 3 formed by Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo versus 3 teams of 3 people)
These two will be in different teams.
(You two can lead separate teams.)
Please make sure every team has at least one female member.
Let me tell you...
how you choose your answer.
(They'll be stacked on each other.)
When the whistle blows,
you'll be stacked on each other.
(They'll compete to be at their desired position in the stack.)
The number of the option will dictate where you want to go.
The lowest layer becomes number 1, the highest number 4.
(The bottom layer becomes number 1, and the top layer number 4.)
Why aren't the assistants doing anything?
(It's so random.)
Are they doing something?
(Seok Jin)
(That's so random.)
You should have planned those words beforehand.
Seok Jin should have had a rehearsal.
(If he turns out not to be an assistant, that'd be weird too.)
Why aren't the assistants doing anything?
Please do something.
(Seok Jin, please stop. I'll deal with it on my own.)
- Kwang Soo, please form the teams. - Okay.
Is Kwang Soo going to decide?
Yes, he'll form the teams.
Team Red...
(Team Red)
- It should be Jong Kook's team. - Okay.
- Me? - Yes,
Okay.
All members of the winning team will watch the video.
- Really? - Really?
- Yes. - Then it's important.
Give me one of those red vests.
(I want to be in the same team as Jong Kook.)
I'm so tired.
(Let me team up with Jong Kook.)
(Ignoring)
Give them to clumsy ones.
One for you then.
(Give them to clumsy ones.)
(One for you then.)
(Embarrassed)
Nice.
- One for his assistant. - Lastly...
So Min.
She's clumsy too.
On Jong Kook's team...
They got caught by me in the last game.
- They're both clumsy. - We're the clumsy ones.
- They're the clumsy ones... - They're clumsy.
Clumsy Jeon and Awkward Jee.
- Team Clumsy. - Team Clumsy.
Cross.
(Clumsy Jeon and Awkward Jee)
(Team Red: Jong Kook, Seok Jin, and So Min)
(Team Green: Jae Seok, Sung Rok, and Ji Hyo)
(Team White: Haha, Se Chan, and Bo Mi)
This question is...
for male members.
Okay. Sung Rok will play for us.
Please pick one male member.
- Jong Kook. - Let's do this.
(Haha is representing Team White.)
If you think number three is the correct answer,
you have to try to be the third layer.
If you want to be the third layer,
do you wait for two people to stack up...
or do you stack them up yourself?
- What do you do? - Do whatever you want.
Can you do what you want?
I suddenly feel so tired.
(I suddenly feel so tired.)
- Respect, respect. - Respect.
Respect, respect.
Respect.
We're so tired.
Here goes question number one.
Here we go.
"You get a text from your crush late at night..."
"asking if you're asleep. What would you do?"
Number 1 is texting "No" right away.
Number 2 is texting "I'm having a beer" after a moment.
You'd do the first one, right? You'd text "No" right away.
Yes.
I think...
I think it's number 4.
- I think it's number 1. - "I didn't see your message."
Let's stick to our first choice, number 1.
- It's either number 1 or 2. - Go with number 1.
I think it's either number 1 or 2.
It could be number 1.
I'm sorry,
but shouldn't you be thinking to yourself?
(Shouldn't you be thinking to yourself?)
I couldn't be standing here quietly.
Have you made up your mind?
- Yes. - Please.
Ready...
(Stacking is more important.)
(Stacking starts.)
I think it's number 1.
(Let me be the 1st layer.)
It's number 1.
(Excuse me.)
Sung Rok is pushing in.
- You want to be the 1st layer? - Yes.
Can you lie on your back too?
- There you go. - Number 2 can't be right.
- You think so? - It can't be.
Is it number 1?
Sung Rok is the first layer now.
- Sung Rok is the first layer. - Jong Kook!
Sung Rok is the 1st layer.
The correct answer might be number 4.
- I can't wait. - Stop.
I'm not sure.
The correct answer is...
Which one is it?
It was chosen by 40 percent of the respondents.
Really?
(It was chosen by 40 percent of the respondents.)
(Is it number 1?)
Number 1, texting "No" right away.
(Team Green wins.)
Number 1 was the simplest.
Number 1.
Number 2,
"I'm having a beer" was chosen by 37 percent.
I see.
It was either number 1 or 2.
I thought it'd be number 3.
Me too.
Number 3, "I was working",
was chosen by the least people, 4 percent.
You're the worst kind of guy.
(It was chosen by the least number of people.)
The worst kind of guy.
I've been getting advice from Jae Seok.
That's why I'm still single.
- We're in that 4 percent. - Yes.
- We're in that 4 percent. - 4 percent.
(They know nothing about dating.)
What would you do, Bo Mi?
- Number 2. - Why?
I couldn't wait too long if he's my crush.
You're leading him to say, "Can I join?"
- Exactly. - Number 2...
What did you do when Kwang Soo video called you at night?
(What about when Kwang Soo video called Bo Mi?)
(Kwang Soo, while drunk, woke Bo Mi up.)
What did you do?
(What did she do?)
I had to work.
"I didn't see your message because I was working."
That's great.
You would have seen it late because of work too.
- Yes. - Right.
She's in that four percent too.
Bo Mi is in that four percent.
What about you, Sung Rok?
If you just write, "No",
the other person will have to say something.
You're so smart.
Then afterwards, I could suggest having a beer together...
- or say I was working. - You'd just write, "No."
Yes.
He's so smart.
He's a dating expert.
- Jong Kook, what about you? - I'd write, "No."
When I have a crush on someone,
I like to tease her.
So...
Because you're shy?
Yes. If she asks me what I'm doing,
I'd say, "Everything except thinking about you".
As a joke.
(Everything except thinking about you?)
- What? - Jong Kook.
(Screaming)
- Calm down. - What's with you?
Let me explain.
It's not like that.
I hate it.
Bo Mi hates guys who do that.
- It's just an example. - Hey!
You hate it, right? She hates it.
Let's say Jong Kook wrote, "Everything..."
- I don't actually do that. - "except thinking about you."
What would you write back?
- I wouldn't write anything. - She'd ignore it.
(I wouldn't write anything.)
(She'd ignore it.)
She'd ignore it.
- She'd ignore it. - Please ask me.
What about you, So Min?
"Why are you not thinking about me?"
- There you go. - She took the bait.
Sometimes, the girl takes the bait.
I would.
Let's say the girl wrote that...
- to me. - What should I say?
"Why are you not thinking about me?"
"If I do, I won't be able to sleep."
(So Min falls again.)
Then what would you say?
(What are they doing?)
Jong Kook, Bo Mi is still ignoring your messages.
She's still ignoring them.
At least one girl took the bait.
So Min loves these things.
- She loves it. - She does.
(What would So Min write back?)
"Why wouldn't you be able to sleep?"
- "Because you'd miss me too much?" - Cut it out.
(Because you'd miss me too much?)
(Cut it out.)
Respect.
- I can't stand it. - Be quiet.
- I've had enough. - Be quiet.
- I don't actually do this. - So Min looks so happy.
What would you write back?
I just say it as a joke.
I can't believe I've been getting advice from those two.
I'm experienced.
Male members will play again.
I'll go this time.
- Those who haven't played... - It's weak ones this time.
You should...
Let's do this.
- You should wait. - You're right.
- I have a chance this time. - You shouldn't lie down too fast.
The next question was answered by men in their 20s and 30s.
- Men? - Only men?
Then I have an advantage.
Here goes the question.
Let's do this.
"Your girlfriend asks how many girls you have dated. What's your answer?"
Number 1, "Tell her how many girls you have dated."
Number 2, "Ask her the same question."
Number 3, "Ask her what counts as a girlfriend."
Number 4, "Of course you are my first and last love."
- Number d4. - Of course it's number 4.
"Of course you are my first and last love."
For me, it's number 1. I reveal everything.
- Why would you do that? - I reveal everything.
I think it's number 4.
- It's number 4. - It's number 4.
Number 4 is too romantic.
No one wants number 2, right? I will choose number 2.
- Get ready. - Get down on the floor.
- Don't tell me what to do. - Set.
(The stacking begins.)
No, no.
Let's put him on the bottom. He is strong.
- Let's do that. - Let's do that.
- Go to the bottom. - I will get away.
Come on.
Wait a minute.
(He strikes back with his sharp chin.)
This is getting dirty.
Hey, hey.
My goodness, wait a minute.
I don't want to choose number 3.
(The stacking ends.)
- Number 2. - Number 4.
- The answer is... - Number 4.
(Everyone in the winning team gets to watch a hint video.)
Number 4 is too cheesy.
- The answer is... - Number 4 is too cheesy.
number 1.
(Team White wins.)
- Respect, respect. - Respect, respect.
- Really? - I would tell my girlfriend.
That's what people do these days.
I thought the answer would be...
either number 1 or 4.
Then I thought a girlfriend might get upset...
- by number 1. - Number 4 is the best.
Bo Mi, in a woman's point of view, which option is the best?
I like either number 1 or 2.
- It's not number 4. - Women don't like number 4.
Do you prefer hearing, "Right back at you"?
I wouldn't like it if he says, "Right back at you."
"How many boys have you dated?"
- Is that better? - He could ask me that.
It's better to ask playfully. "How many boys have you dated?"
It's another way of saying, "The past isn't important."
- That's right. - You are a loving man.
- You are a loving man. - What about you, So Min?
- I like number 4. - Of course you do.
They say ignorance is bliss.
I wouldn't want to keep thinking about my boyfriend's past.
That's why it's better to reveal everything.
Why don't you ask the question to Jong Kook?
Jong Kook says he will tell all. Act out the situation.
How many girls have you dated?
Do I need to reveal it here?
(I am on a shoot.)
- There are a lot of cameras. - Tell us.
This is Truth or Dare.
Even though there are cameras, imagine that we are by ourselves.
- You have dated a lot of women. - That's a lot.
Which one did you love the most? Rank them from top 1 to 8.
(Which one did you love the most? Rank them from top 1 to 8.)
The woman I broke up with the most recently is the one...
- I loved the most. - The most recent one?
- How do I rank? - You?
It hasn't been long since we met. I don't love you.
Are you sure this is better?
- Is this better? - Is this better?
Is this really better?
- This is how the conversation goes. - Then why are you dating me?
It's too early to talk about love.
Will you give me a place only after you break up with me?
So Min got him.
- So Min is hard to beat. - That's right.
You will be top one when we get married.
You can't ensure that we will get married.
Isn't this the end of their schedule?
That kind of a situation means...
(Isn't this the end of their schedule?)
- That kind of a situation means... - They would get annoyed.
the end of their schedule for the day.
Listen.
They would have to stop the car.
- They would have to stop the car. - They would have to do that.
(There is a 100 percent chance the couple would stop the car.)
You didn't marry your previous girlfriends.
- I didn't love them enough. - You might not marry me.
Ask her how many men she has dated.
Stay out of it.
(This is getting interesting.)
What do you think you are doing?
- Who are you? - What do you think you are doing?
Go on your way.
This is the highlight.
For goodness' sake. What do you think you are doing?
We were at the most important part.
Sung Rok, what would be your choice?
My choice would be number 4.
- Right? - That's right.
I have an idea. Ji Hyo doesn't like number 4.
She likes it when men are honest. Please act out the situation.
- Give it a go. - All right.
Ji Hyo, ask him the question.
Sung Rok, how many women have you dated?
- Me? - Yes.
You are the first one.
Don't lie.
(Slapping)
- Ji Hyo. - She looked him up and down.
- Ji Hyo. - The thing is,
he didn't look confident when he said that.
(Despite the perfect line, his eyes couldn't hide the truth.)
(Shifting)
Ji Hyo is a professional.
This time,
the ones with the same style will act out a situation.
Why don't Sung Rok and So Min give it a go?
Both of you chose the same answer.
- Give it a go. - Okay.
It's not a bad answer if you love the woman very much.
How many women have you dated?
Me? You are the first one.
- Am I really the first one? - Yes.
Then why are you such a good kisser?
(Then why are you such a good kisser?)
She began to investigate.
There are women who begin to investigate.
- I mean... - What do you think you are doing?
Why did you ask him that?
- She is ridiculous. - This is crazy.
What do you think you are doing?
Seriously.
Are you an investigator?
She is like a prosecutor.
Are you a prosecutor?
What is wrong with her?
I want Jae Seok and So Min to give it a go.
- Me? - He always says he is an expert.
He always gives advice to Kwang Soo.
As everyone knows, I am Kwang Soo's relationship coach.
To be honest, this happened once.
There was a time a woman dated my body...
and Jae Seok's mind.
(This is an experience I had.)
Were you okay with that?
- He is my relationship coach. - I coach him...
with precision.
I point out the important parts. Let's go, So Min.
Here comes the prosecutor.
(The expert of interrogation)
- Okay. - She is an investigator.
(The relationship prosecutor, So Min)
Here comes the prosecutor.
(Interesting)
She is a prosecutor. She is an investigator.
I am not an easy target.
(The fierce melodrama unfolds.)
- I am not an easy target. - Jae Seok.
Have many women have you dated?
My goodness.
- Don't you know what I am like? - No.
You are my first and last love.
How is that possible? You are very old.
I need to focus on the road.
(Let's have a conversation later.)
- What was that? - Jae Seok.
Are you in Japan? Why are you on the right side?
Why are you on the right side?
Did you go to Japan?
- You are on the right side. - Right now,
- we are in Okinawa. - Okinawa.
- We are in Okinawa. - Okay.
Am I the first woman who came here with you?
(She begins her investigation.)
(The relationship expert seems to be flustered.)
I can't stop laughing.
- I am the first woman, right? - I can't stop laughing.
(The relationship expert seems to be flustered.)
Wait a minute.
(Prosecutor, wait a minute.)
Hey.
- Did you swear at your girlfriend? - It means "Wait a minute."
- Since I am in Japan, - That's right.
- I am learning Japanese. - Okay.
You know this, right?
I don't share my heart with another easily.
- Not even in elementary school? - Of course I didn't.
- What about in middle school? - I had a few blind dates.
Look at his face. Of course he didn't.
(Look at his face. Of course he didn't.)
Look at your boyfriend's face.
It doesn't make sense that you don't believe him.
Believe him.
- Don't you feel bad for him? - Look at his face.
- Look at his face. - Do you really think he is lying?
For goodness' sake.
- You should believe him. - This is driving me crazy.
- Look at his face. - This is driving me crazy.
A lot of people are cool.
These days,
it's better to be confident and cool.
Your answer should match the atmosphere and situation.
There is no right answer.
- There is no right answer in love. - Talking about first love...
Write it down.
Write it down. "There is no right answer in love."
- It's nothing impressive. - Remember my words.
This is Yu Jae Seok's relationship notebook.
"There is no right answer in love."
(Women answer the third question.)
(The stacking involves dirty moves such as a low kick and dragging.)
It's over.
The answer is number 4.
(Team Green wins Temperature of Love Questionnaire.)
The three members of Team Green, please come forward.
(Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, and Sung Rok have the chance to watch the hint video.)
They will watch the video at the same time.
(What kind of a hint does the video contain?)
Aren't you hungry? Shall we order something?
It's already late. What shall we eat?
- Shall we eat jjajangmyeon? - My choice is jjajangmyeon too.
What would you like?
I like jjajangmyeon too.
Please order jjajangmyeon and jaengban jjajangmyeon.
(Everyone likes jjajangmyeon.)
This is...
This is very telling.
(What?)
(Before they played a game, they ordered food together.)
(Se Chan ordered jjajangmyeon to share with So Min.)
(Sung Rok, Bo Mi, and Seok Jin also ordered jjajangmyeon.)
(Are the assistants among these four members?)
This is very telling.
Isn't this too telling?
- It must be a helpful hint. - Did you watch the video?
(Why are they so surprised?)
Okay.
(Let's see if they succeed in apprehending the assistants.)
(Final Mission)
The final mission in the Half and Half Tour Pass Race...
is called Death Signal.
(Death Signal)
USB sticks with hint videos in them are hidden in this building.
- USB sticks? - Hint videos?
You have to guess who the assistants are...
and report using 1 of the 2 hidden walkie-talkies.
You're given only one chance to report,
and the race will end when the assistants are arrested.
(That means Kwang Soo and his assistants have lost.)
When your report turns out to be false,
you will be eliminated immediately. So be careful when you do.
One of the assistants is here. We don't have to do all that.
(This is really the last stage.)
Assistants can eliminate others by removing their name tags.
- Pardon? - Only the assistants...
can do that.
- We have to run. - Really?
If everyone is eliminated before the assistants are arrested,
Kwang Soo will win the right...
to choose two people to follow him to Australia.
(Kwang Soo can bring 2 more people.)
That's big.
If the assistants are arrested,
the surviving members will not be going to Australia.
Two of the eliminated members will be going.
All the surviving members will be excluded?
Yes.
(Then the assistants should do a good job.)
(Restless)
(Look at Seok Jin.)
Seok Jin must have lost focus at some point.
- Why? - He probably gave up.
He suddenly started to do this.
And he started practicing with Bo Mi's name tag.
- Don't say that. - Stop it.
Don't say that.
- It's so obvious. - Stop it.
- You're so mean. - Think whatever you want.
Think whatever you want, but don't forget.
You'll be paying for it.
Please go to your positions so we can start the race.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(They move to their starting positions.)
We can only report using the walkie-talkies,
and only assistants can remove name tags?
(Sung Rok is still trying to understand the rules.)
Haha, who do you think...
are assistants?
- Hey. - I know too, but...
My guess is Sung Rok...
and Seok Jin.
- Really? - Yes.
Where are you going?
- Where are you going? - Seok Jin.
You'll be here? Okay.
I'll come back to get you.
I'll remove your name tag.
(What?)
(Remove his name tag?)
Only assistants can remove name tags.
Are you saying you're an assistant?
I'm just saying.
(Is he really an assistant who is just a bit clumsy?)
I'm sure Seok Jin and Se Chan are assistants.
Yes, Se Chan.
The way he spoke in that video was too obvious.
I'm sure.
(Although the voice was disguised,)
(judging from the way he spoke, was it Se Chan?)
Se Chan usually speaks that way.
He speaks quite fast.
What will Seok Jin do?
I feel so sorry for him.
Dear assistants,
you must love jjajangmyeon.
(She means something by it.)
I think I know who you are.
Seok Jin and Bo Mi.
(Her guess)
(Assistants love jjajangmyeon.)
(Who are...)
(Kwang Soo's assistants?)
The race will start soon. 10,
- 9, 8... - I'm bad at finding things.
(They have to report assistants.)
7, 6...
(If they report the wrong person, they'll be eliminated.)
(Who will survive to the end?)
The race starts now.
Here we go.
(The race starts.)
I have to find USB sticks first.
(They have to find out who the assistants are.)
There might be one around here.
(Nervous)
Gosh, I'm scared.
(She usually gets eliminated this way.)
(If I can find USB sticks...)
(Kwang Soo is following him.)
(Kwang Soo suddenly...)
(runs to him.)
(Approaching)
Gosh.
(What is he doing?)
What are you doing?
- I'm just wandering around. - Kwang Soo.
All right. Anyway...
Kwang Soo. What are you doing?
What's going on?
(You two look suspicious.)
(Kwang Soo disappears.)
Hey.
He's just trying to make me look suspicious.
Gosh, I can't believe Kwang Soo.
Come here.
(So Min searches the convenience store.)
Hello. Have you seen USB sticks?
- No. - Didn't anyone hide anything here?
No.
Didn't anyone come here?
No. We don't carry USB sticks.
Didn't anyone leave any boxes here?
No.
(There must be one here.)
Unbelievable.
(So Min finds hint number 1.)
(Each USB stick has a different hint.)
(Careful)
It's playing.
- Should we order something? - What about jjajangmyeon?
- I want jjajangmyeon too. - Me too.
Jjajangmyeon and jaengban jjajangmyeon, please.
(So Min now knows the assistants like jjajangmyeon.)
Some of us ordered jjajangmyeon today.
(In addition to Se Chan and Seok Jin,)
(Sung Rok, Kwang Soo, and Bo Mi had jjajangmyeon.)
(This is very helpful.)
- Some people ordered jjajangmyeon. - So Min.
- Hey. - Did you watch a hint video?
No.
(She didn't even hesitate.)
I saw you taking off the earphones.
You lie all the time.
You're scary.
- That's not true. - Forget it.
Ji Hyo, I'll tell you something.
Who likes jjajangmyeon?
Jae Seok? Se Chan?
Se Chan said, "I'll definitely order a jjajangmyeon."
(I'm sure it's Se Chan.)
It's Se Chan.
Who ordered jjajangmyeon except Se Chan and Seok Jin?
Who were they?
(Se Chan and Seok Jin are suspicious.)
(Meanwhile...)
Bo Mi.
Hi.
(Se Chan, Bo Mi, and Seok Jin run into each other.)
(They all had jjajangmyeon.)
Is that Se Chan? Se Chan.
Yes? It's Seok Jin.
It's Seok Jin. Run.
(Running)
(Hurrying)
It's Seok Jin.
(Is he gone?)
(Sneaking)
(She found a USB stick.)
Unbelievable.
(She finds a laptop too.)
I can do this.
Finally, I get to watch it.
Jjajangmyeon and jaengban jjajangmyeon, please.
(The hint is jjajangmyeon?)
(Noise)
(Someone is coming.)
Someone watched a video here.
Unbelievable.
Wait.
(Who is coming?)
Who is it?
(The sound is getting near.)
(Who is chasing Bo Mi?)
(An assistant?)
Please lock the door.
They like jjajangmyeon.
(Hold on)
Unbelievable. They like jjajangmyeon.
Who ordered jjajangmyeon?
Se Chan and Seok Jin...
It must be them.
(Se Chan and Seok Jin had jjajangmyeon.)
(Se Chan?)
(Seok Jin?)
(Peeking)
(Someone is approaching.)
(Rattling)
(Come on, Bo Mi.)
(Wait)
(Kwang Soo?)
(It's me.)
Hold on.
Kwang Soo,
hold on.
You can't rip my name tag off.
- You can't, right? - I can't.
(Only the assistants can rip it off.)
(There's a dark shadow that's approaching them.)
Please save me just this once.
Please.
- Hurry. - Why?
Bo Mi.
Hold on.
(Shrieking)
Hey.
Where were you?
(The assistant has appeared.)
(Bo Mi is eliminated.)
Bo Mi is eliminated.
(They're shocked by the news.)
What now? I'm scared.
If I get eliminated,
I can't even talk.
The assistant started moving.
(He's shocked.)
Is there anything up there? I can go up, right?
(The assistant did his first job.)
(Who will the next target be?)
Kwang Soo.
Come here.
There's nobody, right?
And the other person was a woman. It was a woman's neck.
(These two share information on the assistant.)
Who can rip mine off?
(They see Seok Jin and Kwang Soo together.)
(I'm 200 percent sure the assistant is Seok Jin.)
Come here, So Min.
(Let's get away and look for more hints.)
Where's the laptop?
(Jong Kook is also looking for more hints.)
(What's this?)
It's so obvious.
(Sung Rok finds a USB too.)
I got it.
(Hint video 7)
Okay.
A crocodile cage? Why do people have to go in there?
I can't even imagine it. I'm so scared.
The assistant has a mole. Wait...
(He has a mole on the back of his neck.)
I'll never do it. I'm frightened of crocodiles.
We are normal.
(They are all cowards.)
One person has a mole on the back of his neck.
Hair is shaved at the back, so it must be a male.
The assistant...
(It's somebody who has a mole on his neck and is a coward.)
People keep running away from me.
(Is Seok Jin the assistant because Kwang Soo keeps on following him?)
Unless somebody calls and eliminates you...
I have to go on the other side.
(Se Chan looks quite busy too.)
Let's see.
(Jae Seok is hiding and checking his hint.)
I'm pretty worried.
I'm usually not very lucky.
I'm not that lucky either.
Should we perform an exorcism?
(Thinking)
(What is that watch?)
Jae Seok, please tell me. Is it somebody unexpected?
Jae Seok, we have to know so that we can work together.
- Exactly. - Right?
What's so shocking about it?
Hold on.
Is it not somebody you thought it was?
I'll share my hint.
Please tell us.
(He considers Haha's suggestion.)
No, I need to think about this.
Boss.
We made you win...
in Japan.
You are our king.
You are our boss.
(The 1st Place Tour in Osaka during the summer)
(Haha and So Min pledged allegiance to Jae Seok.)
(King Grasshopper, please pity us.)
I am...
really sorry but please leave.
Jae Seok.
(It didn't work.)
- Tell me the name. - I have to think about this.
- Tell us this. - Look at this.
(The new hint...)
(is this watch.)
(At the same time)
(Everybody is busy looking for hints.)
You had seafood jjajangmyeon today, right?
- Yes. - Can you give me a hint?
(She's so random.)
A hint? What does that have to do with eating jjajangmyeon?
I'll tell you one thing too.
- What is it? - A hint.
- Can you tell me? - Can you tell me something too?
(They are busy asking for each other's hint.)
(She's going to tell him a hint?)
You're the assistant, right?
- Me? - Yes.
You can report me and check.
(Se Chan pays attention to their conversation.)
I'm scared.
- I'm so scared. Se Chan. - What?
(He disappears when they're done talking.)
Did you get any hint?
No, I have nothing. He's scary.
- Are you going around together? - Sung Rok's eyes are scary.
(He disappears when they're done talking.)
(Is Se Chan really the assistant?)
s
This must be the set for "Temperature of Love".
(Temperature of Love)
This is so nice.
I can't do this.
I have to work. Let's work first, So Min.
Let's work and come back another time.
I've never been here before. May I come in?
(Se Chan signals somebody.)
There's no way out.
Can I go this way to get to the main building?
You have to get out to go to the main building.
- I think Seok Jin will be there. - You have to go back up.
No. Don't do this.
No way.
(Somebody is after So Min.)
No.
I'm going to lock it.
What do I do?
This isn't right.
(Please save me.)
My gosh.
My goodness. What do I do?
This isn't right. Don't do this.
I didn't know it'll end like this.
(Ripping sound)
So Min is eliminated.
(So Min is eliminated?)
Gosh.
I'm getting goose bumps.
(He doesn't know who the assistant is but he's frightened.)
There's a walkie-talkie.
(You get one chance to report the assistant.)
(If you get the wrong person, you are eliminated.)
(It's dangerous to report before you know who the assistant is.)
I've narrowed down,
but it's too early.
- Haha. - My gosh.
(He almost got a heart attack.)
This is not what I thought.
- Are you trying to get me? - No. Look.
Seok Jin...
Seok Jin didn't do anything...
- when Jae Seok was passing by. - Of course he would.
- Why? - So that he's not suspected.
Why did you look at my back?
- What do you mean? - Hey.
It's not me.
It's not me, Haha.
(Se Chan, you are a bit suspicious.)
- Hey. - Haha.
- Let's go look at it. - What is it? Do you have it?
Okay. Lead the way.
You lead the way.
Haha, we are going to the Nevis Swing together.
- Swing - All right.
- Later. - Okay.
Follow me.
- What? - Go first.
- Let's see it together. Please. - No.
I'll join you later.
I trust you.
- All right? - I trust you, Haha.
Trust me.
(Something is fishy.)
Why aren't there any hints?
(Let me look for some hints.)
(Se Chan is lost. He's just looking for hints.)
There isn't any.
- Let's stop. - What?
Let's stop.
(He was being suspected the whole time.)
Was it you?
Is it you?
(He's eliminated?)
What's this? What are you?
I'm the assistant.
(Se Chan is eliminated.)
You are?
- Se Chan is eliminated. - What?
Se Chan is eliminated?
(You are nothing special.)
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
Go.
Go to Australia.
(Go to Australia.)
Go.
(Am I going to see the crocodiles?)
I'm 100 percent sure that it's Seok Jin.
(With Se Chan being eliminated, there are not many candidates left.)
I got high-level information.
Ji Hyo covered her lips...
when she was talking about jjajangmyeon.
- Jjajangmyeon? - Yes.
(Jjajangmyeon?)
Okay. Got it.
I don't know anymore. I'm going to say it before I get eliminated.
(I'll do what's necessary.)
Find the walkie-talkie, quick.
(However)
I have goose bumps.
He has a mole right at the end of his hairline.
(Haha has a mole on his neck?)
(In the hint video he saw,)
(somebody had a mole at the same position.)
(Is Haha the assistant?)
He has it at the end.
(He does...)
(have a mole on his neck.)
It's Seok Jin, Sung Rok, or Haha?
Each person...
- Did you see the hint? - I did.
- Did you? - It's not you.
No, I...
(What?)
(What's this ringtone?)
(A few minutes ago)
Another positive fact...
is that many members are unlucky. It's not little.
- Excuse me. - Let's work together. Good luck.
(The ringtone rang in the hint video.)
I heard the ringtone in the video.
It was that tone.
(Seok Jin got attacked too.)
(Who is this assistant?)
(Ripping off)
Seok Jin is eliminated.
(Seok Jin, a strong candidate, is eliminated.)
I get eliminated here.
(Five people are eliminated.)
Why are you here?
Stop lying.
- What? - Did you come here on purpose?
No, I'm eliminated.
- You are eliminated? - Did you ask another assistant?
- Hold on. - Let me see.
I'm not an assistant.
Why were you acting strange today?
You did that to me.
I kept on denying it.
(This is so unfair.)
Is it Se Chan? Se Chan.
(They ran away from him.)
(They ran away from him for no reason.)
(She ran away teasingly.)
(You guys have been running away from me all day.)
(Kwang Soo was following him.)
Go.
(He kept on coming back.)
(He handed over an empty box.)
(Ji Hyo saw it.)
(This is driving me nuts.)
(Is he really the assistant?)
(I'm not the assistant.)
I'm speechless.
I've been suspected all day, and now I'm out.
- It's Haha. - I kept on denying it.
It's Haha.
I told you it's him.
- It's him. - It's Haha.
- It's Haha and... - It's him.
(Is Haha the assistant?)
Are you eliminated?
- He's here. - Hey, assistant.
You're so it.
- The assistant? I'm eliminated too. - Really?
(Haha is eliminated?)
(5 minutes ago on rooftop of the annex)
(When you report the wrong person, you are out immediately.)
(Haha reported Seok Jin and Sung Rok.)
(I caught the assistants.)
Haha, you did not state the correct answer.
What?
You are eliminated.
(Haha got eliminated for reporting the wrong people.)
I got confused...
and I remembered that Seok Jin had a mole on his neck.
But it's actually metallic poisoning, not a mole.
Metallic poisoning?
Do you wear necklaces?
- I don't. - You should wear gold.
They are cowards, right? And then?
- They like jjajangmyeon. - It's either Jong Kook or Jae Seok.
It's Jae Seok.
It's Jae Seok then, it can't be Jong Kook.
I told you it's Jae Seok.
(Is it really Jae Seok?)
(He's the new candidate now.)
This...
(Is he really...)
(The hint Jae Seok found said that the assistant is unlucky.)
(The camera closed up on the watch.)
It's Kwang Soo. He was wearing the watch.
There's the watch,
and I know how Kwang Soo's hand looks like.
Those are his hands.
(These hands are Kwang Soo's hands?)
Aren't you hungry? Should we order something?
- Should we have jjajangmyeon? - I like jjajangmyeon too.
Jjajangmyeon and jaengban jjajangmyeon, please.
(Kwang Soo ordered jjajangmyeon for lunch too.)
It means this is a fabricated story.
(He puts the pieces of the puzzle together.)
This is a fabricated story.
(The jjajangmyeon and the watch sound like a fabricated story.)
It's one person.
(Is Kwang Soo the male assistant?)
(They come across each other.)
(Is Kwang Soo the assistant like Jae Seok predicted?)
Did you find a hint?
Yes.
(You found it.)
(He checks Kwang Soo's watch.)
You can't rip mine off.
(You can only give orders.)
No, only the assistant can.
Right.
(Only the assistant can.)
That's right.
Hold on.
(Let me see your wrist.)
(Goodness)
What's wrong?
You are...
(This watch was...)
(on the male assistant's wrist.)
(Does that mean...)
You are the guy.
(Does that mean Kwang Soo is the male assistant?)
I think...
- it's time for you to go. - Where would I go?
(He's scary.)
What's wrong with you?
(Kwang Soo attacks.)
(He chases Jae Seok while calling somebody.)
Main building, 2nd floor.
What is he doing?
Main building, second floor for Jae Seok.
(He keeps on telling Jae Seok's location to somebody.)
It's Jae Seok. He's going back to the first floor.
He's going back to the first floor.
Where are you, girl?
(Is it Ji Hyo?)
(Is Ji Hyo the female assistant?)
(But the woman in the hint was unlucky and a coward.)
(That's totally opposite from Ji Hyo.)
(Then is Kwang Soo making this up?)
Hey.
Come here.
(Let me see your neck.)
(Jong Kook is watching another hint video.)
Hello.
(Kwang Soo went into the meeting room.)
(Some time passed and he came out.)
See you later. Thank you.
(The chair is empty.)
Thank you. Please drive safely.
Thank you.
(Is he talking to the empty chair?)
There's nobody.
(What's this?)
What's this?
Let me see.
(He's still trying to look at Kwang Soo's neck.)
You have a mole, right?
You do.
(Ji Hyo said the female assistant had a neck on her neck.)
- She has a mole? - Yes.
He has it.
(He has a mole in the same position as the female assistant.)
(Is Kwang Soo also the female assistant?)
(They're unlucky and cowardly.)
(They are so much like Kwang Soo.)
(The female assistant had a mole,)
(and the male assistant had a watch.)
(The watch is on Kwang Soo.)
(He also has a mole on his neck.)
(Hold on.)
Hold on.
(Does this mean...)
- Should we get jjajangmyeon? - I like jjajangmyeon.
I like jjajangmyeon too.
(They all like jjajangmyeon,)
(and they are all cowards.)
(They are unlucky as well.)
Is there no assistant?
(What's this?)
Is he by himself?
(Is Kwang Soo by himself?)
(The male assistant who wore a watch...)
(and the female assistant with a mole on her neck...)
(were all Kwang Soo.)
Is there no assistant?
Is he by himself?
Is Kwang Soo by himself?
(He's frightened.)
That's insane.
I just have to find the walkie-talkie.
(He knows who the assistant is now.)
He has the watch hint already?
(Oh, dear.)
(You can eliminate the assistant by speaking into the walkie-talkie.)
This is the end.
The assistant is...
Lee Kwang Soo.
He is faking it.
Eliminate Kwang Soo's name tag.
(Rip off Kwang Soo's name tag.)
You have to rip off Kwang Soo's name tag.
Gosh. This is unbelievable.
(Jae Seok has to rip Kwang Soo's name tag off.)
Where is he?
(Where are you, Kwang Soo?)
(He spots Kwang Soo.)
You are alone.
(Is he calling someone again?)
Who are you calling?
(Give me your name tag.)
(Kwang Soo did not expect Jae Seok's attack.)
(This will end now.)
(The situation reached its breaking point.)
(A phone starts to ring as Kwang Soo makes the call.)
(He stops.)
What's going on?
(Is there another assistant other than Kwang Soo?)
(Whose phone is ringing?)
(Hold on. He is...)
(Shin Sung Rok)
He is not alone.
(Hi, Jae Seok.)
(He starts running after Jae Seok without any hesitation.)
Sung Rok.
Grab him.
(He ran fast...)
(and ripped off Jae Seok's name tag.)
(He helps Kwang Soo to rip name tags off.)
(What's his identity?)
Is he alone?
(10 minutes earlier, after Jong Koon saw the hint.)
This is crazy.
(The hint was not over.)
(After Kwang Soo left,)
(Sung Rok came out quietly.)
We should decide...
who will get penalized this week.
(However)
Jjajangmyeon and jaengban jjajangmyeon, please.
(Jjajangmyeon and jaengban jjajangmyeon, please.)
(Jjajangmyeon and jaengban jjajangmyeon?)
(Jjajangmyeon is for Kwang Soo.)
(Jaengban jjajangmyeon is for Sung Rok.)
Why do we have to go inside the Cage of Death?
Please help me.
(When he reached out his arm for a handshake,)
(someone else grabbed his hand from another angle.)
(It was Sung Rok.)
(The hidden assistant was Sung Rok.)
Let's end this now.
(No one expected...)
(Sung Rok's name tag hunting.)
(Ji Hyo was eliminated by his quick and surprise attack.)
(To complete his mission,)
(he has to rip off Jong Kook's name tag.)
What's going on?
What's going on? Wasn't it you?
Wasn't it you?
I wasn't the assistant.
You were not the assistant?
It was his self-fabricated scenario.
Everyone in the video was Kwang Soo.
Was it computer graphics then?
- I don't get it. - What's going on?
- They were both Kwang Soo. - Were they?
Yes. It was Kwang Soo.
- And... - Then what about...
real assistants were not them.
It was Sung Rok who stayed separately.
Sung Rok is the assistant.
- We know that already. - We were eliminated by him.
- Oh, really? - Gosh.
(He's embarrassed.)
- He didn't know anything. - Why didn't you know that?
The assistant is Kwang Soo.
Rip off Kwang Soo's name tag.
(He is happy as he thinks he found the assistant.)
There is only Jong Kook's name tag left.
That's why we've to look for him.
(Aren't I clever?)
Gosh.
Kwang Soo.
(It's good to see you.)
You found the hint.
- Yes. - You found the hint.
- Okay. Let go of my arm first. - Hey you.
- You little... - Stop.
- Jong Kook. - What's going on?
Hey. What is this?
(What is going on?)
"I'm not the assistant."
(I'm not the assistant.)
(Oh, it's Sung Rok.)
Did he rip Kwang Soo's name tag off?
(Gosh)
I should go and protect the walkie-talkie.
I should go now.
(He wants to block Jong Kook from reporting.)
Let's run. We have to run now.
(If Sung Rok eliminates Jong Kook,)
(Kwang Soo can choose 2 people for the penalty.)
(This is the end.)
(Who will get to the walkie-talkie first?)
(Sung Rok arrives at the place after running with his everything.)
The assistant is...
(Jong Kook got here faster than Sung Rok.)
The assistant is Sung Rok.
(The assistant is Sung Rok.)
(The assistant Sung Rok is eliminated.)
I was lucky to spot Kwang Soo first.
I was so surprised.
(The race ends. Jong Kook receives the exemption pass.)
For the last Death Signal,
only Jong Kook received the exemption pass.
For the final decision,
Kwang Soo can rip the name tag off the member whom he wants to take with him.
(1 person will experience...)
(Cage of Death with Kwang Soo in Australia.)
(Who will experience this horrifying crocodile with Kwang Soo?)
Everyone, make a short speech.
Just choose one.
(He is so sick of it.)
- Yes. - Those two can go to Australia...
- on their way to New Zealand. - It's a good idea.
- It's okay. - Is it?
- It costs us even less that way. - Can we do that?
Kwang Soo.
- Nevis Swing is... - I think...
on the way to Australia and New Zealand,.
Why do you care so much?
I'll listen to him first.
There are also some members who didn't get any penalties.
I think we should balance it out a bit.
- I agree. - I think so too.
I will just say one thing.
Haha and I have to go and experience Nevis Swing.
- Okay. You don't need to go. - I've done everything.
(Okay. I won't choose Se Chan.)
- Why? - Gosh. Thank you so much.
Why? Why are you not choosing him?
(Why did he choose Se Chan over me?)
- I even went to Indonesia. - Good.
- Thank you. - You had a hard time.
Thank you. Let's go!
(Did you forget?)
Gosh. So Min also...
True. So Min also went there.
I even went to Indonesia.
- Why are you doing this? - Why are you kneeling?
Why are you kneeling?
Her knees are lighter than the feathers.
She kneels all the time.
We went to Indonesia together.
(Do you remember that?)
- Okay. Let's not choose So Min. - I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
(I'm scared of crocodiles.)
- I'm sorry too. - I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
Jae Seok and Seok Jin are just standing still.
Why do we have to lie down on the floor?
- I'm even old. - Haha is just standing still.
- Kwang Soo, I'm sorry. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - He isn't lying down properly.
(He wanted to keep his dignity.)
Okay. Get up, Seok Jin.
- Kwang Soo. - First of all,
So Min went to Indonesia a while ago.
She's not going then.
You survived.
Anyway, Kwang Soo still needs to decide...
the person he wants to take from the rest.
Everyone is a coward except Ji Hyo.
That's right.
I can see that only cowards are left.
- We are cowards except Ji Hyo. - That's right.
On Chuseok...
I had to do my penalty mission on Chuseok.
You already had a penalty last week.
Jae Seok, you can come to this side.
- Oh really? - You can come this side.
(Jae Seok survived.)
Why?
(I hate him.)
(Have a safe trip to Australia.)
(Ripping off)
(He just ripped off Jae Seok's name tag. What's going on?)
Gosh.
(What are you doing?)
(What's going on?)
(Kwang Soo chooses Jae Seok as his partner to Australia.)
I thought he was going to take my name tag.
(Everyone is confused.)
I thought so too.
Didn't you tell me to stand this side?
Yes, to rip off your name tag.
All right. Kwang Soo's partner to Australia is...
Jae Seok.
- You did a great job. - Great.
There are so many twists.
You are awesome.
It's awesome.
Am I really going then?
Cage of Death.
(You...)
(worked...)
(so hard.)
(You can do whatever you want.)
(There will be no penalty. It's time to have fun.)
(Let's do anything we want.)
(This is not how I imagined.)
(This is not a penalty, right?)
(I did everything I wanted.)
(I want it to end.)
(Let's stop. My underwear is wet.)
(Autumn Vacation Race)
(Running Man)