(2017 Running Man's 3rd Global Project)
(Half and Half Tour)
(Rome is the eternal city that has the history of the Roman Empire.)
(Bow River lets the visitors enjoy fly fishing in the Rocky Mountains.)
(Antelope Canyon is a sandstone formation created by rain and wind.)
(Alaska is the home of extreme sports and aurora.)
(Bora Bora is Venus' island located in the South Pacific Ocean.)
(Salar de Uyuni is nature's biggest and clearest mirror.)
(Lake Hillier is a romantic lake that is made pink by plankton.)
(Krabi is a fantastic vacation spot where the sky and sea connect.)
(8 recommendations from the members and 8 recommendations from the crew)
(Each week, the members have a match to put their names on the roulette.)
(Jae Seok, the icon of penalties, got Nevis Swing in New Zealand.)
(Today)
What is going on?
(Something strange is happening.)
This isn't easy.
(It's strange,)
(difficult,)
(and frustrating.)
(What kind of air surrounds them?)
It will happen two weeks in a row.
(Chapter 1: It's Always Peaceful in the Beginning)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
(It's a summer day that feels like something good will happen.)
Hello. Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Where is he?
What is this?
- I had forgotten about it. - This is the roulette.
- Hello. - Nevis Swing.
Hello.
For goodness' sake.
Kwang Soo, please clap the slate.
I will clap the slate.
- One... - What is up with your hair?
1, 2, 3.
(He has a tail.)
He thinks he is European.
It's not a hairstyle you should show on TV.
He reminds me of a dog.
That's right.
- Don't say I remind you of a dog. - An old English sheepdog.
Why did you tie the back of your hair?
So Min, you tied my hair and said that it's pretty.
Doesn't it look pretty?
(Why are you laughing?)
If you are trying to be funny, twin tails are better.
I wasn't trying to be funny.
You said that it looks okay.
He is trying very hard to be funny.
You are already funny.
For goodness' sake. They are saying all kinds of things.
It looks funnier in the distance.
Running Man's 3rd Global Project, Half and Half Tour.
(Half and Half Tour continues.)
(8 recommendations from the members and 8 recommendations from the crew)
(Jae Seok is the first one on the roulette with Nevis Swing.)
Nevis Swing is too much.
It will be impossible to go on it.
(I feel bad for Jae Seok.)
(It's a swing with a height of 160m and the speed of 125km.)
(Nevis Swing in New Zealand offers a horrifying freefall.)
Jae Seok put his name on the roulette.
Is it possible for him to put his name on it again?
- That's right. - Yes, it is.
He can fill the four slots with his name.
I think this is a Yu Jae Seok Special.
Yu Jae Seok Special.
Does that mean I won't be in Korea for a while?
- Will I be staying abroad? - It's about time you retire.
- You can do it. - This is driving me crazy.
Before the race,
we will pick the second recommendation.
- That's right. - Let's pick a vacation spot.
That's right. After we pick it, we need to work hard...
and beat the production crew.
(8 recommendations for a vacation that is beautiful and peaceful)
(If they want to go to these places, they must beat the production crew.)
Let's go to Bora Bora.
The place I chose in Canada is nice.
There is a direct flight.
The weather will be amazing in Alaska these days.
To be honest, I do want to go to Salar de Uyuni.
- It's too far. - It takes 30 hours to go there.
It will take forever to go to Bolivia.
You must be out of your mind to recommend a place like that.
- It will take 40 hours to go there. - You're right.
You'll probably never go there unless it's work related.
Exactly. He's right.
(Everything Jong Kook says is an answer to Se Chan.)
You...
- You're forever on his team. - He's my brother.
You should put it correctly.
Se Chan has almost become Jong Kook's lackey.
Right, I'm his lackey.
- You're completely his person now. - Yes.
He knows how to do variety shows.
(Jong Kook's old lackey is upset.)
Who will pick a ball?
- Let's play rock-scissors-paper. - All right.
- The winner will pick a ball. - Okay.
- Both of them? - Then...
The winner will pick a ball for each box.
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
- It was done just now. - No.
- Rock-scissors-paper - This will never end.
(They can't seem to find the winner.)
- It was done just now. - No.
(They'll have to play it all day at this rate.)
How about we play rock-paper instead of rock-scissors-paper?
- What? - That's a good idea.
(How about this?)
That means you lose for certain if you throw rock.
(That means you lose for certain if you throw rock.)
Is he a drunkard or what?
- Is he insane? - What was that?
What's wrong with him?
"Let's throw rock or paper only."
(Drunk)
I said it myself, but it doesn't make sense at all.
Wait a minute. Didn't someone say...
it was a good idea just now? Wasn't it you?
- It was Jae Seok. - Right.
He did say it was a good idea.
- It was Jae Seok. - I thought it was at first.
- He did say it was a good idea. - How about this then?
How about we flip our hands?
- The majority will survive. - Okay.
- Let's flip our hands - Let's flip our hands
- The majority... - This one's the majority.
- Only us two didn't flip our hands. - Goodness.
- Let's flip our hands - Let's flip our hands
(Kwang Soo gets excluded.)
- Let's flip our hands - Okay.
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
(Ji Hyo and Jae Seok win among the last 4.)
Jae Seok shouldn't win.
(It can't be Jae Seok.)
- If you win... - No!
- Make sure you lose. - It's "Let's get it," if I win.
- No way. - "Let's get it."
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
- Thank goodness. - Thank goodness.
Luck is still on our side.
I should be the one to pick the destinations.
(Which destinations will the lucky Ji Hyo pick?)
How can she win this again?
(She'll pick a tourist spot.)
Let it be Alaska.
- Ji Hyo. - I hope it's Thailand.
(They'll be happy with anywhere.)
I hope it's Thailand or Canada.
- Canada is good. - Ji Hyo, pick Canada.
Let's go to Bora Bora.
Pick Rome.
- Let's go to Rome. - It's too far away.
(They want different places, but their goal is the same.)
Canada.
(Their goal is to win the staff and add their destination on the list.)
- What is it? - It's Bora Bora.
(Ji Hyo picks Haha's recommendation, Bora Bora.)
- It's Bora Bora. - Yes!
- Good job. - Goodness.
- She's... - Did you know?
(Bora Bora is...)
- It's great. - I really want to go there.
I want to go there.
- She should pick from the start. - I really want to go.
- She should pick from the start. - This...
- Let's not hope for good. - It's all horrible.
- Any place will be horrible. - To be honest...
Last week's destination was the worst.
I know. It's the worst.
(They already have Nevis Swing on the list.)
I hope it's a nice country.
Somewhere close from here.
(All the destinations recommended by the staff are like fire pits.)
(What will she choose for today's destination candidate?)
- What is that? - "Cage of Death".
- "Cage of Death". - It's the crocodile one.
(She picks Cage of Death in Australia.)
(A private date with a killer crocodile)
(Cage of Death makes you face extreme fear.)
Isn't this the most dangerous one?
- We'll go in a glass tube. - Glass tube?
As a result,
today's destination candidates have become...
Bora Bora, recommended by the Running Man members,
and Cage of Death, recommended by the staff.
It's the second part of Half and Half Project.
Today's race is called Race of Wits.
(Half and Half Project Part 2: Race of Wits)
Throughout today's race, you'll have to clear some missions...
- in which you use your wits. - Okay.
(They'll have to use their wits to clear the missions.)
We lost.
You'll win the race if you clear all the missions before 4pm.
If you can't, the staff will win.
The second destination will be selected according to the result.
Gosh. Let's win the race today.
(They're determined to add their places on the list.)
Okay.
Let's win.
(Which destination will be added to the roulette?)
Before we start the race,
- let me introduce a special guest. - Who is it?
(Is someone joining them for today's race?)
She's the princess of the wit castle.
- Please come out. - Really?
(Who will be helping these slow-witted members?)
- Is it a woman? - Really?
(She's here as the witty princess.)
Gosh, it's Soyou.
- Hi! - Hi, Soyou.
Soyou's here.
- Hello. - My goodness.
- Come to the middle. - Gosh.
Hello.
- Soyou. - Long time no see.
(She's here to send them on a sweet trip.)
She's going to play the missions with us today?
Soyou will be helping us in hosting the race...
and doing the missions with you today.
I see.
(She'll help the members win the race.)
She's recently started her career as a solo artist after Sistar.
- She'll do just as great. - Right.
Of course, she will do great,
but she'll be reminded of old times too.
He's working with his Turbo members again.
I was independent for a while,
- and now... - It's now three members.
Yes, I have sandbags attached to both of my legs.
(He has sandbags attached to his legs.)
What do you mean, sandbags?
(The two members are burdensome at times.)
Which one is heavier?
They're both heavy.
One of them causes too much trouble.
We'll move to the mission place to start with the race.
Okay.
(They'll begin the race now.)
(They enter the mission house with Soyou.)
- Soyou. - How have you been?
- Great. - Hello.
(What mission is waiting for the members?)
- What? - It's a pension.
- Goodness. - My gosh.
(There are many snacks.)
- They prepared some snacks too. - What is all that?
Can we have them freely?
It's party time.
There's ramyeon too.
- What? Gosh, I want ramyeon. - There's cake.
Do we have to collect money to get them again?
Isn't that hopscotch?
- Soyou is hosting the race. - Great.
- Soyou is the host. - Nice.
- Soyou. - MC Soyou.
- What a healthy host. - She's the host.
From now on, Soyou will be hosting the race.
You'll do various missions such as guessing all different answers.
The race will end as soon as you clear at least one of them.
You will win the race if you clear the mission before 4pm.
The staff will win if you can't.
- Let's go to Bora Bora. - Is it nice?
- Let's clear it right away. - Let's go.
- Bora Bora is such a nice place. - Let's take this chance.
We'll begin the mission.
Every one of you needs to clear the mission this time.
The mission is Pilates.
(Pilates)
I've brought a massage ball.
I'll massage your stiff muscles.
That sounds great.
- Jae Seok has a lot of them. - Right.
But the thing is that all of you must not make any sound...
for 10 seconds if you want to clear this mission.
(All of them must not make a sound.)
(They must endure Soyou's painful massage.)
(So they're telling us to fail.)
This isn't going to happen.
It's impossible.
It may be painful, but it may feel good.
Se Chan. Go first.
He's pretty stocky.
He is. Look here.
(You can count on me.)
By the way, Jong Kook.
You're recommending Se Chan for everything.
(Did you guys truly form a team?)
(Feeling guilty)
I am? I mean...
I'm feeling upset now. Why are you being like that all of a sudden?
- I mean... - Isn't that too much?
I'm sorry, but he only does the cutest things.
(He's such a loyal boy.)
(Feeling upset)
- You're good at enduring pain. - Right, Ji Hyo is.
- Right. - She can put up with it.
- Try it. - This will feel good.
This will feel good. I'll go easy in the beginning.
- I'll go easy. - Then I'll do it.
- Then I'll do it. - I'll do it.
(Everyone suddenly volunteers.)
I'll do it.
No, I'll do it.
- No. - No, I'll do it.
What are you doing?
Stop.
(Pressing hard)
Not there.
(He massages Kwang Soo's bottom.)
Goodness.
(While everyone's busy applying for the class)
Maybe I should cook some ramyeon.
(So Min heads to the kitchen as well.)
Let's eat something.
(Wait a minute. He never eats ramyeon to stay healthy.)
Let Haha do it.
What are you doing?
(He glances at the others.)
Can we have ramyeon?
- Do as you please. - Can we?
Let go. Goodness.
So you're doing it, right?
(So Min suspiciously hovers around the kitchen.)
- Hey, So Min. - What?
What are you doing? Come here.
What are you doing? Come over here.
(The members frequent the kitchen.)
I'm sorry, but I'm getting a massage now.
- I mean... Guys. - Goodness.
I'm trying this out now.
- Let's all focus. - Come here.
This isn't right.
Come quick.
(She's preparing to cook ramyeon.)
Haha.
Even if it feels good, don't make any sound.
Goodness.
It's 10 seconds. Tell me when you want to begin.
It's the beginner's stage.
- Your hands. - My neck hurts.
Move up a little.
A little more. Good.
I'll go now.
Start.
Come here.
(Soyou's gentle massage calls for a bright smile.)
How hard will it get later?
(What do you think? Doesn't it feel good?)
Endure a little more.
(He'll succeed if he endures 3 more seconds.)
- Doesn't it feel good? - Endure!
- He succeeds. - Great.
(Haha succeeds.)
(Pinching)
He just pinched me.
It's a misunderstanding.
- That was a misunderstanding. - You endured it well.
- Haha. - Haha pinched me.
- Haha. - Hey, you should get it too.
Don't you feel better though?
- Haha. - My body feels better now.
It feels better after the massage.
So Min!
- I just wanted to drink water. - What are you doing? Come here.
- I just wanted some water. - We're working. What are you doing?
- I should wash my hands. - I got the massage.
(Haha gets into the kitchen after his challenge.)
Hey, we should focus on filming. The same goes for you too, Haha.
I finished my challenge.
- Even so, you should stay. - Come here already.
- What on earth are you doing? - I'm starving.
- Don't eat ramyeon. - This is...
Soyou came to help us out today. You shouldn't be rude.
Who's next?
- What do we have to do? - Which part will you massage?
- Which part is it? - What's the area?
- The one who can endure should try. - Should I massage the bottom?
- Goodness, the bottom? - The bottom?
Then should I give this a try?
(I have the best bottom.)
- No, your bottom is saggy. - Your bottom is flat.
- You can't. It's so flat. - Your bottom isn't good enough.
- What are you talking about? - Do you not have a bottom?
(Soyou is feeling disappointed.)
- No, it's a misunderstanding. - They are so bony.
Fine. I do admit that a long time ago, my bottom was a bit flat,
but not now.
(What is he talking about? For 33 years, his bottom has been flat.)
It took me a while for me to find his bottom and pinch it.
- You didn't pinch my bottom. - What kind of...
(It happened a few minutes ago.)
- I couldn't pinch anything. - That wasn't my bottom.
(Only the universe knows the truth.)
- Let's hurry. Who wants to go? - This isn't right.
- Ji Hyo, do you want to try? - So Min, what are you doing?
(So Min heads to the microwave with ramyeon.)
- You can't cook it like that. - Is it good? Have you tried this?
- Aren't we going to play this? - You can't cook it like that.
Hear me out. So Min put the raw ramyeon inside the microwave.
- What are you doing? - Will that even work?
- Seok Jin, that's how you cook it. - Let's eat ramyeon later together.
What was So Min thinking? Goodness.
- Cook it now. Get rid of it though. - Let's eat it later all together.
(What is the reason for their obsession over ramyeon today?)
Ji Hyo, this isn't easy.
(Ji Hyo, this isn't easy.)
Why do you keep eating today?
(They're acting suspiciously, but So Min is being even more suspicious.)
(Chapter 2: Seok Jin and 7 Missions)
(The start of everything)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hi, Jae Seok. - Seok Jin isn't here now.
- Hello. - I don't think he's here.
He's not here yet.
- Seok Jin isn't here right now. - We know.
This is Seok Jin's special then.
(Seok Jin is the only one who's not present. Does that imply...)
Soon, there will be various types of missions for you to accomplish.
Each mission will require different numbers of members to succeed them.
All of us are bad at reading situations.
Seok Jin is the worst at it, but luckily, he's not here right now.
- We do have some hope. - That's right.
- This race will continue until 4pm. - Really?
If you accomplish even one of those missions, it will be your win.
(If they accomplish a mission, they'll win and the race will end.)
- It will end right away? - Really?
If you don't accomplish any mission, we will win the race.
Depending on the result, the destination will be chosen.
Like last week, the member with the most mission money can buy...
- the name tags for the roulette. - This is the fun part of the game.
You're right. We can't forget about the money.
This is fun.
Your hidden mission will be a way to acquire the mission money.
The mission is Deceive Seok Jin who is usually clueless of situations.
(The mission for them to obtain the money is Deceive Seok Jin.)
- This is an easy mission. - Really?
- This can't count as a mission. - How can we fail at that?
Please bring the board in.
What is that?
(It won't be as easy as you think. What will the hidden missions be?)
(There are 7 slots! There are 7 stages of hidden missions.)
(Empty pot, laundry, peeled onions, Seok Jin's belongings,)
(pace counter, screaming, and the last food)
We have to do all these missions?
- This one is challenging. - This one will be difficult.
- "Don't make him say he wants it." - That one looks hard.
He will definitely want to have some of the ramyeon.
That's almost a given.
He likes to interfere in our businesses.
He always asks what we're doing.
But when he's doing something,
- he won't show any interest. - That's true too.
Let me explain you the mission. This will be an individual match.
Before the group mission ends, you have to accomplish...
seven hidden missions in this order.
- In order? - Really?
You could choose the order after discussing it among yourselves.
Note that you must finish missions placed later in the order more.
Please think about this carefully, and come up with your order.
Everyone can participate in accomplishing these missions.
But only the first member who brings items that proves you succeeded...
the missions will be considered as the winner.
We have to prove with the items.
The winner will receive 20 dollars.
After this, you will move onto the next mission.
But if you all fail, we'll multiply 10 dollars and the number for the...
stage of the mission, and Seok Jin will receive that much money.
(Seok Jin will get 10 dollars times the stage number for the mission.)
- We have no choice but to place... - We'll only do that once?
We should only do it once or twice. We can't eat more than that.
- That's better. - I agree.
Should we put this in the fourth stage?
There are four types of food.
(It's better to put hard missions in the 1st stage and easy ones in 7th.)
(Cook and eat ramyeon without Seok Jin asking for some of the ramyeon.)
(Do the laundry without him asking if they're doing the laundry.)
(Steal 3 of Seok Jin's belongings without getting caught.)
(Feed him 4 kinds of food without him saying he doesn't want to eat.)
(Peel 5 onions, and Seok Jin cannot say, "onion" during that time.)
(Scream 6 times for 3 seconds, and he can't comment that they're loud.)
(Do 7,000 counts, and he cannot tell them to stay still.)
This isn't easy.
This is so hard.
If I can't win the mission with ramyeon, it will be tough for me.
- Everyone will go for that mission. - Exactly.
Should I eat ramyeon today?
(They all aim for the first mission.)
(The members have gotten around to their plan right away.)
(Jong Kook heads to the kitchen while there's chaos.)
(So Min follows Jong Kook to the kitchen.)
(There was a reason why everyone was obsessed with ramyeon today.)
(Everyone tried to cook it since the 1st stage mission was easy.)
(Goodness, they sure love ramyeon, don't they?)
Give it a try.
- Come. - Take a seat.
Show her that you have a strong hip joint.
- This is the place, right? - It is.
- Lie down like this. - Lie on your stomach.
- Lie on your stomach. - I have to hold it for 10 seconds.
- Show your strong hip joint. - Se Chan, I'll step on you lightly.
- But Soyou. - Yes?
You have a proper license for this, right?
(Se Chan has the right to know.)
- I'll step on you just slightly. - Why did you ask her that?
How could you ask her that?
I'll start.
(Can Se Chan hold out for 10 seconds?)
(Making a small sound)
He failed.
- What? - What happened?
- He didn't say anything. - Se Chan screamed.
- When? - No, he didn't.
- Did you scream? - I didn't.
This is what I did.
You can't count that.
Since he failed, you lost your chance. You failed the first round.
(Because of Se Chan, they failed the 1st round.)
- Why? - That's not right.
- What happened? - Why?
- This is what I did, Jong Kook. - Did you scream?
That can't count as making a sound.
Jong Kook, why are you protecting him. You should scold him.
(That's not like you, Jong Kook.)
- I'm sorry. I just closed my mouth. - Jong Kook.
- What's gotten into you? - I just closed my mouth.
- Good job. - What are you talking about?
- You had no other choice. - That's right.
Jae Seok, So Min is looking for something.
- This is what I did. - That's what you did?
Soyou, shouldn't Jae Seok get the massage too?
That's right. He didn't get it yet.
- Kwang Soo should get it first. - Jae Seok, try it first.
- This is the right one, isn't it? - It's bigger.
(Meanwhile, quietly in the kitchen,)
(he finishes cooking ramyeon.)
Jae Seok, that's mine. Come on. I cooked that ramyeon.
You're done cooking ramyeon?
(You're done cooking ramyeon?)
You cooked it with the microwave?
(He flees to the staircase to get rid of it.)
- It really worked? - Where's Jae Seok? He's eating.
(Whoever finishes the mission first can receive the mission money.)
(He eats it with the tongs.)
Hey, Jae Seok!
He left already.
Where is he? Hey, Jae Seok!
(Where is he? Hey, Jae Seok!)
How could you eat it by yourself?
(How could you eat it by yourself?)
You cooked this in the microwave? You could do it?
(Why is he here now?)
"Don't make him say he wants some."
(He has to eat it while Seok Jin doesn't ask for a mouthful.)
(This mission with ramyeon might be easier than they thought.)
(They've known him for 7 years, and considering the way he talks...)
He doesn't say, "a mouthful" often.
(Can Jae Seok avoid hearing "a mouthful" from Seok Jin?)
Hey, is it done?
(Getting close)
Let me eat a mouthful of it.
(Let me eat a mouthful of it.)
(You want to have a mouthful?)
(Jae Seok fails the 1st stage mission.)
(Why did you have to say the word "a mouthful" today?)
Goodness.
- Jae Seok. - Did he eat your ramyeon?
I couldn't eat it. He's not going to share.
Why did he ask for a mouthful?
Goodness, why did you have to eat the ramyeon?
(Then does it mean that this mission is over?)
We should've eaten it together.
(With Jae Seok's failure, no one gets to acquire the mission money.)
But you know that I didn't step on you hard, don't you?
What happened?
(He's clueless. Eating someone else's ramyeon is tastier.)
(Eating ramyeon without Seok Jin saying, "a mouthful" is over.)
(Do laundry for 20 minutes, and he can't say, "Are you doing laundry?")
I guess cooking in the microwave works.
(Changing)
(Since Jae Seok failed the mission, the producer signals a new number.)
(Do laundry for 20 minutes, and he can't say, "Are you doing laundry?")
Laundry machine...
- What are you doing? - Hey!
(She finds the laundry machine in the bathroom.)
(Following her in)
Don't come.
Hey, be civil. Let me run the machine just once.
- Hey, I can't fight with you. - Let me run it just once.
- Please, Se Chan. Let me have it. - I'll put my socks.
- Wait. - Hold on.
Let's play rock-scissors-paper.
- Rock-scissors... - Which one will you play?
- I'll play rock. - You'll play rock?
- Yes. - Keep your word.
Play paper.
- I'll play paper. You play rock. - Okay.
- Understood? - Yes.
Rock-scissors-paper.
(Se Chan wins, and So Min loses. They were contrary to their words.)
(I'm so furious, you little con artist.)
He's mean.
(Se Chan manages to take the laundry machine from So Min.)
- How do I start the machine? - Gosh, it's hot.
I guess this is it.
It's so hot in here.
(Scoffing)
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
(Jong Kook adds his laundry to Se Chan's.)
(Ji Hyo adds hers too.)
(Everyone puts in laundry.)
(They have to wait 20 minutes.)
We failed the first step because of Se Chan, right?
Jong Kook said it was okay.
(Shameless)
- He said it was okay. - Se Chan was just practicing.
Kwang Soo had to succeed.
- But he failed. - But he failed.
(Kwang Soo was the third person to try the pilates class.)
Hey.
(Kwang Soo failed right away.)
(All the blame is put on Kwang Soo.)
It was Kwang Soo's fault.
Jae Seok was given a chance too.
Are you listening to me?
He was given a chance too.
But he made a sound.
Kwang Soo.
(Kiss)
Kwang Soo. I get it.
(I feel jealous of Se Chan.)
This mission has to be fulfilled by everyone.
Balance the Ball.
(Balance the Ball)
- Balance the Ball? - Balance the Ball?
You will run nuts down a straw with one hand.
While doing so, you have to make sure...
the ping-pong ball doesn't fall from the top of the straw.
- That sounds hard. - I can't do that.
Each person has one chance.
You'll be given some time to practice.
- We can practice? That's good. - Yes.
Can you demonstrate?
You put the ping-pong ball on the nuts.
- You have one chance? - Is it possible?
- Is it possible? - You run them down.
(Trembling)
Your hands are trembling.
- I'm nervous. - You are?
- Soyou, do you drink a lot? - Do you drink a lot?
Are you sure it's because you're nervous?
It's so hot.
- Like this. - It's impossible.
- I succeeded. - I succeeded.
Like this.
It's possible.
- Is this a success? - Yes.
- You can use your hand? - Yes.
(Everyone is busy practicing.)
You have to move all three nuts at once.
(Jong Kook is checking on the laundry.)
We have to take out the laundry.
(Let's see.)
(It's not done yet.)
We've put in the laundry.
You hold all three nuts...
- at once. - I have to use the bathroom.
Hey.
- At once. - I have to use the bathroom.
(Seok Jin enters the bathroom where the washing machine is.)
(Their secret mission might get revealed.)
I have to pee.
- There are cameras. - Cameras...
What are you going to do?
I have to use the bathroom.
I have to pee.
What should he do?
(I don't think it's a good idea.)
I have to pee. Can you go out for a minute?
There's another camera. I didn't see it before.
Come out.
There are cameras.
- There are cameras everywhere. - Why are there cameras?
(Seok Jin finds the cameras only now.)
(There are cameras even in the bathroom?)
(Glancing)
Seok Jin is in the bathroom.
(What is going to happen?)
(Has he noticed the washing machine mission?)
(Looking away)
(Has he noticed?)
(The moment Seok Jin says, "Are you doing the laundry?)
(the mission fails.)
It's so hot in here.
(He is not interested in the washing machine.)
- Okay. - Excuse me.
- Your members... - Members?
Don't say that.
- Is this your gang's workshop? - It's not like that.
- Use just one hand. - Just one hand?
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
Give up if you don't know how to do it.
Kwang Soo, let me try.
Se Chan, you try.
- Good. - Sorry.
Se Chan is good at these things.
Get out of his way.
- What happened to you? - Get out.
Move.
(Kicking)
Why are you doing this to me?
Why?
(Jong Kook is mine.)
Let's try one by one. Let's start from Jae Seok.
- All right. - Sit down. Be serious.
(Jong Kook is like a drill instructor.)
Sit down.
- Listen to him. - Come on.
I've been practicing standing up.
- Sit down. - You better sit down.
If you stand up...
- The ball might fall. - Exactly.
My goodness.
What are you?
- Are you his secretary? - I'm assisting him.
It looks very stable. Good.
- Focus. - You have to succeed.
- This is my only chance, right? - You have to.
- Let me go first. - Let's start from someone else.
We should begin...
Why don't we start from Haha?
Let's decide who will go first.
- You go first. - I'll go first.
- I'll do it at the end. - That sounds good.
- Ji Hyo will succeed. - Look at that.
She's succeeded. Amazing.
(Smooth)
(Her movement looks so stable.)
Unbelievable.
(Shaking)
(Will she successfully put the nuts down on the table?)
Done.
(Done)
I'm done.
(Ji Hyo has succeeded.)
Haha, if you fail,
I'll hit you.
You know Jong Kook has my back.
(What do you mean?)
Hold on. He talked to me.
(Distracted)
Don't talk to him.
Excuse me. Please keep quiet.
(Please keep quiet.)
- Quiet. - My goodness.
There were eight eyes glaring at me.
(Hurt)
You, you, you, and you. Why were you glaring at me?
(Why were you glaring at me?)
- What? - Why were you glaring?
- I just wanted to. - Gosh, I can't believe this.
(I'm so hurt.)
I'll try later.
(Nervous)
- All right. - You try first.
I've been practicing, but it's not so easy.
(It's not so easy.)
Why don't you let someone else try then?
(Jae Seok annoys Jong Kook.)
Be polite to each other.
(Be polite to each other.)
(How dare you speak that way to our boss?)
- All right. - Good job.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
(According to the ranking, Jong Kook goes first.)
It looks good. Just continue.
Just keep going.
(He just has to run the nuts down now.)
(Falling)
No.
Remove your tapes.
(Jong Kook should never fail.)
Why did you fail?
My elbow got in the way.
Don't work out too much.
It's your lats' fault.
(It's because you're so bulky.)
- Your lats got in the way. - Come with me.
(Come with me.)
Good that there are cameras.
There are cameras.
Come with me.
Good that there are cameras.
There are cameras.
(Cameras saved my life.)
- Why are there cameras everywhere? - There are cameras in the room.
Thank you.
Guys, we've been giving you many chances so far.
It's already been 20 minutes.
(A staff member sends a signal.)
(Does he mean the laundry mission is completed?)
It's already been 20 minutes.
- I don't think we should continue. - Gosh.
(Swarming)
- Where are they going? - Where are they going?
(Clueless)
(Let me get my laundry back.)
(Seok Jin hasn't said, "Are you doing the laundry?")
(They have to take their laundry to the staff now.)
(They have to compete to arrive first.)
Gosh.
(It's peaceful on the first floor.)
(Jong Kook is busy upstairs.)
(Without Seok Jin noticing anything,)
(Jong Kook arrives at the center.)
Here's my laundry.
It's been 20 minutes.
Darn it. I'm late.
- Jong Kook, you've succeeded. - Yes.
(Jong Kook fulfills the 2nd step.)
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
That was close.
(Jong Kook completes the laundry mission.)
(Stealing 3 of Seok Jin's items)
Are you ready?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Soyou, please read. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo hurries to the shoes as soon as the mission starts.)
(Where are Seok Jin's shoes?)
Where are you going?
- What? - Where are you going?
I wanted to close the door.
Let's go.
Can we really do this?
- Oh, I'm sorry. - What is this?
(Spilling)
- I'm sorry. - What's with you?
I'm sorry.
- It's okay. - I'm sorry.
(Give me your wet socks.)
(What is she doing?)
(I'll try again.)
(Kwang Soo goes back to the shoes.)
- I'm really okay. - I'm sorry.
(Kwang Soo steals Seok Jin's shoes.)
Why are you doing this to me?
You have a bruise on your foot.
I don't have a bruise.
(She touches his sock.)
(You're so careless.)
You poured coffee on me. It's not even water.
How will you get married when you're so careless?
(You're careless too.)
Let's start, Soyou.
This mission is called Make a Sentence.
If you make a reasonable sentence with 5 words in 5 seconds...
in the given order, you clear the mission.
(Make a sentence with 5 words in the given order.)
Okay.
All right. Everyone must...
- clear this mission. - Shall we switch glasses?
(Suddenly)
- I don't look good in them. - Let's switch.
- Come on. - It's Make a Sentence.
I don't look good...
- Each person... - with your glasses.
- Let's switch glasses. - It's Make a Sentence.
I don't look good with your glasses.
(In the back, someone steals from his bag.)
With five words that are given to you...
(He fishes his bag.)
(Kwang Soo steals Seok Jin's phone.)
Make a sentence with 5 given words within 5 seconds.
(Did I feel something?)
I know this game.
(His back pockets are full.)
Shall we start with Jae Seok?
I'll start.
(He takes a peek.)
- Give me the words. - Okay.
- Let's start. - All right.
- I can do a good job. - I know.
(Kwang Soo secretly climbs upstairs.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Here are Seok Jin's phone and shoes.
I brought a pair.
(Kwang Soo brings Seok Jin's phone and his shoes.)
The shoes will be counted as one.
(What did he say?)
That's it.
(Is this how you'll play?)
I also stole the phone case.
(How about this?)
I stole his phone and phone case.
As the phone is inside the case,
they'll be counted as one.
I'll take the phone apart.
No, you brought two items. Please go back.
(He doesn't meet the criteria.)
- Five seconds? - That's right.
- That sounds good. - Count accurately.
Get ready, set, go.
I went to the bathroom for a shoot, and they flogged me.
While I ate some boogers...
(While I ate some boogers...)
- Why would you eat boogers? - Why?
- You were good at this game. - That's not why.
I wasn't mentally prepared.
- Get yourself prepared. - I'm not ready yet.
- Let me try again, Soyou. - Who's next?
You got eliminated. You don't get another chance.
(Someone has to steal one more item from Seok Jin.)
- Give me another chance. - Try it, Seok Jin.
(He stands up.)
- Okay. - What's going on?
What?
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
You should take off your bag.
- It won't be easy. - By the way...
May I try on your glasses?
(He whispers.)
My glasses? Why?
I want to change mine.
- Let's play. - How do I look?
- Shall I try it? - Yours are better.
Do I look good? Let me take a look...
- in the mirror. - I'll play.
May I try them on?
There are no lens in the glasses.
What's wrong with him?
Jae Seok.
- Bring them back. - I look good in them.
They look fine but...
- All right. - Everyone.
Let's play.
- My goodness. - How many sentences...
- Hey. - do we have to make?
Give me your glasses.
Give them back.
Hey, Jae Seok?
(Jae Seok disappeared.)
- Where did he go? - Challenge.
Where did he go?
- Where's Jae Seok? - Have you lost your mind?
Jae Seok disappeared.
- What? - How?
He disappeared.
Why are you calling him?
(He pretends to look at himself in the bathroom mirror.)
(He climbs upstairs as fast as possible.)
Give me your glasses.
(Where's the base?)
Where is it?
- Where is it? - Half of you must succeed.
Half of us?
Okay.
(He enters with pride.)
- Did you bring Seok Jin's item? - Yes.
Kwang Soo succeeded already.
(When did Kwang Soo do it?)
(While Haha was playing the team mission...)
My mother-in-law heard my fart.
(He made an attempt.)
(He pretended to fix his microphone...)
(and successfully stole the microphone cover.)
This is Seok Jin's microphone cover.
- It's acceptable. - Okay.
Thank you.
(Kwang Soo cleared the 3rd mission.)
Let's focus, everyone.
(The producer gives a signal.)
(The fourth mission is...)
(giving food to Seok Jin 4 times without his refusal.)
(He gets up.)
Give us the next hint.
The four who clear the mission should eat delicious food.
(He makes a suggestion in order to give food to Seok Jin.)
- That sounds good. - Okay.
- Okay. - Let's do it.
(He doesn't care.)
- That's good. - Whose turn is it?
It's Jong Kook's turn.
(Everyone is busy deciding the order.)
- It's my turn. - Okay.
Seok Jin...
(There's one difficulty to the fourth hidden mission.)
(Seok Jin has a particular taste in food.)
(It'll be difficult to make Seok Jin eat without refusing.)
(Will they make Seok Jin eat without his refusal?)
- Try it again. - Let's play.
I cleared the mission.
- Get ready. - One.
- Seok Jin. - It's your turn.
(Where are you going?)
- Get ready. - Get ready.
(He takes a bite from an apple.)
(For Seok Jin with a particular taste,)
(Haha offers an apple.)
- Get ready. - Get ready.
(It's a good start.)
(Haha is happy.)
(They have 3 food items to go.)
(That was smart of you, Haha.)
Who else cleared the mission?
(It's Jong Kook's turn to play Make a Sentence.)
Get ready, set, go.
(Wait a minute.)
(Is that Soo Ae?)
(A year ago, she approached him like the sunshine.)
(There was a man next to her.)
(What do you think of me?)
(He recalls...)
(the unforgettable memories he had with her.)
When I saw Soo Ae farting...
(Soo Ae was farting?)
I was so surprised and said...
(He makes up something.)
"It's better to fart in shorts."
- Then I could smell her feet. - That's rude.
That's a horrible thing to say.
I'm sorry, Soo Ae.
- How could you? - I didn't mean it.
(He feels guilty.)
- Kwang Soo. - I'll do it.
It's your turn.
- Get ready. - Good luck.
- I can do it. - In 1, 2, 3.
My first kiss was with Jae Seok while watching...
a horror film.
(Was his first kiss with Jae Seok?)
- Our date was at a dump. - What did you say?
- What did you say? - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Was that his first kiss?
Did you kiss Jae Seok? Have you lost your mind?
- Did you kiss him? - Get out.
Can't you make better sentences?
- Look. - I'm sorry.
(Haha prepares for the hidden mission.)
Did Kwang Soo succeed?
(He prepares a cake, Seok Jin's favorite.)
Am I the only one who succeeded?
Let's give it a try.
- Have you played, So Min? - No.
May I have a bite, Haha?
Here you go.
(There's food everywhere.)
Get ready.
(Give me one bite, Haha.)
(She gets to taste some cake.)
It's so delicious.
Seok Jin, it's very delicious.
(She offers some to Seok Jin.)
(He should be running low on sugar.)
(This cake is for you, Seok Jin.)
He'll refuse to eat right away.
(Will Seok Jin eat the second food item?)
- I'll try one more time. - How many times?
- I'll try. - You've done too many.
Come on.
(Come here.)
Try some.
(The second food item is in front of him.)
(If he refuses to eat, they fail the mission.)
(That's right.)
Get ready.
(He takes a bite of the cake.)
(It's so delicious.)
- Goodness. - My goodness.
(2 more food items to go)
(Haha plans to give him the third food item.)
(It's a chocolate cracker.)
Why do you keep eating?
Why do you all keep eating?
(For Seok Jin,)
(Haha prepares more sweets.)
(He gives him a chocolate cracker with whipped cream.)
(As expected,)
(Seok Jin eats it.)
It's really good.
(Haha succeeds 3 times.)
(Only one food item is left.)
(Everyone starts getting competitive.)
Hurry up, and play.
(The person to bring the last food item...)
(that Seok Jin eats becomes the winner.)
(They start the competition.)
(Is someone trying to steal my turn?)
(Kwang Soo offers water...)
(to Seok Jin who must be thirsty.)
(Kwang Soo takes his opportunity.)
(If Seok Jin drinks it,)
(Kwang Soo will earn 20 dollars.)
(I don't need water.)
(But Seok Jin didn't explicitly say he didn't want it.)
(I didn't expect him to refuse to drink water.)
(Kwang Soo's strategy fails.)
(I'll bring an end to this game.)
(Haha prepares coffee and chocolate crackers.)
- It tastes so good. - What are you eating?
Try this.
(Seok Jin would definitely want to try.)
(Will Haha's final try succeed?)
I'm okay. I'm on a diet.
(Laughing)
I don't eat a lot of sweets.
(He doesn't want it.)
(The mission fails.)
(Seok Jin doesn't eat a lot as always.)
(Funny)
I want some water.
- I'm so thirsty. - Drink this.
(Haha never gives up.)
- I want cold water. - No, this is better.
That water smells bad.
That water is not cold.
(That was so close.)
(The food mission fails.)
(Now, they have to peel 5 onions without Seok Jin saying, "onions".)
(The onion mission starts.)
- That was close. - Right?
That was close.
I want to try too.
The water is not cold.
(So Min searches for onions.)
I want cold water.
One, two, three.
(I'll have onions ready.)
There's a knife. We can eat apples.
It's so hot.
Where are the tissues?
(Seok Jin goes into the bathroom.)
(So Min goes to the room on the other side with onions.)
(She is in a safe zone now.)
I better hurry. I have to succeed this time.
(Everyone gets ready to peel onions.)
It's so hot.
(Ji Hyo goes upstairs.)
(I'll be here.)
(It might be safer near Seok Jin.)
(Guys, here I come.)
(I almost got caught. I have to hide the onions.)
(If Seok Jin says, "onions", the mission fails.)
Where is everybody again?
Fail. The mission failed. Everybody, come here.
Come here.
- Come here, guys. - Come here.
- I'm getting angry. Come here. - Jong Kook.
(I won't let others succeed.)
Come here.
(Se Chan finds So Min.)
Are we doing something? Gosh.
Hold on.
(Everyone comes back.)
- Let's do that. - We'll have to see crocodiles.
I'm fine with whatever.
- All right. - For now,
- no one has succeeded. - It's hard.
You had some snacks,
- but you must be getting hungry. - What?
You can order some noodles.
Noodles?
Do we have to choose the same dish?
- No. You can choose whatever. - Whatever?
- Why don't we... - I've done this before...
- Where are you going? - Where are you going?
- Where are you going? - I'm going to the bathroom.
No. You have to stay.
- Choose a dish first. - Sit down.
Does he need a diaper?
(He's been to the bathroom so many times.)
(Well said.)
What would you like?
- I'd like... - I'll order a jjamppong.
- Me too. - Me too.
(Everyone is choosing a dish.)
- I'd like fried rice. - I'm not kidding.
(I have to go to the bathroom too.)
My stomach hurts.
Come back.
- So Min. - Come back.
See who orders what.
Come back. Where are you going?
So Min, come back.
- What are you guys doing? - Soyou is here.
- I really have to poop. - Come back.
- You have to poop? - Come back.
- She has to poop. - Come back.
- Can't I even poop? - I'm getting angry.
Respect human rights.
My stomach hurts.
(Se Chan sneaks into the kitchen.)
Why is everyone so distracted?
(Seok Jin notices Se Chan missing. Will the mission fail?)
We should order sweet and sour pork.
(We should order sweet and sour pork.)
We should order it.
I want fried rice.
(That was close.)
(Se Chan makes a brave attempt.)
Try here.
- Jjamppong... - Jjamppong and jajangmyeon?
(It might be safer here.)
Can I order both jjamppong and jajangmyeon?
(Se Chan starts to peel onions.)
I'm craving jjamppong though.
It'll be hard for Soyou to remember.
(Focused)
What are you doing, Se Chan?
(Interrupting)
(Se Chan is unexpectedly interrupted by Jae Seok.)
(Will Seok Jin notice?)
What are you doing, Se Chan?
(Dangerous)
What about you?
(Jong Kook helps Se Chan out.)
(Choose what you want to eat.)
- What about you? - I'll have seafood rice.
- Seafood rice? - Yes.
- You can order anything. - Anything?
- I'll have seafood rice. - I'll have jjamppong.
- Let's do this. - Why are you sitting in one line?
(Jong Kook covers Se Chan.)
- Order anything. - Okay.
Se Chan, you're hiding behind Jong Kook.
- You're holding onto him. - I have his back.
Obviously.
I'll be hiding behind his back.
You're glued to him.
What?
(Sneaking)
What did you say, Ji Hyo?
(Everyone is distracted.)
- So Min. - You can order anything.
(Where are you going, So Min?)
(I have something to do.)
(Will So Min win?)
(Will Se Chan's brave attempt pay off?)
(My eyes are burning.)
- Where is my name tag? - Hey.
- What is this smell? - Where is my name tag?
(Looking around)
(Covering up)
(Jong Kook's back is working hard.)
- I'll have jjamppong rice. - Seok Jin.
Where is So Min?
- So Min! - Just a second. My stomach hurts.
I'm usually good at peeling onions.
Why am I so slow?
Gosh, my eyes.
(Her eyes ache more than her stomach.)
They're burning.
(Who will be the winner?)
Gosh, my eyes.
(She's done peeling 5 onions.)
(She has to take the onions to the staff now.)
(I'm watching you.)
(What are you doing there?)
(She leaves the onions in the corner.)
The thing is...
(Seok Jin looks around the room.)
(What is going on?)
Why are you crying?
What are you doing?
My eyes are...
- Why are you crying? - Why is everyone crying?
(The onions made me cry.)
Why are you crying?
My stomach ached so much.
Did you cry?
Did you poop so much that you cried?
(Poor So Min.)
(Seok Jin doesn't seem to suspect anything.)
(So Min starts once again.)
(She runs upstairs with 5 onions under her shirt.)
- Where are you going? - Just a second.
You should have done it at home.
(I'm almost there.)
My stomach aches so much.
- Here. - Do you have them?
Yes, there are five of them.
- Are there five of them? - Yes, count them.
- There are five, right? - Yes.
But...
(But)
Se Chan was here first.
- When was he here? - Just a moment ago.
(Se Chan completed the mission before So Min.)
Gosh.
(When was he here?)
(Se Chan finished peeling the onions before So Min.)
(He watched Seok Jin from the bathroom.)
Did I drop my phone somewhere?
(While Seok Jin was looking for his phone, Se Chan went upstairs.)
- How many do you have? - Five.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
You've succeeded.
(Se Chan has completed the mission.)
(The screaming mission fails.)
- Seok Jin! - Be quiet.
Is it really okay?
I feel so bad for Soyou.
It's okay.
(A pace counter?)
(Taking 7,000 steps without Seok Jin saying, "Stay still.")
(This is the last chance.)
Why don't we dance?
(Taking 7,000 steps without Seok Jin saying, "Stay still.")
Let's dance.
- We're sorry. - It's okay.
(What will they do?)
Is there a bathroom without any cameras?
- My goodness. - Haha.
Do you have to use the bathroom? Go upstairs.
- Is there a bathroom? - Yes.
- I have to go to the bathroom. - Me too.
It doesn't have any cameras?
- It doesn't have any cameras. - There are no cameras.
(Let's use the bathroom without any cameras.)
- There are no cameras? - Cameras are everywhere.
- You go first. - Okay.
There's just one camera?
(Seok Jin uses the bathroom first.)
I'll cover the camera.
(He covers the camera with a towel.)
(Jae Seok is carrying out the mission.)
(Everyone except Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo has no money.)
Seok Jin, hurry.
Soyou, we're sorry.
We're sorry.
Come back.
Is Soyou aware of it?
You're not aware of anything, are you?
(Do you know what we're doing?)
It's so obvious.
(Seok Jin has no idea.)
- What is with Seok Jin? - We're really sorry.
It's okay.
(The spirits gave him a big nose but no wits.)
- Is there a restroom? - Yes.
You can cover the camera with a towel. Cover it.
(Jae Seok pretends like he has to use the restroom.)
Make sure this doesn't turn off. Can you do it for me?
I can't do it. Let me know once you pass the 7,000 point.
Can you do it for me? You have to keep going. Do it properly.
It's 621 right now.
- I have to reach 7,000. - 7,000?
Yes.
(Is this why he followed Seok Jin to the restroom?)
Let's get rolling. Seok Jin is back.
- The light was off. - No, I covered it with a towel.
(They shake the pace counter discreetly.)
My legs are sore.
The light was off though. Why did they put a camera there?
(So Min tries a new strategy.)
(Pace counter spirits, please help me.)
Jae Seok.
- Come back. - Jae Seok.
What are you doing?
Seok Jin.
7,000?
(They all try to shake it more near the end.)
We'll get started, everybody.
- All right. - Keep doing it.
Why is he taking so long?
Keep doing it, Kwon Ryeol.
Can you do it until I come back?
(He passes it onto Kwon Ryeol and gets back.)
Please get back, everybody.
(He has 2 jobs because of their 7-year friendship.)
Yes.
This mission is called Rock-Scissors-Paper.
I'll play rock-scissors-paper with you in a row.
We'll play rock-scissors-paper,
- and the four of you... - Half and half?
Half of you has to win, and the other half has to lose...
to win the mission.
(Shaking)
(They have to complete 7,000 steps during this game.)
- I've played this before. - Let's do this.
- Let's do this. - Please stand in a line.
- Stand in a line? - Seok Jin can go first.
Please make a line. Seok Jin, go first.
- Okay. I'll go first. - Okay.
I'll go first. Rock-scissors-paper?
(Yes, I'm doing it.)
(But I gave up on filming you.)
(Shaking)
It doesn't matter whether I win or lose.
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
(Seok Jin wins.)
- I won. - He won.
- It's better for me to lose, right? - Right.
It's better to alternate.
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
(Jae Seok loses.)
- I lost. - Good. You have to win.
- You have to win. - I have to win?
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
(So Min versus Soyou)
(So Min wins.)
- It's better to win, right? - You have to lose, Kwang Soo.
- You have to lose. - I got it.
Let's keep alternating.
If we win this mission, it's the end.
It's your turn, Kwang Soo.
(I'll beat you, Soyou.)
- Rock-scissors-paper - What are you going to play?
(Just tell me, Kwang Soo.)
(His heart flutters.)
Please don't do that.
- She's shaking him up. - It'll melt him.
I'm going to play scissors.
Scissors? Scissors?
(It's better for him to lose. Will he show his true feelings?)
- Kwang Soo. - Are you going to lose?
Come on.
(It's a dilemma between love and the game.)
(This is a dilemma between work and friendship.)
(Haha runs to the 2nd floor all of a sudden.)
(Let me check something.)
You can't do that. I did that.
You can't.
(He tries to reset Jae Seok's counter.)
(It's the Running Man spirit to rain on somebody else's parade.)
Hey, come here.
(The two cheaters are fighting.)
Come here.
(Do you want to die?)
I'm going to kill you.
Get back and play rock-scissors-paper.
- I'll go. - Hurry.
Go.
(Go away, you petty thief.)
That was close. He was going to reset it, right?
He almost reset it.
Scissors? Are you going to play scissors?
Rock-scissors-paper
- What? - Nothing.
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
Rock-scissors-paper
(Kwang Soo wins.)
- Okay. - Okay.
Two of you have to win.
- Do we only have 1 loss to go? - 2 more people have to win.
- You have to lose. - Let's go.
Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Do I have to lose? - Let's go!
Do I have to lose?
(He earned 20 dollars already, so he wants to get out of here.)
- Please win! - He has to lose.
- Please lose. - He has to lose?
- Okay. - Rock-scissors-paper
(Jong Kook loses.)
- Oh, dear. - Okay.
- That's good. - Did you lose?
- Did you lose? - It's 3 to 2 now.
- 3 to 2. - Rock-scissors-paper
(Se Chan loses as well.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Seok Jin and those who won the mission are happy.)
We can go out.
- It's 3 to 3. - We have hope.
- This is over. - It's 3 to 3?
I'm so nervous. In 1, 2, 3.
- It doesn't matter what you play. - Rock-scissors-paper
(Ji Hyo wins.)
- I won. - You have to lose now.
You have to lose, Haha.
If you lose, this is over. We can get out.
- Everybody. - You have to lose.
If he loses, the mission is over.
- Okay. - Please.
- What is it? He has to lose, right? - Let's do this.
- If he loses, the mission is over. - It's done, right?
- It'll be finished. - The mission will be over.
- It's done. - Really?
- Hey. - Finish it off.
- Finish it. - Haha.
- Think about this carefully. - Finish it.
- You have to lose. - It'll end.
- Really? - It's not up to me.
(Should I win or lose? That is the question.)
(He has to lose so that everybody gets to go to Bora Bora.)
You have to lose.
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
(If he wins, they get to earn more mission money.)
(Will the Race of Wits favor this mission or the hidden one?)
(He loses.)
The mission is over.
(I get no more mission money.)
It's done.
- Is it? - It is.
(The Race of Wits is now over.)
Do we get to go? Is this over?
Thank me.
Is this over? Do we get to go?
We do.
This is the second part of Half and Half Tour.
You have won the group mission that was the deciding factor...
for a trip destination for the tour.
- Okay. - Running Man wins.
(Running Man wins the race.)
On the roulette, we'll add Bora Bora...
as one of the possible final destinations.
- Yes. - Yes.
- Let's have a seat. - Let's sit. Oh, dear.
The mission is now over.
Let's calculate the mission money...
you have earned during the missions.
Mission money?
(There was mission money?)
Jong Kook, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan...
passed the mission, so you each earn 20 dollars.
(They earn 20 dollars for deceiving Seok Jin.)
(What did they win?)
We're a team.
- We're your team. - The rest of you...
have failed the mission, so Seok Jin...
wins 30 dollars, 10 dollars from each person.
Race of Wits: Deceive Seok Jin...
- This mission is over now. - Yes.
What did you say?
- "What did you say?" - I feel...
so sorry towards Soyou too.
Hold on.
We had seven levels of mission...
before we got here.
- Related to me? - Yes.
- Is that why it was chaotic today? - Right.
How couldn't you tell?
I wanted to tell him.
What's this?
(It's the hidden mission board that'll answer Seok Jin's question.)
- This was perfect. - "While you eat ramyeon..."
"Don't make him say he wants it."
That's the first thing he said when he got here.
(He failed so quickly.)
- I was following you. - Oh, gosh.
- That was what it was. - You were following me.
"Do laundry for 20 minutes?"
They ran the laundry machine for 20 minutes.
They did? I had no idea.
- We did the laundry. - "Steal three of Seok Jin's..."
"belongings without getting caught."
- Isn't this a fail? - Why?
I asked where my phone went.
It was over before then.
Oh, really?
- It was long before. - Really?
It was long before.
When you asked us that, we were on the sixth mission.
Really?
It says to peel five onions, and he can't say "onion" during that time.
- You peeled onions? - I peeled it...
behind Jong Kook.
It made me tear up.
My eyes didn't burn at all.
- I'm serious. - My eyes still burn.
- The smell was pretty strong. - Really?
This is a cottage, so that's possible.
That's true.
- Cottages don't smell like this. - He thinks differently.
- It's possible. - He has a different point of view.
You can eat now,
and we'll head to our final location...
where you can switch your mission money.
It's more advantageous for you to get there early.
- Early? - Each member will leave separately.
Why is that?
(Each member will leave at separate times?)
This is our standard.
Besides all of you, Seok Jin had a hidden mission as well.
(He had a hidden mission?)
- What's that? - There was something going on.
(That was totally unexpected.)
There was something going on.
(What was Seok Jin's shocking mission?)
(Chapter 3: Blades of Revenge)
(One hour before the opening)
Hello.
What's going on today? Is this Seok Jin's Running Man?
Why am I here by myself?
(Why was he by himself?)
Soon, we'll conduct a mission called the Race of Wits.
Before the main mission is over,
you'll become Seok Jin the Swordsman.
(Seok Jin the Swordsman?)
You'll become Seok Jin the Swordsman and complete a hidden mission.
(He got a hidden mission while the others got theirs.)
Am I the main character?
We'll give you 30 blades...
as the swordsman.
You need to hide as many blades as possible...
in the bodies of the members.
(He needs to hide 30 blades in the members' bodies.)
The members with more blades...
will be at a disadvantage during the final mission.
This is not easy.
How am I supposed to hide them?
Where do I put them?
This is so difficult.
This is more difficult than a water gun.
That's why...
we have invited another swordswoman who will help you.
Who is it?
(It's Soyou, a beautiful swordswoman.)
Soyou, your job is to...
help Seok Jin so that he doesn't get caught by the others...
while he hides the blades.
You're a hidden swordswoman.
(That's how their secret operation started.)
(He had blades in his hands and looked for chances.)
(While Soyou had the people's attention,)
(he hid the blades in the members' bags.)
(He tried ripping a name tag and put a blade underneath.)
(He got more bold with Kwang Soo right in front of him.)
(So Min left her bag here.)
(Soyou stretched herself and covered him.)
(He succeeded thanks to their perfect teamwork.)
- Rock-scissors-paper - Rock-scissors-paper
(He was darting in and out of places.)
(I'm not old yet. I'm just experienced.)
Besides all of you,
Seok Jin had a mission as well.
- What's that? - There was something going on.
What I found the most strange was...
when Seok Jin was going into the bathroom,
and there were three cameramen on him.
"What's the matter?"
"I'm going to use the bathroom."
(He wanted to use the bathroom while there were cameras?)
I'm going to pee.
(He was startled.)
(He tried to shut the door, but he was unsuccessful.)
- The camera is on. - I know.
What are you doing then?
Seok Jin.
(He ignores Kwang Soo.)
- Is that right? - Seok Jin.
(Why is he acting so awkwardly?)
Seok Jin.
(That's how you react when your wife finds out about your secret money.)
What's going on?
The cameraman was right in front of you.
I was going to tell him to wait outside.
I was going to close the door.
- You even made this gesture. - No, I didn't.
We'll head to our final location where you can switch...
- your mission money. - Okay.
According to the number of blades Seok Jin hid...
(The swordsman's identity is revealed.)
(What blades?)
Each blade counts for a minute you have to wait.
(Number of blades times 1 minute.)
What do you mean? Where's mine?
- Where's mine? - There are blades?
- I have some. - Me too.
- I have blades. - Me too.
Look at these blades.
Why do I have so many?
- Why do I have so many? - I have blades.
- I have 5. - I have 2.
Jong Kook, I have more than five.
- Look at that. - How many do you have?
You have one on your back too.
(She had 7 in her bag and 1 under the name tag.)
- Here's another one. - I only have two, right?
Ji Hyo.
- I have none. - You can get going.
Haha, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo will leave in two minutes.
Jae Seok and Se Chan can leave in five minutes.
- I have 8. - You can leave in 8 minutes.
You can take your time, So Min.
Seok Jin, how many blades do you have left?
- I know. - He has a lot.
- You have six. - I do.
You can leave in six minutes.
What about us?
(Seok Jin will leave in 6 minutes.)
(This is the order they'll leave in.)
Soyou, thank you for coming...
- despite your busy schedule. - She's our family.
- I'm not that busy. - Is that right?
- You should come again. - Please invite me.
We'll invite you as a proper guest.
Come to So Min's housewarming party.
(Please join us at So Min's new place.)
- Please come. - It's So Min's housewarming party.
Don't pressure her.
She's never met So Min before.
- She lives in a good neighborhood. - Don't push it.
(Please invite me next time.)
Please give her a round of applause. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Good work.
- Thank you. - See you.
- Soyou. - Take care.
(It's time to head to their final location.)
Ji Hyo, you have no blades,
so you can get going.
I'll get going first.
- See you soon. - Good luck.
Good thing I was holding onto my bag.
It reads "hydrogen house".
Is this an electric car?
Let's go.
(It's more advantageous to arrive early.)
Look. This car is so quiet.
Kwang Soo, Haha, and Jong Kook can get going.
- Let's go. - Bye.
- See you later. - Good luck.
Jae Seok and Se Chan.
So Min, you can go.
(Their final destination is a hydrogen house.)
I'm here.
It's a hydrogen house.
(She arrives at the hydrogen house, riding an electric car.)
(She gets out,)
(but what is she supposed to do?)
"Pirate's Treasure Box".
"Find the blades hidden in the pirate's house,"
"and use them for the following mission."
"Each blade is worth 10 dollars."
(Each blade is worth 10 dollars?)
(There are blades hidden inside the hydrogen house.)
"Once you plug the car to the house and start the car,"
"the electricity will come on."
(Pirate's Treasure Box)
The other way?
(Power for digital appliances within the house are supplied by the car.)
(You need to connect the power...)
Turn on the car.
(You need to connect the power and turn on the car.)
(The lights come on.)
The lights came on.
(The power is from the electric car.)
(There are 25 blades hidden inside the house.)
(Ji Hyo gets started first.)
(She's fascinated.)
(She finds a key to the car.)
Car key.
(She's amazed by the new technology.)
Did you see that? Did you?
This is awesome.
I have one blade.
(She earns 10 dollars.)
They're here.
(The others come 2 minutes later.)
10 dollars per blade?
It's better the faster you get them.
I was checking out the car.
(She was too distracted.)
(Where are the blades?)
- Ji Hyo. - Yes?
- Did you find many? - No.
I just got here.
What's this? This is where they are.
(He finds a blade under the table.)
What's this? Why did they miss this?
Here's one as well.
Here.
(He overcomes the 2-minute handicap and finds the blades.)
(What's that?)
(It's underneath the pot.)
(Dashing)
(He intercepted with lightning speed.)
You are so sly.
- Don't you think so? - What?
What's wrong?
- That was so cunning. - Me?
- What do you mean? - That's what it seemed like.
- What do you mean? - I didn't even find one.
(His slyness didn't go so well with his bulky body.)
I bet they already took many.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan left 5 minutes later.)
How many did you find, Ji Hyo?
I found a few.
My gosh.
(He gets lucky.)
- I found one right away. - My gosh.
You found one?
I didn't even find one. Where did you see it?
- Kwang Soo. - I didn't find one. I came early.
(Here's one.)
(Se Chan points Kwang Soo towards an envelope.)
(Thanks, Se Chan.)
Gosh.
(It's empty.)
He believed me.
(He loves pranking Kwang Soo.)
I'm going to hit you.
(Haha finds a key to the electric car.)
I'll look inside the car.
(There must be many blades in the car.)
Stay there.
I'll go when they are gone.
(He leaves his cameraman.)
(Everybody is busy looking for the remaining blades.)
(He looks at the car and goes around it.)
(It's bothersome to get the others to come.)
It's better to come early.
- It's better. - It is.
The door doesn't open.
(He acts nonchalantly.)
(I want to find at least one.)
(You can look there. I'll get in the car.)
(He quickly opens the car door.)
(He gets inside the treasure house.)
(This place is full of hidden blades.)
Where could they be?
(There must be many inside.)
(The door is locked.)
(I'll be rich alone.)
Today is my lucky day
(Hello, please open the door.)
(He takes everything without looking outside.)
You'd better brace yourself for New Zealand.
You'll come with me.
- Brace yourself. - Listen, Jae Seok.
Let's be easy. I won't pick you.
(Jae Seok decides to pick Haha.)
- Brace yourself for New Zealand. - Come on, Jae Seok.
(Seok Jin comes running.)
May I go in?
You won't find anything there.
Did you find them all?
(Haha probably did.)
Someone found all of them.
(The race is over.)
(The number of blades that each member has)
You receive 10 dollars for each blade that you found.
Blades will play an important role in the final round.
It's good that you have one.
I have none. Do you have any?
As soon as So Min arrives,
we'll start the final mission with these blades.
(Thanks to So Min, the others enjoy some free time.)
It's run by hydrogen.
- Really? - It exits this way.
When I push the button, the electricity runs this way.
- This is unbelievable. - I see.
Take a look.
Do you see where it's going?
Does the electricity run in the car?
I see it.
- Do you operate the building... - Look, Kwang Soo.
with the electricity from this car?
There's electricity around you too.
- Around me? - Electricity is running around you.
- I'm a human being. - Look at the electricity flow.
This is interesting.
Where should I go?
What happened?
There was a mission to find the blades.
Everyone found all of them.
(The mission is over.)
You may go in.
- Are there any blades left for me? - No.
- Is it over? - Yes.
I risked my life to come here.
You may go in.
(It's too early to give up. What's the final mission?)
My efforts were futile.
Do you have your blades?
- Yes. - No.
(What do you mean? Blades?)
I have none.
I have one blade.
You have a chance to turn the tables during the final mission.
- What's the mission? - It's Barrel Man's Quiz.
(The final mission is Barrel Man's Quiz.)
- I feel most confident about this. - We'll start the quiz.
Listen to the question.
The member to raise the cushion the fastest while calling out...
- his name gets to answer. - Okay.
When you get a chance to answer,
stick and bet as many blades as you wish in the barrel,
and say your answer.
What if your answer is correct?
Then you gain double the number of blades that you have stuck.
(You gain twice as many blades as you bet.)
(You can double the number of blades.)
If another member bets more blades,
he takes the chance to answer.
(Another member may steal the chance.)
You can earn double the number of blades.
If the pirate pops up, the question will be null.
You must know the answer.
We shouldn't bet if we don't know the answer.
- Right. - I can turn the tables.
Who cleared the mission...
at the wit castle?
- Me. - Me.
Each of you won 20 dollars.
- Seok Jin won 30 dollars. - Right.
I converted the amount to blades.
I hardly have anything.
I have three blades at least.
Here's the first question.
Among the choices,
which one wasn't born in an egg?
(Which one wasn't born in an egg?)
- Okay. - Did you say, "egg"?
- I like history. - One, Hyeokgeose of Silla
Two, King Dongmyeong.
Three, King Suro.
Four, King Onjo.
I only know two of them.
(Haha is confused.)
Kwang Soo.
I bet two blades.
What?
(He must stick them successfully.)
- I hope he fails. - Isn't it number two?
- Two? - I hope he pops.
(No way.)
- Please pop. - Come on.
- Please pop. - No way.
(He has the chance to double the number of blades.)
Okay!
(He makes his bet successfully.)
Seok Jin. I bet three.
- Okay. - I hope he pops.
- I hope he fails. - If I succeed this time,
I'll be first place.
- Please pop. - Goodness.
He's going to pop.
(Seok Jin makes a bold move to become the final winner.)
He takes a big risk after three weeks.
I usually take many risks.
(He gets defensive.)
He takes a big risk...
- after three weeks. - The viewers will believe you.
You're holding down the pirate.
Am I?
- I made a mistake. - Do it.
Let's see.
- Please pop. - He's going to pop.
- He'll pop this time. - Okay.
He did well.
Stick two more blades if you want to raise your bet.
- I'll bet two more. - Okay.
- That's right. - Do you know the answer?
You don't know the answer, Kwang Soo.
- It's a war. - Do you?
The pirate will pop.
(Kwang Soo is close to the pirate.)
(He's very unlucky with the pirate oak barrel.)
- Kwang Soo might win. - Stick one more.
- Let's get it. - Let's get it.
- Stick it in. - Let's get it.
- Okay. - He's safe.
Raise your bet, Seok Jin.
(What will Seok Jin decide?)
- Raise it by 3. - I'll bet 3 more.
- Let's get it. - I'll bet 3 more.
(Seok Jin gets ambitious.)
- Let's get it. - He's a real man.
Raise it by three.
- I don't have anymore. - Let's get it.
- Let's get it. - He knows how to play.
He's being bold.
I know how to play it after 25 years of experience.
He knows how to play.
That's right.
Okay.
That's how it goes.
- You lost. - You lost.
He popped.
- I don't believe this. - It seemed suspicious.
Here I go.
- Kwang Soo? - Answer correctly.
You'd better be right.
Kwang Soo bet four blades.
- Yes. - If he gets it wrong,
this round will end in clear results.
- I hope he's wrong. - It's difficult.
What's the answer?
(What will be Kwang Soo's answer?)
- Three, King Dongmyeong. - What?
- 3? - 3 is King Suro.
(What are you saying?)
That's definitely incorrect.
- Wait a minute. - That's incorrect.
(Please listen to me.)
Three was King Suro.
That's right.
Seok Jin loses 6, and Kwang Soo loses 4.
- Let me do it again. - Let me do it again.
- Let me do it again. - Is it over?
- Let me do it again. - You should remember correctly.
Why did you brag?
You were arrogant.
Kwang Soo doesn't feel bad.
You'd call out the wrong answer anyway.
Kwang Soo, make sure that you know the answer.
Here's the next question.
What's the neologism that refers to people who keep their heads down...
- to stare at their smartphones? - I don't know.
I know the answer.
- One, smankenstein. - I have no idea.
Two, smacula.
Three, smombie.
- What's "smombie"? - Four, smummy.
- Jae Seok. - He's very good.
The answer is three.
(He answers too early.)
(Why are you answering now?)
- The answer is three. - Kwang Soo.
(Everyone raises their hands.)
- I should make a bet. - Right.
The real bet starts.
You should raise your bet.
- You must raise the bet. - The answer is three.
What's your bet?
I'll bet six blades.
Let's get it.
Jae Seok, can you say, "Let's get it"?
- Let's get it. - Can you say it?
Goodness, the pirate might pop.
(Thud)
That was loud.
Please, let's get it.
Let's get it. Wait.
Do you hope that the pirate will pop?
- I hope he will pop. - Please.
- Please. - You can do it, Jae Seok.
(He sticks 6 blades.)
Let's get it.
(He makes his bet successfully.)
That was close.
You get 10 seconds.
If you don't raise the bet, Jae Seok gets his turn.
- I don't feel confident. - Jae Seok may win 12.
I bet seven blades.
(She makes a bet of 7 blades.)
- Seven? - Really?
(Can you bet 7?)
- She said 7. - 7?
(So Min is fearless.)
- What's wrong with her? - We only live once.
(She stays positive.)
You can take your turn later.
She bets everything.
(So Min makes another bold move.)
(She must stick 7 blades in 18 remaining slots.)
Do I get to answer if So Min fails?
Is that so?
(She starts carefully.)
(What happened?)
(You definitely live once.)
You shouldn't have made the bet.
Goodness.
That was so unlucky.
- Goodbye. - Give me your seven blades.
What's wrong with me today?
What's wrong with me?
You shouldn't have taken the risk.
What's the answer, Jae Seok?
It's three, smombie.
(The answer is correct.)
- "Smombie"? - What's the reason?
- Smombie is correct. - It comes from zombie.
Was that correct?
Six blades are good enough.
- This is great. - Let's continue.
Let's go.
Which is the standard Korean word?
The questions are too difficult.
All right. I just need to get this one.
One, married woman.
Two, chives.
Three, fritters.
Four, in a flash.
So Min.
(She must know the answer.)
- Is it "in a flash"? - I bet one blade.
Hurry up.
(She bets one blade.)
So Min.
She hardly has any blades.
She tries hard to participate.
(She remains passionate.)
(She sticks one blade.)
Kwang Soo. I bet two blades.
(He waited for his moment.)
What are you two doing? Stop it already.
- Both of them make... - I won't give her a chance.
small bets.
- Seriously... - You got unlucky, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo does it again.)
He is unbelievable.
(So Min gets a chance to answer with one blade.)
You are unbelievable.
- You are amazing. - You are the king of variety shows.
- How did you do that? - Seriously.
- So Min, answer the question. - So Min.
- My goodness. - I think I will get it wrong.
Three, fritters.
- The answer was four, in a flash. - I knew the answer.
I really did.
- Let's change the barrel. - We will change the barrel.
How many questions do we have left?
The blades are in the barrel.
- Maybe they have two in total. - Kwang Soo.
Give them the blade.
(Kwang Soo, give them the blade.)
(A moment ago)
(He takes out a blade on the pirate oak barrel.)
(The members catch him trying to steal it.)
Kwang Soo, give them the blade.
Do you know how many pairs of eyes were watching you?
I was watching you to see what you would do.
- Kwang Soo, don't be like that. - Your hands are too slow.
(My hands are slow now.)
You shouldn't do that.
(It's time for the last question.)
Here comes the final round with the last question.
I will go all in.
- I will go all in. - Let's go.
The symbol of the Olympic Games...
is the Olympics rings which is the five interlocking rings...
of 3 rings on the top and 2 rings on the bottom...
in different colors.
This question is hard.
Which color isn't in the Olympics rings?
Wait a minute.
One, blue.
Two, black.
Three, orange.
Four, green.
- Jae Seok. - Kwang Soo.
Jae Seok was faster.
(Jae Seok is fast.)
Jae Seok.
I know the answer.
I will bet five blades.
(He bets 5 blades.)
- I have three blades. - I must win...
- to take the lead. - That's right.
I am down to two options.
- It's 1 of the 2. - Show us how to play.
Show us how to play after years of experience.
- Let's get it. - Let's get it.
- Show us. - Say,
- "Let me do it again." - Let's get it.
Let's get it.
(Clicking)
- That was a good sound. - I thought the pirate would pop up.
(The careful bet makes them hold their breaths.)
Is the pirate wearing clothes?
(Out of the blue)
No,
he is only wearing the top like Winnie the Pooh.
(Serious)
(Jae Seok is on his 5th blade.)
Did you bet five blades?
- It's the last one. - It's a 50-50 chance.
(He bets the blades successfully.)
He will move up if he gets the answer right.
Three.
(He blurts out the answer.)
Please wait. We need to see if more people will bet.
- All right. - My goodness.
- I'll bet. - I will bet six blades.
Six blades.
This is driving me crazy.
- I indeed have a problem. - No, no.
- Your mouth is the problem. - You are right.
Kwang Soo, I need a beating.
- Kwang Soo, I need a beating. - That's right.
You will get a chance if Haha makes the pirate pop up.
- Haha, push in the blades. - It should pop up.
Haha, push in the blades.
I have one more blade to go.
(Laughing)
The pirate should pop up with the last blade.
(Let's see if Haha succeeds to bet 6 blades.)
My goodness.
Jae Seok can win back the right if he bets two more blades.
You should bet more blades.
(Jae Seok can win back the right if he bets 2 more blades.)
You can't give up now.
- Go ahead. - It's too risky now.
- Go ahead, and bet two more blades. - Okay. I will bet two more blades.
- Okay. - All right.
- Please. - He won't succeed.
Let's get it.
Let's get it, let's get it
(He acts in a silly way.)
Let's get it
(He succeeds in inserting a blade.)
- You have 1 more blade to go. - 1 more blade.
I can't lose when I came this far.
- I... - Let's go.
Show us how to play.
That's it.
(Jae Seok succeeds in betting 7 blades.)
- This is insane. - Who will make the pirate pop up?
- Who will make the pirate pop up? - Seriously.
Haha, you have 2 more left...
- to win back the right. - Two more blades.
This must be what we see on the news.
I can't lose when I came this far.
- I will go all in. - Okay.
All in!
You only get one shot in life.
You should have remembered it, Kwang Soo.
(The Truth of Pirate Oak Barrel starts now.)
Gambling can ruin your entire family.
I will insert two blades at once.
Insert one blade at a time.
(Spitting)
Insert two blades at once.
(He is very serious.)
(Why is he spitting?)
My goodness.
Please make him fail.
Spray water on it.
- My mouth is the problem. - Kwang Soo, spray water on it.
(Jae Seok is facing execution for blurting out the answer.)
My goodness.
(His mouth is full of water.)
(He fails to control the water pressure.)
Are you out of your mind?
- Come on. - Come on.
- I am the double blade of Mapo-gu. - Come on.
- Come on, you jerk. - Come on. Come on.
(Inserting)
(The double blade of Mapo-gu has daring skills.)
- Insert it here. - That's it.
That's it.
Come on. Come on.
(They continue to bet more blades after one another.)
Okay.
That's it.
I did it.
(Only five slots remain.)
(The two of them can't get off the all-in train.)
(One is on his way to Bora Bora...)
(while the other is on his way to failure.)
Haha.
There he goes.
(Jae Seok bets 2 more blades.)
It won't go in.
Maybe you should've chosen another slot.
- It's going in. - Push it in with force.
(They don't know how they came this far.)
My goodness.
(He succeeds in inserting a blade.)
- No way. - The sound was painful.
- You have one more to go. - His legs went weak.
You have one more to go.
Now, 3 out of 4 slots are safe.
(3 out of 4 slots are safe.)
- Come on. - Choose that slot.
My goodness, the pirate talks.
- What does he say? - He nods.
He is telling me not to choose this slot.
It's not this one.
- He says it is. - Is it this one?
He says it is.
He nods.
(He has goosebumps.)
(Insert it into that slot.)
- He says it's that one. - This one?
(Someone is inside the pirate.)
Will you pop up if I insert the blade here?
- He is nodding. - He is nodding.
- No? - No.
- Are you shaking it? - What are you doing?
(Trembling)
What are you doing?
What is going on?
- He is a con man. - Whom are you talking to?
This is a funny skit.
What are you talking about?
Children love puppet shows.
- For goodness' sake. - You know,
- many children were absorbed... - It's neither educational nor fun.
in the puppet show.
Everyone was fooled. So Min, you were fooled, right?
I believed him.
Let's go!
(He succeeds.)
- This is incredible. - Three slots remain.
Did you insert all the blades?
- Will Haha be able to do it? - Will you bet more blades?
- You have to do it. - You have no choice.
Two more blades don't make a difference now.
You can turn around now.
(Haha bets more blades.)
Right there.
- This is crazy. - This is crazy, Haha.
(Jae Seok and Haha put blades in 22 out of 24 slots.)
- Gosh, it's 1 of the 2. - It's 1 of the 2.
- We don't know what will happen. - It's a 50-50 chance.
- Insert the blade. - It's a 50-50 chance.
Kwang Soo said it's this one, right?
No, I said it's the one on the left.
- The one on the right. - This one?
You should trust Kwang Soo this time.
Trust Kwang Soo.
(He aims for the slot Kwang Soo recommended.)
- Trust Kwang Soo. - I am rooting for you.
(Haha listens to Kwang Soo for the first time.)
(If he succeeds, he will have the chance to answer.)
(Is Kwang Soo's hunch wrong today as well?)
Trust him.
(23 out of 24 slots are full, but the pirate is still intact.)
- I think it's broken. - It seems that way.
We need to insert the blades the right way.
Maybe you inserted them too forcefully.
We don't know.
- Shall we insert the last blade? - The pirate might pop up.
If the pirate pops up, that means the toy is working.
Let's insert it.
- Let's check. - Shall we insert it?
- Insert it. - Kwang Soo will do it.
(The last slot was the penalty slot.)
No way!
- This is incredible. - I got goosebumps.
- This is incredible. - It wasn't broken.
- I thought it was broken. - I got goosebumps.
You avoided it until the end.
(Haha gets his chance.)
What's your answer?
Three, orange.
(Haha trusts Jae Seok's slip of the tongue.)
(Is it the right answer?)
(Haha acquires 12 additional blades.)
(I can't believe I gave away the answer.)
Yes!
Is it really the right answer?
There is red.
- That's right. - Let's do a high five.
- I took out all the blades. - All right.
Thus, the winner of the day...
is Haha.
- He won again. - I did it.
(Haha wins in 2 weeks in a row.)
(Haha suggested Bora Bora for the Half and Half Tour.)
(Who goes to Bora Bora is in his hands.)
- I will buy 2 of my name tags. - Okay.
Since Jong Kook wanted to go,
- I will buy one of his name tag. - All right.
- Also, - I am okay with that.
So Min really wanted to go. I will buy one of hers.
Thank you.
I will buy these name tags.
One for Se Chan.
- Ji Hyo. - That's right.
Why won't you cover my name?
(The roulette is ready and on standby.)
I really want to go to Bora Bora.
Let's go to Bora Bora. When else will we have the chance?
In 1, 2, 3.
(The roulette for Bora Bora starts spinning.)
(It's their chance to enjoy the fantastic island.)
I want to go.
(Who is the lucky winner?)
It will be Jae Seok.
It will be Haha.
(Please let it be me.)
(It's either So Min or Seok Jin.)
It will be Jae Seok. It will be Haha.
- It will be So Min. - So Min!
(So Min is chosen!)
Good for you!
She wanted this most desperately.
- Wasn't that... - She looks so happy.
- Jae Seok's? - This is amazing.
- I really want to go there now. - But she didn't do anything today.
If Bora Bora is chosen as the destination,
So Min and the companion she chooses will go on the trip.
Thank you!
(Will she be able to go to Bora Bora?)