This is Running Man's Member's Week.
(Week 6)
(It's a week of rest.)
(It's a paradise in the city. The paradise welcomes the members.)
(It's a marvelous break that they haven't had for a long time.)
(While you are asleep,)
(they start executing their mission.)
(He's a very suspicious clothes thief.)
(Yu Jae Seok against Lee Kwang Soo)
(The robbery in the sauna occurs in Seoul.)
(It's a neck and neck match between two thieves.)
(If you commit a burglary, you must pay for your crime.)
(The dragnet is closing in on the thieves.)
(It's a race between the hunter and the hunted.)
(What will these two thieves' fate be?)
(Taking a rest is a hard thing to do in the midst of a busy life.)
(Sauna is a vacation spot in the city where one can visit easily.)
We are at a sauna.
- You're right. - It's been so long.
You've been participating in Member's Week so far.
You must've been tired visiting...
- cold places. - Yes, it was so cold.
We prepared a break for you since you are...
physically and mentally exhausted.
- Is that so? - Really?
The race is called Walk, Don't Run.
We have prepared a race called Walk, Don't Run.
In order to start resting,
please get changed and gather here again.
- They're going to give us clothes? - All right!
(We are going to change right away?)
- Let's film a bit more. - Hey.
- Then why did we have to dress up? - What is this?
My stylist went to six different places for this outfit.
- Let's film a bit longer. - My stylist visited six places.
- Look at Kwang Soo. - What is your outfit?
- Who wears a long coat to a sauna? - It's not a long coat.
- We can play a game about it. - Look at Ji Hyo's jacket.
- You'd see this on a fashion show. - Hey.
I dressed up nicely today.
(Her arms catch everyone's eyes.)
- Let's go. - What?
- Let's go. - Okay. We should.
(Is this it?)
(Our runway has just started.)
(It's a complete outfit in a sauna that you've been dreaming of.)
(If it could make us stylish even for just 1 second...)
(She attracts attention.)
- That's not very ladylike. - What's wrong with it?
- What kind of lady would do that? - The arms are the highlight.
- Try this one. - The arms are the selling point.
(I will be fine if I can show off my fur.)
I'd like to apologize to my stylist.
- I'm sorry. - Let's wear it again.
- You should've told us before. - What a waste.
(Everyone goes to get changed.)
The number is 283.
Mine is 171.
What are you doing? How far are you going to follow me?
You're going to keep filming?
Fine. Film us. It's fine by me.
(They're filming us up close today.)
Is there a mission? What if someone starts removing the name tags?
(You're filming this, too?)
(Uncomfortable Sauna)
(What is this?)
(A mission card is in Kwang Soo's locker.)
(You are the thieves of the sauna. Steal others' clothes in secret.)
(Whoever steals more clothes wins.)
(Jae Seok and I are clothes thieves?)
(What?)
(The same mission card is in Jae Seok's locker.)
What is this?
(A hidden mission has been sent.)
What is all this now? My gosh. I'll go crazy.
(It's a mission called "Steal Their Clothes".)
How could I steal their clothes?
(If they steal 4 members' clothes, the mission is a success.)
(If the others find out about it, the punishment will be doubled.)
(From the start, the battle between two thieves has started.)
(Will Jae Seok, who has the experience in spying, win?)
(Or will Kwang Soo, who is fast and has good acting skills, win?)
(Who will be the winner?)
(Their mission starts.)
- This is huge. - It sure is.
We really should come here to have fun, but we don't have the time.
It's not like we don't want to.
There are so many things to do here.
- Of course. It will be so much fun. - Let's have sikhye.
(A sight of a warm red clay floor relaxes their bodies.)
I want to go into that room and sleep.
- They have a snack bar, too. - It's a snack bar.
- Where is Ji Hyo? - That's right.
- Ji Hyo has to come. - She's not here?
I thought she might have a separate mission. She's just late.
(What do you mean by a separate mission?)
She's always late.
What a surprise.
No one scolds her for being late.
- We should scold her once. - It's too late for that.
- It's too late. - It's been seven years.
- I will do it. - Why would we do that to her?
- I can't believe she's late again. - Sorry to say this, Seok Jin.
- She doesn't listen to you. - That's true.
(He can't deny it.)
- Let me stretch first. - Seok Jin. If you are going to...
(He seriously gets ready,)
(but he slips.)
- Goodness. - What's wrong with you?
(What an out-dated slapstick.)
(They can't believe Seok Jin did that.)
Seok Jin. Please apologize to the viewers.
- Stop it. - With 20 years of career,
you shouldn't have done it.
- What is this? - He did that on purpose.
(Anyone can do this.)
- Everyone can pull it off. - Everyone can slip.
- Who can't do this? - I didn't do it on purpose.
- Imagine young comedians saw this. - Seriously.
- I slipped because of the socks. - This isn't right.
It's because you wore your socks inside out.
- Hey. - Run. Run!
(Here comes Ji Hyo.)
What time is it?
- What was that? - That's your locker key, not watch.
It's 5:31pm.
(They think it's funny this time.)
Why are you always late?
I was changing.
(That's understandable.)
You're not the only one who went to get changed.
I'm a woman, though.
- That's possible. - Ladies take longer.
- Is this how you'll play it? - What do you mean?
- Hey. Say something. - Girls need more time.
- Girls might need more time. - He must be drunk.
Why is he like this before the shooting?
I apologize.
Why did you scold Ji Hyo?
- Why does it always end like this? - Why is it always like this?
Someday, I will scold you for certain.
- Someday soon, - "I will scold you..."
- I will scold you. - "for certain."
- He will. - I failed again.
In the sauna, you take a rest.
For your rest...
If you have your phones or locker keys...
(Locker room keys?)
(They have to put their phones and keys away.)
- Put them away back there. - My key?
- You have to leave them? - I see.
You usually pay later in saunas.
- We don't have phones with us now. - Let's leave it here.
(They leave their keys without any suspicion.)
Put your phones away, too.
(If the keys are away from the owners,)
(they simply need to steal it in secret.)
(The 4 targets are placed in an open area. Will they be able to succeed?)
This is the break of Member's Week.
Here are the rules of Walk, Don't Run.
In the sauna, there are various relaxing courses.
The members who enjoy each course the most...
will be given mileage points according to their ranking.
- Mileage points? - Yes.
This is an individual match.
With the mileage points,
you can earn prizes and use the snack bar.
If you finish the last course, today's race will end.
Okay.
Now, we'll be heading to savanna,
the first vacation spot.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Savanna. - Savanna.
Where's savanna?
- It's a room? - It's over there.
- Savanna. - It's the tropics.
Are we going to a hot place?
Where's savanna?
(Even by the name of the first course, we can tell it's hot.)
I really like it.
(Gosh)
- What do you mean? - This is it.
(The heat wave will fend off all the cold this winter.)
Welcome to the savanna course.
There will be missions to help you enjoy the heat in savanna.
It's "Lunch at the Savanna".
"Lunch"?
- So we are eating? - How can we eat in this heat?
In that case,
- you should give us iced sikhye. - I want red-bean sherbet.
Enjoy savanna as long as you can.
The longer you stay, the more mileage points you get.
Your lunch is coming in.
- Gosh. Seriously. - What is it?
(What is it?)
It can't be spicy food.
(They want us to eat this?)
(It's hot coffee and a cup of soup.)
It's too hot.
- It looks hot. - It is.
It would be better to have ramyeon here.
If you finish your meal, you can go outside.
(If I finish my meal, I can go outside?)
- You can go outside. - If I finish my meal?
(If I leave first and secure the targets,)
(the stealing would be much easier.)
(Glancing)
(Let's see who wins.)
(Kwang Soo, you thief!)
(Look who's talking.)
(The first one to finish the meal will get the keys.)
They are so creative in making games.
- Can I have water? - I'm already sweating.
(Slurping)
What's wrong with him?
(He sacrifices his mouth to get out first.)
- It's too hot. - What's wrong with you?
It's really hot.
(Savanna doesn't get along with me.)
- Look at this. - It's steaming.
This is too hot.
- This is too much. - It's steaming.
- I can't eat all of this. - Like cures like.
(It doesn't have to be this hot.)
(The temperature is high, the food is hot, and they are stressed out.)
It's regretful that the viewers...
won't be able to feel this heat.
- It's really hot. - You don't have to eat fast, right?
Seok Jin, what's that over there?
(Pouring)
What are you doing?
(Have some more. It's a present from me.)
(He wishes Seok Jin to eat slowly and sweat it out.)
- Did you pour yours here? - No, I didn't.
- I'm being serious. I ate them all. - You don't have much left.
- I ate them all. - I saw you did it.
(Look at his being cunning.)
(He stands up slowly.)
- I saw you did it. - I didn't.
(He's blocking the exit.)
- What are you doing? - It's really hot.
- What is he doing? - He's trying to do something.
- What are you trying to do? - Nothing.
- The speed isn't important here. - It's better to eat slowly.
Can I have this?
- Why are you using that? - I want to cool it off.
- Why are you eating so fast? - Why is that?
- Why? - Why?
Was this your idea?
- He's hiding something. - He probably is.
- I like hot food. - He's hiding something.
He's hiding something. Are you?
- It's not me. - I knew something was off.
There are only giraffes on the wall when they say it's savanna.
- What? Where? - That's true.
(Savanna and giraffe? They are correlatable.)
- Wait a second. - He's right.
We shouldn't let him out.
- Kwang Soo. - We shouldn't let him out.
- He's trying to go outside fast. - He's acting weird.
- Come here. - Come here. Give it to me.
- No, that's not true. - Give me the cup.
- It's a giraffe room. - It's a safari.
- He is sharp. - It's a giraffe room.
This is a giraffe room and Kwang Soo's mission.
- How did you spot the giraffe? - He's so sharp.
How can you not?
This is suspicious.
He's acting strangely now. He's very suspicious.
Kwang Soo is sweating so much.
I just can't stand it here.
Wait. Let's look behind the picture.
- You're not supposed to go out. - It's too hot in here.
(Where are you going?)
It's too hot in here.
Look. He's trying to stop me.
You can't give up already.
- You can't give up already. - It's too hot. My feet are too hot.
- You can't give up now. - Let me out.
- What are you doing? - He's hiding something.
What are you doing?
(Chaos in savanna)
If you finish your meal, you can go outside?
(The herbivores suffering from heat waves are in chaos.)
(The seemingly impregnable fortress is now defenseless.)
(Jae Seok succeeds in escaping without being suspected.)
(He's a nimble grasshopper.)
It's so hot.
(He reaches the snack bar faster than anyone.)
(There are four targets.)
(Who has the heaviest clothes?)
Who has the heaviest clothes?
I think it's Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo's fur jacket?)
I choose Seok Jin.
(He steals Seok Jin's key as it's easily accessible.)
Can I have a key?
(He borrows a fake key so that he won't be suspected.)
(Now that he has the key, he only has to steal.)
It's Seok Jin's.
(I'm going to steal his clothes now.)
It was really hot.
(It's a long way from the sauna to the locker room.)
(The target is right in front of me.)
It's 1731.
Where is his locker?
(Somewhere here...)
(I found it!)
(He even takes the socks.)
(He's running really fast.)
(Seok Jin's clothes get stolen first.)
- Here you go. - Whose clothes are they?
It's Seok Jin's.
- Where's the key? - It's here.
(Jae Seok succeeds in stealing Seok Jin's clothes.)
Did I succeed?
(Jae Seok earns 2.6kg.)
- Why did Kwang Soo stop him? - Wait.
Kwang Soo is hiding something.
- Kwang Soo is very suspicious. - He is?
- He tried to stop Jae Seok. - I know. Why would he do that?
(Why did Kwang Soo stop Jae Seok?)
(This game is about staying as long as possible.)
Why did he stop Jae Seok?
Everything is weird.
(He can't think of an excuse.)
Jae Seok failed because he went out first.
It's driving me crazy.
You came back. Welcome.
I went outside first. I guess I failed.
(Temper rising)
- This is the second dish for you. - What is this?
(What is this smell?)
- It's not steaming, yet so hot. - I can't eat all of this.
(We introduce you to the spicy chicken feet from savanna.)
I want to escape because of the food.
(I'm stressed out already.)
(This is supposed to be delicious when it's eaten in hot places.)
- It's killing me. - This is too much.
I can't eat all of this.
(Ji Hyo, who enjoys spicy food, tastes the dish first.)
This looks so red.
They put too much spicy sauce.
(It's really spicy.)
It's too spicy.
(This is my chance to escape.)
(My tongue hurts.)
It's hot in here.
It's driving me crazy.
(This feels like a virtual reality of savanna.)
It's no joke.
(Heat rising)
- It's really spicy. - It is.
Chicken feet are delicious when it is spicy.
If it's not, it loses its taste.
It's unbelievable.
Can I drink water outside?
(Are you using water as your excuse?)
(No one is thinking straight. This is the only opportunity.)
- Yes. - I can't do it anymore.
He's hiding something.
(His plan fails in 5 seconds.)
- I'm 100 percent sure. - He's hiding something.
You're making it too obvious.
(I don't care.)
Kwang Soo is going out. I'm going too.
Wait. I'll stay a bit more.
- Go out. - Wait.
- It's better when you stand up. - I'm the fourth then.
- Aren't you out? - You are already out.
- He's out. - I'm going crazy.
- Am I out? - You are out.
- Are you going outside? - He's out, right?
I can't stand it.
(Seok Jin gives up and heads to the ice room.)
- There's an ice room there. - I'm going crazy.
(Seok Jin is not helping.)
The ice room is the best.
How can they stay inside?
(What am I to do?)
I really can't stand it.
- What are you doing? - He's leaving.
(Kwang Soo, you should stay inside. Where are you going?)
Maybe Jae Seok and Kwang Soo have something together.
(Are those two going mad because of the heat?)
Why can't I do this?
(Kwang Soo punches Jae Seok.)
(There's a lot going on in this room.)
(He finally escapes from the savanna.)
(While Seok Jin is away, he runs towards the locker room.)
(Kwang Soo's first target is Haha.)
Haha's clothes looked the heaviest.
Here's your third menu.
- What's this? - It's spicy ramyeon.
I love this ramyeon.
(They only focus on the mission.)
I don't want to eat that.
You must leave if you don't eat.
Fine, I'll go out.
- He's heading to the ice room. - What?
Haha's clothes looked the heaviest.
(Haha is too busy eating ramyeon.)
(He's running out of time.)
It's 2127.
(He must steal Haha's clothes before he leaves the savanna.)
Here's a warm jacket for you.
(Haha gives up.)
No, don't leave.
(Ji Hyo is the final winner.)
Ji Hyo wins first place.
(Kwang Soo has no time.)
It's locker number 2127.
(He must steal now.)
Okay.
(There's a heap of clothes.)
(He's in a hurry.)
(He goes to weigh the clothes.)
Hello.
(How much do Haha's clothes weigh?)
Please weigh these.
They're lighter than I thought.
I should have stolen Ji Hyo's.
(Jae Seok is ahead by 0.4kg.)
Is Kwang Soo missing?
(He hurries to go back.)
Things became clear.
What are you doing, Kwang Soo?
(He's in a daze after his first theft.)
How dejected do you feel?
It's because we found out.
He didn't have enough time to clear the mission.
Is that so?
I'm not the one.
His plan was wasted because of you, Jae Seok.
Is that right? You must...
- do something for me in return. - Of course.
- His plan was wasted because of me. - Right.
(Kwang Soo wants to expose him.)
- What's wrong? - Stop it.
What's wrong with you?
- I'm a victim. - This is unfair.
- What Haha said reminded me. - Either way,
- we recognize you for what you did. - Okay.
People were suspicious of me last week when it was Gary.
Why did you try to stop Jae Seok from leaving?
I'm very curious.
It was strange that Kwang Soo tried to stop him.
Why did you try to stop him?
Why did Kwang Soo block Jae Seok from leaving?
- I'm very curious. - Why did you do it?
- Why did you block me? - Follow me, Kwang Soo.
- To where? - Come to this room.
Do you have to discuss something?
They're suspicious.
- It's very hot in here. - Are they up to something?
- We don't have our phones or keys. - They took them from us.
There's something going on over there.
- They may put something in lockers. - That's right.
They shot a video of that.
- There must be a reason why. - They took a video...
of us changing as well.
- Why did we have to leave them? - They recorded me when I was naked.
Stop acting like that, Jae Seok.
What do you mean?
- They might find out. - Okay, let's be careful.
(What will happen to Jae Seok and Kwang Soo?)
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are the remaining targets.)
(The members return to the locker room.)
Why do you keep filming us?
- Why do you film so much today? - What's going on?
It's strange.
(He suspects something.)
Why do you keep filming us?
Why?
They do?
Are you filming us?
It's locker number 2127.
(Kwang Soo searches something.)
Kwang Soo.
(Haha is too quick to notice.)
Kwang Soo? Is he here?
(Haha is suspicious while Jong Kook is the target.)
Things became clear.
- Jong Kook, do you want to go? - Where?
I need to check the counter where I left my phone.
(My goodness)
Something is going on.
(He definitely senses something.)
Shall I check it out?
(He might find out.)
(They must move quickly.)
(Jae Seok must start the mission before Haha finds out.)
(He starts his 2nd theft.)
(He runs for Jong Kook's key.)
Which way?
Where are you going?
- I'm going to the bathroom. - It's this way.
- Where? - The bathroom is here.
(They run for the key.)
(It's a chase in the sauna.)
(The first to arrive takes the key.)
(Kwang Soo won't let him go.)
- Don't go. - You can't do this.
You can't do this, Kwang Soo.
(Their peace breaks after 5 minutes.)
Calm down, Kwang Soo.
(Calm down.)
- Kwang Soo, calm down. - If we don't stop, we'll be caught.
- I'm at a disadvantage. - Let's calm down.
Let's calm down, Kwang Soo.
- How about this? - I'm in a bad situation.
That's why I'm acting like this.
Let's try to control ourselves.
Please give me a break.
Why did you...
Let's just tell them the truth.
(He sighs.)
Don't be such a bully.
You shouldn't talk like that.
Let's tell them the truth.
Let's be honest to them.
I scalded my tongue.
I had to endure the pain because of what you did.
Let's be fair.
Let's play fairly.
(They promise to be at peace.)
(Kwang Soo was lying.)
(They go back to fighting again.)
(They won't be easy on each other.)
(Jae Seok bites him.)
(Kwang Soo hits him.)
(He goes for a vital point as they're in a sauna.)
(Here's a massage for Jae Seok.)
(They struggle.)
(Kwang Soo doesn't let him go.)
(Kwang Soo continues to hit.)
(Disobedience deserves a good beating.)
(It prickles his whole body.)
(He runs as fast as possible.)
(Catch the thief.)
(He continues to run.)
(He grabs Ji Hyo's key.)
Please give me the key.
Give me the key.
(Jae Seok chooses Ji Hyo as his target.)
(He's a little late.)
(He goes for Jong Kook's.)
(Kwang Soo takes Jong Kook's key.)
Will you do it now?
- Will you steal now? - What?
- Are you going to steal? - No, not right away.
My goodness.
When I compete with you, it becomes too messy.
What's wrong with you?
You punk.
(You're so clumsy.)
It's too tight on you.
(He slaps him.)
(He gives a high five to his cheek.)
I was fixing your microphone. It's too short.
It's too short.
I don't understand every time you attack me.
I never know when to expect it.
Wait, Jae Seok.
(He slaps him back.)
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, but I couldn't help myself.
You're a dirty punk.
(They start to fight again.)
(They break into a messy fight.)
(Jae Seok bites him.)
(Kwang Soo attacks him the same way.)
(Electricity runs through his body.)
Kwang Soo, you're a dirty punk.
I'm not the only one.
Whom are you calling dirty?
Let's not make it messy.
If they find out, it's over for us.
(The others are clueless.)
We must be very careful.
We'll look suspicious if we go in together.
- I'll go in first. - Okay.
(They move separately all the time.)
Could you keep it for me?
Keep it for me.
(He gets rid of evidence.)
Are you still filming us?
Are you still filming?
They keep filming us.
(Why?)
(He feels something strange.)
What's going on?
(Where's Jong Kook?)
(Where are you, Jong Kook?)
I'm going to the bathroom.
(Jong Kook goes to the bathroom.)
Okay, now is the time.
Shall I go check? Jong Kook?
(Kwang Soo steals while Haha suspects something.)
(Kwang Soo finds the locker.)
(He steals Jong Kook's clothes discreetly.)
(Will Kwang Soo leave the scene before Jong Kook comes out?)
(He covers up the clothes with towels.)
What are you doing?
(He's startled.)
(Kwang Soo is caught in the act.)
What are you doing?
Kwang Soo.
You're being too suspicious.
What are you doing?
Hey.
(He simply wants to talk.)
(He runs barefoot.)
Gosh.
(He's doomed.)
He's acting very strange.
What's going on?
I think he did something in the locker room.
(My goodness, Kwang Soo is caught.)
- He's on a mission. - Where's Jong Kook?
(He pretends not to know.)
Around which locker was he?
It must be one of ours.
(He's definitely caught.)
What?
Jong Kook.
Pardon me.
Did we get caught?
(They completely ruined it.)
He got caught.
(Why is he still running around?)
Didn't he get caught?
(Kwang Soo is running as fast as he can.)
(I'll just check these in anyway.)
Whatever. It's Jong Kook's.
- Hey. - Don't talk to me.
Hey, come here.
(He submitted 1.1kg of Jong Kook's clothes.)
You got caught.
(I don't care.)
- What is this? - What are you doing?
What are you doing?
(We'd love to hear your story.)
(He's still acting.)
- What are you doing? - What is this?
- How can you be so clumsy? - It's nothing.
What is this?
Don't follow me.
What is this? How can you do it so blatantly?
- From now on... - It's a fail, isn't it?
- What is he thinking? - He's in trouble.
What's his plan?
This is hilarious.
I was wondering why cameras were following us around.
It's a total fail.
Viewers, I'm sorry.
I'm hopeless.
(The hopeless man speaks.)
I'm ruined.
(Miserable)
Viewers.
Please look forward to my Member's Week.
See you then.
(Bye for now.)
I'll work harder from next week.
(I'm a terrible sinner.)
I'm sorry.
(What are we going to do now?)
Hey, look forward to my Member's Week.
(The "Steal Their Clothes" project is off the track.)
I caught him rummaging through your locker.
- Really? - His locker?
- Right in front of my eyes. - Gosh.
What is he going to do now? It's become a total flop.
What are you doing, Kwang Soo?
- What are you going to do? - It's such a flop.
- You blew it, right? - Did you blow it?
(I need to record this moment.)
He did seem suspicious.
(The aftermath of failure.jpg)
It's time for a special activity.
- What is it? - What is it?
It has a theme of Jeju Island, the representative vacation spot.
Welcome to Jeju Island!
(Jeju Island)
(How will they be forced to relax on Jeju Island?)
The mission is called "Resting Room".
- I love it. - Behind you...
are rooms for you.
People actually sleep in here.
You can lie down and relax there.
You're supposed to lie straight.
If your back comes off the floor...
(Funny)
- You're out. - What?
- It's a great chance for Kwang Soo. - Exactly.
Doesn't it remind you of the movie "Saw"?
(Stop talking about my mission.)
(Hilarious)
If you get up last,
you can get something...
- at the cafeteria. - Right.
- They're giving us money. - Really?
We should do our best to the end.
- Let's not get up. - Of course not.
(Do whatever you wish.)
- Okay. - Let's do that.
- Let's not get up. - For Kwang Soo to do his job...
(Forget about stealing clothes.)
- Let's... - Kwang Soo needs to do his job.
Let's not get up no matter what.
Don't take your back off the floor, Ji Hyo.
Shouldn't he be taken home?
- Okay, so first... - He's done with his job.
Let's let him do his job.
- Don't come out. - We won't.
- Let's go. - Let's lie down.
(The Jeju Island course starts.)
It's so nice.
We get to relax while shooting.
(The sound of waves)
- What is it? - What is it?
It's the sound of waves.
We're on Jeju Island.
Will music play?
I wonder what Kwang Soo will do.
Let's leave
(It's Red Velvet's song.)
- What is this? - Is Red Velvet here?
- Are they here? - Really?
(Is Red Velvet here?)
- Wait. - Really?
(They're the most popular girl group right now.)
(Are they really at the sauna?)
(Everyone is extremely curious.)
Is Red Velvet here?
Are they here?
(We're here.)
Really?
(Red Velvet is performing at the sauna.)
- Wait. - Where are they?
(You can't resist us.)
Is Red Velvet here?
- What should I do? - Are they here?
(They're too attractive to resist.)
(Wriggling)
- Seul Gi. - They're really here.
Wait!
(He gets up.)
(They're really here.)
What should I do?
(He falls.)
(Jae Seok is out.)
This can't be true.
(Jong Kook is desperate.)
Oh, my.
("Rookie" by Red Velvet)
What's going on?
(Cute)
What is this?
(Please tell me they're not here.)
(They start to sing their new song "Rookie".)
(I want to see them.)
Why are you here?
Mister, you're blocking me!
(Kwang Soo gets up.)
(You should have gotten up earlier.)
- Even Seul Gi is here. - Seriously.
- Is everyone here? - It's unbelievable.
Nice to see you. What brings you here?
- Why are you here? - Hello.
(Welcome, Red Velvet.)
- Hello. - What is this?
Jae Seok is in 7th place, and Kwang Soo is in 5th.
(They both lose 3 points.)
My goodness.
I have nothing to do with this game. Leave me alone.
- Jae Seok is in seventh place. - My goodness.
- This is unbelievable. - Goodness.
(The others will soon get cramps.)
Welcome to Jeju Island.
You're going to carry out this mission with Red Velvet.
- With them? - It's "Couple Race on Olle Trails".
What's that?
You're going to play charades...
- with Red Velvet... - Joy is not here.
- to decide partners. - Joy isn't here.
The one who says the right answer first will be the member's partner.
Is it a couple game?
- Yes. - Really?
(Is it a couple game?)
Really?
(Motivated)
We need to get it right to become partners?
Can we get up now?
Kwang Soo has been Joy's partner.
(Kwang Soo was Joy's partner in a race before.)
(Today, Joy couldn't come because of another show.)
(Will he stay faithful to Joy?)
No. We broke up. It was a long time ago.
(To get over someone, meet someone new.)
- It was nothing serious. - I'll tell Joy.
- Gosh. - It was nothing serious.
I'll tell Joy.
She had a husband in another show!
That's over now.
(I enjoyed watching your marriage life.)
That's over.
- It's over now. - By the way,
if you take your back off the floor,
you'll be out.
Keep your back on the floor.
- You can still see them. - Can we?
If you do, you're out.
Can't we take our backs off the floor?
(Kwang Soo's neck is off the floor.)
(Kwang Soo, keep your neck on the floor.)
What? My back is still on the floor.
My back is still on the floor.
What are you doing?
My back is on the floor.
- What about other parts? - You can take them off the floor.
(I'm happy I'm short.)
The first question will be given...
- by Irene. - Irene?
(These guys are a bit scary.)
I'll get this one.
Ready, start.
Is it a proverb?
(A bump on the back)
(There's a bump on her back, and she's startled.)
(The one who says the right answer will be Irene's partner.)
(Jae Seok gets up.)
I know.
- You're out. - Why?
(Jae Seok is out as soon as he shouts, "I know.")
Your back is off the floor. Stand over there.
- Why am I out? - Your back is off the floor.
Can't I get up when I say the answer?
No. You're out.
(The other five have the chance now.)
I know.
- "Startled by a caldron lid..." - "Startled by a caldron lid..."
- "after by a turtle." - "after by a turtle."
- Correct, Haha. - Gosh.
(I'm Irene's partner.)
I wanted to help Kwang Soo.
(I want a partner, too.)
- I said the answer, too. - Irene doesn't seem happy.
(Haha and Irene are a couple.)
The second question will be given by...
Wendy.
- Wendy? - Wendy?
(Creeping)
(He's so fast.)
(What is this mysterious creature?)
- I can't see anything! - Kwang Soo.
Aren't there clams like that?
Pen shells.
(Name: Kwang Soo, Habitat: Sauna)
Ready, start.
(Two)
(Diving)
- I think I know. - What is it?
It's a dolphin.
(Fins)
(Fighting)
"When whales fight, shrimps burst."
(I said it first, Wendy.)
- I know. - I know.
(They shout the answer at the same time.)
(Who gets the chance?)
- Kwang Soo. - I know!
- Kwang Soo. - I'm not done yet.
- She's so motivated. - Wait.
Am I...
- not your type? - Hold on.
(She's finishing up.)
I know! "When whales fight, shrimps burst."
Correct. Go.
Wait. Is this how you're going to do it?
(Ji Hyo and Wendy are a couple.)
Are you serious?
(Both his mission and quiz failed.)
I already blew the mission.
Kwang Soo said the answer.
My Member's Week will be a war against the staff.
Isn't this your Member's Week?
- I thought this was your special. - I'm going to go against them.
(They thought it was Kwang Soo's Week for sure.)
Here's the third question.
- Here's question number 3. - There are only 2 people left.
- Ye Ri. - Yes!
I think she'll be good.
Ready. Make sure you say, "I know".
- I'm going to get this one right. - Ready.
Set...
Kwang Soo, you can't look...
Why are you only picking on me?
I'm losing patience.
- You're done. - Ready.
Set, go.
How do I describe this?
(Crouching)
- Are you taking a dump? - No way.
(No way.)
(Why did you do that?)
I know!
(He knows.)
(There are only Ye Ri and Seul Gi left from Red Velvet.)
(If you're unlucky, you'll end up with 1 of these 3.)
I know!
"The pot calling the kettle black."
- Correct. - Yes.
(Kwang Soo is correct.)
- Finally. - There's only one left.
(Kwang Soo finally becomes a couple.)
- Hello. - How did you guess that?
My gosh.
(Are you watching, Joy?)
Now,
- there's only one couple left. - There's Seul Gi left.
It's Seul Gi.
Ready.
Set, go.
(Collapsing)
"Even if you die..."
(The name tag?)
- I know! - "He who leaves the fame..."
- I know! - I know!
- I know! - Jae Seok.
"There's always a way out if you keep your head on..."
I know!
(Let's go down together, partner in crime.)
- I know. - Jong Kook.
- "He who leaves the fame..." - I know.
"of good works after him does not die."
- Correct. - That's the answer?
Of course.
Good job.
She explained it well.
- You're the best. - So...
Jae Seok and Seok Jin are a couple.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin are a couple.)
What is this?
- You're the Team Middle Age. - You didn't answer correctly.
(These are the couples.)
We'll get started with "Couple Race on Olle Trails".
You cannot run. You can only power walk.
If you get two warnings, you're eliminated.
- Do we go together? - I think so.
(It looks like...)
(there's only Ji Hyo's locker left.)
(There are two thieves and only one Ji Hyo.)
(The result depends on Ji Hyo's locker room.)
(Which thief will steal Ji Hyo's clothes?)
(They get ready for the race.)
Ye Ri, I'm sorry...
- but everybody will attack us. - 10 seconds.
- Us? Why? - 10,
nine,
- eight, - They'll come at us for sure.
(He rushes her.)
I'm done today.
- Four, - Get ready.
- He's going down. - three, two,
- Let's go after him. - one.
(The chasing starts.)
- There's a mission. - He ran for a mission.
(They think Kwang Soo left for a mission.)
My goodness.
(Is that Kwang Soo?)
(He ran into a dead end.)
- You startled me. - My goodness.
- I feel so bad. - Leave me alone.
Please leave me alone.
You startled me.
(This must be your day.)
- What if I don't do anything? - I'm scared.
(Leave me alone.)
Is everybody here?
They are.
(Jong Kook's team is not around.)
Is there any other teams?
(The tiger eyes for its prey that's away from the others.)
All right.
What's going on?
(He lies in ambush.)
He's not very useful.
(The cameramen start moving.)
Kwang Soo's coming.
- Let's follow them. - There's somebody.
(Why is everybody moving away?)
(They exchange glances.)
- I saw his yellow hair. - She saw your yellow hair and face.
- He looks like a lion. - He saw your lion-like face.
- That's right, Kwang Soo. - Jong Kook.
- Hello. - Hi.
Help us.
Kwang Soo's having a mental breakdown.
- There's nothing he can do. - There's absolutely nothing.
He has to do something but everybody's watching him.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin are looking for a chance.)
What's going on with Haha?
We have to get started.
We have to rip their name tags.
(We have to look for a chance.)
- Should I start with the guys? - Sure.
What if we become allies, Kwang Soo?
(They join force to eliminate Jae Seok and Seok Jin.)
They're planning to get rid of us.
(They decide to eliminate Jae Seok and Seok Jin first.)
They're coming.
(It's a power walking race.)
Go for it, Jong Kook.
(Is he using the elevator?)
(These two are in trouble.)
(Let's use the elevator.)
(He can't face them by himself.)
(Where are the others?)
Run in immediately.
(He bumps into Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook is in the elevator.)
(They show up in front of Jong Kook.)
- No way. - Eliminate them.
(Kwang Soo joins in.)
- Jae Seok. - Yes.
- We ripped it. - This is no joke.
My gosh.
- Good luck, everybody. - Okay.
You're good.
- What should we do? - What if we join hands?
If we form allies and start eliminating one at a time...
- Hold on. - What's wrong?
- Why? - I'll just...
go upstairs and discuss with her.
- With whom? - Sorry?
- With her. - Why?
You must have something to do on the second floor.
- Why? - Do you think we're that easy?
Do you have to be on the second floor?
- Can you give me some time? - Why?
What's wrong with him?
"What's wrong with him?"
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Save us.
- Where are you going? - Kwang Soo.
- I'm sorry. - Don't go.
(Catch Kwang Soo.)
(They power walk.)
- Are you going to do this? - Don't.
- Stick your hand in. - Okay.
(He's cornered.)
You can't.
Please don't.
Move. You can't.
- Watch Irene. - This is no joke.
This is the right timing. Attack.
(Haha and Irene change their target to Jong Kook.)
- Rip it. - You can't.
(We're going to be the king.)
(Ripping)
Did you rip it?
(Jong Kook and Seul Gi are eliminated.)
- Rip it. - Ji Hyo.
I stopped Kwang Soo even when he was biting me.
(They are not listening.)
I can't trust anybody.
(Nobody is worth trusting.)
Hold on.
Everybody, please move.
What did I do? This week is not my special.
(Kwang Soo and Ye Ri are eliminated.)
- My gosh. - Are you all right?
- Oh, my goodness. - Her hair got ripped.
- Are you all right? - Yes, I am.
(2 teams are left.)
- I hope you all fail. - Good job.
(Only one team wins.)
(Only the winning team gets 30 points.)
- My gosh. - Good one.
Good job, Irene.
(It's Ji Hyo and Wendy versus Haha and Irene.)
You can't do this, Haha.
(Irene goes for it.)
No way.
Good job, Irene.
Just rip it off.
(Her hand reaches for the bracelet.)
- You can't. - Did you get it?
You did. Just grab it.
(Ji Hyo and Wendy are eliminated.)
I tried my best.
We won!
(Haha and Irene are the champions.)
Jeju Island Mission, "Couple Race on Olle Trails".
First place is Haha and Irene.
Really?
That wasn't nice.
It's time to let Red Velvet go.
- Why? - Why?
Do they have to go?
Yes.
- We're sad to let them go. - We like them so much.
We're sad to let them go.
Running Man members will head to Santorini.
- Santorini. - Santorini.
- That sounds good. - Greece.
- Thank you. - Let me use the restroom.
- Can we? - I need to go.
I'll quickly use the restroom.
(Jae Seok disappears.)
- See you later. - Thank you.
See you again.
That's Wendy.
- Thank you. - Really?
Thanks, guys.
(Kwang Soo is focused on the album.)
(Dashing)
(He's busy completing his mission.)
Hurry up, Kwon Ryeol.
(I'm coming.)
What number is it?
(Where's Ji Hyo's locker room?)
(He left Ji Hyo's locker key with Kwon Ryeol.)
Hurry.
I'm done if they see me.
Come out later. Be careful.
- Were you born in 1999? - Yes, I'm 19.
- You're still 19? - Yes, I am.
- When did you make your debut? - I was 17.
- When were you born? - In 1999.
She was born in 1999?
Yes, I was born in 1999.
I got married that year.
(Jae Seok is not returning from the restroom.)
Where's Jae Seok?
Jae Seok?
(He's anxious.)
Did the cameraman go with him?
(He doesn't have a good feeling.)
(Jae Seok has to get out of here as soon as possible.)
1770.
(Here it is.)
(Opening)
I feel like a real thief.
(This is quite thrilling.)
(This is like the story "Fairy and the Wood Cutter".)
I can't get caught while leaving.
(He goes to the restroom to search for Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok?
(Jae Seok is definitely up to something.)
I should go around.
(All he has to do is deliver the clothes.)
(Dashing)
(Here are Ji Hyo's clothes.)
Here they are.
Yes, that's all.
(He hands in Ji Hyo's clothes.)
(He can't let it happen.)
(He'll clear the mission only if he returns safely.)
(He's furious with Jae Seok.)
(What will happen to Jae Seok?)
(Kwang Soo misses him by a split second.)
Where's the women's locker room?
Isn't he here?
(He looks through the locker room only after the clothes go missing.)
(Jae Seok returns with confidence.)
Let's go.
- Did you wash your hair? - Let's go.
Wait a minute.
(They say goodbye to Red Velvet.)
What is it?
(Kwang Soo ran for nothing.)
My goodness, Kwang Soo.
What are you doing? Where were you?
Did you really go to the restroom?
(It's by the Mediterranean and full of sunlight.)
- My goodness. - Is this the place?
Why is it called Santorini?
It's quite hot in here.
Kwang Soo, sit where you're supposed to.
- That's right. - Take your assigned seating.
- Is it here? - Stand up.
He has his assigned seat.
- Is it here? I'll move. - Stand up.
Please have a seat.
- Have a seat, Kwang Soo. - I'll sit here.
- Where will you sit? - I don't know.
- Really? - There must be something here.
- There's nothing here. - Kwang Soo.
I feel bad for Kwang Soo today.
Poor Kwang Soo.
Everyone, it's been difficult for you.
- Now is the time to take a rest. - That's great.
- In Santorini, Greece, - Santorini...
there's a tradition of napping, which is called "siesta".
- I know what it is. - I'm sure you know.
They take a nap when it's the hottest during the day.
Since you're in Greece, you can take a "siesta".
- May we sleep? - Yes, you may.
Do we win the longer we stay here?
I'll tell you once you lie down.
- Kwang Soo is up to something. - Right.
He'll do something again.
(He's tired of defending himself.)
- It's comfortable. - Gosh, this is great.
- Please close your eyes. - Do we close them? Okay.
Something will happen.
- We must close them for Kwang Soo. - The first person...
Be quiet.
(Laughing)
- Please leave me alone. - Okay.
The first person to open their eyes...
will be eliminated.
It's time to meditate.
- Do we sleep? - Yes.
I wish Sistar would come during our "siesta".
(Tired from a demanding race, the members try to sleep.)
It's a good place to fall asleep.
(He gets up suddenly.)
(He waits for his chance.)
(Kwang Soo secretly goes to the locker room.)
(He hears something.)
(While being clueless, Kwang Soo goes to Ji Hyo's locker room.)
(He senses that Kwang Soo has left.)
They didn't say anything about not getting caught.
(He enters the women's locker room.)
I don't care if I get caught...
as long as it weighs a lot.
Kwang Soo is making us sleep because he didn't do enough.
Kwang Soo?
- Is Kwang Soo here? - He's not here.
He isn't.
He left.
He's being too obvious.
Seven.
(Everyone is sleeping in peace.)
(He finds Ji Hyo's locker.)
(The empty locker seems ominous.)
(It's completely empty.)
(It must be Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok already stole everything from Ji Hyo's locker.)
I'm doomed, aren't I?
(Yes, you're doomed.)
Doesn't Kwang Soo...
deserve some kind of punishment?
Just go back to sleep.
I'm so curious to find out.
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes and tell us.
I can't open them first.
- Are you sleeping, Seok Jin? - Seok Jin is good at this.
How amazing. Kwang Soo came back.
(Darn it.)
- Is that so? - Can he do that?
I just woke up.
Can he reappear like that?
He's trying to catch his breath.
(Laughing)
We can't let him do that.
Gosh, I'm doomed.
It's okay.
(Ruffling sounds)
Take a look over here.
I don't want to.
I'm not buying it.
I was so curious that I almost opened my eyes.
Who is it?
- Haha, you must see this. - Who is it?
Wait, what if it's someone famous?
- Is it a celebrity? - You must take a look.
(Oh, my!)
(Kwang Soo tries to trick the others.)
Whose voice is it?
(He opens his eyes.)
(What's going on?)
(It reads, "You're out.")
- Who is it? - Hello.
(Whoever opens their eyes is eliminated.)
- What's going on? - Who is it?
Jae Seok is eliminated.
You couldn't wait, could you?
Kwang Soo, you brat. Hey.
I did a good job.
This is the best thing I've done on this episode.
I thought he saw someone.
(Eliminating Jae Seok was the best thing he did.)
My goodness.
Jae Seok, please leave the room.
Is he leaving?
I should put the beds together.
Stop it. Stop it.
You can't make me look by stealing from me.
(He takes something out.)
(Where are my points?)
- Hey. - What's going on?
Come on, you can't do this.
Come on, don't take it.
Did he steal your points?
Hey.
(You stole Ji Hyo's clothes, too.)
(I'm taking you down with me.)
It's a big mess over here.
I feel like I'm being bewitched.
Don't touch that.
- I want to see what he's touching. - I'm curious.
- Don't touch that. - What is he touching?
Don't get fooled by what they're saying.
(Seok Jin talks too much.)
I won't open my eyes even if Jeon Do Yeon is here.
I'm serious.
(He spills something on him.)
(He forces Seok Jin to open his eyes.)
What's going on?
- Jae Seok. - What are you doing?
- Come on, he can't do that. - What happened?
(Haha wants to see what's going on.)
(Haha is eliminated.)
I'm nervous. Tell the ones who are out to leave.
- She opened her eyes. - She's out.
(She's also curious to see the fight.)
- What happened? - Jong Kook is the winner.
(Jong Kook wins.)
- He didn't open until the end. - It's incredible.
Open your eyes. Please go to the last course.
- It's the last. - There's another one?
Did Kwang Soo clear his mission?
- Only the last course remains. - What is it?
You may go home after you finish this.
(It's a chance for them to run away.)
Go home right away?
Change into your clothes and go back to where we opened the show.
We don't have clothes, do we?
(Look at Kwang Soo's face.)
- We don't have clothes. - Look at him.
His face completely changed.
No, I just didn't understand when he said we could go home.
Can we go home right after?
Please go to the locker room to get changed.
- What a surprise. - Yes.
I'll act surprised.
I'll act very surprised.
The cameras are following us to catch our being surprised.
(Everyone, I'll do better next time.)
(They head to the locker room.)
I will act surprised.
(They're ready for the last mission.)
I wonder what's waiting for us.
How should I act surprised?
(Jae Seok is very close to winning.)
It's locker number 1731.
(There's something inside.)
What is it?
- There's something here. - Kwang Soo.
(Jong Kook acts surprised.)
What is it? Goodness.
"Your clothes are stolen. One of the members stole them."
- "Within the time limit..." - "You must eliminate his name tag."
"If not, you'll return home with the clothes from the sauna."
"If the thieves are caught by the members..."
(What?)
(The thieves get their last mission.)
(They win if they protect their name tags for 15 minutes.)
(They must change into their clothes hidden on the second floor.)
No one is surprised at all.
(They must separate themselves from the others.)
Has Kwang Soo gone far?
Where's Kwang Soo?
(Kwang Soo goes to get changed.)
Where is Kwang Soo?
We're leaving together.
We're starting together.
I'm in trouble.
(It looks like Jae Seok is stuck with the other members.)
I'm speechless.
(I'll show you what hiding is about.)
The clothes...
They took the clothes.
Everybody.
You know, right?
We don't even have to mention it.
It's obvious.
This is funny. It made me laugh.
(He feels anxious while everybody's laughing.)
- This is too funny. - I'm speechless.
(They're relaxed.)
- This is too funny. - Silence.
Come on, Kwang Soo.
(He keeps acting.)
(Kwang Soo runs for his life.)
I'm in trouble.
Let's start hunting.
Where could he be?
If I were him, I'd go to the water park.
(Bingo)
Where am I?
Please.
Where do I go?
Where am I? Hold on.
Where am I? I have nowhere to run.
(Kwang Soo is here.)
I have to last only 15 minutes.
(Sliding)
(He decides to hide in the water slide for 15 minutes.)
We have to run if we see them.
Five, four...
(Would they be able to survive for 15 minutes?)
- This is easy. - One.
This is too easy.
("Catch the Thief" race starts now.)
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Kwang Soo stole our clothes.
- We have to catch him. - That's right.
I'm not surprised. We weren't even surprised.
- We only have 15 minutes. - That's why he took our clothes.
I think he went far.
I think he headed for the water park. I'll head that way.
(They start looking for him on the 1st and 2nd floors.)
He might be pretending to be a staff member.
- Right. That's what I thought. - He could be.
(Haha, Jong Kook, and Jae Seok look around the water park.)
(Do your best to hide well.)
This place is huge.
Where should I go to change?
I can't be here right now.
(Meanwhile, here's Kwang Soo.)
(He's right in the middle of the water slide.)
I don't know where the middle is.
The water slide...
Could he be stuck in the middle?
(Yes, that's possible.)
(Jong Kook's hunch is scary.)
Okay. I'll get through this.
(Haha approaches the slide.)
We're here. Where's...
(Whose voice is that?)
Don't shine the light that way.
(He's enraged.)
Do you want to die together?
(I found Kwang Soo.)
Hey.
(I can't do this alone.)
(Kwang Soo can't get caught already.)
Where are you?
(Startled)
Turn off the light.
What's wrong?
(Assistance arrives.)
He's in the slide.
- I thought so, too. - He's in the slide. I heard him.
(Kwang Soo's arrest is imminent.)
(This is his only chance to escape.)
Jae Seok.
(Did Jong Kook find out about my identity?)
Stay near the bottom of the slide.
(That was very close.)
They're moving.
(I can smell the thief close by.)
Turn off the light. Turn it off completely.
I'm sorry, viewers.
You can't see anything, right?
Give me a second.
Kwang Soo!
Turn off the camera. Turn it off.
Haha, go to the bottom.
Okay.
(It's a mop-up operation to catch Kwang Soo.)
(They seal the bottom, and Jong Kook will pressure him.)
I hope he gets caught here.
Somebody is trying to run away. He's running away.
Hey. What happened?
He's in here.
(They miss Kwang Soo by a whisker.)
Where did Jae Seok go?
I told him to be at the bottom.
(Jae Seok heads upstairs to get changed.)
This is too scary.
That was close.
That was so close.
- What happened? Is he gone? - He ran away.
- Did you see him? - He was inside the slide.
- Didn't you see him outside? - No.
He's in here.
(He's nervous.)
(Glancing)
(With 10 minutes left, Jae Seok finds his clothes.)
Close the door.
He wasn't near the top. He climbed from the bottom.
- We almost had him. - He might be here.
He probably panicked and just went in anywhere.
That was so close.
(You just wait.)
We almost had him.
(Where did he go?)
Kwang Soo is here!
Where? Where?
- Where? - He's in the water.
(They finally spot Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo!
I'm going to go down by myself.
(Jong Kook and Haha started inching in on him.)
(He slipped away with perfect timing.)
He's running away.
(He's careful and even removed his microphone.)
(I can't ruin today like this.)
It's cold.
(He left without a camera.)
Go away. Don't film me.
He's in the water.
- In the water? - He's in the water?
- The tube. - That way's faster.
- Where? - I'll corner him.
What are we supposed to do?
He's here.
(Here's the clothes thief.)
Hi, Kwang Soo.
- Don't come. It's really cold. - I think we have to go in.
(She doesn't care.)
(There's only 7 minutes left. There's no time to lose.)
(She's no joke.)
(He moves farther away. Would he manage to run again?)
(Here's Jong Kook.)
(Kwang Soo falls into danger.)
(Ripping)
(Sadly, he is eliminated.)
Why did you make me come in here?
(Justice prevails.)
Why did you steal everybody's clothes? Come here.
- Hey. - What's the time? We were close.
I don't have extra underwear.
It's five minutes before the race is over.
The race is not over yet.
(It's not over?)
(There's another thief...)
(who was plotting the perfect crime when nobody was looking.)
Kwon Ryeol.
They have no idea it's me...
so you should stay away.
(They had no idea Jae Seok was the thief.)
It's Jae Seok.
Everybody!
We're Running Man!
Let's do this!
(There's not much time left.)
(Jae Seok finds a hiding spot.)
(He's urgent.)
Don't film me.
(He tells Kwon Ryeol to stay away.)
(He hides underneath a stack of chairs.)
(He springs up.)
Don't film me.
(Jae Seok spent all day committing a perfect crime.)
(He can see the end of it.)
(Catch Jae Seok.)
Please.
I'm so nervous.
(Jong Kook approaches Jae Seok.)
(His gaze fixes on the chairs.)
(Is it Jong Kook? Please go on your way.)
(He stares in Jae Seok's direction.)
(Jong Kook can't look away for some reason.)
(Will Jong Kook spot Jae Seok?)
(He passes by.)
(He is 1m away from Jae Seok, but he passes by.)
(He hid well. Where did he hide?)
(I'm safe.)
I can't trust no one in this world.
(They've been betrayed. They start speeding up their search.)
(Wait! That's a familiar figure.)
(Kwon Ryeol, don't film me.)
(Thanks to Jae Seok, Kwon Ryeol started his Week.)
Hey.
Why didn't you follow Jae Seok?
- Pardon? - What are you doing here?
- I got hungry. - Forget that. Where is he?
Hey. Where is he?
You should be filming Jae Seok.
Would you like an egg?
Hold on. I think he might be around here.
If you're not with him...
(Kwon Ryeol, buy some time for me.)
He must be somewhere here.
Kwon Ryeol, you must be filming Jae Seok. What are you doing here?
There's a door here.
Hey. We might go home in this outfit.
I'm so mad.
(It's difficult to find his hideout since no one paid attention to him.)
Where would he be?
Jae Seok. You're seriously good.
(It can't be. Is Seok Jin's voice getting closer?)
(He's desperate. Please go away.)
(Will he be lucky and raid Jae Seok's hideout?)
(He holds his breath.)
(Jumping)
Could he be underneath this?
(As Seok Jin jumps, the pile of chairs shakes.)
What? There's a hat.
(Is he referring to this hat?)
(Smiling)
(He's caught.)
He's here. He's here!
(He faces the biggest crisis 30 seconds before it ends.)
Where?
(Haha and Ji Hyo join.)
Hold him.
He's here. What do you mean I should be quiet?
Come here!
- Come here. - I only have to hold out a minute.
- I just need a minute. - Hold him.
- Hold him. - This is it.
- I only need a minute. - We have only a minute left.
- It's less than a minute. - Hey. Move aside.
- It's not even a minute. - My goodness.
Quickly. Move in.
- In 1, 2... - Get him up.
In 1, 2...
One minute.
I got it.
(Time's up.)
Did it end?
- Is it over? - Is it?
Time's over.
(Jae Seok miraculously accomplishes his mission.)
We didn't get to remove it.
(They are disappointed. Is it really over?)
I'm so angry.
(This is the perfect crime.)
Do you know what he said when I found him?
"Quiet." Why would I keep quiet?
(The members were fooled the entire day.)
If he lies down on his back, I wouldn't have had any shot at it.
I made it.
Were you here all along?
I passed by and wondered if you were here.
- I looked at it. - You should've come here.
(Trudging)
- Kwang Soo. - Did you get his name tag?
Did you remove his name tag?
- No, I couldn't. Jae Seok hid well. - You look mad.
- I guess they were the thieves. - I'm sorry.
Kwang Soo, I am sorry.
(You took advantage of me?)
Kwang Soo, I am sorry. I apologize.
(The punishment for failing the mission will be revealed soon.)
Kwang Soo. I am sorry.
(The week of rest ends.)
It's been a while since I've done well after the spy episode.
(He's proud.)
(Slapping)
(Are you happy that you won?)
Kwang Soo helped him win.
- Seriously. - If you didn't do what you did...
I think I have to get a health check after the shoot.
- Why? - I've been so stressed out...
the entire day.
Today,
it was a week of rest.
Ji Hyo, who was the most well-rested member of all, has earned a trip...
- to South East Asia. - Really?
- Is this real? - I have?
- How can she be so lucky? - Are you serious?
The hidden race, "Steal Their Clothes",
- goes to Jae Seok. - You're right.
Congratulations.
- Isn't there a prize? - Is that it?
This is it.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
- Hold on. - Congratulations.
Congratulations.
I'm no match for him.
- Goodness. - What a performance.
Come on. Are you serious?
- Jae Seok is the winner of the day. - He's great.
We will return your clothes now.
Clothes only Kwang Soo stole will be returned.
(Since he lost the race, clothes only he stole will be returned.)
It's because he got caught.
- You stole my clothes. - Nice. I'll get my clothes.
(I almost had Jae Seok.)
I knew I only had to catch Kwang Soo.
Cross!
- I knew it. - This is making me so angry.
Seok Jin and Ji Hyo, who didn't retrieve their clothes,
will go home as they're dressed.
- We have our clothes! - Yes, we do!
Thank goodness we caught him!
Kwang Soo lost the race.
- Is there a punishment? - As it's the Year of the Rooster,
- we've prepared a rooster costume. - It's a rooster.
(It will catch everyone's eyes.)
(The rooster costume was made manually.)
- Where is it? - It's the red rooster!
It's a continuation of last year's monkey costume.
(In 2016, he started the Year of the Monkey with this outfit.)
(What sort of an eyesore will he present this year?)
It's the same one. Instead of monkeys, they are roosters.
Try the shoes on.
This is heavy.
(Even the shoes crow. Many roosters are on the costume.)
Look at that.
(Laughing)
(What kind of a punishment is this?)
- It's cute. - The roosters cry so weirdly.
(Seok Jin, Ji Hyo, and Kwang Soo go to a nearby train station.)
- This is so embarrassing. - It's embarrassing.
It's freezing.
- How can you be embarrassed? - Be quiet.
- I said to be quiet. - You're wearing a shirt and shorts.
People are starting to gather around us.
- It's a road. My goodness. - I'm starting to see people.
It's a road.
- They're starting to stare at us. - They're staring because of you.
- Try to keep quiet. - You should be quiet.
Let it go. I will give it to you later.
I will give it to you later.
- Ma'am. - Sir.
- Please take one. - It's for the Year of the Rooster.
- Take one please. - Here you go.
- You can take one. - Happy New Year.
You can just yank it out from him.
I will allow it. You can pull one out.
Hold on. What are you doing?
Wait. Why are you pulling it out?
Hold on. Why did you do that?
Let's cross here.
- You can take one. - It's for the Year of the Rooster.
Am I a display shelf?
(The Giving Tree, Kwang Soo, gives away roosters and receives love.)
Hold on.
(Pulling)
(He's willing to give everything.)
(He's embarrassed all of a sudden.)
It's freezing. We're almost there.
(Is the rooster crowing or is he crying?)
This is better.
(They've reached a nearby train station.)
We have arrived.
We are here. Can we go now?
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
I won't burgle anymore.
I didn't steal them...
- because I needed them. - Hey, you.
- Everyone. Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
All right. Let's hurry.
- I'm freezing. - I'm embarrassed.
(The members made the best out of the week of rest.)
This is Running Man's Member's Week.
(Member's Week)
(The 6th host is...)
(Yu Jae Seok.)
This is Jae Seok's Sports Day.
(We are Jae Seok's friends. We've been waiting for this day.)
(Lee Chun Hee, Heo Kyung Hwan, KCM)
(They are stronger and more determined than Jae Seok.)
(Their top-notch performance dominates the members.)
(And)
(What is the element of surprise behind their performance?)
(Jae Seok's Sports Day)