(2017 Running Man's Global Project)
(Dangerous Trip Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear)
(6 members were chosen to go to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(Running Man goes to Russia and Mongolia.)
(Team Mongolia must meet the nomads and milk their sheep.)
There is no milk.
(Team Mongolia fails the mission.)
(Team Russia must catch 10 types of seafood and king crab.)
(They catch 10 types of seafood and a small crab.)
(1 member can be exempted.)
(Haha is exempted from the trip to Japan.)
(Jong Kook, Haha, and Ji Hyo go to Yokohama.)
(They eat delicious food without knowing anything.)
(However)
(Based on Team Happy Trip's expenses, number of ghosts rises.)
(One member must enter the labyrinth alone.)
(Select a person who will go alone.)
(When one fails the mission, the name is added to the roulette.)
(Kwang Soo's name gets written on the roulette.)
(Kwang Soo's name takes 6 slots on the roulette.)
(Kwang Soo's consecutive failure fills up the roulette.)
(Fun times are over.)
(Finally, )
(they enter the labyrinth.)
(It's time to face the fear that makes your skin crawl.)
(Find the name tag and escape Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(Which 1 of the 5 members will enter the labyrinth alone?)
We've only been on the freeway and rest stops in Japan.
- It doesn't feel like Japan. - I'm so bored.
It's So Min's first time in Tokyo, but she didn't get to see any of it.
Is this Tokyo?
- Yes. - Is this how it is?
Doesn't it seem like Gyeongbu Expressway towards Anseong?
It does.
Isn't Tokyo fancy and full of skyscrapers?
Are we moving away from Tokyo?
That's correct.
Will we get to see Tokyo Tower?
- No. - That's impossible.
We'll only visit the unprecedented labyrinth.
It's called Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
It doesn't matter.
I got used to calling it by that name.
(They travel to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(They arrive in Yamanashi Prefecture.)
It's Mount Fuji.
- Can you see it? - That's amazing.
Look at that.
- That must be it. - It looks beautiful.
- That's Mount Fuji. - I haven't seen it before.
Is that snow on top?
It's permanent snow.
I didn't expect a mountain to be so beautiful.
(They must be near.)
I think we're almost there.
We get another mission when we arrive,
right?
(His name takes most of the roulette.)
Don't look forward to it.
Can I bring it to use it?
(Stay tuned.)
(Becoming a ghost after eating)
- It's beautiful. - It's amazing.
- It's beautiful. - It's incredible.
(They arrive at a restaurant to enjoy their last meal.)
As long as I avoid this time...
The person who gets picked will be it.
(What's the last mission?)
How about So Min?
It'll be fun if So Min gets picked.
How could you say that, Seok Jin?
All of you are so cruel.
It's only my hope.
We don't know what will happen.
Aren't I free to think what I want?
(He's being sensitive.)
Are you okay?
- Are you okay? - Stop pitying me. I'm fine.
- I'm okay. - You aren't angry, are you?
Give us the mission.
Everyone is getting sensitive as the time draws near.
That's true.
(The 5 members are getting very sensitive.)
(Which unlucky member will enter the labyrinth alone?)
Everyone.
This is the last stop before Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
It's a houtou restaurant where you get recharge.
It's similar to sujebi.
This is the last mission to determine the teams.
Okay.
It's on 10 slots of the roulette.
(10 roulette slots)
(10 roulette slots?)
Is it 10 slots per person?
It's 10 slots per person.
(This is the last mission.)
(Who will be the 2nd member of 10 slots?)
Let's go for Kwang Soo of 20 slots.
(She's very excited.)
Will it be Kwang Soo of 10 or 20 slots?
It can't be 10 slots.
Will it be 10 or 20?
The third mission is called...
Your Pass.
(The third mission is Your Pass.)
(Your Pass?)
You'll be given a total of four missions.
You pass every time you clear a mission.
(The one who passes survives.)
The last member to remain will come last.
(The last member to remain will be sacrificed.)
Here's the first mission.
We ordered three types of houtou.
This is the first mission.
The person closest to the dish that's served first passes.
(The person closest to the dish?)
- Kwang Soo has an advantage. - The food is usually...
served from the corner.
They could serve it at the center.
It's at the center.
Do we have to remain quiet?
This seat is advantageous.
Can we sit however we want?
(Can we sit however we want?)
(He points toward him.)
- It'll be the center. - You should stay still.
The food is served at the center.
I want that seat.
Does anyone want to switch seats?
I want to switch with Jae Seok.
I want his seat too.
That seat is the best.
Shall I switch?
(Considering feng shui...)
Do you want to switch, Seok Jin?
(Do you want to switch?)
If I were Seok Jin, I would.
I would too.
- Deal! - Really?
(They change seats.)
(Seok Jin sits at the innermost side and Jae Seok sits at the center.)
Be careful not to drop the spoons.
It's coming.
(Houtou is on its way.)
- It's here. Everyone be quiet. - Stay still.
- Put your hand down. - Put it down.
(Who will be the first lucky member?)
You'll be exempted if you're sitting the closest to the first dish.
- Can I come in? - Sure.
(She wonders where to put the dish.)
(After a mysterious hand gesture, )
(she walks toward the innermost side.)
(She walks past Jae Seok, who's sitting in the center.)
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
Well...
- Wait. - Excuse me.
- Why... - Be quiet already.
- Go ahead. - Everyone be quiet.
Thank you.
(The first dish is placed right in front of Seok Jin.)
I knew it.
(That was my seat a while ago.)
(Thank you, ma'am.)
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
(Seok Jin clears the mission.)
- Jae Seok, I was right. - Why did you change seats?
- Awesome. - I see you're getting irritated.
- Goodness. - Seok Jin's the first to clear it.
She didn't even look at Kwang Soo's side.
She didn't.
We'll move right onto the second mission.
- What is it? - Here it comes.
It's the mission for the rest.
The three orders of houtou have different meat inside.
- It's pork in the middle. - It has pork inside.
The one in front of Jae Seok has boar meat inside.
- It has boar inside? - Boar meat?
What kind of meat does the one in front of Seok Jin have?
Each of you will get a chance to speak.
- Can I take a look? - Shall I show them?
- Go ahead. - Show us.
- It's this. - What is that?
(It looks unfamiliar.)
(What on earth is that?)
- Isn't it fish? - No, it's not.
- I've never seen that before. - It looks strange.
(It has a big chunk of meat stuck to a tiny bone.)
- I think I know. - Jae Seok!
Go ahead.
It's Silkie.
(Jae Seok's guess is Silkie.)
Wrong!
- So Min! - I know the answer.
Who will guess first between you two?
- So Min said it first. - So Min, go ahead.
Hold on.
(He's suspicious of biased judgement.)
- Hold on. - Let's do it from the start then.
- So Min was faster. - It's obvious I said it first.
- You can't do this on purpose. - So Min was faster.
You have to shout your name to guess the answer.
- It's to make it less confusing. - He's right.
So Min.
I think it's chicken.
Her guess is...
wrong.
Kwang Soo.
(It's finally my turn.)
- It looks unfamiliar. - I've never seen it before.
- Isn't it fish? - No, it's not.
- I've never seen that before. - It looks strange.
(Judging by its tiny bone...)
- It's duck! - Duck?
(It may be duck meat!)
(Will desperate Kwang Soo guess it right?)
- It's duck! - Duck? It's wrong.
- So Min. - It's my turn now.
- Right, Se Chan. - Okay.
What is that?
- It's pheasant. - I think he's right.
It's wrong.
- Jae Seok! - So Min!
Jae Seok.
Maybe it's soft-shelled turtle.
(It looks similar to yongbongtang.)
(Is it soft-shelled turtle that's good for regaining your health?)
Maybe it's soft-shelled turtle.
- Soft-shelled turtle? - I don't think so.
It's soft-shelled turtle.
That's correct.
How did you know?
(Jae Seok's answer is correct.)
(It's soft-shelled turtle!)
- My goodness. - I can't eat this then.
My goodness.
- My gosh. - What made you think so?
I took a closer look...
and saw its arm.
(Shocked)
(He found its biceps.)
Are you serious?
(It's been a precious food ingredient since the past.)
- Really? - It's really soft-shelled turtle?
- But it's expensive. - Is that the arm?
- Look over there. - I can't believe you found that.
- How did you find that? - It's hard even knowing the answer.
- It's one of the most famous menus. - Really?
- I've never seen it before. - My gosh.
- Is this place famous? - It is.
It was sold out before we arrived at this restaurant,
but they have bear and fox meat as well.
- Fox meat? - Yes.
Anyway, I'm out.
(Jae Seok clears the second mission.)
(Joyful)
It's so annoying to see him like this.
(I get to avoid writing my name 10 times in the roulette.)
I was going to say it was crow meat.
Things are moving toward writing 20 of Kwang Soo's name.
(There are 3 people left with 2 more missions.)
Only the three of you remain.
One of your names will be written 10 times on the roulette.
So Min, Se Chan, and Kwang Soo.
They need to move onto the next mission.
So we'll put these three dishes in front of each of them.
(It's about the houtou? They don't have a good feeling about this.)
- It's for the mission. - So Min will...
- I'll have this pork houtou. - Se Chan, you take this.
- And Kwang Soo... - Wait, Jae Seok.
- Se Chan, you take this. - Wait, Jae Seok.
Hold on.
- I mean... - He's doing it on purpose again.
- He pushed what was next to me. - I just gave him the closest one.
Please pass this onto him. It's hot.
What's going on? It's unfair.
- Take your spoon and chopsticks. - Okay.
Maybe it's about eating quickly.
If this is really about eating...
- I... - It's either boning or eating.
Then let's draw lots.
(They decide to be fair.)
- Give me the chopsticks. - I like the idea.
- The short one, right? - Yes.
You get only one chance.
(They won't have a choice if they draw a short chopstick.)
(They must draw a fine chopstick to avoid eating soft-shelled turtle.)
Where is it? I closed my eyes.
- Here. - Okay, 1, 2...
(What will be Se Chan's choice?)
Three. Yes!
Kwang Soo!
(Se Chan avoids it.)
(Kwang Soo, I'm safe!)
Are you okay?
You just sounded very offensive.
No, I didn't.
- Yes! - Who will be the next?
Kwang Soo.
It's unpredictable. It totally depends on your luck.
I really don't want to go alone.
(Kwang Soo is afraid he might go to the Labyrinth alone.)
I really can't do it.
I might end up doing all my business there.
(He's now threatening the others.)
Go ahead and try it.
Don't you regret it after it happens.
Don't say things like, "How could you actually pee?"
- They have about 20 underwear. - I'm serious.
(Even the menu choice is so crucial to him.)
It's not the end yet.
I'm tearing up.
(What if the mission is about eating soft-shelled turtle?)
(It'll be advantageous for him only when he draws a regular chopstick.)
What will he draw?
- I can't watch it. - Raise a little higher.
- I can't stand watching it. - There you go.
- He picked 1. - It's 1 of the 2.
- He picked 1. - 1, 2...
(It's best to avoid unfamiliar food ingredients.)
(Who will be the one to take the soft-shelled turtle houtou?)
(Ta-da)
(He draws the shortest chopstick.)
(Kwang Soo gets to take the soft-shelled turtle houtou.)
(He must be cursed by an unlucky ghost for certain.)
How could you...
Perform an exorcism or something. How could you be this unlucky?
You're just...
- My goodness. - It's...
- It's so hilarious. - I mean,
he's so talented in things like this.
- Japanese ghosts must like him. - How could it go this way?
This wasn't planned.
Your name might really be written 20 times.
It'd be better for you to just volunteer to go then.
- 20 times. - Gosh.
- All right. - How could this happen?
It's still too early to give up. The third mission is very simple.
- He says it's simple. - We don't know what it's about yet.
Maybe it's about eating quickly.
You better not say gibberish.
(He warns the producer.)
- Eating quickly. - Then just eat quickly.
It won't be good for So Min either if that's the mission.
- Right. - Since she's the only female.
There are meat and noodles in each dish.
You'll clear it if you finish all the meat inside.
(Finish all the meat?)
(So it's about eating quickly. I knew it.)
Kwang Soo...
What is this, seriously?
(Why does it have to be you, soft-shelled turtle?)
I can't differentiate the meat from the bones.
- What is this? - Kwang Soo.
- What is this? - Poor Kwang Soo.
(So Min and Se Chan can eat with no problems.)
What is this? It's the neck.
How is it?
- You must know it's expensive. - It's really expensive.
(His hand shakes intensely.)
It's because you're scared, right?
- I can't even chew. - Are you done?
I'm done.
(Raising his hand)
- I can't even chew. - Are you done?
I'm done eating all the meat.
(He's done eating all the meat.)
We checked his dish,
- and he did finish his meat. - Okay!
(Se Chan is the 3rd person to clear the mission.)
(It's the battle between the two now.)
I can't go in alone.
- I really can't. - You have no choice.
I don't want to be on the front page of a newspaper.
I don't want them to write an article about my poop.
- Come on. - Hey.
(Don't you see we're eating now?)
- We're eating here. - Why would you bring that up?
I'm serious.
I'm really serious.
- That was too much. - We're still eating.
I don't understand why she had to bring that up.
I lost my appetite and was put off by her. This is crazy.
I just realized my dish's color is weird.
I'm serious.
(Will it be 10 names of So Min or 20 names of Kwang Soo?)
(Only the last mission is left. How will their fates turn out?)
This place is incredible.
(Team Happy Trip in the meantime)
"Yokohama".
(Every 20 dollars they spend during their trip...)
(will lead to one more ghost in the Labyrinth.)
(Without knowing the rule, they focus on taking pictures.)
(Sorry, Team Scary Trip, but we're having a great time.)
You don't have to try doing anything.
- You just come here and relax. - Come catch me.
(Try catching me.)
Come catch me.
(How about we play this game?)
Do you want to die?
- Come on. - You're dead meat if I catch you.
- People play this at the park. - Right.
To be honest, I haven't seen anyone do that at a park.
Haha, you are old enough to know it. Don't pretend otherwise.
Only a few people do it at the beach.
(Kicking)
Catch me if you can!
For goodness' sake.
Why would you play that game at a park?
You are dead when I catch you.
(She risks her life to play a game of tag with Jong Kook.)
(They arrive at a shopping center.)
How pretty.
(This is fun.)
(What should I buy?)
(They enjoy their unlimited amount of money.)
These shorts are nice.
This is great.
Where should we go next?
Let's eat meat with enjoyment.
(They feast on wagyu, the delicacy of Japan.)
(Well-marbled wagyu makes them salivate.)
This is high-quality.
(They lock in the juice by grilling the surface on a hot stone.)
- You can eat that piece. - Really?
(The perfect piece of meat fills the mouth with juice.)
(It's really tasty.)
It's so soft that it doesn't feel like meat.
(He savors the meat.)
It's so soft.
(The delicacy results in more ghosts in Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(We are sorry for spending a lot of money.)
(Team Scary Trip doesn't know this.)
While you eat, you will take part in the last mission...
that involves 10 slots.
So Min and Kwang Soo,
please remove your name tag on your back...
and put it on the table.
You startled me.
Remove your name tag, not each other's.
- You startled me. - Put it on the table.
We will ask the employee of this restaurant to come in...
and pick a name tag he or she likes.
This is...
The person whose name tag is picked will receive 10 slots.
This is bad.
We will order another glass of Coke...
and ask the employee to choose a name tag.
(In this crucial moment...)
(Farting)
(Did someone fart?)
(What was that noise?)
What was that?
(Did someone really fart?)
(Farting)
- What was that? - What is Seok Jin doing?
I can't believe him. Wait a minute.
- Wait a minute. - You heard it, right?
He should get a slot.
(He's ill-mannered.)
- He farted. - He farted.
Seriously.
What do you think you are doing?
What was that? What happened?
- What do you think you are doing? - My goodness.
I thought it was a frog.
I thought there was a frog behind me.
(Seok Jin becomes a frog during a meal in Japan.)
(There is a frog inside me.)
- I thought it was a frog. - What do you think you are doing?
What was that?
It's bad if the employee takes your name tag.
Is it good if the employee takes your name tag?
- It's bad. - It's bad.
The person whose name tag is taken will place last.
Should the penalty go to the one with a remaining name tag?
- The one with a remaining name tag. - The one with a taken name tag.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors. Rock-paper-scissors.
(The winner will decide.)
(So Min wins.)
The penalty should go to the one with a remaining name tag.
(The person whose name tag is chosen will pass.)
The server is here.
- Is the server here? - Yes.
Excuse me.
(The server is here.)
- Thank you very much. - Excuse me.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Please pick one name tag.
- Please choose one. - One name tag.
- You can choose one. - Okay.
One. Okay.
- Choose the one you like. - It's good to be chosen, right?
(The final rule)
(She holds two people's fate.)
(Please pick a name tag.)
(Grabbing)
(I am saved.)
(Kwang Soo lost the war of 10 slots in a roulette.)
(It looks like I am cursed.)
Kwang Soo is so unlucky.
(Kwang Soo will have 20 slots.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Kwang Soo. - Thank you.
(I can't believe it.)
Because she didn't know what we were doing,
she had no qualms about choosing one.
"Do you want me to pick one?"
Would you be okay?
- He is so unlucky. - Thus,
Kwang Soo will fill in 20 more slots with 10 additional ones.
- Firstly... - I am filling the slots...
with Kwang Soo's name.
20 slots out of 24 slots have Kwang Soo's name.
It will be incredible if someone with a single slot gets chosen.
You are the master of bad luck.
(Spinning)
(Should I spin it for fun?)
Yu Jae Seok.
(Yu Jae Seok)
- Yu Jae Seok. - Yu Jae Seok.
We don't know what will happen.
- We don't know what will happen. - I won't lose hope until the end.
I won't lose hope until the end. I won't give up.
(Will it happen again?)
- That startled me. - Jeon So Min.
- Jeon So Min. - Jeon So Min.
- We don't know what will happen. - Seriously.
We don't know what will happen.
(So Min gets picked this time.)
- We don't know what will happen. - Seriously.
- We don't know what will happen. - How did this happen?
(The 5 unlucky members made a scary game of roulette.)
- We don't know what will happen. - Seriously.
- We don't know what will happen. - What is going on?
Every slot belongs to Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo.
(Lee Kwang Soo is chosen this time.)
(Disappointed)
- Out of three rounds... - He was chosen once.
He was chosen once.
Kwang Soo was chosen twice.
It's Lee Kwang Soo. That makes sense.
Almost every slot has his name.
Our names are hardly visible.
- We don't know what will happen. - It's Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo.
- This is too much. - Lee Kwang Soo.
Lee Kwang Soo...
is an unlucky name.
- My grandfather named me. - I'm sorry.
- It's unlucky on the roulette. - It's a name I have to live with.
I meant that it's unlucky on the roulette.
If there is a way...
It looks like you found your appetite.
(The last match made her forget her hunger.)
So Min.
I am sorry, Kwang Soo.
You received a penalty because of a change in the rule.
Your name tag was left behind.
The original rule was different.
The penalty was originally for the one with a taken name tag.
You should have left the rule as it was.
Why did you change it?
It doesn't help.
I sat still without doing anything.
I even lost in the round of rock-paper-scissors.
I didn't get to choose the rule.
- I sat still. - That's your problem.
Why did you sit still? Confront your fate.
Confront your fate like me.
Fight.
- Win. - For goodness' sake.
I confronted my fate, fought and won.
- I am so annoyed. - You are too passive.
That's his problem.
I am so annoyed that they are telling me those things.
(Lee Kwang Soo, the unlucky man in Tokyo)
So Min, you offered to take a slot from Kwang Soo earlier.
Did I?
I remember that.
You offered to take a slot for a bracelet he gave you.
- You offered to take a slot. - When did I do that?
(Will she take a slot?)
- When did I do that? - She is acting again.
- She is shameless. - You won't take a single slot.
I can't believe you.
I will write my name on one of your slots.
- Will you do that? - I will take three slots...
if you win in three rounds of rock-paper-scissors.
- Really? - Three slots?
Are you offering to write your name in three of his slots?
- I will do that if you win... - Rock-paper-scissors?
In three consecutive rounds of rock-paper-scissors.
Don't give me that nonsense.
I haven't won in rock-paper-scissors once...
- in the entire day. - Kwang Soo.
- Fight against your fate. - Fight.
- Otherwise, you will fall back. - Kwang Soo.
If you lose in all three rounds, write your name in my slot.
- If you win in all three rounds... - If I lose in all three rounds?
Yes. If you win a round,
I will take a slot.
(If Kwang Soo wins a round, So Min will take a slot from him.)
I will take three slots.
- Really? - Three slots?
Are you offering to write your name in three of his slots?
(If Kwang Soo wins all 3 rounds, 3 slots will go to So Min.)
There is no way I will lose in all three rounds.
Winning in all three rounds will be equally hard.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay. - He is doing well.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - That's good.
Let's go.
(The real game starts.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(What will be the result of the first round?)
(Kwang Soo wins.)
Okay. Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins again.)
Rock-paper-scissors. Okay.
Wait a minute.
(What is going on?)
(Kwang Soo charges like a storm and takes 2 wins in a row.)
- One slot goes to So Min. - That's right.
One slot goes to So Min.
- Shall we clear the table first? - Shall we do that?
(The final match will decide who gets Solo Tour Card.)
- All right. - Thank you for the bracelet.
All right.
(Kwang Soo is desperate to get rid of 3 slots.)
(The last round will decide who gets 3 slots.)
Kwang Soo has nothing to lose.
That's right.
It's his chance to walk on the flowery road.
Let me win a round. Kwang Soo.
Will you play rock or scissors?
- What will you play? - What?
I am sorry. I am not good at that.
- Stop it. - What will you play?
Kwang Soo, what will you play?
- Rock. - Rock?
- Will you play rock? - Yes. Rock.
(Really?)
(3 slots depend on this round.)
(Who will be the winner of the last round?)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min wins.)
(I hate myself.)
(I won!)
I can't believe he played scissors.
For goodness' sake.
We can't help him in any way.
I will take a slot.
- One slot goes to So Min. - Thank you, So Min.
(It's still beneficial to Kwang Soo.)
If that slot gets chosen,
- it will be incredible. - It will be uncanny.
If that slot gets chosen, it will be incredible.
- I think it'll get stuck here. - No, it won't.
- I think it'll get stuck there. - Thank you, So Min.
- It'll stop here. - Thank you so much.
It's heavier there.
(What are their fates?)
(It's getting dark.)
It's getting late.
I'm getting even more worried.
I shouldn't drink too much water.
You'll want to go to the bathroom.
(Kwang Soo and So Min are more worried than the others.)
There won't be any bathroom.
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo and So Min are more worried than the others.)
- My goodness. - It'll be so scary.
(Finally)
- Are we here? - Are we here?
(They arrive at Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(They'll enter the labyrinth soon.)
- My goodness. - The camera can't film it all.
You'll say all kinds of swear words in there.
We shouldn't. We're shooting.
You will.
(You will say swear words before anyone else.)
You'll only hear beeps.
My goodness.
(This place makes you say all the swear words you know.)
What is this sound?
Are they rehearsing?
Is it a rehearsal?
It'll be finished soon.
- Is it a rehearsal? - What was that sound? Who is that?
- Who said a swear word? - Did he just say a swear word?
Was it a staff member?
- My goodness. - Who was that?
We're doomed.
Staff members don't usually say swear words.
- Someone said swear words. - Someone swore in Korean.
- Who was that? - It's our staff member.
- Gosh! - Oh, my.
- Who is it? - What are you doing?
Who are you?
(They're even startled by a floor director.)
All right. Let's go.
- Sorry? - Let's go.
(Finally)
My goodness.
- I don't want to go in. - So Min, don't lag behind.
Come to the front.
Look at that.
(I miss my mom.)
What's with that blue light?
- Gosh. - What's that?
(It is located in Yamanashi and takes 50 minutes to go through.)
(Many people have witnessed ghosts in the labyrinth.)
(It's been introduced many times on Japanese television.)
The employees here have a memorial service every morning.
- Really? - They do?
Why?
This is where they hold memorial services.
Why do they do that?
It's for the ghosts living here.
- It looks so creepy. - It looks scary.
My goodness.
This is not just a set.
All right.
The grand finale of Running Man's Global Project.
Welcome to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
(Welcome...)
(to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
How do you feel to finally be here?
What do you think?
What answer are you expecting?
Do you want me to kick you?
As I told you earlier today,
the expenditure of Team Happy Trip...
was supposed to determine the number of the ghosts.
As the other team spent a huge amount of money,
it's been decided that you will see all the ghosts they have.
(All the ghosts)
- All of them? - Yes.
Haha is unbelievable.
- Gosh. - What should we do?
Alone...
(For now, they can only imagine.)
(The horror will become real in a short while.)
(The maximum horror)
(It's never been worse.)
Please.
(This place is included in the Guinness World Records.)
(They will soon learn why.)
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, Haha, thank you so much.)
Before you enter,
we will turn the roulette wheel.
- What should I do? - It will determine who will...
(The roulette will determine who will enter the labyrinth alone.)
It will determine who will go through the place alone.
Gosh, it's here.
- We've been turning it all day. - It's real now.
- It's on for real. - It's real now.
- It's real now. - It is.
I'll work hard.
I mean it.
(Kwang Soo has a 80-percent chance.)
My goodness.
Kwang Soo.
(He is pretending to feel sick.)
Stop pretending.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
He's pulling his tongue in.
Why are you rolling your tongue in?
I seriously feel sick.
- Me too. - I feel sick.
I have neutral fat, I mean, visceral fat.
Neutral fats?
I'm not in a good condition.
(I have the worst condition here.)
Hey.
Why do I have a bad feeling?
You can't even find other names than mine there.
(Kwang Soo's name is written in 19 slots.)
Please decide who will turn the wheel.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan win.)
You might get to turn the wheel.
What's the point of winning now?
(The only reward is turning the wheel himself.)
What's the point?
He practiced so much.
It doesn't matter. Of course, if you enter alone, it'll be scarier...
What is it?
What happened?
Do you think you will enter alone?
I don't want to go in there.
(I don't want to go in there.)
Do you think we do?
- Why did you do that so suddenly? - Hey!
You will be punished for this.
(You will be punished for this.)
- Why are you doing this? - So Min is crying.
- So Min just cursed you. - Why do you curse me?
- She cursed you. - Don't do this.
Let's just get it over with and go home.
- Let's do this. - You guys don't say anything.
(How can you say that in front of me?)
Don't say that in front of me.
(Do you know how much I want to cry right now?)
You brats...
- What did you just say? - I'm sorry.
- I want to go home. - I'm sorry.
Let's get it over with.
Let's get it over with and go home.
This is too much.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(The roulette wheel...)
(will be turned by Se Chan.)
- Kwang Soo lost. - Se Chan will...
- turn the wheel. - Why did I win?
I don't want to decide the result.
(Kwang Soo's fate is now in Se Chan's hands.)
(The roulette wheel will be turned.)
- Se Chan. - Yes.
The wheel has to turn at least five times.
- I'll turn it hard. - Are you doing this?
- Will this decide the result? - Let me practice first.
Don't practice. Just do it.
- Just do it. - Don't practice.
Turn it hard. Do it right.
- Turn it. - Challenge.
- Here we go. - Turn it.
1, 2, and 3.
Challenge.
(Who...)
(will...)
- Challenge. - This will decide.
(Who will enter the labyrinth alone?)
1, 2, and 3.
- Challenge. - This will decide.
(Kwang Soo will enter alone.)
- Oh, my. - That was close.
- Gosh. - Seriously.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Gosh.
- I was so surprised. - Thank you.
I was so surprised.
So Min, Jae Seok, Se Chan, Seok Jin...
They were all here.
- They were all here. - Gosh.
Please let me turn the wheel.
Please, give me some hope.
Just once.
Kwang Soo, you can't...
(Bowing)
(I beg you.)
- Just once. - Kwang Soo.
(The other members bow to him too.)
I won't ask for anything more. Just once.
- Kwang Soo. - Just once.
(You have to fall for me to survive.)
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - We can't help it.
- We have no choice. - Kwang Soo.
Please let me turn it once.
If it's you again,
will you go in without any cameramen?
(Will you go in without any cameramen?)
It has to benefit us somehow.
- Look at his smile. - He loves that idea.
How can you do this to me?
It has to benefit us.
We can't keep giving you more chances.
Then...
I think you should just go.
(Jae Seok turned the wheel for fun.)
It's Se Chan.
(Se Chan is chosen.)
- It's Se Chan. - Se Chan.
- Okay. - Thank goodness.
(There is hope.)
What do you mean?
Give me another chance.
- I won't say anything more. - If it's you again,
- don't say anything more. - Okay.
- Just once. - Go ahead.
Okay. I don't want to play dirty either.
- Turn it. - I don't usually do this.
I mean it. Here I go.
It's the other side.
(Kwang Soo gets the last chance.)
Start within 3 seconds. 5...
Challenge.
(The last chance)
(There is a high chance Kwang Soo will be chosen again.)
(The chance is 19 out of 24.)
(That's 79.17 percent.)
(Will the fate...)
(turn its back on Kwang Soo again?)
(It stops.)
(Lee Kwang Soo)
It's the same slot.
What is this?
- Thank you. - What is this?
That was close.
- So Min, - That's a relief.
- it was really close. - I'm so relieved.
We're all entering the place anyway.
Kwang Soo, you can't help it.
- We're all going in. - My heart...
My heart is...
So Min, that was close.
It's been decided that...
Kwang Soo will enter alone.
(I'm entering the place alone.)
Unbelievable.
(Jae Seok and So Min, Seok Jin and Se Chan)
(Kwang Soo goes alone.)
So Min, take good care of Jae Seok.
I'll take care of Seok Jin.
So Min, I'm so scared.
I really don't want to go in.
Kwang Soo, you'll be possessed if you go there.
I mean it.
I hate you, Running Man crew.
(They all get serious as they are about to face the horror.)
- I hate this. - Everyone.
You might enter the place and just run through the whole house.
That's why there's another mission.
(It's a special mission for them to maximize their experience.)
There are three name tags including the cameraman's in the place.
- There are three name tags. - What is he saying now?
- Why is there the cameraman's? - What did you just say?
You have to find 1 of 3 name tags.
The exit door will open when you show the gatekeeper the name tag.
Whoever finds his or her name tag first can escape the place first.
(They can escape the place separately.)
- We can escape separately? - What did you say?
How can we do that? We should get out all together.
- Excuse me. What about me? - Jae Seok.
(If the cameraman leaves, he will really be alone.)
He ditched me when we were at the deserted school.
(Yoon Sang left Kwang Soo alone during another scary special.)
What am I going to do?
Now, let's go through the gate and put on necessary equipment.
- We need equipment? - After that, we'll go in.
Let's head in.
(They finally enter.)
(They enter the final destination of the Dangerous Trip at last.)
- I am about to lose it. - Look at the iron gate.
Something is on top of the gate.
It's a head.
(They are already scared.)
- There's a head on top of it. - We are in big trouble.
I can't handle this.
(Sighing)
- I don't know anymore. - I can't...
- I can't do this. I'm serious. - I'm about to go crazy.
I don't feel good already.
(I want to go to the toilet already.)
Please give them the helmets.
(Jae Seok and So Min get ready in order to enter the place.)
(He lets out a sigh.)
(Kwang Soo seems serious.)
You are not going in there, are you?
- I already experienced it. - You did?
- How was it? - Look. I can't stand straight now.
(He can't stand up after his experience.)
Oh, my. It's scary, isn't it?
- I'm drenched in sweat. - Really?
(I am not joking.)
- Why are you trying to scare us? - Hey.
Why are you trying to get us worked up? We are already scared to death.
I am not kidding with you. I mean it.
He's not lying.
I've never been to a place like this before.
(He has never gone to a place as horrendous as here before.)
When I was listening to him, I was about to kick him in the side.
(It could have been a disaster.)
(Kwang Soo, good luck.)
(He's pale.)
All right then. The first pair...
(Everything is set.)
Jae Seok, So Min,
and the cameramen for this pair will go in now.
(The door of Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear finally creaks open.)
- So Min, - What are they doing?
It smells weird here.
You're right. I smell medicine. I can smell disinfectants.
That's right.
It's a medicinal smell.
We are in big trouble.
- It's a strong smell. - The medicinal smell is strong.
(They can't seem to start.)
- Good luck. - Jae Seok, what are we going to do?
(Hesitant)
(The start of the longest journey that takes up the most time)
(They take the first step forward.)
Gosh, this is so eerie.
(He turns back right away.)
So Min, this feels eerie.
Go in. You can't waste time here.
Come on. Go inside.
Don't look at us.
- This is so scary. - Hey.
(They enter again after a lame excuse.)
So Min, come here.
So Min, you can hold my arm.
(Let's do this.)
(It's too dark in here.)
So Min, we have no choice.
- Gosh, I can hear the music. - They went in.
(The horror of the place isn't factitious, but rather realistic.)
I'm so scared.
I'm really scared. Gosh, that startled me.
Me too. I'm scared to death too. This isn't a joke.
(The Labyrinth overwhelms them and forces them to be on alert.)
What are we going to do?
(From outside, they can only hear sounds.)
Their voices are even scarier.
- Hold on. - Come this way.
Wait.
- Hey, what are you doing? - This is...
- I can't wear the helmet. - Why can't you?
I'm sorry, but we had the helmet on.
It's scary, but the problem is that it keeps...
coming down no matter how well I put it on.
- My face won't be shown. - I can't see with this either.
It really does.
- Then return the helmets. - Can we do that?
We will film you with the installed cameras inside and the cameramen.
You came out because you were scared, right?
- To be honest, it's really scary. - It's really scary.
- It really is. - I'm about to go crazy.
- I can't move my feet. - I can't move forward.
- Go and come back quickly. - Hey, show us the power of Korea.
(Se Chan speaks out of the blue.)
How is that pertinent to this?
"Power of Korea"?
Show what a Korean man can do.
(It's the power of a coward.)
This is no joke.
- Should we walk quickly? - No.
We have to find the name tags.
Be careful.
(Sighing)
- Goodness. - That startled me.
(This is how dark it is.)
- Didn't you hear a noise just now? - What? My gosh.
(It's too dark for them to navigate.)
- So Min, what do we do? - What are we going to do?
Jae Seok, how are we going to do this?
I'm easily scared, but you're scaring me even more.
(We have to go through there, right?)
This is insane.
(They only walked 3m, but it feels as if they walked longer.)
Wait. I can't pass through here. Jae Seok, I can't go there.
- Hey. - I think someone will pop up.
So Min, standing here won't do us any good.
Don't you know that I'm scared too?
(The scariness of the place is more realistic than the reality.)
What if someone just pops up now?
(They take one step at a time.)
- Oh, my! - Oh, my goodness.
- Why did you scream? - You scared me.
Why are you screaming?
Kwon Ryeol, come on.
(These sounds scare the members waiting outside.)
Shouldn't we go in there?
We have to find our name tags.
(Gosh, I am exhausted.)
(Jae Seok and So Min have just gotten past the entrance.)
(Grabbing)
Why are your hands so cold?
They are like ice.
(In this mysterious space, there are no signs of others except them.)
(He gets scared by himself.)
You startled me.
(They have a long and scary way ahead of them.)
- Shoot. - Why are you doing that?
You scared me.
- Why are you doing this? - What's the matter?
Kwon Ryeol, stop being scared.
Hey, you shouldn't.
(It feels like a ghost is accompanying them.)
Keep an eye out for the name tags.
They wouldn't have put it inside the room. I'd be able to see it, right?
It's dark. It's so dark in here.
It's pitch dark.
(They enter the prop room full of frightening materials.)
- I can't go in there. - Something's going to be in it.
- I can't walk in there. - This is...
It's completely dark in there.
This is impossible.
(They can't take a step forward from where they are standing.)
- It's completely dark in there. - This is impossible.
Oh, my goodness!
(Screaming)
- Oh, no. - Goodness.
That was so scary.
(In an instant, it becomes a place of wailing.)
- Hold on. Let's hurry. - This is insane.
(The real wailing has begun.)
They are scared now.
That must have horrified them.
Please turn it off.
- Please turn it off. - Please.
- We don't want to listen to it. - We're sorry. Please turn it off.
(We want to rest for the remaining time.)
- Why are you doing this to us? - Let's just hurry.
Please stop. That's enough.
Hold on.
- Wait. - Goodness.
That really scared me to death.
(You scared us even more.)
Jae Seok, hold on a moment.
- So Min, wait. - I want to get this over with.
- Oh, my. - Okay. I got it.
I'm scared even more because of you.
- So Min, don't cry. - That really did a number on me.
Please don't cry.
- I was so shocked. - Please don't.
(She starts crying within 5 minutes.)
Jae Seok, it's too dark over there.
(Kwon Ryeol and So Min maximize the horror of the Labyrinth.)
There's a sound coming from there. I don't think I can go there.
That really scared me.
The ghost did the job, but why didn't they leave?
(The ghosts are fully dedicated.)
- What if you cry again over there? - It was so scary.
- What am I going to do if you cry? - I can't handle this.
(They hear a sound again.)
There's a sound coming from there.
- What am I going to do? - Hey, go check it out.
You want me to go there alone?
A sound is coming from there. Come on. Go and see what it is.
(The reason why they are hesitant to go is because...)
(an operating room full of surgical tools is before their eyes.)
(They muster up the courage and make stealthy footsteps.)
What is this sound?
What should we do?
There it is. There is a name tag.
(Did they find a name tag in the operating room?)
- It's right there. Look over there. - Where is it?
It's Kwon Ryeol's.
Seriously? Why does it have to be his?
(What? It's mine?)
You should go get it since it's yours. Hurry.
(The four of them set foot in the operating room.)
What are we going to do?
(This room is the scariest of all. They get serious.)
(A name tag is placed.)
- I'm about to lose my senses. - I keep hearing the sound.
Hey, this is Kwon Ryeol's.
(Kwon Ryeol is the 1st one to obtain the name tag.)
- Kwon Ryeol, don't go out. - Don't go out by yourself.
The exit is that way. You have to go through the exit.
(He exerts all of his strength to take the name tag.)
- You should go through the exit. - I'll hold onto it for you.
No, I'll hold it.
(Let's not trust him. We should hurry and find our name tags too.)
Where is my name tag?
(Sniffling)
Goodness, I want to cry.
- My goodness. - Where's my name tag?
I have to find it.
From where are they coming out?
(Every corner is dark and suspicious.)
I don't know whether it's a person or not.
Gosh, here's my name tag.
(So Min finds her name tag.)
(She finally smiles after finding her name tag.)
(They're scared out of their wits.)
(You must stay alert at all times.)
- Goodness. - I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
I didn't know this would happen suddenly.
I'm sorry. Wait.
Wait a minute.
That was so sudden.
He should have said something.
- Stop crying. - Jae Seok.
Come on, stop crying.
- Stop crying. - It was too sudden.
I was shocked.
Why does he keep following us? Wasn't once enough?
- Someone stepped on my toes. - Gosh, I was scared.
- I'll go quickly. - Wait.
- Are you serious? - I'm leaving.
How could you?
(You're a traitor.)
I have to leave now.
(She's too scared to move.)
Do you know there are many ghosts where it's crowded?
(He's too exhausted to respond.)
I'm serious.
You can't enter there alone.
- You can't leave alone. - I know.
How could anyone go there alone?
It's the worst for Kwang Soo.
The cameramen went inside to take a look around.
There's one cameraman who refused to enter.
- Who was it? - It was Yoon Sang.
(He's Kwang Soo's designated cameraman.)
Can I have a different cameraman?
(Switch to a cameraman whom I can trust.)
Where is Yoon Sang?
Yoon Sang?
- Where is he? - Yoon Sang.
Did he run away?
Choi Yoon Sang.
He's gone.
Isn't this his camera?
(He left his camera.)
Where is he?
(What's going on?)
Where did that punk go?
(What will happen to Kwang Soo?)
What is that sound?
What's that sound?
(Is it the sound of a baby crying?)
(It's time to pass the patient's room.)
What's that sound?
My goodness.
(The silence feels eerie.)
Please let us pass.
(He begs the ghosts.)
What's going on? What's that?
I think your name tag is inside.
Where?
- It's inside. - Where?
There's your name tag.
(They find someone's name tag.)
- Where is it? - It's inside.
(Screaming)
What's this?
There's a name tag inside.
Why is it inside?
- Your name tag is inside. - So Min.
Your name tag is inside.
(Mommy said we need to find our name tags.)
It's inside.
- It's inside. - I can't go.
You must take your name tag.
Stop crying.
Your name tag is inside, but the bed is moving.
The bed inside is moving.
How will you take your name tag? You need it.
I don't know whose it is.
It's Se Chan's. Let's pass.
- They found yours. - They found mine.
It's somewhere visible.
It's Se Chan's.
Let's hide his name tag.
(Let's hide it somewhere deep.)
- What? - Let's hide it.
Hide his name tag?
(She's still sly.)
- She said to hide yours. - What?
- So Min said that. - What's wrong with her?
My goodness.
- Where's Se Chan's? - How about...
My goodness. There's no one here.
That startled me.
(She makes sure to take care of the name tag.)
I hid it.
(When will they get to leave?)
- Gosh. - Where do we have to go?
- Come this way. - We should go this way.
- No. - There's an arrow.
- We have to go in. - It's too narrow.
What's going on here?
What do we do?
What is this?
- Gosh. - Goodness.
Where are you filming? Why are you looking away?
- Jae Seok. - What on earth are you doing?
(Screaming)
Oh, my goodness.
(Sighing)
How can you film like that?
Kwon Ryeol should go in first.
- Come on. - You go in first.
You should lead at least once.
- Just this once. - I'm supposed to follow.
Come on, Kwon Ryeol.
Why are you sweating so much, Jae Seok?
I'm so scared right now.
What should we do? I'm about to lose it.
(It's more difficult for those who are waiting.)
(A baby crying)
Is that a baby crying?
A baby's crying?
(It's a cry full of resentment.)
- I thought it was a cat. - Can you turn it off?
- Until when do we have to listen? - Please stop.
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
(She screams out her apologies.)
(What is going on inside the Labyrinth?)
I have a sore throat from screaming.
(They finally leave the operating room.)
(They can't get used to the fear.)
This is so scary.
- Gosh, it's a bed. - My goodness.
I'm sweating so much.
(Where is Jae Seok's name tag?)
My goodness.
(They are frightened again.)
(Kwon Ryeol runs away.)
- I'm so sorry. - Gosh.
Please don't do this, sir.
- I'm so sorry, sir. - Please don't do this.
- Please. - I didn't do it.
Please don't do this. I'm sorry.
Please stop it.
(They run away.)
(Kwon Ryeol speaks gibberish.)
Hurry up.
(Kwon Ryeol loses them.)
Come here now. Hurry up.
My goodness.
(Kwon Ryeol doesn't come, and So Min is crying.)
Why is the man following us all the way here?
- Please stop it. - Please.
- Please don't come near us. - Kwon Ryeol.
- Come here. - I'm serious.
Where are you going?
- Kwon Ryeol. - Hey.
(This is real Running Man.)
Sir, how far...
How far will you follow us?
That man keeps following us.
Be careful of the stairs.
Stop following us.
Goodness.
(They're getting exhausted.)
Gosh, he keeps following us.
- Gosh. - Hey.
Isn't that too much? He followed us all the way here.
How could you follow us all the way here?
(Panting)
Why were you all the way there?
- How could you, Kwon Ryeol? - Seriously.
You were doing this while we were here.
How could you?
(Everyone knows that he gets scared easily.)
(He doesn't know what to do.)
(Don't come near me.)
(This is the most scared Kwon Ryeol has ever been.)
(He follows.)
- What? - What?
- Come on, Kwon Ryeol. - What's wrong with you?
You scare me even more.
Didn't you hear that?
What sound? It was you.
It's the sound you made when you walked.
(He gets scared by his own footsteps.)
(They continue walking.)
There are no stairs.
Okay.
Where's your name tag?
I have to find it.
(I want to find it and leave.)
It seems suspicious that there's a cushion.
Here it is.
- Here it is. - There it is.
(Screaming)
- That startled me. - Stop it.
My goodness.
- I'll bring your name tag. - So Min.
- Give it to me now. - So Min.
- Please give it to me. - So Min.
Hurry up.
(Run away now.)
- Wait a minute. - So Min.
(The name tag is hard to get.)
I almost died, So Min.
- Thank you. - I was so frightened.
Let's catch our breaths.
- How far have we come? - My throat hurts.
- How much farther must we go? - I don't know.
(It's been 35 minutes.)
There is no end.
(How much longer must we listen to them?)
"I'm sorry."
I'm telling the truth.
We went out of battery.
(They went out of battery.)
- Whose camera? - Both cameras went off.
- Did yours turn off too? - You mean these cameras?
(That's scary.)
- What's going on? - Aren't the batteries charged?
- When did you change them? - Before we started.
- It hasn't been long. - Then what happened?
Both cameras turned off.
How about yours?
(Both of the cameras turned off.)
- What's going on? - How about mine?
- Both of them? - Seok Jin and Kwang Soo's went off.
The batteries were charged.
(This has happened before.)
(Whenever Running Man did a horror special, )
(mysterious incidents happened.)
(This time too?)
The battery has run out?
Why? When did you change it?
- Right before coming here. - Right before coming here?
How long does it usually last? An hour?
It usually lasts a day.
- And it's already out? - It hasn't even been 30 minutes.
(The battery has run out after only an hour.)
What's happening?
- What's going on? - It really is out.
Really?
Why you of all people?
Bad things usually happen to you.
(The three members' energy is running out too.)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear has been waiting for today.)
Let's hurry.
(Let's hurry.)
We must be finished.
We must be finished. Here you go.
Here you go. Please save us.
- Save us. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Bye.
Thank you.
(They return the name tags.)
Can we go out now? Thank you.
Bye.
(The gatekeeper shows them the way.)
(We're safe now.)
- No, it's not the end. - What is this?
It should end here.
(Is this not the end?)
This place is weird.
Aren't we finished?
This seems to never end.
(They are not even halfway through yet.)
Aren't we finished?
When is this going to end?
(They arrive at a steel bridge.)
Your hands are sweaty.
(Nervous)
I'm sweating all over too.
I have no energy left.
(Noises)
Gosh!
My goodness!
(Running away)
(So Min's cameraman runs away.)
He's running away.
Your cameraman is running away.
- Hey! - Are you leaving us behind?
Are you leaving us behind?
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(They're startled by a camerman who has been hiding.)
- Gosh. - Why are you doing this?
- Why did you run away alone? - My goodness.
- Why did you run away alone? - I can't believe you.
How could you leave us alone?
Gosh.
(Hello)
(They run away.)
- Where is Kwon Ryeol? - Where is Kwon Ryeol?
(Why am I left here?)
Where is he?
I'm not one of them.
Kwon Ryeol!
(I'm just a staff member.)
(They just run away without Kwon Ryeol.)
- Gosh. - My goodness.
Gosh!
- Guys. - What is this?
You two.
Guys. How could you?
(How can you do this?)
Hey.
You guys are unbelievable.
What are you doing?
Pull yourselves together.
Hey.
Kwon Ryeol, Si Yeon.
- Hey. - Pull yourselves together.
We have to get out of this place.
We have to survive. Pull yourselves together.
Pull yourselves together, guys.
(Will they safely escape the place?)
My goodness.
I'm all sweaty.
They're screaming a lot.
(Team Happy Trip arrives.)
- How did it go? - Was it fun?
- Are you guys okay? - Some are in there right now.
- I heard them scream. - It sounds horrible.
- It's extremely scary. - What happened?
- What will happen? - What happened?
Why do you look so thin?
He's become thin.
I'm exhausted.
You seem to have gained weight.
We ate so much.
- We ate so much. - You know what?
The number of ghosts was decided by your expenditure.
What?
- Do you understand? - Is that true?
We'll see the maximum number of ghosts.
- Really? - You didn't know?
We just had beef.
Gosh.
It melted in our mouths.
Hold on.
(It still hasn't ended.)
Gosh.
There's something again.
There's something over there.
(An evil ghost is wandering in the hallway.)
(What should we do?)
- My goodness. - Let's run.
Let's run.
Let's run. We have no choice.
Let's run all together.
- There's no other way. - Let's run.
- Let's run. - Let's run.
Let's run to the end of the hallway.
There's no other way.
Let's see.
My goodness.
- Let's run. - This is too much.
(The ghost is watching them.)
Let's... Let's run.
(They are extremely nervous.)
1, 2, 3.
Run!
(The ghosts are behind them.)
(Where is the exit?)
(So Min's cameraman comes out first.)
So Min!
(Jae Seok and So Min are finished.)
What's wrong?
What happened?
- Jae Seok. - So Min.
What's going on?
- What's wrong? - What happened?
What's wrong?
He's sweating.
He's covered in sweat.
He's all sweaty. His clothes are wet.
His clothes are all wet.
How scary was it?
Get up.
You won't be able to escape.
- Sit on a chair. - You can't go alone.
You can't go alone.
Kwang Soo can't go alone.
He can't?
- Gosh. - How was it?
We heard you scream.
- We heard something. - So Min, you've become thinner.
Why did you keep apologizing?
- I heard, "I'm sorry." - Go in.
- Just go in. - Was it that bad?
- Just go in. - Is it unimaginable?
My goodness.
It never ends. It's so scary.
Do you know what's scary?
Two cameras suddenly ran out of battery.
That can happen if they weren't charged properly.
That's not it.
(Jae Seok...)
Seok Jin is angry.
He looks annoyed.
He's seriously annoyed.
- He really is annoyed. - Let it go, Seok Jin.
That can happen.
That punk.
- He should become possessed. - The ghosts follow you all the way.
They don't leave after startling you. They follow you.
- They follow you all the way. - They follow you all the way.
Now, Se Chan and Seok Jin will enter.
(It's Seok Jin and Se Chan's turn.)
We can do this.
- We can do this. - We can do this.
It looks so creepy.
(Hold on.)
(I have something to tell you.)
Will it be okay?
Are you going in?
(Jong Kook stops Seok Jin and Se Chan.)
(What does Jong Kook want to say to them?)
What is he doing?
(I want to capture this moment.)
Are you taking a selfie?
- What is he doing? - Gosh.
(Good luck in the Labyrinth.)
Do you want to remember this moment?
- Are you a tourist? - Come here.
What is with him?
Why are you taking a picture?
Do you want to fight with me?
(Seok Jin wants to fight him.)
Sure.
(He accepts the challenge.)
That sounds good. I've been bored all day.
I'd rather go in there.
(Seok Jin's afraid of him.)
Wait.
(They go in to meet the ghosts.)
Here we go.
Let's go.
That place looks suspicious.
I don't think so.
- Stop it. We haven't even started. - Stay still.
- Hold on. - Nothing will happen.
Why do you walk so quickly?
It's okay. We're just starting here.
This part seems safe.
- It'll be okay. - That's not what I'm talking about.
Let's go.
Why do you walk before me?
Let's walk together.
(Their steps look so desperate.)
(Dance with the ghosts in the Labyrinth.)
(Don't let go of my hands.)
(It looks like they're dancing the tango.)
Please don't show up.
I think this part is safe.
(They drag their feet.)
It's okay. Stop it.
- I can't do this. - It'll be all right.
I can't walk.
Seriously.
Walk.
(Thump)
(Their cameras hit each other.)
Gosh!
It was just our cameras.
I can't go in.
Come on.
My goodness.
We haven't even started.
Let's go in.
Let's go.
- Okay, okay. - Okay.
Welcome.
What's that?
(He's an employee.)
(Screaming)
(It's just a flashlight.)
Why? What happened?
It's broken.
You broke it.
(They broke the only light they have.)
How will Kwang Soo do this alone?
(Exactly)
"How will Kwang Soo do this alone?"
(Why?)
(Why are you giving me this ordeal?)
- Something's here. - Seok Jin.
You're walking too slowly. It's too hard for me.
- What? - It's too hard for me.
- Why? - You're too slow.
(They finally arrive at the entrance.)
Seok Jin, I have a bad feeling about this.
- Something's going to come out. - Exactly.
Excuse me!
(Who's there?)
I can't do this.
(There has to be something here.)
(Peekaboo)
(Screaming)
(It sounds like one voice.)
(They look like a fantastic duo.)
- That hurts. - I bumped into this.
(Shrieking)
(What's going on?)
- Who's that? - Are they getting eaten alive?
It sounds like they're playing a tug of war.
Why are they yelling at the same time?
(Among all the laughter, )
(one person refuses to even smile.)
(How will Kwang Soo do it solo?)
Kwang Soo.
This is driving me nuts.
(What in the world is in the Labyrinth.)
Cameraman Yoon Sang asked,
"I can come out if I find my name tag, right?
(Yoon Sang is Kwang Soo's cameraman.)
(Excuse me, sir?)
They're the same.
(He's been Kwang Soo's cameraman for 7 years.)
I won't come out by myself.
I won't come out. I promise.
After 10 minutes, both Kwon Ryeol and Si Yeon...
(Screaming)
- What was that? - That startled me.
That startled me.
(What? It's Seok Jin's cameraman.)
Who's that?
(Their hearts almost dropped.)
- Who's that? - That startled me.
- I'm startled. - He came out?
- He came out? - He came out by himself?
- That scared me. - Hey...
(How did he come out without Seok Jin?)
(10 minutes ago at the operating room)
Whose is this?
(The cameraman found his own name tag.)
- What does it say? - Let's see.
Bye.
- Hey, hey. - Where are you going?
- Hey! - Yoo Seok is gone.
- Darn it. - That loser.
- Here's your camera. - Are you...
(The filming must continue.)
Are you out of your mind?
Don't go! Hey!
What's wrong with him?
(I wish you luck, Seok Jin.)
(This is the story of his survival.)
He came out by himself?
I thought he was a white-haired witch.
(Today's lesson: Beware of people closest to you.)
- You're supposed to come out here. - That scared me.
- That startled me. - Hey.
You're supposed to come out that way.
(Kwang Soo is about to faint.)
- This is no joke. You should leave. - This is no joke.
(He is worried sick.)
Yoon Sang. You won't, right?
- I won't betray you. - I beg you.
- Really? - I won't.
- You know I trust you, right? - I won't betray you.
I'm serious.
(Seok Jin, can you hold my hand?)
- What? - Hold my hand.
Are you scared?
(The cameraman left inside is also a big coward.)
Is that a person?
No, Seok Jin.
(This is the first ghost after Yoo Seok left.)
(They unite in face of crisis.)
(Friendship is about running together.)
(They have a shared fate whether they want it or not.)
(They leap in circles.)
(It's impossible to film properly.)
This is crazy.
- Don't do that. - Don't!
Don't do that. Stop following us.
(Why did Yoo Seok leave them with a camera?)
Why did he leave his camera?
Can we sit down?
- Excuse me. - What is wrong with you?
Excuse me!
Why did he leave his camera with me?
(30 minutes have passed.)
- It's a hallway? - Why is the hallway so long?
(Shaking)
Why is the flashlight out?
- It's out of battery. - Slow down.
(Se Chan found his name tag by a moving bed.)
- I love you. - Welcome.
Come. Don't push me.
Please don't push me.
Who's that? Is that a person?
(It's a ghost.)
(The three friends are united again.)
(Let me be your friend too.)
That hurts, Sung Oh.
- My name tag. - That hurts, Seok Jin.
- That hurts. - My name tag.
- My name tag. - Let go.
- Hold on. - Come.
- Sung Oh. - That hurts.
This is crazy!
(This is crazy!)
Seok Jin just sounded like his mom.
(Seok Jin found his name tag.)
They won't let you go without your name tag.
Thank you.
Really? How do we go? It won't open.
(The gatekeeper shows them the way.)
(Is it over?)
Really?
(Only the viewers know the truth.)
Something's coming.
(It's not over yet.)
(Run until the end.)
(Three friends come out together.)
(I won't film something like this again.)
This is crazy.
- Yellow-haired guy! - My gosh.
- What was that for? - Hey, you.
- What was this for? - That was so heavy to carry.
You should have taken it with you.
Come on, Yoo Seok.
Seok Jin dropped the flashlight in the beginning and broke it.
I kept on pressing it...
for 30 minutes.
This made it worse. It kept on going on and off.
It was like a strobe light.
It's more scary because the ghosts come and go.
Usually you see the ghosts like this,
but because of the light effect, they looked like this.
(Dancing)
(It was as if the ghosts were clubbing.)
I almost died.
(Seok Jin and Se Chan's scary trip is over.)
Drink some water.
- Let's go, Yoon Sang. - Kwang Soo.
- Good luck, Kwang Soo. - See you later.
- See you later. - What's this?
- Come on. - Why are you doing this?
- That's so mean. - What's this for?
- What are you doing? - Why?
(Don't wet yourself, Kwang Soo of 19 Slots.)
- You can do it. - They're nice in the beginning.
Be careful. If your cameraman finds his name tag,
he'll leave you with the camera.
It'll be hard to go by yourself.
- Right? - You can't go. You can't go alone.
It's hard to go alone.
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear makes you sigh and groan.)
I'm going insane.
(He feels helpless and fearful.)
(I have no choice.)
I have no choice. Yoon Sang.
Promise me you'll go with me, Yoon Sang.
Yoon Sang. Promise.
What's this?
Wait. Don't push me.
I'm not scared.
You can go first.
Let's go together.
I was the host for your wedding.
I'm okay.
(I did you a favor, so do me one.)
This is crazy.
You don't have to film me. Please go first.
(He doesn't need the camera.)
(He stops.)
Here.
Can you peep with your camera?
(He peeks with the camera.)
You don't have to film me.
- Is anybody there? - No.
(They move ahead.)
This is driving me nuts.
Yoon Sang, keep going. Please.
(Yoon Sang and Kwang Soo push each other and advance.)
I'm... I'm sorry.
(Coughing and gagging)
(He's about to throw up.)
I can't do this.
(He fakes an illness 5 minutes in.)
I threw up.
(He acts like a baby.)
(He attempts to leave early by pretending to be sick.)
This isn't right.
Yoon Sang, please.
What's this? It's a tent.
(He enters the prop room.)
Is something here?
(Of course, there is.)
(You thought it was a tent, right? It's actually a ghost.)
Don't do that. Please.
I'm sorry!
Wait.
(Let me pass.)
(His sickness comes back after meeting the first ghost.)
Please. I won't do it.
Wait. Hold on.
Hold... Don't!
Just once.
Please wait a minute!
(He's very polite.)
Stop.
I'll go.
(Thanks to the ghost, he learns Japanese.)
Please stop!
Yoon Sang. Don't.
(It's like he's dancing to a beat.)
(A ghost calls for him.)
What was that?
I'm done for.
(Grabbing)
- That hurts. - I'm sorry.
(Kwang Soo hasn't moved an inch after cursing.)
Darn it.
(My gosh)
I don't think I can do this.
Something's here.
What is it? Somebody's lying down.
What's this? Somebody's lying down.
(He enters the operating room.)
Go, Yoon Sang. Go.
(Yoon Sang listens to him.)
Go, Yoon Sang.
Yoon Sang.
(Screaming)
(Kwang Soo is aghast.)
(Yoon Sang is scared even more.)
(It's a cowardly duo who gets scared over a mere sound.)
My goodness.
I broke my leg.
(Here comes the 2nd illness.)
Excuse me, sir. Yoon Sang.
Sir...
Please let me pass.
Can you go an inch forward?
Just here, Yoon Sang. I'll be in the front after this.
My gosh.
What's this stupid noise?
What's that noise?
(Shrieking)
(Falling)
(They bump into each other.)
Please...
(Whatever. Let's just take a rest.)
I hurt myself. I really did.
Producer Cheol Min!
(The audience breaks out in laughter.)
- He hurt himself? - I hurt myself. Cheol Min!
You stepped on me three times.
What happened? How did you step on me?
(Did I?)
Do you hear me, Cheol Min? We both broke our legs.
(They don't believe him at all.)
What?
There's a barbed wire fence. What do we do?
(They're still lost in the operating room.)
That scared me. I hear the sound again.
(Were you talking about me?)
Please. Please let me go, sir.
I'm Korean. Please.
Please let me go. Hold on.
Wait.
(Strangely, the ghost brings out his patriotism.)
Please. I'm sorry.
Thank you for the food.
I'll leave.
I'll go, sir.
Please let me rest. This is crazy.
Thank you... Please.
Wait.
They didn't see anything by the stairs.
There's something here. They said there was nothing.
Gosh, So Min.
What? Me?
(It's just a doll.)
How are we supposed to pass?
(I don't know.)
This is too much. How are we supposed to pass?
Hold on.
The ghost is right here. How do we go?
(Darn it.)
What am I supposed to do?
(They've been peeking with the camera for a few minutes.)
I'll go.
(Please go.)
(I'll go.)
I'm by the stairs. I might roll down.
It sounds like a baby crying.
Is there something here?
I'm injured. I broke my leg.
I can't go here.
(The crying continues.)
The baby is crying.
(Please stop the baby from crying.)
(It makes us want to cry as well.)
This is driving me nuts.
The baby's crying. How are we supposed to pass?
(He's been repeating that a few times.)
Why is the baby crying?
(Why do you want to know that?)
Can you go in first? Yoon Sang.
I broke my elbow too.
Just once.
Is there a kid?
No, that's not it.
I can't go in.
What then?
What do I do if you can't go in?
- You can go first. - You just have to turn.
I can't go.
Should we take a break? Should we sit down?
- Yes. - Should we sit down?
- Hold on. - Let's sit down.
This is driving me nuts.
Please wait.
I hurt myself. I broke my leg.
There's something here.
(They can't sit forever so they keep going.)
Is this the right way?
Yes, this is the door.
Let's hurry.
(Frowning)
(Why is there a hand?)
This won't do.
(He backs up quickly.)
Okay.
Let's go.
(They came this far. A bloody hand can't stop them.)
(Let's not be cowards anymore and get through this.)
This... Yoon Sang, what do I do? This won't do.
What then? Wait.
(We should just go back, right?)
I think something's here.
What's going on?
- They're still far from done. - Can you...
just tell them to come out?
They're taking forever.
(We may see sunrise at this rate.)
There's something here. Okay.
(He decides to go forward.)
Let's go.
(He clenches his teeth and moves forward.)
Wait, sir. Can you let me pass?
(I think I need another break.)
Excuse me.
(Excuse me, Mr. Ghost.)
One chance.
Can you make them stop crying?
(They're not stopping.)
How are we supposed to pass?
- Let's go. We have no choice. - Go.
(Are you saying you can't go?)
Go.
Wheelchair, wheelchair!
(It's the terrifying, wheelchair ghost.)
Please... Please wait!
Wait. Where is it going? Wait.
I'm sorry!
(He says, "Thank you," in Russian.)
Hold on!
Thank you. Please wait.
I'm sorry.
(This wheelchair ghost has a story.)
(The ghost was waiting for them all along.)
(It got sick of waiting, )
(so it came to meet them.)
I'm sorry.
(It's a very kind ghost.)
Don't. Stop.
Please, sir!
(I'm dying, Mom.)
(Goodness)
I'm sorry!
(I said, I was sorry!)
I can't pass.
Why do you keep saying that?
(Do you think I can?)
Let's go. We have no other choice.
Can you tell it to take a step back?
Can you take a step back?
I'll pass.
I want to...
(It's Kwang Soo's free talking class.)
Please stop.
Please, sir.
Please move back. A little bit.
Please move back a little bit.
Thank you so much.
(The wheelchair ghost actually moves back.)
Stop. Just once.
- How are we supposed to pass? - What's here? This is impossible.
(It's a moving bed after the wheelchair ghost.)
Bed, stop.
(I'm back.)
It's over. It's over!
It's over. I saw you. What's wrong with you?
Sir, how long are you going to keep this up?
(Farewell doesn't mean forever.)
Sir, what do I have to do for you to stop?
If you need me to wet myself,
I can do that right now.
(We need to buy Kwang Soo new underwear.)
We need to find our name tags, Yoon Sang.
I haven't seen a single one.
(They have to find their name tags to escape from this darkness.)
(Kwang Soo finds his name tag.)
(Not only does he find his name tag, but he always finds a ghost.)
(Wailing)
(Yelling)
(Screaming)
(Laughing)
- He must hate it. - Is that an animal?
He must hate it.
I hate this. I hate this so much.
(Kwang Soo finds his name tag first.)
(Let's go, Yoon Sang.)
That startled me. What's that?
- I can't do this. - What's that?
What should we do? Where are you going?
(Yoon Sang tries to quit in the middle.)
Where are you going? What's wrong?
What then? I found my name tag.
- I found it for you. - I can go back the way we came.
Just here.
You want me to go first?
(Please go first.)
- I'll just go back. - No, wait.
(I can just go back the way we came.)
Look.
(How am I supposed to go first?)
Let's go together.
(Shrieking)
What? Why?
(This time around, he wants to know why the woman is screaming.)
We can't walk through.
Why is she doing that?
This is insane.
(They finally enter the reception area.)
(I've been waiting for long.)
It's there.
How are we supposed to pass?
It's coming. It's coming!
(They back off again.)
My gosh.
You can't do that from both sides.
(These cowards are stuck.)
(He walks like an ape to try again.)
For goodness' sake.
This is insane.
What should we do?
I will do this.
(Running)
(The cowardly duo escapes the reception area at full speed.)
(Stomping)
(Is the ghost following them?)
("Fantastic Duo 2", coming up)
(The sentimental balladeer, Kim Yeon Woo's sad cry)
(Sir)
(When he called for "Sir", )
(Boohwal made a comeback.)
(Boohwal versus Kim Yeon Woo)
I will do this.
(Running)
(The cowardly duo escapes the reception area at full speed.)
(Stomping)
(Is the ghost following them?)
(It's a cameraman.)
My goodness.
(After seeing ghosts, they are surprised by a cameraman.)
Don't do that.
For goodness' sake.
(I have been here all along.)
It's a door. Push, push.
(Yoon Sang acquires his name tag on the way.)
(Unsurprisingly, another dreary place appears.)
Here we go again.
I don't even know anymore.
(The end is near.)
You can go first.
(But this red room stops them.)
Come on.
How will we go through?
- I can't do this. - For goodness' sake.
What do you suggest we do?
Do you want to live here forever?
We need to go.
Look at how tightly I am holding onto your name tag.
(The cowardly duo enters the stairs.)
I am sure we are almost done.
Can we sit down for a second? Let's hurry up and go.
Let's sit down for five seconds.
I can't do this.
Why couldn't I catch a king crab?
(He only caught strange sea creatures.)
(For goodness' sake.)
(Did you think he was a ghost?)
I can't do this anymore.
(The duo arrives before the gatekeeper.)
We must be at the end.
(Kwang Soo and Yoon Sang safely turn in their name tags.)
All right.
Can we go?
(Let's go together.)
Yoon Sang.
(Their pain will be over if they get out safely.)
This really is the end.
(A mysterious figure watches them from afar.)
Wait a minute. We found our name tags.
(We may be able to dodge him.)
Come on.
This is insane.
(We may be able to dodge him.)
(Let's try to talk to him.)
(The ghosts who are angry by the long wait run out.)
(They run as fast as they can.)
(The cowardly duo finally escapes.)
My goodness.
(He is utterly exhausted.)
Good work, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - Good work, Kwang Soo.
(The duo held hands until the end and displayed their friendship.)
(The two cowards' epic escape of Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear ends.)
You did a good job. You are a true man.
You were speaking nonsense.
You were very cool, Kwang Soo.
It's over. It's over.
- Thank you for your hard work. - It's over.
We are done with Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
With the tour of Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear,
Running Man's Global Project: Dangerous Tourist Attractions ended.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
I will now reveal Running Man's new project.
(Running Man's new project will be revealed.)
(Is there more?)
- Is there another project? - There are so many projects.
(They suddenly deliver...)
(a new project.)
Where are we going this time?
Will we start a new project right away?
1, 2, 3.
(What will it be...)
(this time?)
"People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent".
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
A Place for 1 Percent?
Running Man's new project is...
People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent.
Among the tourist attractions that are recommended by the viewers,
you will go to a place that is recommended by one percent.
We are currently receiving recommendations on our website.
The recommendations include Salar de Uyuni in Bolivia.
(The magical salt flats, Salar de Uyuni in Bolivia)
The Grand Canyon in the US.
(The nature the world loves, the Grand Canyon in the US)
Machu Picchu in Peru.
(The unsolved mystery of the nature, Machu Picchu in Peru)
And the boat tour at Iguazu Falls are among the many.
(The best tourist attractions in the world)
- Those places are very well known. - Those places are nice.
Those places are very well known.
However...
(However)
(However?)
Too many people suggested them, so those places were eliminated.
(The well known, tourist attractions are eliminated.)
(Which place for 1 percent will Running Man go to?)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(A taste of places for 1 percent, number 1)
Bonjour. Hello.
I am a viewer of Running Man who lives in Paris, Kim Cho Rong.
This place was recommended by Cho Rong.
The unique tourist attraction I recommend is...
the Catacombs of Paris,
which are underground ossuaries in the heart of Paris.
Ossuaries?
Why would you do that to us?
It has been less than a minute since I came out.
A myth says that inside, a gate to the underworld exists.
You must be careful...
because seeing the gatekeeper of the underworld...
means you will be dragged under.
Why would we go to the ossuaries?
This is a real place.
- This is ridiculous. - Some tourists have gone missing.
Why would we go there?
Come to the Catacombs of Paris for a scary experience this summer.
(A taste of places for 1 percent, number 2)
Hello, I am a 28-year-old who lives in Seoul, Hong Se Hee.
I am sending a video because there is...
a tourist attraction I want you to visit in my place.
It's a ride that is located in Colorado, US,
called the Giant Canyon Swing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
- There is no way we can ride it. - It's impossible.
What is that?
It's so scary that even the designer of the ride only rode it once.
Simply put, it is like riding a swing on a cliff.
(Shocked)
There is no way we can ride it.
Even the designer of the ride couldn't ride it.
I can't ride it because I have a fear of heights.
It will be thrilling to see the members experience it.
Let's go, Running Man.
We all have a fear of heights.
We all do.
(A taste of places for 1 percent, number 3)
Hi, Running Man. My name is Abril Elguezabal.
I am 21 years old. I am from Mexico.
The place I want to recommend, Copper Canyon,
is an amazing place with an amazing view.
What is the place?
- Does it include rock climbing? - It looks very cool.
You can get on the zipline,
go to viewpoints, get on the cable car,
hanging bridges, and rappels.
It's a single-line zipline.
My goodness.
- We can't go on it. - Seriously.
That's impossible.
Why are you doing this to us?
(A taste of places for 1 percent, number 4)
Hello, I am Park Ji Ni from Seoul.
I recommend Crater of Diamonds State Park...
because you can keep the diamonds you find after paying seven dollars.
What?
I like this place.
That's incredible.
- That's incredible. - Crater of Diamonds State Park.
You can keep the diamonds you find.
- That sounds great. - Do you really get to keep it?
That's why I recommend Crater of Diamonds State Park.
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
Not all recommendations by one percent...
- are terrible. - You are right.
There was one good one.
The biggest diamond that was found in Crater of Diamonds State Park...
was 16.3 carat.
A 7.44-carat diamond was found in March,
and a 2.65-carat diamond was found in May.
We will receive recommendations until the project ends...
and choose from a shortlist.
Who will go?
(Who will go to the fascinating place for 1 percent?)
(Who will go?)
The one who will go to Place for 1 Percent...
is the member with three I Go Stickers.
(The member with 3 I Go Stickers and another member)
They will also choose another member to go with.
The die that is thrown by the winner of the race...
will decide who gets the Sticker.
It's going to be a little bit different this time around.
This time, the winner will get to choose your fates.
It's "I go" in English, so it means "I will go."
- "I go." - "I go."
(Poor me. I'm going.)
How is this Sticker different from the one what we had before?
Goodness.
My gosh.
Are you playing tricks with us?
Are you slacking off these days?
Do you even do meetings?
It's now called I Go Sticker?
After this special, you'll be going somewhere, is that it?
- This is crazy. - My gosh.
This time, however, only two people will be designated to go.
People's Recommendation Project, A Place for 1 Percent.
The first race is...
about finding the highest 1 percent. It's called "The 1st Place Tour".
(The 1st Place Tour)
(They head out to find everything that's ranked 1st in Japan.)
(The special guest, Jung Hye Sung)
(The best)
(The highest)
(The longest)
(The 1st Place Tour takes place in Japan.)
(They begin their new project to search for only the top best.)
(Which team will win this race?)
(The 1st Place Tour in Tokyo)