My gosh, I like this place. This is nice.
(A secret base of heroes in Busan)
Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Goodness. - We are in Busan.
We get to film this week's episode in Busan.
- It's definitely warm in Busan. - It is warm here.
- It got warmer. It's not cold. - I agree. It's not cold.
Jong Kook, but it's not warm enough to be in such outfit. Are you okay?
(You're not wearing a winter coat.)
(It's spring for him. He's not wearing a padded jacket.)
I agree. You still need a winter jacket.
This is the outfit I had on when I left for the shoot.
I got on the KTX in this outfit and arrived here.
When I walked in, my outfit coordinator said,
"Jong Kook, the outfit I brought looks the same. Just wear yours."
(Jong Kook, the outfit I brought looks the same. Just wear yours.)
- That's too much. - I said, "Really?"
So I agreed to keep my outfit on.
- Why on earth... - I woke up at 3:30am.
My mom cooked me the loin end.
- I had the end loin. - At 3:30am?
- At 3:30am? - Yes.
You ate the loin end at 3:30am?
Yes, I had that for breakfast.
Only your mother can cook for you at three in the morning.
- She did it because you're her son. - This is hilarious.
It's been two years since I had breakfast.
(Forget about the beef. Last time I had breakfast was 2 years ago.)
She did it because she's your mother.
Seok Jin is on the intermittent fast.
- Sure. - Seriously?
That wasn't his choice though.
- It's true. - He can cook breakfast himself.
- Sorry? - Seok Jin weighs about 47kg, right?
(His weight is that of an elementary schooler.)
(No, I weigh more than 50kg.)
- What are you talking about? - He weighs over 50kg.
Today's race will be held in Busan.
- Let's meet today's guests first. - We're having guests today?
(No way! We have surprise guests today?)
- Who do you think it is? - They came all the way to Busan?
- We have guests today? - Who are they?
Okay!
You're getting your hopes up again. Don't do that, Se Chan.
Why not?
Today's guests, please come on out.
(Two guests who will join the outing in Busan are behind the door.)
- Who are they? - Who are they?
(Who are the surprise guests?)
- My gosh, how long has it been? - We haven't seen you for ages!
(Their silhouettes are enough to excite them.)
Kang Han Na. It's Han Na...
My goodness!
How long has it been?
(Kang Han Na and Kyung Su Jin)
(Unusual Han Na and Competitive Su Jin brought heat to Running Man.)
(This time, they are in Busan!)
- Long time no see. - It's great to see you.
- Have you been well? - Hello.
- Have you been well? - It's nice to meet you.
- Hi. - It's been a while.
(Did you see Seok Jin?)
My goodness. Hang on a second.
- I just saw... - What is it?
- I just saw something hilarious. - What is going on?
- Seok Jin said to Han Na... - What happened?
"It's nice to meet you."
- He was Han Na's partner. - Seok Jin, you don't remember her?
- She played games as your partner. - With me?
(Seok Jin and Han Na spent the whole day as each other's partners.)
He was all polite and said, "It's nice to meet you."
(He was overly polite.)
Han Na...
I remember now. We had kalguksu with Ji Hyo.
- Stop it now, Seok Jin. - That's enough.
- Try to remember her. - How can I remember everyone?
But how could you not remember your former partner?
All right. I'm sure you all know how Su Jin is.
Whenever she joined us on our show,
she showed us great games and got very competitive.
- She's really competitive. - She is indeed.
She's the one who blocked the elevator with shoulders, right?
(She's a true fighter who doesn't hesitate to go against machines.)
- I really admire her. - I didn't know she was daring.
During the shoot, I saw the whites of her eyes a lot,
but I didn't see them on TV.
- You saw the whites of her eyes? - I've never seen eyes turning.
- Stop lying. - She was just trying her best.
Su Jin and Han Na are joining us today.
(Next up is Han Na whom only Seok Jin hasn't met.)
- She is a dancer. - She's very unusual.
You must've had an early start in order to join us in Busan.
Actually, I'm currently filming a JTBC drama in Busan.
- It's called "Just Between Lovers". - Really?
(No, I'm filming a JTBC drama in Busan.)
- You can't promote it that bluntly. - This is a bit...
She can't be too blunt about this.
It hasn't aired yet.
- You might not know. - It hasn't started yet.
- The promotion sounded rushed. - I agree.
It was too direct.
Did you not think that this could be edited out when you said that?
(Did you think that at all?)
- Please don't edit it out. - Let this part air.
We will air this clip,
but you have to include, "Running Man" in your line.
(Include "Running Man" in your line in exchange.)
Well...
- "I saw Running Man yesterday." - Please do that.
- Okay. - Add, "It airs on SBS at 6:30pm."
You will have an intense mind game in order to win the prize money.
The race is called, Same Money, Different Dreams Race.
(Same Money, Different Dreams Race)
You will divide into two teams, and through games,
the winning team will be determined.
The individual with the most money in the winning team...
will be the final victor.
(The player with the most amount of money in the winning team will win.)
The victor will receive the tenfold amount of the leftover money.
The victor can choose four members who will receive the water bomb.
- Four members? - Yes.
(The victor will win the money and pick four members for the penalty.)
- Water bomb? - One from the winning team...
and three from the losing team will face the penalty.
(1 from the winning team and 3 from the losing team will be chosen.)
If I face water bombs in Busan...
(He's worried.)
- You're already thinking about it? - Try to win the game... Hey.
- No. - You always think about penalties?
- Don't think about the penalties. - My outfit coordinator...
Whenever we have this kind of penalty,
my outfit coordinate always tells me to bring extra underwear.
- Why does she think I'll get it? - You always get the water bomb.
Why would you assume that it's me?
I have about 40 underpants in the trunk of my car.
(You and I are in the same boat.)
Before we start the race, we'll decide the teams.
Today's guests, Su Jin and Han Na,
will each become team leaders and scout players you want.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - I should make good impressions.
The way you scout the members is simple.
You'll write down the members you want and submit it to us.
You can take the members who don't overlap on your lists to your team.
The winning team of Song Ji Hyo Game will get to scout...
overlapping members and members who haven't been chosen.
(The winning team will get to choose first.)
(The game is named after Ji Hyo who's the best at talking nonsense.)
(The players must provide 3 absurd answers within 5 seconds.)
Before the announcement,
Ji Hyo and So Min...
- will demonstrate the game. - Great.
- After the game, the winner can... - They'll play the game?
choose the team she wants.
- This is too hard. - If they go against each other,
it will be crazy.
Their clips can't air.
They have no limits.
These two members are the ones...
who managed to liberate the censorship of the TV stations.
(They managed to liberate the censorship of the TV stations.)
- They played a major role. - They did indeed.
- They were the stepping stones. - They are experts.
For them, these major TV stations are just platforms.
- They are their playgrounds. - Exactly.
- Major TV stations don't mean much. - They act first and think later.
"Censoring the show is up to you."
That's their motto.
Seriously.
- Ji Hyo, you can start. - Me?
(Ji Hyo gets to ask first.)
Watch them.
Name three moments when you find Kwang Soo lovely.
When he smiles, buys me meals, and plays games.
(Do you mean that, So Min?)
(You are so lovely when you smile, eat your meals, and play games.)
She says you are lovely when you smile.
Show her a smile. Smile to her.
Are you two going out?
(What is going on?)
You should hurry up and tell us.
Hey.
Why would you go out with him when you held my hand?
Seok Jin.
(Optical illusion made it seem like they were holding hands,)
(but both hands were actually Seok Jin's.)
- You held my hand. - My mom scolded me.
- Why? - She thought we held hands.
(Don't do that.)
People really think we held hands.
- Both hands were mine. - It's easy to misunderstand.
There was even an article...
that said we held hands.
It's a trick of the eye.
- All right. So Min. - Okay.
Name three parts you like from Jae Seok's body.
Eyes, nose, and mouth.
(Eyes, nose, and mouth.)
Body!
I said body.
- Come on. - Face...
- is a part of the body. - Of course, it is.
I can't believe you.
- What were you thinking? - Seriously.
What were you thinking?
- Which words do you want to hear? - What were you thinking?
She makes the game dirty.
I don't know what's inside her head.
I wanted to ask a question Ji Hyo wouldn't be able to answer.
I would answer such questions easily, So Min.
- She would. - I would.
Han Na and Su Jin are astonished.
- They are astonished. - They haven't even started.
(Ji Hyo wins the game.)
(Ji Hyo joins Team Han Na, and So Min joins Team Su Jin.)
I will now announce the male members the team leaders want.
- The team leaders want. - This is the important part.
- Who picked me? - I hope both of them picked me.
The names Su Jin wrote down are...
It would be embarrassing if neither one of them wants you.
- That's right. - That's the worst past.
It would make you feel uncomfortable.
(Which male member will have the honor of getting chosen first?)
Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok)
- Why did you do that? - Be quiet.
- Let's see the other names. - You never know.
- You never know. - Kwang Soo.
Okay!
(Kwang Soo)
Why did you do that?
Hold on.
It's Team Australia again.
- This team is... - No.
- the worst. - The last one is...
Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - You know my name.
- My goodness. - How did this happen?
- Se Chan. - This is nice.
- It's okay. - I want to join Han Na.
I am Han Na's former partner.
The names Han Na wrote down are...
Han Na.
(Who are Han Na's 3 candidates?)
Jae Seok.
(Han Na also chooses Jae Seok.)
- Did she choose him as well? - For goodness' sake.
Gosh, I can't stand the sight of him.
He went to Han Na's side right away.
She called me.
He left us right away.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes!
(I am going too.)
- He is popular. - What is going on?
Are they top 1 and 2?
They picked the ones who'd bring up the mood.
- We are the minions. - Here is the last one.
(Seok Jin, Haha, and Jong Kook have yet to be chosen.)
(Is there Han Na's last candidate among them?)
Here is the last one.
Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin. - Yes!
Han Na!
(My former partner is the best.)
My goodness.
(For goodness' sake.)
(I can't believe this.)
Han Na, you are the best.
Do they find us burdensome?
Don't you like H.O.T?
(We are dressed like H.O.T today.)
(We like them, but...)
- I like H.O.T. - Please take a step back.
Kwang Soo.
They don't know about Anyang Hothead.
I am about to become Anyang Hothead.
He gets the nickname...
because he is a hothead who lives in Anyang.
I am about to become Anyang Hothead.
Even if I become a team member,
I will feel uncomfortable.
The Kim brothers.
The members who were only chosen for one team are set.
For Jae Seok and Kwang Soo, who were chosen for both teams,
Su Jin and Han Na will play...
the Song Ji Hyo Game.
Play the game with ease. You don't have to feel pressured.
(Han Na versus Su Jin)
Han Na attacks first.
Su Jin would ask hard questions.
Ask a question.
Su Jin,
name three people here you don't like.
Se Chan, Jae Seok, and Kwang Soo.
(Se Chan, Jae Seok, and Kwang Soo.)
Why would you say that when you chose me?
Why didn't you say our names? You should have mentioned us.
- Why didn't you say our names? - We are behind you.
- We are here. - We are two people you don't like.
They are like the grim reapers.
Stop it. It's scary.
Don't think about collecting her soul.
- She first said she didn't like us. - Beware of Anyang Hothead.
- Why didn't you say our names? - I can't hear them.
They will be ferocious today.
(You will regret not choosing us.)
- Is it my turn to ask a question? - Yes, Su Jin.
(Su Jin asks a question this time.)
Name your favorite games.
Baskin-Robbins 31, Game of Wits, and King Game.
(Baskin-Robbins 31, Game of Wits, and King Game.)
- King Game? - King Game?
- My goodness. - It's not like that.
- I just remembered it. - She likes to order people around.
Did you play the game...
- by writing numbers on cigarettes? - No, no.
Stop it!
(I know how King Game is played.)
- What did she say? - For goodness' sake.
- I just remembered it. - My goodness.
I haven't heard of King Game in a long time.
King Game is the legend.
King Game.
So Min.
Han Na.
Name your three favorite poets.
- Poets. - Name three.
(Her lips tremble.)
(My goodness.)
You should have named anyone.
Su Jin did this.
(Despite of moving her lips, she fails to answer.)
That was a good question.
The first round came to an end.
Han Na, choose between Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.
Su Jin, choose between Jong Kook and Haha.
Then we will have the second round.
- That's a good idea. - Do I say the name out loud?
Yes.
- Me? - At least act like you are torn.
(At least act like you are torn.)
- I will join Team Han Na. - I will win the next round.
Now, Su Jin will choose...
between Jong Kook and Haha.
- Okay. - I want Haha.
(She doesn't hesitate.)
My goodness.
(Welcome, Haha.)
Why doesn't she want me?
- It looks like... - Why doesn't she want me?
- she hates hotheads. - I don't understand.
Is that what it is?
(Jong Kook doesn't get chosen for the first time.)
- Does she hate hotheads? - She hates hotheads.
- Does she hate hotheads? - Su Jin.
You should have given it some thought.
All right.
It's Han Na's turn.
Name three inferiority complexes about your personality.
Well, I am easygoing.
(She smacks her lips.)
(Despite of smacking her lips, she fails to answer again.)
This is a terrible game.
Su Jin is angry. She is angry.
Pulmuone! Pulmuone! Edit this part out.
Su Jin yelled out a brand name...
to edit this part out.
Edit this part out.
My goodness.
I learned it from watching TV.
We can bleep out the brand name.
- It's not a problem. - She is really competitive.
Kwang Soo joins Team Han Na,
and Jong Kook joins Team Su Jin.
- Am I joining her team? - Yes.
(He is angry.)
(For goodness' sake.)
I think Su Jin lost her pace.
Anyang Hothead is being a bit...
- I will act as a middleman. - Anyang Hothead.
I will be the X-Man of this team.
We are with the grim reapers. This is bad.
We're all dressed in dark colors.
(Team Red and Team White)
(The first team mission unfolds at a very special place.)
(It's the outpost of the heroes who protect the Earth.)
This place suits me.
Black Panther.
(Amidst the true heroes who make the world go wild...)
(are Grasshopper, who shows an unimpressive jump...)
It's a workout.
(and Haroro, the kindergartners' hero.)
(What is the first team mission?)
There are suitcases.
They must be important.
Our names are written on them.
- Really? - Don't touch them.
Don't touch them.
- It's your favorite race, So Min. - What is it?
The prize is money.
- Really? - The prize is money.
They donate the money anyway.
(They donate the money anyway.)
- If you win, they go, - I have never won.
"We will donate the money under So Min's name."
I still want to win.
It will feel nice to donate money under my name.
I have never won.
You don't have a winner's face.
(He takes a physiognomic approach.)
I will help you win.
Jong Kook, teach him a lesson.
- Jong Kook, teach him a lesson. - My goodness.
- You jerk. - Teach him a lesson.
Do you think he'll listen?
What are you doing?
How is it different from hitting me yourself?
(She doesn't know how to use the hero.)
Today, you will have...
an intense mind game to win the prize money...
in Same Money, Different Dreams Race.
- You see the suitcases, right? - Yes.
Each suitcase contains 100 dollars.
- 100 dollars? - Yes.
I will buy the same stocks that Seok Jin has with 100 dollars.
Why would you throw away 100 dollars?
It will be difficult to buy them.
Okay.
After each round,
you can turn in a portion of your money...
to Running Bank...
in the tens.
The total sum will be calculated for each team.
The team with the higher amount will win.
There are three rounds in total. After the final race,
the member of the winning team with the highest amount wins.
The winner will get tenfold of what's left in the suitcase...
and the right to choose the four members for penalty.
If you leave behind 100 dollars, you will get 1,000 dollars.
You can turn in a portion of your money...
to Running Bank.
The team with the higher amount wins.
The member of the winning team with the highest amount wins.
For the team, submit a big sum.
- For yourself, submit a small sum. - For the team...
- For the team, you must sacrifice. - Right.
What's good about your team winning?
Only one member of the winning team will receive the penalty.
- I see. - There is the water bomb.
Three members of the losing team will receive the penalty.
You need to work for the team.
(You need to work for the team.)
- Don't be ridiculous. - Don't be ridiculous.
Your facial expression says otherwise.
You need to work for the team.
There is a big mountain we need to overcome...
in our team.
(She is Mount Everest when it comes to betrayal.)
- So Min is a big mountain. - That's not true.
- We are a team. Nevis! - Swing.
- You were not on our team. Go away. - Nevis!
- Swing. - You were not on our team. Go away.
- You went to see crocodiles. - We should deposit money.
Before depositing money, you'll carry out a mission.
I'll tell the winners how much a member of the other team deposited.
That's nice.
You'll play Don't Stop Relay and compete for Chance Cards.
It'll be a team relay and has four stages.
The team that finishes the race first wins.
The first part is rock climbing.
- The wall is on your left side. - Look at that.
Rock climbing.
For the second part, there's a laser maze behind you.
Is it that one?
One member of each team has to go through the laser maze.
They'll pull out the flag at the finish line...
and take it to the next stage.
The third part is couple jump rope.
Depending on how many times you touch the laser beams in the maze,
your team members' jump rope goal will be determined.
The fourth part is Ttakji Othello.
Within a minute,
you have to make sure more ttakjis have your team color.
(Rock climbing, laser maze,)
(couple jump rope, Ttakji Othello)
I'll win.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan get ready for rock climbing.)
I'll win by all means.
I'll show you guys.
- Okay. - They're changing positions.
- What? - They are.
- What? - What did he say?
- They're changing positions. - They are.
(What?)
- What did he say? - Say something.
Say, "Good luck," at least.
- All right. - What?
- Go away. - What did you say?
You didn't say anything. What's wrong?
- I can do it! - Hey.
(Su Jin learns a strange behavior.)
Why did you blow in my ear?
- She blew air into my ear. - She likes you.
Where is Han Na?
She's in position.
- Se Chan, good luck! - Thank you.
- Good luck! - Good luck!
Han Na, wish me luck.
Why is Han Na's shirt tucked in?
- So it doesn't touch the beams. - Laser beams.
Han Na, I love your attitude.
She's amazing.
Han Na is the best.
So Min, do the same.
- So Min, don't copy her. - Gosh, So Min.
That's not how you do it.
(Uncomfortable)
- They are hitched up too high. - Gosh, So Min.
(So Min is overzealous.)
I'll win by all means.
(They give up on their style.)
- Let's start. - Okay.
- Se Chan, go for it! - Let's do this!
- Gosh. - Let's start.
Ready.
Go for it!
- Ready. - Gosh, I feel burdened.
- Kwang Soo, you can do this! - Kwang Soo!
- You can do this! - Kwang Soo!
- They've started. - Stay calm.
- Use your legs. - You're doing great!
Se Chan, keep going up.
- Se Chan, go. - You're doing great!
- Use your legs. - Se Chan.
Se Chan, you can do this!
Kwang Soo.
I have nothing to step on.
Kwang Soo, go up!
- Use your legs. - Your left foot.
- Push your body up. - Se Chan.
- Keep going up. - Way to go!
Keep going!
- Your left foot! - Your legs...
- Your left foot! - Use your legs.
- You're doing great! - Your left foot!
Use your legs.
(Se Chan falls.)
(What?)
(Kwang Soo takes advantage of his height and succeeds.)
Way to go!
Don't go this way.
- It's over there. - It's not that way.
- It's over there. - Over here!
- Over there! - It's not that way.
(He's supposed to go in the other direction.)
- It's over there. - Over here!
- It's over there. - What happened?
- Go that way. - Over here.
- Kwang Soo. - Over here.
- We'll win! - Here.
- Over here. - Kwang Soo!
(So Min intercepts him.)
Come here.
- Put the flag in. - Se Chan, hurry!
Se Chan, hurry.
- Put it in. - Se Chan!
Hurry, Se Chan!
Se Chan!
- Kwang Soo! - Se Chan!
Can I put it in?
Se Chan!
It's in.
(Han Na enters the laser maze.)
Go for it, Han Na!
(The laser beams are on.)
(Flexible)
(She goes through the beams smoothly as in a movie.)
(Still, she's losing points, and the jump rope goal goes up.)
(Focused)
Are you going to play some background music?
(Singing)
(Han Na is shooting a spy movie.)
(Meanwhile, a wrestling movie is being shot over here.)
That's a cobra twist.
- That's a cobra twist. - Gosh.
(So Min is punished for cheating.)
Hold on. Hey!
Stop it!
Gosh!
Se Chan, what are you doing?
- Why are you not coming? - Han Na, go!
Hold on.
I got it. Where do I go?
(Se Chan finally finishes the first part.)
- Go! - Run!
(Laser maze score, couple jump rope goal)
(Alarm)
(After touching the laser beams a few times,)
(Han Na wins 4,050 points.)
- Did she win 4,050 points? - I'm done.
- Over here. - Han Na, put the flag in here.
(Team Red is ahead.)
- Jump rope 10 times. - 10 times.
- Let's do this. - Let's go.
- Start. - Start.
- Run! Hold on. - One.
- Hey! - Run!
(Excuse us.)
What are you doing?
What are you doing now?
What is this? What do I do?
How do I go?
(Striding)
What do I do?
Oh, my.
- 3, 4, 5, 6... - 3, 4, 5, 6...
(Team Red is struggling with the jump rope.)
(So Min wins 4,450 points.)
I'm out.
So Min is out.
- Hurry. - 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
- 7, 8, 9, 10. - 7, 8, 9, 10.
- Done. - Done.
- The flag! - The flag!
- Ji Hyo. - We did it.
- Over there. - Ji Hyo.
(They have to make sure more ttakjis are red.)
- Start. - What's our color?
The flag is in.
(What?)
(He changed red to white.)
(Everyone hurries him, and Seok Jin starts without thinking.)
Aren't we supposed to change white to red?
(We're Team Red.)
- Change white to red. - Oh, red.
Gosh.
Change white to red.
- Change white to red. - Red.
Come on.
- Good. - Okay.
Here.
It's too short. Is it okay?
(Will Jong Kook do his best for his team?)
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Take the flag!
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Okay!
Let's hurry.
- Haha! - Hurry.
- Start. - Stay calm.
1, 2,
- 3... - We might lose.
You don't have to use so much force.
Way to go!
- Seok Jin! - What is he doing?
(What?)
(There are more white ttakjis.)
- Seok Jin! - What is he doing?
(He's mostly groaning.)
- Gosh, I can't believe him. - Seok Jin!
You don't have to use so much force.
(He aims for a white one,)
(but a red one flips.)
- Gosh, that man... - Seok Jin!
(He keeps flipping the same one over and over.)
No!
- We might win! - 10 seconds left.
Gosh.
I can't believe it.
What's with him?
(When he's supposed to flip ttakjis,)
(he's making his team members flip out.)
Seok Jin!
We're going to win.
(It's too heartbreaking to watch.)
- What is this? - What happened?
(Most of the ttakjis are white.)
- We won! - We did it.
- I mean... - Gosh.
- We caught up with them. - I couldn't be a hothead.
It's unfair.
It's unfair. I can't believe it.
This is impossible.
You don't have to use much force.
You can flip it like this.
- It's so easy. - Han Na, why did you choose him?
Jae Seok should have played the ttakji game.
- Okay. We won. - We won.
Let's move.
- All right. - How many rounds are there?
Gosh, we lost because of Seok Jin.
(The team with more money in the bank wins.)
- We won. - The bank is here.
- The bank is here. - It's the bank!
Let's go to the bank!
- Each team should gather together. - Okay.
Since Han Na's team lost,
you'll deposit money 1 by 1.
Seok Jin, you should go first.
- Can't I go later? - Go first.
Team Su Jin, come here.
Let's see how much Jae Seok deposits.
- Of course. - Or...
Kwang Soo.
We don't have to see his.
We need to see Jae Seok's...
for us to destroy that team.
- Then I'll deposit a lot. - What?
(Team Leader's attitude)
To win, we have to deposit more money...
as a team. It's been just a game so far.
Okay.
- Am I right? - Han Na, you're so...
- You're so nice. - I don't want water bombs.
- If I were Seok Jin, - You're amazing.
I'd say, "It's okay. I'll deposit a lot."
- But you said, "You're so nice." - And then he gave me a high five.
- It's a team game. - I was trying to persuade you.
- You should deposit 30 dollars. - I will.
- Okay. - Then we'll deposit...
20, 40, 50, 60...
90 dollars in total.
- Okay. - We have to deposit...
How much do you plan to deposit?
Tell me.
I was thinking of more than 40.
- Either this or this. - Either this or this.
- Stop lying. - Will you?
That's absurd.
Just remember...
if any of us deposits less than 10, we might lose.
- I'll deposit 20. - Then we can win.
- If we deposit that, we'll win. - We'll win.
- Okay. - I'll deposit 20.
- Kwang Soo. - We'll definitely win.
Seok Jin will go first.
Seok Jin will deposit money.
We should keep an eye on him.
If he doesn't deposit 30...
(Seok Jin promised to deposit 30 dollars.)
- Seok Jin, this is... - Seok Jin.
- You're starting this thing. - Keep your promise.
If you don't...
We won't forgive you.
I'll keep my promise.
(Hold on...)
It's not obligatory, right?
(For the team to win, you have to deposit more.)
You'd better pay, Seok Jin.
We won't leave you in peace.
(Keeping money is beneficial for individuals.)
I should deposit 10 dollars.
I promised 30 dollars,
but I'll go with 10 dollars.
(30 dollars is too much.)
(He only pays 10 dollars.)
I feel bad.
(He feels bad for breaking the promise.)
- 30 dollars. - Who's next?
- I'll go. - Okay, Ji Hyo.
- You know how much to pay, right? - You know it, right?
- Yes. - Okay.
I'll pay 20 dollars that I promised.
Okay.
(Even Jae Seok...)
(deposits 10 dollars as promised.)
(He hopes that he can trust others.)
(Han Na should deposit 20 dollars.)
(Is she only paying 10 dollars?)
(At least she deposits 10 dollars.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Do as you promised. - I will.
(No one seems to trust him.)
How does it work? How do I deposit?
(How do I pretend like I paid?)
How do I pretend like I paid?
- Tear it, and give it to me. - Tear it?
Like this?
(He pretends to pay.)
(Kwang Soo is meticulous even as he betrays.)
(Team Red pays 50 dollars in total.)
- Our team is done. - It's over.
The other team decides whose amount you want to know.
- I see. - The amount...
won't be revealed to Team Red. Only you will find out.
- Is it a secret to us? - Yes.
- Listen. - How about Jae Seok?
To be honest,
I want to know 1 of those 3.
Who are you talking about?
What did he say?
What did you say?
Are you being satiric?
- I mean those three men. - Do you mean those...
- who talk? - That's right.
- I mean those who talk. - What about them?
Let's find out one of their amounts...
and react in a suspicious way.
- It'll destroy them. - Do you mean Jae Seok?
How about the one with a pouting mouth?
- Pouting mouth? - Shall we pick him?
- Is it okay? - That sounds good.
We'll find out Jae Seok's.
I paid...
the amount that I promised.
Won't you tell us?
Let's see.
(They check that he paid 10 dollars.)
- Gosh. - Goodness.
That's funny.
- He's such a trickster. - Goodness.
- How could you do that, Jae Seok? - Jae Seok.
- Didn't he pay? - How could you, Jae Seok?
Come on, I'm telling the truth.
I swear.
What if no one paid?
- Han Na, I'm being honest. - You can't trust him.
So Min, what did it say?
Tell us exactly what you read.
It said zero.
How dare you, So Min?
Wait. Was I not supposed to say it?
- Can't I? - We'll keep it to us.
I'll stay quiet.
So Min is lying again.
I don't think Jae Seok paid.
- Gosh. - I don't think he paid.
Let's look at the total amount.
- Right. - Yes.
Each member from Team White will deposit now.
- Go first, So Min. - Okay.
I bet So Min won't pay.
There's no point of her going.
I bet all my money that she won't pay anything.
She won't pay.
I'll make many go bankrupt today.
Kwang Soo, Jae Seok, and Ji Hyo will lose all their money.
- Seriously. - So Min.
- Trust me. - Just pay the minimum.
Please trust me.
Pay what we agreed on.
- Pay the minimum. - I don't think So Min will pay.
- Hurry up. - I trust you.
So Min.
We'll be fine if she doesn't betray us.
I...
made a promise.
(Is she really paying?)
To get my reputation back,
I'll do as I promised.
(Is she really paying 20 dollars?)
I was also water bombed.
(She keeps her promise for the first time.)
(She decides to become trustworthy.)
(Next is the team leader, Su Jin,)
(who promised to pay 20 dollars.)
(Moving slowly)
(Su Jin also pays 20 dollars.)
(We can win by paying the minimum.)
(Two members of Team White keep their promises.)
We'll win if we pay the minimum.
(Did the rest pay 10 dollars each?)
(All members finish paying.)
I'll announce the total amount...
- of the losing team. - Okay.
- Here's the result of Round One. - Please.
It should be 90 dollars.
It should be 90.
We'll win if we pay the minimum.
(If Jong Kook, Haha, and Se Chan kept the promise, Team White wins.)
(Here's the result of Round 1.)
The total is 50 dollars.
The scores are tied.
- Really? - Gosh.
(The total is 50 dollars.)
(There's no winner.)
- Wasn't I right? - The scores are tied.
(Everyone looks at Seok Jin.)
- Seok Jin. - How much did you pay?
You didn't pay, did you?
- I paid. - I paid too.
- I really paid. - I can prove it.
Then how is this possible?
- How much did you pay? - I can't show you.
- Me? - Come on, Han Na.
- You promised! - You didn't pay.
- I paid. - No, you didn't.
I did, but I paid less than what I promised.
- Did you pay? - I did.
- I paid. - You didn't, did you?
- I paid 10 dollars. - Really?
- How about you? - I paid.
Come on, So Min.
- So Min. - Why didn't you pay?
I really paid. I want to cry.
- I paid 20 dollars. - You didn't pay, did you?
I can show you.
What's wrong with you, So Min?
- This is so unfair. - Wait.
- Han Na. - Who didn't pay?
- Come on. - You didn't pay.
- Gosh, So Min. - It was So Min.
Someone should tell them the truth.
- Seriously. - You said you would deposit.
- It was the minimum. - It's you who didn't pay.
- Why didn't you pay the minimum? - You really didn't pay.
- I paid 20 dollars. - Here's what I think.
- I really paid. - Me too.
Two people didn't pay.
I paid 20 dollars.
Stop lying.
- I swear that I paid. - That's so mean.
You didn't pay 20 dollars.
- I'm innocent. - Two people didn't pay.
- Our team leader paid. - I'm serious.
- We couldn't win because of you. - Okay.
Our team leader paid.
- She did. - Two people didn't.
She looks like she paid.
(No one trusts each other.)
(What will happen in the next round?)
(They move onto the next mission site.)
We asked you to sit with your team members.
Why is Kwang Soo sitting between two women?
(What's the reason?)
- We talked about it. - It was because of me.
It's because So Min changed her seat.
- Why did you sit there? - It's a present from me.
- Like this? Okay. - Okay.
Change your seat with Se Chan.
With Se Chan? Okay.
What's the matter?
- You can't stand sitting there? - Is it that bad?
- So Min told me to sit here. - What's going on?
Do you like Su Jin that much?
- Can't you stand it? - All the seats...
- were taken. - He doesn't talk to me at all.
(Kwang Soo doesn't talk to me.)
- What do you mean? - He's like that.
He only shows the side of his face...
- when he's next to you. - I'm always criticized...
whether I talk or not.
- The profile of your face... - What should I do?
isn't handsome.
What are you talking about?
You'll stand out.
How could you do that, Seok Jin?
- How could you deposit nothing? - I deposited 30 dollars.
- I bet Jae Seok didn't pay. - Jae Seok is more suspicious.
- We know the truth. - Right?
They're trying to set me up.
- If you had paid... - They're lying about the hint.
Why didn't you pay when you make...
so many donations?
(Jae Seok makes donations to earthquake victims in Pohang.)
- Was 10 dollars too much? - Goodness.
(Jae Seok turns into a miser.)
- All he had to pay was the minimum. - I can't believe it.
- This is making me angry. - 10 dollars isn't much.
You should have paid 10 dollars.
- Don't you have an conscience? - Even Su Jin is accusing me.
He swore to us with his hand on his chest.
He said that he paid.
- Where did he put his hand? - Where?
- Where was it exactly? - There.
That's not the chest.
His chest is right here.
- Come on. - This is where his chest is.
He's telling the truth if he puts his hand here.
- That's ridiculous. - This isn't his chest.
- It's on the appendix. - That makes no sense.
To be honest,
it's surprising that there was even 50 dollars in total.
- I trusted our team members. - Listen.
If I could turn back time, I'd take my money back.
I really paid 10 dollars.
I saw their faces when the total was announced.
Kwang Soo looked so shocked.
I really paid 10 dollars.
- I paid. - He definitely didn't pay.
I think Ji Hyo paid 20, I paid 20, and she paid 10.
Neither of them paid anything.
How much you have individually is important.
Right.
Next mission is called 5-Second Logic Game.
(5-Second Logic Game)
- What's that? - It's difficult.
Do we play in order?
(What is 5-Second Logic Game?)
It's a team game. If you make a logical sentence with...
five given words in order, you clear the mission.
- In order? - 10 dollars will be taken away...
from a member of the losing team.
- You'll take it away? - Yes.
(10 dollars will be deducted.)
- From anyone? - It can't be mine.
Once someone with experience plays the game,
everyone will understand.
- Let's play without practice. - Okay.
Jae Seok is good at it.
- I'm very good. - Jae Seok should play.
Let's start with Jae Seok.
Okay.
Start.
Crown of the head, did you use the bathroom?
Was Kwang Soo there?
- Jack Spot... - He fails.
(He can't continue the sentence.)
What kind of demonstration was that?
There are people who don't understand.
They'll misunderstand.
(What kind of game is this?)
- Why is he talking that way? - Haha.
Tell them that I'll try again.
"Crown of the head."
"Did you use the bathroom?"
Do we speak with an accent?
- I'll try again. -"Crown of the head."
- Hey. - "Did you use the bathroom?"
- Let's go. - Let's do it.
Everyone, you should read more books.
If you read more books,
- you can make sentences easily. - That's good.
- That sounds good. - You should read books.
- Besides, we're in Busan. - Get ready.
- We should speak with their accent. - Right.
- Start, let's go. - Next is Se Chan.
- Go. - Have you been to New Zealand?
That's where I broke up.
While riding a jet boat, Kwang Soo's pants...
(Kwang Soo's pants?)
(Se Chan fails.)
- What did he say? - What did you say?
You should read more.
- What did he say? - You should read more books.
You should read more books.
- Did I doze off while reading? - That didn't make sense.
(He blurts out sentences that make no sense.)
- Kwang Soo, you should try. - Sure.
Jae Seok, let me try this.
- I need to be quick on my feet. - Exactly.
- I just need to focus. - Precisely.
Get ready. Start.
So Min will be my love interest.
It started in Darwin...
when we got waxed with crocodiles.
(Kwang Soo succeeds.)
- You did it. - Okay!
- You did it. - No way.
- Where is Darwin? - He got waxed...
- What's "Darwin"? - This doesn't count.
- It's a name of a region. - It's a name of a city.
- It's where we faced our penalty. - It's in Australia.
- Really? - It makes sense, doesn't it?
Kwang Soo, we did that in Darwin?
(We did that in Darwin?)
You were each other's love interests.
I was just making up. It was just a sentence.
(Were we each other's love interests?)
Their potential love affair started from So Min's house.
Didn't it start from So Min's house?
- What are you talking about? - I'm right about this!
- There was no love affair. - You should come clean about it.
Su Jin, you can choose a member,
and the chosen member will pay 10 dollars.
But someone probably didn't pay 10 dollars earlier, right?
Or two people might not have.
- Let's be honest. - I really paid 20 dollars.
Why don't you pay? Okay?
(So Min, you didn't pay the money earlier, right?)
- I bet they're Haha and So Min. - I paid 20 dollars.
Jae Seok, I really put down 20 dollars. I'm serious.
If you pay 10 dollars now,
I'll believe that you paid 20 dollars.
- She wouldn't put down 20 dollars. - Exactly.
So Min, don't you dare lie!
(He suddenly speaks with an accent.)
Hey, you. I'm going to...
(There comes Choi Min Sik.)
She's getting mad now.
Hey, I even went to the sauna with Dream.
(Dream is Haha's son.)
(Choi Min Sik's impression is the only one she can do.)
(She does the impression again.)
- He's too young to go to a sauna. - Why would you go there with him?
Who is Dream?
- Smelly Hair, you better watch out. - You're...
- Dream's dad, right? - How dare you get my son involved?
- Seriously? - Hey.
- Isn't the accent from North Korea? - I feel so wronged.
- What are you saying? - Hey.
Isn't that from Hamgyong Province?
- Hamgyong Province. - Is it from that province?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors. That's fair.
- Let's do that. - Okay.
- All right. - Get ready.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(So Min and Jong Kook lose.)
- Okay! - Yes!
- This is great. - My goodness.
(I can't believe this.)
- You're being punished. - You deserve it.
My gosh, this is one filthy world.
Did you just realize that?
So Min, pay 10 dollars.
So Min.
(Will So Min have to pay?)
- So Min. - I was going to lead a good life.
- Rock-paper-scissors - You'll have to pay.
(Whoever loses will pay 10 dollars.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Can So Min, who thinks the world is filthy, keep her 10 dollars?)
(Poor So Min! She loses the game.)
- So Min, you must pay 10 dollars. - So Min.
- You must pay it now. - You're doomed.
So she ends up paying it.
- Is it your first time paying? - Are you paying it?
So Min, I saw this coming for you.
(Unbelievable. The world is so not fair!)
(A restaurant next to the sea)
This is a crab restaurant.
(Why are there boxes with crab drawings?)
A chance card and meal tickets are at stake for this mission.
(A chance card and meal tickets are at stake for this mission.)
(They can get both the chance card and meal tickets.)
- Hey, our meals depend on this. - This is for the meal tickets.
- Food! - Food!
(All of a sudden, they feel competitive.)
- We must win. - We can eat crabs.
- We must eat these. - Hey, I thought...
- I actually like... - Look at the crab shells.
I really like shellfish.
- What is that? - Can you smell it?
- It looks delicious. - My gosh.
- It looks so good. - Seriously.
(The crab shells are the tastiest. They are perfect with rice.)
It looks really good.
- You can't eat it yet. - Put that down.
- It looks so good. - We can't even touch them.
A chance card and meal tickets are at stake for this mission.
The mission is called Box Sweeper.
- Box Sweeper? - Box Sweeper?
Two members from each team will play the game.
They will choose random boxes and cross by stepping on the boxes.
You may dance to the song until I blow the whistle.
Then stand on the box of your choice.
For the first box, you must step on the box in front of you.
After that, you can choose the boxes freely and continue on.
If you fall into a box with ice water, you're out.
There's ice water?
(If they fall into a box with ice water, they're eliminated.)
When everyone is done crossing,
the team with a higher number of survivors wins.
The boxes have ice water in them?
- In that case, we will... - Let's choose Ji Hyo.
- choose Ji Hyo. - She's mostly lucky.
Ji Hyo...
- and Seok Jin will play. - Me?
- Ji Hyo and Seok Jin. - Okay!
Jee and Ji Siblings.
(This is the combination of lucky and unlucky members.)
- Which one of us should try? - Anyone can try it.
- Then you should play. - Sure.
So Min and I will play this game.
- Let's go. - Let's do this!
Okay.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo versus So Min and Se Chan)
We'll begin now.
(They will dance before choosing their positions.)
(He dances like an old man. He looks silly.)
My goodness. That's terrible.
(That's my box!)
(Should I move up to the stage now?)
Seriously. This is such an eye sore.
I hate it.
Her dance doesn't suit the song at all.
What's wrong with your move?
Seriously.
I hate it so much.
(You... You are something else.)
- Unbelievable. - Stop shaking your bottom.
- I hate So Min's dance. - Look at So Min's bottom.
I hate it.
I seriously don't like her dance.
- We need to eat crab. - Let's eat crab!
(Their dance time before choosing the boxes is over.)
- Okay. - Okay.
(They finish selecting the positions while dancing.)
(For the first move, they must step on the box in front of them.)
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(Which one will be the first to fall into the ice water?)
(Splashing)
Okay. He had to be eliminated anyway.
That was bound to happen.
How could that happen?
How is that possible?
How is this possible?
(Seok Jin is out.)
How on earth...
From this point on, you can choose any boxes you want.
It's up to you.
Se Chan, that's the box.
- Okay. - Let's get it.
Pick one in front of Seok Jin's box. There won't be another one there.
He has a point.
- You'll jump at the same time. - Jump at the same time.
- I'm going this way. - One!
- Are you going that way? - Yes.
- 1, 2, - If you move forward...
3.
(Which one will be the second one to fall into the ice water?)
My gosh, everyone made it.
(Se Chan, So Min, and Ji Hyo all pass.)
- Everyone made it. - Everyone passed.
- Everyone passed? - My gosh.
I'll choose the one in front of me.
I'll do the same then.
I'll move forward.
- I think this one is a good one. - That one looks great.
- This one? - Yes.
- The whole line seems good. - You never know.
Ji Hyo, just trust your instinct.
So Min, you should choose that one.
(Which way should I go?)
- 1, 2, 3. - What will I do?
(What's the result of the third box?)
(Screaming)
We need to beat one more member.
Let's just beat one more member.
- Ji Hyo. - Here we go.
1, 2, 3.
Okay!
(Se Chan makes it to the third row safely.)
- Okay! - 1 of 2 is a good one.
It's either this or that. Ji Hyo, it's 1 of these 2.
- That was good, wasn't it? - Which one has a better chance?
- We're not sure about this one. - Exactly.
- This is likely to be safe. - This box has a better chance.
All right.
Are you serious, So Min?
(She suddenly dances to celebrate Se Chan's success.)
Get out of the way!
- 1, 2, 3. - I don't know anymore.
(What's the result of the box Ji Hyo chooses?)
(Ji Hyo makes it to the third row just like Se Chan.)
- What's the deal with her? - We need to get through one more.
She's amazing.
We only have one row to go.
(Se Chan is feeling nervous for some reason.)
- Se Chan, move forward. - Forward?
Se Chan, move forward.
- Okay, I'll take your advice. - My gosh, this...
- Move forward. - That one looks safe.
- No, I'll listen to Su Jin. - Choose that box.
I'll take your advice.
Is that the box?
- Okay, I'll choose it. - She's the leader.
Ji Hyo, follow your instinct.
(He repeats his advice.)
(Will Su Jin's decision win? Or will Ji Hyo's instinct win?)
- 1, 2, - This one?
- 1, 2, 3. - This one?
(Who will be the final winner?)
(Both members fail to choose.)
- Both of them fell. - Both of them fell.
- Both of them fell into the water. - That was close.
- What a bummer. - I told you so.
- The boxes can't be in a row. - Both of them fell into the water.
Hey, Ms. Team Leader.
But she fell too.
- The first round is tied. - We are tied.
(Team White and Team Red both fail.)
(Kwang Soo and Han Na versus Su Jin and Jong Kook)
- I'm excited for this round. - Me too.
- I have a good feeling about this. - This is going to be fun.
- Han Na majored in ballet. - Yes.
- Han Na. - That's right.
- Can you do ballet for us? - Can you show us?
What should I do?
(She feels pressured.)
Here it goes. Go, go, go!
What do I do?
(A familiar song, "Chococo" is played.)
Shake it.
(Everyone starts dancing to the song, "Chococo".)
(She looks confused alone.)
- That's right. - Han Na, you can just dance.
Just dance however you want.
I don't know what to do.
What's up with her dance?
- Why do you dance like an old man? - Han Na, you're doing well.
(Oh, boy!)
I don't know what to do.
(This is a wrong mix of ballet and random dance.)
What is that? What is Han Na doing?
What is the dance Han Na's doing? What is that?
- What's wrong with her? - Did she really major in ballet?
Han Na.
(She doesn't feel shy anymore.)
I don't know.
(Jong Kook dances in an elegant manner with his muscular biceps.)
Hey, stand behind the boxes.
(Shaking)
- Han Na is doing great. - They are...
- They're terrible dancers, right? - Han Na.
I love Han Na's dance. I love it.
(Their dance time is over.)
(Everyone chooses the boxes in their original positions.)
- Are you sure that's the box? - Move back.
I have a bad feeling about Kwang Soo's box.
- Here I go. I must succeed. - I think he'll fall.
I have a feeling I'll fall.
(They must win this round to get the chance card.)
- Here I go. I must succeed. - I think he'll fall.
1, 2, 3.
(Falling)
I like it! We are off to a great start!
I like it.
(Laughing)
(Jong Kook is unlucky!)
It's so cold!
I haven't hit Kwang Soo in a while.
- Okay, I'm sorry. - Do well.
- Good job, Jong Kook. - Good job.
- Amazing. - Good job.
It didn't feel right.
All right. Next.
(It's the second row.)
Have you decided?
- This one. - This one?
- What about you, Han Na? - What?
Me?
This one.
(Who will pass the second row?)
(Su Jin passes the second row.)
- Nice. - Good job.
This one.
(Team White's leader succeeded.)
(What about Team Red's leader?)
My goodness. This is scary.
Kwang Soo, bye.
- Kwang Soo's last try. - Bye.
Bye, Kwang Soo.
- Bye. - You've lasted long.
You might succeed.
Goodbye.
All right. Let's do this.
- Bye. - Bye.
- 1, 2, 3. - Bye, Kwang Soo.
(Will a miracle happen to Kwang Soo?)
(Splash)
It was predictable.
Kwang Soo.
Of course.
It was predictable.
- Kwang Soo never succeeds. - It's never wrong.
(It's okay. Next year might be different.)
- All right. - Which one is it this time?
- Su Jin versus Han Na. - Our team leaders.
- Han Na, let's have crab. - Which one do you think it is?
- They can't be next to each other. - What?
(Su Jin looks determined.)
1, 2, 3.
Okay!
What is this? What do I do now?
Hold on.
This one.
- Han Na. - Han Na, you can't fail now.
- I think this one is okay. - Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. - No.
(Han Na is sure about the fourth row.)
(Is her hunch right?)
Yes!
(Han Na survives.)
Is it my turn?
(Unbelievable)
(Team Red is expected to win.)
(But Team White still has a chance.)
(I don't know.)
(With a slight chance, Su Jin jumps for the last time.)
(Su Jin survives too.)
(Both team leaders survive.)
What is this?
(What?)
We're tied!
(They're back in the game.)
I can't believe it.
(The teams are tied again.)
Is it a tie again?
- What's going on? - How is this possible?
Good job.
Let's do it like this.
1 from each team will do just 1 row.
- Just one row? - Okay.
- Who should do it? - Han Na.
- Han Na? - Han Na.
Do it. Go.
- It's... - We shouldn't touch it.
Don't touch it. It's a 50-50 chance.
This one.
This one feels right.
It might be that one.
Su Jin might have chosen the right one.
Please jump onto the box on the count of three.
Will this one be all right?
- It might not be. - We don't know.
- Gosh, I'm worried. - One...
- It might be ice. - 1, 2, 3.
(Who will win the 2nd round?)
(Team White wins.)
(Sturdy)
Yes!
How is this possible?
- We were lucky. - Oh, my gosh.
(Su Jin leads her team to victory again.)
Gosh, I fell. We won't get any crab.
(Han Na's hunch was wrong. Team Red loses.)
Han Na's team lost.
Please deposit money in the bank 1 by 1.
The same amount?
- Let's... - How much are you going to deposit?
Jae Seok, you should deposit money this time.
Let's do it like this. To find out who betrayed,
- let's deposit 10 dollars each. - 10 dollars each?
- We have to win this time. - Last time...
If we deposit...
Han Na, you should deposit a lot this time.
Okay. I'll deposit 30 dollars.
Okay.
We've agreed, right?
- I'll go first. - Han Na should go first.
- Han Na, go first. - Okay.
- Han Na, start it off. - Don't worry.
- Do it. Let's go in this order. - I'll do it.
In the order of the suitcases.
Hello. I'm here to deposit some money.
It's time to deposit some money.
(Han Na promised she'd deposit 30 dollars.)
(Will she keep her promise?)
- He was surprised. - What?
He was surprised at the amount I deposited.
- You're being suspicious. - It's true.
He said, "Oh, my."
Han Na, it didn't take so long.
I took out the money without hesitation.
- He was surprised. - How?
Like this.
(Without hesitation)
Go.
As long as we stick to our promise... Keep your words.
- Kwang Soo. - Otherwise, we'll lose again.
Go first.
- You have to deposit some. - You have to.
- We'll be watching you. - Hey.
- Do it. - Don't put your own interest...
(What will Jae Seok do?)
- Hello. - How much did the others deposit?
It's a secret.
They're misunderstanding me.
(I did deposit 10 dollars.)
(Let me see.)
I won't deposit anything.
(They're already misunderstanding me.)
- Okay. - Okay.
I've been betrayed. I won't deposit anything.
(I have to live.)
Why did you think so much?
We agreed on an amount. Why did you think?
I deposited the amount without hesitation.
- Did you? - Yes.
(It's the betrayer's turn.)
Did they deposit money?
I can't tell you.
He won't deposit anything. Never.
Kwang Soo would...
- have 100 dollars left. - He won't deposit anything.
- Did you deposit some? - Yes.
- What? - You didn't, did you?
I did, I swear.
I can even show you, I promise.
Gosh. I did.
- See the result later. - You...
- Are you sure? - Watch Seok Jin.
(You have to choose between the team and yourself.)
(Team Red is done.)
Now, Su Jin's team can choose...
a member of the other team and see the amount he or she deposited.
All right. We'll check the team leader's sense of responsibility.
Han Na.
See all you want.
I'm not afraid.
I'm really curious how much Han Na deposited.
- Right? - The man in the bank...
was surprised. "This much?"
How much she deposited...
All right.
(Did Han Na deposit 30 dollars as she promised?)
- This time? - I see.
- She's shameless. - She's unbelievable.
- It was predictable. - This is unacceptable.
With that kind smile on her face,
- she did this? - They're tricking us.
Cut it out.
- I mean... - Did you deposit 30 dollars?
I can swear on my whole family.
- Really? - Yes.
I definitely deposited 30 dollars.
- Her family? - Don't do this.
(Why would you drag your family in?)
You don't seem to believe me.
- 30, 20... - 10.
- 30, 10, - 30, 10,
- 20... - I deposited 30 dollars.
- 30... - How much is it in total?
- 80. - 50...
- 80. - 80.
(The total amount is estimated to be 80 dollars.)
- Guys, come here. - Come here.
One of us has to deposit at least 30 dollars.
We have to make a move.
Who would do that?
Hurry up.
So Min, I'm really going to do this.
(I'm determined.)
(40 dollars?)
I'm going to do it. I'm not lying.
I really hope my team will win.
(Will Haha become a hero?)
(He rips out bills without hesitation.)
(Thinking)
(He really is depositing 40 dollars.)
What?
Yes. Put them down.
- Really? - Yes.
I'm so cool, right?
(Satisfied)
Yes.
Give me a kiss on my forehead.
(Give me a compliment.)
(Kiss)
I got a compliment.
(Happy)
Are you done?
Is it my turn?
I did it.
(Thanks to Haha, Team White has an advantage.)
(Will they maintain it to the end?)
(Team White is done too.)
All right. Let me announce the result.
(Result)
Wait and see.
Even if they deposited 80 dollars, we might still win.
- It'll be so cool. - The losing team is...
(Who will win the dilemma game?)
All right. Let me announce the result.
(Result)
Wait and see.
Even if they deposited 80 dollars, we might still win.
- It'll be so cool. - The losing team is...
(Who will win the dilemma game?)
With 40 dollars...
(With 40 dollars...)
The scores are tied.
- What? - What?
(Wait, I paid 40 dollars.)
- Gosh. - Goodness.
- That's terrible. - How could they?
- My goodness. - It's obvious who didn't pay.
- Listen. - Wasn't I right?
- I was right. - What happened?
I paid 10 dollars.
- You're terrible. - I paid this much.
I swear that I paid.
- How could you do this? - Who was it?
How could you?
- I really paid. - You're terrible.
- I'm serious. - How could you?
- Let me ask you. - Seriously?
- I promise that I paid. - I definitely paid.
I paid too.
You punks.
The three didn't pay.
- If you paid 30 dollars... - What about him?
- I paid this much. - I paid 10 dollars.
Stop it, Haha.
You didn't pay.
- I paid 10. - You didn't.
- I did. - You didn't pay.
If you paid 10 dollars,
I'll come to your house every morning.
I'll clean the house and do your laundry.
I'll fold your siblings' underwear.
That's enough, Haha.
- All right, let's go eat. - This is so unfair.
It's time to eat.
None of you paid.
- Right? - No.
Gosh, look at the food.
- It looks delicious. - It looks amazing.
I'm so hungry.
(Team White wins a feast of snow crab.)
(It includes soft white crab meat...)
(and savory crab fried rice.)
Didn't we eat that before?
It's the same dried laver.
- Dried laver? - Yes.
(The losing team gets rice with dried laver.)
- Gosh. - This is so upsetting.
It's upsetting that we get so little food,
but their lies make me more upset.
I don't need to eat.
Please change the members on my team.
- Seriously. - What did you say?
We lost because of you.
- What did I do? - Stop it.
- I don't believe Han Na. - Forget it.
Thank you for the food.
Is this real?
- Gosh. - Thanks for the food.
(As soon as they take a bite,)
(they can't stop being impressed.)
It's delicious.
Dip it in the sauce.
By the way,
they can't finish that much food.
Isn't it delicious?
That looks so delicious.
I'll give you a bite because it's too delicious.
(He takes a spoon of crab fried rice.)
(It's a mixture of crab meat and savory intestines.)
(It's the amazing crab fried rice.)
I want to give them a bite.
(They get up suddenly.)
(I want a bite.)
- Give them a bite. - Have some.
Give them some.
- That was quick. - Her mouth is too big.
- Gosh, she took such a big bite. - It's really good.
(She applauds at the taste.)
- Here you go. - It's so delicious.
- He gives it to everyone. - Does he?
It's so delicious.
Tasting is over.
(Tasting is over now.)
(My goodness)
I'm sorry, but it's over.
That's so annoying.
Couldn't you tell us how much you were giving?
- That's annoying. - I meant to give two spoonfuls.
I'll give three spoonfuls later.
(He offers to give three spoonfuls later.)
- It must be fun to wait. - That's right.
It must be fun to wait.
(Those who wait will get fried rice.)
Are you waiting for a bite?
(What are you doing?)
I heard the market will open soon.
That's funny.
- The market is open. - Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Don't give it for free.
(He gives sushi this time.)
- Try some. - It's delicious.
I saw it.
(It tastes so strong.)
I put a lot of wasabi on it.
- Really? - Yes.
I'm sure it was an edible amount.
- Of course. - Sure.
I don't think so.
I have one bite.
- 1st come, 1st serve. - I'm coming.
(I'll eat it.)
Okay.
What are they doing?
How did he eat that?
She gave him all the sauce.
Really?
(It's a combination of green and red sauce.)
- My goodness. - That's impressive.
- Come on, So Min. - Goodness.
That's impressive.
Why did you eat it?
Let's play Game of Wits.
(They start Game of Wits.)
One.
- 2. - 3.
- Four. - Come, Jae Seok.
- It's Jae Seok. - Jae Seok.
What? He didn't even play.
He wasn't paying attention.
Is it given if you don't play?
- What? - It means that he was quick.
It was the person who stays still.
- He did a good job. - He's quick.
He's good.
1st come, 1st serve.
(Haha offers food.)
I never did this.
(He's determined to eat well this time.)
He must like ginger a lot.
(He gets a spoonful of ginger.)
He must like it.
Goodness, Kwang Soo.
It's because you're being too easy.
It's delicious.
I'll have diarrhea tonight.
(He's sure of having diarrhea.)
There's something here.
It's a cultural center.
Here's your last chance to win the Chance Card.
The mission is called Random Shoe Space.
(Random Shoe Space)
Obtain the opponent's name tag, and fill in...
any of the 20 empty shoe spaces.
Once you steal a shoe of the opposing team member,
you obtain the person's name tag.
You may stick the name tag...
on any of the empty spaces on the name board.
Before the race,
each team will receive reflection cards.
You may discuss in whose shoes you'll put the reflection cards.
Last scenes are set up in various parts of the building.
Find a small shoe in a box.
If you hit a member of the opposing team with the shoe,
- you obtain his name tag again. - That sounds fun.
Can you hit any part of the body?
Yes, it's the same as dodgeball.
Each team will take its place.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(Which color will the name board be filled with?)
If there's someone who only speaks the truth...
(Let's have an honest talk.)
- Tell us. - It makes no sense.
Tell us honestly since there's no camera.
- There are no cameras? - There aren't any.
No one else is here.
- It's only the five of us. - No way.
There are no cameras.
- This is real. - Tell us what you want to say.
Someone might hear us,
so I'll make a gesture.
(Please trust the 4 of us.)
Whom are you talking to?
I want everyone to see it. During Round Two...
(I paid 40 dollars.)
You paid 40 dollars?
(Believe me too.)
(The members become habitual liars.)
I believe you since there's no camera.
Show us how much you paid since there's no camera.
Right.
(They continue to lie.)
(Will they work well as a team?)
- Goodness. - There's no camera.
Why do you keep lying?
(Will they work well as a team?)
We should use the reflection card wisely.
- The easy target... - You should keep it.
should keep it in his shoe.
- Do you want it? - He should keep it.
(Between Kwang Soo and Jae Seok, who will keep the reflection card?)
Do we have to take off the shoe that has the reflection card?
If we take off the other shoe,
- it doesn't count. - I see.
Which shoe you put it in is important.
The reflection card is effective only once.
It can be used only once.
An easy target should keep it.
- I'll keep it. - I'm an easy target.
People will expect you to have it.
(Between So Min and Haha, who will keep it?)
Let's start the race.
- Let's do well. - Seriously.
- 10. - Let's win this time.
- We should win. - We kept losing.
- Let's win. - Also,
- let's pay. - Let me make it clear.
- Seven. - I have no greed.
- Six. - I'll give all my money.
- We don't need to win. - I'll give it all.
You should pay before saying anything.
- It's because... - Four.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Two. - We can do it.
One. The race starts.
(The race starts.)
- Go. - Go.
We should find something first.
Is that a box?
(Did Kwang Soo find a box?)
- Is there a shoe? - No.
- It's where you take photos. - It's a photo zone.
- Like this. - I thought they were shoes.
It's a photo zone.
Is there anything?
I'll go this way, So Min.
What's this?
"Kwang Soo is a fool."
(What is this?)
(It's so amazing.)
It was printed.
It says "Kwang Soo is a fool."
(What is she doing in the middle of a race?)
It's so cool.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
Where are you?
She's so needy from the start.
Look. This is cool.
What?
(Reflection card)
I made a reflection card.
Really?
(Her ability to deceive is advanced.)
I made it.
I must find the shoes.
Where could they be?
Jong Kook, I think it's here.
(Team Red finds Haha alone.)
It's Haha.
Let's get him. Keep watching.
Let's go.
Jong Kook.
Where's Jong Kook?
(Hello, Haha.)
Come on, hurry.
(Ji Hyo approaches him stealthily.)
Hurry.
(You're mine, Haha.)
(It's our chance to get him.)
(Haha reaches a dead end.)
I think Jong Kook's coming.
It's now. Close the door, Jong Kook.
Wait. Be careful.
Be careful.
If he uses a reflection card, it's over.
- It'll be over. - No.
You can't.
(They need to finish before Jong Kook gets here.)
Hold on. I don't think he's trying on purpose.
(She slips a shoe off.)
(Does Haha's shoe have a reflection card?)
- It's a reflection card. - Right? I knew it.
(It's what they thought.)
- Let's see. - See you later.
- Please go ahead, Haha. - All right.
Thank you.
I told you.
It looked like he wasn't trying on purpose.
(He exits with a deep sense of satisfaction.)
An easy target should keep it.
I'm an easy target.
People will expect you to have it.
Me. I'll be fine.
Inside? I see.
(Haha volunteered because it's not as predictable.)
I'll do it.
I told you.
It looked like he wasn't trying on purpose.
- It was a bait. - No.
Now,
they don't have it anymore.
That's good.
We would have gotten the reflection card at one point.
It's gone now.
(4th floor auditorium where the name board is)
Hello.
(The first sticker goes to Han Na.)
(Su Jin is going around by herself.)
Ji Hyo, where are you...
What are you doing?
(I'm here to catch you.)
No way.
(She's everywhere today.)
(Help me.)
Help me!
(We'll help Ji Hyo.)
It's Su Jin.
Get her.
(They don't have a reflection card anymore.)
(Su Jin is out, and they get her name tag.)
There's nothing. I don't have anything.
(We can't give the center spot away.)
Let's get them.
(Team Red is unstoppable.)
Get them.
Hold on.
We were going up.
Go the other way.
Hold on.
What do you mean?
- Grab him. - No.
Se Chan!
I have a reflection card.
It's a reflection card.
(It's a fake one.)
It's fake.
(She is cheating all day.)
It's a reflection card.
Go up. Let's go up first.
Let's go up.
Let go.
No, he's faking it.
(No, he's faking it.)
- Let go. - This one.
(Does Jae Seok have a reflection card as well?)
It's a reflection card.
(He does.)
(I tricked you all.)
Okay.
So Min.
(That was a waste of energy.)
(He looks around.)
Shoes? Small shoes?
(Where are the small shoes?)
My gosh.
(He finds the Lost Shoe he can use to eliminate people.)
I'll put it in my pocket.
(He feels confident now.)
I can see them.
(You're all dead.)
They used their reflection card.
Let's go.
(Let's go and fight.)
They're coming. What should we do, Se Chan?
What should we do?
(I'm scared.)
(Seok Jin leads his team with the Lost Shoe.)
(Jong Kook approaches quietly...)
(to help Se Chan who's alone.)
It's Jong Kook.
(Be careful.)
It had begun.
(He attacks Jae Seok who already used his reflection card.)
(If you throw the Lost Shoe and hit somebody,)
(you get their name tag.)
It's the same rule as dodgeball.
Now, Jong Kook.
(It's time to throw the Lost Shoe.)
Shoe.
(He threw it.)
(What?)
He caught it.
I got it.
What?
I got you.
He's out.
(He caught the shoe and threw it at Jae Seok.)
How did you catch that?
- How did you catch that? - Hold on.
Why did you let him catch it?
No, he wasn't supposed to catch it.
You wasted it.
My goodness.
He's so skilled.
Seok Jin, you're more skilled than him.
- You're the skilled one. - No.
You're the truly skilled one.
That made me so mad.
Seok Jin is a joke.
I was going to use it earlier but saved it.
I saved it for later.
Where are you going?
- What? - Where are you going?
It's dangerous to be alone.
- I want to blend in. - My gosh, Seok Jin.
(Can you send him to the other team?)
(The teams are tied 3 to 3.)
Isn't it more beneficial for us to attack him?
- Haha. - He has a shoe.
- You hid a shoe, right? - He has a shoe.
- You have a small shoe, right? - It's a shoe.
I think he has it.
We can catch it.
The small shoe?
(Haha looks for a chance and runs at them.)
Catch him. It's a fake shoe.
(It's a big shoe.)
- Catch him. - It's fake.
We got you.
Let go. It's the scriptwriter's shoe.
It's the scriptwriter's. It's her shoe.
I knew it. That scared me.
It was fake.
- His shoe was this big. - It was too big...
to be a small shoe.
Wasn't that so smart?
- No! - It was her shoe.
(So Min accidentally drops by.)
Catch her.
Help me.
- Help me, Se Chan! - Get her.
- Help me. - Catch her.
Please, Se Chan.
Catch her. Rip it.
Don't do that.
- Catch her. - Don't do that.
(When something happens to...)
(my team member...)
Don't get close.
(Here comes the problem-solver.)
Don't!
(He shows up quietly and turns the situation around.)
- He got Han Na's shoe. - It's Han Na's.
Han Na.
He's here.
What's wrong with you?
(You tried to get me out?)
- You're so mean. - What?
How am I mean?
(The race is halfway done.)
Out.
(The name board fills up after fierce battles.)
- I'm coming. - Out!
Watch out.
- No, no. - Out.
You're out.
- You first? - Here. You're out.
There's one space left.
I wish I found one shoe.
Let's go down using the stairs.
(There's one space left. It's pure war.)
- There was nothing upstairs. - Right?
Is it downstairs?
(Where's Team Red?)
- Hey! - You scared me.
(You scared me.)
Hurry.
(Block them.)
Everybody, come here.
- There are too many of them. - If we...
- There are many of them? - have to fight here...
There are too many of them.
I think it's better to back off.
What if we fight in this small space then?
They're here.
They're all here.
Come out.
Kwang Soo, you're a coward. Come out.
Come out, Kwang Soo.
I'll face you.
(They try to lure Kwang Soo with Jong Kook hiding.)
Come out, Kwang Soo. I'll face you.
I'll face you.
- Is it 1 on 1? - Yes.
- Is it? - Yes.
Come in then.
No, I can't trust you.
- No way. - Do it here.
- No... - Kwang Soo!
Jong Kook is next to her.
Look at So Min.
(Their 1st attempt is not successful.)
We can face them head-on. There are only four of them.
- Open it. - One...
Hold on.
It's Jong Kook.
(We can only go forward now.)
Grab his hand.
- I grabbed him. - Okay.
Push it. Go.
Go.
Three.
(Grabbing)
Push it. In 1, 2, 3.
(They both have their teams on their backs,)
(so let's face ace versus ace.)
Take Jong Kook's shoe.
Take his shoe off.
- Hurry. Take it off. - Good job.
- Good job. - Good job, Ji Hyo.
Good job. The other shoe.
(They have nowhere to back off now. It's a battle of strength.)
(Kwang Soo appears out of nowhere.)
- So Min is out. - Hey.
So Min is out.
(He came from the back. How did that happen?)
I'll go to the first floor.
(He left the battle to his team members...)
(and decided to take a detour.)
(While everybody was busy,)
(he approached from the back and attacked So Min.)
- So Min is out. - Hey.
So Min is out.
(Their plan worked.)
The situation is over.
So Min is out.
- I didn't know he was there. - You have to look.
- It's over. The situation is over. - All right.
Good job.
(Team Red's teamwork and Kwang Soo's strategy stood out.)
- Go upstairs. - Good job.
We have to decide who the winner is.
It's the same rule as penalty kicks in soccer.
(They'll decide the winning team by applying the penalty kick rules.)
(Penalty kicks?)
(People's names are in the squares.)
Each of you get to kick a shoe.
It's better for Team Red to get it in Team White's boxes,
and it's better for Team White to go for Team Red's boxes.
For example, if Kwang Soo goes first for Team Red...
and Haha goes first for his team,
if Kwang Soo gets his shoe in Team White's box...
and Haha does as well, Team White loses.
(If Haha gets his shoe in his team's box as well, they lose.)
- Right away? - You lose right away.
Really?
If you get the same team in a row, that team loses.
It's so far.
- It's too far. - It is far.
Who's going first?
- Let's start right away. - Go, Se Chan.
Let's go.
Go, Se Chan.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
- What's the order? - The winner?
- The winner goes first. - Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo wins with paper.)
You're first place.
- Okay. Ji Hyo. - Yes.
Nevis.
Swing.
You'll do great, Se Chan.
(He gets ready...)
(with Haha cheering for him.)
All right. Get a white box.
(They're hoping them to fail.)
(If he gets it in a white box, there's a good chance they'll lose.)
(It's beneficial for his team to get it in a red box.)
- White box. - White box.
- Yes! - Yes!
(He's unlucky.)
(He's in despair, and she's delighted.)
Ji Hyo, it's over if you get it in a white box.
End it. Get it in a white box.
I can't believe I got it in my name.
(He got it in a white box and his own name.)
- Be quiet. - Get a white box.
- Go for it. - Relax.
- Relax. - Let's end this.
(Her shoe flies low as if she's skipping a stone.)
Okay.
Let's end this.
(It heads left. She might miss the board entirely.)
(Please miss.)
(Nice shot, Ji Hyo.)
(It went straight into a white box.)
It went in.
(What are you, Ji Hyo?)
Is this how you do it?
- This is how you do it. - This is how you do it, right?
- This is how you do it. - This is amazing.
So the final winning team is...
Han Na's team.
(Team Red wins.)
- We did it. - This is amazing.
(Ji Hyo is so trustworthy.)
That was like skipping a stone.
(When will I be like her?)
(Running Bank is finally open.)
(Give me your money.)
(The team with the most money wins.)
(The person with the most money left wins tenfold.)
Explain this to me.
- What's going on? - I paid a lot of money earlier,
so the rest of you should pay.
Don't do that.
It doesn't make sense for the other team not to pay.
Because we have the same amount of money left.
But they gave us 10 dollars.
- That's right. - They have 10 dollars less.
If we all pay, we win.
(If Team Red deposits all their money, they win.)
The only way for us to win is...
to deposit everything.
Hold on. If we deposit everything...
If we deposit everything,
how do we decide who's in first place?
We have to do rock-paper-scissors.
- It's only right to do that. - Let's do that.
Let's deposit everything.
He's saying we should win as a team first.
- Right. - Okay.
- Don't be a traitor. - I'm serious.
Don't be selfish.
- In 1, 2, 3. - Hands down.
Bring a suitcase each, and hand in your money.
I trust you. I'll pretend I'm your mom.
(Han Na's team has 410 dollars.)
(Su Jin's team has 400 dollars.)
(Team White has to go all-in to have a chance to win.)
(They usually don't trust each other. Would it be different today?)
I'm a big fan of myself today. I'm so cool.
I'm happy I'm doing this for my team.
(He is impressed with himself.)
All right. Han Na's team...
can choose one person and ask for their amount.
In 1, 2, 3.
- So Min. - So Min.
You'll be shocked.
I'll be reborn today.
Get ready...
- to shed tears for me. - Stop it.
I mean it. This is so not fair.
For this round, So Min handed in...
This round?
For this round?
Of course, it's this round.
(If So Min betrayed her team, Team White's strategy will fail.)
(60 dollars)
It's all-in.
(From So Min's amount, it's obvious they are all-in.)
- Jae Seok. - I'll go first.
I'll go, Ji Hyo.
- Go ahead. - I'll go.
Don't betray us.
(If Team White is all-in, Team Red has to as well to win.)
(They have 410 dollars, and Team White has 400.)
(Is it all-in for the team or saving up for a personal victory?)
(Kwang Soo goes last.)
I have a question.
- What happens if it's a tie? - Don't ask.
If it's a tie, we'll do something to decide.
What if I'm first place but tied with the other team?
Will I still be first?
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Hey.
We'll have a match off between the first places.
- Between the first places? - Yes.
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Hey.
What are you going to do?
(He takes a deep breath...)
(and steps into Running Bank with a dilemma.)
The winner gets tenfold the amount...
that the winning team has.
(Is that right?)
Even if it's tenfold, it won't be much.
It's only 100 dollars.
Are you going to lose our trust?
With 10 dollars, how much gimbap can you get?
Rather, if you win and get to pick,
you can pick me for penalty.
(There's the money, but you can also choose who gets the penalty.)
(There was that too.)
You can soak me in water.
- No. - You can do that.
- Kwang Soo. Kwang Soo! - Kwang Soo.
(He puts his money in his pocket.)
- Hand it in. - Do it.
- You have to hand it in. - Kwang Soo.
- Think about it. - Hurry up.
(Kwang Soo deposits the money.)
We trust you.
Yes. There's no point...
- hesitating. - Right.
- There's no point hesitating. - We trust you.
There's no point. Okay.
We have the results.
I'll announce the losing team.
The losing team deposited...
The losing team's total is...
- 360 dollars. - See?
- See? - They lose.
- Somebody kept the money? - They did.
- They lose with 360 dollars. - They're missing 40 dollars.
- I think we won. - Someone betrayed.
(Who betrayed their team?)
The winning team is...
Han Na's team.
(Team Red wins.)
(Where did 40 dollars go?)
- Yes. - This is beautiful.
- We deposited everything? - I told you this would happen.
(This is hard to see on Running Man.)
That's right.
The winner in Team Red with the most amount of money...
- There's somebody? - They have money left?
- There is somebody? - I gave up everything.
Kwang Soo wins with 20 dollars left.
(When everybody went all-in, I took the road not taken.)
- He did it. - My gosh.
He's unbelievable.
Tell me this.
Who's the winner in our team? Who won from the losing team?
The winner in Team White is...
Se Chan with...
- 30 dollars. - See?
2nd place is So Min with 10 dollars.
Gosh.
It's only 10 dollars.
If we deposited everything, it would have worked.
Wait, I have a question.
Is there a second place in our team?
- There isn't. - They have nothing left.
You're the only one who have money left.
- You have to be punished. - You need to be punished.
Why are you booing at me?
- I heard that. - You need to be punished.
- Take your 200 dollars. - Take your money.
- You need to get the penalty. - Take the penalty.
Hold on.
According to the rules,
don't I pick 1 from my team and 3 from the other?
- Yes. According to the rules, - We talked about this.
the winner picks one person from their own team...
and three from the other team.
Okay.
- Jong Kook mentioned himself. - Right.
I'll pick him...
- for sure. - Okay.
I'm so sweaty. I want a shower. This is driving me nuts.
- I'll exclude you then. - No, no.
- I won't pick you. - I'm so sweaty.
- Come on. - It's not you.
Go to a public bathhouse. No.
I'll pick.
I remember that scene.
When we were eating, Jae Seok was...
supposed to treat Haha like an older brother,
but what did you do instead?
- He finished his food. - I don't know. I don't remember.
Do you want the penalty?
No, let me repeat myself.
- I'm on your side, Kwang Soo. - Then...
- Then let's... - You're on his side?
- I'm on your side, Kwang Soo. - Seok Jin.
- What's wrong with you? - Seok Jin, you're exempt.
Okay. Yes. Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is our sun
- Hey! - I always love you
- Kwang Soo, you're beautiful - Kwang Soo
I'm jealous that you're tall, I'm really jealous
I'll give you a kiss
- I'll give you a kiss - I'll give you a kiss
Let's do this. You can stand,
and Kwang Soo will push three people forward.
- All right. - Okay. Three people?
- Three people. - Finish this off fast.
Don't be so hopeful.
Don't be.
(So Min gets picked.)
I can take my shirt off.
(Which two should I pick?)
- He didn't even stop to think. - Kwang Soo.
I have to receive the penalty.
Ask him to pick you.
Kwang Soo, I have to receive the penalty in this situation.
Don't pick Se Chan so that his heart will stay heavy.
(Don't pick Se Chan so that his heart will stay heavy.)
Don't pick Se Chan.
Kwang Soo,
- why don't you pick me instead? - Today,
who left money behind besides Se Chan?
- So Min. - So Min.
- Then I will pick again. - Ask her to come back.
- No. - You will pick other three members.
(It shouldn't go this way.)
You will pick other three members.
What are you doing? Get up.
- All right. - We will receive the penalty.
- We will make them feel bad. - Why did choose me?
Okay. I will receive the penalty in their stead.
(I get it.)
With the heart of a mother, I will receive it in their stead.
For Se Chan and So Min,
- I will receive it in their stead. - We need to fix their habit.
Kwang Soo, please pick me.
No, please pick me.
Kwang Soo, you have to pick me.
I will receive the penalty twice.
I will push.
I will receive the penalty.
Please push me hard.
I want to receive the penalty with Se Chan.
(With a generous heart,)
Okay.
(he picks So Min and Se Chan.)
Thank you. My heart feels light now.
He doesn't pick Jong Kook when he wants the penalty.
My goodness.
So Min, Se Chan, and Haha are chosen.
Now, Kwang Soo will pick a member from Team Red.
Please push him or her from behind.
Can't Kwang Soo receive the penalty?
Kwang Soo shouldn't receive the penalty.
He is the winner. That wouldn't make any sense.
In my team...
He makes me so angry.
He makes me angrier than getting hit with water bomb.
He is so annoying.
- Feeling! - Intuition!
- Cross! - Cross!
- For goodness' sake. - Kwang Soo is the best.
This is why I like Seok Jin.
This is why I love you.
Gosh, I am angry. I am so angry.
From my team,
I will pick the person who is on my right.
(He wants his favorite member to take a shower.)
- Kwang Soo. - That was good.
- Come here. - It's a wonderful idea.
I made up my mind...
- during the first game. - The first game?
- That's when I made up my mind. - Good choice.
You made the right decision.
Thus, water bomb goes...
to Se Chan, So Min, Haha, and Seok Jin.
All right.
Kwang Soo will receive the prize money of 200 dollars.
(Kwang Soo, the winner, receives the prize money of 200 dollars.)
He even gets 200 dollars.
Why did you pick me?
I decided to pick you...
when you put so much sauce under the rice.
- There is a reason. - He did that.
- I added ginger. - He added ginger.
- Ginger. - Hold on.
Didn't you guys put ginger, wasabi, and chogochujang?
(Ginger, wasabi, and chogochujang)
- Wasabi. - Okay!
- I know you did it. - Yes, we did.
There is a reason behind my decision.
There is a reason.
Hurry up, and stand over there.
Okay.
Today, Kwang Soo...
- left behind 20 dollars. - He is incredible.
- Seriously. - Had I not done that,
I would have received the penalty.
(Had I not done that, I would have received the penalty.)
That's plausible.
- You are right. - My goodness.
- I have done this many times. - You are mistaken.
I have done this many times.
- I understand. - Before anything,
Su Jin and Han Na did...
a great job today.
- Thank you. - How was everything, Su Jin?
Visiting Running Man and playing games...
made me want to come back.
- I know. - It was fun.
I also had a lot of fun.
I want to come back when the weather is warm.
- All right. - It doesn't get warmer than this.
(It doesn't get warmer than this.)
Why are you so grumpy?
What's wrong with you?
Why do I get hit with the water bomb when we worked together?
It's warm enough.
This is how the weather normally is in November.
I will pull the lever at the count of three.
Han Na and Su Jin, you did a great job today.
In one,
two,
three.
(Splashing)
(This is what happens to traitors.)
(Seaweed appears.)
- Look at Haha. - My goodness.
(They show that no evil goes unpunished.)
Look at Haha.
This is hilarious.
(It's so refreshing.)
(The presentation of the prize money is a happy event.)
(A woman gets taken out in a mysterious way.)
(Then the prize money disappears.)
(Is there an evildoer among them?)
(What are you doing?)
(The culprit needs to eliminate the witness.)
(I learned something.)
(I have information on the woman.)
(The evildoer tries to destroy the evidence.)
(More information on the evildoer surfaces.)
(Find the evildoer who is hiding his or her identity.)
(The culprit is among us.)
(Who is the evildoer with an angelic face?)
(Bad Guys: War against the Evildoer)