(Do you remember I-Go Project?)
(Those with 3 I Go Stickers must go on a penalty trip with a member.)
(So Min's destination is Indonesia's Manual Wooden Cable Car.)
(So Min's partner for the penalty is Kwang Soo.)
(Jakarta)
(Kwang Soo and So Min left for Indonesia.)
(Indonesia Tiger Moth Tour started.)
(The door to the underworld of missions opened.)
(The tiger moth siblings' fierce survival in Indonesia)
(Who will earn more mission money and become the winner?)
(Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game)
(Find the one who is speaking the truth.)
(The professional liars searched for the truth.)
(The unchosen one and the fooled members received penalty badges.)
(The toll of penalty badges)
(They accumulated penalty badges through Round 1 and 2.)
(Jae Seok and Se Chan had to go on a slingshot ride.)
(They were forced to enjoy the sky from a height.)
(The toll of penalty badges)
(Finally,)
(the tiger moth siblings arrive at their destination.)
(They must ride a wooden cable car and fight against the waves.)
(Did they safely carry out the penalty?)
(Today comes a legendary penalty that is even scarier.)
(The 2 members with the most number of penalty badges...)
(will receive a live penalty for Chuseok.)
(Who will be the 2 members?)
Everyone, Round Two is over.
Let's move to the next location for Round 3 and 4 of Truth Game.
Okay.
Let's go.
- For goodness' sake. - This ride has cameras.
What is this?
(A ride blocks them on their way to Round 3.)
Will we get dropped from a height again?
From where will we drop?
It looks like we will get dropped from a height again.
It's called Big Swing.
(At the height of 40m,)
(the riders charge forward as they make a semicircle.)
(It's a VIP ride that lets you feel the nature with your entire body.)
- My goodness. - I can't go on it.
- I am getting motion sickness. - Nevis Swing.
Nevis Swing.
(The others worry about Big Swing, but he goes on about Nevis Swing.)
(Haha and Se Chan must go to Nevis Swing due to visa issues.)
(Nevis Swing in New Zealand is the scariest swing in the world.)
(Why do we need to go?)
(Am I going on...)
(Nevis Swing?)
(Nevis Swing occupied Haha's mind throughout the shoot.)
Please help me.
I really don't think I can do it.
Please give me another way.
I can go on anything but that.
Don't do that to the scriptwriter.
It's you, right? You are the one who is riding Nevis Swing with me.
It's you, right?
What are you doing here?
Hurry up, and return to your position.
My goodness.
We are ruined.
We will reveal the penalty of Round Three first.
- The penalty of Round Three is... - There is a penalty.
an extreme ride that lets you fly like a moth from the height of 36m.
It's really scary.
Please focus.
I'll be really focused.
Tiger Moth Tour Truth Game Round 3.
- Play video. - I can't do it.
(Will they win or be penalized?)
(Tiger Moth Tour Question 3)
(Kwang Soo and So Min head to Pantai Timang.)
I still can't believe it.
- That we're in Indonesia? - Yes.
(Depressed)
Let's stay in a good mood by laughing.
We can laugh like this.
(Let's enjoy it.)
I'll try to enjoy it.
- How... - It was really pretty.
The color of the sea was beautiful when I saw it yesterday.
(The cable car that So Min saw on video)
(It's a bright emerald color.)
(In the middle of the vast sea...)
(is a relaxing ride.)
(Cable car at Pantai Timang where you can relax and enjoy)
It'll be beautiful.
(It may turn out better than expected.)
(With hopes in their hearts, they travel for 3.5 hours.)
It's cloudy.
It might rain.
- I think... - Are we here?
We have to take a four-wheel jeep from here.
- Do we have to travel more? - Do we transfer?
- Yes. - We aren't here yet?
The road is too dangerous to travel in this car.
Where are we going?
Is this "The Law of Jungle"?
How far are we going?
I thought we arrived.
Please transfer to the jeep.
(It's another penalty.)
(You're watching Tiger Moth Penalty Tour.)
They continue traveling.
We went farther.
Much farther.
(One hour left until the cable car)
(What's going on?)
- It's endless. - On the way...
to be penalized isn't easy.
The trip itself is a penalty.
- It's so cute. - Which do we ride?
It's this one.
- It's really cute. - Are we supposed to take a jeep?
Does it wobble a lot?
It seems like a honeymoon.
They're wearing matching outfits.
- It was by accident. - It was.
They look good together.
You're too tall to fit.
It's cool.
The jeep is so small.
(They'll arrive at the destination soon.)
(He doesn't forget to wave to his fans.)
(It's exciting to ride the jeep.)
It feels like we're traveling.
It doesn't wobble as much as I expected.
(After traveling for 5 minutes,)
(they enter an unpaved road.)
- Goodness. - I feel nauseous.
(Shaking)
All my insides are shaking.
This is only the start.
I was excited for nothing.
(It's definitely not a pleasant trip.)
Is this necessary?
That must be nauseating.
It was terrible.
We came in farther.
It's a long trip.
I keep thinking whether I did something terribly wrong...
since yesterday.
(He blames Unlucky Ones' Race.)
I hope this suffering will end.
- I know. - It's painful.
It feels like overdue homework. Let's finish it.
We travel much farther.
Much farther.
It's a rough trip.
(How far must they go?)
(The trip is endless and rough.)
(They're on their way to finish their overdue homework.)
Let's pretend to look happy from the back.
They're filming us behind.
(It's a wonderful trip.)
(She's with the Prince of Asia.)
Are you pretending to be excited?
(The smell of wood from the cable car)
(Cable car and Pantai Timang, here we come.)
(They look happy from the back.)
Doesn't it smell like the sea?
- I start to smell it. - It smells like the sea.
- This is great. - I smell the sea.
What's this?
(What do they see?)
- We're here for a penalty. - I know.
- What's going on? - It was crowded with his fans.
Really?
Were your fans there?
They came all the way here.
(You're awesome, Kwang Soo.)
(Prince of Asia appears.)
(Not only do the fans welcome Kwang Soo,)
(but they also welcome the other Running Man members.)
I knew it, Kwang Soo.
Will Kwang Soo make another disgusting face?
(No way,)
What did you say?
- I don't want to see it. - What?
There it is.
- He starts again. - There's the look.
(He shows his charming smile.)
(Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo.)
They even liked his hairstyle.
I don't understand why.
He seems so happy.
He can't stop smiling.
He doesn't stop waving his hand.
Let me see.
You don't forget to wave your hand.
You keep waving.
(They arrive at the final destination.)
I'm exhausted.
Welcome to Pantai Timang.
(The cable car is right in the front.)
Look at that.
- It looks unreal. - We might break a camera.
(It's a steep cliff.)
Is that it?
It looks amazing when that happens.
Are the waves that big?
Yes, they're huge.
Is that it?
It looks quite different from the photos.
(It looks very different.)
(It's a thrilling ride over the emerald ocean.)
- The video was unrealistic. - I can do that.
- I can't ride the Nevis Swing. - I can.
It's much different in reality.
- Is it really scary? - Look at that.
(Welcome to Pantai Timang.)
(Will we be safe?)
Do you see what the locals prepared for you?
"Running Man".
They hung it for us.
(The locals made a welcome sign.)
- Really? - They made a sign.
- That's nice of them. - It's so cool.
- It's such a big welcome. - I know.
- We should be happy... - I'm grateful.
and try to enjoy it.
We can enjoy it, right?
Please do.
Let's go.
(Thank you, everyone.)
The waves are very strong.
(As soon as he tries to enjoy himself...)
I've never seem them so big.
They're unreal.
(They seem modified by a computer.)
Seriously.
- What's that bridge for? - That must be a bridge.
Do we cross the bridge?
No way.
This is the way.
You're at the penalty site after a long trip.
Yes, we are. This is the site of the accident.
(Do you see what's behind us?)
- In "Haeundae"... - We'll be on SBS News.
(It's not a movie.)
I've seen it before.
- Recommended by Syifa Amalina... - What?
- What did you say? - Say it again.
- The destination was recommended... - That's right.
by Syifa Amalina.
- Made with clotheslines and wood, - Clothesline?
it's a 100m Manual Wooden Cable Car.
Are these clotheslines?
Yes.
- They're real clotheslines? - Yes.
- Where we hang laundry? - Yes.
It's often used by fishermen to catch crayfish...
that lives near that small island.
It's not a tourist spot. It's used for transport.
It's to catch crayfish.
A net is laid out a day before to catch crayfish.
- It sounds delicious. - With the help of the village head,
we laid out a net.
Bring the crayfish in the net from the island.
What? I'm not a fisherman.
That's a professional task.
Bring the crayfish in the net.
As it's a wooden cable car, there's a weight limit.
You'll ride it separately.
Decide who will go first.
They can't go together?
So Min will go first.
(Good luck, Kwang Soo.)
So Min?
No.
An ant bit me.
Look, I'm hurt.
- I have an ant bite. - I got injured here.
- An ant bite. - I got hurt.
It's a fire ant.
You should go first. I want to see how it is beforehand.
Gosh, look at that.
(The waves suddenly crash.)
The waves came all the way here.
Do you want to choose by Plus and Minus?
Shall we spin the roulette?
I pick plus.
You pick minus.
(He's in a turmoil.)
Pick one.
I pick plus.
(If So Min picks plus...)
Do you pick minus?
Yes.
(Kwang picks minus.)
Here we go.
(Will it be So Min...)
(or Kwang Soo who goes first?)
(Unsurprisingly, it's Kwang Soo.)
(It's only natural.)
Kwang Soo will go first.
You know I wanted to go first, right?
- No. - Just remember that.
No way.
Even if it were a plus, I'd have gone first.
The waves have calmed down.
You should go now. The time is now.
(The waves calmed down?)
(That's not calm.)
- Gosh. - Look at the waves.
They look scary.
(Is the time now?)
(Kwang Soo mentally prepares himself.)
- We don't have much to carry... - My goodness.
(Screaming)
(Shrieking)
Goodness.
I can't do it.
- I can't do it. - I won't do it.
Gosh, they're in trouble.
(She's shocked by the waves.)
- That's frightening. - That's impossible.
(As Kwang Soo gets ready to go,)
(the waves frighten him at the perfect time.)
I won't do it.
- I won't do it. - I give up.
(He gives up.)
(The locals are used to the waves.)
(The waves are crashing down heavily.)
(Will he be able to go through the penalty today?)
Okay. All right.
(I can do this.)
- Look at the waves. - Everyone rides this.
- I bet you must've hated riding it. - From here...
(He says he can ride it, but he keeps going to the back.)
I can just sit there. That's all.
This is the same as spraying water on me when I'm sitting on a chair.
(This is just a common penalty.)
Let's go.
You can swim. You learned how to swim.
(He tells himself that he's a swimming prodigy.)
There's no way I'd fall into the sea.
(He's about to face the penalty after hesitating for 30 minutes.)
Kwang Soo, good luck!
(She sincerely roots for him.)
(It's time to end the long-lasting homework of the I-Go Project.)
- Should I go this way? - You want me to put this away?
Yes, just for a moment, please.
Please help me with this.
(Kwang Soo, the 1st one to face the penalty, gets on the cable car.)
Should I do this after lunch?
(Is it safe for me to ride this on an empty stomach?)
(No, I should get this over with quickly, right?)
(Tired of waiting, the spirit of variety shows slaps his cheeks.)
I don't think I can do this! I can't do this!
I lost!
I don't think I can ride this cable car!
What a timing.
- This doesn't seem possible. - It looks like a skit, doesn't it?
(Oh, poor Kwang Soo. What an unfortunate timing!)
Did you see Kwang Soo?
(Giggling)
I want to go back to Korea!
(Mom...)
All right. Let's do this.
Let's go. I should get this over with.
Please move up a bit.
- Put this up. - Gosh, this is shaking.
- You can just put this up. - This is shaking.
(At the news of Kwang Soo's appearance,)
(the color of the waves begins to darken.)
(So many of my fans are watching me now.)
(He goes inside the cable car after 40 minutes.)
Go forward. Wait, no.
(He puts on the safety gear to prepare just in case.)
It fits perfectly.
This is...
Now that I'm sitting here...
I can't...
(What should I do?)
I can't do this now that I'm sitting here.
What's your name?
- I'm Murphy. Yes. - Murphy?
How old are you?
I'm 25 years old.
Tell him that I'm older than he is.
(He feels proud of his age.)
- He's older? - Yes.
- I see. - I'm older than you.
(I'm counting on you, Murphy. Don't forget I'm older than you.)
Be careful.
He told you to be careful.
Be careful? How can I be careful here?
How?
(I can't do anything here!)
(Murphy explains something to Kwang Soo.)
I speak Korean.
- I'm Korean. - It was calm for three days.
But today, the waves are big today. So you should grab the handle...
tightly because it might be dangerous.
It was calm for three days, but the waves got big just today?
No, that's not how it happened.
Kwang Soo made the sea angry.
Hold on. What did I do to upset the sea?
(But the sea does look like it's upset.)
(Screaming)
(He's completely soaked. This guy has upsetted Poseidon.)
Please. Please spare me!
(His misfortunes even upsetted the sea that had been calm.)
After Kwang Soo rode the cable car, the waves are crashing even harder.
So it's been confirmed.
He has the energy that upsets everyone.
The sea is very angry now.
Were you having fun?
(Feeling guilty)
- So Min, you had to ride that next. - Right.
- Right now, I can't laugh. - That looks so scary.
- That must be so terrifying. - Goodness, that cable car...
The waves were so big to the point that it was so weird.
Please. Please stop this!
Please stop the waves.
(But it can no longer be delayed as the waves are getting stronger.)
(I can do this.)
(The 1st one to face the penalty of I-Go Project)
(Kwang Soo sets out at last.)
Go!
(It stops.)
- What's going on? - Oh, dear!
- It's going. - He's going.
- What's going on? - Hey.
- Be careful! - What is it?
(Because of the cameras, it can't speed up.)
What's wrong?
It's shaking. The string got stretched because he's heavy.
The string is stretched out.
(When he's about to have a moment of peace,)
(the fierce waves visit him.)
(For Kwang Soo, the locals are speeding the process.)
(However, as he penetrates through the strong waves,)
(he begins to advance little by little.)
I'm sorry.
(He keeps on mumbling.)
What's happening to me now?
This is where I am after I regained my senses.
(Why am I here?)
I'm doomed.
My life is in ruins.
I should've removed Ji Hyo's name tag.
I should've done it at all cost.
(During the last race of I-Go Project,)
(things would have been different had I removed hers.)
I should've caught the king crabs.
- I should've done that in Russia. - Did you catch them?
(No, if only I caught the king crabs 5 months ago...)
(If only the king crabs were hanging at the end of my fishing line...)
(If only a king crab bit my bait by any chance...)
Where did I go wrong?
(Sighing in despair)
It must be after that time. No, it's not.
It started even before then.
(He begins to regret his past misfortunes as the waves flood in.)
I'm almost there. I'm almost there.
What a beautiful view. The scenery is dazzling.
This is pretty. How beautiful.
(The view is amazing.)
This is straight from a painting.
(At that time, the painting comes alive.)
Hold on!
(Gosh, that looks horrifying.)
This is... Oh, no.
Everyone was so surprised. They all screamed.
Kwang Soo disappeared for a second.
(He comes to his senses.)
Hold on!
(A helicopter camera was filming him.)
Oh, no! The helicopter camera!
Did you see the drone camera that just fell?
(The drone crashed down.)
- That's a helicopter camera. - It fell!
Oh, no!
- All the cameras turned off. - What's going on?
- Really? - The waves were just too big.
- It's all my fault! - Goodness.
It's just...
(While Kwang Soo is facing the waves that crashed the drone...)
It's all my fault.
It's dangerous.
I should put on suncream.
(She doesn't show much interest.)
Where is my bag? Would you like something to drink?
Do you want a drink?
- No? I'm rich. I have 100 dollars. - On which car did you leave it?
(Someone is shaking this cable car!)
Please!
Pull me back! Pull!
Hey, pull me back there! Come on!
It's coming again. Don't do it! Stop!
(Screaming in agony)
(He swears at Poseidon.)
(While Kwang Soo is doing this unforgettable activity...)
Where is she?
(So Min's "Backpack Travels")
Would you like to try this?
What is this?
(Longan is a tropical fruit from dry seasons.)
She told me to press it in the center.
This has a hint of garlic smell.
But the aftertaste is quite fruity, isn't it?
(Thus, she continued experiencing the culture.)
You weren't watching him?
When I turned back, that's how she looked. She crossed her legs.
(I'm sorry. I got scared watching you.)
I shouldn't have been chosen by the roulettes!
(Gosh, I can't believe I went through those waves.)
(Kwang Soo is soaked in waves, sweat, and tears.)
(Kwang Soo has reached the island on the other side.)
(Who am I?)
(Where am I?)
(At last, I feel much better. I am done with my penalty!)
(Kwang Soo, the 1st one to face the penalty,)
(reaches the island on the other side.)
(So Min, you're up next.)
I'm getting all nervous.
(Gosh, you did well.)
- But why do people... - The waves are crazy.
cross to the other side?
(Why do people cross to the other side?)
To catch shrimps.
- He told us that. - He already said that earlier.
He already told us that. Why are you talking about that again?
(You're so frustrating. Please listen to others.)
- For the locals there... - When?
Why are you keeping this a secret from me?
(Seok Jin is hilarious.)
But that's better than Nevis Swing.
(You're laughing now, Haha?)
- Jae Seok, please stop it. - I'm serious.
If you keep this up, he might stop filming.
- This is better in every aspect. - This is way better than that.
(Compared to Nevis Swing, this is easy.)
All right, So Min. You'll get on the cable car now.
I ate too many fruits.
I think I should go to the bathroom.
Let me pray before I go.
(Please help me make a safe return.)
Hello.
(The 3rd question of Truth Game)
Thank you for your help.
(So Min finally gets on the cable car after a long wait.)
This is so high. This is higher than I expected.
(Seeing it up close makes her feel dizzy.)
What should I do?
(How did Kwang Soo ride this?)
(Question number 3)
(What did So Min hand Kwang Soo as soon as she finished the ride?)
- What? - What is it?
(It's the third question.)
(It's the 3rd question to determine who will take the penalty.)
(What did So Min hand Kwang Soo as soon as she finished the ride?)
All right, you two. Please come out...
and pick Truth or Lie.
What did she give?
(Only one of the two will tell them the truth.)
(The others must pick who's telling the truth to avoid the penalty.)
I really don't know.
I can't trust them anymore.
Who will speak first?
Can we listen to Kwang Soo first?
All right. I'll speak.
I picked Truth this time for certain.
- Is that right? - So Min handed me...
the fruit which she was eating a while ago.
(Kwang Soo claims that So Min gave him the fruit.)
(After riding that dangerous cable car,)
(So Min handed him the fruit?)
What nonsense is he talking about now?
- That's not funny at all. - What's wrong with you?
- This is the truth. - It's not funny.
I'm telling you the truth.
I only said two sentences just now.
Why on earth would she give you the fruit?
I'm telling you the truth.
- It was the fruit for certain. - Kwang Soo.
I trust you. I know you're telling the truth.
- Listen to me. - This isn't it.
- He's lying for certain. - Hey.
- Because... - Goodness.
Jong Kook isn't getting things right today.
As soon as I heard the question, I thought it was the fruit.
- I thought it was the fruit too. - Listen to me.
There were fruits...
beside the entrance of the cable car.
What kind of fruit was it?
I had never seen that kind before.
- It was... - Was it dried or not?
- They were hanging on a tree. - He doesn't know...
- It was sweet and sour. - because he didn't have it.
(He had never seen it before, but it tasted sweet and sour.)
- I forgot its name. - All fruits are sweet and sour.
Are you kidding me?
- It was yellow. - I know what it was.
- What was it? - I know what that was.
It was yellow,
and it tasted like grapes.
- One of them was like snake skin. - Right, right.
- What do you mean? - Say its color at the same time.
Tell us the color at the same time.
It's a fact that So Min had the fruit.
So why would she give you the fruit?
- It had a huge seed inside. - Listen to me.
- Why would I... - It's the fruit.
- give him the fruit? - What did you give him then?
- You tell me then. - She wouldn't give him that.
- Tell us. - What did you give him?
Think of an idea quickly.
I swore at you.
(So Min claims that she gave him swear words.)
- You gave him swear words? - That wouldn't be aired then.
He shouted at me from the other side...
because he became upset...
that I enjoyed eating the fruit and watched him get the penalty.
He yelled at me from the other side.
So as soon as I got off, he went,
"You brat, you're dead meat."
What's that?
(Kwang Soo swore at So Min?)
(What is she talking about?)
It's all right if she lies, but...
Hold on.
Hold on. When did I...
- I didn't say that. - Goodness.
- Did I say that to you? - You're impossible.
- Did I? - Is this real?
- Is this real? - No, listen to me.
Does it make sense?
You helpless punk!
- How could you... - Gosh.
I'm sorry,
but why is Seok Jin upset?
I got upset too late.
I thought about it for some time, and it made me mad.
That was so sudden.
I became righteous all of a sudden.
I'm sure about this.
It's what Kwang Soo usually behaves.
So what did you give him?
- So what did you give him? - You'll find out soon.
So I gave him...
- You gave him the finger? - Yes.
You'll know if you hear me.
That's what she'd do.
(It sounds about right.)
She often does that.
- You're right. - She often does that.
I'm getting goosebumps.
- My goodness. - A while ago,
- Haha guessed... - I didn't believe it at first.
the same thing.
- Because it's plausible. - He guessed this.
(Right after the question was given)
By any chance,
is it what I think it is?
Is it?
(Haha guessed if So Min gave him the bad finger.)
- Goodness. - She was...
She was too frightened...
- to give me such a thing. - Guys.
Listen to me.
You tend to comfort each other when you face some kind of trouble...
even though you're filming a variety show.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm aware So Min is such a playful girl,
but she must've given him the fruit in that situation.
Hold on. I'm suspicious of one thing.
How did you know So Min was eating the fruit?
I watched it on TV.
(He was receiving the penalty, so how did he know?)
- Don't you think so? - You're right.
- I kept telling you this. - He's being suspicious.
How did you know what she was doing behind you?
- His eyesight is that good? - At that time,
I didn't know she was eating fruit.
- He couldn't see. - I only saw her...
- take selfies at that time. - He saw her take selfies.
- Right. - I saw that.
Because where I was wasn't that far from the other side.
Jae Seok must really not want to get penalized.
He's thinking so hard.
- He's never been... - He's being extra careful.
It was an important moment.
(If they can't guess this, they'll get closer to the penalty.)
It was the moment when she just finished her ride.
There's no way I swore at her at that moment.
You must be aware of how Kwang Soo usually behaves.
- You must all know. - Right.
- I had no strength either. - Think about it.
Do you think I crawled to her and swore at her?
I had no strength to even walk.
But I swore at her?
- Trust me. - I can't...
trust either of them to be honest.
That's true.
Hold on, guys. You have to ride that one this time.
- Keep that in mind. - Guys, look behind you.
(So Min gave Kwang Soo the fruit or swear words?)
(Who's telling the truth?)
It's an extreme ride...
that you fly from 36m above the ground to the lake.
(Those who pick the wrong side will experience the big swing.)
(Who will get to fly across the sky like a moth that jumps into flames?)
- One. - Trust me this once.
We're in the same situation again.
(1 of the 2 will be exempted.)
You'll never get married in your life if you're lying.
- Are you still sure? - Yes.
(Whom will the members choose?)
All right. One.
Two.
(Is it Kwang Soo or So Min?)
- Three. - It's so hard to decide.
(They're torn.)
I don't know.
(Turning)
(Only two chose So Min.)
- I really don't know. - They didn't give us enough time.
(Ji Hyo decides to trust So Min.)
(It's 4 to 2.)
Why?
Why don't you trust me?
I suspected Kwang Soo at first.
But he's persuasive.
He wouldn't have sworn at her when he just finished his penalty.
- Right? - He wouldn't have done that.
Only Ji Hyo and Se Chan chose to trust So Min.
- What? - Ji Hyo chose So Min?
Ji Hyo chose to trust me.
- I chose So Min. - Give us a final chance.
- Look at you. - Don't be swayed.
- Step away. - I'm telling you the truth.
- See? - Ji Hyo...
Don't be swayed.
- Why did she choose So Min? - I'm right.
Anyway, it's decided that So Min will get the penalty.
- I don't know. - Let's check the answer now.
(What's the truth behind this question?)
Hello.
Thank you in advance.
(So Min gets ready for the ride.)
(Frightened)
Wait a second.
This is much higher than expected.
Wait a second. This is much higher than expected.
(Kwang Soo must've felt this way a while ago.)
What should I do?
So Min!
So Min, you must come back.
(Focus!)
We must return home.
What is that on his head? Is it a jellyfish or what?
- It's my hair. - Is that seaweed?
- It's my real hair. - Oh, I see.
You must come back.
(His seaweed hairstyle captures attention.)
You can return home.
(It turns the Prince of Asia into a beggar.)
Let's go, So Min!
This is much scarier than I thought it'd be.
Gosh, this seems so fragile.
(It's difficult to even fit her body into the tiny space.)
It might break.
Gosh, it's frightening.
(Will she successfully finish the ride?)
What if a wave hits me?
What should I do then?
(Welcome. It's your first time at Pantai Timang, isn't it?)
(She didn't realize it then.)
Be careful!
(I love Indonesia.)
(She had no idea then...)
(just how nice it was to relax and wait for Kwang Soo.)
(Now, she's sitting in the cable car.)
Okay.
Goodness, I don't think I can do this.
Goodness.
(She's about to enter the world of waves.)
(Nervous)
Be careful.
(She can't take it back anymore.)
What should I do? My goodness.
Hold on. Oh, no.
- Please. - That looks so scary.
- That's scary. - I'll never be able to do that.
Hold on. Oh, no.
Hold on.
Gosh, the waves.
Please don't come near me.
Please don't. Not the waves.
Please.
(Will she get to avoid facing the waves as she wishes?)
Oh, no.
(It doesn't seem that bad.)
(It doesn't seem as bad this time.)
Here come the waves.
Gosh, the waves.
Oh, dear.
(What's going on?)
Let's go.
(Pantai Timang never disappoints you.)
(It's a gift only for So Min.)
(The waves are here again.)
After those waves?
She can't have sworn after those waves.
It was scary when it wobbled.
Those waves were huge.
They're so strong.
(Waves)
(Scary waves hit the cable car.)
(Screaming)
Gosh!
(Engulfed)
(What is this?)
I hate this.
(Wasn't she taking selfies and eating fruits until a moment ago?)
(Am I being punished for being too happy?)
Seriously.
I hate this so much.
(After a few big waves, So Min finally gets to the other side.)
(She's smiling again.)
(She's smiling now.)
Gosh.
Did you see how the car wobbled?
- Do you know how it was for me? - Did you see it?
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Excuse me. Sorry.
(So Min and Kwang Soo's cable car rides are finished.)
We have to go back, right?
Yes.
(So Min is about to give something to Kwang Soo.)
- Kwang Soo. - It wasn't that bad.
(What is she going to give him?)
Kwang Soo might have said something to make her swear.
That's possible.
- Kwang Soo... - This is an important moment.
(What is she going to give him?)
- Kwang Soo. - It wasn't that bad.
(She takes something out.)
It wasn't that bad.
(If So Min swears to Kwang Soo, So Min is the truthful one.)
(If she gives Kwang Soo fruits, Kwang Soo is the truthful one.)
(What is she going to give him?)
(The correct answer is fruits.)
- Yes! - Yes!
(So Min was lying.)
(So Min and those who believed her are going to be penalized.)
Of course, she didn't swear.
Of course.
It was wrong.
(We were fooled by So Min.)
- Of course, it was fruits. - By the way,
you guys are so sweet.
- I had never tried them. - It's so heartwarming.
- They're called lychees. - Throughout her ride,
she must have wanted to give the fruits to Kwang Soo.
- It's so sweet of her. - It's so heartwarming.
(She carried the fruits throughout her ride.)
(I'm going to give him fruits.)
So Min, it's so sweet of you.
What's this?
(She takes them out of her pocket.)
- What are all these? - They're fruits.
I brought them for you.
- Did you eat them? - Yes, I ate a lot.
(I brought them in my pocket for you.)
Don't eat the seed.
Eat the skin too. It tastes good, right?
Are you okay?
Yes, I am.
(She successfully delivered the fruits to Kwang Soo.)
- I'm okay. - Are you mentally okay?
I actually panicked a little during the ride...
because...
(The waves crash again.)
The car wobbled during your ride too.
You were invisible for a moment.
When I looked back, you were looking at your phone.
You were sitting down, looking at your phone.
(That's not true.)
(Truth or Lie Quiz is finished.)
- It brings back memories. - I don't want to go on that swing.
Gosh.
So Min, Se Chan, and Ji Hyo will receive penalty badges.
I'm doomed. I already have two.
(What have they done wrong?)
- Se Chan is doomed. - He is.
- We don't know yet, right? - We don't.
Someone might get more than him.
Right. Gosh, that was a mistake.
(Ji Hyo and Se Chan get penalty badges.)
- So Min... - I'm sorry.
A cameraman has to be there too,
so only two people will ride the swing.
(Only 1 person will go on it.)
- Only 2 people total. - Only 1 of us?
All the cameramen look so shocked.
(A cameraman has to be there.)
Right?
(One of us will be there?)
Have the cameramen agreed on this?
Why don't our cameramen play rock-paper-scissors?
That sounds good.
- Let's do that. - Rock-paper-scissors.
The cameramen will play rock-paper-scissors.
Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and So Min's cameramen, please come out.
Seong Oh hates these things.
Rock-paper-scissors. Ready.
(The loser will be penalized.)
Please.
(The cameramen will determine...)
(the members and their own fates.)
(The loser and a member will go on the swing.)
(Who will that be?)
(Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and So Min's cameramen)
(Ji Hyo's cameraman loses.)
All right! Yes!
(Chan Gyu and Ji Hyo are going to ride the swing.)
He's so bad.
- I was so surprised. - How is that possible?
Ji Hyo will ride the swing.
I'm escaping many dangers today.
Ji Hyo, I didn't expect you to go on that swing.
Neither did I.
(I didn't expect it either.)
Ji Hyo.
(Are you okay?)
(I miss my mom.)
Why did you lose?
Why did you lose rock-paper-scissors?
(Sorry)
(It's not enough to be the lucky one yourself.)
It's at least better than Nevis Swing.
Maybe it's a good thing.
- Ji Hyo is the only one... - Ji Hyo is the only one...
- who can do this. - who can do this.
Among all of us.
She's the bravest one.
She's my hero.
(She did the 233m bungee jump in Macau.)
(She's successfully managed many extreme sports.)
(Ji Hyo is the queen of extreme sports.)
(You're the only one who can smile in this situation.)
Ji Hyo.
Are you okay?
I'm scared too.
Just so you know, Bo Gum has done it.
- He has? - Really?
That's great.
(Bo Gum is Ji Hyo's favorite.)
(She was so thrilled when she took a picture with him.)
(If Bo Gum was with me,)
(I could do it a hundred times.)
(Sorry, I'm the one who will be with you.)
You look great.
You look fantastic.
(Thumbs up)
This is crazy.
(The swing ascends.)
Mom, Dad, friends, Running Man members,
and the staff,
thank you for everything.
(Why is she making a confession?)
Chan Gyu, I don't blame you.
(We're in this together.)
We can do this.
Ji Hyo, are you okay?
I don't know. I'm scared.
Ji Hyo!
It's going up so high.
It's going up too high.
(My goodness.)
Gosh, it's too high.
This is not okay!
- Ji Hyo. - I can't watch it.
How high is it going?
Gosh.
Are we there?
You can do this!
(Screaming)
(Jae Seok's legs fail him.)
Gosh.
We'll count down for you.
(Countdown)
- 5, 4, 3, 2, 1. - 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Let's go!
(Launching)
(Plunging)
(Screaming)
(Cutting through the wind,)
(the swing plunges.)
(Shocked)
(It comes back at an incredible speed too.)
Gosh.
(Ji Hyo is smiling.)
(So is the cameraman.)
(They're both so brave.)
They're not even screaming.
(The others are holding their breaths as they watch.)
- This is crazy. - It's incredible.
You look like Wonder Woman.
Superman!
- Superman! - Superman!
(Mapo-gu is under my protection.)
We survived.
- We're still alive. - That's amazing.
- We survived. - Ji Hyo, you're amazing.
- We're still alive! - Superman!
(Ji Hyo is incredible.)
Superman.
I have so much respect for you.
A big respect for you.
It's you guys next time.
- You're going on Nevis Swing. - I respect you.
I respect you.
- I respect you. - You're going on Nevis Swing.
Which was scarier, bungee jumping in Macau or this?
This was a bit scarier.
- Really? - Really?
It must be really scary.
If Ji Hyo says so...
We survived.
(They've safely landed.)
We're still alive.
(Ji Hyo's swing ride is finished.)
- Let me summarize it for you. - Okay.
Se Chan has the most penalty badges.
- He has three. - He's doomed.
(Se Chan is likely to be penalized.)
So Min and Jong Kook have two badges each.
The other members have one each.
There's only one more person who has two.
I'm at risk.
Is it decided that I'll be penalized?
We don't know yet.
- We don't? - No. Those with two badges...
- might receive more. - That's right.
That's right.
She and I should give different answers.
- That's right. - We should give different answers.
Think about this.
If the two of you answer correctly...
and the ones with 1 badge come to have 2 badges,
- 4 people will compete. - 4 people will have 2 badges each.
- Okay. - That makes sense.
In that case, what does the one with three badges do?
If that happens, the one with three badges,
you, will choose among the ones with two badges.
- Do I get to choose? - Yes.
- That's a good idea. - Let's get it.
Here comes the fourth problem.
Play the video.
(Tiger Moth Penalty Tour, The 4th problem)
Let's go and get crayfish.
- What does crayfish look like? - Wait for me, Kwang Soo.
- I wonder what it looks like. - Doesn't it look fragile?
You will be surprised when you see it.
- Why? Is it because it's big? - It's my first time seeing it.
- It's my first time seeing it. - It's incredible.
- This place looks cool. - It's a cave.
- It looks cool. - Is it a cave?
(Are the crayfish here?)
It's fascinating how people made this structure.
- There is a crab. - It must be here.
- Crayfish live there. - This must be it.
There were crabs too.
- There is a crab. - This must be it.
There is crayfish.
Where?
Is that crayfish? It looks like a lobster.
- It looks like a lobster. - Is this crayfish?
Why is it so big?
- Isn't that a lobster? - It's crayfish.
- It's huge. - It is.
- That's crayfish? - Yes.
There are two crabs.
(The local fisherman gives them the crabs too.)
Wait a minute.
This is "The Law of Jungle".
(I've seen this somewhere.)
It really is "The Law of Jungle".
It would have been complete with Kim Byung Man.
(Kwang Soo and So Min succeed in catching crayfish and crabs.)
- My goodness. - There are two crabs.
- The color is different. - That's a lobster.
- How pretty! - No, it's crayfish.
- Is that crayfish? - Look at this.
It's hanging on to the trap.
I have never seen this kind of a crab before.
(Hello, crabs with a blue carapace.)
They look like a porcelain.
- Thank you so much. - It's a lobster.
- It doesn't look like crayfish. - That one is on the small side.
You are watching Running Man.
(Do you want to see crab roe?)
- It's roe. - It has roe.
(It is filled with roe.)
(Telur means "Roe".)
- Did he say, "Daughter"? - May we try it now?
It's a daughter, not a son.
It means "Roe".
Daughters.
I am sorry.
This crab is foaming.
May we try it now?
Do you want to try it raw?
Crab roe can be eaten raw.
Can crab roe be eaten raw?
While it tastes a bit fishy, you can eat it raw.
(This is how you eat it.)
You should try it.
How fascinating!
Try it.
This is my first time seeing crab roe like this.
(He carefully gives it a taste.)
- How does it taste? - It's delicious. It tastes nutty.
Is it delicious?
- Did it taste nutty? - It was good.
- Wasn't it salty? - It was nutty.
- It's good, right? - Yes.
I have seen this scene from somewhere.
It was "The Law of Jungle".
People on that program look dirty...
because they can't take a shower.
You can't say that just because I touched a crab.
This is fascinating. They are really pretty.
- Let's go. - Do we need to carry them?
Let's get going.
I don't think that part is edible.
- Are we taking the cable car? - Yes, we are.
(Are we taking the cable car?)
How are we going back?
I don't want to go on it.
The waves were really scary. There are no waves under the bridge.
(I prefer walking across the bridge.)
Try walking on the bridge.
If it's okay, I will follow you.
(The producer goes first.)
He is going.
Let's go. This is better.
Kwang Soo is a man.
He takes the lead.
This is my choice.
(He charges forward like a man.)
(There is nothing scary about a short walk.)
It's shaky.
(The spirited man who took the lead turns back.)
The bridge is shaky.
Really?
Si Yeon, you should go first.
You should go first.
Don't add weight to the bridge.
- Seriously. - Hurry up.
(Why do these combinations look familiar?)
She wants you to go first.
(Kwang Soo and Yoon Sang were a duo at Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(So Min and Si Yeon were a duo with a tearful welcoming ceremony.)
She wants you to go first.
- Come on. - I can't take a follow shot.
(I am too scared.)
- Come on. - I can't do it.
Don't move all at once.
Come on.
(The junior cameraman, Si Yeon, moves forward in the end.)
Don't look down. Don't look down.
Go quickly because I am scared.
(Don't look back either, So Min.)
I am sorry for suggesting to take this route.
(He walks back because he is scared.)
(This route isn't any easier.)
It's really windy.
I won't go this way.
(I am sorry. You should go ahead.)
No, I won't go this way.
(An angry wave intimidates the tiger moths.)
The wave is so big.
It came up as high as the bridge.
I won't go this way.
Let's go. Let's go.
- We must go when the sea is calm. - What should I do?
What should I do? The bridge is shaking.
For goodness' sake.
(With Kwang Soo's encouragement, she gathers up her courage.)
(I don't think I am ready for this.)
(He is going back from the middle.)
(If you can't avoid it, overcome it.)
What should I do?
(Let's pick up the pace and cross the bridge quickly.)
You are almost there. Stay strong just a while longer.
Go quickly. Go quickly.
Go quickly.
(They finally reach the land.)
How scary!
My legs are shaking.
It was so scary.
(Kwang Soo is coming safely, right?)
Are you okay?
(No, I am not.)
- My hands are shaking. - I think I lost weight.
(The duo of scared men is at a standstill.)
(I can't take a step forward.)
(They remain standing on the bridge for a long time.)
- I have no strength. - I used up all my energy.
- My legs are shaking. - I used up three days' worth of it.
Now, it's time to try...
crayfish of Indonesia.
- Crayfish. - Crayfish.
(Come on, crayfish.)
(It's time for the seafood party they've been dreaming of.)
I wonder how it tastes.
I can't describe it with words.
My goodness.
- How pretty! - The crabs are so pretty.
- They're not seasoned. - They are really pretty.
You will see that we have brought your luggage.
Yes.
(It's the luggage they have forgotten about.)
From your luggage,
please choose and bring two items you need.
- Right now? - Two items each?
Two items each.
(We are on Tiger Moth Tour.)
(The person with the higher amount of mission money remaining wins.)
Don't you think you should give us a change of clothes?
- I need a change of clothes. - We need that much.
(Taking out an item from the luggage costs 30 dollars.)
(Kwang Soo opens his luggage.)
You have so many clothes.
(What should I take out?)
How much time do we have?
For goodness' sake.
(Why do I need to do this?)
He is truly annoyed.
Kwang Soo, children are watching. Calm down.
It's nothing.
Look at that fake smile.
Kwang Soo.
(Don't be mad, Kwang Soo.)
Take out what you need.
(What should I take out?)
Take out what you need. My goodness, there is ramyeon.
In that situation,
- ramyeon was the best. - Of course it was.
- Let's get ramyeon. - There's ramyeon.
Let's take out ramyeon. I really want it.
- Ramyeon? - Yes.
I need a top and a bottom.
You took this out already.
Let's pay 15 dollars each to take out ramyeon.
We are going to eat it together anyway.
We will pay 15 dollars each for ramyeon.
Let's pay 15 dollars each to take out ramyeon.
- Where is my t-shirt? - Currently,
So Min has 155 dollars.
You shouldn't reveal that.
Kwang Soo has 88 dollars.
I won't pay for ramyeon.
I won't eat it.
Are you sure about that?
- Yes. - You said you won't eat it.
I will pay 30 dollars to take out ramyeon.
- 30 dollars. - Yes.
Don't eat it.
Shoes.
Kwang Soo.
- Shoes and clothes. - A pack of clothes and shoes.
- So Min. - I will take out...
a top and a bottom.
I will pay for ramyeon.
A t-shirt, a pair of pants, and ramyeon for 30 dollars.
- Yes. - You paid for it.
We will now close the luggage.
(Taking out the 2 items comes to an end.)
- Let's go and eat. - Let's go.
- Please bring them in. - Please bring them in.
(Since they worked hard to catch them,)
(they are that much happier to finally eat crayfish.)
It looks so good.
Seriously.
- It looks tasty. - I can't describe it with words.
Were they steamed without any sauce?
Yes. There is a sauce for dipping.
- Really? - Yes.
- Is this the one I caught earlier? - Yes.
The color of the crabs changed.
They look like regular crabs when they are steamed.
They are the ones we saw earlier.
(The crabs return to them after getting steamed.)
- Before you dig in... - Yes.
- It looks delicious. - You see the crayfish...
- on a small plate, right? - Yes.
Try that first.
This?
- What's happening? - The tiny one.
It's not a crayfish?
It is. Try it.
Be careful not to hurt your hands.
Look at all that flesh.
- You caught it? - It was a bit small.
(Soft flesh is hiding inside the hard shell.)
It must be expensive.
- It was so tasty. - It looks so tasty.
It looks so tasty.
It deserves a thumbs-up.
- This? - Yes.
(It's a gift from the sea.)
It feels like we're in a jungle.
You should pay for that trip.
- Totally. - It's not a penalty.
Thank you.
- How does it taste? - It tastes great.
It's so fresh.
(The taste is fabulous.)
It has so much flesh.
(It's steak from the sea.)
Look at this.
(Let me try some.)
That looks like a lobster.
It's so tasty.
You should dip it in sauce.
- It gave me goosebumps. - It tastes amazing.
But...
for some reason, Kwang Soo doesn't make it look appetizing.
- He doesn't make it appetizing. - Look at it closely.
(Kwang Soo doesn't make food look appetizing.)
It tastes like meat.
(They're enjoying meat from the sea.)
It has so much flesh. I've never tasted anything like this.
The texture is so nice.
Does it taste good?
It tastes fantastic.
(It's beyond words.)
- The tasting session is over. - Sorry?
I knew it.
(Shocked)
Are you trying to be mean?
What's happening?
(Why are they taking it from us?)
How is this different from "12 Years a Slave"?
How is it different?
You're tasting crayfish.
(The producer gets to the point.)
It's quite rare in Yogyakarta too. Even locals...
- It must be. - don't get to taste it often.
Even locals don't get to taste it often.
You can choose to either retrieve some of your items...
or eat some more food.
Would you like to retrieve two of your items...
or eat more crayfish?
If you choose crayfish,
you can continue to eat.
(If they give up on their items, they can eat more.)
- Just eat. - I choose my clothes.
(So Min chooses clothes over crayfish.)
What are you going to choose?
- What will Kwang Soo choose? - What are you going to choose?
- You should choose crayfish. - He'll choose crayfish.
- I choose... - He'll choose crayfish.
- He definitely will. - I'm 100 percent sure.
I choose crayfish.
(Crayfish)
You choose crayfish.
Kwang Soo will continue to eat then.
I have no clothes.
Can I continue to eat?
Not everyone gets to taste it.
- Right. - The flesh is...
- seasoned. - Really?
(That looks tasty.)
(It looks like she is breaking up with someone.)
Can he even eat that?
(Amazed)
(There is so much meat.)
My hands are big.
(I should have been there.)
(Amazed)
I choose crayfish.
(So Min changes her mind immediately.)
- Me too. - What's this?
I choose crayfish.
- Make up your mind. - I don't need clothes.
- Okay. - Let's have it together.
Let's share it. I can't help it.
- I have no choice. - You can't do this.
I was wrong.
(Excited)
It's incredible.
(It's dipped in chili sauce.)
(A big bite)
(Her eyes become big.)
- It tastes amazing. - Gosh.
It tastes so good.
That looks amazing. How did it taste?
It tasted amazing.
You forgot about your penalty.
It was just...
It hasn't been frozen.
It was 1 of the 5 tastiest foods I'd ever had.
- Really? - Yes.
(They fall in love with the taste of the crayfish.)
It tastes amazing.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn.)
Is this chili sauce?
(He skillfully removes the flesh and dips it in sauce.)
It tastes so good.
Has his face been enlarged?
It looks longer than before.
You look so ugly.
He looks like a horse.
The flesh is so soft.
It melts in your mouth.
They all taste different.
It's amazing.
I've seen this somewhere.
Isn't this "Youn's Kitchen"?
(They're having food on the beach.)
You're Shin Gu.
- He's Shin Gu. - You're Youn Yuh Jung.
Jung Yu Mi is not here.
(You're watching Running Man.)
The flesh is so chewy.
(Their stomachs are filling up.)
I've never filled my mouth with shrimp before.
(Slurping)
This is the first time.
(So Min is slurping 30-dollar noodles.)
I feel pain in my chest.
- Why? - I don't know.
Isn't it because of instant noodles?
- No. - Are you okay?
(Can I have some?)
I'm sorry, but I can't give you any.
(It cost 30 dollars.)
I gave up on my clothes.
(Kwang Soo uses crayfish to lure her.)
It's filled with flesh.
Let me have a bite.
- I'll have a bite first. - Okay.
Let me have a bite of your noodles.
(So Min's in a dilemma.)
(Check this out.)
- I'm tired. - Look at this.
That looks so tasty.
Let me have a bite of your noodles.
(Desperate)
Fine.
(You can have a bite.)
Let me have a bite of your noodles.
(So Min gets to have a bite of the crayfish.)
Did her tooth just fall out?
Right.
Have just one bite.
(Kwang Soo gets to try the noodles.)
It tastes amazing.
(One bite)
(One big bite)
It tastes so good.
Hey!
(Empty)
(What is with this guy?)
He looks so ugly.
He ate everything.
After going into the water, instant noodles taste amazing.
(Angry)
- Give me some crab. - Okay.
Kwang Soo peeled all the crayfish for me.
- He deserved the noodles. - He's feeding her.
(Satisfied)
It tastes so good.
It tastes a bit lighter.
How can you be so good at peeling them?
You must have done it many times.
- Are you jealous? - You must have done it many times.
You've done it for many girls, right?
What are you talking about?
It tastes so good.
It shows.
Can you fry the heads for us?
(He changes the subject.)
- They usually do that. - They do.
Did you know? Shrimps are the cockroaches of the sea.
What do you mean?
They're called so.
Why?
(They take pictures to celebrate the successful trip.)
(I-Go Project is over. We did it!)
(They did some sightseeing on their own the next day.)
(Tiger Moth Tour is over.)
- You had so much fun. - Right.
(This question will determine who will receive the live show penalty.)
Kwang Soo looks like a celebrity.
His face looks bigger than Darth Vader's.
- It's because I'm in the front. - Are you sure?
I can't stop laughing.
(The memories make them laugh.)
Was everything just a dream?
A midsummer night's dream.
Whoever will be going to Australia...
I feel sorry for you.
It'll be harder than you imagine.
It's beyond your imagination.
- It was painful... - Really?
- and exhausting. - But we're still alive.
We managed to buy some souvenirs for you.
I bought what Seok Jin wanted too.
No, you didn't. I was watching you.
Again?
Attention, guys.
Is it whether he bought my present or not?
No way.
I was with you the whole time. You didn't get it.
- He didn't get it. - On the last day,
I went with Chul Min.
I couldn't buy one for everybody,
but I got a small present.
No, he didn't. I'm sure.
Yesterday, I...
bought a present for sure.
(Kwang Soo claims that he bought small presents for the members.)
I assure you.
Kwang Soo never bought any presents.
(So Min claims that he's lying and that he didn't buy anything.)
I was so tired.
(Did Kwang Soo buy presents for the members?)
He mentioned it earlier.
Kwang Soo claims that he bought the presents,
and So Min claims that he didn't.
- Kwang Soo? - For us?
- Can it be for just one person? - I couldn't buy one for everybody.
I couldn't.
It's something memorable. We didn't film the last day.
- We couldn't film it, - I see.
so we went out on our own.
I bought a few memorable things.
- He usually buys presents. - He does.
Did the two of you go around together or separately?
We went around together.
- All day? - Yes, we went around together.
We ate with the camera crew.
- We went out without the cameras. - We went...
If there were no cameras, he probably didn't buy it.
What do you mean?
- Someone has to be filming him? - Yes.
(He likes to take credits for what he does.)
We went and when Kwang Soo came back to the hotel,
he only had a shopping bag.
He only had chocolate wrappers...
and trash. That was all he had in the white plastic bag.
(So Min argues that Kwang Soo came back with a plastic bag.)
(He did go around downtown with a plastic bag.)
Didn't you talk about Seok Jin's present earlier?
He asked me for something over the phone.
Did I? I told you to get something, right?
- You mentioned it. - Right,
- I remember. - He said it in the morning.
He called me and told me to get something.
I remember it clearly.
- I told him to get fish jerky. - Fish jerky?
- Fish jerky. - Jerky?
- You asked for the marinated ones. - The marinated ones...
- You didn't get it. - from Indonesia and Thailand.
- The spicy ones? - Yes, the spicy ones.
- I know. - You know, right?
- It's good. - We couldn't find them.
- He didn't get it. - It's the red one.
Hold on. If I didn't get it, why would I say that?
Why?
If he took his sunglasses off,
we could have seen his eyes.
You won't be able to tell.
If we knew, we wouldn't be here.
(Come on, Se Chan.)
(That's true.)
When did you get it?
- When was it? - I walked...
- You guys were together. - I walked from the restaurant...
- to the coffee shop. - You were walking.
- What did you buy on the way? - There were no coffee shops.
Where? Where was it?
- Where was it? - They had it.
On the way...
Hold on.
Are they playing detectives?
- It's called an interrogation. - An interrogation.
That's what I meant.
I knew I had to get it.
Was it a grocery store?
- Hey, did you get it or not? - You didn't see him?
- You punk. - Look at this guy.
What are you doing?
This is annoying. Did you get it or not?
I got it. I got it, Jae Seok.
- Did you? - Yes.
- He was busy taking pictures. - This is annoying. Did you get it?
- There was a lot of construction. - Did you?
Don't they look like a couple who defrauds people?
If I didn't get it...
(They are both tiger moths.)
Did you use cash or credit card?
- I used cash. - What did you say?
Stop lying. You brought a credit card with you.
I paid cash.
What did you say?
(Why is he stuttering?)
You didn't get a refund, right?
- When you play games, - A refund?
you need betting money.
- Did you get money exchanged? - Isn't it an exchange?
What did you say?
- My bad. - It's because of the Nevis Swing.
It's because of the Nevis Swing. Please understand.
(This is how much he's scared of it.)
Please make your final decisions.
He might not have gotten the presents,
but Seok Jin asked for it.
So Min knows that...
- I got it for sure. - There was nowhere to buy it.
- Did you get it yet? - No, I didn't.
It's whether he got the present or not.
This is your final decision. In one...
- No way. - She saw me getting it.
- Two, - No, I didn't.
three.
(Kwang Soo named what he got, so he sounds trustworthy.)
(So Min had a picture to prove her point.)
(Se Chan has the most penalty badges.)
(Jong Kook and So Min are closely after him.)
(This question decides what they'll be doing on the holiday.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Which of the tiger moths will they trust?)
- I want to trust him. - I trust Kwang Soo.
- I pick Kwang Soo. - I trust him.
(3 pick Kwang Soo, and 3 others pick So Min.)
(They are tied 3 to 3.)
All day...
I didn't trust him all day and now I do.
The thing is...
- It might not be something big, - I think he got it.
but he usually gets little things.
He usually doesn't get money exchanged.
He could have borrowed it.
So Kwang Soo gets a penalty badge.
(Kwang Soo gets another penalty badge.)
- Right. - It's 3 on 3.
There might be a twist to this story.
(If they tie, Kwang Soo gets a penalty badge.)
- Hold on. - We are safe now.
So Min and I are safe now.
I lost this?
He ate it all. He bought and ate...
- all the snacks and chocolate. - Okay.
He ate it all.
(Their fates depend on who's telling the truth.)
The person...
who's lying will stand up...
- on my count of three. - The person who lied?
The person who lied?
- That person will stand up. - Okay.
- 1, - 1,
- 2... - 2...
(Se Chan, Seok Jin, and Jae Seok think he got the present.)
- 2, 3. - 2, 3.
(Jong Kook, Haha, and Ji Hyo believe So Min.)
(They think Kwang Soo didn't get the present.)
(Who's lying here?)
(Kwang Soo is lying.)
How can you lie to me about my present?
Are you human?
Sorry.
I said he didn't get it.
Why would I get presents when I went there for a penalty?
You should have said you didn't get it.
Why did you lie?
- Well... - What if I...
You know I didn't get once right?
I changed my mind at the end.
- You wanted me to trust you? - I'm sorry.
How can I trust you?
I'm sorry.
I think I know now.
Good job, So Min.
It depends on Se Chan's decision.
(The Tiger Moth Tour finally came to an end.)
All right. I'll tell you the final scores.
Se Chan has four penalty badges.
I didn't even get one right.
- How's that possible? - You're incredible.
He must be a shaman.
What is he saying?
(This is all because of you.)
So Min, Kwang Soo,
Jong Kook, Jae Seok,
and Seok Jin have two each.
For me, it's a big accomplishment to get half right,
but I can't believe I'm in crisis again.
(You should have trusted me.)
Ji Hyo and Haha...
are exempt from the penalty.
Enjoy your holidays.
I'll watch you guys on TV.
I'll watch you on TV.
Nevis Swing.
(It makes him tear up.)
I'd rather work on a holiday.
Now,
- Se Chan... - Does he get to choose?
will choose one person.
I'll introduce the live broadcast you'll be doing on Chuseok.
- What is it? - What is it?
It's a water bomb penalty with the citizens.
What did you say? Water bomb?
(It's a water bomb penalty with the citizens.)
(Se Chan and another member will complete a mission.)
(The loser gets the water bomb.)
Depending on the viewer's pick,
one of you will be exempted and the other will get the water bomb.
It'll be live.
I'm fine with the water bomb,
but we have to go all the way there.
We have to leave early from home.
Right.
Cars make an endless line.
Highways around the country had traffic from the morning.
The congestion has been the worst.
(They must fight the traffic and get to the rest stop first.)
Se Chan is in last place.
This is so tiring.
I'm so tired.
To be honest, Se Chan.
I'm not lying about this.
I have to go on a trip from the 5th or the 6th.
- It's from the 5th to the 12th. - So what?
- That's what I mean. - So what?
What am I supposed to do about that?
Are you asking me...
- to refund your flight? - He can go another time.
What am I supposed to do?
That's what I was thinking. What are you supposed to do?
It's until the 12th.
Just keep it in mind.
(I'm away until the 12th, just to let you know.)
Let me say this one thing.
If you skip me,
I'll skip you too.
That doesn't bother me at all.
I already have the Nevis Swing, so what would I skip?
I have nothing to back off from.
I'm just going forward.
He has to go to Oceania anyways.
- I have to go. - You might provoke him even more.
Why are you provoking me?
I was just saying.
What do you want me to do?
This is a coincidence,
but candidates for the penalty are sitting on one side,
and you two are sitting on the other side.
You're my sister from Mapo-gu.
I feel at ease.
Se Chan, stand behind...
and rip the name tag of the person you want to go with.
On October 18,
you two will go ahead with the penalty.
Ask who wants to volunteer.
Who wants to come with me?
(They're silent.)
- Goodness. - Look at all of you.
I see. Hold on.
- Hold on. - Wherever it may be.
- I'll go. - I was going to pass that person.
- I guess none of you want to come. - Where ever it may be.
I want to join you.
- By the way, - This is a mental game.
- I don't like what he's saying. - He's on my team.
He's on the Nevis team.
You have to think about this too.
Who do you think the viewers would like to see?
That's right.
He's a present to them.
He's a present himself.
Who do you think is the best in Running Man?
He's really a present.
- People will be so happy. - What are holidays for?
Who do you think can make people happy?
I'll exclude two people.
I'll exclude the Indonesian team.
- Thank you. - Why would you exclude them?
- Why would you do that? - I watched the video,
and they worked too hard. You know.
You have to admit that it was tough for them.
- Run towards me. - Yes.
Gosh.
(We'll watch the live broadcast at home.)
Please count down so that he can choose.
This is something good.
- Of course. - Please smile for me.
- From the sixth. - Show me your beautiful smiles.
We know how to smile.
I have a nice smile.
- Show me your beautiful smiles. - From the 6th to the 12th...
I get it. So what?
Why are you telling me that?
I'm Smile Kim.
Five.
- No way. - It's coming.
- Three, - Jae Seok.
two...
Make up your mind.
What is Se Chan's decision?
- Hurry up. - Everybody,
who would you like to see?
- Se Chan. - Who is it?
Is it Jong Kook or Seok Jin?
It's...
(Is it Jong Kook?)
(Is it Seok Jin who has a trip planned?)
(Is it Jae Seok who's the best emcee out there?)
Jae Seok.
It's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok will be joining him for the live broadcast.)
(Se Chan and Jae Seok will be broadcasting on Chuseok.)
Everybody wanted to see him, right?
(We'll be watching from home as well.)
It's Korea's best emcee, Yu Jae Seok.
We'll see you at the rest stop.
Good job, Se Chan.
- I listened to Jong Kook. - It's a present.
It's a present for the people.
- That's right. - Jong Kook was convincing.
I was convincing.
People will be so happy. They'll be so thankful.
Good job, Se Chan.
Bring your car, and pick me up.
Of course. I'll pick you up.
All right.
(He tries to calm down.)
- On the 8th... - Are you all right?
(Are you all right?)
- Are you all right? - He's not happy.
- Jae Seok. - Please smile, Jae Seok.
- Please. - He's not happy.
You should spend some time with him.
- I will. - Sure.
After this, the live broadcast will continue.
- We'll follow it. - Please smile.
"At the scene..."
(That's what they say on live broadcasts.)
You and I...
Reporter Yu Jae Seok.
You can call yourself.
Let's get to the scene.
I'll be there.
(Yes, I'll be there.)
(As the top emcee, he starts the broadcast right away.)
Yes, I'll be there.
Let's get it. Okay.
I'll be there.
(Jae Seok and Se Chan's Chuseok live broadcast starts now.)
(Deokpyeong Rest Stop, Icheon)
(Yu Jae Seok, Yang Se Chan)
- Hello. Nice to meet you. - Hello.
Hello, I'm Yang Se Chan.
Nice to meet you.
Finally,
- as you see, it's Chuseok. - You're right.
There's not much of it left,
but Se Chan and I...
- are here with many guests. - That's right.
We're doing a live broadcast at the rest stop.
It's a penalty.
That's right. Today finally came.
- Of course. - I didn't think it would come.
I thought about this.
Do we have to do the penalty on live broadcast?
Anyway, I'm here now.
We're here, and so many people are cheering for us.
- Isn't it great? - I'm so happy...
- that they are welcoming us. - So many people are here.
I'm so happy.
Did you enjoy the Chuseok holidays?
Se Hyung and I went to Dongducheon.
- I guess you met your friends. - Yes, we had many meatballs.
I heard Se Hyung was catching up with his friends...
and woke up at 5pm the next day.
Yes, he got a hangover.
- He's still bedridden. - I see.
Anyhow, Se Chan and I are at this rest stop...
doing a live broadcast. We have around 14 minutes left.
- Time flies. - I hope that...
we finish off nicely without making any mistakes.
- We'll get the penalty... - That's right.
and return home.
We still have tomorrow left of the holidays,
so please join Running Man during your long weekend.
I hope that you enjoy the rest of it.
Can you explain the rules to us?
- Should I explain it? - Should I?
- Yes. - I'll do it.
You're good at this.
I'll say it then. It's simple.
Today, we came here early...
and recruited three people per team.
We divided them up into Team Jae Seok and Team Se Chan.
We'll play three rounds.
There are four rounds in total.
We'll play four rounds. You see the roulette there?
- Yes, I do. - Whenever you lose,
- The name tags. - we'll put our names on it.
We'll spin the roulette at the end,
and if it stops on my name, I'll take the water bomb.
If it stops on your name, you'll get the water bomb.
If it lands on both of us, we'll both get it.
We'll both get the water bomb.
This is live, so we can't fake it.
We have to speak quickly...
because we have to finish in 15 minutes.
We have 13 minutes left.
We'll get started with the games for the live broadcast.
- Let's go. - Let's get started with round one.
The first game...
is something our viewers would have wanted to try.
- Many people would have. - It's Pirate Roulette.
Here it is.
Kwang Soo, Seok Jin,
- and I... You are one of us too. - Kind of.
- We are unlucky. - You are unlucky.
Our producer is rushing us.
Why did you set up a live broadcast then?
- You should have filmed it. - Let's get to the point.
- All right. - Shall we play?
He wants to get to the point.
Once I start talking, I can't stop.
Please interrupt me.
Here's round one. The game is,
as I have mentioned, it's Pirate Roulette.
Let me take one person from each team.
- Please come up. - It's Mr. Jung Bong Jun...
and Mr. Um Ki Young.
- Please come up. - Let's welcome them.
Please.
Nice to meet you. Hello.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Let's conduct a short interview.
Did you have a good holiday?
Where are you coming back from?
I went to Jecheon.
What were you doing there?
I went with my friends.
This is live, so you must be nervous.
Yes, a little bit.
You're joining us for the penalty today.
You'll be playing this game. How are you usually?
Are you lucky or unlucky like us?
I'm unlucky.
You chose the wrong person.
- I have to win. - Let me ask.
- Please introduce yourself. - How about you, Ki Young?
I'm Um Ki Young from Suwon. I'm 37 years old.
Do you usually get lucky?
I get really lucky.
- Really? - Where are you returning from?
- I was in Daegu. - I see.
- So you are lucky, right? - Yes.
- All right. - We would love to...
conduct longer interviews.
- But we have no time. - We have no time,
so we'll get started with round one right away.
You're unlucky like me,
- but I trust you this time. - Let's get it.
- Please come forward, Bong Jun. - Please come forward, Ki Young.
Please do rock-paper-scissors.
- The winner... - The winner will go first.
You can choose.
Please do rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
- He won. - You won.
He can go first.
Good job.
It won't pop up from the beginning, right?
That'll be fun.
Okay... What?
Everybody.
(Team Se Chan wins.)
Everybody, this is live broadcast.
This wasn't made up.
Bong Jun, you are so unlucky.
You're so unlucky.
- Ki Young didn't even do anything. - I know...
I'm unlucky but not this much.
You're Kwang Soo's level.
- I just got goosebumps. - Me too.
Ki Young didn't even go.
Round one is over.
That was too short.
You're in disbelief.
How do you feel?
I'm happy.
You're happy?
- Really? - I'm so unhappy right now.
- How can you do that in 1 try? - He lost in 1 try.
- So round one, - I won.
I lost. Thank you, Bong Jun and Ki Young.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Please have a seat.
I'll stick on your name tag.
I'm so...
Thank you.
During the holidays...
You're supposed to stick mine up.
- That was close. - This is live,
so it's...
a small glitch.
You can put it anywhere.
Sure.
I was so flustered...
on live television.
As soon as Bong Jun said that he's unlucky...
- As soon as he said it. - As soon as he played,
- the pirate popped up. - Right.
This could have been made up.
I was so flustered that I almost stuck my name up.
Bong Jun had no idea.
I find something else really strange.
Bong Jun looks too happy.
He looks so composed.
He thinks he did something grand.
He forgot that he's on my team.
Ki Young didn't do anything. I feel bad for him.
That's right. He only introduced himself.
He merely said he's from Suwon.
He didn't do anything, and he's back in his seat.
- Thank you, Ki Young. - Thank you.
Let's get started with round two.
This is live so we must hurry. Please understand.
Round two is another roulette game we played a lot.
We did.
- It's Water Gun Roulette. - Let's go.
Let's invite our guests.
It's Ms. Kim Min Soo and Mr. Cho Seung Hoon.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I'm... - Sorry?
I'm Kim Min Soo, and I'm a mom with two kids.
- She's Kim Min Soo. - Please introduce yourself.
I'm Cho Seung Hoon from Suwon. I'm 33 years old.
He's Seung Hoon.
I heard that...
you are a married couple.
- Is that right? - Yes.
One of you are on my team, and the other is on Se Chan's team.
- You're separated. Is that okay? - It's okay.
- Is it okay? - Yes, it is.
Are you okay too, Min Soo?
- Yes, I am. - I see.
We separated the team. I'm sure you saw earlier.
During the first round,
our team lost.
We need for you to win.
Okay.
Are you good with games? Are you usually lucky?
Yes, I am.
- That's great. What about you? - I'm relieved.
- I'm usually unlucky. - He...
- Are you really? - He has bad luck.
Thank goodness.
We need to win this time...
for the game...
- to become neck and neck. - That's right.
How has your Chuseok holiday been so far?
My family... Our family...
went on a trip.
- A trip? - Where did you go?
- The east coast. - That's so nice.
How was the trip?
- It was fun. - Was it?
Were you driving the whole time?
No, my wife...
took turns with me. It was a relaxing trip.
Were there any funny happenings on the trip?
It was my first time seeing the sunrise.
It was very meaningful for me.
- Wish. - When you saw it,
- did you make a wish? - Yes.
What did you wish for?
For my family to have luck.
- What about you? - What about you?
- I was sleeping then. - You were sleeping.
Did you only sleep?
- I slept in. - You shouldn't say that.
This can't be aired.
She just told me something.
Did she say something? Is she mad about him sleeping?
- I can't say it since we're live. - You can't.
I would say it if we're recording since we can edit it out.
However, I can't say this. She was so mad...
- that she told me something. - She was mad.
I'll tell you what she said after the live show finishes.
Do you have any idea what she might have said?
- I'm not sure. - No?
- You'll be shocked. - Shocked?
Since we're live, we'll hurry and move on.
- Water gun. - If you keep rolling that,
you might accidentally roll forward...
since it's their first live show. Please be very careful.
Anyway...
Anyway, the live show continues.
First round of penalties.
They're a married couple.
One water gun has water in it...
- while the other doesn't. - No.
You must choose 1 on the count of 3,
then shoot toward your opponent.
Toward the face.
- Will that be all right? - Yes, it's fine.
- Are you okay with it? - Yes, I'm fine.
- Great. - They're so into it that...
- we question their marriage. - You're right.
- They're so focused. - They're focused.
- Okay, move up. - Please move up.
We'll now start the Water Gun Roulette.
You can choose the one you want.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors
Okay, Seung Hoon.
Are you sure it's that one?
Okay.
Min Soo.
Please be careful with what you mouth.
- All right. - Min Soo.
Point it towards your opponent.
- Don't shoot it yet. - Not yet.
- Now... - Aim it towards the face.
- Towards the face. - Yes.
One. Towards the face.
1, 2, 3. Shoot.
Okay! Hold on.
- Stop. - Stop shooting.
- She's really mad. - She's your wife.
Are you all right?
She's so mad.
We lost again.
- In the middle... - I'm going crazy.
I thought you were lucky.
I guess I'm not.
What I'm worried about...
- is that they'd fight. - They might fight.
You shouldn't do that.
Are you all right? There's a lot of water. Sorry.
- With that, Se Chan won again. - This round too.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
Min Soo, are you okay? We don't have any towels.
It's my name again.
Why are we doing this?
It's just my name on the roulette.
We only have about five minutes
- You have to stick it on faster. - All right.
Se Chan.
We have to proceed to the third round...
- within 2 minutes and 30 seconds. - It's your turn.
Let's invite Hyun Jung and Gyu Ri up.
- Come on up! - What is the next game?
- This will be our last game. - Yes.
- It's Egg Roulette! - Egg war!
It's Egg Roulette.
One will be boiled...
- while the other will be raw. - It's raw.
The two of you will strike...
the eggs on our heads as hard as you can.
The one with the raw egg loses.
- We'll put on the name sticker. - That's right!
How will the last round go?
Hyun Jung,
this is a live show. Are you nervous?
I'm really nervous.
- Are you all right? - Yes.
Where are you coming from?
We went to visit my grandpa's grave.
You saw how hard our teammates played,
but we're losing. I really want you to win.
Gyu Ri, please introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Kim Gyu Ri from Incheon. I'm 20 years old.
Gyu Ri, are you the lucky type?
- No. - You're not?
She's not. Gyu Ri,
I heard that you're a fan of Yang Se Hyung.
Yes, I'm his fan.
- Really? - You're in front of Se Chan.
- He's Se Hyung's brother. - What do you think?
Do you prefer my brother?
Pardon?
All right, all right.
We don't have time, so we won't interrogate.
- Please don't. - All right.
Hyun Jung and Gyu Ri, please step forward.
- Should we prepare ourselves? - All right.
Yes, let's get started right away.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Hyun Jung and Gyu Ri,
you don't have to be nice to us.
Just strike us as hard as you can. Rock-paper-scissors
- We keep on winning. - Please pick one first.
- Great. - You too, Hyun Jung.
- Let's go. - Only one is boiled.
Hit us on our foreheads. 1, 2, 3!
Great.
Thank you, Hyun Jung.
- I lost. - Put it down here.
- It's fine. - Are you all right?
- Go wipe your hand. - You can wipe it over there.
Thank you.
I lost this time.
Since I lost, we have to put up my name.
Did we use that again this time?
Great.
Thanks to Hyun Jung, I won.
- Now, we don't have time. - Time...
It'll be our last round.
Se Chan and I will play rock-paper-scissors...
to stick on the last two names.
Let's go.
Yes. You and me.
- One against one? - A single-round match.
- Okay, rock-paper-scissors - Scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors - I won!
Okay!
(Se Chan wins!)
This is driving me crazy.
Okay, we don't have much time. I'm so sorry.
If you see us rushing on the screen,
you would feel anxious too.
- However, it can't be helped. - I'm putting on two, right?
Last 1. Yes, 2.
Min Ki, please come up.
All right.
- This is the last bit. - It's the final.
Thank you for waiting, Min Ki.
Since we're out of time,
I need you to turn the roulette right away. Min Ki,
- please turn it well. - Okay.
- Okay. - Please get Se Chan.
- Good luck, Min Ki. - Min Ki.
All right.
(Final Roulette)
We...
- We have to put this down. - The penalty...
Whoever gets picked will get the water bomb.
Turn it!
(Their fates lies with this roulette!)
(Who will get the water bomb?)
Who will it be?
Please! Please. Please...
Yu Jae Seok!
(Yu Jae Seok gets the water bomb.)
- Microphone. - Hand it to me.
All right. I'm fine.
Don't worry.
You got the penalty again.
We should be saying...
- our last goodbyes. - Yes.
Whenever I play these games,
- I see how unlucky I am. - You're unlucky.
However, I had fun.
Thank you for joining us today.
As I've mentioned before,
- the holiday is almost over. - That's right.
I hope you all spent a lovely, long holiday.
Do you feel refreshed?
It's very refreshing. I want to thank those that helped us.
Bong Jun, Min Soo, Hyun Jung,
Gyu Ri, Seung Hoon, Ki Young,
- and also Min Ki. - Min Ki.
I want to thank all of you that joined us today.
All of the citizens that participated in our shoot...
and also the audience joining us at home, thank you.
We have a minute left.
We rushed,
- and now there's a minute left. - You told us to rush.
We have a minute left now.
- We have about 50 seconds left. - About 50 seconds.
We were saying goodbye, and it didn't occur to us.
Today, you came...
all the way to a rest stop and proved how unlucky you are.
How do you feel?
Aside from how I feel,
I...
My pants are really wet right now.
- Do you feel damp? - It's damp.
- That is Chuseok. - Yes.
Chuseok should be damp.
- It should be damp? - Yes.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Anyway, I think we can take our time...
- to say our goodbyes. - Yes.
I suddenly thought of this.
We're always rushing too much with our lives.
It just occurred to me.
- We could have taken it slowly. - Yes.
We rushed too much.
My microphone was put on in a rush.
- It's such a mess. - Yes.
The lines are tangled.
- There are seven seconds left. - We should say bye.
We'll send you our goodbyes now.
Dear everyone, please look forward...
- to next week. Bye! - Bye!
(Next week)
(It's finally here.)
(They need to decide who will join him in the crocodile cage.)
(Mission name: Find Kwang Soo's Assistant)
(Shin Sung Rok)
(Yoon Bo Mi)
(No one knows...)
(about their mysterious existence.)
(The clues about the assistant...)
(will be revealed one by one.)
(It's him?)
(They must be eliminated!)
(Find the Assistant)