(This is Running Man's global project of 2017.)
(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by bloggers)
(Shark cage, USA)
(Cage of Death, Australia)
That's crazy.
(Fly Toledo, Spain)
(Active volcano in Mount Bromo and Mount Ijen, Indonesia)
(The two newcomers face the risk of dangerous trips.)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan)
(Nevis Swing, New Zealand)
(3 Tour Stickers will earn them a trip to the tourist attraction.)
(The members have been accumulating Tour Stickers.)
(Global Race)
(The final round, Dangerous Shoe Throw)
(Eliminate the others to win mission fees.)
(By winning 100 dollars, Jae Seok has 200 dollars in total.)
(Buy Tour Stickers and Reflecting Cards at the Store of Fate.)
(Tour Stickers or Reflecting Cards?)
(How will this end?)
(They're on their way to the Store of Fate.)
After watching the show, my mom told me...
not to behave like I do at home.
(Her mom told her not to behave like she does at home.)
She said I give others trouble.
Do you give your mother trouble too?
- Yes. - Really?
(They didn't know...)
(how much trouble So Min was about to give them.)
All right. You can purchase the cards at the Store of Fate now.
We buy them first?
(It's been decided that Seok Jin and Se Chan are going on the trip.)
(They can buy Tour Stickers and Reflecting Cards with mission fees.)
I want a Tour Sticker.
Thank you.
(Haha buys a Tour Sticker for 50 dollars.)
Please give me a Tour Sticker.
(Jong Kook buys a Tour Sticker too.)
So Min.
(By earning 200 dollars, Jae Seok is the richest member.)
Jae Seok could send two people on the trip.
I'm still thinking.
So Min, think carefully.
See you in a while.
(3 Tour Stickers, or 1 Reflecting Card and 1 Tour Sticker?)
I prefer being unhappy together...
than being happy alone.
(I prefer being unhappy together.)
- Gosh, you're... - You're unbelievable.
You're so...
(What will So Min choose?)
I want to shout from the top of a mountain.
- Shout what? - What?
So Min is crazy!
(So Min is very crazy!)
(Wait and see.)
(Glancing)
(What is she buying with a smile on her face?)
(So Min's purchase is done.)
- How many did you buy? - How many did you buy?
- Is it a secret? - Yes.
Everyone's done purchasing, right?
I'm not.
(I'm not done yet.)
(Jae Seok accidentally won the Dangerous Shoe Throw.)
(Did I just win?)
(He can get either 4 Tour Stickers or 2 Reflecting Cards.)
The man of the day.
- Jae Seok, go ahead. - Go ahead.
(It's the richest member's turn.)
I trust you, Jae Seok.
Let's be unhappy together.
With this money,
I can even send someone who has no Stickers at all.
(He can send someone who has nothing.)
In addition to that, I could send Kwang Soo too.
(Global Race)
Please don't.
Do you understand?
(Jae Seok's purchase...)
(will determine everyone's fate.)
(A Tour Sticker costs 50 dollars, and a Reflecting Card costs 100.)
(Defend with Reflecting Cards or attack with Tour Stickers?)
Should I get Reflecting Cards?
(I should be careful. I could be counter-attacked.)
(Reflecting Cards will keep him safe...)
(while Tour Stickers can get everyone in trouble.)
(After a long pondering, what will Jae Seok choose?)
Please.
(All 4 members with money have made purchases.)
All right.
Let's decide the attacking order now.
The attacking order is important.
Ladies first.
Go ahead.
(This attack will...)
(determine who will be sent on the trip.)
Can we save the Reflecting Cards for later?
No, you can't.
Everyone will find out who has them.
If your turn comes early...
- It's useless. - So you have to...
How many times do we have to tell you?
(What?)
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
- Who's number one? - Who is it?
(It's a war of nerves.)
(Number 1 won't be able to use their Reflecting Cards.)
Let's check. It's So Min.
(So Min goes first.)
So Min is number one.
(Then my strategy should be...)
(As long as we're together, I don't mind misfortunes.)
(3 Tour Stickers, or 1 Reflecting Card and 2 Tour Stickers?)
So Min goes first. What did you buy?
What did you buy?
(3 Tour Stickers, or 1 Reflecting Card and 2 Tour Stickers?)
She bought three.
(So Min got 3 Tour Stickers.)
(So Min has 3 Tour Stickers.)
You bought three Tour Stickers?
You want to be unhappy together.
That's what I want.
- Great job. - So Min.
Number one.
- So Min. - In my opinion,
a Reflecting Card can take away only one Sticker, right?
- Yes. - Then...
(If that's what a Reflecting Card can do...)
I think Jae Seok has Reflecting Cards.
So...
if I give him three Tour Stickers...
(Tour Stickers)
- Wait. - She's so scary.
She's crazy.
She's lost her mind.
So Min, you're the best.
- Why would you do that? - I'm so surprised.
That's my plan number one.
- Plan number two is this. - Is it Kwang Soo?
Is it Kwang Soo?
(Her second plan is sending Haha and Kwang Soo.)
Plan number three is...
like this.
(She can send Jong Kook and Kwang Soo too.)
- Me? - So Min.
Why am I included in both plans?
If Haha can promise me...
- If he can promise me, - Okay.
then here and...
As soon as you put one here, we'll be one.
(Let's attack Jae Seok together. We'll be one.)
If you attack Jae Seok, we'll all help you.
What are you talking about?
If Haha can promise me, even if Jae Seok uses a Reflecting Card,
Haha will attack him again. Then I can attack Kwang Soo too.
- Deal. - Wait.
Look. So Min, look at this.
It's been too long since Haha got his last Tour Sticker.
Send him away.
- So Min, I promise you. - Send him away.
- I promise you. Trust me. - Fine.
It's fun and unexpected.
Let's keep our backs turned. Come here. My gosh.
So Min will make a decision on her own now.
Please put your Stickers on the board.
She's crazy.
I don't know what So Min wants.
What if I put one here?
I have to put two here no matter what.
(Whom did So Min pick?)
It's impossible to know what she's thinking.
(So Min makes her decision.)
Everyone, come and take a look.
(She quietly walks away.)
So Min is confident about her decision.
(She believes in her decision.)
(Who is the lucky member that she chose?)
She lost her mind.
(She picked Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.)
(Jae Seok gets 2. Kwang Soo gets 1.)
She lost her mind.
(Come here, you.)
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong, So Min?
- I'm sorry. - Why did you do that to me?
What's wrong with you? I told you to look at the overall picture.
- Look at the overall picture. - Why did you do that?
- What's wrong with you? - It's...
It's because you had two Tour Stickers.
- My goodness. - She made her decision.
Who's next?
- It's all because of you, So Min. - How many does he have?
He has two.
(Does Jae Seok have two cards?)
What if Jae Seok has two Reflecting Cards?
There's no way he has two.
- Definitely not. - No.
It's because Jae Seok is the type to attack others.
(Attack others?)
- He has Tour Stickers. - Right?
He may not have any Reflecting Cards.
He'd never buy two of them.
- That's what I thought. - Okay, everybody.
(Haha makes his decision.)
It's Jong Kook.
(Haha puts a Tour Sticker next to Jong Kook's name.)
(How dare you?)
(Laughing)
What a piece of trash.
(How dare you target me?)
(Haha puts a Tour Sticker on Jong Kook.)
- I understand now. - This is the last one.
(Haha and Jong Kook target each other.)
Is it finally my turn?
(The last member to go is Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok has about 200 dollars.)
(Does Jae Seok have 4 Tour Stickers or 2 Reflecting Cards?)
(What does he have?)
I've been waiting for this day.
You know exactly the type of person I am.
(You were right.)
(What does he mean by that?)
(He targets them.)
He has four of them.
(I have four Tour Stickers.)
(He bought four Tour Stickers and no Reflecting Cards.)
He has four?
He will always attack.
(It's better to attack with Tour Stickers.)
So Min, you're in danger.
I choose you, So Min.
(She's doomed.)
So Min.
(So Min is about to be doomed.)
- I had no idea that he had four. - So Min.
I choose So Min.
I like to jump into the fire.
(He likes to be daring just like So Min.)
Jae Seok is so fiery.
- Here's one for Haha. - Come on.
Ji Hyo will be bored, Jae Seok.
And then he suddenly attacks Ji Hyo.
(Let us surprise her with Tour Stickers.)
She doesn't say a word at important times like this.
(4 Tour Stickers leave her speechless.)
- I have no idea. - Should we look away?
- Should we stay away? - Should we?
- Please turn around. - Come to the back.
Everyone knows that...
- he'll attack So Min. - Jae Seok.
(I beg you on my knees not to give me three Stickers.)
- Jae Seok. - Don't you remember...
what you've done to me?
Did you put this here, So Min?
(What is he talking about?)
- Yes, she did. - I see.
What's wrong with you?
Goodness.
I just wanted to ask.
He has no idea what's going on.
- What's wrong with him? - He was confused.
Then why did he laugh with us?
(What was Seok Jin laughing at?)
It's because we sacrificed sleep to see the dolphins.
I couldn't sleep.
(He blames the dolphins.)
- Shall we move back? - Yes.
Let's step back.
I'll go to Hawaii.
(He ponders.)
For now...
(The past is in the past.)
(Jae Seok has four Tour Stickers.)
(Will he choose So Min who attacked him mercilessly?)
(Or will he choose other members?)
I was completely duped.
(Whom will Jae Seok appoint to go on the Dangerous Trip?)
(He makes shooting sounds again.)
(Jae Seok makes his decision.)
Let's go.
Are you finished?
I made a clear decision.
(Everyone is at risk.)
(Who will go with Jae Seok on the Dangerous Trip?)
- Darn it. - It's time to party.
It's time to party.
- It's time to party. - Goodness.
(Jae Seok chooses Haha and So Min.)
- It's time to party. - It's fine.
That was a wise decision.
- Kwang Soo and So Min. - That's right.
This is like "The Sixth Sense".
There are twists within twists.
I understand now.
- Isn't that too many of us? - It is.
- That's too many. - What about Jong Kook and Ji Hyo?
(The chosen members are finalized.)
There's a total of 6 members with 3 Tour Stickers.
It's 6 out of 8 members.
- Everyone goes somewhere together. - Really?
(The other 2 members will come.)
Everyone will go somewhere together.
Everyone?
Only the six members will experience the Dangerous Tour.
That's too many. Let's move the stickers.
Could you exclude 2 out of 6 members?
Among the six members,
please choose a leader.
What will the leader do?
- The tour destinations include... - Does the leader choose?
Hawaii, Indonesia, Japan, and many more.
(It's a difficult decision.)
The leader decides where you will go.
(Shark cage, USA)
(Cage of Death, Australia)
(Fly Toledo, Spain)
(Active volcano in Mount Bromo and Mount Ijen, Indonesia)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan)
(Nevis Swing, New Zealand)
(Insano water slide, Brazil)
(Where will the members go?)
- You should be the leader. - I'll be the leader.
He's lucky today.
- It's because... - He's lucky today.
I'm lucky today.
Okay.
(Jae Seok will choose one ball.)
Which Dangerous Tourist Attraction will Jae Seok choose?
Please don't say it like that.
Don't pick anything with heights or ghosts.
Didn't you see me win during Dangerous Shoe Throw?
Jae Seok, pick a ball with your foot.
- Your feet are lucky today. - Listen.
- I saved you today. - That's true.
- Haha was being annoying. - Okay.
- Hurry and choose. - Okay.
Don't pick Labyrinth of Fear.
You should practice picking.
You'd better pick well. Don't pick the one in Japan.
(It's scary enough to appear on the Guinness World Records.)
No heights and no Labyrinth of Fear.
(The pressure is immense from an incredible height.)
(Nevis Swing, New Zealand and Insano water slide, Brazil)
I'd rather die.
- Labyrinth of Fear is the worst. - I agree.
Volcanoes are also scary.
(Among the world's seven Dangerous Tourist Attractions...)
- Did you pick one? - No heights or Japan.
I don't know.
You must pick well.
No heights or ghosts.
(Which place did Jae Seok pick?)
(He shuffles the balls.)
(This one feels right.)
(Please pick a good one.)
- Did you pick one? - No heights or Labyrinth of Fear.
- I don't know. - Let's see.
(Which one did Jae Seok pick?)
- Gosh. - Why did you pick this?
(What kind of reaction is it?)
No heights or Japan.
- I don't know. - Let's see.
- Gosh. - Why did you pick this?
- No. - Let's see.
- He lost his mind. - He picked one.
- I saw it. - He picked a ball.
(Which Tourist Attraction did he pick?)
- Please show us the ball. - I can't believe him.
Everyone is murmuring right now.
I've lost my mind.
Let's pick another one.
- He's so unlucky. - Which one is it?
(He picked Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan.)
It's Japan.
Why did you pick that of all places?
- Gosh. - He's so terrible.
Did you really pick that?
Please show it to us.
The Dangerous Tourist Attraction is...
- the one in Japan. - Hey!
(Everyone gets upset.)
(Welcome to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
How could I have known?
- Are they all for Japan? - My goodness.
No, he picked one ball for Japan.
I wanted to go to the shark cage in Hawaii.
(He wanted to go to Hawaii.)
He's an American.
I wanted to go.
Here are the members...
to be punished on Dangerous Tourist Attractions.
They're Jae Seok, So Min, Seok Jin, Se Chan, Kwang Soo, and Haha.
This is so unfair.
- You'll be going to Japan. - This is the least fair to me.
Getting a visa to film in Japan will take some time.
We'll go to Japan as soon as we're ready.
What if you're haunted by the ghosts?
You have no other choice.
What if while children watch Running Man on TV,
we crawl out of the screen?
(What if the members pop out of the screen and scare them?)
What will you do then?
You should give R Badge or something to the ones who get possessed.
If that happened, you should admit they got possessed...
for the program's sake.
Jae Seok is the one at fault.
- What did I do wrong? - So later,
let's spin it once more...
in front of that ghost's house.
That's a great idea. Let's do it just once.
- Are you possessed already? - We...
(Possessed)
- "Who are you?" - "Who are you?"
(Hey, producers. Aren't I cute?)
(It's for certain they really don't want to go.)
Goodness.
Just once.
- Okay? - You...
- In front of the entrance. - Let's say he's in.
- In front of it. - Do you think I'm crazy?
- For us five. Okay? - Why should I go in?
- Okay? - Deal!
(Those 6 cowards play especially dirty today.)
While we're issuing the visa,
we will have some time.
So we will plan a special to exclude whom in the meantime.
- Great. - Okay.
- Thanks. - We'll think about it.
(How will their fate turn out to be?)
(A week later, Mok-dong SBS)
(Let's go on the tour!)
(Congratulations on your tour for Super Scary Labyrinth!)
- Hello. - I'm going for certain.
- It's almost decided, right? - Right.
(It's the cruel ending of the Tour Sticker battle.)
(The victor is relaxed and excited.)
Everyone, did you see the banner behind you?
What is that?
- Goodness! - We're going at last.
Is it something to congratulate?
Yes! We're going.
It's rather something painful.
After a long journey of our first global project,
Dangerous Tour,
we have decided...
- I'm going crazy. - the six members...
- to leave for Japan. - So why did he choose Japan?
Six members?
- It's all the same anyway. - We had the shark cage.
It's close to here at least.
- I heard from them briefly, - Six members are too many.
and it's worse than your imagination.
- That's what I'm saying. - He's so annoying.
- You're not even going. - I know. He's not even going.
- Why did you do the research? - He can't stop smiling.
Move aside. Just get lost.
(He's so annoyed.)
He keeps teasing us when he's not going.
- He's so annoying. - Come here.
Whatever. You guys just date.
Come here, Jong Kook.
(It's more annoying because they accept the teasing.)
Don't tease them.
- You can't tease them. - We never get worked up.
- They don't care. - We're never upset about our jokes.
So we're on the progress of issuing the visa at the moment.
The staff has visited the place last week.
- I see. - We know.
You guys look so pale.
- They said it's no joke. - I think some of you are missing.
- Are you sure you're not possessed? - The number is fewer than before.
- They look so blank. - Bring me salt, please.
We noticed something unusual.
They were selling underwear near the exit.
(It's for the visitors to take care of accidents.)
(Two days ago in Tokyo)
Look at the mannequins.
(It's scary from the start.)
(My gosh, it's so scary.)
Goodness.
(Freaking out)
(Frightened)
(Some of them gave up in the middle.)
(Main scriptwriter)
- Do they really sell underwear? - Yes.
We're already...
(They should bring extra underwear.)
Before we leave for Japan, we've decided to...
throw you a party since you worked hard...
- for this special. - I see.
It's not something to celebrate.
- Are you serious? - Must you have prepared this?
They're feeding us before making us suffer more.
The celebration party we've prepared for today...
is about sending only four of you off to the tour.
It's called The Chosen Four.
- Only 4? - 4?
(They're surprised.)
(Did you just say only four will go?)
- Are you serious? - What?
- Did you say 4? - 2 of us can survive?
- 2 of us will be exempted. - 2 of us!
- Yes! - Only 4 will go!
- Yes! - This is it!
(Due to team balance, 2 will be exempted.)
- This is why people live in hope. - I'm serious now.
In my opinion, Kwang Soo...
would want to go.
- Why would I? - I mean...
Why would I want to be possessed?
Why would I want to pee in my pants?
He wants to go.
So Min would want to go as well.
- No way. - She's curious.
You don't want to go, but you will have no choice.
(It's the fact that he will eventually have to go.)
- Right. - You're going for certain.
- Hey. - I'm serious.
I...
We will exempt the two of you...
according to the results...
- of today's mission. - Okay.
(Desperate)
There will be two courses of meals prepared at a dining place outside.
Really?
The two people whose names are called will head there.
They will choose a course they want after checking the ingredients.
- Then... - Okay.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo will go first...
- and choose a course. - Are we up?
So the two have to make different choices.
- They can't make the same choice. - Right.
(What is hidden behind today's course meal?)
What is that? It's alive.
(Lamb chop versus king crab)
(It's the highlight of seafood that looks amazing and tastes great.)
My goodness. I'm choosing lamb chops. Those king crabs are alive.
(Juicy and delicious lamb chops)
This is it.
- What do you want to have? - I choose this.
- All right. We've done choosing. - I want something dead.
King crabs are good for your health.
- Goodness. - And...
Move to the table if you're done with your choices.
- Okay. - Table?
(It does look like a party.)
My goodness.
(The table on the left has various grilled meat.)
- Right. - This table is for lamb chops?
(The table on the right has tasty dishes including king crab.)
I see they grilled the lamb chop like steak.
(What do these ingredients mean?)
(Next up are Jae Seok and Haha.)
Do you have king crab in the morning?
I'll choose these lamb chops.
(Jae Seok chose lamb chops, and Haha chose king crab.)
Jong Kook chose king crab.
I chose king crab too.
(Next up are So Min and Se Chan.)
- All right. I choose this. - Will you be all right?
- Is that right? - So Min is in our group?
- Welcome. - Thanks.
(He's worried with Ji Hyo and So Min in his group.)
- I think Kwang Soo... - I think...
- Welcome. - Kwang Soo...
- I chose the king crab. - Okay!
- My goodness. - This should be the way it is.
- Well... - We're in trouble now.
It's going strange now.
How did it turn out this way?
We have the weakest members here.
- I haven't felt this in a while. - Gosh.
- It's not right. - I may not go to the ghost's house.
All right. Go ahead and enjoy your meal.
- Can we eat now? - Gosh, this...
- Haha. - Do we just eat?
- Give us gloves. - I have a bad feeling about this.
Goodness.
What is this tea?
- It's called suutei tea. - What is this?
(Suutei tea is a kind of milk tea that is seasoned with salt.)
- Suutei tea. - Milk tea.
(Why are they giving us this special tea?)
(Without any doubt, they start boning the king crab.)
Look at this meat.
It's so plump.
(It's filled with meat.)
(They're fully enjoying the party.)
Look at this meat.
It's so delicious. I haven't had this for a long time.
(They have completely forgotten about the labyrinth.)
It's good.
Now, I'm craving king crabs.
- Hey. - Look at those king crabs.
(The two teams enjoy their meals.)
It's only in the morning.
- But we're filling ourselves. - Right.
So Jong Kook and Ji Hyo...
are just helping out their teams?
Yes, they are the team leaders.
- I see. - Team leaders?
(They are the team leaders for today.)
That's good to hear.
If I were in that team, Jong Kook would be my team leader.
- Gosh. - That's one good thing.
I should have him as my team member someday.
Lucky me.
Your team looks...
exactly like Jong Kook and his lackeys.
You could've made our team perfect.
What did you just say?
Jong Kook...
- and his lackeys. - You'd have been the same.
- Be quiet. - You would've been the same.
I see your team...
has two female members.
You're not having one-sided love, are you?
(Two middle aged men's one-sided love)
(So Min and Ji Hyo are like volunteers.)
Give up on them already.
- What did you just say? - This is ridiculous.
- You must spend a lot of money. - What did you just say?
- One-sided love? - What?
- Sit down. - All right.
(Good boy, Jae Seok.)
(Ji Hyo is the queen bee in the team.)
I'll sit down immediately if that's what you want.
- You're lucky to be in this team. - Of course.
For your information, the two team leaders...
will decide the two members to be exempted from the tour...
after today's mission.
(The team leaders will decide...)
(the two members to be exempted from the tour.)
I'm so glad I'm not on his team.
(Standing up immediately)
(Sorry, I didn't get to say hi yet.)
He wouldn't choose me for certain.
- Do you want to eat anything? - Go sit down.
- Ji Hyo. - Let go.
- Ji Hyo. - Let her go.
- Stop bugging me. - Ji Hyo hates things like that.
- I hate things like this. - She doesn't like it.
(They're treating him like a VIP.)
- I count on you. - Ji Hyo hates things like that.
By the way, Se Chan didn't call me even once...
- outside the shooting. - My goodness.
- He thought lowly of you. - That was too harsh.
(You rude punk!)
Why would you do that?
- That was out of line. - Scold him.
Se Chan, you may not know well about...
how variety shows work,
but this is all... You know?
- It's all about relationships. - Right.
(The relationship is irreparable now.)
Considering you're done with your meal,
I will now give you the first quiz that has Chance Card on the line.
Chance Card?
Trust me.
Here's the quiz.
Where are the dishes you just ate from?
Haha!
(They're ready to answer already.)
- Russia. - Russia.
- It's Russia. - King crabs are caught in Russia.
It's not caught in Korea for certain.
- New Zealand. - No.
- It's from New Zealand. - Lamb meat...
It's usually from New Zealand or Australia.
- It's not right. - Hold on.
- It's right. - Shut it!
I buy them often.
- So I know. - That's only the usual case.
It says they're from New Zealand.
I think it's done once they answer.
- What? - Why would you shout?
- Don't shout at our team leader! - Seriously.
How dare he!
- Good job. - You can't do that.
How dare you point at my team member?
He wasn't pointing at him.
How dare you!
(How dare a newbie act rude?)
(Ji Hyo's attack started the battle between the two team.)
- What's wrong with her? - Stop it.
- You punks! - Seriously!
Seriously.
(Nice catch!)
(He caught Seok Jin's slow throw.)
I caught it.
(Our team must not lose at anything.)
I should step in after a long time.
(Killer Yu of Sanitary Glove Gang)
- Jae Seok. - What do you think you're doing?
Don't wear those gloves. They might get hurt.
Shall I bring it on, wearing my gloves?
- They might get hurt. - Stop.
- What are you doing? - You're safe thanks to me.
Killers like us don't leave a trace.
- Both of you, sit down. - Will you serve me the food?
- Both of you will get hurt. - Don't put on the gloves.
You punks.
Go to Russia. This king crab is from Russia.
No, this is from Chile.
This king crab is from Chile.
- I advise you to go with Chile. - I second that.
Have you ever had king crab from Chile?
I have seen it.
- Please make your decisions. - We should choose this one...
since this one is the most well-known.
- Okay. - This is better.
Team Jong Kook.
- It's Russia. - It's Russia.
(Team Jong Kook's answer is Russia.)
Team Jong Kook, the answer for its origin of the product is...
(Is the king crab Team Jong Kook ate really from Russia?)
This has to be correct.
The answer is Russia.
(Their answer, Russia, is correct!)
(Yes! We got it right!)
- Jong Kook. - Trust me.
(Gosh, we're envious.)
Jong Kook, I thought the answer was Russia from the start.
- Hey, you said it was from Chile! - Stop it.
- Stay out of this, Se Chan. - Hey, he said it was from Chile.
- Chile? - Haha, I'm on your side.
- Do you want Jong Kook to fail? - Jong Kook, I am sorry.
What is the origin of your food? In 1, 2, 3.
- New Zealand. - Seok Jin keeps saying...
Let's go with New Zealand. I'm telling you. It's from New Zealand.
Team Ji Hyo, your answer was New Zealand.
- Now that I think of it... - The origin of your food is...
(Seok Jin insists the answer is New Zealand.)
(Just like Team Jong Kook, will Team Ji Hyo's answer be correct?)
The answer is Mongolia.
(The answer is Mongolia.)
(Seok Jin has done it again.)
How can the lamb be from Mongolia?
It has to come from New Zealand. Go to the supermarket.
- It's all from New Zealand. - The answer was Mongolia.
Since Team Jong Kook guessed the origin of the food correctly,
- you may take the Blue Chance Card. - Okay!
Don't read it yet.
- Don't read it yet. - Don't read it yet.
- My goodness. - Kwang Soo.
(Team Ji Hyo gets the Pink Chance Card.)
- How many are there? - There are four.
- We had a great start. - Yes, we did.
Everyone, now you can read the card inside the envelope.
- Can we read it now? - Do we each get one?
Everyone can read a card each.
- What is this? - See? Look at this.
- "Vladivostok..." - What?
(What is this now?)
- Hold on. We're going there? - Hey.
(The identity of the Chance Cards was...)
(flight tickets.)
What on earth is this?
- Lately, you've been... - Let me tell you...
- Wait. - what this race is about.
The food you enjoyed just now...
is the Dangerous Meal.
Each team will travel to the origin of the food...
(They will set off for the country.)
You must find the ingredients in that country and come back.
- Excuse me. Hold on. - We are going to Russia?
(Go where? What is he saying?)
He must be out of his mind.
We are going to Ulaanbaatar in Mongolia?
Since Team Ji Hyo enjoyed a meal from Mongolia,
you will go to Mongolia, meet nomads,
milk the sheep personally, and bring the milk back.
(You want us to meet nomads and milk the sheep?)
Since we ate lamb, we have to go to Mongolia?
We have to go to Mongolia, meet nomads, and milk the sheep?
Since Team Jong Kook had a Russian meal,
- What is this? - go to Russia,
visit the Sea of Okhotsk, and catch king crabs.
- Sea of Okhotsk? - Sea of Okhotsk?
- Did you say Sea of Okhotsk? - You must catch king crabs.
(They are completely bewildered. They can't believe it.)
You mean the Sea of Okhotsk that I learned about in school?
- The Sea of Okhotsk? - You must be out of your senses.
What have we done wrong?
- Our mission is better than theirs. - How will they catch them?
I saw how they catch king crabs in a documentary. I saw people dying.
- A couple of people really died. - Were you aware of this?
At first, there were 10 people on the ship and when they were...
at the sea, all of a sudden, there were only eight.
(Let us reveal the documentary Jong Kook watched.)
(It only looks tough.)
(In reality, it is quite a safe job.)
- We have to get on that ship. - We must go to Japan after this.
Exactly.
We have to get the punishment.
But we figured out where the food came from.
- There's a benefit for that, right? - Do we get something for that?
Hold on. What do we get for our correct answer?
There isn't a benefit. They just received the envelopes first.
- No way. - Come on. Seriously?
- Hey. - There must be something.
I should have said Chile.
- I can't believe this. - Really?
This is driving me crazy.
- Jae Seok, are we really going? - We are really going there.
I guess so.
Since we are catching king crabs, shouldn't they catch the sheep too?
- Why would we do that? - You should.
- Why would we catch them? - Then we will milk the king crabs.
(That is only fair.)
- That's right. - Hey, how can we milk them?
- If we try, it might be possible. - There must be something.
Seriously.
(Moments later, at the land of Genghis Khan,)
(the members have arrived.)
(They went with the sole purpose of sheep milk.)
In my opinion, this isn't the right ship.
(Catch king crabs with methods you have never heard or seen)
(Their journeys will air soon.)
We will begin Dangerous Quiz, and a Chance Card is at stake.
We must decide the order you will solve the quizzes.
We will play Be Irrelevant which is the official game of our show.
All right.
- I don't know about this. - I am so bad at this.
I don't even like the name of the game.
- The game is named after Seok Jin. - Right.
The game should have been famous long before.
This game isn't popular because it's named after him.
- I see. - What? Hey.
- This is actually a fun game. - Should we name it after you then?
- My friends are crazy for the game. - Right.
- Since the name isn't appealing... - Exactly.
- Why are you being mean too? - You have a valid point.
- Hey. - It's true.
Did I come up with the name?
(He feels this isn't fair.)
It's true. Seok Jin wasn't involved in the naming process.
- Don't call it after me then! - If you...
- Seok Jin didn't say anything! - Stop it then!
- Did I name the game? - In the history of his career,
this was the first time something was named after him.
(He bragged to his friends.)
It's a small segment of the show,
- but this is the first time. - Did I name the game?
- I've never done it... - All right.
- Let's start Be Irrelevant. - in my entire career.
Which team would like to go first?
- You should go first. - We got the correct answer.
- Haha, you should start. - We will let them start first.
- Why? - Team Jong Kook will go first.
- We got the correct answer. - We guessed the right answer.
Let them make a fool out of themselves first.
Fine. I will do an acrostic poem with Russia.
Team Russia is starting.
Did you get that?
Gosh, that was so annoying.
- Who's up? - Jong Kook. We'll start.
- Get ready. - Okay.
Start. What do you have in your refrigerator?
A person.
- Jong Kook, wait. - Hey, you!
- You are scary. - He's a scary guy.
(We thought you took out chicken breast from your refrigerator.)
(There must be other things along with chicken breast.)
(Strangely, it makes sense.)
- This is... - Please keep it a secret!
- Let's arrest him. - Viewers, don't report him!
He has to be arrested.
- No. - The person isn't dead.
- Arrest him! - I can swear on my life.
- That's what you said. - I was going to say something else.
But I said, "person". I didn't mean it.
- I really... - Let's do it again. This won't air.
- Don't kid yourself. - No.
- I saw the body. - Let's do it again.
- I don't think it's his first time. - Stop it.
Gosh.
- All right. It's our turn. - Ji Hyo, we'll start.
Okay.
Get ready.
Start. What do you want to eat right now the most?
ABC.
What do you want to eat right now the most?
(She's confident.)
- Hey! It's a chocolate brand! - It's a brand!
(She's flustered. That's not what she meant.)
- That's the name of the chocolate. - Hey, that's chocolate.
- It's the name of the chocolate. - How can you eat the letters?
We can't mention brands on air!
- So I avoided company names. - Fine.
- Fine. - You can't think in advance.
(Ji Hyo fails.)
- So... - Both teams failed.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors. We have no choice now.
- Pretend you are playing... - That was all for nothing then.
This is intense.
- You can do it! - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They came up with the order easily with this game.)
- Okay. - You can go first.
- You never lose this game. - You are so good.
Before you set out to the country,
the Biggest Chance Card is at stake.
(The Biggest Chance Card?)
We will start Dangerous Quiz.
(They may earn a Chance Card.)
Okay. The Biggest Chance Card!
The quiz is presented by the natives of Mongolia and Russia.
Get the right answer for the quiz meant for corresponding teams.
I think this is going to be hard.
When the team comes up with a wrong answer...
- Then? -Yes?
The opposing team will use the tool set aside for the question...
and punish the other team.
It will happen right now?
The team that answers more questions...
will get the Chance Card which will be...
- advantageous during the mission. - Okay. I got it.
(The team that answers more questions will get the Chance Card.)
(The Chance Card was a decisive factor in the last mission.)
(The Chance Card managed to drag Team Osaka from its victory.)
(Which team will take the Chance Card this time?)
- I will get this one right. - First, let me introduce...
Aengkeubayaseu Gallang...
and Ilya Belyakov who will present the questions.
- Hello. - Goodness.
- They're here. - He's from Russia.
Isn't he from "Non-Summit"?
- Goodness. Hi. - Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
(They're Isijanchan Aengkeubayaseu Gallang and Ilya Belyakov.)
All right. Please bring in the multiple choices.
- What are these? - Gosh.
- We'll be all right. - Are those stockings?
"Draw a hotel on my face."
"Draw a hotel on my face"?
Team Ji Hyo.
All right. We can do this.
Which of the following means "Where is the hotel" in Mongolian?
- Okay. - Yes.
Number one.
(Which of the following means "Where is the hotel" in Mongolian?)
(Well, I don't know this at all.)
Number two.
(Which of the following means "Where is the hotel" in Mongolian?)
- Does it mean we should lie down? - What?
Number three.
(Which of the following means "Where is the hotel" in Mongolian?)
- Bed! - She said, "bed".
Number four.
(Which of the following means "Where is the hotel" in Mongolian?)
- Two of them said, "lie down". - There were two of them.
- It has to be one of those. - There were two choices.
(This was the second one.)
(This was the fourth one.)
(Hotel means a place we lie down. That's the answer!)
- Don't you think so? - Aren't we right?
- There were two choices for that. - Mongolia and Korea are similar.
- We have Mongolian spots. - That's not relevant at all!
- Did you seriously say that? - We do.
My brother has a Mongolian spot too.
Since we heard, "lie down", that has to be the answer.
Let me explain this in a historical context.
Our culture doesn't use beds.
- That's right. - We lie down on the floor.
I've heard it from somewhere.
- When she said, "lie down", - She said, "lie down".
- it's derived from our culture. - Can you elaborate on your claim?
Even our elders say, "Hey, lie down."
(Listen to me. Doesn't it sound exactly the same?)
But you spoke with a heavy dialect from the Gyeongsang Province.
- "Lie down." - The residents are from Mongolia.
- That's right. - Is that so?
It's between number 2 or 4.
I think it's number three.
- What? - So Min, what do you think?
I think number two. The one with "lie down" is the answer.
- That was number two, right? - Yes.
- Number 2? - But number 4 could be it too.
- Number 2 sounded more precise. - It's between number 2 or 4.
Number two? That's great.
- Let's get ready. - The answer you chose...
- The answer is number 3. - It's number 2.
(If they're wrong, they'll be penalized according to the option.)
Number two.
(They heard "lie down" in number 2.)
(Is their choice as logical as they think it is?)
"Put clothespins on my face."
We're ready.
- It was number three, right? - Yes.
I knew it.
What do you mean "lie down"?
What were you talking about?
(We clearly heard it.)
- Do they say "bed"? - I knew it was three.
Whom should I go for?
- Each attacks one. - Okay.
Here we go.
(Seok Jin gets a nose ring.)
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
It hurts.
- What should I do? - I'll pick another place.
Gosh.
(This looks familiar.)
(Do you remember this?)
(Having clothespins on your eyelids hurts every time.)
Jae Seok, lie down.
- Lie down. - Lie down.
(At Hotel Running Man, they even close your eyes.)
(All this started from one sentence.)
(Number 3 was the correct answer.)
It hurts so much.
It's Team Russia's turn now.
Again?
- Please get ready. - Get ready.
- It hurts so much. - Right?
"Help me" in Russian.
- "Help me?" - "Help me?"
- "SOS"? - How do you say it?
One.
(Pondering)
Two.
(Confused)
Three.
Four.
I have no idea.
It's so difficult.
Kwang Soo, Se Chan, you don't have to listen, do you?
(You don't have to listen, do you?)
What?
- Can't we listen one more time? - The thing is,
Jong Kook likes it when we look like we're thinking.
- I am thinking. - He likes it when we do.
- This is so difficult. - We should pretend.
They don't even have to listen.
- Let's go for number two. - Should we?
- Let's do it. - Okay.
- He listened to me. - I was thinking the same.
Jong Kook listened to you guys for the first time in a long time.
If it turns out to be wrong, he'll blame us.
- Exactly. - Let's go.
The penalty can't be that bad. One, two, three.
- 2. - 2!
Number two means...
(It sounds so unfamiliar.)
(Was Kwang Soo's hunch right?)
"Please pull my sideburns."
(It means "please pull my sideburns.")
The correct answer is number three, right?
Yes.
(Why did I trust Kwang Soo?)
(It means "please pull my sideburns.")
"Pull my sideburns."
Start from Kwang Soo.
Go.
Harder.
Hey, hold on.
- Stop. - It hurts, right?
(It's fun. Let me go on.)
Go on.
(Extreme pain)
(You're crazy.)
So Min, good job.
(Seok Jin pulls Jong Kook's sideburns.)
- Hold on, what are you doing? - What?
My sideburns... Can he do this?
You look like a Chinese doll.
(Jong Kook in pigtails)
- Come on. - You look so cute.
You look so cute.
You look like a Chinese doll.
- I don't get to do this often. - What is this?
Are they my sideburns?
(Seok Jin groans while pulling Jong Kook's hair.)
Seok Jin, what are you doing?
He's afraid he'll be counter-attacked.
He's not doing it properly.
His hands don't go up.
- What are you doing? - They don't move.
What did you do?
They're not my sideburns.
He just pretended.
Pull my sideburns.
I'll pretend I'm pulling it. You pretend it hurts.
(He whispers his plan to Jong Kook.)
- What is this? - This is not okay.
- Come on. - Did you hear that?
(Please pretend it hurts.)
He said, "Pretend it hurts."
- Come on. - Just pull my sideburns.
You just need to play along.
You can pull this.
Just play along.
It's more fun that way.
Ask someone else to do it. I'll do it for you.
- Why would you? - I'll just get it done.
Why would you?
My sideburns...
(Determined)
Good job. That's great.
I just wanted to get it done.
- It's done now. - Great.
I just wanted to get it over with.
- Good job. - I just wanted to get it done.
- That's why. - Gosh, this is...
Jong Kook is angry.
Thank you for helping me decide.
- Kwang Soo will be sent to Japan. - Japan.
Exchange some money to Japanese yen beforehand.
Get a Japanese conversation book.
(I have no regrets.)
It already starts to hurt.
- Get a conversation book. - It already hurts.
(Screaming)
It's not that bad.
(It's not that bad.)
Do it one more time.
Gosh.
- Do it one more time. - I mean...
- Gosh. - I mean...
He followed my hands.
I couldn't pull his hair.
What were you doing?
(Was it funny?)
Good job.
Okay.
It counts.
(The correct answer was number three.)
It's our turn now.
Let's do this.
Give us some hints.
No, you shouldn't.
The prize is the Biggest Chance Card.
It's the last question.
(Who will win the Card?)
It's the same question.
One.
(How do you say, "Help me", in Mongolian?)
- It's not this one. - Two.
It's not this one either.
Three.
Please help me.
Four.
(Is it, "Help me?")
- Number one sounded like, - Hold on.
- "Will you help me?" - What?
Number one sounded like, "Will you help me?"
It sounded like, "Will you help me?"
She said, "Will you help me?"
(It sounded just like Korean.)
(This was number one.)
(She said, "Will you help me?")
"Will you help me?"
- She has a different perspective. - I think it's number one too.
- You too? - Yes.
- Seok Jin, what about you? - Number two.
I'll go with Ji Hyo and So Min.
One, two, three.
- 1! - 2!
- I think it's two. - What is it?
You said different answers.
- It's 1. - It's 1.
Please set up a partition here.
Please divide us.
- He's not on our team. - I'm on my own.
- We need a partition. - I'm on my own.
Number one.
Let me announce the correct answer.
You chose number one.
(They chose number one.)
(So Min thinks she heard, "Will you help me?")
(Ji Hyo has a hunch that it's number one.)
(Are they right?)
It means,
"Please help me."
See?
- Ji Hyo. - See?
- See? - What about number two?
- It means, "Pinch my thighs." - "Will you help me?"
Number one sounded a bit peculiar.
It could have been bad.
How did you know?
I thought it was number four.
Team Ji Hyo wins.
(Team Ji Hyo wins Dangerous Quiz.)
(How are we going to catch king crabs?)
I knew it.
Good job.
(Team Ji Hyo wins the Card.)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan)
(6 members are being sent on the Dangerous Trip.)
(But 2 of them get a chance to be excluded.)
(What's the secret behind the Chance Card?)
Please have photos taken for the visa before you go home.
My hair looks like this.
- What about me? - For the passport?
(He might be denied entry.)
(He even became an ambassador for the police.)
Is this a mission?
Will they let me enter the country?
(His hair looks neater than before.)
Like this?
I can't see your ears.
(Neat)
Like this?
(More like this.)
(His hair looks neat now.)
Team Mongolia, see you next week.
(All photos have been taken.)
(A few days later)
(The night before departure)
Hello, I'm Se Chan.
We're leaving for Russia tomorrow.
To be honest,
I'm very excited.
I'm looking forward to our trip.
I don't think they'll be too strict about our mission.
I'm not sure what I should pack.
Se Hyung.
Se Hyung, I'm going to Russia.
You've been there.
(Se Hyung appears, looking natural.)
What should I pack?
- What? - What should I pack?
(Se Hyung is familiar with Russia.)
- Is it an overnight trip? - Yes.
Just go.
I don't have to bring anything?
- What? - Isn't it cold there?
Will I need my winter jacket?
(Are you filming?)
(How does my bare face look?)
Do I need my winter jacket or not?
Warm underclothes,
- gloves, - Gloves.
- and thick socks. - Gloves?
Bring them.
(Gloves in the summer?)
(His gloves become his lifesaver later.)
(Heating pads)
What are they?
Are they heating pads?
(Thank you, Se Chan.)
Heating pads.
- That'll do. - Okay.
If it's cold, get some more there.
All right.
What time is it?
(It's already 12:30am.)
(There's another person who is packing.)
Is it working?
Gosh.
I can see myself.
(You can only see her eyes and forehead.)
How do I do it? Wait.
I have to pack my things.
I'm not sure what to pack.
(She packs a thick jacket in case it gets cold at night.)
I packed some cup noodles.
I also packed really delicious dried laver...
and nurungji.
These are eye masks for sleeping.
(She packs cup noodles, nurungji, cute eye masks,)
(facial masks to share with Ji Hyo, bug repellent,)
(and heat packs.)
I heard that there are no bathrooms...
where we'll be.
We have to go somewhere in the grassland.
(She feels embarrassed.)
There is no separate bathroom.
In case I can't wash my face,
I packed wet tissues.
I bought them.
I heard the children in Mongolia love hairpins.
I went to Jeonju recently.
They were selling heart and dragonfly-shaped hairpins.
I bought some.
It's a heart-shaped one.
(She has a heart-shaped one.)
It's a dragonfly.
(She also has a dragonfly-shaped one.)
(She plans to bring them.)
Can you see it?
Hairpin?
She's so cute.
(She gives a big present to a child in the grassland.)
Is the suitcase too big for the amount?
(It's big enough to fit a person.)
Is it too big?
(An ordinary suitcase would've been fine.)
It's better to take a big suitcase.
I feel excited.
What I'm excited about the most...
is the beautiful, night sky in Mongolia.
(So Min is excited...)
(about the beautiful, night sky in Mongolia.)
(She watches the shooting stars with other members.)
(They spend time together under the Great Bear.)
See you in Mongolia.
Goodnight.
(Their trip to Russia and Mongolia is coming up next.)
(On the day of their departure at Incheon International Airport)
I thought about this last night while packing.
"Why do I need to go to Mongolia?"
What's the purpose?
If you clear the mission successfully,
two members whom Ji Hyo selects...
- That's right. - will be exempted.
That's my only hope.
Honestly.
Here comes Seok Jin.
I'm going to Mongolia.
To Ulaanbaatar.
The weather is beautiful.
Seok Jin.
You're necessary for the trip.
Hello, Jae Seok.
Why are you wearing makeup?
- Are you not? - Of course not.
You should feel free when you travel.
That's not proper for the camera.
What?
That's a big suitcase for a two-night trip.
(It's because...)
(I'm precious.)
Did you bring a long jacket?
Why would I?
I heard it's cold.
- What's wrong with him? - I heard it's freezing.
I heard it's freezing.
The temperature falls below zero at night.
What's going on?
(The leader comes with a backpack.)
- Why did you bring a suitcase? - Here's the team leader.
Hello, Team Leader.
You didn't bring anything.
What do you mean? Everything is in here.
The trip is only for two nights.
What did you pack?
- Ji Hyo. - Did you pack kimchi?
Did you bring kimchi?
There's no suitcase like that.
I didn't know what I would need.
- Jae Seok, what's this? - Jae Seok.
- It looks so tacky. - I might lose my suitcase.
- It's really tacky. - There are many suitcases like it.
- Goodness. - It's tacky.
- I don't want to lose my suitcase. - Is that why?
- Let it go. - Write your name on it.
- Seok Jin. - Do you have a marker?
A suitcase like yours...
- will be okay. - Yours is tacky too.
- What's this green thing? - Look at that.
(A bigger suitcase approaches.)
Did I pack too much?
I should hurry.
Hello.
Hello, So Min.
(What is that?)
(It's a huge suitcase.)
- Hello. - So Min.
- Hello. - What's that?
Did you pack a person inside?
Are you moving abroad?
- She's moving. - Are you opening up a business?
Mine is for three days.
His is for five days to a week.
Yours is for over 15 days.
Mine is enough to stay in Mongolia for a month.
- Look at Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
She will come back after dropping us off.
- After she drops us off, - Is she a tour guide?
- Ji Hyo will... - Is she a tour guide?
- Did you call me a tour guide? - Yes.
I'm the team leader.
- I'm sorry. - I have No Tour Cards.
Ji Hyo made her decision.
I already decided.
Ji Hyo, put your backpack in here.
No, it's okay.
(Will Team Ji Hyo clear the mission without trouble?)
(Team Jong Kook must catch king crab.)
- You're coming too. - Right.
I didn't know I'd go to Russia.
- You're going to Russia. - I know.
(They're going to Russia but...)
Are you going there with shorts?
- It's for the flight. - It's cold there.
I wanted to be comfortable during the flight.
- Really? - Yes.
I thought...
Since you're obsessed with wearing shorts...
I thought you were wearing them for Russia.
I like to wear shorts,
but I want to see how cold it is.
- Will you be okay? - I want to see how cold it is.
- Someone is coming. - What's that?
- Is it Kwang Soo? - He has a strange hairdo.
Hello, Haha.
- Hello. - Hello.
If you wear shorts, you'll die there.
(His shorts are hard to miss.)
I told him already.
It's raining and snowing over there.
- For now, - No, you'll freeze.
I'll keep them on.
- He loves shorts so much. - I'll see.
- He doesn't like being stylish. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello, Kwang Soo.
I looked up some information about Russia.
There's a place we must go.
- Where? - We must go to a maritime park.
Will you be our tour guide?
- Yes, I will. - That suits you well.
(He speaks Russian.)
(The tour starts with learning the language.)
- Do you know what it means? - Yes.
What does it mean?
- Hello. - Excuse me.
It means hello.
(It means hello in Russian.)
- Thank you. - Okay.
(What did you say?)
- It means... - Listen.
Don't say that to us.
- Okay. - He's prepared.
Say it only to Russians.
Don't say that to us. We may misunderstand.
- Thank you. - He's prepared.
Let's go to the maritime park.
Then let's figure out the rest.
- How? - We have to ask them...
- where we can find crab. - Do we have to ask?
- Who else would ask? - You should prepare beforehand.
- Ask me the question. - Pardon me?
- Ask me. - Ask where we can find crab.
(Here's another phrase.)
What did he say?
What does that mean?
(What did he say in Russian?)
"Please help me."
What does it mean?
I only know that.
We must know this phrase.
We must remember this phrase.
- Se Chan. - What is it?
(Do not forget this word.)
If we fall in the water while catching crab,
say, "Please help me!"
We must say that.
We'll say thank you when we fall in the water.
(Thank you.)
What do we have to do once we arrive?
- We'll go to the maritime park. - The maritime park?
They sell seafood.
Our mission is...
to find king crab, right?
Why don't you look at Jong Kook?
You keep...
- avoiding my eyes. - He doesn't look at him.
He's scary.
Do you want to go to Japan?
- No way. - Don't do that.
- You should look at me. - I'm very sorry.
He responded to us when Jong Kook asked.
Didn't you learn...
to look at the adults when answering?
- I should look. - Right?
It's because your eyes are small.
(It's because...)
(your eyes...)
(are small.)
I'm really sorry, Jong Kook.
(Se Chan upsets him.)
I haven't heard it in a while.
- It's been a long time. - I made a mistake.
(Se Chan is out of the picture.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Are we really going to Russia? - To Russia.
Let's go to Russia.
(How will their trip turn out?)
You had mutton last week. Now, you're going to Mongolia.
I'm so excited.
If you meet a nomad and milk their sheep,
you'll clear the mission.
If you clear the mission while the other team fails,
two members will be exempted from the Dangerous Tour.
Is this notepad for me?
It's a type of blacklist.
(Once your name is written on it,)
(you'll be in trouble.)
It's a blacklist.
I'll take a peek later.
- You will? - Goodness.
Write So Min's name.
Write her name down.
- I know you will. - I'll deduct half from So Min.
- Write her name down. - I'll deduct half a point.
Your thoughts...
make us speechless.
She's always deceitful.
You're dumb and out of it.
- "Dumb and out of it"? - You're like sisters.
- What do you mean? - You're out of it, and she's dumb.
Goodness.
- They're like a team. - Dumb and out of it.
(Ji Hyo becomes aggressive again...)
(and blames the clueless So Min.)
(When So Min makes silly comments,)
(Ji Hyo explodes in anger.)
(So Min who's happy-go-lucky...)
(makes Ji Hyo lose her temper.)
(Banging)
(Are you okay, So Min?)
(They take care of each other at times.)
What should we do with them?
Let's go and get your plane tickets.
There's always someone who didn't bring their passport.
Come here, So Min.
(Team Ji Hyo and Team Jong Kook...)
(enter the airport.)
- We're really going. - This is the airport.
I can't believe it.
- Where should we go? - We leave once we enter the gate.
We leave once we enter the gate.
(They're really going to Russia.)
I'm so happy that I'm going to Mongolia.
It's my first time.
Hey, Ji Hyo. Ma'am.
- Yes? - Will you cross out if we do well?
- Sure. - Okay.
Just buy a flight ticket to Japan while you're here.
I can't go there. You can't send me there.
Did you see the blog?
Did you see what's written about that mysterious case in that blog?
(Do you mean the Labyrinth of Fear?)
- Mysterious case? - It's the Labyrinth of Fear.
You understood, so it's fine.
It's strange we understood you.
- Right? - Yes.
- You get it all. - Even if you say it wrong...
It's the same when it comes to you.
(Don't say it like you're not the case.)
Do you think you say things clearly?
It's hard understanding her point.
- Ms. Chun Soo Yeon. - I have no bags.
- You don't? - No.
Who is Chun Soo Yeon?
Your real name is Chun Soo Yeon?
- That's my real name. - It's not Chun Sung Im?
I guess you changed your name to Soo Yeon.
Yes, I changed it since too many people recognized it.
I see.
Jae Seok was blabbering my name to everyone.
He kept on calling me Sung Im.
That's funny.
- It was Chun Sung Im. - I wondered who Soo Yeon was.
I was surprised too.
Your name sounds very modest.
Okay, so you be quiet.
- I don't want to change it again. - Soo Yeon.
Write this on your note.
You look like an informant or something.
- Why? - You have so many names.
Chun Sung Im, Chun Soo Yeon, and Song Ji Hyo.
Should I write it down? Jae Seok?
- Well... - This is worth writing.
Jee...
Why me?
(But I'm loyal to you!)
- I wrote your name four times now. - Seriously?
- You should write his name instead. - That was strange.
Don't touch my note.
Chun Soo Yeon was hilarious.
- I wondered who that was. - He says it's hilarious.
Don't you feel a little...
(Don't you think his remark is a little...)
It was nice, right?
I was just asking. Okay.
- Did you just see? - What?
(He didn't want to upset the team leader.)
- Okay. - That was a nice try.
- That was funny. - Why...
I almost cried.
(Staggering)
Stay focused, will you?
You almost became luggage.
Thank you.
(They excitedly depart to Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia.)
- Let's go! - Let's go.
(How far have you been to explore the world?)
(Getting along so well)
(The female members are busy with their chitchat.)
(The middle-aged men are very different.)
(While they're crossing the wide desert,)
(Jong Kook's lackeys are busy trying to survive.)
(Scuttling)
- Is it not uncomfortable? - It's okay.
(Have this.)
- Thank you in advance. - All right.
(That young punk!)
(It's me, your right arm, Kwang Soo.)
(Hurting)
(Unpleasant)
(Kwang Soo, you're out.)
What?
Did you just tell me to get lost?
Have a great rest.
- I'll visit you later. - I love peanuts.
- Thank you. - No problem.
He doesn't eat food that has sugar on top.
- He doesn't eat sugar. - I was just taking care of him.
(It's my careful heart to you.)
- I'll see you later. - Bye.
You're annoying.
(He's opening the peanut bag after losing to Se Chan.)
(Is his plan to serve Jong Kook the peanuts?)
(Not a chance)
(I'm Lee Kwang Soo, and I like peanuts very much.)
(He's eating like Ha Jung Woo.)
(Did you enjoy the peanuts?)
(Laughing)
(You're dying to visit the Labyrinth, aren't you?)
Why did you eat my peanuts?
- Sorry. - Why did you steal them?
(They almost flew back to Korea before even arriving.)
(30 minutes after the peanut incident)
(They have successfully landed on Vladivostok, Russia.)
(They arrive at the Vladivostok International Airport at 1pm.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Hello, Russia.)
Nice.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Hello, Running Man!)
(People are gathering because of the members.)
- I'm so thankful. - Guys, come here.
- The weather is so nice. - Running Man!
(People are gathered at Chinggis Khaan International Airport too.)
(They're surprised to see people welcome them.)
They're here to welcome us.
(Welcome, Running Man!)
My goodness. Hello!
Ji Hyo!
Sorry. We're passing through.
(They're careful.)
Look this way, please!
This way!
- Excuse me. - Love you!
(They decided not to shoot at the airport due to everyone's safety.)
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
- The luggage first. - Yes, the luggage.
Thank you.
Where is Seok Jin?
(He's apart from the members, outside the guard.)
You all know the reason why we're here, right?
- Yes. - We do.
- We came to milk sheep. - That's one,
but we came to be exempted from the penalty.
- Right. - To be chosen by Ji Hyo.
- Again? - My gosh!
- Gosh. - What is this again?
- Do we throw a shoe again? - This is driving me crazy.
It won't go as we want because it's so windy today.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
(Are they doing the shoe throw again?)
Here's your mission.
Like we told you, you must catch king crab.
Along with it, you have to throw a shoe on the mission board...
- that has 9 missions on it... - 9 missions?
and clear the mission you picked.
- It's the Shoe Throw. - That.
(Shoe Throw)
- I remember this. - We did this before.
- I remember it too. - I did it in Jeju Island.
- But the missions are different. - It's tough.
(They reveal the upgraded mission board.)
- You can't catch that. - "1m-long king crab"?
- Does it even exist? - It'll be as big as that board.
It'll be about this size.
It'll be same as that picture.
What about pollack?
We have to catch a pollack as well as a king crab...
if we throw a shoe in that box.
"10 kinds of fish"?
That means we have to catch a dolphin too.
Whatever the mission will be, it won't be easy.
What are they?
"Find a nomad who raises more than 100 sheep and milk one of them."
This doesn't make sense. "Eyesight..."
We'll never be able to find a nomad with such good eyesight.
How will we find the descendants of Genghis Khan?
Is that even possible?
(They're worried about today's mission.)
- Goodness. - Look at the blue sky by the way.
Ji Hyo. Look over there.
Look at the sky.
This is just amazing.
I didn't know Mongolia was...
- this beautiful. - Look at the mountains.
How did you feel as soon as you arrived in Mongolia?
I happen to run.
(I just have to run like this.)
- Gosh. - She's strange.
- I told you. - Don't you agree?
It's that you want to run and enjoy the field.
Weren't you surprised in the plane?
I was.
- It's flatland. - There were no cities.
(They were impressed by the vast flatland.)
She said we were crossing a desert, and it continued for 10 minutes.
- Right. - The trees were scraggly...
like Seok Jin's hair.
(She only tried to explain the greatness of it.)
Come over here. You really...
- What did you say? - So Min.
(So Min still attacks Seok Jin even in Mongolia.)
- My gosh. - That was a wrong comparison.
Do you have any idea?
(Meanwhile, in Russia)
Catching 10 kinds of fish will be more difficult.
If you use a net,
you'll catch many kinds of fish.
Just catching 1m king crab would be better.
- Does it even exist? - No way.
You can never catch it.
This is the easiest.
- You think everything's so easy. - Catching a pollack.
- I mean... - Now, I know...
that you're the type he hates the most.
- Gosh. - I know you're trying...
- to alienate us. - It's not true.
Sorry, I was too thoughtless.
How it turns out doesn't really matter to me, you see.
That's my point.
But you're leading us for our sake now.
- Thanks so much. - He's so considerate.
I'll throw my shoe then.
- Okay. - Just avoid throwing here.
- Not this. - Not the 1m king crab one.
- You know me. - Okay.
- You know I'm good at this. - Pick the first one.
What's in season?
Pollacks are in season.
Is that right?
Then let's aim for the pollack mission.
All right. I knew it'd be in season.
Challenge.
(Jong Kook is ready.)
(With his lackeys' desperate wishes,)
(he throws his shoe to the mission board!)
(Their only hope is to catch pollack in season.)
(The other missions look impossible.)
Please!
(It lands on "Catching a king crab and 10 kinds of fish".)
- Wait. - Let's do this again.
It'll not be fun at all.
"Catching a king crab and 10 kinds of fish".
Well...
He didn't shout, "Challenge!"
He did, but we didn't.
That doesn't count.
- We had to do it all together. - One of us should throw.
We should say "Challenge" all together.
I should be the one shouting it.
No, we should do it together.
He's right.
Just do it. Catch 10 kinds of fish.
I'm not doing it, so you do it.
He would've scolded so much if someone else picked this.
- My gosh. - I didn't say a word.
- What did you say? - Kwang Soo crossed the line.
- I didn't say anything. - I was joking.
- I was just saying. - He's hurt now.
- I'm hurt. - You're out.
- Are you okay? - It was a joke.
- We'll be able to make up for it. - Yes, I'll work hard.
- You know what Kwang Soo said? - What?
If he's going to win anyway,
he'd rather lose all the missions so that the three of us can go.
Thank you.
He means "Thank you."
- He means "Thank you." - He means "Thank you."
- Thank you. - He means "Thank you."
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you, Haha.
(They never got to say how thankful they were to each other.)
So which one's the best?
"Find a nomad..."
Isn't it faster to find a nomad who has over 100 sheep?
- I don't know which one's better. - Seok Jin.
Let's just give it a try.
- Challenge. - So Min.
(So Min gives it a try.)
(She didn't have any luck in Japan.)
(So Min is not good in the shoe throw.)
- Challenge. - So Min.
Aim for the right corner because...
Descendants of Genghis Khan is better.
- When I did it last time... - Just go for it.
You won't get a penalty anyways.
(She doesn't hesitate and kicks her shoe.)
She did it.
(What did we expect?)
- Here we go again. - How far are you kicking it?
You won't get a penalty anyways.
(So Min never fails to impress.)
- Here we go. - Look at her.
This much is good.
Aim for the center.
- Challenge. - Challenge.
(Dropping)
Oh, gosh.
You're such high maintenance.
Challenge.
(That's enough fun for now. She'll do it right this time.)
(What will the mission be in Mongolia?)
(Descendants of Genghis Khan, milk a sheep with the nomads)
I don't know if we should be happy about this.
She said she wanted to do this.
So you must find Borjigit Tribe...
- where Genghis Khan belonged to. - Borjigit Tribe?
I guess that's the name of the tribe.
They're 20 percent of the Mongolian population.
What's that like for us?
- They're 20 percent of population? - That's Kim or Park.
20 percent is not that much.
- It's not? - It's kind of like Jeon.
I think there may be more of Song.
My last name is Chun.
(Right, your last name is Chun.)
Are you a secret agent?
- My last name is Chun. - Hey,
your passport says you're Soo Yeon,
and you say your last name is Chun when I thought you were Song Ji Hyo.
- My last name is Chun. - What's wrong with you?
Chun is my last name.
Look at you. I don't know what the truth is with you.
Hey, this is good. Descendants of Genghis Khan.
- Right. - We'll have to milk a sheep anyhow.
Have you milked a sheep before?
- Don't you just pull on them? - But...
Is this how you do it?
- I haven't done it before. - Only the females milk, right?
(Only the females milk, right?)
- What did you say? - Why would rams milk?
- Only ewes milk, right? - Of course.
I had to think about that for a second.
Don't all sheep have udders?
- Don't they? - No.
All cattles have udders. Even bulls have them.
- Only cows milk though. - Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
And...
- I was thinking about cattles. - Stop being ignorant.
They all have udders.
- That's why they're cattles. - When you go to a farm,
they only bring out cows that milk.
- Don't all females and males... - That's not why.
- have udders? - Bulls don't milk.
They don't milk.
They don't, right? They might still have udders.
Hey, why would you mention this? Stop it.
(Stop talking nonsense.)
Excuse me,
- Ms. Chun Soo Yeon. - Do it.
She has three personalities in her.
There are Chun Sung Im, Song Ji Hyo, and Chun Soo Yeon.
- Stop it. - She has three identities.
- Ms. Chun Soo Yeon. - My goodness.
- She's not being herself. - Why did you mention it?
- Don't say anything. - You know what?
So Min is not intimidated by us...
but she's intimidated by Ji Hyo.
She's intimidated by Ji Hyo but not me.
- She's intimidated by Ji Hyo. - I mean...
- All cattles, females or males, - They all have it.
- all have udders, - They do.
but bulls don't milk, right?
- Of course now. Do you milk? - But still...
(That's a very clever answer.)
- This is driving me nuts. - You don't milk, right?
They have udders to balance themselves.
Stop it.
We just got here and...
My father has disproportionate nipples so what does that mean?
Stop it.
What are you saying?
- Of course, he has nipples. - So it might be the other way.
- They still don't milk? - They have udders.
(This argument has to be over.)
- They don't milk, right? - Of course.
- You squeeze their udders, - We finished this discussion.
- Hey! Stop it! - Why are you still talking?
- That's Ms. Chun Soo Yeon. - It's Chun Soo Yeon.
- They all have udders! - Ms. Chun Soo Yeon.
(She's relieved now.)
- Don't. - They all have udders.
- We are... - They all have udders!
We are talking about...
- udders too much in Mongolia. - Don't be angry.
- They all have udders, Jae Seok. - We talked a lot about it. Sorry.
- Your mission... - Yes.
is to catch king crab and 10 kinds of fish.
Team Ji Hyo's mission is to find a nomad who are descendants...
- of Genghis Khan and milk a sheep. - It's Chun Sung Im.
Each member has to collect 1L...
- to a total of 4L. - That's too much.
- 4L? - That's the mission.
Before you start your mission...
Before you start your mission, you will be provided money for the trip.
You will be provided money for the trip.
- That's good. - Good.
- Really? - It's a debit card.
(It's a debit card?)
You can go to the ATM...
- Do we cash it out? - It's 800 dollars...
- or around 40,000 Russian rubles. - 40,000 rubles?
For a trip of 1 night and 2 days, you get 120 dollars each.
That adds up to 480 dollars and we added 20 dollars to a total of 500.
Please cash it out and start your mission right away.
- Do we cash it out now? - Yes.
Where are we going to stay?
You must find your own lodging.
- We do? - Yes.
- We'll only provide transportation. - With 480 dollars?
You must find your own boat, captain, and lodging.
- We must find them ourselves? - You must recruit them.
So what do you guys do?
(What do the staff do?)
(We'll make great shots of you.)
What do you do?
- They film us. - Is that what they do?
- Let's go downtown. - Let's do that.
- Let's go there first. - Okay.
Let's face it first.
All right, so our team...
Captain Song's team...
- Chun Soo Yeon's team... - Chun Soo Yeon's team.
- will be heading to Ulaanbaatar. - Yes!
- In Mongolia, - Yes!
Excuse me. Don't say that when I haven't even finished speaking.
- Why do you sound so robotic? - Don't you know something?
We'll head to Ulaanbaatar...
Jae Seok, you've already said that. Let's go.
Because the sheep...
One for Jae Seok.
Give him like three.
- Come on. - Give him three.
- Yu... - This is tight.
But she likes me.
- She likes me better. - She really likes me.
- Ulaanbaatar! - I like So Min the best.
Let's go.
This is nice. Mongolia is nice.
(What adventure awaits this team?)
(They don't know where to go.)
Yes.
How are the prices here?
Five cents...
is around one tughrik or something.
You must have looked into it.
(During the flight)
(She wakes up and starts studying about Mongolia.)
(So Min is the expert on Mongolia.)
(She knows about their bills and the local food.)
(She knows their language...)
(and even knows the Mongolian traditional games.)
Hey.
(Trust me when it comes to Mongolia.)
(They drive across an unfamiliar scenery.)
Mongolia feels so foreign.
It's what you expected Mongolia to be.
I haven't been to a country with such clear sky.
(An endless plain extends under the clear sky.)
It's so vast.
It looks like a sheep farm.
I guess this is what we saw when we got off the plane.
I was wondering what that was.
Isn't this fascinating?
Mountains are like lawns.
There are no trees in the mountains.
There are mountains everywhere.
This is where Genghis Khan would have ridden his horses.
We don't know if it was here.
- It would have been here. - We don't know that.
I'm talking about Mongolia.
- It's a ger. - I'm talking about Mongolia.
- Look. - You're right.
- It's a ger, right? - It is.
(Ger is a portable tent that the Mongolian tribes use.)
It feels like the past and the present exist together.
Let's go downtown and exchange money first.
We should eat.
- We have to eat. - Let's eat.
- Let's have something good. - Let's eat something good.
- Let's go to a convenience store. - Sounds good.
- We need to get toothpaste. - When you come to a new country...
- You didn't bring toothpaste? - I didn't.
- You didn't bring it either, right? - Of course not.
I knew he wouldn't bring it.
I didn't like him for it so I didn't bring it either.
Hey, you...
That must be downtown.
(They're finally here.)
- I'm getting excited. - It's interesting.
It's a city between the mountains.
I bet lamb is good.
This looks like downtown.
- Look. It's big. - It looks good.
(It's Ulaanbaatar, the capital city of Mongolia.)
(Meaning "Red Hero", it's a city of politics, economy, and culture.)
- Shall we get off? - Let's get off.
This is Mongolia.
(Nice to meet you.)
- This must be a city hall. - Exactly.
(Sukhbaatar Square is in the center of Ulaanbaatar.)
It's quiet.
It looks like Sejong Center Chamber Hall.
It looks like Sejong Center Chamber Hall here.
It looks like Sejong Center Chamber Hall, right?
- He's Genghis Khan. - I see.
Here he is.
That's his son.
- That's his son? - I was going to say that.
- They usually sit in the middle. - There's one there too.
- This is his son. - So that's Genghis Khan.
That's why it's smaller.
- That one's bigger. - Yes, it's bigger.
- He's just talking random things. - I don't get anything.
Just talk about whatever you feel.
There's another statue there too.
- That must be his older son. - It's a bit bigger.
- The other one was his younger son. - It's large, medium, and small.
That's right.
This is Genghis Khan.
He's magnificent.
- He has a fine appearance. - He does.
- He's majestic. - He looks dignified.
(He was a military strategist and founder of Mongol Empire.)
He looks awesome.
Look.
It's the same as in Korea.
- Look at the cop. - I thought he was Korean.
- He's a Korean cop. - They look the same.
That looks like a Korean bus.
(The police uniform looks similar to ones in Korea.)
I don't know what it says.
- It says... - I can't read it.
Mo...
- Mo... - Isn't it a motel?
Isn't it something like that?
It looks like a motel, right?
- It's like... - Hey.
Look to the left.
Don't motels have that sauna symbol?
- That's not right. - It's not?
It doesn't look like a sauna symbol.
- It is. It's a sauna symbol. - Is it a motel?
(Mohroa Ophoo Mahavyalar?)
- It's the building for trade union. - Is that right?
It's for a trade union?
It started with "Mo" so we thought it was a motel.
It's a trade union building.
We're sorry. Excuse us.
The important thing here...
is that you guys don't know much about traveling.
- What do you mean? - Everybody,
so you're here. What time is it by the way?
- It's 7:15pm right now. - What's the time?
And it feels like broad daylight?
It's 7pm, and it's so bright.
- Aren't you guys hungry? - I am.
- Let's eat first, Captain Song. - Let's eat.
So Min,
let's withdraw cash first.
- Let's withdraw money. - Let's look for the ATM.
Let's check out...
- where we got off. There's an ATM. - I don't know if we can do it.
Babies are so cute.
They look like Korean babies.
- They look like Korean kids. - They do.
It feels like I'm in Korea.
- It fees like a relaxing afternoon. - It's the weekend.
It is the weekend.
- Isn't it so nice here? - Yes.
The air is so fresh.
Where's the ATM?
There it is. It's an ATM.
There it is.
- It says ATM. - Let's wait outside.
It says Busan Terminal.
- It's Busan Terminal. - Right.
It's Busan Terminal. It leaves from Gyeongju and Pohang.
- My gosh. - Let's go to Busan.
It leaves from Gyeongju and Pohang.
- Hi. - I'm so glad to see it.
I'm really glad to see it too.
- These are used cars. - A lot of used cars...
get exported to Mongolia.
- Here it is. Captain Song. - Yes?
Do we know how to use this?
It's all in Mongolian. What do we do?
Should we insert the card first?
How much is 20,000?
- English. - English.
- That's 1,000 dollars. - Divided by...
- Two... - Password.
It's six digits.
(They can't get past the password.)
- It's six digits. - Please...
"Please enter your..."
(They stare at the screen without doing anything.)
This...
- What's the ID? - We can't do it?
I knew we wouldn't be able to do it.
We can't eat because we don't have money.
We just got started.
- I knew it. - Look at him.
I couldn't withdraw money one time so I couldn't buy food.
- It's six digits. - We won't be able to do it.
What just happened?
- Jae Seok. - It took our card.
The card...
It took our card.
What happened?
Let me see.
I think it's an error.
- It took our card. - Wait.
It came out.
My gosh.
(That was close.)
- Give it to me. - Let go.
- That startled me. - Me too.
I was startled. I thought it took our card.
We almost had to sleep at the square.
He keeps instilling fear in me.
We can't withdraw money here.
- We can't do it. - Can't it take another bank's card?
- Wait. Give it to me. - What do you mean?
See if it says Visa on it.
It doesn't.
We have this though.
It's not Union Pay.
It's at the back.
- It should work. - Visa should work then.
(If they can't withdraw money, they'll be abandoned here.)
(They focus and try again.)
- We can't get past the password. - Password...
(He enters a password.)
Enter.
- It worked. - It worked.
Isn't it "withdraw"?
- Balance... - Go there.
Wait. "Please select your..."
(It's reading comprehension time.)
Do you understand? Excuse me, Mr. Yu.
Of course I do.
Just press anything.
(Do you even understand it?)
There's more English!
- Do we go to savings? - Checking.
Isn't it checking...
- Account? - Yes.
Why does it say, "respect"?
Seok Jin, that's not what it says.
It's "receipt".
My gosh. Did you say, "respect"?
That's what I thought it was.
What was that for?
Maybe they'll treat us nicely and respect us.
There are too many options. We just need our money.
- It worked. - Did it?
- What? - It's just a receipt.
I didn't want to check the balance.
(It prints the balance instead of withdrawing cash.)
Hold onto this.
Say yes. Don't you have to do that first?
Can we withdraw money here?
- You have to do it again. - My goodness.
- Let me try it. - Okay.
This...
- "Press if correct." - If it's correct...
Correct.
(They're not sure.)
- Press yes for everything? - Yes.
- Again? - It went back to the first page.
Move.
- Gosh, this is so annoying. - Let me see that.
I'm going to do this.
I don't know if we can do it.
My gosh. This is driving me nuts.
Okay. From checking account...
Try the checking account. We already tried savings.
This is to check your account. We have to press savings.
Don't you have to press the password?
- Wait. "Please enter..." - You have to enter something.
- I get it. - How much you want to withdraw?
Press 80,000.
- Press 8. - Ones, tens, hundreds, thousands...
Try 80,000.
- Let's try 80,000. - Try that.
There must be a limit.
- This... - It worked.
- Look. - I think it'll work.
- It's coming. - It is.
80,000 is not enough.
It's coming out!
Good job.
(It's like they won a lottery.)
It worked.
- It's coming out. - Let's see.
This is great.
- Jae Seok. - We did it.
You saw that, right?
(They're all amazed.)
Did you see that?
(He's proud of himself.)
Did you see that, Captain Song?
- Did you see the money come out? - This is no joke.
We're so happy.
Surviving in Mongolia.
This is our 1st day. 1 day.
First, withdrawing money from an ATM machine in Mongolia...
We finally did it.
- Look. - This is great.
- We did it. - We figured out the ATM.
(While Team Ji Hyo was struggling with the ATM machine,)
(Team Jong Kook is in Russia.)
Let's complete the mission today and take tomorrow off.
I think we are here.
Are we here?
It's the ATM.
(They also try to withdraw money from the ATM first.)
(How much will this team struggle?)
There's the ATM machine.
- Let's go. - There it is.
Who would have imagined we'd be strolling in Russia?
How do we withdraw money? Do you know?
- Put the card in... - Put it in first.
The first icon on the left is always withdrawal.
- Is this right? - I think so.
(It's all Russian on the screen.)
Okay.
Wouldn't it tell us to select a language? English?
(It's all Russian.)
Password.
- Red. On the right. - That's not it.
- Which one is it? - Enter.
- Enter? - Yes.
- It worked. - It worked.
- How much was it again? - How much was it?
- 4... - 40,000...
This is 10,000. Do I press this 4 times?
- Isn't this "others"? - Others.
How?
Press it.
(Kwang Soo doesn't hesitate and presses the button.)
- It's right. - 10,000?
- 4... - 40,000.
Can we add another zero?
- Is this good? - Yes. Okay?
- It worked. - It worked.
- We did it in one try. - We did.
That's unbelievable.
I guess you've done this before.
- I haven't done this before. - I have.
You look like a Russian.
- You can trust me. - Thank you.
- This is awesome. - Okay.
- We did it right away. - We're so good in this.
- We're so good. - This is good.
It's like we live here.
My mother became a victim of a spam call not long ago,
so I'm little bit sensitive over these kinds of things.
We did it really easily.
- Let's... - We're one.
have one person be in charge. You can be the secretary.
Okay, I will.
If there's money missing, you're dead.
(Terrified)
- Okay, don't worry. - If there's money missing...
You become a king crab.
Just imagine living in the sea.
- Are you serious? - Deep in the water.
Hold it. Take good care of it.
(Trembling)
Are you crying?
- Are you crying? - Sorry? No, I'm okay.
He's still here, right?
I think I'll cry soon.
Where are we off to?
- The maritime park. - Maritime park?
- Let's go. - Are you certain?
- Okay, let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go to the maritime park.
We can do everything.
(They move in perfect order under the guide of Secretary Yang.)
- We have to go downtown first. - Downtown.
- Let's eat street food there. - Let's eat Russian food.
This place is famous.
They have lamb, pork, and veal.
It's the best shashlik restaurant.
- It sounds expensive. - That won't work.
We need some street food.
How's this? It's called pelmeni.
They're Russian dumplings.
- He doesn't eat dumplings. - He doesn't?
- Se Chan. - How's tornado potato?
It's fried so he won't eat it, Se Chan.
How's kebab?
I can't eat carbohydrates.
Ice cream?
Hey!
Wait. Give him one last chance.
Then...
How's chicken breast salad?
- Let me see. - What's wrong?
- Are they known for it? - They are.
- Let me see. - Chicken breast is everywhere.
- They should have it. - Where?
- They have it. - Let me see the menu.
- Chicken breast is okay, right? - Yes.
- Let's go with that. - Sure.
I'll ask for chicken breast salad at a street food stand.
- You just have to say "Thank you." - Okay.
Is that okay?
- It's great. - Chicken breast salad.
Look to the left.
Is that where we are headed?
("Fantastic Duo 2" in a moment)
(Find Rising Diva Ailee's fantastic duo.)
(Ailee becomes excited over how skilled the contestants are.)
(In Soon I and Ailee will have their final match!)
(It will air shortly.)
Look to the left.
That's the sea, right?
- This is so pretty. - I see the sand.
- The sand. - The sand.
Usually, it's white, sandy beach,
but the beach here is surrounded with the field.
(The Northeast Sea meets the field.)
Hey, it's not cold here. This is so interesting.
(They follow the coast road...)
(and slowly get closer to the center of the city in Vladivostok.)
I think we are close to the city center.
We are in downtown now.
Now, I see some fancy buildings.
I can see big buildings now.
Look at the buildings. The buildings have been preserved from long ago.
I do feel like I'm in a foreign country.
Goodness. What is that?
(They arrive at a maritime park.)
(Couples and families visit here for the sea and cultural attractions.)
- Everyone. - Yes?
Let's get going.
(It is famous for various kinds of food and beautiful scenery.)
First, let's head there...
- Okay. - and get something to eat.
- This street is pretty. - Gosh, this looks cool.
Gosh, how pretty.
This is a beautiful city.
Vladivostok's animal symbol is a tiger.
They are two baby tigers.
- I should take a photo. - Let's take a photo.
- Jong Kook. - Okay.
We will start taking photos. Jong Kook, you're first.
Jong Kook will take his photo first.
- We will start with you. - Okay. I'll go first.
- All right. - Gosh, they're so cute.
Look at the camera. In 1, 2, 3.
(Reunion of a Separated Family?)
Jong Kook, can I take a selfie with you?
- Sure. - Let me take one too.
(I want to take a photo with Jong Kook.)
I want to take one with him.
In 1, 2, 3.
(I Am Jong Kook's Right Hand Man!)
- Should we go there? - No, there's no such thing.
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
(I'm excited.)
(They start humming a Russian folk song.)
Do it right here.
It's just like Tetris.
(Haha, you are so good!)
I'm so excited!
(We are not done yet.)
(They start dancing right away at the sound of music.)
(Jong Kook, I am your right hand man, aren't I?)
(This is a dance competition to win over Jong Kook's heart.)
Haha, you are not doing your best.
- Didn't Haha do his best? - No, I did my best.
I think...
there is another mission.
- I agree. - I feel dizzy.
Can we take a break?
- Wait. - This is too much.
- I think I'm about to cry. - He's way over the line.
What should we eat?
I'm sort of craving chicken breast salad.
(It's difficult to please Jong Kook.)
I want to eat something.
Shall we go into a restaurant?
All right. Let's do that, Jong Kook.
- This one serves chicken and pork. - I think there's chicken breast.
- Look at that. - Is there a toilet around here?
- Hey, find a toilet. - That's shrimp.
I see one right there.
- I will be back. - Okay, Jong Kook.
Hey, you guys are...
Hey, Jong Kook is going to the toilet.
- One of you should come with me. - I'll go with you.
Kwang Soo, come with me.
Let's go. Gosh, this looks great.
Jong Kook, you made your decision, right?
- What? - You made your decision, right?
I can't make it now. I have to make it at the end.
I can't decide now.
- "Toilet" - This way, sir.
(I will polish the path for you.)
- Isn't this for the ladies? - No, this is for men.
- This is a unisex, public toilet. - I think we have to pay for this.
(No way! Someone is coming.)
Do we have to pay?
(This is a problem. Jong Kook already went in.)
(He's about to pay 40 cents.)
2? 20?
Twenty.
I am not using the toilet. Someone is already inside.
I am not using it.
He went in because it was urgent.
(She must have experienced this often.)
- We have to pay, right? - Yes.
Se Chan!
(Se Chan, help us!)
Se Chan, please give me some money.
- Why? - You have to pay for the toilet.
- Really? - I need 40 cents.
Seriously?
- Hey. - 40 cents? Hold on.
(I can't believe we spent money on toilet.)
Run, run!
For how long do we have to keep this up?
Will it last for two days?
Do we have to spend two days working like a dog for him?
(They paid 40 cents because Jong Kook had to use the toilet.)
- Bye. - Bye. But this...
I should hold it if I can.
I should have held it in and gone to the toilet at once.
- Haha. - Should we ask him?
- Can you help us? - The king crab!
- How do I say, "Please help us." - Show him the pictures.
(Please help us catch king crabs.)
- King crabs. - We want to fish for king crabs.
(Russky Island)
(We should go to Russky Island?)
- What? - Isn't that an island?
- It's an island, right? - Russky...
(If they go to the island...)
- It's called Russky Island. - Hey.
(Will they be able to accomplish their mission?)
(Vladivostok in Russia)
(It's their last struggle before they go on the dangerous trip.)
(If you want to come out alive, survive the tough sea of Russia!)
(And)
(Are they crying in the sea?)
(Ulaanbaatar in Mongolia)
(In the midst of this vast field in Mongolia,)
(they have to find the descendants of Genghis Khan.)
Didn't we fail the mission?
Where did it go?
(This is the unprecedented, ultimate mission.)
Didn't we fail?
Sheep!
(Seize the last opportunity...)
(to avoid going on the Dangerous Trip.)
(Last Chance in Mongolia and Russia)
(Ji Hyo and So Min get to spend time together.)
(So Min,)
(you are so cheerful and positive.)
(No, that's not true, Ji Hyo.)
(I am very pessimistic.)
(It's the end of a tough day on an unfamiliar land.)
(They sincerely share their feelings.)
(This is a special story between Ji Hyo and So Min.)
(We will tell you this story next Sunday.)
(The 2nd project of the global project)
(Recommend a destination! Members will go to the destination!)
(Running Man will air next Sunday)