It's 2017 Running Man's new project, Member's Week.
The first member is Song Ji Hyo.
I've been wanting to go on a trip with the members.
We'll have a barbecue and a campfire.
We can roast sweet potatoes with the bonfire.
We will go on a trip as a whole. I can't wait for it.
(However...)
(Is this a tangled link between you and me?)
(The staff members are bullies.)
(This isn't the trip I expected.)
(The ultimate winter trip beyond imagination is here.)
(Even the 900-year-old goblin visited here.)
The drama, "Goblin", was filmed here.
- Really? - I'm certain.
- Look at this. - Thanks to Ji Hyo, we are here.
- Let's hear why she picked here. - Yes, let's do that.
Besides, she wanted to go on a trip...
- without the cameras. - This isn't what she wanted.
- We can't do this with cameras. - If only there were no cameras...
Can't we each have an individual camera on our own?
Ji Hyo, why are we here?
- At least we should know why. - Why are we here?
- Thanks to Ji Hyo, we are here. - Everyone,
- we are on our trip! - Why are we here?
- We are on a trip. - She looks happy.
I'm glad we are here, but we should've come without the cameras.
I didn't know there were so many cameras here.
- That's exactly my point. - How can you not know?
- How can you not see them? - What are you saying?
- It's been seven years. - You really didn't know?
- Why are we here? - Yes, why?
- Why? - Why are we in Pyeongchang?
- Let's hear it. - Today, I...
Just like we told you last week,
today is the first day of Member's Week.
- The first member is... - It's Ji Hyo.
Right, it's Ji Hyo.
I will reveal the theme that Ji Hyo has decided for Member's Week.
What is it?
- "Ranch"? - There's a barbecue?
This does look like a trip.
- There's a campfire. - We're going to Daegwallyeong?
- Are we going to a sheep ranch? - Barbecue and campfire...
Ranch in Daegwallyeong?
- This is my first time going there. - Someone told me to prepare...
two sets of underwear, but I can't see where we would get wet.
Soon, the season of winter trips will begin.
During the snowy winter,
as Ji Hyo wished to go on a trip...
that brought the members together,
we have prepared a winter trip for the members...
right here in Pyeongchang.
The itinerary that you are looking at was...
put together to suit your preferences.
Do you like the itinerary?
- Why do we need extra underwear? - We have to see it.
Are you worried we might pee during the campfire?
The board wasn't big enough.
- Could you flip it? - There's a back side of it?
I guess there is.
(What is it? What are we doing today?)
(Is it a romantic trip on a snowy field?)
(Is it a trip that will unite us as one on a romantic snowfield?)
(The last stop is ice shower at an icy valley.)
(This is why they need two sets of underwear.)
My goodness.
- What do you mean by ice shower? - Are we really doing that?
We can just go to a sauna.
- Another ice shower? - We did that last week.
What's the point of it if it's going to be edited out?
It's no use if it will be edited out.
It might not be edited out this time.
(His part for the shower was cut.)
Water in Pyeongchang is known to be cold.
- Look at that water. - It looks so cold.
Look at it. Chunks of ice are floating.
My goodness. This is no joke.
(If Ji Hyo wants us to do it, then we will.)
(Who will face the ice shower? It will be the highlight of the trip.)
This isn't the end.
We've prepared something to bring you all together.
What is it?
- Why? - Come on.
- This is too much. - Is this what Ji Hyo wanted?
- We're going to be tied together? - My gosh.
- Come on. - Please.
- Did I want this? - Is this what you wanted?
- This isn't what I expected. - Why do we need to be tied?
- I don't understand why we should. - This isn't what I wanted.
- How do we... - With this...
When I said I wanted the trip to unite us as one,
I didn't mean it literally.
- My gosh. - We are united as one indeed.
Hey, we are at last united as one.
What is all this?
- Is this it? - This is it.
- She's going to lead us? - She will drag us?
- Ji Hyo will... - We aren't dogs.
We look like slaves.
Ji Hyo, can you pull the rope?
- The secret of this rope is... - Move as far as it allows you to.
When she pulls the rope...
(When she pulls the linked rope...)
What's going on?
- It's pulling us closer. - I see now.
- We are all clustered. - What is this? Come on.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
- What is all this? - Is it really necessary?
- What is this? - You don't have to do this.
- We can't be united like this. - This looks weird.
The first week of Member's Week.
It's Running Man Link Trip.
The subtitle for this episode is "It's Not What You Think".
This is it.
Do you want us to bury you in a mountain?
We made this link following Ji Hyo's wish...
to bring all the members together through the trip.
Starting now, you will have to survive...
until the trip is over.
- Even when we go to the restroom? - Yes.
Moreover, you must be chosen in order to enjoy...
what's on the itinerary. Chosen members will be...
able to get off the rope for it.
There's a chance we can get out?
- Yes, there is. - I see.
Until the trip is over, you can only...
- disengage the rope twice. - Is that so?
When you want to disengage the rope,
Ji Hyo has to give you permission.
How do the members get selected? Does Ji Hyo get to choose?
Will our beautiful Ji Hyo pick?
(My gosh.)
- You're glowing today. - You get one point.
We're 30-year-old friends!
- She will personally choose. - My gosh.
- Last week, you had the ice... - It will be too cold.
Shower, representing the Running Man members.
(Last week, the first episode of the new year)
(She endured the pouring water as they welcomed the new year.)
- Ji Hyo. - I was the first one to get it.
I felt a bit disappointed for the members who didn't...
have the chance to get it.
I wish they can feel what it is to become one with water.
- Ice shower? - We did that last week.
She wanted to share this since it was...
- a great experience for her. - I experienced it.
I did, too.
- I did. - When did you do it, Seok Jin?
- It was edited out. - When did you get it?
- Where did you do it? - When did you do it, Seok Jin?
- I did it. - When?
- Don't you remember? - Seriously. When did you do it?
- It wasn't aired. - Please stop it, Seok Jin.
Seok Jin.
- Please stop. - I mean...
How can you not remember it? It was only last week.
- I don't. - What is he talking about?
- When did he do it? - This is how you ruin a person.
This is how.
Members who may face an ice shower are...
all the members except for Ji Hyo.
- She's exempted? - But I had it last week.
- Exclude the ones who did it. - However, as always,
there's hope.
There are several missions during the trip.
Every time you accomplish your mission, we will grant you...
- a chance to exclude one member. - Is that so?
- Is that true? - Let's enjoy the trip as you...
come together as one. Let's go to the first stop.
- Are we going to the sheep ranch? - Yes.
Let's go.
- Disengage us. - Where should I go?
Give us some room.
Let's get our trip started.
Are we your huskies?
- I'm hungry. Let's eat ramyeon. - What is this?
- Let's start our trip. - Ji Hyo, let's eat first.
- I should've worn boots like yours. - Ji Hyo,
I like your outfit today.
- My outfit? - You look like a foreigner.
- You can release two people. - I like your outfit.
You look better when you show your forehead.
- Her forehead is so pretty. - That's a pretty forehead.
- Ji Hyo already started. - This isn't the trip I wanted.
- Ji Hyo, you are so pretty. - I can't stand cheesy comments.
- She hates this kind of thing. - Please stop it.
I knew she was pretty, but her forehead is stunning.
- Seok Jin, you lost a point. - Why?
- Seok Jin, you lost a point. - I didn't do anything, Ji Hyo.
She can take away a point from Seok Jin.
- Are we going to have lamb? - I like lamb.
Kwang Soo deserves to lose two points.
Hey, you lost five points.
- You can't bribe me. - It's not that cold today.
- It isn't a bribe. - Yes, it's not cold.
- Pre-schools are on a break. - This is so pretty.
- This is pretty, but will we go in? - It is beautiful.
How beautiful.
- You are prettier. - You are prettier.
You are more beautiful.
- Seok Jin, you lost two points. - I only complimented you.
- Why do you keep deducting points? - This is beautiful indeed.
Why don't you take off points for Seok Jin from the start?
- Ji Hyo. - Should we take a photo there?
- Yes, let's take a picture. - Shall we?
In 1, 2, 3.
- Hey, why am I not in the frame? - Seok Jin's not in it.
Hey.
- Seriously, Seok Jin isn't in it. - Well done, Ji Hyo.
(They are excited to be on a trip.)
- Did you see that? - This is too cruel.
Do you know how many points you have lost so far, Seok Jin?
He's going to get it today.
I'm certain you will get it, Seok Jin.
I think we're going there by bus.
- Let's get on the bus. - Can we get on it like this?
- Can we sit? - It's cold.
- How can we sit? - I see towels on the bus.
- What are the towels implying? - I see them.
- Does it mean we'll get wet? - Towels are on the bus.
You can scoot over and I will sit here.
It feels like we are all tangled up here.
- We are tangled. - Kwang Soo, sit there.
- I think you should come here. - That's better.
- Why is the rope twisted? - That's it.
- Hold on. - We can sit down.
Seok Jin will get in the water.
- No, to be honest... - I bet you won't be chosen.
- Ji Hyo. - Seok Jin.
Since his part was edited out last week, this week's part won't be.
Seok Jin, you should just give up.
After that, I was only in the full shot.
Ji Hyo's side face is so...
How would you grade that, Ji Hyo?
That made you really uncomfortable, didn't it?
Seok Jin keeps studying her face.
I never compliment women.
- That's not true. - I don't even compliment my wife.
She's the only woman you didn't give compliment to. I saw you...
Be quiet. Shut it.
(The compliment relay left nothing but scars.)
Why would you say that?
Doesn't this place really feel like winter?
Yes.
(Now is the time to flatter her.)
I can't express how grateful I am.
I'm so happy.
What's his score? Is it in the minus?
It's not in the minus. It's a positive score.
(Why do you only hate me?)
Ji Hyo won't even look to Seok Jin's side.
Why am I the only one in the minus?
- Why do you only hate me? - Look at the mountains.
(Let's enjoy the scenery and relax ourselves.)
- It feels like winter now. - If we kept staying in Seoul,
- we wouldn't have known. - Right.
There's actual sheep.
- Where is it? - Over there.
- They're sheep. - She's right.
(They're sheep.)
- They look so cute running around. - Look at the sheep.
(This ranch is the first course of Running Man Link Trip.)
- Where is it? - It's a sheep.
They look so cute running around.
(It's therapeutic to just look at the cute herds of sheep.)
Look at the sheep. Hello, sheep!
- There really are sheep. - Hello.
- There are even horses. - There are.
(The snow covered field creates a beautiful scenery.)
(It's a therapeutic ranch in Pyeongchang.)
- How do we unlock this? - Just hop over it for now.
(It's a chaos.)
- Does this go in here? - How does this work?
(It won't be therapeutic like this.)
- Hop over it. - You have to come back, Seok Jin.
- You have to do it over, Seok Jin. - You have to do it again, Seok Jin.
- I do? - Yes.
This is such a mess.
Is this it?
Gosh.
Don't drag us around.
Can I not go forward?
(Ji Hyo is the only one who looks happy.)
- There's sheep. - Gosh.
- I can't move forward like this. - There's sheep. Come on.
(Ji Hyo has gone wild by the sheep.)
Come on!
- There's sheep over there. - Come on!
- Gosh. - I don't know how this works.
- We'll have to look into it. - There are even horses.
There are even horses there.
- Stop running! - I can't look forward.
- Sheep! - There really are sheep here.
(Who's calling us?)
- Ji Hyo. - Sheep!
(Answer me, Sheep.)
- I didn't know it'd be this cold. - It's so cold.
- Look at the sheep herd. - I have to wear the hood.
- We really have to. - What do we do now?
Let's go look at the horses.
- What? - Let's go look at the horses.
- Why would we go there? - We can see them from here.
(The link is unintentionally having them go through winter training.)
- We can already see them from here. - Are you...
(Unlike them, the horses are free.)
Come over here.
- Ji Hyo, this episode is ruined. - This is not looking good.
We should untie ourselves and go home after eating soondaeguk.
- Trips are supposed to be fun. - Why is it so windy?
(What are they doing here?)
Gosh, it's so cold. What is that?
(The members of Running Man arrive at the place of the mission.)
Isn't this the electric thing?
(Are those lie detectors?)
There are only five of them.
- Ji Hyo must not be doing it. - I guess so.
Ji Hyo's Week, Running Man Link Trip.
The first course is called Shepherd Running Man.
You will go look around the ranch...
as it's the first event of Ji Hyo's trip.
- We're looking around? - Only one member...
can be free from the link and look around freely.
Nice.
Ji Hyo will conduct a polygraph test on the other members.
She will take the person who only tell the truth...
to go look around with her.
For Ji Hyo and that other person,
we've prepared a sled.
(Succeeding the mission will grant you a two-seater sled.)
I bet the rest of the members will be pulling it.
Are you kidding me?
(The group opposes.)
- Do you take us as Rudolph? - Gosh.
Is this a Slave Special?
The other four members...
will pull the sled and show the two around the ranch.
I want to untie myself. It feels so uncomfortable.
I feel nauseous because of this.
I never thought a rope would do this.
Especially for Kwang Soo who falls in love quickly...
- Jae Seok. - He does.
- Don't call me that. - Why?
Let's call him that from now on.
(Kwang Soo is at it again in Daegwallyeong.)
I watched the show with my mom last week.
I've never seen my mom laugh so hard.
- Your mother likes it too. - She was laughing so hard.
- My mom was... - Your mother likes it too.
- My mom loved it. - See?
It's good that your mother likes it.
It's good.
We just have to tell the truth, right?
- That's right. - That's all we have to do.
- That's all it takes. - That's right.
(Kwang Soo goes first.)
Let's start with Kwang Soo.
"Honestly, I think I'm just as popular as Song Joong Ki."
That's a difficult question.
This is annoying.
But isn't this an obvious question?
(He doesn't even need to think about it.)
- Isn't this an obvious question? - Yes.
You think you're just as popular?
- Okay, let's see what it says. - That's what I think.
That's what I think.
You're very confident.
(You're definitely taller and funnier than him.)
(Kwang Soo told the truth.)
Are you serious?
(Kwang Soo is a very confident guy.)
He thinks he's as sexy and as popular as Joong Ki.
He's a psychopath.
I'm entitled to my own opinions.
- You think you're as sexy as him? - He's not lying right now.
Fine. Take a seat.
- He's not lying. - I'll ask another question.
Haha just called you a psychopath.
- Why am I a psychopath? - Gosh.
- He really thinks that. - You should try again.
- He's so weird. - Fine.
- Let's do another one. - Ask a question.
"I'd marry my wife again in the next life."
That's...
- Isn't it obvious? - He has to say yes.
- Of course. - That is correct.
This is obvious for Seok Jin.
(It should be true.)
(It's obviously...)
(true.)
- Okay. - What's going on?
Is he serious?
He must be.
Are you serious right now?
Of course.
- I got so surprised just now. - Hold on.
Ask him one more time, Ji Hyo.
I didn't know you could fool yourself.
- It's my turn now. - I'm a romantic person.
(Jae Seok goes third.)
Ask him if he'll marry his wife in the next life.
- I'm confident. - Ask him.
- Yes. I'm sure of it. - Are you sure?
- Let's see. - Will you marry your wife again...
- in the next life? - Of course.
I'll marry her again.
By the way, Seok Jin passed.
I passed.
(Will Jae Seok become a romantic person too?)
(It's a lie.)
(The lie detector knows a thing or two.)
There's something wrong with the machine.
Oh my.
- She might get the wrong idea. - Jae Seok.
- There's been a misunderstanding. - How shocking.
(Jae Seok fails.)
- She'll get the wrong idea. - I'm better than him.
- This isn't... - Humans are imperfect beings.
There's been a misunderstanding.
This is so shocking.
Even I passed.
- This result is shocking to me. - Goodness.
This is the best twist since "The Sixth Sense".
- I love you. - Gosh.
It's Jong Kook's turn now.
"I still like Yoon Eun Hye."
(Does he still have Yoon Eun Hye on his mind?)
Gosh.
(Everyone wants to know the answer to that question.)
(What will his answer be?)
(They met 10 years ago.)
(Does he still have feelings for her?)
This one's nice.
(Thinking carefully)
Look at Jong Kook.
- Answer her. - Do I still like her?
- No. - It's a no.
(His answer was no.)
(Has he completely...)
(gotten over her?)
(He hasn't.)
What a liar.
(They caught me.)
You still haven't gotten over her.
- How many years has it been? - The machine is faulty.
(Jong Kook became a romantic person.)
- You still haven't gotten over her. - No.
No. That's not true.
If you think about it, he's so clingy it's scary.
- I know. - There's been a misunderstanding.
You should meet again this year.
- That took me by surprise. - Jong Kook is amazing.
He still hasn't gotten over her.
He's a fool who only loves one person.
(You should let her go in 2017.)
That was such a long time ago.
Next up is Haha.
(Haha goes last.)
"Among all the female celebrities in Korea,."
"Byul is the prettiest."
- You're doomed. - He has to say yes.
- It won't be right otherwise. - He has to.
Is she the prettiest to you?
- Yes. - He said yes.
It's so obvious.
He says it's obvious. What will it be?
(Is his obvious answer the truth or not?)
(Are you watching, Byul?)
(To me, )
(you're the prettiest.)
(What is the result of the polygraph test?)
His hands are shaking.
(It's a lie.)
(I have to beg for forgiveness.)
Who is it then?
(Will you be able to go home after this?)
Who do you think is the prettiest then?
Can you let me go again? I'll say no.
She's not the prettiest. She's the most beautiful.
This man still hasn't gotten over Yoon Eun Hye.
- Stop it. - This man...
will marry a different woman in another life.
- That's right. - That's a misunderstanding.
She may not be the prettiest celebrity...
But she's the one I'll marry.
- I'll marry her. - Are you happy?
Yes.
- It's either one of these two. - Right.
- I'll ask Kwang Soo now. - Okay.
"To be honest,."
"I'm better than Jo In Sung."
- Personally, I think I am. - In Sung?
(Kwang Soo over In Sung?)
He's so confident.
- We have different charms. - How?
- You think you're better? - Better than In Sung?
I think I am.
(What does Kwang Soo really think?)
(He couldn't beat In Sung.)
(Kwang Soo is the only one who doesn't know.)
- What's wrong with this? - He's absolutely crazy.
- He's so confident. - He's crazy.
Who are you calling crazy?
- He's a lunatic. - It's my personal opinion.
I'm just speaking my mind.
You think you're better than...
In Sung and Joong Ki?
It's my personal opinion.
- That's true, but... - Everyone is unique in a way.
He's completely crazy.
Why does this make me a crazy psychopath?
- It's Seok Jin's turn. - Gosh.
Do you always want to go home early?
Yes.
Is it because you want to see your beloved wife?
He says he always wants to go home early.
- Must you ask that? - Yes.
It's to save his own face.
Of course.
I always want to go home early to eat dinner.
Is it to see your wife?
Yes, I want to eat dinner with my wife.
(Is he telling the truth about his love life?)
(It's true.)
Gosh, Seok Jin.
- That's impressive. - He's such a romantic guy.
He's romantic after all.
He's like Choi Su Jong.
- He's very romantic. - He's like Sean.
- That's right. - That's me.
Seok Jin isn't actually like this.
- I feel like I'm born again today. - What a gentleman.
Ji Hyo and Seok Jin will take a look around the ranch.
Please get on the sledge.
The remaining four members will pull the sledge.
- All right. - My goodness.
He looks excited.
(It's time to take a look around.)
This is the sledge.
- Where is it? - It's over here.
(It's a great sledge for the ranch tour.)
- Are you okay? - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Come on.
(Rudolph, let's go.)
- What's this? - What's wrong with this?
Here you go, Seok Jin.
There's no cushion on it.
There's no cushion on a sledge.
Here we go.
(Struggling)
(They wonder why they came on the trip.)
- Hurry. - I can't stay seated.
Pull harder.
(What kind of cruel passenger is this?)
My goodness.
Okay, in 1, 2, 3.
What's this?
This isn't a trip. It's a boot camp.
Riding the sledge is more difficult.
- Ji Hyo. - What on earth is this?
This is not a trip.
(What are they doing in the middle of winter?)
In 1, 2, 3.
- This isn't a trip. - What are we doing?
What kind of trip is this?
This isn't a trip.
- This isn't a trip. - What are we doing?
(We feel bad for you.)
It's time for your mission.
- If you succeed, - We don't go in the water?
One of you is exempted from the punishment.
- Okay. - At this place,
there are many sheep running in the snow.
Do you see the sheep shed in the back?
If you put 30 sheep in the shed within 3 minutes, you succeed.
- Which sheep? - Sheep are very heavy.
You herd the sheep.
- You herd them. - Why would you carry them?
- You herd the sheep. - I see.
You don't carry the sheep.
- There's no need to use strength. - That's such foolish thinking.
I've carried sheep before.
Can we carry sheep?
They're very heavy.
I'm surprised that you've carried them before.
- I've carried them before. - You can carry them if you want.
Go this way.
- Let's go. - Herd them to one side.
The sheep are very cute.
- Come here. - Ji Hyo, Seok Jin.
They're looking at us.
- Come here. - They're looking at us.
- They're looking at us. - They're so cute.
It's like they're challenging us.
It's okay because our color is similar to theirs.
- I was born in the Year of Sheep. - They're so cute.
We're wearing the same color.
- They're coming. - They're coming.
- Come here. - They're coming to eat.
That sheep looks like Kwang Soo.
- One of us can do it. - Come this way.
- Herd them on one side. - That's good.
- Herd them to that side. - Go to that side.
- Which side? - Let's go over there.
Come here.
- Come here, guys. - Come here.
- Come here. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(More sheep follow them.)
Shall we start the challenge?
Come this way.
(They get closer together.)
That sheep looks like Kwang Soo.
- One of us can do it. - Come this way.
- Herd them. - Herd them on one side.
- That's good. - Herd them first.
Send them to the shed right away.
(They finally get a chance.)
- Challenge. - Challenge.
(They move forward.)
- Let's go. - Challenge.
- Let's go. - Guys.
- We're doing well. - Wait.
- What do we do with that sheep? - Go.
(The sheep move in a herd.)
- Kwang Soo. - Gosh.
Gosh, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok falls on his bottom.)
- We're doing well. - Wait.
- What do we do with that sheep? - Go.
(Falling)
(He slips twice in a row.)
- Kwang Soo. - Keep them together.
(The shepherds lose control of their bodies.)
- Wait. - There's poop everywhere.
- Look at this. - I think I slipped in their urine.
- Be careful. - I slipped in their urine.
- They're moving. - Kwang Soo.
Let's go.
(The herd moves toward the exit.)
(My dear sheep, let's go home.)
- Go out. - Go out.
- Everyone, get out. - Go out.
We might make it.
- They're leaving. - Keep going.
(It's time to go home.)
- Keep going. - Go out.
- Go out 1 by 1. - Be careful.
- You're getting stuck. Go slowly. - Be careful.
(One sheep stays inside the fence.)
Go slowly.
What about this sheep?
- Come here. - We have one sheep left.
- Come this way. - Take this sheep with you.
- Hey. - Don't go.
Hey!
- Come this way. - Take this sheep with you.
(The sheep runs away.)
- No. - Get it!
(The sheep wants to play alone.)
It knows how variety shows work.
(They have an escapee.)
- Come here. - He's coming.
Go back to your friends.
- Come here. - Come this way.
Jong Kook, carry him.
No, lure him slowly.
Come here.
(The sheep is upset.)
- Here. - Don't go that way.
- It's not that way. - Go up there and block him.
Don't go that way.
What's going on?
He's moving away.
- What's going on? - He's moving.
- He's moving. - Get out.
(He decides to leave due to their effort.)
The exit to the left is open.
- That's right. - Right.
- Go out that way. - Go out.
(The sheep goes out.)
Let's go to the sheep shed.
Where's the sheep shed?
He's going in.
- They know where to go. - They're moving.
They're already trained.
Go inside.
- All right. - Did all go in?
- Go inside. - Close the door.
- No. - Don't go that way.
That's not the way.
(It's the 2nd escape.)
Hey, hey.
(The whole herd escape.)
- Don't run away. - Stop.
(Did you think we were that easy?)
Stay inside.
Ji Hyo has to go inside with the food.
- Go inside, Ji Hyo. - I'll go in.
- All of us have to go in. - Wait.
We must lure them in first.
- I'll go in first. - Sheep, it's time to eat.
All we have to do is lure in the rest.
Be quiet.
Guess what we have.
- Here you go. - They'll come toward us.
- Here you go. - Come here. Let's eat.
- Let's eat. - Let's go in.
- We should go in. - Let's go in.
- Come here and eat. - We should go in.
Don't go in yet.
Wait until all the sheep are near us.
- Let's eat. - We're trying to feed you.
Open the gate.
Wait. Let's go in.
- Open the gate. - They're coming in.
- Stop. - Wait a minute.
- Go in. - In 3, 2.
- Come here. - Go in.
- One. - Come here.
(The time is up.)
- Come here. - They're leaving.
(They run out without turning back.)
- Come here now. - All the sheep are leaving.
- Hey. - Hey.
They're all leaving.
My goodness.
- Where are you going? - This is difficult.
It's not easy at all.
Are they trying to tease us?
Ji Hyo.
(Look, Ji Hyo.)
Is this the kind of trip you wanted?
What happened?
(They're exhausted after the 1st 2 hours.)
That was so tiring.
It's difficult.
- It's not easy at all. - You failed the mission.
- You seem happy that we failed. - It was difficult.
You were very close.
Five of you will still go in the water.
- Fine. - We'll be doomed.
- Let's just go in. - It's time...
- We'll go in together. - for the barbecue. Let's move on.
Let's go.
- Barbecue. - Barbecue.
- Let's go. - It's my favorite time.
- I'm hungry. - We'll get barbecue.
- We were so close. - Barbecue time.
The sheep were so cute.
- Right now, - I've never seen them in person.
Ji Hyo who suggested this trip is very upset.
- It's not the trip she wanted. - She's been upset for a while.
This isn't what I wanted.
Here's what was scary.
At first, Ji Hyo said that the sheep were very cute.
When things didn't turn out well, she cursed at them.
She said, "Are you a gangster?"
I'm being serious.
I think this rope is the problem.
- It's a big problem. - What does it mean exactly?
- It means we should become one. - The rope is...
- soaked with sheep poop. - Really?
Kwang Soo stepped on poop and slipped.
(During the sheep herding mission)
- Kwang Soo. - Keep them together.
There's poop everywhere.
(The link is covered with sheep poop.)
He fell on his bottom.
I slipped on where the sheep pooped and peed.
(He fell in sheep poop.)
Kwang Soo can't help but attract poop.
- He can't pass by poop. - Did you see him?
There are two who slipped on poop.
They're me and Kwang Soo.
That's right.
When will we take a beautiful trip that we want?
- It's time for barbecue. - Without the cameras and shooting.
- We need to schedule it. - We'll eat barbecue soon.
- We're going to have barbecue. - What?
- We're having barbecue, right? - That's right.
We won't get barbecue so easily.
- There's no way. - I hope I get some barbecue.
Here's a mission for the barbecue party.
- Okay. - First,
Ji Hyo will write 10 ingredients...
she wants for the barbecue.
Don't include meat.
- Ji Hyo likes ramyeon. - Right.
- Do you know her well? - We need ramyeon.
- These are for barbecue. - How about potatoes and such?
- I have so much I want to eat. - Ramyeon and kimchi.
How about a leaf of lettuce?
- The list is ready. - How about chocolate chips?
- Did you write down bread? - No.
- We need some bread. - I'm hungry.
She wrote down the 10 ingredients.
- Here's the mission. - Sure.
You have three minutes...
to buy all 10 ingredients that Ji Hyo wrote down.
Here's the condition. Ji Hyo cannot move from the front.
(Ji Hyo cannot step out of the designated area.)
Let's get started.
- Let's go. - Ji Hyo has to stay at the counter.
- Let's try to go fast. - We have to know what she picked.
(They'll be awarded meat according to how many they get right.)
- Go in the red square, Ji Hyo. - Let's get fish cake bar.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- Do you remember them? - Haha.
- Tell us, Ji Hyo. - Tangerine, rice, and mushrooms.
- Tangerine. - Let's go this way.
- Tangerine. - Tangerine's right here.
- You can't move, Ji Hyo. - Chili peppers,
- sweet potatoes, and potatoes. - Get set...
- Tangerines. - And?
You have three minutes. Get mushrooms.
(They get lucky and find tangerines right away.)
Weren't there also chili peppers?
- Chili peppers. - Here's garlic.
- Garlic. - Garlic?
(They find chili pepper, tangerines, and garlic.)
- Get mushroom. - Here's king oyster mushroom.
(They get chili pepper, garlic, mushrooms in the vegetable section.)
- Mushrooms and what? - Garlic.
- We have garlic. - Get snacks.
- Ramyeon. - Get kimchi.
- This one? - Yes, that one.
- Get instant rice. - Is there rice?
- Get tuna. - We don't have tuna or potatoes.
(What?)
(Why would he get a whole sac?)
Why would you get that, fool?
- It's instant rice. - She means instant rice.
Get instant rice.
- Don't. - It's okay.
(I don't know anymore.)
- Get instant rice. - She means instant rice.
Where's potato?
(Would we be able to do a proper barbecue?)
- Get potatoes. - It's below here.
- Here's sweet potato. - That's potato.
(They find potato and sweet potatoes together.)
- I got potatoes. - Did you?
- One minute has passed. - Really?
What else?
- Hurry up. - Here's sweet potato.
- Get some snacks. - I see snacks.
- It's over there. - All right.
(They look for snacks now.)
Raise the rope.
(He's so close.)
Pull on the rope.
(The link limits their movement.)
- Hold on. - Sit down.
(It's so tight.)
- Sit down. - You're done.
- Please, get me that one. - That's enough.
- I really like that one. - The rope is getting in the way.
(Snacks?)
Can I get the one next to it?
- Get back. - Stop it. Come back.
(He shows perfect teamwork with the lady.)
- Raise the rope. - Didn't we get bread?
- Where's tuna? - You have 30 seconds.
- We didn't get bread. - Get tuna.
- Tuna's a hard one. - We need to find it.
(The length of the rope is limited.)
- We need tuna. - Get instant rice.
- Where's tuna, ma'am? - Go.
- Keep going. - Ask one of them.
Excuse me. Can you throw me one?
(She's like the 7th member of Running Man.)
(Here's tuna.)
- Get instant rice, too. - Thank you.
Excuse me.
- We have 10 seconds. - Can you throw me instant rice?
- Throw it. Thank you. - Ten.
- Bring it. - Can you throw me another one?
(She comes to their aid again.)
- This one. - Five.
(Thank you, ma'am.)
- Thank you. - Four, three...
You're good.
- Two. - Hold it.
- Put it in. - We're good.
(Time's over.)
- I'm sorry. - Hey.
How much sweet potatoes and rice did you get?
- Potatoes. - Where's garlic?
(They check the ingredients.)
- It was right in front. - What about ramyeon?
- We have it. - Did we get it?
- We don't have ramyeon. - We missed it.
- We don't have it, right? - Why didn't we get it?
- Why didn't we get it? - I didn't even think of it.
You are missing ramyeon. You got nine items correct.
(They got 9 out of 10 ingredients.)
You have earned five servings of Korean beef.
- That's good enough. - We get five servings.
- We did well. - That's fine.
- I think we did pretty well. - We did.
It wasn't easy.
(This is where they'll get meat.)
We got a lot of good ones.
Did we?
(This is where they'll get meat.)
(They earned the meat by completing the mission.)
- I can already smell it. - There's meat.
- It's Korean beef. - We need to get five servings.
- It looks so good. - Right?
- It does look good. - How many grams is two servings?
It's 300g for 1 serving. You can get 5 servings.
That's for 1 serving? How many grams is this? It's 200g.
(They try to measure 5 servings.)
That looks good, too.
- Get some sirloin. - Let's get rib eye.
- This is 200g. - That doesn't look good.
It sounds funny when you say, "sirloin".
I like sirloin.
- I mean... - What if I like it?
(Grabbing)
This looks so good.
I didn't think we'd eat beef in Pyeongchang.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(They head to the barbecue place.)
(A resort in Daegwallyeong, Pyeongchang)
(This is the highlight of winter trips.)
(It's barbecue time in Pyeongchang.)
Can't we untie the rope while we eat?
- We can untie it twice. - Let's untie it.
Let's untie it while we eat.
- Let's do that. - We have two chances.
- Let's untie it. - Seriously.
We need to untie it while we eat.
Isn't it so much better without it?
Yes.
I'm getting excited.
Can we eat now?
- Let's grill the meat now. - I'll do it.
- Sorry? - I'll do it.
- Seok Jin, you... - You shouldn't, Seok Jin.
He's known for being bad in grilling meat.
I'm so good.
I'll make kimchi jjigae.
- Sure. - Let's make kimchi jjigae.
Get some meat.
Meat...
(He cooks each piece like a master.)
- Here. - Where's tuna?
(It's prime beef.)
We have to eat it right away.
It's done.
(It looks so delicious that it might dance inside your mouth.)
Come here. Hey.
(I'll take it, then.)
(Swallowing)
- Let's eat... - Open your mouth.
(It turns the grumbling tiger...)
(into a gentle sheep.)
- Oh, dear. - Isn't it insane?
Eat some meat first.
(It's like something came alive...)
(in my mouth.)
It's good.
(It's like something came alive in my mouth.)
- It looks good. - It's so good.
Let's see. Is it good?
(They all fall for it.)
It separates easily.
(He's amazed. It's so juicy.)
It's so good.
It finally feels like we're on a trip.
I agree.
Really?
Let's see what this is.
- What is it? - Brisket?
Brisket?
Go ahead and grill some basket.
How about grilling some bosket?
(The older members laugh...)
(over old jokes.)
That was seriously not funny.
(There's no age limit to going on trips, though.)
Why didn't anybody get ramyeon?
We should have gotten some.
- I'm glad we didn't. - Kwang Soo.
- Yes? - Can you get some from a neighbour?
Stop talking about ramyeon.
It's the highlight of outdoor trips.
We have so many food. Why do we need ramyeon?
(Isn't there any ramyeon?)
- Do you want some ramyeon? - Yes.
(Why would you even ask?)
We'll give you a special utensil.
If you eat with them, we'll give you one bag each.
What is it?
(What's the special utensil?)
(It looks like wooden sticks.)
Come on.
(Everyone but Jong Kook wants ramyeon.)
(They can only eat with 100cm chopsticks.)
Let's stop the joke since we all laughed about it.
- Good joke. - How can we eat with it?
- Is it even possible? - It is.
(It looks rather inconvenient.)
Are we supposed to eat with this?
Let me get started.
(Let's try eating with this.)
Be careful. Don't drop them.
I'm going to eat with this.
- I love the sirloin. - I'm going to do it, too.
You need to use these, Seok Jin.
Kwang Soo's doing it.
(He sticks his tongue out.)
He's good.
It's good.
- He's good. - It's delicious.
(Should I try it?)
Be careful. Don't drop them.
(You should just eat. Don't close your eyes.)
(They start sharing.)
(They are being kind to each other without intending to.)
Is it good? I was pleasantly shocked.
(They harmonize due to large chopsticks.)
Kwang Soo, come and wash the vegetables with me.
Now? I don't like vegetables.
- Hey. - Are you going to wash them?
Eat some mushrooms. We can put them in kimchi jjigae.
(It's cold and dangerous out there.)
I'll make ramyeon instead.
Come with me, Kwang Soo.
- Somebody has to make it. - Come with me, Kwang Soo.
- I'll make it. - Hurry up.
- I'll make it. - I mean...
- Hurry up. - I'm the youngest...
(They were never this nice to me before.)
Isn't it hard to chew?
(12 minutes of Kwang Soo's slavery begins.)
Hold this.
Aren't these pre-washed?
Hurry up, Kwang Soo.
(You talk too much, Kwang Soo.)
You should have just sent me on my own.
(It's cold.)
- It's not hard. - Don't just wash one.
Wash the other ones, too.
(Can't you wash them more carefully?)
- It's good, right? - Yes. Come.
(She punishes Kwang Soo for being lazy in the first place.)
- That's too much. - Is this good?
- Isn't this how you do it? - Come here.
You're dripping water.
Good.
Why did you even come?
(Meanwhile at the tent...)
I'll make some good soup.
(Add kimchi.)
(Add anything else you can get your hands on.)
Try tasting it.
(Add some gochujang to make it spicy and flavourful.)
It looks good.
(How does Haha's kimchi jjigae taste?)
It's like ramyeon.
Ramyeon's genuine taste...
(This won't work.)
Let's add some meat.
It doesn't taste like anything.
What about mushroom?
(They add mushroom.)
(His first attempt is unsuccessful.)
Should we add some meat?
(They add meat to revive it.)
It's so bad.
(Pondering)
We need to add this if nothing works out.
(Their last hope is the ramyeon seasoning.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
(Would they be able to revive the taste with the seasoning?)
(How is it? Would rice go well with it?)
It doesn't taste anything like kimchi jjigae.
(Even the ramyeon seasoning can't save kimchi jjigae.)
(Everyone has given up, )
(It leaves me no choice, but to...)
- Jae Seok. - Let's put ham in it. We have it.
- That's spicy tuna. - It's spicy tuna.
(She completely empties the spicy tuna can.)
How can you put the spicy tuna?
What's the matter with you? Is there a secret mission?
(She made a bold choice. Was there a reason for it?)
How can this work?
- This is tasty. - It's delicious.
Isn't it delicious?
(What a miracle.)
This almost tastes like tomato soup.
This is so tasty.
(Kimchi, mushroom, beef, ramyeon, and spring onion aren't necessary.)
(You only need a can of spicy tuna.)
(This looks very delicious.)
He hated ramyeon when we filmed "Family Outing". He still doesn't.
But I cooked all the stew he ate with ramyeon seasoning.
- He enjoyed them though, right? - He never figured it out.
I cooked all of them with ramyeon seasoning.
It's delicious.
He could've eaten it pretending to be clueless.
It's tasty because the seasoning is in it.
It's all cooked. Let's eat.
- I didn't put a lot of seasoning. - It's cooked.
- No, it's not. - Let's eat before it's overcooked.
- What's wrong? - Leave it.
That's how I eat my ramyeon.
- But I'm cooking it. - Boil it more.
I will do it.
- Boil it more. - I will do it.
- Why did you put garlic? - Why did you put garlic?
- It's delicious. - How can you put it in?
- Did she put garlic in it? - It will taste good.
- Ji Hyo. - Why are you ruining it?
Why did you put that in?
I think it will be tasty with it.
- Have you never cooked ramyeon? - Yes, I have.
(She gets a handful of hot chili peppers.)
We need to eat ramyeon as it is.
- What? - Hey.
(His plan to taste it as it is goes out the window.)
You've never cooked ramyeon with toppings before, right?
(They can't complain since it's Ji Hyo's week.)
This is a culture shock.
Let's dig in.
- My gosh. - Here is the ramyeon.
Jong Kook, how can you not eat this?
We have meat.
(He's always the first to eat.)
You're so frustrating. Can you bring kimchi?
(He eats before it gets swollen.)
Let's eat.
(Pushing)
(Please move aside.)
- Hey. - What?
(I don't have energy for any more struggles.)
This is delicious.
(The highlight of the trip is eating ramyeon.)
Ramyeon tastes great.
Ji Hyo, we could've put more hot chili peppers in.
(Ji Hyo was right after all.)
Since hot chili peppers are in it,
- Isn't it spicy? - it's spicy and delicious.
She did a good job.
- Her decision was good. - Garlic suits well, too.
You thought well putting the garlic in.
(He's on the move.)
(He tries to eat the sweet potato first.)
This is a hit.
How delicious.
It's hot.
He never eats with us. You saw it, right?
After eating the meat first, he ate ramyeon first.
After he finishes eating ramyeon, he reaches for this first.
He's eating them all.
(Did everyone know about it?)
He comes here after he finishes eating ramyeon.
- You should take it out. - Excuse me.
I'm glad you're eating well, but don't trash the wrappers.
- Clean up afterwards. - Where would I throw them out?
- Put them here. - I did.
Are you happy?
My goodness. You're like a nagging mother-in-law.
You're like a nagging mother-in-law.
- Hold on. - You're just like a mother-in-law.
Did you just disrespected every mother-in-law in Korea?
- I mean... - What's wrong with them?
- You just disrespected them. - That's not what I meant.
The mother-in-law association will be furious about this.
How do you plan to straighten things out with them?
- My mother is no joke. - My mom's also a mother-in-law.
My mom's also a mother-in-law.
I ask that you make a formal apology.
- Seok Jin. - We're in trouble because of you.
Disrespecting a family member is the worst.
I didn't mean any harm by my comment.
I would like to apologize to every mother-in-law in Korea.
- If I hurt or upset you in any way, - I'm sure they are hurt.
Please understand I didn't mean to.
- I would like to apologize to you. - Let's gather and protest.
Okay, this is good.
- Sorry. I didn't mean to. - Apologize to them.
- My gosh. - Don't disrespect them.
- Let's not do that. - Kwang Soo, is there a plate?
If things go wrong...
- But this is so delicious. - I was totally framed.
My gosh. I was falsely charged.
- My mom is pacifist. - That's not true. Oh, dear.
(Ji Hyo's special dessert is the steamed bun.)
Steamed bun.
I want a red bean steamed bun.
By the way, isn't this plate part of the microwave?
Isn't this plate part of the microwave?
(Feeling guilty)
- I mean I thought you... - I couldn't...
- find a plate. - I wondered where you got this.
Did you pull it out from the microwave?
I thought it looked a bit fancy.
- How can a plate like this be here? - The microwave...
- Did you pull it out? - There were no plates.
It's like the board of the microwave.
- She's a good housekeeper. - She is indeed.
(Their meal started off with Korean beef and ended with steamed bun.)
This was a delicious meal.
(But the water is getting colder.)
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you.
- Did you enjoy your dinner? - Yes, we did.
We very much enjoyed it.
Five of you will still face the ice shower.
- That's right. - Five of us?
It's the second mission to lower the number of members for the shower.
It's "Song Ji Hyo Speed Quiz".
(Song Ji Hyo Speed Quiz)
(What is "Song Ji Hyo Speed Quiz"?)
You will have two ice cubes in your mouth.
You will take turns to explain certain words.
Ji Hyo will have to guess the answers.
- I have to guess the answers? - Yes.
All the questions are related to Ji Hyo.
If you complete the mission, one of you will be exempted.
Okay.
(There are too many things to do on this trip.)
- Give me the ice. - Here you go.
(They put the ice cubes in their mouths.)
I can see the steam from your mouths.
(Let's hurry. It's cold.)
Hey, hurry. Hurry.
Get ready.
Start.
("Song Ji Hyo Speed Quiz" starts.)
(The answer is sleeping.)
(Sleeping is her talent and hobby.)
(You think of sleeping when you think about Ji Hyo.)
(Will she be able to figure out right away?)
You like this a lot.
- You like this a lot. - Sleeping.
- Like this. - Sleeping.
(She gets the first question right.)
(Jong Kook is next. The answer is ice shower.)
You and I did this last week.
(Ji Hyo, you remember last week, right?)
(She was picked as the first runner and had the ice shower.)
(She picked him as the next runner and he faced the ice shower, too.)
You and I did this last week.
We faced the water.
We are doing it today.
- Is it water shower? - No.
Shower... New Year...
I don't think she knows this word.
- You and I did this. - We will do it today.
It's ice shower.
(She gets the second question correct.)
Hurry.
(The third one is curse.)
(This is too easy.)
You do this a lot.
(I do this a lot?)
(He's frustrated.)
It's curse.
(She gets the third question correct.)
(I will see you after the show.)
Cheer up, baby.
(We have a lot of memories with this song.)
It's Twice's song.
Twice.
(Twice?)
(Then could it be...)
Cheer up, baby.
(She was so sure the answer was "Shut it, baby.")
(Her answer made everyone speechless.)
It's Twice's song.
- It's a song. - It's "Cheer up".
(I won't get it wrong this time.)
(She gets the fourth question correct.)
(Ji Hyo the Thug)
Ji Hyo.
(This nickname suits you the best.)
(The answer is Ji Hyo the Thug.)
(Ji Hyo the Thug)
Ji Hyo, you are...
(He stutters since it's too cold.)
- Hurry. - Talk faster.
When you are mad, this is whom you turn into.
It starts with your name.
(If it starts with my name, it has to be...)
Hey, you.
(Ji Hyo the Thug appears.)
Why? What are you doing? Hold on.
(Ji Hyo turns into a thug.)
(It's another side of her. Will she get it right?)
It has your name in it.
It's Ji Hyo the Thug.
(She gets the fifth question right. Only the last question remains.)
What is it?
(It's the dance.)
(It's the only dance she manages to do. They saw it more than 10 times.)
(The song came out 8 years ago, but it's still a new song for her.)
That dance is the only talent she has.
(It's her version of "Hot Issue". It is lovely to watch at any time.)
(She will get this right away.)
- From my head to my toe - "Hot Issue"!
- It's "Hot Issue". - That's right.
What's wrong with me?
Mission success.
(She successfully answered 6 questions within 1 minute.)
(Ji Hyo is the best!)
(She is indeed the best player of them all.)
- We did it. - We sure did.
The number of members who will face the ice shower...
went down to four.
- That's great. - Nice.
- Great. - Let's move to the next place.
Let's go.
(Ji Hyo's Week)
(They move to have the campfire.)
(They have the campfire at late night in Pyeongchang.)
- Everyone. - Yes?
Do you like the trip Ji Hyo prepared for you?
- Can you get rid of the rope? - The trip...
- It will be much better without it. - You're right.
You are united as one.
It's the highlight of the trip. It's the campfire.
It's time for "I'm Sorry, I'm Thankful, I Love You".
(It's time for "I'm Sorry, I'm Thankful, I Love You".)
"I'm Sorry, I'm Thankful, I Love You"?
(What is "I'm Sorry, I'm Thankful, I Love You"?)
I'm sorry I came late.
Thank you for working hard today.
I love you.
(They have to express such feelings towards each other.)
We will now begin "I'm Sorry, I'm Thankful, I Love You".
Ji Hyo will pick two members.
- I will? - Ji Hyo's not playing?
Ji Hyo has to play, too. We are six people.
Should I do it with my junior, Seok Jin?
- I pick Jae Seok and Seok Jin. - I'll go with Seok Jin.
Okay.
- I'll go with Seok Jin. - He needs to be taught a lesson.
You're supposed to be my junior.
- I got these for you two. - What is that?
You have to wear these.
(What is that for?)
There's no way of avoiding eye contact this way.
You have to make eye contact from up close.
(It's a tool that will fix their eyes.)
- Come over here. - Gosh.
You won't be able to avoid eye contact unless you close your eyes.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
(They begin.)
- Do you want to go first? - Should I?
The junior may start first.
I've been meaning to tell you this.
When we have get-togethers,
I wonder if I have to pay the bill since I'm the oldest.
I wonder if I have to pay the bill.
(Stingy Seok Jin says he's sorry.)
- He is serious. - I wonder...
if I have to pay or not. I worried about that a lot.
When you pay the bill, I...
Seok Jin loves going to the washroom.
I should've said, "I'll get it, Jae Seok."
When you paid the bill, I said, "Thanks for buying."
On my way home, I thought to myself whether I should've paid the bill.
- He really is a junior. - But...
- Since you're the senior and all, - Right.
I thought that's why you paid the bill.
I'm sorry about that.
- You do pay the bill sometimes. - It's okay. And...
(This time, Jae Seok says he's sorry.)
- I introduced you to your wife. - Right.
You do know that now is the time to say that you're sorry, right?
I'm sorry to your wife.
But not to me?
- I'm sorry to your wife. - You must feel sorry for me.
She made the wrong decision because of me.
- I'm sorry to your wife. - If you knew the details,
- you'd feel sorry. - I feel sorry to your wife.
And you were the one who gave me...
- the nickname, Big Nose. - That's right.
It's been over 20 years since I made my debut...
and that is my only nickname. So I thank you.
- Thanks for giving me a character. - This is heartwarming.
I remember. I think it was the second episode.
- That's right. - Yes.
(He gave him that nickname on the first episode.)
You have a pretty big nose.
- That's right. - I remember that.
- You called me, Big Nose. - Right.
After that, the whole country knew me as Big Nose.
Your DJ name for your radio show is "Nose DJ".
- I got that from Big Nose. - Right.
- Thanks for that. - You don't have to thank me.
- Thank you. - It's nothing.
I...
I'm thankful that...
your wife is happy with you.
- What? - What does that mean?
- Why would you thank her for that? - What's that supposed to mean?
I'm really thankful...
- that you and your wife are happy. - Why would you be thankful?
If you knew the situation I'm in, you wouldn't be.
- I envy you. - I'm really thankful.
(Seok Jin is as bold as the size of his nose.)
Right. Anyway, I remember when...
you used to live in Bbalaegol...
- You used to live in Gao-ri. - Right.
- We met on the number 725 bus. - That's right.
- We've known each other since then. - We go way back.
Right. But I've never said this to you all this time.
I'll take this chance to say it.
I love you.
(He confesses his love for Jae Seok.)
(I love you, Jae Seok.)
(Oh, gosh.)
I'm saying it for the first time in 20 something years.
I don't usually say this.
We've known each other since we were in our early 20s.
That's right.
(After 25 years of time, they're still together.)
(May the two be together for a long time.)
(I'm inside you and you're inside me.)
Now that you said that, I'll say it, too.
I love you, too.
Okay.
(I love you, Seok Jin.)
- This is nice. - I love you.
(Let me give you a hug, Jae Seok.)
(I don't know about that.)
(Jae Seok killed the mood.)
Seok Jin was about to hug you.
- Why would you reject him? - It's awkward now.
(Let's stop here so people won't feel cringy.)
- This is so awkward. - It sure is.
- We never talked like this. - You're right.
- We never said these things before. - We met on the number 725 bus.
- Haha and Ji Hyo will go now. - I have nothing to say to her.
(Up next are Ji Hyo and Haha.)
- It's Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo is...
the host of today's episode.
- That's right. - Ji Hyo.
Do you remember when we used to be in a love triangle?
That's such a long time ago.
You don't seem to remember. You, Gary, and I were in a love triangle.
(That was such a long time ago.)
Ji Hyo is...
so pretty.
(Haha made Gary nervous seven years ago.)
(Is it true that you have absolutely no feelings for Haha?)
(Yes.)
(It was a lie.)
In what ways is Haha better than me?
That's not correct. It's really not.
(There was a love triangle seven years ago.)
- That was seven years ago. - I...
(I...)
(You felt sorry about that?)
- It's been a long time since then. - I'm sorry...
I married Byul.
(I'm sorry I married Byul.)
Why would you be sorry?
- Why would you be sorry about that? - Why would you be sorry?
- Why would you be sorry? - If it was okay with you,
I could have made you my girlfriend.
This is funny.
Haha.
Do you remember when we went to Dongbaek Island for shooting?
- It was in the early days. - Right. We went there.
When we were there,
I was overzealous...
and wasn't communicating with other members.
I didn't know how to talk to other people. I had a closed mind.
At the end of the shooting,
I saw you and felt sorry.
When I said I was sorry...
(When she apologized to Haha...)
You said it was okay.
(He told her it was all right.)
- You're sorry? - I'm sorry.
I'm just really sorry.
(What happened in the past was still troubling her.)
You're apologizing for what happened seven years ago?
She can be strange like that.
(It's late, but I wanted to say it.)
Ji Hyo.
You have loyalty.
We didn't work out but...
- Stop that. - But really...
- What are you talking about? - We don't even remember that.
Anyway, Ji Hyo...
It must've been hard because of me.
- Why would she be? - What are you talking about?
Especially when I got married...
Ji Hyo.
Thanks for letting me go so that I could be happy.
(Thanks for letting me go so I can be happy.)
You do know that we used to be in a love triangle, right?
We were famous for that.
- This is what Haha did on "X-Man". - That's right.
- He was the playboy of "X-Man". - Right.
Okay. I'm thankful that...
Byul made you get it together.
It's too early to say he's gotten it all together.
Ji Hyo.
(Haha is sincere now.)
We guys can be insensitive.
We couldn't take care of you that well.
We're not good at that since we're all guys.
It must've been really hard on her.
Thank you for putting up with us...
and staying by our side for seven years.
- I love you. - It's not an easy thing to do.
(Thank you and I love you.)
(Ji Hyo has always been cheerful. We love you so much.)
Haha.
I'm a very lacking person.
I did try to become friends.
You stayed by my side for all the seven years.
Thank you and I love you.
I love you.
You do know that we used to be in a love triangle, right?
Stop it now.
Stop it. Gosh.
Yes. Let's have Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo go next.
- Yes. - Kwang Soo and I?
Kwang Soo will start crying soon.
- Kwang Soo can do that. - Not at all.
I saw him at the awards ceremony.
- He really is an actor. - He can start the waterworks fast.
For seven years,
even when you're a woman,
I grabbed you by the hair, kicked you, and punched you in the stomach.
(I'm sorry I did mean things to you.)
(He didn't go easy on her to make this show funny.)
(They were like realistic siblings.)
(He did get beaten up from time to time, though.)
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry about that, Ji Hyo.)
Don't be, Kwang Soo.
I felt more comfortable around you than the others,
and I behaved a bit carelessly towards you.
So...
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
(She apologizes as well.)
Six years ago,
you called me out and bought me bori gulbi.
When I moved, you bought me an electric fan.
At times, you sent me text messages...
to congratulate me...
and encourage me, so thank you.
Three years ago, when I left home after arguing with my mom...
What?
You said I could come to your place because I had nowhere to go.
Thank you for saying that.
Is this my cue to say I love her?
(Something seems very strange and inappropriate.)
Wait a minute.
Was something going on between you two?
How many people are in love with Ji Hyo?
(Is that why they fought often?)
(You get closer as you fight.)
(Were all those fights simply lovers' quarrels?)
- That's not it. - No.
I ended up not going to his place.
- You didn't go? - No, I didn't.
He told me to come.
I invited her because I was away from home for a shoot.
- She didn't come as I wasn't there. - Tell her you love her.
It felt strange back then, too.
Tell her you love her.
You're like a sister to me. I love you.
(Thank you for being a sister to me. I love you.)
I'm thankful that you're there for me,
(They're always there for each other.)
(Thank you and I love you.)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo love each other like family.)
- It's Seok Jin's turn with her. - Let's stop.
- Come here. - Seok Jin should have his turn.
He's the last one.
- You're the main member today. - This is the last time.
- You like it, don't you? - Don't be shy.
I don't like it.
Ji Hyo doesn't like it.
Ji Hyo, this is my opinion,
and the other members agree because we've talked about it a lot.
When other actresses are on the show,
we called you unlucky only for fun...
and said you're ugly.
You know we don't mean it, right?
It always bothered me.
We all talked about how sorry we felt towards you.
However, we never had the chance to bring it up to you.
I hope you know that we didn't mean it. I'm very sorry.
We were only playing.
You know that it was only to be funny, right?
(The members' favorite actress is Ji Hyo.)
You're the eldest one...
among the members.
(Ji Hyo wants to apologize to him.)
You aren't as young and healthy as us,
- I'm healthy enough. - but we...
I'm sorry for complaining that you're a slow runner...
- and that you're a handful. - I understand.
There's something I really want to thank you for.
You know exactly what I like to eat.
You sent dried herring twice to the other members.
But since you knew that I don't like dried herring,
you didn't send it to me the second time around.
Oh, my goodness.
Thank you for that.
- You know my taste in food. - Gosh.
- You said you didn't want it. - She sent it to everyone except me.
- You told her not to send you any. - I'm very thankful.
I didn't know you knew my taste in food.
My family really enjoyed the first dried herring you sent us.
I don't eat herring, but my family enjoyed it.
I wondered why you didn't send me the herring for the second time.
I realized that it was because I said I can't eat herring.
That's what I thought.
Thank you.
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
(Ji Hyo wants to thank Seok Jin.)
I'm still glad that you're there.
Thank you.
"Thank you for your existence."
Is that what you mean?
What?
- "Thank you for your existence." - She has nothing else to thank for.
For my existence?
- I hope you'll stay healthy. - I love you anyway.
(Please be healthy.)
All right.
Here's the last mission for Running Man Link Trip.
- It's "Great Minds Think Alike". - What's that?
For this mission, Ji Hyo and...
the remaining five members must choose the same thing.
You clear the mission when more than three people agree with Ji Hyo.
When their choice agrees with Ji Hyo's,
one member is exempted from the punishment.
If it's 4 members, 2 are exempted.
- If it's 5 members, 3 are exempted. - Okay.
- This isn't easy. - It's difficult.
First player, please come out.
- Shall I start? - Okay.
- Go ahead. - Are you starting?
Here's the first game.
In the count of 3, choose 1 of the 2 flags.
Our choices have to match, right?
It's a short game.
(Let's avoid the ice shower.)
One.
(They hope for the same flag.)
Two.
(Are we thinking about the same color?)
(Sometimes they argued, but they worked well as a team.)
(Will their seven years of teamwork prove itself?)
Two.
(The success rate is 50 percent.)
Three.
(Will they lift the same flag?)
(Ji Hyo and Seok Jin choose the same flag.)
They did it.
(That was too easy.)
- That was great. - They wouldn't choose the blue.
- This one was easy. - Choose what Ji Hyo would like.
The success rate is 50 percent.
- Choose what Ji Hyo would like. - That's right.
Choose what Ji Hyo would like.
Second player, please come out.
They're bungeoppang.
I like bungeoppang.
- Is it which part you eat first? - They look like real fish.
- Go ahead, Haha. - Wait.
- I'll play. - What about Kwang Soo?
It's okay.
You can go last.
Here's the same game.
Among the head, tail, and belly of bungeoppang,
choose a part and eat it.
- Eat it the way you usually do. - Of course.
(The success rate is one-third.)
(Will they choose the same part?)
One.
(Is it true that opposites attract?)
(The two showed great teamwork and strong friendship.)
One.
(They test their friendship.)
(Wait, they're holding different parts.)
Two.
(Eat it the way Ji Hyo would eat it.)
(Which part will they eat first?)
Three.
What happened?
- Please. - What happened?
(Ji Hyo bites the tail.)
- They chose the opposite. - Why did she eat the tail first?
Why would you eat the tail first?
I eat the tail first, too.
Isn't it because the tail is the crunchiest? It's crunchy.
- What's wrong with her? - Do you eat the tail first?
Most red beans are in the head.
- I know. - Calm down, Kwang Soo.
There are no red beans in the tail.
- Look. - Many people throw out the tail.
- Don't make her upset. - Stop it.
- I'm sorry. - It's not her fault.
- It's okay. - Thank you.
- I'm sorry. - Why do you eat bungeoppang then?
- I'm sorry. - You eat it for the red beans.
Why don't you eat plain batter instead?
- You haven't had your turn yet. - You need red beans.
Don't people say fish heads are the best part?
What are you talking about?
What did you say?
You know what I mean.
You said the wrong word.
- What? - There's a saying.
- What did he say? - You failed.
(Two more members must succeed.)
Third player, please come out.
- Who's going third? - I'll play.
- This is the last chance. - We may have to take an ice shower.
This is the third round.
With one hand, indicate a number.
Indicate a number.
One.
(There are five numbers you can indicate with a hand.)
(Ji Hyo and Haha are close like family.)
(After a love triangle, they continue to be close friends.)
(The success rate is one-fifth.)
One.
Two.
(Will they choose the same number?)
Three.
You're the best.
(They choose the same number.)
(The two are the best.)
They did it.
- I love you. - That was impressive, Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - We did it.
I thought you'd choose this.
I'm so nervous that my heart is beating so fast.
I'd have chosen this sign.
- The peace sign? - Yes.
Here's the next round.
- It's not easy. - Really?
(It's a difficult one.)
(No matter how hard the mission was, Ji Hyo and Jong Kook cleared it.)
(They make the strongest team.)
This is the fourth round.
Please open them.
What's that?
Open the lid.
- No way. - Gosh.
- This is too difficult. - It's impossible.
The success rate is too low.
Do we have to get the same number?
- You choose the number. - They choose the number?
Really? That's easy.
Okay.
This one is easy.
Let's start.
Wait, I'm not ready yet.
Show the number to the camera.
- Show it to the camera. - It's not the side facing you.
- One. - It's easy.
(Everyone expect them to choose the same number.)
Two.
(If they succeed, they save one more member from the ice shower.)
Three.
(Jong Kook chooses one.)
(How about Ji Hyo?)
(She also chooses one.)
Three.
(Both choose the same.)
Did we get it?
- That's right. - Did we get it?
- That's right. - We chose the same number.
We chose the same.
- Thank you. - We chose the same.
- Are we of one mind? - A moment ago,
she chose number one.
Gosh.
That's not it.
(Haha is so cute.)
Isn't it the six of us? I would have picked this.
- There's six of us. - You would have picked that, right?
- I would have done this. - I wasn't sure either.
I thought she might pick 6. She really liked "7012".
- One is the best. - No,
there wasn't 7 and I didn't think it'd be 6.
There was no seven.
- We just did this, too. - You got this one right...
but why did you eat the bungeoppang's tail first?
(It's a 7-year-old telepathy.)
How did you get it right?
I told you.
There's the last round left.
(It's Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo. How tough will the mission be?)
(They always quarrel but they take care of each other.)
(These two know each other very well.)
Bring in the question.
(We can do this, right?)
Is it one exemption so far?
- We have one exemption so far. - What's that?
Wait. No way. What's that?
- It looks difficult. - Eight?
You each have a calendar placed in front of you.
- In a count of three, - You know, right?
- flip to the same page. - You know, right?
(Here's the real test.)
You know right, Kwang Soo?
(You know that number, right?)
We've been doing the same all this time.
- One... - Hold on.
(His eyes move.)
You know it, right?
- I would have done this, too. - Of course.
One,
(Everybody is thinking of the same number.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Is this the number?)
(The answer to the 3rd mission was number 1.)
(The answer to the 4th mission was also number 1.)
(Is it January?)
(But there are 6 Running Man members.)
(There's also June.)
(What did Kwang Soo choose?)
(He picks July.)
(That was unexpected. What did Ji Hyo choose?)
Did they match?
(They both chose July.)
It's right.
It's seven.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo pass.)
- I was thinking of January. - Me, too.
Running Man started in July.
- No, there are 7 of us. - We have 7 people.
- That's right, too. - We have seven people.
(We did it, Kwang Soo.)
- I would have picked number one. - Me, too.
(They started in July 2010 and spent 7 years together.)
("7012" means that the 7 of them are together forever.)
(She starts tearing up.)
- I would have picked number one. - Me, too.
- Ji Hyo. - Because it's January.
(No, we'll be 7 until the end.)
But why did you eat the tail first?
(Still, their chemistry was unbelievable.)
- How did you guess this correctly? - It was close.
7012.
(The 7 of them are 1 forever.)
You have successfully completed this mission.
It's two people.
Two people have been exempted from the penalty.
(There will be 2 less people taking the shower.)
- We have 1 from before... - It's 1 of us 3.
- We have 1 from before... - Up until now,
three people have been exempted...
- so two will receive the penalty. - I see.
These people will be picked.
Should we head down there?
- Please head to the valley. - Sure.
Let's go.
If we got the bungeoppang question, it would have been three people.
If we had gotten it correct...
(How would they take a shower on a winter night?)
- At least we won't be alone. - We're still incredible.
- We got them right. - Turn on the hot water.
(Final penalty spot)
Hold onto this.
- Is that cold water? - Is this it?
Cold water is good for men.
(Why are they so shocked?)
(It's nature's gift...)
(created by the freezing wind.)
(It's a freezing, outdoor sauna.)
- This is unbelievable. - This is no joke.
(They better not get picked.)
- It looks so cold. - It looks so cold.
Look at the ice.
This is impossible.
It's pure ice.
This is a lottery.
Pick a spot and stand behind it.
Pick a spot.
(Ji Hyo will pick 2 people who will receive the penalty.)
My goodness. I don't know.
This is unbelievable.
I'm going to go with whatever's left. I can't choose.
I don't know.
(Ji Hyo will pull 2 ropes in random and pick 2 people.)
- I'll go with whatever's left. - I don't know.
- I'm going to change. - Let's go.
- Go. - I'll pick this one.
- I don't know. - You'll die in this weather.
- It's fine. - I can manage.
- We can change. - Of course.
(She feels the pressure.)
- Right? - I think it's me.
It's two from here, right?
- It is. - I don't think it's me.
- Who wants to switch? - I don't think it's me.
(Please...)
Me.
- Anything can happen. - Let's switch.
- Never mind. - Just once.
(He refuses Kwang Soo.)
- Let's just go. - Come on.
- Switch with me. - I don't feel good about switching.
Why? What's wrong with me?
I think two from the Unlucky Trio will be picked.
I don't have a good feeling about this.
(Would it be from the Unlucky Trio?)
It's up to Ji Hyo, right?
It's up to me?
You need to pull on the rope.
- Good luck. - This is driving me nuts.
(There are 5 ropes tangled inside the box. Her choices are random.)
- Ji Hyo. - There's a lot of anger in me.
I love you.
- Ji Hyo. - She won't know either.
I'll let you walk on the flowery path.
- This is driving me nuts. - I'm filled with anger.
Just pull one.
These are the last moments.
It's already cold.
I'm so cold.
- I'm cold. - How did you pick today?
We're deep in the mountains of Gangwon-do.
Ji Hyo will pull on the ropes now.
If you get picked, are you saved or do you get the penalty?
- You get the penalty. - Would our hands go up?
(Don't blame me.)
(Nobody knows who'll get picked.)
(Pick anything.)
- We know. - It's random.
- I love you. - Go for it.
(I just hope it's not me.)
- It's okay. - Thanks to you, we had meat...
- in Pyeongchang today. - Let's go.
(It's a difficult situation at the end of a happy trip.)
(Who will be the first one to enter the icy water?)
Who wants to take a rose petal bath...
in the new year?
Ji Hyo.
Who wants to take a rose petal bath?
(Me)
(Jae Seok gets picked.)
(She feels so bad.)
Ji Hyo, it started with the bungeoppang.
He got picked again. One is done.
That's good.
- What happens next? - That was so intense.
This is driving me nuts.
He was the first one to pick.
I had a bad feeling.
(A few minutes ago)
(Jae Seok was the first to pick.)
I can't choose.
(He thought today might be different but no.)
- I'll go. It's okay, Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo picked.
- She's picking. - It's okay. Pick one more person.
(I can't do this.)
- It'd be funny if it's Kwang Soo. - I agree.
(I don't want to be funny today.)
Please let it be Seok Jin or Kwang Soo.
- It's not me. - This is killing me.
- I don't think it's me. - Please.
- It's not me. - Let's make it funny.
- Go, Ji Hyo. - Pull hard.
Pick whatever.
Who wants to...
(Ji Hyo was the first host of Member's Week.)
(Who will be the last person to enter the icy water?)
Who wants to take a rose petal bath?
(Me?)
(Haha gets picked.)
(I'm sorry.)
(He's in despair.)
He wanted to switch with you.
I told you to switch with me.
(I should have switched with Kwang Soo.)
Pyeongchang has fresh air...
- and beautiful landscape. - That's right.
We hope that many people visit and enjoy their time.
- That's right. - Let's go,
- Haha. - It'd be funny if it was Kwang Soo.
What can you do?
- Let's go. - I'm sorry.
(It's time for icy water bath.)
Don't you have to wet your chest to protect your heart?
You should.
- I'm an expert in this. - Is that right?
Look at their feet.
(That's a fancy warm up.)
You're going in the water in the new year...
so I hope that you'll be healthy this year.
- That's for sure. - Health is of foremost importance.
Please be healthy.
- Be healthy, viewers. - Running Man will last forever.
It's time for Jae Seok to have his second child.
- Okay. That's great. - This will bring you good luck.
- Running Man, forever. - Let's do this.
There's ice.
(It will wake them up.)
They added ice.
- Hold on. - Let's check it out.
(They check the temperature.)
For goodness' sake.
(It's "Frozen" in the middle of winter.)
Hey.
(I hope you come out alive.)
- Is it that bad? - This is ice water.
(Come. I'll give you your second child.)
It's cold water.
(Let's go in.)
You're amazing.
Viewers, I wish you the best in the new year.
Happy New Year!
(Choking)
Are you all right?
- Are you all right? - What's wrong?
- Go in the warm water. - What's wrong with you?
Let's go in the rose petal water.
All right.
The flowery path.
Don't worry.
Viewers,
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
(The icy water will bring everyone luck.)
(Let's do this and bring in all the luck for Ji Hyo.)
(Let's go in on three.)
(Neither of them move.)
- You shouldn't jump. - We have our own timing.
- It's slippery. - Don't jump.
- We should just go in. - Just stand.
- One, two, - Two.
Three.
(Jae Seok dives in.)
(He's completely submerged.)
(Way to go, Jae Seok!)
(Haha goes in as well.)
(Ji Hyo, we will make you walk on the flowery road.)
(This trip isn't what I thought it was going to be.)
(I'm sorry, I'm thankful, and I love you.)
Happy New Year, viewers!
Happy New Year!
(He aggressively washes his face.)
(The trip of becoming one was a huge success.)
Wear this, Jae Seok.
- Here you go. - Get out of there.
(What will Jong Kook's wish be for next week?)
It's Running Man's New Year Project for 2017. It's Member's Week.
The second runner is...
Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
(Have you ever seen Jong Kook like this?)
I won't get upset no matter what you say to me.
(Jong Kook has never been shy like this before.)
(Jong Kook goes on a real date.)
(His brother is there.)
(His friends on Running Man are there, too.)
(Let's make Jong Kook get married.)
Where should he go next?
(How will this date end?)
(Next week's Member's Week, Marrying Jong Kook Off)