(2017 Running Man's Global Project)
(Dangerous tourist attractions picked by bloggers)
Jae Seok will pick...
(The dangerous tourist attraction has been decided.)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear in Japan)
(6 members were chosen to go to the Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(Before leaving the country,)
(they were given one last chance.)
What is this?
(Go to Mongolia and Russia,)
(and seize the last chance to be exempted.)
Only the two team leaders will get to choose...
who will be exempted from the penalty.
(Team Ji Hyo's mission is to find the descendants of Genghis Khan.)
(Team Jong Kook's mission is to catch 10 kinds of fish.)
(They travel the grassland and cross the sea.)
(They have started the real, survival battle.)
(If you want to avoid the Labyrinth, win the team leader's favor.)
(The 6 members try their best in flattering their team leader.)
(Who will be the one to grab the last chance?)
(And)
(They land on Japan at last.)
(Don't expect anything beforehand.)
(The extreme fear)
(Who will be lucky enough to avoid the Labyrinth?)
Please.
(Team Ji Hyo is still searching for Borjigit.)
How will we find the Borjigit family?
(Will they be able to get milk?)
We need to find them as soon as possible because...
- we... - It'll be dangerous when its dark.
We have to find them before it gets dark.
We're running out of time.
Let's say goodbye.
(It's time to say goodbye to them who have been so generous.)
- Bye! - Bye.
Goodbye.
(We hope you find the Borjigit family.)
Bye.
Goodbye.
(And they start their journey again.)
Borjigit...
I'm not sure if we can milk sheep within today.
(Will they be across this land?)
Amazing.
Look over there.
(Will they be across this land?)
- There's one. - Look over there.
(They find another ger.)
Let's look for them over there.
We will end up going to the Labyrinth if we can't find them.
Those cows look like they're from Korea.
Nonsense.
- They're not. - They aren't from Korea.
- Their color is like Korean cows. - They're Mongolian cows.
- Really. - Be careful not to get struck.
- Its horns are very sharp. - If you get struck by it,
- They're not like Korean cows. - you'll get hurt for certain.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Hello, ma'am.)
(Ignoring)
(She goes inside to prepare for the greeting.)
- Ma'am. - I hear a baby sound.
- She went in to treat us already. - Well...
Oh, no. We don't have much time left.
She's bringing something to treat us.
- Goodness. - Really?
Well... What was it?
- The right foot first? - Your right foot.
(Open the door with your left hand and enter with your right foot.)
She says to enjoy the aaruul.
Thank you.
- Aaruul? - Dried milk.
- Oh, that? - That...
Aaruul...
What is this?
(A few hours ago at the market)
Aaruul.
(They found a Mongolian, traditional snack.)
(The strong taste passed through their throats and noses.)
This is...
I heard...
the exact description...
of its taste from the native.
- It smells like a baby's puke... - Right.
after eating a milk product.
- Aaruul. Thank you. - Here.
- We tasted them before. - Try some.
(They encounter the taste of nature again.)
- Try. It's dried yogurt. - Dried yogurt.
(What will So Min think of it?)
What do you think?
It tastes like sheep.
Maybe because it's sheep milk.
The shapes are all different, but the taste is the same.
- Well, we should ask her now. - Let's ask.
- We don't have enough time. - Right.
Let's ask her.
Are you from the Borjigit tribe?
(Are they from the Borjigit tribe?)
No.
- She's not. - I see.
(She's not from the Borjigit tribe.)
- I see. - She's from a different tribe.
Do you know anyone from the tribe?
She can't understand Korean.
- She probably knows. - Borjigit.
Maybe there is.
(It seems like they're nearby.)
She says they live near here.
(They live around here.)
Sorry.
Is she saying we'll find their gers if we go straight?
Is it around 2km from here?
(He translates by feeling.)
Gosh, seriously.
- 2km away from here. - Am I right?
(It's 2km away from here.)
- Let him be the translator. - Goodness.
(He's now going for a global host.)
She said you might find them if we go downwards.
- See? - This is the best news yet.
But we don't have enough time.
- Let's go then. - We need to go.
- Thank you, ma'am. - Thank you.
(Thank you, ma'am.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It's getting dark.
(It's 5pm, and they're about to head for another villiage.)
Will you take pictures?
- I brought a camera to take photos. - All right.
(Mongolian nomads like photos...)
(as gifts since it's hard for them to print pictures.)
Look here.
(The day I showed off a little)
- Cheese. - You come here too.
- Sit down. - Sit.
1, 2, 3.
(5 Mongolian siblings)
- These dogs... - They're all outside.
Here.
Here. This is you.
(Will you remember us?)
- Bye. - Bye.
- The dog is in it too. - It's in it.
But it's facing the back.
(Give photos to nomads if you run into them.)
Can we even find a Borjigit within today?
I don't think we'll be able to milk sheep.
(The sun goes down in the endless plain.)
This is really a vast plain.
(Genghis Khan must have run across this plain 1,000 years ago.)
I'm reminded of these lyrics.
"I build a beautiful house on the green plain."
That looks like a movie set.
- It's so vast. - It's like a movie set.
- Goodness. - I hope we find them here.
(At 7pm, they find another ger.)
Look. They're there.
- We're running out of time. - Well...
(It may be their last shot.)
- The sun's setting. - If we can't find them here...
If the sun sets, we'll fail the mission.
Why are they so big?
They just poop anywhere.
(Walking past the warm poops)
- A calf is eating. - It's drinking its mother's milk.
- It's so cute. - Cute.
(Drinking)
Look. It has a facial mask on its face.
- Really. - My gosh.
- Right? - It does.
- Really. - I see dark patches under its eyes.
- It's wearing a facial mask. - A facial mask.
They're milking now.
- Where? - How do you say hello again?
(They find a shepherd family.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Nice to meet you.)
So cute.
- Look at the baby. - The baby's so cute.
(A smiling baby welcomes them.)
It's a girl.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
Hello.
- She's so cute. - We can't go near them.
- It's so cool. - She's so cute.
- Hello? - Hello.
- So cute. - She looks upset.
- She's shy. - Don't sit on the ground.
They're going inside.
(I'm too shy. I'm going inside.)
- No wonder. - They're milking a cow too.
All children are the same around the world.
It's so natural for them to sit on the ground.
- Is that so? - Sure. All of them.
- That red bag... - Excuse me.
Borjigit...
- Are you from the Borjigit tribe? - Borjigit?
(The entire family is wearing traditional clothes.)
(Can Team Ji Hyo make an end to their long journey in Mongolia?)
(Are they the descendants of Genghis Khan, the Borjigit tribe?)
(Yes, I'm from the Borjigit tribe.)
- What? - You are?
(Did they hear it right?)
Are you?
- You're a Borjigit? - Borjigit?
(He is the one they've been looking for.)
(It's their joyful and touching journey in Mongolia.)
- My goodness. - Borjigit.
We've finally met them.
My goodness.
- Awesome. - I was surprised.
Let's ask for their permission...
- and milk sheep. - Let's do that.
- All right. - I'm sorry,
but could you let us milk about 4L from your sheep?
It doesn't sound positive.
- They don't sound okay with it. - 4L may be too much.
(Their long answer doesn't seem so positive.)
They may be in some situation.
In the morning...
- They milked them already... - In the morning.
The lambs already had the milk.
They're not sure if you can milk that much.
- We're in trouble. - This is bad.
(It's not good.)
(Sorry, I didn't know you were coming.)
Will milking 4L be too hard?
Sheep usually have small amount of milk.
The lambs have already sucked on the milk this morning.
- It doesn't look promising. - We're in trouble.
- Usually, you can milk about... - How much?
200g of milk per sheep.
- 200g? - 4L is too much.
So it means we have to milk 20 sheep.
(4L)
(While they're all serious...)
(Struggling)
- This is bad. - What should we do?
(What is this familiar feeling that we're getting from him?)
He's wearing a Jordan t-shirt inside.
(Ta-da)
You can take the entire thing off.
Is it okay for us to milk your sheep?
Go ahead and do that.
- Thank you. - Thank you so much.
(They need to hurry before the sun sets.)
- We need to hurry. - It's not time for dinner.
(It's getting dark in Russia as well.)
(They've caught 6 different kinds of fish so far.)
(Pollack, flatfish, brittle star, zostera, sargassum, salpa)
I caught something.
Reel in the line.
(Even the captain seems surprised.)
- Did you catch something? - Yes.
(Did you catch something?)
(Team Russia must catch king crabs and 10 different types of seafood.)
Oh, it's a king crab.
- Really? - It's a king crab!
(Did Kwang Soo really catch a king crab?)
I caught a king crab!
(Surprised)
(Even experienced fishers don't get to catch king crabs often.)
(Did Kwang Soo really succeed?)
Gosh, what is this?
What is this?
It's not a king crab.
It's a new kind.
What is this?
(It's not a king crab.)
It has wings.
What's that? Is that a rockfish?
(The fish has wings.)
- Look at this. - Is that a monkfish?
Look at this.
It must be a monkfish.
The hook might break.
- We caught another kind. - It's a new kind.
(They've caught 7 types of seafood now.)
That's a difficult one to catch.
- Look at that. - It's so aggressive.
(They now have to catch king crabs and three more types of seafood.)
(But it's getting too dark.)
- Let's go! - When it gets darker,
it'll be hard to go back to the port.
Let's call it a day...
and try again tomorrow.
- Okay. - We have to go back now...
- for safety. - You're right.
We have no choice.
(They'll try again at 5am tomorrow to complete the mission.)
By the way, I have a question.
Does everyone have to be here tomorrow?
(Does everyone have to be here tomorrow?)
No, that's not necessary.
Let some of the members look around Russia.
It doesn't matter how many members go fishing.
- It doesn't? - No.
Then...
- Then... - Just two of us will go fishing.
- Just two of us will go fishing. - Okay.
The two highest-ranking members...
(The exempted members from work will be No. 1 and 2.)
- Wait. - Why are you number two?
- I caught four different kinds. - I caught so many pollacks.
I caught 4 out of 7 types.
Everyone worked hard today.
- Who didn't work hard today? - You're right.
- Can we play roulette? - Russian roulette?
As we're in Russia, it's Russian roulette.
Russian roulette!
- Russian roulette. - Let's do it.
- Tomorrow... - Amazing.
You're not going, right?
- I'm not going. - Come on.
(We need our leader.)
- Just do it. - Wait.
Jong Kook, we'll write your name in just two slots.
- Good. - Just two.
Just one.
Two will be more fun.
I think it'd be nice if you take more initiative.
As you're our boss...
Just two.
- Just 2. - Take just 2.
- Is it to decide who will not go? - How does it work?
- It's to decide who goes fishing. - The chosen ones will go fishing.
- The chosen ones will go fishing. - They'll go fishing.
- They'll go on the boat. - 1, 2, 3.
Here we go. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
All right. Russian roulette.
6, 7, 8, 9, and 10. This is it.
Just so you know, you'll go fishing at 5am tomorrow.
(2 members have to go fishing at 5am tomorrow.)
Haha!
(Haha is chosen.)
(Haha the Pollack Catcher will go.)
- Haha. - Haha.
Next.
- Here we go. - 5am.
Thank you!
I'll turn it three times.
1, 2, 3.
(The ranking does not matter in Russian roulette.)
(Who will go fishing tomorrow morning?)
There you go.
(Kwang Soo is chosen.)
(Kwang Soo is unlucky even in Russia.)
Oh, my.
- It's exactly what I predicted. - It's exactly what you predicted.
Haha and Kwang Soo will go fishing tomorrow morning.
(Haha and Kwang Soo have to catch king crabs.)
(It's getting late.)
This is the perfect time to have a candid conversation.
(They make wishes.)
Make a wish.
I hope Jong Kook will always be healthy.
(Haha is making pleasant comments for Jong Kook.)
All right. Se Chan.
I hope Jong Kook will recover from gout quickly.
All right. Kwang Soo.
I hope I won't be sent to Japan.
- What? - He's speaking to himself.
- Is that your wish? - Is it for your own sake?
For your own sake?
- Yes. - Whey can't we be one?
- It's for my own sake. - For your own sake?
- That's who you are. - See?
You've been hiding it for a long time, right?
To me, it seems like you're going to Japan as well.
(You think you're different? You're going to Japan as well.)
No. I'm going to succeed tomorrow.
Only you'll be sent to Japan.
I'll throw your king crabs back into the sea.
I'll eat your king crabs as soon as you catch them.
(The competition will be fierce tomorrow.)
Jong Kook, can you say something?
- Say something. - I really hope...
we'll complete our mission tomorrow...
so that only one of you...
will have to go to Japan.
It'll be so hard to choose one.
- That's right. - I know.
It's such a difficult decision. You guys have just one goal.
I have to choose one among you three. It's been torturing me.
- You must be so stressed out. - Do you understand me?
- Do you understand me? - We do.
Right? Who is suffering the most among us?
- You. - It's me.
It's so difficult.
I suffer even more watching you.
I...
It's true.
Just laugh instead.
(I must cry.)
I understand how you'd be feeling.
- You do? - Yes, it's so painful.
I'm crying for the first time...
since the award ceremony.
(They teased him for crying at the award ceremony.)
Jong Kook.
I'm seriously shedding tears right now.
(I'm seriously shedding tears right now.)
(He's shedding tears.)
- How did you do that? - How did you do that?
Jong Kook, I know how you're feeling.
- I'm getting scared. - How did you do that?
These tears are speaking for me.
What Kwang Soo is shedding is just crocodile tears.
- No matter how hard he tries... - Unbelievable.
Jong Kook, I'll...
- Jong Kook... - Se Chan.
Let me just go to Japan.
- No, I can't. - I'll just go.
- No. - Let me go to Japan.
- Look at him. - It's been hard for you, right?
- No. - Just let me go to Japan.
It's been hard for you, right?
(All of a sudden)
(It's hard to watch Haha.)
It's been so hard for you, right?
(I'm sad.)
- Look at Kwang Soo. - Look at him.
You cry often.
Jong Kook, it's been hard for you, right?
You guys understand me.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
(The night in Vladivostok is filled with gratitude.)
Thank you so much for today.
We haven't booked hotels yet.
- Can you ask the captain? - Can you ask him?
We should find a place near here.
Do you know any hotels around here?
(For the fishing tomorrow morning, they should find a place nearby.)
He'll call his daughter...
so that we can stay at their summer house.
- His daughter? - Really?
Does he have a daughter?
Thank you.
- What should we do? - Thank you.
- Really? - He has a daughter?
Yes, I have a daughter.
- Yes, he has a daughter. - How old is she?
(There he goes again.)
- She's 24. - He says she's 24.
Is she married?
- What are you doing? - No. Wait.
- It's just that... - What are you doing?
I want to know about her before I meet her.
- She's not married. - He says she's not married.
- Does she have a boyfriend? - Hey.
It's just...
- We should know about her. - Fine.
That's enough.
Tell him I'm 33. I'm not so much older than her.
(Nervous)
Please apologize on my behalf for any mistakes I might have made.
(Please apologize on my behalf for any mistakes I might have made.)
(With the surprise turn of events, Kwang Soo's heart is fluttering.)
- I can't believe this. - Kwang Soo's getting excited.
He looks nervous.
(I failed to find king crabs, but I might find love tonight.)
He'll soon meet her.
(My Russian love,)
(here I come.)
She's beautiful.
- Hello. - Hello.
Come on in.
(Kwang Soo is smiling.)
Sit here.
(Kwang Soo is tense.)
Can you ask her about her first impression of Kwang Soo?
(How is her first impression of Kwang Soo?)
She thinks you're handsome.
(Look at you.)
- Look her in the eye. - What are you doing?
Look her in the eye.
(What is going on here?)
He fell in love in Russia.
(Sighing)
- She's... - She wants to take a picture.
Does she want to take a picture?
(Great)
A photo with a star.
(We Got Married)
(Friendly)
It looks nice.
Can you ask her about her plans for tomorrow?
I have no plans.
She's free tomorrow.
We have to...
Se Chan and I have to go fishing tomorrow.
Go fishing tomorrow.
Me? Kwang Soo, do you want us to help you?
Do you want us to help you?
Do you want to go on a date with her? Then I'll help you.
- Then I'll help you. - Kwang Soo looks so happy now.
Can she go sightseeing tomorrow with him?
I want to go to places that couples go to on a date.
(Today, he's not a hopeless romantic.)
(Kwang Soo will be a guy in love.)
(It seems something might be there between Kwang Soo and her.)
Okay, Kwang Soo. I'll help you. Don't forget I helped you. Okay?
- Congratulations. - You must not forget about today.
(At this time, it seems the captain has something to say.)
He said there's no need for you to marry her.
(Don't even think about marrying her. He gives a warning in advance.)
- Oh, no. - He's cool.
(Goodness, you are so funny.)
He said you can only go for a walk with her.
All right. I understand.
(Thanks to Se Chan, Kwang Soo has a date with Dasha.)
- Hello. - Hi. You're already here.
(It's time to go sightseeing with Dasha.)
You two should sit in the front. I'll take the back seat.
There you go. Hey, get off first.
Let me.
Jong Kook.
(Thank you. I will make sure to return the favor.)
(Kwang Soo, good luck.)
(Smiling)
Here you go, Dasha.
(He offers her juice.)
Jong Kook, here you go.
What is it?
(She talks abruptly.)
I like your sunglasses.
- Really? - Gosh.
Thank you.
I have sunglasses too.
Have you been to Korea before?
- Yes. - Really?
Yes, I've been to Seoul.
How many times have you been to Seoul?
- Four days. - Four days? Oh, I see.
It was a short trip.
(He's the only one studying her responses.)
(Dasha laughs.)
I went to clubs.
Clubs? Great.
(He laughs too.)
Right. It'll take about 40 minutes.
Are you a student?
No, I work.
Oh, you have a job?
(Gosh, I don't have the faintest idea what they are talking about.)
Have you been to a lot of different countries?
Like Korea?
(Drinking)
(Unintentionally, he becomes a man of few words.)
You should sit in front.
No.
Dasha's head is about to be turned this way permanently.
(Dasha naturally looks back.)
I think I am not the one on a date.
- No. - Se Chan and I...
- I just thought... - can't speak the language.
we should keep the conversation going.
- Okay. - Ask her questions.
(I have to get close to Dasha.)
(They arrive at the observatory on Eagle's Nest Hill.)
The view is great here.
Goodness. This is pretty. It's so beautiful.
Don't you love that kind of antique buildings?
(They start talking in English.)
Wasn't that built a long time ago? That one too.
- It was. - Great.
(Next to a couple, there's a tall tourist.)
(He pretends not to care.)
- But the view here is spectacular. - What?
It's a picturesque scenery.
(Kwang Soo, good luck.)
(I like guys whom I can talk to more than quiet guys.)
(Looking around)
(Hold on. This isn't going according to my plan.)
- Really? - Yes. I see.
There are a lot of rocks...
on the wall and everywhere.
They keep talking in English from the start. I don't know why.
Kwang Soo.
She only looks at Jong Kook.
(Now, he has become a telephone pole.)
- Oh, yes. You're right. - Right?
You are Russian. I thought you didn't know.
- It's strange. - Yes.
- Shall we go to that side? - Sure. Let's go.
But this is...
I didn't know this kind of place existed.
(Kwang Soo wants to fall in love today more than ever.)
(They arrive at a maritime park.)
This is the street of the youth.
They talk while they take a walk.
(There are many affectionate couples.)
- Look at the boats. - This is a place for a date.
You are right.
(This is my chance.)
- Are you enjoying this? - Sorry?
- Do you like it here? - Yes.
It doesn't smell here.
(Sighing)
- No? - I go to the seaside all the time.
- Really? - Yes.
I think the cameramen are only filming them.
Don't forget that I am here as well.
At least you should film me.
(I can't give up not just yet.)
But this is such a nice view.
Oh, I've seen this before.
(Goodness, look at that.)
(She can't hear Kwang Soo.)
We are just trying to...
- I just said something. - Oh, right.
(He's getting angry.)
- I've seen there before. - Do you want to ride it?
(Can't you hear me?)
Do you want to? Do you want to ride?
Let's ride this. Have you ever tried this before?
(Jong Kook and Dasha have never ridden Segway before.)
Do you want to ride it?
Yes, Jong Kook.
I am going to show her what I've got.
(All right. I'm going to show you my charm.)
You have to put both of your feet on it. That's it.
No, you have to lift your heel.
(He starts showing off his charm.)
How do you ride this?
- Try it. Try. - You can do it.
- Ladies first. - Come on.
(What is Kwang Soo doing next to them?)
What do I do?
What should I do?
(Dasha is busy learning how to ride it.)
Wait. She doesn't even pay the slightest attention to me.
- Lean forward. - What should I do?
- Forward. Okay. - How do I stop this?
(Everyone ignores him.)
How do I stop this?
Turn. Turn right.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, they are getting closer.)
(Laughing)
Gosh, what a pretty couple.
Gosh, this is fun.
(While they are filming "We Got Marred",)
- Can you turn me facing this way? - Okay.
(he is filming "I Live Alone".)
- Are you okay? - I'm ready.
I'm ready.
(I know that phrase.)
(I've been ready.)
Kwang Soo.
This is nice.
Good.
(I should leave them alone.)
Perhaps, we can have a competition?
Oh, no. Not in here.
(Kwang Soo starts filming "I Live Alone".)
Do you want to go faster?
What am I so slow?
(He's frustrated.)
(As time passes,)
(they are getting further away from Kwang Soo.)
(I can't let this be. I should start speeding up now.)
(Falling)
Kwang Soo. You fell.
What happened?
(That's all right. It didn't look like I fell.)
He fell.
(Kwang Soo brings them smiles.)
Hey, did you fall?
- No, I didn't. - Hey.
I didn't fall.
How?
- How could you fall? - No, I didn't fall.
- What? - I didn't fall.
- You fell. - Sorry?
- You fell. - No,
- I didn't fall. - What are you doing?
- Sorry? - What did you do?
- Go. Just move on. - What?
Move on.
- You fell though. - I was admiring the view.
What is this?
What kind of boat is it?
- What kind of bat is it? - He drives me crazy.
Be careful. Look at your palm.
Let me see your hands.
- I said I didn't fall. - You...
(He can't grab the handle.)
Goodness. All right. Get on it then.
Go.
(Staggering)
- Go. You should go first. - Go.
- Hurry. - Come on.
When you push it with your heels, it moves forward.
Push it.
I wasn't supposed to push it with my hands?
You can do that. When you push it lightly... Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - What do I do?
- Kwang Soo. - It's not working.
Push it forward. Move your feet forward.
Move your feet forward.
(Kwang Soo moves away from them.)
This is...
sort of similar to Santa Monica in LA.
(The street is filled with antique buildings.)
The street is well decorated.
It's pretty.
Goodness, this view is so pretty. This is amazing.
Isn't this pretty?
- I think that must be the place. - This one?
- This is the one. - Okay.
(They arrive at a restaurant Dasha recommended.)
It looks delicious.
(The authentic, Russian restaurant comforts Kwang Soo's mind and body.)
The food is already ready? Really?
(Our order must be out already.)
- It's fast. - It came out really fast.
- I see. - Is this the pancake?
(Dasha ordered them blini which is a typical, Russian snack food.)
It looks like a pancake. Let's try it.
(The dough is made with mixture of buckwheat flour and flour.)
(He takes a bite.)
This is delicious.
- This one is tastier. - Isn't it delicious?
It's for you.
This one is for me.
(Let me pay you some attention.)
(You are making my heart race.)
How is fishing going? Did they catch a king crab?
If they succeed in catching a king crab,
you should remember the memories we made today.
- It's just that... - Yes?
I think it would greatly hurt my feelings.
You and I spent a whole day together in Russia.
If I had to choose only one member,
which member should it be?
The newbie?
(Jong Kook puts out feelers.)
Don't you think it's only fair that he goes?
I don't know. I'm still thinking about it. I don't know what to do.
I thought that if there were sheep, milking them wouldn't be a problem.
Nomads go to bed around 9pm.
Okay. So what?
- Right now, it's 7:45pm. - Right.
- You have to finish before 9pm. - We can only milk them until 9pm?
- Yes. - Are you serious?
Things are different from what we expected.
- I'm sorry, but... - I was...
- just informed as well. - There's no milk left though.
- There is no milk left. - They were out with their babies.
- This is too much. - Think about it.
They would care more about their babies than us.
In that case, we will bring down the amount to 2L.
- 2L? Please do that. - Please do that.
Admit your failure if you don't get 2L of milk before 9pm.
- Let's go. - We can't see after sunset.
- Let's do this in an hour. - We need to go.
This is a disaster.
- This is a disaster. - I know.
There is no milk.
- Sheep are next to the goats. - There are here.
- How cute! - My goodness.
- They look like Oreos, Ji Hyo. - They are next to the goats.
Look at them.
How fascinating!
My goodness.
- Will we be able to milk them? - How fascinating!
- I don't know if I can do it. - They are scary.
- How cute! - Which ones are females?
I can't differentiate them, let alone milk them.
That baby isn't scared of them.
- That baby isn't scared of them. - The sheep are running away.
They are running away. They must find us scary.
(Let's play together.)
- They find the baby scary. - Are you okay?
Baby.
Are you okay?
She didn't even bat an eye.
I can't believe it.
- They won't stand next to her. - Seriously.
- The sheep avoid the baby. - It's fascinating.
They are looking for a lamb...
because sheep only give milk when their babies suck.
How can you expect us to do this task?
That's why they are looking for a lamb.
They found it.
- It's fascinating. - It's sucking.
(We thought we could simply milk the sheep.)
We can't do this.
- We can't do this. - It's impossible.
You jerk.
- It's an impossible mission. - Give us something we can do.
You should give us a mission we can complete in Mongolia.
This is ridiculous.
It's coming out.
That's not a lot.
(Milk comes out after a lamb sucks.)
Milk only comes out after a lamb sucks.
That's right.
(Is that all?)
- That's not a lot. - There is no milk.
For goodness' sake.
- Even an expert got a small amount. - Look at that.
- Look at this. - It's a small amount.
She got this much from four sheep.
- This is too much. - This is an impossible task.
Even if we milk 300 sheep, it won't be enough.
Then I will bring down the amount to 1L.
- 1L? - Get 1L before 9pm.
Fill this container.
- This is impossible. - I can't compromise further.
(They must get 1L of milk.)
In that case,
let's take turns in milking the sheep.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo have scissors, and Seok Jin and So Min have paper.)
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo lose.)
- We will take turns anyway. - You are right.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok has scissors, and Ji Hyo has paper.)
- Get a lot of milk. - Okay.
Get a lot of milk.
I don't know if we will succeed.
It's impossible.
(It seems like an impossible mission.)
- Sheep. - She is catching one.
Get to work.
The sun is setting.
- Sir, what should I do? - This is a disaster.
I will put this in the back.
(She starts to milk the sheep without hesitation.)
Thank goodness other sheep aren't coming near.
You're right.
I need to squeeze its udders with force.
(Crying)
(She lacks time and experience. Will she succeed in milking?)
- Milk is coming out. - Really?
(Milk is coming out.)
Is it a lot?
Milk is coming out.
Really? Is it a lot?
- The sun is setting. - We might be able to do this.
We might be able to do this.
(Will we avoid going to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear?)
I am scared.
(You can do this, Ji Hyo.)
(They came to the grassland for milk.)
(Ji Hyo makes leaps in the task.)
- Is it coming out well? - Yes.
- How much do you have? - Right now...
Let's see it.
How much do you have? Let's see it.
You need to squeeze hard.
Do you need to put force into it?
- You got a lot of milk. - You got a lot of milk.
We might be able to do this.
- Go in. - I will go in now.
My goodness, I am not good with something like this.
It looks like they are playing a leap frog game.
Let's go over there.
It won't kick me, will it?
I must squeeze hard.
I am sorry, guys.
Listen. We will leave after we get 1L of your milk.
I am sorry.
I am sorry. Stay still.
Where are they?
(I can't look.)
- Jae Seok, - Find them on your own.
put your hands in like this.
You need to squeeze...
- like this. - Like this?
Put your hands in like this.
Jae Seok, you will get the hang of it.
(My goodness.)
- I know how it feels. - I know how it feels too.
- Squeeze like this. - I can't do this.
- Jae Seok. - I know how it feels.
- I don't think I can do this. - Jae Seok, hurry up.
Do you want to go to Japan?
We don't have much time.
- Hurry up. We don't have much time. - I don't think I can do this.
- Hurry up. - We don't have much time.
They are too warm.
Squeeze like this.
(My goodness.)
(I really can't do this.)
- Milk won't come out. - Let me try.
- For goodness' sake. - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo, you should do it. - I don't think I can do this.
(Ji Hyo, please do it for me.)
- Is it coming out? - No, it's not.
I guess it's not coming out.
(It's too bad that milk isn't coming out.)
It's not coming out.
- My goodness. - They came out.
(The sheep attempt to escape.)
What should we do?
They escaped. What should we do?
They came out.
- They are running away. - What should we do?
Gosh, I can't believe them.
Don't run away.
For goodness' sake.
- Don't run away. - Hey, hey, hey.
They are running away further.
- Move that way. - This is a disaster.
- All right. - Move that way.
(Let's use tactic 1 to chase the sheep.)
Go back into the fence.
- Go that way. - Go back into the fence.
Run towards them.
- My goodness. - That's not the right direction.
(We refuse to be caught.)
Don't go that way.
(Come back, sheep.)
This is a disaster.
(While the sheep are moving further away...)
- This is a disaster. - Where are they?
(The sun sets, and the mission continues.)
Okay, okay.
(Let me give you this instead of milk.)
(Laughing)
(It looks like the sheep exerted too much force.)
My goodness.
It pooped.
(She now has something she doesn't need.)
Give me milk, give me milk
Come here.
(It sounds like a spell for milk.)
I just need one.
Please.
Give me milk, give me milk
There is no milk.
The clock is ticking.
You liar! There is no milk.
These sheep don't have milk.
This is "The Silence of the Lambs".
We should have come in the morning. This is ridiculous.
- I didn't expect this. - These sheep don't have milk.
Milk isn't coming out.
(No matter how hard she squeezes, milk doesn't come out.)
There is no milk.
Is milk coming out?
(Dripping)
This is bad.
- This is impossible. - The sun is setting. This is bad.
I thought...
milking sheep would be easy once we find the nomads.
This is driving me crazy.
(It's an unexpected hardship.)
What should we do? What time is it right now?
- It's 8:20pm. - 8:20pm?
The sheep go to sleep at 8:30pm.
The nomads will leave for dinner.
(The Borjigit couple will leave for dinner at 8:30pm.)
There is no milk.
(She approaches them carefully. Is something the matter?)
What?
We need a translator.
(What is the message she relayed?)
She is suggesting that you have dinner with them.
Ma'am...
She is suggesting that you have dinner.
I know. She is suggesting that we have dinner instead.
That means we will go to the Labyrinth.
(When you think it's late, the truth is, it's really late.)
My goodness.
- We really need milk. - We can't give up.
We really need milk.
It was a struggle to come to Mongolia.
We should have come here earlier.
- Everyone. - Come on, staff.
- You threw shoes upon your arrival. - Right.
- You got this mission. - Right.
- Right? - Right.
We went to a Korean restaurant as you wanted.
It's an impossible mission since there is no milk.
There is no milk. It ran out.
Seriously.
Wait a minute.
You should bring back...
the four sheep before the sun sets.
I know what they look like.
I asked them earlier.
The locals can recognize their sheep and find them later.
I talked to them.
We reduced the amount from 4L to 2L.
You only got an incredibly small amount of milk.
The current time is 8:30pm.
You failed the mission.
(They fail the mission of milking sheep.)
Also...
The sheep are coming out.
What is going on?
They must be moving for dinner.
It's time for them to come out.
The other four sheep will join them.
(It's dinnertime for the sheep.)
They are looking for the four sheep.
They must be looking for the lost four.
(We will eat well and replenish our milk.)
They are really fast.
There is one.
Come here.
You might have some milk.
(Scared)
- Just in case. - You're going too far.
Who knows? It might have much milk.
If you come out...
- Look. - Look at it.
- What's wrong with her? - She's running away.
- It might... - If you come out...
- Look. - Look at it.
(She runs away before she gets caught.)
- What's wrong with her? - She's running away.
Maybe she heard you.
I'm sorry.
(They fail the mission by sending away the last sheep.)
- Gosh. - Thank you for the meal.
Wow, look at this.
(They're excited to have a Mongolian traditional dinner.)
- Are they sweet potatoes? - Just potatoes.
This must be it. Is this sheep meat?
That's sheep.
(Horhog: Sheep meat and vegetables are steamed with heated rocks.)
This must be the soup.
(It's the broth which is made from steaming the horhog.)
The meat.
(They finally get to taste the sheep meat.)
- How is it? - It's delicious.
- It's really good. - Join us.
- Is it good? - It's really good. Try.
- Isn't it because you like lambs? - No, it's really delicious.
They recommended having the meat with this sauce.
It's onions with salt.
It's like a sauce.
- Okay, I'll try. - Try it.
What is it?
(His small eyes open wide.)
- Try it. - It's amazing.
How should I eat it?
- Don't you think so? - It's good.
- It doesn't smell bad at all. - It tastes similar to what I had...
- while filming a traveling TV show. - It smells just a little bit.
- It doesn't smell bad. - I don't smell any odor.
I don't want to exaggerate, but it's really good.
- It's really good. - Thank you.
(The generous Borjigit father offers enough food...)
- It's really good. - Right?
(for the staff members too.)
- Try this. - My goodness.
The meat is so good.
(Everyone enjoys the dinner thanks to his kindness.)
- It'd be great if we had kimchi. - Right.
- So good. - I'm surprised.
- Isn't it good? - Yes.
- They cut the meat. - Kwon Ryeol.
Shouldn't you hold your camera?
Kwon Ryeol, Shouldn't you hold your camera?
(The night in Mongolia darkens with the warm dinner.)
I was too busy eating.
I don't think I can go.
(Today at dawn in Russia)
I'm so burdened now.
It's the night of fishermen.
(Haha and Se Chan prepare to go fishing.)
We don't know if we can catch any fish.
(Burdensome)
(With a determined mind to catch a king crab)
- I feel... - Yes?
Honestly, I have a good feeling today.
I hope we're lucky today.
It's the end of us if we can't...
- catch it at this early hour. - The end?
It'll be the same as yesterday then.
We'll have to buy tickets to Japan and fly over from here.
And Jong Kook, that punk...
- Don't get upset. - Why did he pick this mission?
Only if he had picked the pollack... I caught so many of them yesterday.
We can't do anything about it.
He thinks he can do anything he wants.
(They blame their leader.)
Why did he come here in the first place?
Even my senior comedians don't go that far.
- Right? - He's too strict.
Even the athletes don't go this far.
Their coaches don't discipline them like this.
We call it a team when the members support each other.
Let's teach him a lesson one day when we have a chance.
He must learn how scary the world is.
He's...
How should I put it?
(He thinks he's the only one existing in the world.)
- He thinks he's the only one. - Yes, in the world.
I'm so tired.
(He becomes tired after thinking shortly.)
(With their tired bodies,)
Get off.
I hope we get lucky today.
- We have to fish no matter what. - We have to catch.
(They have 3 kinds of fish and a king crab left to catch.)
(Will they catch them all and clear the mission?)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They depart with a determination.)
Do you remember the chance card...
Team Ji Hyo acquired last week?
(Chance Card?)
(Team Ji Hyo acquired a Chance Card during their previous mission.)
(It turned out to be the right to delete a fish type from the list.)
(They deleted flatfish from the list to hinder Team Jong Kook.)
- They deleted flatfish. - Okay.
- That's not a big deal. - It's not crucial.
We've got plenty.
I caught pollack and flatfish at once with one throw yesterday.
We let the baby flatfish go yesterday.
Flatfish is nothing.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's eat king crab noodles today. - Sure!
(They're determined to catch one.)
Just one. Just one is enough for us.
(Nothing matters as long as it's a king crab.)
I'd like just one king crab.
(Focusing entirely on his finger)
Okay, I caught one.
(Se Chan catches one from the start.)
Let it be flatfish.
Did I lose it?
(What will be their first catch?)
My gosh! Look!
What are they?
(He catches two big fish.)
- What is this? - It's monkfish.
(It's ganko and flatfish which have been deleted from their list.)
Congratulations!
- It's halibut! - Yes!
Awesome!
(Haha catches halibut.)
(He's the real fisherman.)
- Haha. - What?
What is this?
(Did you catch something again, my friend?)
Its color is weird.
(He catches something with an unfamiliar pattern.)
What is this?
Isn't this bream?
- What is this? - Isn't this bream?
- What is this? - It has striped patterns.
(It looks similar to flatfish, but has a different pattern.)
- We caught all 10 kinds of fish. - What is this?
It's different from flatfish.
What is that?
- Is it a different kind? - Yes, it's different.
(- Is it a different kind? - Yes, it's different.)
You did it, Se Chan!
(Se Chan succeeds to catch the 10th kind of fish.)
We accept it as the 10th kind.
(It's accepted as the 10th kind.)
(They succeed in catching 10 kinds of fish.)
- We're awesome. - Right.
("Fishing Is the Easiest", Russia Special)
If you catch a king crab,
you will clear the mission.
We can't be staying here for a long time due to the flight time.
We'll check the fishing rods one last time.
Shall I pull out king crabs now?
(They're hoping for the best with the fishing rods.)
Please.
- Let's start with this and move on. - All right.
Okay.
(They check the first rod.)
Please.
In Russia, king crab...
It is or isn't here.
- Not here. - I see.
- The first rod is a failure. - A failure.
(The second rod is a failure too.)
A miracle will happen.
I hope for a miracle.
(The third rod is a failure too.)
(They want a king crab desperately.)
Wait, I can feel something.
(He feels something different.)
(It's the last rod.)
(Did he catch a king crab?)
It's our last hope, Se Chan.
(Nothing is caught.)
- Nothing? - We didn't catch it.
Nothing.
(It was their last hope.)
(They're disappointed that a king crab didn't show up until the end.)
It was close, but you couldn't catch a king crab.
So you failed the mission.
(They fail the mission.)
I can't believe this.
We were so close.
(It was so close.)
(He feels bad.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you for your help, captain.)
- Let's go. - Okay.
- I feel bad. - Gosh, seriously.
(They were so close to clearing the mission.)
I won't be able to eat king crabs for a while.
- It doesn't feel satisfying. - It doesn't.
Only if we had caught it, everything would've gone as we wanted.
- Right. - Everything.
Hey, so many crabs are here.
(Hey, so many crabs are here.)
(They find crabs near the port.)
(Catch us if you can.)
- It's here. - I found them.
- We need a net. - A scoop net.
We must catch this.
(It was so hard to find any, but they run into the crabs here.)
We still have a chance.
It's our one last chance.
But this net is not knitted tightly.
Wait. Hold on.
- Where is it? - Here.
Gosh, how should we catch it?
(They can't miss this chance.)
- It's our last chance. - Yes.
- What should I do? - Should we just scrape it up?
(It's really a failure if they miss this chance.)
(Will they catch it?)
What do we do? Hold on.
Hold on.
I'll go get a stick. Hold on.
(You can't catch it with just a net.)
Hold on.
(Dropping)
I can't take this any longer. This is so frustrating.
(Preparing)
(He takes his jumper off and prepares to go in the water.)
Are you going in?
We can't catch it otherwise.
- Can you go in? - I can't catch it if I don't go in.
(He's willing to sacrifice himself...)
(if at least one of them can be saved.)
- It's our last chance. - Yes.
(He's willing to sacrifice himself if one of them can be saved.)
(Going into the Russian sea)
Goodness. I can feel the water soaking up.
There we go.
(They show perfect teamwork by helping each other.)
Okay.
- Do you see it? - Yes.
It's here.
- Get me the gloves. - The gloves.
Hold on.
(They put on the gloves to catch it.)
Here's a king crab. Here. I'll do it.
That's it!
It's a king crab!
(Are you sure it's a king crab?)
- Here. - You actually caught one.
- Let me see. - We caught it!
Gosh.
Don't laugh!
(They finally catch a king crab.)
It is a king crab.
- It is a king crab. - What happened?
How's that a king crab?
When it grows, it becomes a king crab.
What?
We caught a king crab.
- Please make a judgment. - Please make a judgment.
We're here to find crabs. It's a crab anyway.
You've caught 10 different types of seafood.
- Yes. - However,
you failed to catch king crabs.
However,
- you caught a small crab. - It's a medium crab.
We'll have to think if it counts as a king crab.
We'll let you know the result...
at the next shooting.
(What will happen to Team Jong Kook?)
(A few days later, at Incheon International Airport)
(It's finally the Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear day.)
- Well... - I don't feel so good.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
I can't believe we're actually going.
Kwang Soo, here.
(No-looking passes are popular at airports these days.)
Gosh.
Why did you pass me your luggage without even looking at me?
- Just hold it. - What?
- Keep an eye on my luggage. - Okay.
- Do you want to go in? - No.
- Do you want to? - No.
- Where is Jong Kook going? - What do you mean?
It's just an overnight trip.
You never know what will happen.
- Oh, my. - The funny thing is,
he probably has 30 pairs of shorts in it.
30 pairs of shorts.
- 30 pairs of shorts. - That's accurate.
Hey.
He's making fun of you.
Se Chan.
- You're hiding there. - He's making fun of you.
It's not decided yet.
- Se Chan. - Jong Kook.
- It's a no-looking pass. - Se Chan.
- Be careful. - It's so funny.
- Be careful. - Okay.
Seok Jin, where is all your stuff?
Last time, you guys didn't bring so much stuff.
That's why.
- Everyone has so much today. - You should have brought more.
I'm using the bag from our Mongolia trip.
- Really? - Did you steal it?
- Did you steal it? - No.
You should return it.
- Return it. - Return it.
- It was in the car. - Stop stealing stuff.
She's a famous thief in Yeonnam-dong.
- It's true. - It's true.
(So Min is a famous thief in Yeonnam-dong.)
- Tell them the story. - She's a thief?
We had a drink together the other night.
- She has sticky fingers. - Really?
That's not true.
It's Kwang Soo's fault.
These two have a problem.
(You'll find out what happened among them soon.)
As the finale of the Global Project,
we'll visit Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear)
(We're finally going.)
We finally got our visas today.
My family has been wondering.
- Why you're not going? - Exactly.
They wonder why I'm still not possessed.
My family has been wondering.
Before we leave, let me announce the mission result...
which will determine who will be excluded from the visit.
(The results are announced.)
(If the mission has been completed, the team leader will exclude 2.)
(Who will visit Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear?)
Team Russia's result is not clear.
- That's right. - We completed the mission.
You said you'd let us know the result today.
- I'll announce it now. - Okay.
First, Team Mongolia...
failed to complete their mission to milk sheep.
(Team Mongolia failed to complete their mission.)
The thing is, the lambs drank all the milk that morning.
- You should have squeezed it out. - They drank all the milk.
- We squeezed the udders until... - It didn't work.
Let's stop talking about udders already!
(Those darn udders!)
I'm sick of hearing about udders.
- What happened? - Why?
Udders are beautiful.
- Stop it. - I'm sick of it.
Team Russia.
Jong Kook, Haha, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan...
were supposed to catch king crabs and 10 types of seafood.
Yes.
- We did it. - We did everything.
It's not clear.
You succeeded in catching 10 types of seafood.
- Yes. - Yes.
But...
(But?)
- The crab you caught at the end... - Yes.
- It was very hard to tell. - Yes.
So we consulted the Marine Biodiversity Institute of Korea.
- Really? - You did?
(They caught a crab right before the deadline.)
(This crab will...)
(determine their fate.)
- Really? - We found out what it is.
(They consulted a professional.)
It turned out not to be a king crab,
but an Asian shore crab.
(Did we fail?)
- An Asian shore crab? - It's not a king crab?
They failed.
However,
it's a type of crab anyway.
- So? - Really?
After a discussion,
we concluded that you completed half the mission.
Jong Kook can choose one person...
who will be excluded from the penalty.
(Just one member will be excluded.)
(Hurrying)
I'm sorry for mentioning about your shorts.
I'm sorry. I didn't know this would happen.
- Pass me your luggage! - No, pass it onto me.
You know how easily I get scared.
- Go away. - I'm so easily scared.
Go away.
I'm so unlucky.
I did my best.
Do I have to decide right now? I want to wait.
- Do I have to decide right now? - Please.
Jong Kook, please.
Your arms need to breathe.
Stretch my t-shirt.
- Please. - Stretch my t-shirt.
(Please)
Guys.
Do I have to choose one member right now?
Jong Kook will decide, among Haha, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan,
who will be excluded from the visit to the Labyrinth...
by hugging the member from behind.
This is hard.
Isn't it already decided? Hey, come here.
(Hey, come here.)
- It's over. - Why?
- It's over. - Seriously...
Stand over there.
Guys, stand over there.
Kwang Soo is...
He's...
- He doesn't have to do this. - It's a competition.
Isn't it already decided?
Here we go. This is not that important.
Jong Kook.
If you've made up your mind, choose one member now.
Please. Jong Kook, please.
It won't hurt to experience it once.
I did my best.
I have no regrets.
- Please. - Hey.
Please.
(Their fate is in Jong Kook's hands.)
(Is it Kwang Soo?)
(Is it Se Chan?)
(Or is it Haha?)
- Please. - Please.
- Hey. - Please.
(Is it Kwang Soo?)
(Is it Se Chan?)
(Or is it Haha?)
(Haha always ratted on the other members.)
(Se Chan has been thoughtfully taking care of Jong Kook.)
(Kwang Soo has found every opportunity to betray Jong Kook.)
(It's not easy to choose just one member.)
(It's such a difficult decision.)
(Who will Jong Kook exclude from the visit?)
Here we go. 1, 2, 3.
(The final decision)
(Whom will Jong Kook choose?)
(Turning)
(Haha is chosen.)
Three!
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo receive the honor of the Labyrinth.)
That was predictable.
(I'm safe.)
I'm safe.
Kwang Soo, why are you...
- What were you expecting? - What were you expecting?
- Seriously... - I made up my mind...
when we were leaving for Russia.
We knew that. Kwang Soo must not have known.
Only he did not.
You were worse than me.
(Jong Kook, you were the worst.)
- Me? - You.
- Are you talking about me? - Yes, you.
I see.
I'm talking about you, the tanned one.
All right.
When you enter the Labyrinth,
I'll be in there wearing scary makeup.
You think it's over?
Do we have no chance at all?
The five of you have to enter the Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
It's going to be so fun.
- Right? - Stay tuned.
- So Min. - Gosh.
You have to do it.
I'm a bit worried because there are five of us.
- What? - One will be left out.
The three of you look like the group Koyote.
(You guys look like a set.)
- Koyote? - You're Kim Jong Min.
- Koyote? - Is Kwang Soo Bbaek Ga?
- No. - He's Bbaek Ga.
He's Bbaek Ga.
We're Koyote 2017.
(Koyote 2017)
(I'm Shin Ji.)
You two are Yukgaksu.
Heung Bo is dumbfounded
- Do it. - What?
My goodness.
They're Green Area.
Green Area?
- Green Area. - Green Area.
- They're Soo and Jin. - Forever with you
This is not fun.
- Let's go. - I don't feel happy,
- so it's not fun. - Why do I feel depressed?
- Haha is too happy. - You never know.
(They will be receiving the penalty.)
(Narita Airport, Japan)
(Complaining)
It feels like spring.
(The weather is great, but they look concerned.)
We're on a trip, but I don't feel great.
Everybody, you have arrived in Japan.
I feel...
- heavy at heart. - I don't feel great either.
For those who have been exempted from penalty...
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo and Haha are exempt.)
- You'll be going to Yokohama. - What?
- Are we going to different places? - It's a beautiful port city.
Your expenses will be unlimited...
- No way. - Why?
(They can travel freely with no cap on expenses.)
- You can't do that. - Really?
(They get a map and a corporate card with no limit.)
(Yokohama Tour)
(It's a free tour without penalty or limit on expenses.)
(It's truly the best tour.)
- You can't do that. - We can go together.
(I'm sorry.)
(He provokes them.)
We're unlucky.
Have fun. I'll watch you on television.
It'll be funnier to go with you.
You're the main show.
(He provokes them more.)
Let's go!
- Yes! - They look so happy.
Come on in.
Look at Haha.
They look so happy.
I can't go. I can't.
I can't go to the Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
We're leaving.
(Laughing)
- Oh, dear. - My gosh.
Are we really going?
- Take me while I'm sitting. - I really...
- don't want to go. - This is unprecedented.
We have to go to the Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear...
- while... - Is that what it's called?
I have a stomachache.
Stop lying.
You're lying.
- No, Jae Seok. - Come on.
This is the finale of the Dangerous Trip...
we've been working towards for a long time.
(This is the final destination.)
(These five members will be celebrating the finale.)
You'll get in a car and head to...
Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear for your penalty.
However...
(However?)
However?
- There are five of you, right? - Yes.
You can't all go in together,
so it'll be 2 groups of 2 and 1 person by himself or herself.
We can't do one person.
(2 groups of 2 and 1 alone)
(You have to enter the Labyrinth alone?)
(It's too much to go in there by yourself.)
(Going in there will test your limits.)
Let's do 3 and 2. It's too scary to go by yourself.
- 1 person? - Just 1?
- Would you be okay, So Min? - Why would you say that?
- Is there another way? - Would you be okay, Kwang Soo?
No. Don't do that.
I was born in 1985. Don't do that.
How will you choose who goes alone?
On our way to the destination, there will be three rounds of missions.
It'll be me for certain.
The person who loses a mission...
will write their name on the roulette multiple times.
- Roulette? - It might be 4 or 5 times.
(They'll spin the roulette at the end to choose who goes alone.)
I'm actually confident with these people.
(It's the Unlucky Avengers.)
I don't know about others, but I can beat these people.
This is so close. I have no idea who will lose.
Watch me. I'll never lose.
To start off, write your name in a space each.
- This is driving me nuts. - I'm not so sure about this.
(Lee Kwang Soo, Jee Seok Jin)
I don't want to be next to Seok Jin.
(What will be the result of the roulette?)
- Let's go. - Let's see who's the worst.
- Let's go to the haunted house. - Let's go there...
Let's go there first. I heard they sell underwear,
- Okay. - so let's...
- Let's buy 20 each. - Let's just go.
If we end up needing extra underwear, please keep it a secret.
- Please edit it out. You have to. - Of course.
You five are united right now,
but there's a hidden mission.
(This is not the end.)
- There's a hidden mission. - What's that?
This is never-ending.
It's the longest labyrinth according to the Guinness Book of Records.
There are 15 ghosts in total.
Depending on Yokohama tour team's expenses,
more ghosts will be added.
(Ghosts will be added.)
(It'll be 1 ghost for every 20 dollars spent.)
You should have said that before they left.
They already left.
Why are you trying to make our lives harder?
- If it's for every 20 dollars... - We've been here in a while,
but we haven't enjoyed anything in Japan.
If they eat, it'll be 3 more ghosts for us.
What did we do so wrong?
(How could you add ghosts as if you're ordering food?)
This is driving me nuts.
Let's leave for Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
Let's go.
(They leave for Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
Thank you.
She's the only fan here to welcome us.
- Thank you. - She's a Japanese fan.
(Be careful. You'll end up crying.)
"You will cry?"
- Really? - Yes.
It's really, really scary.
(That Labyrinth is beyond frightening.)
- What do we do? - Are you part of our group?
- Did you recruit her? - No, not at all.
(She's a local fan who was worried.)
- Is it really scary? - Yes.
- It's really scary. - What do we do?
You might cry.
You think I'll cry?
You will.
(Be careful. You will cry.)
Oh, gosh. This is driving me nuts.
Bye.
(Please don't wet yourselves.)
It must be really scary.
I hate this.
I don't feel well.
What do I do now?
Let's just not go.
- Sure, let's go somewhere fun. - We can turn around from here.
- Sure. We'll do something else. - I didn't do anything wrong.
I'll try my best, Producer.
- I'll try my best. - Why are we even going?
I just don't want to go alone.
Wouldn't it be hard to go by yourself?
What now? What if I have to go in by myself?
I don't think I can do it.
(This is their instinct coming from 7 years of being on Running Man.)
This is driving me nuts.
(You can't go in there by yourself.)
How long does it take?
You must be hungry, right?
- Yes. - I'm hungry.
- There's a rest stop in 10 minutes. - Really?
You can eat.
I didn't know you'd feed us. Thank you.
- I like... - Food at rest stops are good.
- I'm trying to talk here. - Their food is good.
- I'm trying to talk. - Hey.
I can't even talk with you?
- Can't I say something? - We don't know what'll be edited.
- You don't know either. - Let's take turns.
Even if you go in pairs, who will it be safe to go with?
If you go in with either Seok Jin or Kwang Soo,
- you're dead. - That's the end.
It's better to go by yourself.
If I see a ghost, I'll hit you in the face and run away.
I'll hit you. I'm sorry.
He'll throw you to the ghost as a victim.
- He'll throw you. - I'm going to tell my mom.
Don't do that.
- I'm going to tell my mom. - Don't do that.
- Did you hear? - What?
- Kwang Soo slept over at So Min's. - He slept over.
(It's what the rumor says.)
- What? - He slept over at her place.
- Can you tell us about this? - Hey.
- You slept over at her place? - Tell us about it.
- That's not it. - You have to clarify yourself.
- Hey. - Why would you sleep over?
If you put it that way, you might get the wrong idea.
Let me say this then.
I won't think about it that way.
(He won't think about it in the wrong way.)
- Why not? - Well...
We are young, unmarried man and woman.
I'm not interested in what's between you guys.
- Why not? - But...
- why did you go to her place? - Why did you sleep over?
Did he sleep over while your parents were there?
Her brother was there too.
- Her brother is a bodybuilder. - He slept with my family.
You must be out of your mind.
Tell us about it.
We went out drinking with Se Chan and a producer,
and I fell asleep in my car.
I couldn't wake up so the chauffeur...
picked up the phone when So Min called me.
- He said you're not waking up. - He said I fell asleep...
and asked where she was. She said she was in Ilsan, so he went there.
She paid the driver.
She told me to sleep at her house where her parents were.
If I wasn't drunk, I would have said sorry and left but I was drunk,
so I asked if I could sleep over for the night.
(Can I sleep over?)
- This is... - I went upstairs...
He had a plan in mind.
This sounds too intentional.
- How? - The funny thing was...
that the chauffeur said Kwang Soo wasn't waking up,
but as soon as he got to my house, I called him and he woke up.
- Goodness. - No, I woke up midway.
- This isn't... - No way.
What are you talking about?
- So Min. - Yes?
That hurts.
- That's not it. - You...
- You need to... - That's not it.
- get hit. - No way.
- Why would I? Jae Seok. - Are you serious?
- No, that's not it. - Look at him.
I fell asleep and while I was sleeping,
- I felt somebody staring at me. - So?
I woke up,
and her dad was looking at me with the door slightly open.
(Who are you?)
He was staring at me while I was sleeping.
(There was a strange man sleeping at his house.)
I didn't know it was her dad in the beginning.
I was so shocked.
(Then So Min's dad said...)
I said, "Hello, sir. I'm sorry." Then he said,
"Can you come out and take a picture with me?"
(Can you come out and take a picture with me?)
We took a picture in the living room with his arm around me,
and I went home.
(We are another family. This is our Day 1.)
Let's eat first.
Let's eat first and think about it later.
- First place I'm going in Japan... - Let's think about it later.
is a rest stop.
What?
- What's that? - Have one each.
- One each? - You're giving us money.
Is it 10 dollars or 100?
- It's 100 dollars. - That's great.
- You're giving us 100 dollars each? - That's 100,000 won.
Why are you giving us so much?
Okay, everybody. Here's your first mission.
- What is it? - Your first mission here...
is called Your Turn.
(First mission is Your Turn.)
(What turn?)
- Your Turn? - It must be from "Your Name".
You'll be eating at the rest stop.
Please order something different from each other,
and the owner of the dish to come out last loses.
(Your name goes on the roulette if your food comes out last.)
I'm in trouble.
We have to order at the same time, right?
You can order whenever.
- We have to hurry. - If we...
Look at these guys.
(This was as predicted.)
You guys are so cheap.
(You must run to the rest stop first.)
(They were supposed to enjoy the atmosphere, but they just run.)
What's wrong with you? Why did you block me?
(They were supposed to enjoy the atmosphere but they just run.)
(Dashing)
Pick anything.
Order whatever. What's what?
(What's the vending machine for?)
Do we have to use a vending machine?
- Hold on. - My gosh.
This is it.
There's a separate vending machine for each restaurant.
It's per restaurant?
I don't know what this is.
(He doesn't know what he ordered.)
Where's this?
(Everything is in Japanese.)
What did I just order?
Quick? Quick?
(He starts speaking in Korean because he's in a hurry.)
Which one's fast?
- This? - Yes.
(Check him out.)
Which one's fast?
Fastest one. Hurry.
- Number 1 maybe. - Does number 1 take 2 minutes?
- 2 minutes. - 2 minutes. This one?
Okay.
(He chooses number 1 that's supposed to take 2 minutes.)
Number one.
Number one menu.
Hurry up, please. Hurry up. Please.
Excuse me.
Yes.
(We'll call your number. Please wait in your seat.)
(I'm Korean.)
(How are they talking to each other?)
Thank you.
Do you know what she said?
(What did she say?)
This is too intense.
Did you order, Jae Seok?
- What? - This wasn't what I wanted.
I don't know. I just pressed whatever.
They're going to say our number.
(Is this...)
(It's not yours.)
Sorry.
(When's mine coming out?)
I hope it comes out soon.
Thank you for waiting. Number 1 is ready.
Is it udon? It's udon.
Who ordered udon there?
Who ordered there?
(They've been waiting to be called. Who ordered udon there?)
Is it Jae Seok?
(I ordered from there.)
- Did yours come out? - Is it yours?
- I'm so jealous. - Did it come out?
His food came out.
(Is it Jae Seok's dish?)
- Thank you very much. - Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
(It's vermicelli, not udon, but he's still 1st place.)
I'm happy. I'm so happy.
So Min's food came out.
It came out.
(She actually picked something good.)
Thank you very much.
(She comes in 2nd place with a warm steak.)
Something came out. What is it?
- This? - Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
(He won't lose this round.)
Soy sauce? Thank you.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo are still waiting.)
(Where's Seok Jin's food that's supposed to take two minutes?)
(What about Kwang Soo who tried to communicate in Japanese?)
This is driving me nuts.
Hurry up, please.
(If your food comes out last, your name goes on the roulette.)
If your name gets picked, you'll be going to the Labyrinth alone.
The rest of you will be going in pairs.
(It's bad enough to go in pairs. Going by yourself is death.)
My goodness.
Thank you.
(Seok Jin comes in 4th place with stir-fried udon.)
(He just spreads it.)
Thank you.
(Thank you for the 2-minute udon.)
(4 of them get their meals.)
Did you get it?
What about Kwang Soo?
(His food is nowhere to be seen.)
Kwang Soo is the worst.
What did he order?
He can't help it.
Why is his taking so long?
(Enjoy your meal.)
When I watch Kwang Soo, I get energized.
Of course. I'm not even joking.
Watching him gives you a lot of energy.
(Kwang Soo is unlucky but modest. He's a good role model.)
(Thank to his noodles, he loses.)
Is he coming?
It's not even something amazing. Why did it take so long?
- You ordered noodles. - It was noodles.
It was noodles.
- It looks good. - It's because I kept on talking.
- It looks really good. - Eat first.
(It's greasy.)
This is really good. Try it.
It's a rest stop, but their food is really good.
(Before we cry, let's eat first.)
It's good.
- It's good, right? - Yes.
(This is a moment to relax before they go on the Dangerous Trip.)
Do you want to see it?
- It's so good. - Who ordered it?
Did you?
(It's still good.)
I'm happy you joined us because...
on Running Man, one of us always received the penalty.
Always?
Yes, it was strange.
- You two joined us. - Our chance of losing...
- went down significantly. - For sure.
- Welcome. - It would have been just us.
If you guys weren't here,
it would have been just us.
- That's right. - It would be us again.
- That's how it's been. - It would have been us again.
- It's always been that. - Always?
It's always been that.
- It was always us in jail. - Exactly.
- It's always been like this. - That's right.
Since you joined us, there's been more of us.
Who's the worst from you three?
- Him. - You don't think it's yourselves.
- You didn't pick yourself. - It's not me.
- You should pick. - It's either one of them.
- I'm a bit better. - I don't agree.
- Kwang Soo just lost. - Right.
I'm filling up another space, right?
This round was for four spaces.
(Sorry? What did you say?)
(Kwang Soo takes up one-sixth of the roulette in this mission.)
Wasn't it one space?
- It was 4 spaces. - It was 4?
That was close.
You're done, Kwang Soo.
We have a lot of money left.
- That's right. - There are a lot of spaces left.
Okay.
(Kwang Soo: 5, Others: 1 each)
Everybody, it's a long way there, so please buy some snacks.
There are so many things.
It's dried fish.
Dried fish.
I'm going to buy it all.
This peanut cookie looks good.
It's a bracelet. I want it.
Is this expensive? It's a bracelet.
Look.
It's 1,200 yen.
- That's 12 dollars, right? - Isn't that what Do Yeon likes?
- Yes, it's 12 dollars. - It's expensive, right?
It's not.
Can you get this for me?
(She's scared of going into the Labyrinth,)
(so you should give her a gift.)
Stop talking rubbish.
(He bursts her bubble.)
- Don't try to pick a fight. - It's the chauffeur fee.
Why would you mention that now? That's so cheap of you.
I can get it for you...
Are you done?
(Fine, don't.)
(She walks away.)
(She leaves Kwang Soo and the bracelet.)
I'm just going to get this.
Should we buy one each, Kwang Soo?
- It's quite cute. - Right? It's cute.
Should we get it? Should we get one each?
It's cute, right? Which one do you want? I want this.
- I want this one. - This color?
- Should we get one each? - Okay.
Thank you very much.
(Kwang Soo is an impulsive buyer.)
Kwang Soo.
Aren't you spending too much?
I just bought them.
(He hands her something.)
- Is that for her? - It's a bracelet.
(Here. I found it on the way.)
(Few minutes ago)
Let's go.
(He felt sorry for So Min because she wanted the bracelet,)
(so he picked it up when nobody was looking.)
Lee Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo.
(What's going on? Is love in the air?)
Would you like water?
Jae Seok, Kwang Soo got this for me.
- What is it? - It's a bracelet.
(You're the best, Kwang Soo.)
You're awesome, Kwang Soo.
You're awesome. You're a true man.
(What's going on between them?)
- Here's dried fish. - Let's eat.
- Have some dried fish. - I bought the rice cake...
- because it looked good. - Dried fish looks good.
Can I have a small piece?
- This is enough. - Okay.
This is good.
- Hey, I just forgot. - What?
Where are we going again?
(They're on their way to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
Why did you mention it?
I was having a good time. Why did you say it?
We would have been happier if we didn't think about it.
Did you all get your snacks?
- Yes. - Yes.
Before you eat your snacks...
- So Min. - Yes?
Please give me the leftover change.
(Change?)
- Please give me the change. - Sorry?
Are you taking our money?
Everyone, please return your change.
- What are you doing? - Are you serious?
Is there a mission with the change?
Is there?
- Please give me the change. - I have a bad feeling about this.
Were we supposed to spend a lot or little?
I think we were supposed to spend a lot.
The person with the smallest change will get one more slot.
(This was a hidden mission at the rest stop.)
(We knew it. Kwang Soo will be selected.)
(Gosh, I want to curse at him.)
- It's Kwang Soo. - Hey.
- Isn't it definitely Kwang Soo? - Hey, here you go.
- Hold on. - Kwang Soo, it will be you.
- You spent a lot of money. - I couldn't spend a lot of money?
How can this be?
Why did you spend a lot of money?
Give me the bracelet money.
Come on. Pay me for that.
I didn't buy it for you.
- I didn't. - Why are you doing this now?
Kwang Soo, your change is 37 dollars.
(Kwang Soo is a big spender.)
- Goodness. - You squandered the money.
- Why did you buy the wallet? - I...
(It's a character-shaped wallet.)
- Why did you buy a wallet here? - Did you not?
I didn't. It was expensive.
(What are you talking about?)
- I was about to buy one too. - You little...
(You wanted to buy it together.)
Look at this guy. Hey!
- Are you serious? - He didn't buy it.
- It's not that. - Why did you buy a wallet here?
It was you who wanted a matching wallet. Hey!
Hey, Se Chan. Why are you doing this to me?
No, Kwang Soo.
- You didn't know about the mission. - I didn't know.
- Jae Seok's change is 84 dollars. - 84 dollars?
- Seok Jin's change is 56 dollars. - Yes!
- Se Chan's change is 76 dollars. - Okay!
I'm sorry.
But thank you for the bracelet.
Let's see what happens now.
I didn't know about this mission.
I have two snakes with me.
You sly, sly snakes.
You should write it yourself.
Write down your name. You spent the most amount of money.
(Sighing)
- Write it. - Hey.
Let's settle that Kwang Soo should fill in all the slots.
No, Jae Seok. Half of these slots are empty.
I can do this.
- He's really unlucky. - Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo has 6 slots on the roulette.)
Had I not been tricked by these two snakes,
it could have been Seok Jin. He ordered an expensive dish.
Right. I bought a lot. I spent about 50 dollars.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, he was saved.)
You and So Min are developing your relationship.
Relationship? What relationship?
You are.
If you two get married and have a kid, that kid will be the best.
Your child will be the best traitor.
(They will be a pure-blooded traitor.)
(Kwang Soo and So Min will make the best traitor.)
- The best traitor. - Your child will make a new era.
Kwang Soo, your names are on six slots, right?
Each of us has only one slot.
You are Kwang Soo of Six Slots.
(Congratulations!)
- That's not my name. - Kwang Soo of Six Slots.
- You do have six slots. - Goodness, come on.
Let's see what happens at the end.
- Gosh. - I was happy for a brief moment.
It was brief. Now, I am feeling depressed again.
Exactly. When I think about it, it's depressing.
The members in Yokohama should be over the moon.
They don't have any burden pulling them back.
What are the members in Yokohama doing now?
(They have a different fate under the same sky.)
It's been a while since I've been here. I have nothing to worry about.
If there's a punishment, there should be a reward.
- I'm at ease now. - But why do I feel anxious?
There's nothing to be anxious about. We have a credit card to have fun.
(It's because you are adding ghosts unknowingly.)
Sir, please drive us to the fanciest, coolest,
and best place.
- Okay. - All right.
By the way, are you Japanese?
No, I am Korean.
- You are Korean? - Are you Korean Japanese?
No, I am from Yeongju, North Gyeongsang Province.
I see.
(They start their trip that will raise the number of ghosts.)
(The scenery starts to look fancy after driving for 1 hour.)
(They arrive at Yokohama.)
(Welcome to Yokohama.)
(What is their first tourist attraction?)
Let's go!
- Let's go. - Goodness.
This is amazing.
This is crazy.
This is so pretty.
What a spectacular view.
(Yokohama is a romantic, port city.)
(Oh, yes! I love this trip.)
Hey, this is it.
This is the Yokohama Landmark Tower.
We have to take a selfie from below. Jong Kook, come closer.
This is incredible.
(They seem relaxed.)
In 2, 3.
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear? Not for us.)
Jong Kook.
(Their second tourist attraction is a famous ramen restaurant.)
(Will you be able to enjoy ramen like we do?)
It's here.
- Thank you. - Gosh.
Look at this.
(This is a Japanese ramen meal that even the ghosts will be envious of.)
- This looks so delicious. - Let's eat.
- Look at the egg. - This is amazing.
This is incredible.
(The more food they order, the more ghosts will be added.)
(Look at this.)
(He takes a big bite.)
Why is this so delicious?
- This is so tasty. - Jong Kook, they are calling us.
(Vibrating)
Jong Kook, they are calling us.
Answer it.
(Why are they calling us?)
- Everyone. - Yes?
- Here's the second mission. - Here he goes again.
- Okay. - There's another one?
Four slots on the roulette are at stake with this mission.
- Four slots? - If I fail again, I'm done.
This mission is called Your Name.
(Your Name is the next mission.)
You will call the members in Yokohama,
and the first name they say will be written on the roulette.
(The member whose name is called first will earn 4 slots.)
(The caller and the receiver hold the key to the mission.)
- What do we ask them? - Who will make the call?
Do rock-paper-scissors and anyone can make the call.
When they pick up and say, "Kwang Soo?" Then Kwang Soo is picked.
Goodness.
- It doesn't matter what I say then? - Avoiding this gives you a chance.
- If we avoid that first answer... - You're right.
We can say, "Who is that tall member?"
- "You know him." - "Kwang Soo"?
When they say that, it's over.
- All right. - Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
(Not calling the members is the best way to go.)
(I have to win rock-paper-scissors and avoid becoming the caller.)
Four slots are at stake.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo loses.)
(Screaming)
- You lost, Kwang Soo. - Hold on.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(What are you doing?)
Hold on. The loser...
(Oh, no. I lost again.)
Wait.
Kwang Soo, I think you've been possessed.
- Everyone played paper except you. - Hey, you.
- You are possessed. - How can this be possible?
- I can't believe you. - Kwang Soo, you are incredible.
Hey, you should perform an exorcism.
- How can this be possible? - Fine. I'll make the call.
(Kwang Soo is chosen.)
Whom are you going to call?
When they say, "Hey, Kwang Soo," it'll all be over.
No way. I don't think they will answer.
- It's up to you. - I'll call Haha.
- All right. - I'll call Haha.
Hey, say that we are playing a game.
Ask him, "Who is the grasshopper?"
I think he's going to say your name.
(He's calls Haha.)
(Haha, please don't call my name.)
(Just say, "Hello?" It's nice and simple.)
Hey, Kwang Soo.
(Haha calls his name immediately.)
(What is it, Kwang Soo?)
We were right.
(Haha, clueless of their mission, was gobbling up ramen.)
It's Kwang Soo.
Hey, Kwang Soo.
(Due to Haha's nonchalant greeting, "Kwang Soo",)
(Kwang Soo earns 4 slots on the roulette.)
That's it.
(His misfortune is praiseworthy and impressive.)
Kwang Soo.
Nice job, Haha.
- Kwang Soo, just hang up. - Haha.
Kwang Soo, why are you laughing?
- Haha. - Haha.
- Yes, Kwang Soo. - That's enough!
Come on. Cut it out.
(I am about to go to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear by myself.)
- Hey. - Kwang Soo, what's wrong?
(Goodness)
- Kwang Soo. - What's wrong?
I'm sorry, Haha.
- Where are you guys? - Haha, did you arrive in Yokohama?
Yes, we did. We're having ramen now.
- Gosh, it must be delicious. - That sounds tasty.
- Sorry. I don't know what it is. - Kwang Soo, just enjoy it.
You'll feel sorry when you watch this on TV.
- All right, Haha. - That's it.
- Kwang Soo got 4 slots. - 4 more slots.
- 1, 2... - He has 10 slots.
- Kwang Soo of 10 Slots! - 10 slots!
- I have 10 slots? - He has 10 slots.
- Kwang Soo has 10 slots! - Already?
Thank you so much.
- Kwang Soo has now 10 slots, not 6. - 10 slots!
10 slots!
Why did you write my name all on one side?
We didn't have much space.
- If you do this... - All the slots have your name!
- 10 slots. - We had no other place.
Kwang Soo, let it go.
- That mission was out of my hands. - When I am with Kwang Soo,
- I am so lucky. - So am I.
- Me too. - I am so lucky.
- He doesn't let me shine. - Let's do this.
- This is amazing. - Don't do this.
- By the way... - This is enough.
- This isn't just luck now. - He's possessed by other spirits.
I think he's been possessed by an evil spirit.
An evil spirit?
- Jae Seok. - How can you say such a thing?
- You should have an exorcism. - Why would I do that?
- If you are this unlucky... - You should perform one.
How can this happen consecutively?
- I will show you I'm normal. - Why did you buy this Dotoro?
Why did you buy this Dotoro?
- Dotoro? - This is Totoro.
- How can you call it Dotoro? - You were...
- You were so lame. - He said you were lame.
- I really think he's possessed. - Why did you play rock alone?
Why did you have to call Haha?
I agree.
- Japan must want Kwang Soo. - I think so too.
- Hey. - Kwang Soo.
What's the matter with you? Just watch.
Kwang Soo, please cheer up
- Don't sing that song. - You have
- You have ghosts - Us
- Just watch. - Kwang Soo of 10 Slots
Please cheer up
- You have ghosts - You have us
You can do it, Kwang Soo of 11, 12, and 13 Slots!
- What's the name of the song? - Kwang Soo, this song is for you.
What is it?
- It's "Amor Fati". - "Amor Fati".
(This is how life is)
(Isn't it?)
(DJ Yu decides to play a list of dedicated songs.)
Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, baby
Kwang Soo will go alone, baby
I love it, I love it, I love it, Kwang Soo of 10 Slots
(I want everyone to just shut it.)
(Kwang Soo of 10 Slots, Kwang Soo of 10 Slots)
(There is a 99 percent chance Kwang Soo will go alone.)
(He is the top 1 candidate.)
Why would you sway the camera?
(Do you think you are filming "Inkigayo"?)
("Plz Dont Be Sad" by Highlight)
(Please don't be sad, Kwang Soo of 10 Slots.)
Kwang Soo of 10 Slots, Kwang Soo of 10 Slots!
Your face is divine
(I give up.)
All right.
What is going on? Turn on the light.
(They enter the tunnel as soon as he begins to dance.)
Lee Kwang Soo!
(Dancing without restraints)
You will end up at Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear
("Oh, My Kwang Soo of 10 Slots" by Country Kkokko)
Will you go to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear alone?
(So Min teases Kwang Soo.)
(I say Kwang Soo, you say Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
- We are forgetting something. - What?
We are acting as if we're not going there.
- Seriously. - We will go with him.
- It's not like I am going alone. - The music made me forgot.
We either go in alone or with someone else.
I don't think I can go in alone.
That ruined my mood.
We will pee our pants together in a few hours.
(We are all in the same boat.)
(After a while, they arrive at a restaurant near Mount Fuji.)
(The candidates fill the roulette with their names.)
(Will another candidate rise as the most likely to be chosen?)
(Who will have the highest chance of entering the attraction alone?)
(Night falls.)
- I feel down now that it's night. - I'm lethargic.
I shouldn't drink water.
If I drink water, I will end up going to the bathroom.
(The van arrives at the entrance of Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
There is no bathroom.
- I am going crazy. - I don't want to pee my pants.
- I am going crazy. - I heard it's really scary.
We are going.
- Are we going? - Are we going?
That's where they hold the memorial rites.
They hold one every morning?
My goodness.
Why do they hold a memorial rite every morning?
(They enter Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
This is where they hold the memorial rites.
- Why do they do it? - The buildings are apart.
My goodness.
- It's so scary. - The place looks frightening.
- I am so scared. - This isn't a set.
We will decide on the member...
- who will enter alone. - I'm about to die.
(Will it be Kwang Soo of 10 Slots or someone else?)
(Don't make a rash prediction.)
(Imagination will become reality, and reality will become fear.)
(All 5 members enter Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(Fear wraps around their skin.)
(They must find their name tags and escape from the pit.)
(What will they face at the end of darkness?)
(Who will enter the pit alone?)
Sir, please.
Please move back a little.
Thank you.
(Dangerous Trip Final: Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(A new project will be revealed next week.)