(Running Man's 7th year anniversary)
I love the seventh year anniversary.
(Congratulations on the 7th year anniversary.)
(They happily started the day of the 7th year anniversary.)
(However,)
(heavy rain watch is issued on the day of the shoot.)
(Running Man and the family are rushed inside.)
(However)
(She becomes a complete mess.)
(Do you love your friend?)
(I don't exactly love him.)
(Heavy rain couldn't stop Running Man and the family.)
(They made people laugh by talking, dancing, and singing.)
(Also)
(Jeon Wook Min is the rising star of arm wrestling.)
(He challenged Jong Kook to an arm wrestling match.)
(Jong Kook used all of his muscles to gain the mission fee.)
(The final match begins now.)
(Kim Jong Kook versus Jeon Wook Min)
(Jong Kook was unrivaled.)
It feels like an international competition.
(He finally meets his match.)
My goodness.
He is very strong.
Look at his arms.
Look at his hips. What will happen?
(By kicking with his left foot in a nonchalant manner,)
(he received the best score on the machine.)
(Wook Min is on the top in terms of kicks.)
(His current goal is to beat Jong Kook's iron arms.)
- He is very strong. - Look at his arms.
- My goodness. - They are so thick.
- Get ready. - This is unbelievable.
Set, go.
(The final match begins with their pride on the line.)
(Who is stronger?)
(Hitting)
- Jong Kook won. - What happened?
(In 2 seconds,)
(Wook Min's arm touches the table.)
- What happened? - You are in a bad condition, too.
What happened?
You are in a bad condition, too.
- I mean... - What happened?
- What was that? - Say something.
Let's have another match.
- Let's have another match. - Seriously.
- He is too strong. - Really?
- Yes, he is really strong. - Arm wrestle against Hang Ho.
Seriously.
- Stay back. - Let's have another match.
We can't change the result.
Jong Kook wins.
We won 10 dollars.
My family member's specialty...
is quizzes on general knowledge.
(Kim Jong Myung's specialty: General knowledge)
To test Jong Myung's specialty of general knowledge,
we will have Family Golden Bell.
(Family Golden Bell)
You don't need to be worried. Except for Jae Seok,
there is no one you need to worry about.
In human body,
what are the three most important nutrients?
What?
What are the three most important nutrients?
Should we write down all three nutrients?
All three nutrients?
Nutrients?
(Carbohydrates, proteins, and fats)
I wrote down my answer.
Everyone wrote down their answers, right?
- Yes. - I don't know the answer.
Could this be the answer?
One.
(How did the family members do?)
Two.
Three.
(Jong Kook and Jong Myung's answers are correct.)
(Jae Seok and Sae Ho's answers are correct as well.)
Three.
He wrote down vitamins A, C, and D.
(He wrote down all vitamins.)
(Vitamins are nutrients.)
(They wrote down vitamins as their answer.)
Someone wrote down carbohydrates, proteins, and vitamins.
- Carbohydrates? - Yes.
Seok Jin wrote down proteins, water, and salt.
(Water is life.)
It makes sense.
He wrote, "Ji Hyo, I am sorry."
(It's in the style of "The Golden Bell Challenge".)
You don't need to be sorry.
(Don't be sorry, Sung Moon.)
(Your sister doesn't know the answer either.)
The answer is...
carbohydrates, proteins, and fats.
(Jae Seok, Sae Ho, Jong Kook, Jong Myung, So Min, and Wook Min)
What about water? Isn't water important?
70 percent of human body is made up of water.
Vitamins wasn't the answer.
It's different from what we have learned.
(Isn't it vitamins?)
People learn different things outside of Dongducheon.
- Here comes the second question. - Okay.
What does G in G20...
stand for?
This one is hard.
G of G20?
One. All right.
1, 2, 3.
We don't need to write it down in English, do we?
My answer is global.
Global. Global. Global. Global. Global.
- Giant. - General.
General. Gee, gee, gee, gee.
There are 20 Gs.
(They are every words that start with the letter G.)
G20. Global. Global. Global. Global. Global.
Go.
So Min wrote "Go".
You think it means the 20 nations will go.
Global. Global. Global.
- Haha wrote "Group". - Group.
Someone got it right.
- Really? - The answer must be global.
(Most people wrote "global" as the answer.)
G in G20 stands for...
- group. - Really?
(Group)
(Haha is the only one with the right answer.)
- Really? - This is unbelievable.
Who got it right?
It's not Jong Myung.
- I thought it stood for global. - He is shocked.
- I wrote "global", too. - Haha's answer is correct.
Haha's answer is correct.
(What is going on?)
- I thought it stood for global. - Me, too.
I thought it was "global".
Here's another easy question.
What are the names...
of the mothers of Chun Hyang and Sim Chung...
from the classical novels, "Chunhyangjeon" and "Simchungjeon"?
- Chun Hyang's mother? - "Chunhyangjeon"...
Sim Chung's mother?
- I know the names of their fathers. - Right.
You're talking about Mr. Sim's wife, right?
Yes, his wife.
(He's not interested in others' family business.)
One...
(Those who already got one right win if they guess this correctly.)
Two.
(Will there be a winner?)
Three. Please show me your answers.
(Chun Hyang's mother is Wol Mae.)
(Sim Chung's mother is Ms. Kwak and her stepmother is Bbaeng Deok.)
(These two got their answers wrong.)
He wrote Chun Hyang's mother's name to be...
"Kim Sook Hee"?
And he wrote Sim Chung's mother's name as "Bbaeng Deok".
- "Gong Yang Mi". - Gosh, that's so funny.
Who wrote that?
(He guessed her name to be Gong Yang Mi.)
- Maybe it's Yang Mi. - So Min...
And So Min wrote...
Chun Hyang's mother's name as "Chun Lee".
(That sounds American.)
You're helpless. What's Chun Lee?
(That's the only name she knows that starts with Chun.)
(Chun Hyang's mother may be somewhat violent.)
Chun Hyang's mother...
He didn't write anything.
He wrote "Kim Hye Ja" for Chun Hyang's mother.
(He gets the answer wrong again by writing an actress' name.)
- It's just his guess. - I see.
And who is "Kim Chun Ok"?
(Whose name did he write down?)
Chun Hyang's mother.
I'm sorry, but can you erase "I love you, Geun Sik"?
Why?
- It bothers me. - You're supposed to do this.
Goodness.
(He's embarrassed by his friend.)
So it's "Wol Mae".
I thought the name "Bbaeng Deok" comes out in another story.
Jong Myung got it wrong again.
I don't know these kinds of stuff.
He got only one question right so far.
Why can't you get the questions right?
We got it right.
How could you place first...
- Goodness. - when the guests are here?
- I know, but I can't help it. - That's not polite.
We're doomed.
I got Jong Myung's.
(As a result, Team Jae Seok places 1st with 30 dollars.)
It's Summer Race with Running Man members' friends and family.
The race is called Dangerous Family Crisis.
(Summer Race, Dangerous Family Crisis)
You will make a team of two with your guest,
and the team with the largest sum of money at the end will win the race.
The winning team will be given the prize and exempted from the penalty.
The losing team with the least amount of money...
and the team chosen by the losing team will take ice shower.
Today's penalty is ice shower.
Ice shower.
- The team who gets picked too? - Yes.
After each mission, the top two teams will be given...
the chance to switch their partners.
(The top 2 teams will be given a chance to change partners.)
My partner?
(Shall I aim to get a new family member?)
Your partners can be changed frequently.
You seem to love the idea.
When it happens, you'll move to another team...
with the money you have in possession.
So you'll have to divide the money well.
(The race is about the teamwork and trust within each team.)
You'll get changed into uniforms now.
Then we will start our race for today.
- Let's go. - Let's go!
(They start their race 7 hours after the shooting.)
Everything we did so far was just an opening.
That was just a warm-up game?
I'm hungry.
(They're exhausted already.)
(So Min and Wook Min are the first to finish preparing.)
1, 2, 3.
(Let's take pictures and send them to our dad.)
Send the pictures we just took to Dad.
(Dad will love this.)
- Is it done? - Done.
Send.
It's working. It's being sent now.
It's done.
Mom will love this.
(Satisfied)
All right, everyone.
We'll start the mission now.
The first mission of Dangerous Family Crisis is...
called Money or Loyalty.
(Dangerous Family Crisis, Money or Loyalty)
Okay.
2 teams will be playing a game together in 1 group in this mission.
Simply speaking, 4 people will be in 1 group.
- Okay. - Good.
- Really? - We should choose carefully.
For example, if all 4 members in each team write 5 dollars...
on the papers given to each member,
all of them will be provided five dollars.
(If they write the same amount, they'll be given the money.)
However...
If there's a member who wrote something lower than five dollars,
that person will be given 10 times the amount.
That person will be given 10 times the amount.
The other three will be given the low amount that person wrote.
- Why do you keep testing us? - It's confusing.
I remember this game. Last time, So Min and Kwang Soo...
- wrote 50 cents. - I remember too.
(Last Spring, Haha wrote 3 dollars and 90 cents.)
(But So Min wrote 50 cents.)
(Kwang Soo wrote 50 cents as well.)
(Let's stop now.)
(So Min, you know how I feel, right?)
(It's the game of betrayal that revealed their true nature.)
Don't be hopeful. I know we won't be writing the same.
This is war. We'll do anything to win.
We'll now divide you into groups.
Choose a team whom you think is easy to deal with...
- and make a group with them. - 4 members in 1 group?
4 people will be in 1 group to play the mission.
It means 2 teams in 1 group.
Gosh, even our uniform color doesn't look intimidating.
(Gosh, even our uniform color doesn't look intimidating.)
(It's yellowish.)
It's a good color.
Why...
It looks damp and nice.
Does any team want to do it with us?
(By any chance, does anyone want to do it with us?)
Us.
Come here then.
(You guys are our prey.)
(Come on, Kwang Soo.)
(Teams Haha and Team Kwang Soo become a group.)
How much do you have?
We have quite a lot.
(Raising hand)
We're looking for a team as well.
(No one's interested.)
We welcome you.
She's totally like a moth that will jump into the flames.
Guys, come here.
(Please trust me.)
So Min...
is too much of a moth.
I can't trust her.
(Wook Min, your sister is treated this way here.)
- Shall we do it with them? - Let's do it.
Okay.
- Let's do it. - Let's trust each other.
Beauties have to survive in order for Running Man to survive.
Take So Min out.
So Min will definitely write something weird.
We have to focus.
(They finish dividing themselves into groups.)
(First group: Jae Seok, Sae Ho, Seok Jin, Soo Yong)
- Let's just write 5 dollars. - Let's take 5 dollars each.
It's hard for me to play smart, so I'll just write five dollars.
- Let's write five dollars. - All right.
- Let's not use tricks. - Let's all write...
- 5 dollars. - Let's write 5 dollars.
(And he tries to write it in secret.)
Jae Seok, where are you going? Just write it here.
Write it here.
- I'll write it here. - There's no need to go over there.
Gosh, Seok Jin.
Let's not betray each other and write five dollars.
- Let's make it simple. - Let's be loyal.
We'll all write five dollars.
We'll do that and take five dollars each fairly.
- We should. How much do you have? - We should.
I have five dollars. You gave it to me.
But... Hold on.
What? You have five dollars only?
No, it's supposed to be 15 dollars.
(What? Kwang Soo gave me 5 dollars.)
You need to have 10 dollars each.
- You won the mission earlier too. - Right.
- I have five dollars. - Okay.
That's right. He's right.
Why is that right?
It's right.
See? Don't let him fool you.
It's right. You have five dollars, right?
- 5 dollars. - You need to have 5 more dollars.
Kwang Soo won the mission earlier.
- Remind me later. - You have to have 10 dollars each.
- So that I don't forget. - You have to have 10 dollars each.
I'm sure he hid it somewhere.
If you behave like this,
we won't be able to trust each other.
Shouldn't you have five more dollars in possession?
(It's strange.)
- I mean... - I know.
Should we split the money in half?
(Is it necessary?)
- See? - Goodness.
- I mean... - In half?
How can you do that to your family?
(A just civilian, Haha, revealed Kwang Soo's embezzlement.)
(Slap)
(Hang Ho is in rage.)
You told me you didn't have any more money.
- How could you? - I didn't know.
- I'll give it to you. - Seriously.
Here.
- Are you sure about trusting him? - I...
- I didn't mean to... - He gave me four dollars.
(He's in shock.)
- I'll give it to you. - I can't believe this.
- Here! - You're sickening me!
So this is how things work. Okay.
You're the one who's at fault.
- Whom are you taking it out on? - I thought we'd go until the end.
That's what I thought as well.
I can't believe this.
You're such a jerk.
- I had it here. - So give me a dollar.
- Why? - I got you five dollars.
(Revealing his true intention)
Here.
- Thank you. - Are you serious?
What about me?
"What about me?"
(I won't give you a dollar.)
(Will Hang Ho finish the mission without getting emotionally hurt?)
- It's unpredictable. - Right.
It's a bit...
Write your name on the envelope.
(Ji Hyo and Sung Moon start discussing their plan.)
(She's nervous.)
You really can't betray me.
(She only has Se Chan to trust on.)
Will you betray us and turn this into a war?
It can't be helped because it's an individual game.
Our partners can be changed.
(Our partners can be changed.)
- Our partners can be changed. - Wait.
You're thinking of switching partners, aren't you?
- I think so. - No way.
- How can I dare do that? - He has it in mind.
I need to have enough money in order to protect you.
- Na Eun, don't trust him. - I'm telling you the truth.
He doesn't sound trustworthy at all.
- Na Eun. - I won't ever do that.
But I'm worried she might change her partners.
Will you?
No, well...
(Mumbling all of a sudden)
You're not answering properly.
- We got him. - I have to see how it goes first.
I have no choice.
(What will Se Chan, Na Eun, Sung Moon, and Ji Hyo decide?)
All right. We will start with Hang Ho, Kwang Soo, Haha, and Geun Sik.
Our team is going to go first?
- It's going to be a messy one. - I bet it will be messy.
- No, we agreed on a number. - You did?
I think it'd be better if we reveal their numbers at the end.
(The producer sighs.)
- You all made different choices. - It was...
It was a battlefield.
- I'm so sad. Who is it? - I can't believe it.
- Don't make that face, Kwang Soo. - You...
- Look at Kwang Soo acting. - Did you write the number we set?
How can you betray us even on our seventh year anniversary?
I will check the amount Seok Jin, Soo Yong, Jae Seok,
and Sae Ho wrote down.
- We decided to write five dollars. - Yes, we did.
Soo Yong wrote...
(If everyone wrote 5 dollars, everyone will receive 5 dollars.)
(They didn't want to play mind tricks. Did their plan work?)
He wrote five dollars.
- I knew it. - We did it.
- Goodness. - I knew you were an honest friend.
Soo Yong is known to take care of his finances well.
He doesn't make mistakes when it's about money.
We made a promise.
Sae Ho wrote...
(The number he wrote down is next.)
He wrote 3 dollars 50 cents.
Sae Ho wrote 3 dollars 50 cents.
- You wrote that? - Sae Ho, you are unbelievable.
- Even cabbages cost more than that. - Sae Ho, you are unbelievable.
- Think about the cost of cabbages. - Didn't I write five dollars?
- You wrote 3 dollars 50 cents. - I did?
- Did you hear what he said? - Stop acting.
- What are you doing? - Stop acting.
- Soo Yong is really mad. - Hey.
I don't get mad easily.
It's so scary when it rains, and Soo Yong moves like that.
- His feet didn't move. - He's like Gaonasi.
(You wrote 3 dollars and 50 cents?)
- He looked like Gaonasi. - He does.
Jae Seok wrote...
1 dollar 10 cents.
(He's shocked.)
You told us to write five dollars.
- The amount I wrote was decent. - 1 dollar 10 cents?
What are you talking about?
- His amount is less than mine? - We don't know about Seok Jin's.
Seok Jin wrote 60 cents.
(He only wrote 60 cents.)
Seok Jin will receive 6 dollars, and the rest of you will get 60 cents.
What am I supposed to do with them?
- Take 60 cents. - I'm sorry.
- I can't play with these people. - Hey.
- How can you write 60 cents? - I can't believe Seok Jin.
I almost wrote 52 cents.
(Seok Jin gets 6 dollars and the rest get 60 cents.)
Se Chan, Na Eun, Ji Hyo, and Sung Moon are next.
(These 4 young adults are next.)
- What did they write? - Na Eun wrote...
five dollars.
- She's the first. - She's an angel.
- I haven't seen anyone like her. - She is truly an angel.
- Someone like her does exist. - I didn't know such person existed.
- She does exist. - How incredible.
She's an angel.
I hope everyone wrote five dollars, and gets the money together.
- I mean it. - And...
- But Se Chan... - If he wrote that, it'll be moving.
- I agree. I do. - He valued her heart more.
Se Chan.
- He must've wrote the same thing. - Of course he did.
That's right.
(It was a one-sided love and loyalty.)
(How can I abandon you?)
(It's an opportunity to prove that his heart hasn't changed.)
Se Chan wrote...
90 cents.
(But he wrote 90 cents?)
(Capitalism shattered his love.)
Se Chan.
Ji Hyo and Sung Moon wrote...
- 2 dollars 50 cents. - I knew it.
(This is how things are on Running Man.)
Se Chan will get 9 dollars, and the rest will get 90 cents.
(Se Chan gets 9 dollars, and the rest get 90 cents.)
- Se Chan! - How can you do that to Na Eun?
- How could you do that to her? - You were mean to Na Eun.
- He's a jerk. - You are unbelievable.
- Se Chan. Goodness. - I had no choice, Haha.
- But still. - Na Eun.
You have to meet the right guy.
- You need to choose the right guy. - I'm looking at the bigger picture.
I shouldn't have trusted men.
(Se Chan teaches Na Eun a lesson about love.)
We will move onto the next group.
Jong Kook, Jong Myung, So Min, and Wook Min are next.
I trust them.
Wook Min gave me a chicken breast protein shake during the break.
- We really bonded. - That's right.
Jong Kook wrote...
five dollars.
He's a true man.
Our family used to be aristocrats. We are of noble birth.
- Jong Myung wrote... - Jong Myung!
- I bet he wrote 5 dollars. - 5 dollars.
- Really? He's so cool. - Our family is noble.
(For the first time, 2 members wrote 5 dollars in a row.)
(What is this group's strategy?)
(30 minutes ago, during the strategy meeting for the mission fee)
(Jong Myung's strategy is to have only one person write...)
(4 dollars 90 cents and divide 49 dollars among 4 members.)
(I like your strategy.)
(Who is going to write 4 dollars 90 cents?)
(You should write it.)
He wouldn't betray us.
He's the youngest and your younger brother.
(He wouldn't try to pull anything funny like So Min does.)
(This is how Jong Kook and Jong Myung submitted 5 dollars.)
However, you have So Min. She jumps into the flame.
She's like a moth who jumps into the flame without hesitation.
(The biggest obstacle, So Min, remains.)
So Min wrote...
(If So Min wrote 5 dollars, their strategy will be a big success.)
1 dollar 20 cents.
She betrayed them.
- So Min. - 1 dollar 20 cents.
(The Kims are furious.)
She wrote 1 dollar 20 cents?
- So Min wrote 1 dollar 20 cents? - She's no joke.
- Hey. - She played Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook, she deceived you. - You wrote 1 dollar 20 cents?
- 1 dollar 20 cents. - I knew it.
She never disappoints me.
- Goodness. - She's something else.
- So Min's brother, Wook Min, - Wook Min.
- wrote 49 cents. - Hey, what?
I can't believe you.
(What did he say?)
What a family.
- They make a nice family. - Hey!
(The Kims are at a loss for words.)
(Wook Min has fully adjusted to the show.)
Wook Min will get 4 dollars 90 cents and the rest will get 49 cents.
Younger siblings are worse than the older ones.
We're not the only opponents he has. He has to go against everyone.
Jong Myung is quite angry now.
- He is. - How can you write 49 cents?
- He wants no one to get the money. - He got 4 dollars 90 cents.
But he went too far though.
(He gets 4 dollars 90 cents, and the rest get 49 cents.)
It's the turn of the last group in question.
(Everyone has been waiting for this last group in question.)
- Why are we in question? - This group...
Why did you say that?
- Why is our group in question? - I didn't do it.
- Everyone wrote five dollars. - Hang Ho wrote...
(Hang Ho wrote...)
5 dollars.
- We were supposed to play fair. - That's right.
(Isn't it only natural I write five dollars?)
(They are anxious, and hope he doesn't get hurt.)
Geun Sik wrote...
1 dollar 90 cents.
- How can you write that amount? - I wanted to win the money.
- I'm so disappointed in you. - I'm sorry.
- I'm disappointed. - But we talked about this.
- Hang Ho is mad now. - This is how we play this game.
- Hang Ho is upset. - This is how we play this game.
- Look at Kwang Soo acting. - You made a fool of Hang Ho.
(Kwang Soo and Haha remain, and this pair seems quite suspicious.)
- You made a fool of Hang Ho. - Kwang Soo wrote...
- 49 cents. - Hey!
(This was unexpected of him.)
(He feels betrayed.)
- How much did Haha write? - Haha's amount is less than his?
(Kwang Soo is indeed different from others.)
How much is Haha's amount?
- Did I write more than Haha? - I didn't betray you.
Haha wrote...
- Why? - How much is it?
15 cents.
(This is shocking and scary even.)
Goodness.
(You jerk!)
Goodness. You're unbelievable.
- What about you then? - You wrote 15 cents?
- How can you write that? - How about you?
- You should've written 50 cents. - I'm sorry.
(But Kwang Soo wrote 49 cents.)
- The minimum amount is 50 cents. - 15 cents are too little.
- Hang Ho, I'm sorry. - Writing 15 cents was too cruel.
- 20 years ago... - We paired up with the wrong team.
It'd have been better receiving 5 dollars after you wrote 5 dollars.
Haha will get 1 dollar 50 cents, and the rest will get 15 cents.
- Why did he do that? - You must write more than 50 cents.
15 cents?
(Haha gets 1 dollar 50 cents, and the rest get 15 cents.)
(Current status of mission fees)
(Se Chan and Na Eun are in the lead.)
We prepared your favorite dishes since you must be hungry by now.
What are they?
Before we move to the restaurants,
I will present you Hit or Miss Bus Mission.
(Their mission for their dinner is Hit or Miss Bus Mission.)
Get ready to run.
Two buses will head to the restaurants.
The menu for one bus is chicken soup.
The other one is mandarin fish stew.
One of the buses is an express bus.
Everyone will head to the restaurant and enjoy the meal right away.
The other bus is a layover bus. Before your arrival,
you must stop by at a place to find your Meal Cards through a mission.
We have to find Meal Cards.
(One bus is a layover bus, and they must find Meal Cards to eat.)
However, there are only two Meal Cards.
The teams who find these Meal Cards first will have dinner.
The rest can't eat?
- 2 teams won't be able to eat. - Only 2 teams won't get to eat.
We have to choose the right bus.
Then everyone,
please go and get on the bus.
Hey, let's hurry.
Hey! Hurry, Sae Ho.
- Let's go. - Hurry.
- Be careful when you run. - Let's run.
Hey, Sung Moon.
Which one is for chicken soup?
Here it is.
- Sae Ho. - Yes, Jae Seok.
Let the unlucky ones choose first.
Should we let them choose first?
- Choose the one on the left. - Why are we getting on this one?
- Chicken soup. This is right. - I don't think it's this one.
- What is this? Mandarin fish stew. - This is fish stew.
(Which one is the express bus?)
- Mandarin fish stew. - Let's go with this.
Actually, I wanted to choose chicken soup.
- That's right. - That's a fancy meal.
This will be the express bus, and we'll have the fish stew right away.
- Let's eat mandarin fish stew! - Yes!
Let's go, mandarin fish stew! Trying doesn't hurt.
(Will their dreams come true?)
Judging by the people who got on the bus for chicken soup,
a lot of moths are here.
(The bus for chicken soup is crowded with moths.)
- That's right. - Aren't I right?
- I chose the wrong bus. - So Min, Kwang Soo,
- and Se Chan. - Why did you exclude yourself?
(You are the biggest moth.)
(What have I done?)
Jae Seok is the scariest.
A lot of scary members are on the bus for chicken soup.
Why did you choose chicken soup?
I like it. I'm in the middle of the promotion period.
I should avoid food that is too spicy or salty.
You should watch your weight.
- What about you, Se Chan? - I wanted to choose fish stew.
But I had to follow Na Eun.
You two seem to have different tastes.
We're just getting to know each other.
You look a bit like a fish.
(You look a bit like a fish.)
(Se Chan looks like a fish.)
- What does that mean? - A bit.
Just a bit.
- Just a little. - Do I look like a fish?
- You know what I mean, right? - I think I get it.
(Nodding)
He looks a bit like a fish.
- Especially your mouth. - Here?
Your mouth looks a bit like that of a fish.
I look like a fish?
By the way, Wook Min...
is the most handsome guy on this bus.
(Wook Min is the most handsome guy on this bus.)
(Of course.)
(Look...)
(how...)
(the others look.)
(Embarrassed)
Hang Ho, what do you think?
- The most good-looking one here? - Yes.
- Na Eun? - Yes.
- And then? - So Min, don't glare like that.
(So Min, don't glare like that.)
And then So Min. I'm sorry.
- I'm satisfied. - And then?
- This guy. - Wook Min?
Who is next?
(It's been predictable so far.)
(The real competition begins now.)
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo ranks 4th.)
- All right. - Jae Seok.
- You have prejudice against me. - Okay.
- Who is next? - I'm not...
- You. - Okay.
Am I competing with Sae Ho?
Who is next?
It's...
(Being the least good-looking one on this bus is problematic.)
(Will it be Se Chan or Sae Ho?)
- Se Chan. - Of course.
You're at the bottom.
(Sae Ho is the least good-looking one.)
(Offended)
(It's so fun to offend Sae Ho.)
It's not important.
When I see Hang Ho...
- Be quiet. - I'm sorry.
He spoke for the first time.
You're not talking very well today.
You're not talking very well.
He usually talks very well, but not today.
I specialize in talking,
- but today... - You're not doing it well.
Where did you go wrong?
Right from the start.
- From the start? - What happened yesterday?
- My stomach hurts. - Are you okay, Hang Ho?
- It's so funny. - He's crying.
What's so funny?
You guys are so funny.
We do this all the time.
(He finds Jae Seok and Sae Ho so funny.)
We'll give you the chance...
- to win additional five dollars. - Sounds great.
We'll play Jae Seok's Game.
(Jae Seok's Game)
- Jae Seok's Game. - What's that?
I'm not so confident.
It's...
- Na Eun, do you know what it is? - Yes.
You know it, right?
(You have to give an irrelevant answer 3 times in a row.)
- Se Chan. - I'll start.
(Se Chan goes first.)
- Start. - Say something to the president.
I love Na Eun.
(I love Na Eun.)
What?
I said, "I love Na Eun."
(He declared his love in front of the whole nation.)
- You could say that to him. - To the president...
(I see, Se Chan.)
I confessed my feelings anyway.
(I confessed my feelings.)
Good job.
(Even the president knows about his love now.)
Next, Na Eun.
It's Na Eun's turn.
Ready, start.
Say something to your fans in English.
I don't think so.
- Who do you want to travel with? - Red.
- Say something to your mother. - 4 times 2 equals 8.
(Success)
- You're so good. - Amazing.
She's so smart.
(Someone is looking worried.)
(Shaking eyes)
(Na Eun makes it look so easy.)
(Na Eun wins 5 dollars.)
Na Eun is so smart.
- It's Hang Ho's turn. - Hang Ho.
Hold on. I'm so good at giving answers.
- Say it right away. - Ready.
Start. Say something to your fans.
I don't have any fans.
(He's honest.)
Gosh, wait.
- What? - He...
- doesn't understand the game. - He just answered the question.
- Try again. - You answered the question.
- "I don't have any fans." - Try again, Hang Ho.
- Let's give him another chance. - He doesn't have any fans.
He revealed his weakness.
Try again, Hang Ho.
Hold on.
(Hang Ho gets another chance.)
Okay. I'm ready.
Ready, start. What was your childhood nickname?
To be or not to be, that is the question.
- Say something to Kwang Soo's dad. - Hamlet.
(Fail)
You could call him Hamlet.
(You could call him Hamlet.)
- I mean Hamlet. - You don't know Hamlet?
Hamlet.
- Hamlet. - Hamlet.
He calls my dad Hamlet?
Hamlet?
- He could call him Hamlet. - Of course.
- Hamlet. - Hamlet...
It's hard.
Hang Ho, try again.
Ready.
Start. What was your childhood nickname?
Four seasons.
(Four seasons)
(That's a pretty nickname.)
Hey.
He's so bad at this game.
- You're so bad. - It could be your nickname.
It could be your nickname.
Spring, summer, fall, and winter.
My nickname was One Season.
(My nickname was One Season.)
Fail.
- Kwang Soo. - Ready.
Start. What role do you want to play?
"Souvenirs Entomologiques".
(Do you want to play an insect?)
You want to play an insect after a fish?
- It's a book. - Hey.
An insect after a fish?
You look like a long-headed grasshopper.
What are you talking about?
It's Sae Ho's turn now.
Are you ready?
I'm very ready.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- He's ready. - Here we go.
- Sae Ho is very clever. - Ready.
Start. What do you have in your fridge right now?
Quadratic formula.
- What dream did your mom have? - Law of universal gravitation.
(Fail)
- That makes sense. - Law of universal gravitation?
(She had a very scientific dream.)
She probably had a dream where the earth gets drawn.
(Please give me a son who will become a comedian.)
What kind of mother would have a dream like that?
It's possible.
- Try again. - I'll try again.
- I can do this! - You can do this.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
- All right. - Ready.
Start.
- What will you be in 10 years? - Chicory.
(He wants to be a vegetable.)
His stage name used to be Cabbage.
Now, he's Cho Sae Ho. He'll become Chicory later.
Cabbage, Cho Sae Ho,
and then Chicory.
I can't do this.
(I can't do this.)
(Sae Ho gives up the game.)
I can't do this.
You're so bad at this.
We gave you so many chances.
- Why do you fail every time? - What's with you?
Why do you talk to me like that?
I'm just sad.
(Why do you talk to me like that?)
(I'm just cheering you up.)
I'm just cheering you up. You failed again.
Sae Ho can't say more than...
- 100 words a day. - Yes.
I'll try again. I'm so offended.
Here we go.
Ready, start.
- What was your childhood nickname? - Department store.
What was your childhood nickname?
(Sae Ho fails.)
I can explain.
Sae Ho's family was rich. He went shopping often.
That's why.
My nickname was Police Station.
You don't want to give me the money, do you?
(You don't want to give me the money, do you?)
- I just want to make sure. - Don't be like that.
Na Eun got the money.
Na Eun got it.
She got it.
Oh, she got it.
Just admit it.
It's my turn.
Ready.
- Look how I do it. - Start.
- What is in your washing machine? - Where do you live?
What do you do first thing in the morning?
Where is it?
What's that?
(What is that?)
- Jae Seok. - What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Don't stall in the beginning.
What's that?
There's nothing wrong with it.
You speak so slowly.
Anyone could do that.
- I'm speechless. - You shouldn't do that.
It's not okay.
He says, "Where am I?", when he wakes up.
(He says, "Where am I?", when he wakes up.)
- What am I doing? - Where are we going?
Where does that dialect come from?
- Soo Yong will go first. - Soo Yong.
(Soo Yong tries.)
Which member did you want to see the most?
Sausage stew.
When was your happiest moment today?
A cow.
- What is your hobby? - Hair loss.
(Hair loss)
(Is your hobby getting bald?)
He loses his hair as a hobby.
(Soo Yong enjoyed his hobby thanks to Geun Sik.)
Does that make sense?
His hobby is losing hair.
Most things make sense.
- Most things make sense. - All right.
All right. Here we go.
- Who does Soul look like? - This guy is so unlucky.
- What do you want to give Dream? - 5 times 3 equals 15.
- Say something to Mother-in-law. - I'm pretty.
I'm pretty.
(Haha fails.)
What?
- "I'm pretty?" - "I'm pretty."
Mother, I'm pretty.
(You know I'm pretty, right?)
- Is it hard? - Yes.
- It is? - Yes.
(Is it hard?)
(It is.)
(I've failed too many times.)
(I'll succeed this time.)
- What is Haha's weakness? - Elephant poop is huge.
- What do you want to get Haha? - Your shoelaces have come untied.
What do you want to eat right now?
(The last question is what he wants to eat.)
(If he can do it right, he'll succeed for the first time.)
Grapes.
(Grapes)
Gosh.
(I've been craving grapes today.)
He was almost there.
- That was so close. - That was so close.
Did you want to eat grapes?
You were doing great before that.
I'm craving something sweet.
- He wanted grapes. - Yes.
- Okay. - Give him an easy one.
- Let's go, Geun Sik. - Let's go.
What's the most recent lie you told?
I like my family.
(His answer is "I like my family.")
(His answer turns out to be meaningful.)
(Geun Sik fails yet again.)
- Family? - Family.
- What are you thinking? - Is that a lie?
(Will Geun Sik succeed in anything today?)
The bus will stop at some point.
(The buses get closer to the destinations.)
If the bus stops at the restaurant, you may enter it.
(They eat without clearing any missions.)
If it stops at a museum,
you may start the mission.
- We have to start running then. - Do we have two Meal Cards?
You only have two.
Will this bus be a hit or a miss?
What will it be?
I hope my team gets lucky.
(Will the bus head to a fish stew restaurant?)
We're on the same bus as Kwang Soo.
(Or to a chicken soup restaurant?)
The bus you chose will go...
directly to the restaurant.
(The 4 teams head directly to a chicken soup restaurant.)
(It's time to eat chicken soup, everyone.)
- That's great. - I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
You may enjoy your meals.
(Their chicken soup feast starts.)
We got lucky today.
(Those who find Meal Cards...)
Food is provided only to the 1st 2 teams to find the Meal Cards.
- Don't lie to us. - Goodness.
(They must find Meal Cards.)
(They arrive at a museum.)
I really wanted chicken soup.
Your mission will start now.
The mission starts now.
(They look for Meal Cards.)
My goodness.
(There are only 2 Meal Cards.)
Geun Sik, let's split.
(They must find Meal Cards within five minutes to eat.)
Could they be anywhere?
(Jeongok S Museum was built at Jeongok, a prehistoric relic site.)
Where could they be?
(It's full of relics related to the prehistoric age.)
One team member has to find it.
Soo Yong, we must find it.
(Could it be here?)
- Sung Moon. - Yes?
I don't think it'll be there.
There are no cameras here.
(She's experienced.)
(Ji Hyo is an experienced member.)
(She searches places where it's most likely to find them.)
Goodness.
I really want to eat it.
(What is Haha up to?)
(Is that a Meal Card?)
(He almost passes it, but finds it by instinct.)
(I knew I'd find it.)
Did you find it? Where is it?
(Wait for me, mandarin fish.)
That's impressive.
(However, Soo Yong and Seok Jin wander about without finding any.)
Where did he find it?
It's not it.
(What he finds is a dud.)
It's a dud.
I bet it's around here.
(Experienced Ji Hyo spots something.)
(Did she find a real Meal Card?)
(As she's lucky, she finds a Meal Card.)
(Sung Moon, I'll buy you fish stew.)
Sung Moon.
Did you find it?
(Stay quiet.)
- Did you find it? - I found it.
I found it.
Someone else will find the other one.
(The Meal Card mission is over.)
Time is up.
We're doomed.
(The others return empty-handed.)
- Did you find it, Soo Yong? - No.
I didn't find one.
Who found it?
- Let's eat. - Is it Ji Hyo?
(Let's eat, Jong Kook.)
(A few minutes ago)
(Jong Myung searched everywhere in the museum meticulously.)
(He found something in the tree.)
(He grabbed something.)
(He remains quiet.)
Will this be right?
(He remains quiet until the mission is over.)
Let's go.
(He's competent like Jong Kook.)
He found one.
- Did he find it? - Jong Myung found one.
He's hilarious.
He told me, "Let's eat."
(Jong Kook is impressed.)
- It felt like a horror movie. - It's because he's hungry.
Team Jong Kook and Team Ji Hyo...
will eat.
- The others will watch them eat. - Okay.
Let's go to the restaurant.
(Team Haha and Team Seok Jin are forced to be on a diet.)
(At a chicken soup restaurant)
We finally get to eat.
- Do you smell it? - It smells delicious.
- It smells good. - Goodness.
It's going to be delicious.
Kwang Soo, this is amazing.
This is authentic.
It's nutritious.
(It's a chicken soup set for their 7th anniversary.)
It looks impressive.
Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you for the meal.
Let's eat.
(I'll debone the chicken for you.)
Goodness.
(What a lucky day.)
The chef did a good job cooking the chicken.
- It's so tender. - Isn't it?
The soup is amazing too.
It's hot.
(He devours a chicken leg.)
You ate both chicken legs.
No, there's one left.
(Jae Seok finds him greedy.)
(He denies it.)
There's one left.
(There are only bones left.)
Where did it go?
- There is one left. - Let me see.
I only had one.
Did you leave the bones after you finished?
- No, I didn't. - What?
(He's flustered.)
Did you eat from our pot?
(What do you mean?)
I only had one.
(He denies after eating it unconsciously.)
- I'm telling the truth. - You have something on here.
- Where? - It's on the other side.
I only had one.
- The meat is at the bottom. - Eat it.
- Wasn't it a bug? - Was it?
(Didn't he eat a bug?)
Was it a bug?
- Did you eat it? - It wasn't a bug.
- It was a bug. - Was it?
- It seemed like a bug. - Was it really a bug?
- Was that it? - Did you eat a bug?
Wasn't that the bug?
(Did he eat a fly?)
I'll digest it.
(A bug is a source of protein after all.)
Come in.
Team Seok Jin and Haha are on the left.
- This looks delicious. - Look at that.
(They're buckwheat crepe and fried crab.)
There are crabs and fried food.
It looks amazing.
There are fried crabs.
Let's start.
Everything looks delicious.
Gosh, food on our table makes me sad.
(It's a minimum food amount.)
I don't feel the shell at all.
- Is it tender? - Yes.
- Isn't it delicious? - Yes.
(He wants at least a drop of the stew.)
Ji Hyo.
- Yes? - Can u sell a crab for a dollar?
- Do you mean the fried crabs? - Yes.
- For a dollar. - A dollar?
On top of that, we'll show a personal charm.
- A personal charm? - Yes.
Show us.
I can catch this bowl of rice.
(He'll toss and catch a bowl of rice.)
I bet you've never seen it.
(He's being serious.)
(His personal charm with a rice bowl has never been shown.)
(Will he impress her and win a fried crab?)
(He misses it.)
(Unfortunately, the rice falls on the table.)
We'll eat it anyway.
Were you supposed to catch it with your hands?
(You don't deserve fried crabs.)
Geun Sik can mimic the voice of a detective from "Tazza".
He'll do it for two pieces of buckwheat crepe.
(He asks for buckwheat crepe.)
(Will Geun Sik mimic such a famous line from "Tazza"?)
He'll do it for two pieces of buckwheat crepe.
I know what it is.
I've never done it before.
(He's never done it before.)
How can I do it all of a sudden?
- Do it standing up. - You've never done it before?
Do it with modesty.
They'll give it to you out of pity.
I can't wait to see it, Geun Sik.
Do it with modesty.
If he does a good job,
Jong Kook should give him buckwheat crepe.
Sure.
(He gives it a try for 2 pieces of buckwheat crepe.)
(He's been failing all day. Will he surprise everyone?)
Agui got off before that.
There was a game in Nonsan.
"Over there..."
(Which line is that?)
(There's no such line in that movie.)
Geun Sik.
Say something more.
I've never done it before.
- It was so sudden. - Do it one more time.
Isn't that the voice of your father?
(Are you mimicking your father?)
- Seriously. - Listen, everyone.
Do it one more time. Do it once more.
I don't know what to say.
It's not such a big deal.
- All right. - Okay.
- Okay. - Will it require strength?
Let's not be penalized today.
You're having a hard time today, aren't you?
I'm tired.
What are you working on these days?
I'm so tired.
It feels like...
we've spent several days together.
- That's true. - It feels like a week.
- I feel like we spent a night. - I know.
- Is the shoot usually like this? - What?
Do you usually shoot like this?
- No. - Is that so?
Take a look at Soo Yong.
(He appears.)
He's about to collapse.
- Can we get an IV? - He's about to die.
I need medication.
What are you talking about?
The color of his face looks terrible.
Next mission is called Pull Out the Radishes.
(Pull Out the Radishes)
It's called Pull Out the Radishes.
- Pull Out the Radishes? - Pull Out the Radishes.
It's a team competition.
The defense team lies down with their arms linked.
Two members of the attacking team must pull...
the other team members off of the mat to succeed.
After two members pull them out,
the other two will take their turns.
- Heavy people have an advantage. - Teams will switch roles.
The team to pull out the other team more quickly wins.
Each team has one chance to pass their turn.
The winning team...
gets 10 dollars and a member exchange opportunity.
- Member exchange? - A chance to exchange?
(The winning team gets to exchange a member?)
Do we have to exchange a member with a lot of money?
We invited guests to join us,
so how do you exchange your real family?
You can do this.
I don't think you can exchange a real family member.
- Isn't that hurtful? - You have to make a decision.
(Will he guard his family...)
(or go for the win?)
We have to divide up the teams first.
Jong Kook is strong.
- Wook Min is strong. - Wook Min is strong too.
The two of you can do rock, paper, scissors, and pick team members.
- Me. - Okay.
Isn't that team...
- stronger? - I like that team...
- or this team. - That team is good.
- I like that team. - Kwang Soo's team is good.
Pick heavy people.
- Pick heavy people. - From there?
- Yes, from that side. - How much do you weigh?
I weigh 100kg.
He doesn't look that big.
(He must have 100kg of muscles.)
- You weigh 100kg? - Yes.
Hang Ho and Wook Min weigh the same.
- He's 100kg. - I am.
- He weighs 100kg too. - Does he?
(Hang Ho is 100kg too.)
- I'm not. I don't weigh that much. - You don't?
- How much do you weigh? - 96kg.
He's 96kg.
(He's 4kg lighter.)
He's 96kg?
Please get started.
Rock, paper, scissors
(Jong Kook is the winner, and he chooses...)
Kwang Soo. Our youngest member.
(Kwang Soo and Hang Ho are heavy and tall.)
- Great. - Jong Kook.
You're strong.
They're tall and heavy.
(Whom shall we choose?)
I pick Haha.
Okay.
(Haha and Geun Sik are witty and built.)
Haha is easy.
We just need to get Haha. The rest will follow.
Okay.
Let's go. Rock, paper, scissors
He's consistent.
Right?
(Wook Min pulls out scissors again.)
I come from a family of strong people.
- Where did you do business? - In all sorts of places.
Really? I see.
- We were everywhere. - Oh, really?
I usually don't work under people.
I know that.
- Do you want it? - All right.
Okay.
Yes.
Welcome.
Pick Seok Jin.
- I pick Seok Jin. - Yes. Let's go.
I can already see we're weak.
- We're already done. - No, we'll win.
Rock, paper, scissors
(It's scissors for him once again.)
- See? He lost again. - Did you do scissors again?
Wook Min keeps on losing.
- Did you do scissors again? - Yes.
- Wook Min keeps on losing. - He's stubborn.
What shall we do now?
- Well... - I pick Se Chan.
(Jong Kook picks Se Chan and Na Eun.)
Okay.
- You didn't pick Ji Hyo? - This is bad.
You chose them instead of Ji Hyo?
Let's do this.
This is bad.
(Team Jong Kook and Team Wook Min have been made.)
Try to unlink me. I'll defend.
- This is enough. - Let me see.
- Is this okay? - It doesn't matter.
- You should hold onto me. - You have to get the hand off.
- Do it the other way. - You have to get the hand off.
Jong Kook.
We're on the same team.
- It's for practice. - You can't do that.
You have to get a feel of it.
(In pain)
It hurts.
It's practice.
You have to know how it feels.
- That was just practice. - Practice?
- Lie down. - Do we lie down?
Lie down.
(They all lie down.)
What are you doing?
- Do I have to move sideways? - Wait. Move your arm.
Where should I go?
- We have to get closer together. - Get close.
- Move left. - Stick together.
- Right or left? - Left.
Here's next.
- Na Eun is free. - Sorry?
- Na Eun is free. - I'm not.
- She won't be eliminated. - Really?
You have five minutes.
In five minutes, we'll count how many are out.
Stop.
- I'll get them. - You go second.
No. Second?
We'll go second.
- Are you going to get them? - Yes.
- You can go after. - Right.
All right.
- Stand in order. - Go in order.
We'll go second.
- I'll go third. - You have to go in order.
- You can't go multiple times. - All right.
(How many radishes will Team Wook Min pull out?)
(Try if you dare.)
Let's do this.
- Ready. - Let's do this.
Let's do this!
We can do it!
- All right. - We can do it.
- Ready. - Let's resist.
(Pull Out the Radishes...)
(starts now.)
(Ji Hyo and So Min attack first.)
Go after Na Eun. We're in trouble.
Tickle her.
- Resist. - Tickle her.
No, resist. Resist, Na Eun.
(She yanks at Na Eun's hair.)
Don't pull her hair.
- She's pulling my hair. - You can't do that.
You can't pull her hair.
- Take her out. - They're moving right. Move right.
Move right. Good.
- Stick together. - You can't bite!
You can't bite.
Don't bite, So Min.
We're in trouble. Can't you go for Na Eun's arms?
- We got it. - You got it?
- Get her arms. - Resist.
Resist. Move to the right more.
I did it.
- We did it. - We got it.
Move right.
(The ace member, Ji Hyo, shakes up the defense.)
All right.
No! No!
Let go. No!
(Na Eun's foot touches the outside of the mat.)
- She's out. - She's out.
Na Eun is out.
- Na Eun is out. - That was a good one.
Na Eun is done.
Next.
(Haha and Sung Moon are next.)
Resist.
Keep going.
Good job.
- It has to touch the ground. - Touch it on the ground.
(Haha suppresses Jong Myung...)
(while Sung Moon touches his foot on the ground.)
- We did it. - You're out.
Jong Myung is out.
Okay.
Jae Seok!
(Hold on tightly, Sae Ho.)
(Sae Ho lets go.)
(You should get rid of radishes that are not worth the time.)
(Dragging)
(Is this the end?)
(We'll try to survive.)
(Jae Seok is not helpful. He's out.)
Jae Seok is out.
(Wook Min and Geun Sik are in charge of the heavy radishes.)
Go for him.
Good job.
Hold him.
- Good one. - Drag him.
(They pull together,)
(and the other team is being dragged.)
(That's so cool.)
Do it all together.
- Touch his head. - Touch his head on the floor.
- Come out. - Let go.
Let go!
- Let go. - In 1, 2, 3.
Let me go! Let me go!
Let go!
I said to let go!
(Jong Kook resists desperately,)
(but his foot touches the ground.)
- He's done. - Jong Kook is out.
Jong Kook is out.
You can't do that.
Did you throw me out?
You're trash.
- No. - Did you take him out?
Hurry.
Pass.
- What should we do? - Pass.
Get Sae Ho.
Let go!
(Screaming)
(He makes animal-like sounds.)
(Ripping)
(They keep pulling.)
What's that?
(You can see his bare skin.)
(He unexpectedly exposes himself.)
(He's in tatters.)
(Yelling)
(He lets out a naked and painful cry.)
(Summer is the season for off-shoulder tops.)
Tickle Kwang Soo.
(He holds onto Hang Ho.)
They're so strong.
(There's 1 minute left.)
Kwang Soo!
Stick together.
Kwang Soo, don't squish my right foot.
That hurts!
Kwang Soo.
- I'm sorry. - Don't squish my right foot.
Kwang Soo, stop.
Free my right foot.
No.
You can't.
Don't do it.
We're in trouble.
- Take both out. - Take both of them out.
These two are going together.
- Kwang Soo. - Haha.
- Haha. - Who's this?
Get my arm.
(Kwang Soo's back gets exposed.)
My wrist is getting squished, Kwang Soo.
(Ripping)
(Kwang Soo's underwear is revealed.)
Hey!
(Kwang Soo is flashing rainbows on his back.)
(Say hello to Mother Nature.)
Let go.
- Stop it. - Don't.
- You can't! - Don't go, Kwang Soo.
Let me go!
Let go!
(That's still not enough.)
- Go for his foot. - Try the foot.
- Take his foot out. - Come on, Kwang Soo.
Take his leg out.
(They go for Sae Ho who's barely holding on.)
Let's go. In 1, 2...
- Touch his foot on the ground. - In 1, 2, 3.
That's good. Touch it on the floor.
His legs are too short. They don't reach.
His legs are too short.
(It's almost touching the floor.)
10 seconds left.
We're almost there. You can do this.
You can do this!
8, 7, 6,
- 5, 4, - 5, 4,
- 3, 2, 1. - 3, 2, 1.
- Okay. - Time is up.
(Team Jong Kook defends successfully.)
Kwang Soo.
(They're completely exhausted.)
My ear hurts.
How far did you pull up my underwear?
- What have you done? - What happened?
Someone performed a colonoscopy on me.
My underwear almost went through my throat.
Good job, Kwang Soo.
That was great.
- Thank you. - Good job.
You did well.
Whose is this?
Most things will be mine.
Great job.
(His pants fall off.)
(He shows his underwear.)
(His pants fall off easily with the smallest movement.)
What are you doing?
Kwang Soo.
What's wrong with you?
- I'm sorry. - Na Eun is here.
- What are you doing? - I'm sorry.
- Why did my pants get so loose? - I'm sorry, Na Eun.
Why did my pants get so loose?
I'm sorry that you saw that, Na Eun.
What happened to my pants?
Kwang Soo.
- What on earth happened? - Goodness.
What happened?
I was standing still, but why did they fall off?
(4 members get pulled out, and 4 members survive.)
Let's switch places.
(They switch positions.)
- Get ready. Let's go. - We can do it.
Let's do a cheer in 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Will Team Jong Kook take out more members?)
- Get ready. - I'm angry.
Set.
(The team competition starts.)
(Se Chan and Na Eun start the attack.)
- She's out if she's off the mat. - No.
(So Min's foot touches the floor.)
- She's out. - So Min is out.
(Jae Seok and Sae Ho are up next.)
Okay, pull now.
Come on.
- He's out. - Seok Jin is out.
- Seok Jin is out. - He's out.
- Get closer. - It's this side.
- It's this side. - Come here.
Come here now.
- One. - Don't let go.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
Did you separate them?
- Kwang Soo, pull now. - Pull now.
- Pull. - Pull.
(At that moment, Jong Myung lowers himself.)
(He grabs Wook Min's leg.)
You got it.
Come on.
(He puts down his foot on the floor.)
He's out.
(Jong Myung grabs Wook Min's muscular leg.)
- He did it. - Wook Min is out.
Wook Min is out.
Who's up next?
Is it us?
- Yes. - Is it our turn?
(Jong Kook and Hang Ho enter.)
(The real game starts.)
Get closer.
- Get closer. - Get on top of him.
- Is it our turn? - Get closer.
(Today is the day...)
(the radish field gets destroyed.)
(Soo Yong is the first victim.)
- What's going on? - No.
(Soo Yong is eliminated instantly.)
(He can only resist once and scream 3 times.)
He's out. We're up next.
- We're up next. - Who is it?
- Come on. - What are you doing?
(Only 1 minute remains.)
Geun Sik, you're strong.
He's so strong. He's pulling everyone.
(Geun Sik grabs onto all the members.)
He's so strong.
Pass your turn if you can't do it.
- Pass your turn if you can't. - Pass it.
- It may be possible. - Pass.
- We're next. - Hurry up.
Pull them up.
Grab someone in the middle.
Go.
Come on.
Be careful of the foot.
What happened?
(It's a brutal attack.)
(He throws a fit.)
What happened?
- What's wrong? - My foot.
- Hurry up. - Come and pull now.
- Are you okay, Sae Ho? - Hurry up.
Are you okay, Sae Ho?
Come on, you can do it.
(It's a strenuous task.)
- Bite him. - You're doing well.
Ji Hyo is almost out.
- Ji Hyo is out. - Ji Hyo is out.
- Okay. - It's our turn.
- It's our turn. - Come this way.
- It's our turn, Jong Myung. - Hurry up.
(He calls for Jong Myung.)
- Wait. - Hurry up.
(He speaks impolitely as he's in a hurry.)
Jong Myung.
In 1, 2.
- Three. - Come on.
Sung Moon is out.
- Okay. - It's Jong Kook.
(Screaming)
(Let's go home, Geun Sik.)
(Sung Moon and Geun Sik are out.)
- Who's next? - It's me.
Here I come.
My goodness.
That was excellent.
We were at a disadvantage.
We work well as a team.
I completely agree.
It was great.
I'm not joking.
Geun Sik hasn't won once.
Not even once.
That's true.
He didn't win during Yu Jae Seok's Game.
Poor Geun Sik.
"What do you want to eat the most?"
He answered, "Grapes".
Goodness.
He wanted grapes.
- What should he do? - He wanted some grapes.
(It's Round 2.)
- What? - That's how to do it.
- This is a good strategy. - Should I lie the other way?
- That's a new strategy. - Look at that.
- Like this? - That's a good idea.
That's a good position.
Na Eun and Jong Kook will start.
Let's go, Jong Kook.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Come in.
(Na Eun and Jong Kook start.)
- Get ready, set. - You can do it.
Okay.
(They separate Soo Yong first.)
They're moving everyone.
Resist with your legs.
Resist.
(The whole group is being pulled.)
(He grabs Soo Yong's pants.)
(He pulls with all his might.)
(Pulling)
That won't work.
(He's in tatters.)
- Wait, Soo Yong's pants got torn. - You're doing well.
(Shocked)
- His pants got torn. - They're his pants.
His pants really got torn.
- They're his pants. - Why?
Jong Kook tore them.
- No. - He's out.
Soo Yong is out.
Turn toward this way.
Pull them by the leg.
Grab the leg.
Let's pull.
1, 2, 1, 2.
- 1, 2. - Wait.
- Hold on a minute. - He's out.
- He's out. - He's out.
- Jong Kook is up next. - Na Eun.
Come on, Na Eun.
- Let's pull them up. - Keep yourself wrapped.
- Pull him up. - Move out of the way.
(Geun Sik the Radish is pulled again.)
(His strength is always surprising.)
Move out of the way.
(Geun Sik and Ji Hyo are about to be eliminated.)
(They'll be eliminated at the same time.)
(She separates before being eliminated.)
- Who's next? Go. - Hold on.
It's Kwang Soo.
Pull Ji Hyo out.
(It's good to see you, Kwang Soo.)
Come on.
(This is today's main competition.)
(They use fancy techniques.)
(It's entertaining for the audience.)
Hey.
Stop it.
(She gives him a special massage.)
Get out.
(He expresses pleasure with his whole body.)
(He pushes Ji Hyo out with all his strength.)
She's out.
(Will she be eliminated...)
(by Kwang Soo?)
No, she's not out yet.
(Ji Hyo is Wonder Woman.)
Ji Hyo is impressive.
(She overcomes the biggest risk.)
Hurry up and help me.
Hang Ho.
Eliminate Ji Hyo now.
Hurry.
(Hang Ho carefully attacks Ji Hyo from behind.)
Come on.
(Come with me if you don't want to be bald.)
She's out.
(Ji Hyo is finally out.)
Goodness.
(Why did you pull out my neck?)
(Kwang Soo, life is a game.)
I feel like we won.
- You won. - Good job, Ji Hyo.
- You were impressive. - Good job.
- I feel like we won. - You were impressive.
- We won. - You won.
You led your team to victory.
That was impressive.
Your record is 2 minutes and 2 seconds.
(Team Jong Kook prepares their defense.)
I'm in pain from top to bottom.
(He feels the aftereffects on his scalp and bottom.)
(What is this?)
What's wrong?
I think I'm bleeding.
- It's okay. - You're okay.
Besides, Jong Myung is a doctor.
You'll be okay.
- Isn't he a plastic surgeon? - Right.
- He's still a doctor. - Of course.
A plastic surgeon can do it too.
He's great at stitching up wounds.
Can he sew this up too?
(Can he sew this up too?)
(My jeans are torn.)
The jeans are his own.
(He has no stylists.)
- He has no stylists. - Are you okay?
He has to go home that way.
(He has to go home grabbing onto his jeans.)
Look at his belt.
His belt is torn too.
Jong Kook!
He has no stylists.
They're his personal belongings.
He has to sew it up himself.
Even his belt got torn.
Jeans like these are in fashion these days.
It's in fashion.
I was just going to tear them anyway.
(Nonchalant)
He's so generous.
- Thank you. - He's so generous.
- Thank you. - It's in fashion now.
I was going to tear them.
(Soo Yong is a fashion leader.)
It's in fashion.
- Put these on. - Put these on.
(He changes into work pants.)
Change into those behind the folding screen.
- Do that. - That'd be better.
(Go change.)
Wait, don't go in there.
(Don't go behind the folding screen.)
- Don't go there. - It's okay.
Don't go behind the folding screen.
No!
Don't go there, Soo Yong!
(Soo Yong was such a nice friend.)
(Most of all, he was a fashion leader.)
Say goodbye to him.
(Eye-catching)
(Any pants look great on him.)
Soo Yong.
Take your jeans.
(Don't forget your limited-edition jeans.)
Don't throw them away here.
Shouldn't you wear those over the jeans?
It's better this way.
(Soo Yong has become fashionable.)
All right.
Team White won the game.
You'll get...
(Team Jong Kook wins 20 dollars.)
I feel bad.
Where should we keep the money?
Everyone gets five dollars.
Hey, you gave me only four dollars.
(Are you tricking me again?)
- You can have it all. - Why?
You worked so hard. You can have it all.
(We won thanks to you.)
Take it all.
(Se Chan and Na Eun have 53 dollars.)
Everyone, as I said earlier,
the four teams that just won...
can choose to change their partners.
Let me know quietly.
Come closer.
We can change our partners.
We won 20 dollars. We don't have to change partners.
(Their decisions will change the situation of mission fees.)
Jong Myung, please come here.
(Jong Myung makes a decision first.)
We come from a family with tradition.
(Will he take his family tradition into account?)
(He makes a decision without hesitation.)
Please go back to your position.
Na Eun.
(It's Na Eun's turn.)
I'm curious what she will choose.
She might surprise us.
What will Se Chan do if she wants to change her partner?
I was happy today.
(Na Eun has made a decision.)
(Everyone has made a decision.)
Jong Myung...
(Did he choose a rich partner...)
(or his little brother?)
(Who did he choose?)
Jong Myung does not want to change his partner.
(Little brother, you're all I have.)
- That's beautiful. - My brother is smart.
Give your brother a hug, Jong Kook.
(A beautiful decision has been made.)
That's beautiful.
Na Eun...
(Na Eun has made a choice.)
Se Chan...
(Se Chan is waiting to hear her decision.)
(They made beautiful memories together.)
(Se Chan has been so kind to Na Eun.)
(We shared happiness together.)
(You share the same feelings with me, right?)
Na Eun does not want to change her partner.
(Na Eun does not want to change her partner.)
(I'll be with you.)
- Na Eun is loyal. - Se Chan is so kind to her.
Se Chan will suffer for at least two months.
Na Eun.
(The share a shy handshake.)
- Sae Ho. - Yes.
- Your current partner is Jae Seok. - That's right.
(It's time to see if Sae Ho still wants to be with Jae Seok.)
I always wanted to be close with Jae Seok,
but he never showed any response.
(Jae Seok always felt a bit distant.)
(This is Sae Ho's chance to express his feelings.)
Sae Ho wants to change his partner.
(I'm going to find someone else.)
(I'll make a new family.)
(Speechless)
Yes.
You're a betrayer.
No, I'm not.
It's just my situation.
I have to change my plans.
(Success means more to me than Jae Seok.)
Hang Ho's current partner is Kwang Soo.
He has no reason to change his partner.
He wants to change his partner.
(You're wrong about that.)
(It can't be because of money.)
He has no reason to change his partner.
He wants to change his partner.
(They have different ideas.)
But...
(But)
Both Hang Ho and Sae Ho...
want to change places with Na Eun.
(Both Hang Ho and Sae Ho want to change places with Na Eun.)
What?
(They want to be with Se Chan as he has the most money.)
It's because he has the most money.
- Actually... - I hope Hang Ho will win.
So...
We have so many different kinds of equipment today.
Oh, that one.
What's that?
We have so many different kinds of equipment today.
(It's an electric shock roulette.)
Na Eun should participate too.
Yes, that'd be fair.
- All right. Na Eun, - Gosh.
- Hang Ho, - I'm so scared.
and Sae Ho, put your finger in this.
The one who gets an electric shock will be eliminated.
Keep your finger in it.
I'm scared.
Start.
(The equipment is turned on.)
Stick it in.
The one who gets an electric shock will be eliminated.
(I hope it's not me.)
Na Eun, keep your finger on it.
(Screaming)
Yes!
(Se Chan has a 50-percent chance to stay with Na Eun.)
Hang Ho is eliminated.
I'm relieved.
I don't have to do it again.
What happens now?
- He'll stay with you. - He will?
You'll stay with me.
Yes!
(Disappointed)
(They stay together although their trust is broken.)
I don't want to do that again.
Na Eun and Sae Ho.
I want to stay with Na Eun.
Ready, start.
(The game starts.)
Na Eun.
If Sae Ho has to stay, he'll be so embarrassed.
(Sae Ho is worried after expressing his feelings.)
(Screaming)
(I guess this is the end.)
Yes!
(Goodbye, Jae Seok.)
All right. The partners have changed.
Na Eun becomes my partner.
I'm here.
I wanted to stay with Na Eun.
Na Eun, let's win the game.
Let's win.
(My heart will be with you.)
There is only one mission left before the finals.
What is it?
You're going to play Knock Them Out.
What's that?
You'll lose in these three cases.
If your hands come unclasped, if your back touches the floor,
or if you go out of the mat,
you'll lose.
The winning team will win 10 dollars...
and get the chance to change partners.
It sounds hard.
(It's the last chance to change partners.)
This is our last chance.
(Who will win the game and avoid the penalty?)
We're one.
Let's do this.
- They're coming. - Come here.
Come here.
- Come. - 1, 2, 3.
Your feet smell.
So Min.
(The smell of So Min's feet is distracting Jae Seok.)
What are you doing?
(It's a smelly attack.)
(I don't like the smell.)
(Smell attack)
Jae Seok is out.
Come on.
Na Eun, run away.
(Moving)
Are you attacking me?
- No. I'm supporting you. - You're attacking me.
I'm supporting you.
(I said we were one.)
- Are you attacking me? - No. I'm supporting you.
You're attacking me.
Push him.
- Push him. - There you go.
- Push him. - Na Eun, that's great.
That's great.
Soo Yong and Seok Jin are out.
(Both Seok Jin and Soo Yong are out.)
Hey, So Min!
(Who is next?)
Se Chan.
Let's attack Se Chan.
(So Min noticed Se Chan.)
Se Chan.
Let's attack Se Chan.
Why are you attacking me?
(Girls versus Se Chan)
Hey! It hurts.
(The old partners have become enemies.)
What should I do?
(I couldn't attack my lady.)
(I'll leave for your sake.)
(Screaming)
Na Eun is out.
(So Min betrays Na Eun because she isn't much of a help.)
I can't believe her.
(How dare she attack my lady?)
(My lady, I will avenge you.)
So Min is out.
(The betrayer meets her end.)
(I will protect you until the end even if we are in different teams.)
Let's go slowly.
(While this beautiful story was unfolding...)
Wook Min. Wook Min.
Let's get Jong Kook.
- Hurry up. Let's get Jong Kook. - Let's get Jong Kook.
- Wook Min, let's go. - Wait a minute.
(They recruit the strong Wook Min.)
Let's go.
(Let's put our faith in Wook Min and attack.)
In 1, 2, 3.
He won't budge.
What is going on?
Wook Min, kick.
- Can I kick? - Kick his thigh.
- Kick his thigh. - In 1, 2, 3.
- This is ridiculous. - Here comes Jong Myung.
Here comes Jong Myung.
(Jong Kook, let me help.)
(With a kind smile,)
(he enters the fight to defend Jong Kook.)
Push him.
It worked.
(It took him 1 minute to come, but 1 second to get eliminated.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Good luck, Jong Kook.)
We are almost there. Push.
- Can he go over the mat? - No, it's prohibited.
- It's prohibited. - He will be eliminated.
(Is this the end of Team Brothers?)
(Of course not.)
My goodness.
(He runs towards the top.)
(Jong Myung is out, but Team Brothers is on the rise.)
Gather around.
(Move out of my way.)
Ji Hyo is out.
(He easily overpowers the ace member.)
- Ji Hyo is out. - Wook Min is out.
(When was Wook Min eliminated?)
Wait a minute. Who should push Jong Kook?
Wook Min, go.
Bye.
- Wook Min. - What is this?
(He eliminates Wook Min because he isn't much of a help.)
- There we go. - My goodness.
His effort was futile.
(Team So Min is eliminated.)
Wait a minute. We should join forces now.
Geun Sik, don't go that way.
He is attacking me.
(I am Park Geun Sik.)
(I always pay back.)
No, no.
You are out.
- No, he isn't. - Geun Sik, come here.
(Geun Sik kicks.)
Se Chan is out.
(The fighter's cells within his body are awakened.)
(He uses force...)
(to challenge Jong Kook to a one-on-one match.)
Hurry up.
(If I beat Jong Kook, victory will be near.)
Jong Kook is out.
(He beats Jong Kook.)
Geun Sik, you did it. We can win.
(We can win.)
(We can get back up.)
(Let's join forces and seize victory.)
He is the last one.
Geun Sik will win for the first time.
Let's go, Geun Sik.
Geun Sik.
- Geun Sik. - You jerk.
(We seized victory as one.)
Sung Moon is out.
(They can't contain their joy after taking a win.)
Good job.
(He kneeled,)
(shouted,)
(and showed his worst in the day of embarrassment.)
(The friends were ashamed of each other,)
(but united once again after a win.)
Congratulations.
Good job.
(Haha and Geun Sik acquire 10 dollars.)
I am glad.
(Proud)
Everyone gave him a standing ovation.
I will give you half.
Now,
Geun Sik, please come forward.
It would be hilarious if Geun Sik changed his partner.
Please tell me if you want to change your partner.
I will announce Geun Sik's decision.
Geun Sik, who has been Haha's friend for 20 years,
(Geun Sik has been Haha's friend for 20 years.)
decided...
to change his partner.
(Thank you for giving me a chance.)
- My goodness. - You are good.
I have so much respect for Geun Sik.
- I respect him. - I respect him.
Geun Sik.
Geun Sik is good.
- It's the right choice. - Geun Sik is good.
He wants to change places...
with Sae Ho.
- Am I chosen again? - He wants to change places.
(Se Chan, the wealthy man, is very popular.)
He has good taste.
(Hello, my wealthy friend.)
(Haha is disheartened.)
Geun Sik hugged him right away.
(Geun Sik hugged Se Chan as if they were friends for 20 years.)
(Let's hug as well.)
I can't believe him.
(You know how I feel, right?)
Before we have the final mission,
I will reveal the rankings in terms of the mission fees.
I bet we are the last...
now that Haha has a new partner.
Jae Seok and Na Eun have 60 dollars and 50 cents.
- That's a lot. - 60 dollars?
- Jong Kook and Jong Myung. - Isn't it me?
- Are we in second place? - 45 dollars and 98 cents.
Are we in second place?
Geun Sik must be very poor.
- He must be very poor. - You have no idea.
In third place are Se Chan and Geun Sik.
How much do we have?
With 33 dollars, you are the richest member.
- Oh, nice. - He has 8 dollars and 15 cents.
I am so annoyed. He has 8 dollars and 15 cents.
(He contributes about 19 percent to the team.)
I have so much respect for you.
In fourth place are Kwang Soo and Hang Ho.
- Are we in fourth place? - 34 dollars and 30 cents.
I revealed the rankings...
because you have a chance to turn the tables.
Let's do this.
(How can they turn the tables?)
The final mission of the summer vacation special...
with the dangerous families gives a chance to turn the tables.
It's Revival of the Families.
In front of you are two game boards with numbers and units.
One will throw a shoe to the board with numbers,
and the other will throw a shoe to the board with units.
The team will receive mission money that follows the combined amount.
(The team will receive mission money that follows the combined amount.)
(Last place will get an ice shower.)
(1st, 2st, and 3rd places will get presents.)
Na Eun, we shouldn't be greedy.
Let's aim for the middle.
- 2 or 10 would be nice. - 5.
Five is a good choice, too.
This is nerve-wracking.
Let's go!
Let's do this.
Na Eun, let's do this.
(Let's throw a shoe to the middle and remain in 1st place.)
- That's good. - She is good.
(The shoe makes an arc, and flies towards the board.)
You did it.
(She gets 4.)
Go for 10 dollars.
(The number is 4.)
(If Jae Seok gets 10 dollars, they will get 40 dollars.)
- This is unbelievable. - Four is a good number.
It bounced in.
- What was it? - 40 dollars.
(If Jae Seok gets 10 dollars,)
(they will remain on the top.)
Get one cent.
- Then they will get 4 cents. - Get 1 cent.
- Let's get 40 dollars. - Get 1 cent.
(Please let me get 10 dollars for the unit.)
(Will they get 40 dollars...)
(and run away with a total of 10 dollars?)
- 1 cent. - 1 cent.
(He gets a cent unit.)
(Jae Seok is unlucky through and through.)
(He doesn't disappoint.)
(The other unlucky members pay their respect joyously.)
- I am in awe. - In front of it is 10 dollars.
This puts a lot of pressure on me.
Throw it however you would like. Don't be nervous.
- It's okay. - Okay.
You can make money by performing more surgeries.
Throw it.
Clear your mind, and throw the shoe.
Here I go.
- Okay. - All right.
That's too rough.
(He tries to avoid 1.)
(My goodness.)
(Glancing)
(I am older than Jong Kook,)
(but why am I worried about his reaction?)
Jong Kook, smile.
Smile, smile
There is no hope.
Still.
10 dollars.
(He gets 10 dollars.)
- Jong Kook. - Jong Myung is flustered.
(It sends a chill down his spine.)
Smile, smile
(Seething)
(They get 10 dollars, and fail to take 1st place.)
That was incredible.
- Aim for the end of the board. - Okay.
- The left side is okay, too. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Please do it right, Geun Sik.
- Geun Sik. - It's a good throw.
(Even though he only has 8 dollars,)
(he will redeem himself.)
Geun Sik.
(He becomes lucky and gets 10.)
(He is on fire towards the end.)
(He moves his new friend's heart.)
You're my friend.
That's incredible.
Geun Sik has renewed energy.
That's incredible. They are already in third place.
He got 10? If they get 10 dollars, they win.
- Nobody can beat them. - It'll turn your lives around.
(He needs Geun Sik's luck right now.)
Ready.
Geun Sik.
(He needs Geun Sik's luck right now.)
(It's Se Chan's turn to get 10 dollars.)
(There's a 25-percent chance.)
(Go for your dreams.)
(It was a good day for Se Chan.)
(Will he get 1st place as well?)
(It's a penny.)
(He becomes breathless.)
What's that?
(That's what you get for leaving me.)
(When you're once unlucky, you're forever unlucky.)
My gosh.
It's a penny.
You're a true comedian.
- You're a comedian. - Geun Sik.
I'm sorry, Geun Sik.
(Se Chan and Geun Sik add a penny to 41 dollars and 15 cents.)
Should I do this? You do the other one?
Okay.
This team currently has 34 dollars and 30 cents.
They get 1st place if they get 30 dollars.
- First place? - I like those eyes, Hang Ho.
- It's looking good. - I mean it.
(What did he work so hard for?)
(He endured so much pain.)
(If he gets over 3, it would all be worth it.)
(Is it really 3?)
(Everybody is watching. Is it possible to turn the tables around?)
10!
What's that?
(This team is very unlucky. He lands on 0 exactly.)
- What's that? - 10!
(The screen is not frozen.)
(Kwang Soo doesn't even get a turn.)
(He freezes while getting ready to throw his shoe.)
(What went wrong?)
Come back. It's done.
It's done.
How's this even possible?
(Kwang Soo and Hang Ho shouldn't have stayed together.)
This is so funny.
(They finish off with the same amount.)
- Let's go, Sae Ho. - Let's go!
(Haha and Sae Ho are currently in 5th place.)
(Haha gets 2.)
Go for cent.
It's cent.
(Sae Ho gets cent.)
(So Min and Wook Min are currently in 6th place.)
That's good. He got three.
- Good. - It's cent.
(She gets cent.)
That's three cents.
Good.
- It's 4. - It's 4.
(Ji Hyo gets 4.)
A dollar.
(Sung Moon gets a dollar.)
(They stay in 7th place with 19 dollars and 80 cents.)
This team is our hope.
Would they be able to get 100 dollars?
- Let's get 1st place. - We just can't get 0.
We just can't be last place.
That's right. This decides who's in last place.
- 50 dollars is good. - I'm praying.
- That's right. - 50 dollars is good too.
- I'm rooting for you, Seok Jin. - Let's show them!
Soo Yong!
- In 1, 2, - He's strong.
- 3. - That was good. It's 10.
(They're seasoned comedians. This is what variety shows are about.)
10!
(It's a 10.)
(It's a small miracle born out of hope.)
(We're going to be in 1st place.)
It's 10.
(That's touching.)
It's okay.
It's not yet.
- Don't be nervous. - I am nervous.
You're in the spotlight. How many years has it been?
(He feels the pressure of being in the spotlight.)
(All cameras are on me.)
If he gets a dollar, he won't be in last place.
(If he gets a dollar, he's not in last place anymore.)
Let's go.
(If he gets 10 dollars, he's in 1st place.)
(This shoe is Seok Jin's hope.)
Good job.
(Please give me a miracle.)
It's 10 dollars!
(It's a 10-dollar miracle.)
(Seok Jin's team is the winner.)
(He gets 100 dollars in 1 shot.)
That's 100 dollars.
(They're shocked.)
Really?
I'm happy for you.
Are we in first place?
(They turn the tables around with 113 dollars.)
That's insane.
Ji Hyo and Sung Moon are in last place.
You can pick one team that'll join you for the ice shower.
(It's irrelevant to us.)
This is insane.
Don't look at them.
Please discuss first.
(Ji Hyo and her brother are thinking.)
I...
(Ji Hyo doesn't like moths.)
What's that?
That punk.
(How dare you fly at Ji Hyo?)
- How dare you? - Goodness.
- How dare you? - Are you crazy?
- How dare you? Are you all right? - Are you okay?
Are you okay, Ji Hyo?
Are you okay?
- Come here, Ji Hyo. - Did you see what I did?
- Are you okay? - I was the first to charge.
Are you really okay?
(He snatches it,)
(and fights with it.)
It flew away. There it is.
It's flying away.
He has nothing in his hands.
(He tries to earn some points from her, but fails.)
Stand up.
(That didn't work.)
Try being more sincere when acting.
All right.
- My ribs hurt. - We've made up our minds.
We've made up our minds.
On my cue, please say the team's name...
out loud.
(Who will join them?)
Ji Hyo, I love you.
That's so random.
That's too random.
What's she doing?
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Hurry.
(This is X-rated.)
Kwang Soo and Hang Ho are not doing anything.
In 1, 2, 3.
(It's time to decide.)
(Who will be joining them for the ice shower?)
Team Green.
(Congratulations, Kwang Soo and Hang Ho.)
Congratulations
(They all feel the same way.)
(Welcome to the ice shower.)
Please join us.
I'm coming.
It's summer, so it'll be refreshing.
(Welcome. Is this your first time getting showered in ice water?)
There's so much water.
That's a lot.
Hang Ho did nothing wrong.
Do they stand up?
(I guess that's what the penalty is.)
This is the Family Special for Running Man's seventh anniversary.
It's the final ice shower penalty.
Ji Hyo, Sung Moon,
Kwang Soo, and Hang Ho.
Let's go.
- Let's do this. - Let's count down from seven.
This is the seventh anniversary after all.
Set, go.
- 7, 6, 5, - 7, 6, 5,
- 4, 3, 2, 1. - 4, 3, 2, 1.
Let's go.
(They get showered in ice water.)
(Not again)
(His pants fall off again after the radish game.)
What happened?
(Look at your pants, Kwang Soo.)
- Your pants. - Kwang Soo.
(What about my pants?)
What are you doing?
- What are you doing right now? - Hey.
- What are you doing? - This is too funny.
Put them back on.
My gosh.
This is too funny.
(You're the scene stealer.)
He's unbelievable.
This is not even possible. Is this a fiction?
It's not a fiction.
Is this computer graphics?
(What are we supposed to do about Kwang Soo?)
I'm sorry.
(Thank you for joining us for the 7th year anniversary.)
(Hot summer in 2017)
(There are 3 summer specials.)
(Part 1 is Find the Boss.)
(They are rising stars.)
(Park Seo Joon and Kang Ha Neul are ready for Running Man.)
(It gets more intense.)
(Part 2 is Bad Girls' Generation.)
(They're an idol group with 10 years of experience.)
(They're not naive anymore. They're seductive ladies.)
(It's more thrilling.)
(Part 3 is Running Man's Horror Special.)
(There are ghosts in here?)
(It's 100-percent real.)
(Don't trust anyone in here.)