(Parental guidance is advised for viewers under the age of 12.)
(Running Man roamed the world for Global Race Part 1 and Part 2.)
(They betrayed each other endlessly for I Go Stickers.)
(The first race took them to a dangerous tourist attraction.)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear)
(The second race took them to a place for 1 percent.)
(So Min and Kwang Soo)
(Se Chan and Haha)
(They were chosen to go to a place for 1 percent.)
(Now)
(The upgraded Global Project Part 3: Half and Half Tour)
(The production crew and Running Man have a showdown.)
(It starts now.)
(Sinsa Park)
(Fall is just around the corner at a park in Seoul.)
(What does the day have in store for Running Man?)
(Why are there only two members?)
I can't believe Kwang Soo and I are in the same team.
Do you want to see us play dirty?
- Is this a competition? - Tell us what we are doing today.
I am confident when it comes to a competition.
I don't want to lose in a competition against him.
(While one pair has equally-matched rivals...)
- We were partners. - We make a strange pair.
(Another pair has unlikely partners.)
That's right. I think it will be great.
(What kind of a mission do the pairs have?)
Running Man's new project will begin today.
Before we get started with the race...
You will have to play a game for the mission money.
- It's called Friends, Go. - You will play Friends, Go.
Friends, Go.
- Friends, Go? - Friends, Go.
I will explain the rules.
Two members will make a team for this mission.
You will each spin a wheel with gender or the year of birth.
Then you will go to a celebrity who fit the combined condition...
and complete a hidden mission...
- separately. - We will each have a mission.
You will decide your mission with a draw.
The first one to complete the hidden mission gets 10 dollars.
(The first one to complete the hidden mission gets 10 dollars.)
- That means we aren't a team. - We aren't a team.
- Let's take this to the end. - He needs to be...
taught a lesson.
- I am confident today. - He needs to be taught a lesson.
- I will bet my everything. - He is a dirty liar...
who needs to be taught a lesson.
She is bound to betray me when money is involved.
- No, you and I are a team. - Hey,
forget it.
I would trust a stray dog over you.
I would trust the fish in Han River over you.
- Ji Hyo. - What will you do to me?
- Loyalty! - I am scared of her.
The first four members to arrive at the place for the opening...
after completing the mission...
get additional 10 dollars.
(The first 4 members...)
(get additional 10 dollars.)
She is bound to betray me.
- Ji Hyo. - I am afraid...
she will trip me like Kwang Soo.
The members will leave if their partners are taking too long.
- They will move on their own. - Wouldn't it be better...
- to move separately? - Seriously.
(What does the fate have in store for the competitors?)
Here are the wheels.
- My goodness. - We need to spin it right.
It will be a disaster if we choose the 50s.
There is the 50s.
Who was born in the 50s?
- They will be over 60 years old. - Heung Gook was born in the 50s.
Joo Byung Jin. Lee Hong Ryeol.
- I can give you a list. - There are quite a few of them.
There are a lot of them.
Weren't you born in the 50s?
What are you talking about?
I will spin the wheel.
(Ji Hyo spins the wheel with the year of birth.)
Please.
(She needs to pick her peers to have an easy mission.)
The 70s.
(A celebrity who was born in the 70s)
(So Min spins a wheel to determine the sex.)
- Male. - Male.
Meet a male celebrity who was born in the 50s.
My goodness.
(Seok Jin and Jong Kook get...)
It's nice.
- Female. - Female.
(A female celebrity who was born in the 90s)
A female celebrity who was born in the 90s.
Female in the 90s.
Let me get the 90s.
(Haha and Se Chan get...)
(a female celebrity who was born in the 80s.)
The 80s is a wide pool.
So many celebrities were born in the 80s.
- Firstly, - Male or female.
let's spin this wheel.
It will be better...
(They want to meet a female celebrity.)
- We may not get what we want. - It doesn't really matter.
That's right.
- Let's go. - I will spin the wheel.
(Please let it be a female.)
(Dreams do come true.)
Yes. We got a female celebrity.
If we get a female celebrity who was born in the 50s,
I don't know anyone.
- We can do this the easy way. - That's right.
- All right. - Jae Seok.
(Please let us get the 80s or the 90s.)
- The 90s would be a good choice. - That's right.
(The 70s)
Someone who was born in the 70s?
(A female celebrity who was born in the 70s)
(It's much different from their expectation.)
- Shall we... - Goodness.
A female star who was born in 70s...
(They're searching online.)
(Who was born in the 70s?)
Lizzy lives around here.
I can't find anyone.
What are you going to do?
You ruined it.
- It's ruined because of you. - Because of me?
- Me? - Yes.
- The 70s is not a problem. - It's not a problem?
- It's hard because it's a woman? - Yes.
(It's hard to find a woman born in the 70s.)
(Will Jae Seok and Kwang Soo be able to find the right celebrity?)
All right, Kwang Soo. Turn your head around first.
- Jae Seok will pick one first. - Okay.
(They must clear their hidden mission before the other does.)
Pick one, check what's written inside, and put it back in.
(What is Jae Seok's hidden mission?)
(Make her grab you by the collar.)
(How should he make her want to grab his collar?)
(What is the unlucky Kwang Soo's hidden mission?)
Gosh, hold on.
(Make her splash water on you.)
(Why did he have to pick such a mission?)
(Ji Hyo and So Min pick their hidden missions as well.)
(Make the guest splash water on you.)
Gosh, it's bad. What should I do?
(Se Chan and Haha pick their missions too.)
Gosh, what should I do?
Gosh, is yours hard?
My goodness.
(They finish picking their hidden missions.)
Why...
Gosh, it's so frustrating.
(He's reminded of Sook while looking through phone numbers.)
- Let's try calling her. - Should we?
(He calls his close friend, Kim Sook, who was born in 1975.)
Sook seems to be very busy these days.
(Will she accept their sudden request and join them?)
Hi, Jae Seok.
Sook, where are you?
- I'm home. - What's your plan for today?
- Me? - Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
It's 12pm now. Until when will you sleep?
Sook.
What's the use in waking up? I have nothing to do.
You have a point there.
Did you play computer games and sleep late last night?
- No. - Then?
I worked a bit.
- Did you work until late yesterday? - Yes.
Until what time?
7pm.
(She worked until 7pm.)
That's not late at night.
That's not even late. 7pm...
- You finished early yesterday. - That's before dinnertime.
I worked too much yesterday.
I was supposed to leave work at 6pm sharp.
- So you worked an hour overtime. - Yes.
Hello, Sook. I'm Kwang Soo.
- Hey, it's been a while. - Yes, hello.
Oh, it's Running Man.
- Yes. - How did you find out?
You two are together, so it's Running Man.
I see. You're very smart.
- It has nothing to do about it. - Stay still.
- Stay still. - But...
She likes to be complimented.
Hello?
(You need to give many compliments in order to cast someone.)
You must be a genius.
- Sook. - Yes?
- Don't you live in Mapo? - Yes.
We need to do a simple mission.
Gosh, I'm too lazy.
We can ask anyone to do this mission together,
but we decided to ask you after 30 minutes of discussion.
It's you.
- It has to be someone we know. - It's you.
- Right. - That's how we decided to ask you.
Gosh, I'm too lazy.
- Well, Sook. - Yes?
We'll visit you soon.
Don't you dare.
We won't go to your house.
You need to hold a housewarming party.
Wash your face, and come out.
There's my favorite coffee shop nearby.
Okay, we'll go there.
(They'll go with their missions to see her.)
Seeing how it's starting to rain,
I think we'll have to ask either Na Rae or Gook Ju.
This gloomy weather will go perfectly with Na Rae.
- I'll try calling her first. - Try calling Na Rae.
All right.
- Hello? - Hello?
- Hey. - Where are you?
- I'm home. - You don't work today?
Well... Not until later at night.
I have filming tonight.
- Oh, is that right? - Yes.
So you're free right now.
Are you free now? Where is your house?
- It's Seogyo-dong. - Gosh, that's so close.
- Na Rae. - What is this about?
What year were you born in?
- I was born in 1985. - Okay, 1985.
And your gender?
(What is Na Rae's gender?)
What? Gender? I'm probably a female.
That's a success for now then.
So you have time right now.
Yes. What is this about?
Tell her to wait about five minutes.
I'll call you in five minutes.
I'll call you after five minutes, so go back to sleep.
- Okay. - Hey, I can smell...
your bad breath even through this phone.
(Being careful)
It's just my feeling, right?
Sure.
Okay, I'll call you later.
- Okay. - Bye.
(They succeed in casting Na Rae.)
(So Min is calling someone.)
Hello.
I'm so sorry for calling you after such a long time.
I'm filming Running Man now.
- Ji Ho. - Oh, now?
(Is it Oh Ji Ho?)
Hello. Ji Hyo's with me now.
Hello, Ji Ho. I'm Song Ji Hyo.
- Oh, hello. - We're filming now.
You were born in the 70s, right?
- Yes. - Okay, thanks!
Can we go meet you for a second?
You'll come to where I am?
- Where are you? - Where are you?
I'm at a department store in Gangnam.
- So you're in Gangnam. - Gangnam.
Okay, then we'll go to where you are now.
Let's go.
- Thank goodness. - We found our target.
(They move to meet Ji Ho.)
He keeps texting me.
(He must be surprised by the sudden cast.)
So how should I clear my mission?
This is going to be tough.
Is your mission okay?
No, my mission isn't easy either.
(They're now worried about their missions.)
I'm in trouble.
So Min, don't think about betraying me.
I won't betray you. Why would I betray you?
I want to get along with you...
and be on your side.
What?
(She likes to be on someone's side.)
I didn't know you liked that stuff.
So Min, I didn't know that.
I'd like to be on your side.
- Let's try calling him now. - Shall we?
Tell him that we're almost there.
The number you have dialed...
(His phone is turned off?)
(They're about to arrive, and his phone is off.)
His phone is turned off.
- What? - Goodness.
What happened?
His phone is...
Hold on. It can't be.
(She tries calling him again.)
(The phone is turned off. Leave a message after the beep.)
What should we do?
Did he turn it off on purpose?
He must not have done it on purpose.
No, right?
No way.
- That can't be. - No way.
- If he turned it off on purpose, - Let's try calling him again later.
then I'll have to think back on my life.
I'll really have to think back on my life.
Goodness.
I once had to wait...
for my crush at a place where we promised to meet,
but he did not show up.
Goodness.
- It happened to me several times. - Goodness.
You're so hilarious.
- The phone is turned off. - Gosh, what should we do?
(He's still out of reach.)
I can't help but laugh now.
Did he turn his phone off on purpose?
- No, right? - I'm worried he might be waiting.
- I know. - He might not know about this.
Text him, and see if he answers.
(Do they have to wait for his call or move to somewhere else?)
- The phone's turned off. - Daddy.
- Hello? - Ji Ho.
- Ji Ho, where are you? - Ji Ho.
(Ji Ho is back!)
Your phone was turned off.
I'm about to cry now.
(It's like a reunion with their brother after 10 years.)
We were so surprised. We're nearby.
We're near the place.
- What? - Do you have time?
I do.
We're right in front of the department store.
(Ji Ho, we're on our way.)
Where is he?
Let's go.
(Ji Ho, we're on our way.)
Hi, Ji Ho.
(She's so glad to see him.)
- Hello, Ji Ho. - Hi.
- Nice to meet you. - Hello.
(Actor Oh Ji Ho)
Your daughter got so big.
- Right. - Say hello.
- Hi. - Your phone was turned off.
- It freaked us out. - Why...
- I mean... - We just filmed a drama.
Sorry...
My daughter put it in airplane mode.
It freaked us out.
Thanks to you, we were able to film a drama out of it.
Thank you so much.
- Sorry. - Hi.
Each of us have a mission to clear with you.
You need to find out what that is.
(Who will clear the hidden mission first between the two?)
Sook. Take your time.
(She's on her way to clear our missions.)
Sook.
Hi, Sook.
(She's here to meet them even though they asked her so suddenly.)
Sook, sorry.
- It's even raining. - Thank you.
(Comedienne Kim Sook)
- It's raining. - Gosh.
You came out right away.
(They woke her up on this rainy day.)
You came straight out from your sleep.
- Is your house near here? - Yes.
Where is it?
When did you move here?
- Please don't bother me. - When did you move?
It's Jae Seok's birthday today.
What? August 14.
- Right. - It's right.
- It's your birthday. - Thanks.
- Thanks for coming. - August 14.
You gave me a birthday gift by coming here.
Happy Birthday, Jae Seok.
Thanks for coming to my birthday party.
What birthday party?
- Then you should eat something. - This isn't a birthday party.
- No. We already ordered. - Should I order something?
It's your birthday today.
Let's have your birthday party. Should we have a meal?
- Do you want to have lunch? - Lunch?
There are a lot of good restaurants in this area.
- Really? - Yes.
Let's eat.
- I should treat you to a meal. - No, I should treat you.
- You don't make a lot of money. - No, I'll buy then.
- Men don't earn a lot of money. - That's true.
You're buying.
I can't stand men spending money.
That's right. She is very generous.
I ought to buy you a meal. Eat before you go.
(He's only observing the situation.)
- Now is the time. - Oh, my.
(Thus began a beef brisket party out of the blue.)
Have I ever had beef brisket for lunch?
- Who knew I'd be having this? - Do you want the sauce?
You don't want the sauce?
I'm happy to buy you a meal for your birthday.
It's a nice meal for my birthday.
(What on earth...)
(are we doing here?)
Let me go to the bathroom.
- Where's the bathroom? - It's outside.
Okay.
(Great. This is my chance.)
(Since his competition has left, he begins his scheme.)
(My face has to be splashed with water.)
Eat up, Kwang Soo. Do you have meat?
(He's displaying his conning skill he has been mastering.)
- What is it? - It's nothing.
- Did the oil get into your eye? - Yes.
Oh, no. What should we do?
- Are you okay? - Do you have eye drops?
- Sorry? - Do you have eye drops?
- No, I don't. - Should I pour some water?
What should we do?
Should I pour some water on it?
- Yes. - Should I?
- Look at me. - Is my eye red?
(Splashing)
- I have to pour a lot on it. - Really?
- Are you okay? - I think I'm okay.
- It doesn't feel hot now? - No, it doesn't.
- Then you're okay. - Thank you.
(Hey, I just accomplished my mission.)
Kwang Soo, you have accomplished the mission.
- You... - Sook.
I'll call you.
What is going on?
(I'll get going. Finish the meal with Jae Seok.)
I have to finish the meal.
- Sook. Yes, I know. - We ordered three servings.
- Did Jae Seok leave? - No, he didn't.
Did he finish his mission and leave?
- He finished and left? - Yes.
(Where... When...)
Goodness, he's a total jerk.
- What is this? - Jae Seok left!
Goodness. Sook...
(Oh, my. How can she...)
How could she grab me by the collar as soon as she walked in?
Goodness, that surprised me. I was about to scream and just leave.
(The moment they met Sook at the cafe)
(Sook came in looking angry.)
(She grabbed him by the collar right away.)
(Sook, that was excellent.)
(Jae Seok got up pretending to go to the bathroom.)
(See you later, Kwang Soo.)
Hold on.
(Without knowing this, Kwang Soo was trying hard.)
He really left like that?
He left? What was the mission?
(Oh, no. What am I going to do?)
Eat up.
(Anyways, eat up.)
Really?
Eat before you go.
(Kwang Soo and Sook ate 3 servings of beef brisket.)
I'll call Na Rae.
(Haha and Se Chan came to meet Na Rae.)
Hello.
Na Rae.
Hello, Haha.
Did you put on makeup?
- Sorry? - Are you wearing makeup?
No, I didn't do anything.
- Really? - Tell her to just come out.
- Do I have to wear makeup? - No, that's not necessary.
But you have to look pretty on camera.
- Do I look repulsive without it? - No, you don't.
No, I just thought it might be helpful if you looked your best.
- No, I don't need to be helpful. - You don't?
Na Rae, can we film at your house?
- At my house? - Yes.
Or we can film outside. It doesn't really matter.
But what are you filming now?
We are not doing much. We are just...
- We are just going to catch up. - That's right.
- We're going to catch up? - Yes.
It doesn't have to be your bedroom. What about Se Chan's room?
What are you talking about? Stop it.
I've never been to her house.
My house is such a mess. But we can film it upstairs, can't we?
- Upstairs? - That works too.
- It's not a problem at all. - I got it.
Then we can talk upstairs.
- Thank you. - Send us your address.
- Okay. - Thank you.
- She's so kind. - She's so cool.
(They are on their way to Na Rae's house.)
(They arrive at her place.)
Goodness, she's a professional. She left the door open.
She's an expert. She wanted us to walk in naturally.
Does she leave it open when you come?
Stop talking nonsense. It's my first time here too. I'm serious.
I've never been here. Why would I go to Na Rae's house?
Let's do our best.
- Haha, don't interfere. - Okay, okay.
She left the door open. I'm telling you. She's an expert.
What is that? Gosh, that startled me.
- What was that? - Goodness.
(What have I just seen?)
Haha, let's get out of here. It's scary in here.
- This is so weird. - Her house is so scary.
- Look at this. - It's like a haunted house.
Take a look inside.
What is that? What is it?
(Who are you?)
- What is it? - It's a cardboard cutout of her.
- A cardboard cutout? - Gosh, that scared me.
I was so surprised.
(The cardboard cutout is protecting the gate like a guardian.)
(The actual person, scarier than the cardboard cutout, appears.)
Why are you so late?
(Park Na Rae, a comedienne born in 1985)
Put that cardboard cutout away before I kick it.
- Why? - Let's go in. Thank you by the way.
Thank you for inviting us in.
- This is the famous Narae's Bar. - That's right.
- This is it? - This is the bar,
and this is the DJ booth.
(There's a mirror ball and a booth. It's as good as any other club.)
Na Rae. Well...
- Can you lighten up the room? - No, I can't.
- No, I can't do that. - Children watch our show.
My house can't have bright lights.
Oh, my.
There are small things here.
- Is this your guesthouse? - Yes.
(A world-wide collection of liquors)
Goodness. This is...
This is like Na Rae's Bed and Breakfast.
Even your outfit looks like an owner of a bed and breakfast.
(This is the trendy outfit of bed and breakfasts' owners.)
I need a guy like Lee Sang Soon.
- And that guy is you. - Stop it.
- Cut it out. Stop it. - You're my Sang Soon.
That's enough. People will look us up online then.
Haha, coming here wasn't a good idea for me.
Na Rae, this place is awesome.
In summer, this is a good place to hang out.
(Look at how spacious it is.)
Goodness, it's so hot.
The ceiling might be too low for others, but it's perfect for you.
Of course, but doesn't that apply to Haha too?
I'm sure it does.
- That's true. - He'll fit perfectly.
What is that projector? Is that for watching movies?
Yes.
With whom do you watch movies?
I ought to watch them with you.
(Do you want to watch a movie?)
It's been eight months since I moved here. I'm not lying.
- I've never watched a film here. - Really?
I didn't have anyone to watch it with.
(This is a dangerous place.)
You know,
- Se Chan gives me goose bumps. - Why?
It's so surprising how he's acting like this is his first time here.
- It's my first time, Haha. - I'm serious.
- Exactly. - He's surprising me today.
This is my first time coming here.
It's true. I haven't even been to her previous house.
Just take your pants.
(I'm just kidding.)
I was just joking.
(This is a joke that she wished was true.)
You look cute without makeup.
- Where does she look cute? - She has a cute face.
(He's touching the water bottle for his mission.)
No, she looks terrible right now.
Hey, don't make me angry.
(He gets rid of any chance for Se Chan to do his mission.)
What's going on?
He got to me.
What's going on? Is that alcohol or what?
What are you doing?
(He empties the bottle completely.)
What was that?
- What was that about? - That was my water bottle.
- Do you have water? - Sorry?
- Do you have water? - Do you want some water?
- No. - I'll get you water.
- Get me cold water then. - Okay.
Thanks.
- Why did they come here? - Na Rae, come here quickly.
- Get me some water, please. - I'll be back.
- Na Rae. - Yes.
- Please bring me cold water. - Na Rae, hold on.
Haha, I'm sorry, but I only listen to my husband.
Haha.
Haha, why did you drink up all my water? Why?
- Na Rae. - Yes?
Don't you think you're being unfair?
- What are you talking about? - I mean...
I think I can see that...
some other men stayed at your house other than Se Chan.
- Goodness. What are you saying? - I mean...
How could you do that when you're with Se Chan?
How could you see other men?
- Haha, let's come clean now. - Honey.
(A soap opera unfolds.)
What's going on between you two?
- Tell me. - I...
- What's going on between you two? - Nothing's going on.
Don't do it.
- Tell me now. - Just tell him now.
- Tell him everything now. Tell him! - Honey.
- I can't. - Come here. Go upstairs.
Go upstairs, and tell him what happened between us.
- What kind of skit is this? - Na Rae.
- Sit down. - What's the mission?
Take a seat. If you have something to tell me,
go ahead.
Let's date.
- What? - This was the mission.
You filthy animal.
(Haha is feeling impatient.)
- Hold on. Na Rae. - Yes.
- Don't you remember how we greet? - I do.
- It's an unusual way of saying hi. - That's true.
Then let's say hello to each other.
Get up.
Na Rae and I just met.
- Oh, my, Haha. - It's different. Oh, my!
- Nice to see you - Nice to see you
(Haha is grabbed by the collar.)
(Haha wins 10 dollars.)
(Has he completed his mission?)
What is this?
What?
(Could this be...)
(Splash)
Thank you. I'll be nice.
Thank you, ma'am.
- Get out of my house. - I will.
- "Get out"? - I want to clean up,
but I have to go.
- Get out. - Thank you.
What is going on?
- Thank you. - Na Rae,
I'll come over again.
Se Chan, take your pants.
(I know you're in a hurry but...)
What pants?
Why are you in such a hurry?
(We appreciate Na Rae's cooperation.)
This mission is too difficult.
It is.
- They're shooting. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hi.
(Whom are they visiting?)
- Hi, Eun Ji. - Eun Ji.
Hi. Sorry for the trouble.
(Jeong Eun Ji from Apink)
- Eun Ji. - Yes?
Why don't we play a game?
- Sure. - As soon as you arrive?
- Running Man... - What game?
- We play games on Running Man. - It's too obvious.
- What are you doing? - What?
- You're acting weird. - What's with your cap?
It's nothing. Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jong Kook wins.)
Best 2 out of 3. Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jong Kook wins again.)
Best 3 out of 5.
- Play with me. - Why are you so bad at it?
Why are you so bad?
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Eun Ji.
(Jong Kook finally loses.)
- Okay. - Eun Ji.
- Look. - What is this?
On Running Man, you get hit on the forehead as penalty.
(You didn't know, right?)
- Really? - Yes.
(Was your mission getting hit on the forehead too?)
- Are you sure it's okay? - Of course.
- I can hit you very hard. - It's funnier that way.
(Jong Kook is so happy to be hit on the forehead.)
(Hitting)
- Eun Ji. - What is this?
- What is going on? - I succeeded.
(Jong Kook wins 10 dollars.)
I have to go now.
- Okay. - Where are you going?
Thank you.
Eun Ji is the best.
- Eun Ji. - Yes?
- Good luck. Win the game. - Thank you.
See you, Eun Ji.
See you.
(Jong Kook heads to the opening venue.)
Let's go.
Okay.
I'm leaving first. Let's go.
(Sorry, Seok Jin. I'm leaving.)
Let's go.
(Running)
Where is he?
Has he left?
Has he?
Gosh, he's unbelievable.
How could he leave?
Hey! Jong Kook!
(All 4 members have completed their missions.)
(They're on their way to the venue.)
The first four people who arrive...
will win additional 10 dollars.
I'm sure we'll arrive first.
(Thanks, Na Rae.)
When you're in a hurry, you get stuck at the lights.
It's strange.
Thank you.
(Jae Seok arrives at SBS Prism Tower.)
(Haha and Se Chan arrive as well.)
Run!
The flags are still there.
(Jae Seok)
(Se Chan is following.)
(Haha passes Se Chan through the side door.)
What?
- The flags are still here. - What?
(Jae Seok arrives first.)
(Haha follows.)
Hey.
Se Chan.
(Se Chan wins 3rd place.)
Jae Seok and Haha, who arrived first,
will win additional 10 dollars.
(Jae Seok and Haha wins 10 dollars.)
Only them? What about me?
(You said the first 4 people would win the money.)
What happened?
Ji Hyo, what are you doing there?
(Ji Hyo and So Min, what are you doing there?)
(An hour earlier)
My forehead is so hot.
Right? "Mom"?
(Hitting)
What is this?
Thank you.
(So Min won 10 dollars.)
Drink some water. It's new.
(Ji Hyo completes her mission too.)
I'm done. I'm sorry.
We're the first ones. Let's hurry.
Hurry.
Ji Hyo arrived first, and So Min arrived second.
- Unbelievable. - Let's hide.
(Relaxed)
Jae Seok and Haha, who arrived first...
(They have been watching them compete.)
will win additional 10 dollars.
(What are you doing there?)
(Good job, guys.)
You guys...
(The first 4 people win 10 dollars each.)
(Mission Money)
(SBS Prism Tower in Sangam-dong)
This morning, you completed missions assigned by the roulette wheel.
- Yes. - Today, a new project will start.
(A new...)
(project?)
- Again? - Following the first two tours,
the third global project is called...
Half and Half Tour.
(Half and Half Tour)
- Half and Half? - I want to go this time.
I was thinking of another name.
- I'm getting tired. - Isn't it just the same thing?
Shouldn't the name be Psycho Tour?
(Psycho Tour instead of Half and Half Tour)
- Psycho? - Psycho?
- Are we penalized all year around? - What is this?
We haven't even left yet.
Let's think after we come back from Indonesia.
- This is too much. - The Indonesia trip...
is scheduled in September.
First of all, please bring in the roulette wheel.
(Roulette wheel?)
- What? - Right now?
- We should burn all those wheels. - Roulette wheels again?
I don't like roulette wheels anymore.
We spin it right away?
- They're here. - They're big.
- What are they? - Thank you.
- Look. - It's empty.
- What's this? - What's this?
We asked each of you...
- where you wanted to go. - That's right.
There are eight destinations you recommended...
and eight other destinations...
that were not chosen in the first two projects.
You'll be visiting one of those 16 places.
(They will be visiting one of the 16 places.)
- I like it. - I've never been to Rome.
- Not many get to visit there. - I'd love to visit.
It sounds great.
- It's hard to find time otherwise. - Rome sounds nice.
- Colosseum. - That's right.
You have to visit there once in your life.
I can't wait.
Look at that.
Rocky Mountains.
- It looks amazing. - Rocky Mountains.
Look at that. Fly fishing.
- Fly fishing. - Fly fishing.
Catching salmon.
- "A River Runs Through It". - Exactly.
- Brad Pitt. - Brad Pitt.
You don't get to visit a place like that otherwise.
That's the place I want.
Where's that?
It looks amazing.
The US has amazing places.
What is that?
Antelope Canyon.
- Look at that. - It suits Haha.
I knew it.
Look at that.
- I love places like this. - When would you go there otherwise?
- The water is so clean. - I love places like this.
- It's beautiful. - Bora Bora.
Nice!
- I'd love to visit that place. - It looks fantastic.
I knew it.
Look at that.
- Australia. - Australia.
- What is that? - It's pink.
It's a pink lake.
Amazing.
- Is there a place like that? - It's a pink lake next to the sea.
- It's pink? - Oh, my.
- Can you go in there? - Is there a place like that?
- It's right next to the sea. - Doesn't it look beautiful?
It's right next to the sea.
- It's beautiful. - Salar de Uyuni.
- You can take amazing pictures. - It's beautiful.
- Look at that. - Amazing.
You can't tell where the horizon is.
(Salar de Uyuni in Bolivia)
- What did So Min choose? - What did So Min choose?
- It's pretty. - It's Thailand.
- Krabi? - I've never been to Thailand.
It looks nice.
(Krabi, the dream vacation spot in Thailand)
(Beautiful rocks and beaches)
- I've never been to Thailand. - Really?
- Never. - You should visit there.
It's a place you want to visit.
Where did Kwang Soo choose?
(Extreme sports on Alaskan snowy fields)
- Why would you go there? - It's cold there.
Why would you go there? It's cold.
Why would you go there?
- Isn't that a penalty? - What's that?
It's not a penalty. Just watch.
(Snowy fields)
- Northern lights. - It's not easy to see them.
Can you see them in the summer too?
I'll remember what you just said.
I mean...
I'll remember.
- Northern lights... - I've been there.
You have?
- It's a place I want to visit. - What is it?
What is it?
(And)
(8 scary destinations chosen by the staff)
Oh, those places.
(Do you remember?)
(Spain, New Zealand, US, Indonesia, Australia, Brazil, Mexico)
(The world's tallest swing)
- What's that? - I remember now.
- What's that? - Have we seen it before?
We've seen it.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
- You show it to us every week. - We can never forget.
That place is included again.
Why do you relieve your stress on us?
(It's a 14-story, vertical water slide.)
- I can't do it. - I'll go.
- I can't do it. - It's in Brazil.
(Insano Water Slide in Brazil)
- That's impossible. - It looks intense.
Where is that?
Is it Copper Canyon again?
Didn't it disappear?
It's an active volcano in Indonesia.
Why would you visit an active volcano?
Why did they hang a hammock at an altitude of 2,078m?
Why would you do it?
I don't like hammocks.
- It's a zip-line. - Look at that.
Goodness.
- I'd go. - I can do it.
I couldn't do it in Dubai.
- What's this? - Come on.
Is that a free fall?
That must be thrilling.
How did they even find it?
- Seriously. - How did they even find it?
(Extremely anxious)
- What should we do? - I can't go.
How can we go?
Remember that, Kwang Soo.
Why are you telling me?
- Why are you telling me this? - I can't go.
- I can't go either. - Remember that.
We took a look at eight locations.
Every week, it will be...
places recommended by the members versus by staff.
If you win, a place recommended by you will be selected.
Mine is great.
If the staff wins,
a place recommended by the staff will be selected.
It'll be recorded on the roulette.
- Is that so? - Yes.
The member to be sent to the location...
will be selected by spinning the roulette.
Every week, the final winner of the mission...
will purchase a name tag and attach it on the roulette.
He selects a member to go to the location by spinning it.
(The member to be selected is sent to a designated location.)
- We purchase the name tag. - We have to buy it.
(A member may be selected multiple times.)
I see.
Once the members and locations are determined,
Half and Half Tour will end.
You determine the final location by spinning the roulette.
Selected members choose another member to accompany them.
- They will go together. - We get to select someone else.
(The chosen member can choose another member.)
Before we start the mission,
you will choose the location for today's competition.
- Do we have to select one? - Let's go together.
Locations recommended by you are on the left.
The red ones are recommended by the staff.
Decide who will pick...
- from each side. - This is stressful.
I don't feel good about it.
Pick a good one.
- How? - Which do you want?
- Pick Canada. - Which do you want?
- Australia. - Let's go to Alaska.
Let's see.
- One has to be good. - Pick Canada.
- Show it to us. - Let it be Alaska.
- Canada. - Put it back in.
- Pick again. - It isn't Alaska.
- What is it? - Salar de Uyuni.
- Okay. - It's Salar de Uyuni.
(He picks Salar de Uyuni.)
(It's a site that you must visit before you die.)
(Se Chan's choice, Salar de Uyuni)
- It's Bolivia. - Bolivia.
- It's Salar de Uyuni. - It's amazing.
- For this one... - I don't want to go.
Avoid places like zip-lining.
It can't be the hammock.
- I don't want free falling. - It can't be the hammock.
(It's time to pick from the other pool.)
(Which location recommended by the staff will be selected?)
- Active volcano. - What will it be?
- Pick the active volcano. - Right.
- The active volcano? - Bitten by a crocodile is better.
- Crocodiles are better. - Let's go to the US.
- What is it? - That's great.
- Isn't it the US? - It's New Zealand.
- New Zealand? - Where is it?
- It's Nevis Swing. - It's a ride.
It's Nevis Swing in New Zealand.
- What if it breaks? - It's like bungee-jumping.
(Nevis Swing in New Zealand)
(Let's jump off a cliff from 160m.)
- New Zealand? - What's in New Zealand?
It's that swing.
- Which one is it? - When it breaks, you fall.
Gosh, we can't do that.
Locations are selected.
This is impossible.
(It's Salar de Uyuni versus Nevis Swing.)
Round One of Half and Half Tour.
The result of the mission must be half and half in order to win.
It has to be half?
- What does it mean? - It has to be four each.
It's a competition between members and staff of three rounds.
Based on the result, you gain or lose your mission money.
If the total mission money is more than 200 dollars,
Team Running Man wins.
- We're on one team. - That's right.
- We're one. - Why did we fight?
Here's why individual mission money is important.
The member to obtain the highest amount of mission money...
is given a chance to purchase a name tag for the roulette.
(Highest mission money gives a chance to purchase a name tag.)
Money is important.
Sacrificing your gain for the team will be important.
- Is it individual or team? - Doesn't that mean...
it's an individual competition?
(He doesn't think twice about it.)
- Right? - That's possible.
I know what I must do.
(He won't play for the team.)
If I get selected, I'll travel with you.
I'll spend all my money on buying your name tag.
(While expecting competition, they move to the next location.)
We're heading to a restaurant.
It's a chance to win additional mission money.
We'll play Hit or Miss.
(Round 1 is Hit or Miss.)
- That sounds great. - Okay.
(They're determined to compete.)
What is it?
You'll play Hit or Miss as a team.
You win if the result is split into half of the group.
(The result must be split 4 by 4.)
Different results?
You can win 10 dollars for each round.
(10 dollars per round)
That means one of us has to give 10 dollars.
If you win, we'll give you 10 dollars.
If you lose, we won't give you any.
We won't take it from you.
- Okay. - That's good.
- Here's Round One. - What is it?
You must guess odd or even.
(Round One is Guess Odd or Even.)
Guess if the number of coins in my hand is odd or even.
You succeed if half of you guess correctly and half of you don't.
You'll win 10 dollars for mission money.
- This is difficult. - How can we guess?
- It's a great game. - It's 7 to 3.
The first four won't be important.
- Right. - The last four is important.
Only half of you must guess correctly.
I'm very bad at this.
In my neighborhood during childhood,
- I used to play a game... - To divide into teams?
to divide into groups.
- My friends didn't want me to play. - Was it because you were bad?
I was terrible at it.
I lost everything that my friends won.
I don't like friends like that.
You shouldn't play to begin with.
- He should give up his turn. - Right.
How could you be so tactless?
He should have gone home.
You should have gone home.
- He shouldn't play the game. - He should go home.
They're so mean.
(He's very disappointed.)
Let's start.
(They start the game including Jae Seok.)
Seok Jin is up.
I bought a lot of bread...
with money I earned from this game.
- We know by the sound. - It's odd.
- Three coins. - It's even.
(The opinions differ.)
(It's an odd number.)
- Odd. - He got it.
- We don't know yet. - You got it right.
- Should I guess wrong? - That's okay.
You can guess either way. It doesn't matter now.
Guess however you'd like.
Right, wrong, right, wrong is the best.
Come on.
- That's the best. - Even.
- That's incorrect. - It's okay.
- Okay. - We got one wrong.
- We got one wrong. - You're on the staff's side,
aren't you?
(You're on the staff's side.)
(What does he mean?)
- It's right and wrong. - He did well.
- You did a good job. - Really?
We have 1 right and 1 wrong.
They criticize you even when you did well.
(Kwang Soo is surprised.)
What he did made it easier.
1 right, 1 wrong is good.
I'm losing confidence.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
- I bet it's two. - It's even.
- Even? - I think it's two.
I think it's odd.
- Do what you think is right. - It's up to you.
It's okay for now.
- Go. - I think it's two.
- Even. - Even?
- Yes. - I think it's odd.
My guess is...
- even. - Even.
(Ji Hyo's guess is even, but it's odd.)
- It's okay. - You were right.
Do you see why I always lost?
(He speaks with confidence.)
Can you please be quiet?
- Stop calling out your guesses. - Okay.
So Min should guess correctly.
- Chul Min is good at shuffling. - Right.
- Even. - It's odd.
- It's even. - Even.
He knows the answer.
- Even. - It's odd.
- It's even. - Even.
He knows the answer.
(It's even indeed.)
The members in the front row are split in half.
(The result is split in half.)
Go.
(They're close to winning 10 dollars.)
It's even.
Chul Min took out one coin.
- It doesn't matter what I guess. - No.
It's even.
(Haha's guess is even.)
- It's odd. - Okay.
(There are three coins.)
It was incorrect.
- Shall I guess correctly? - Yes.
- You must guess correctly. - Is that so?
(They have 2 right and 3 wrong.)
It's odd.
(Is it a correct guess or not?)
That's incorrect.
Must I guess incorrectly?
Both of you must guess correctly.
(They have 2 right and 4 wrong.)
Must I guess incorrectly?
- Both of you must guess correctly. - This will determine the result.
Is it over if I guess incorrectly?
(If Se Chan is wrong, the game is over.)
I played this game a lot in Dongducheon.
(He feels confident.)
(He claims to be a king of Guess Odd or Even in Dongducheon.)
(Will he guess correctly?)
It's odd.
I think it's even.
(His guess is correct.)
Okay, what did I tell you?
I was good in Dongducheon.
Jong Kook.
Come on, Jong Kook.
We win if you guess correctly.
- I'll guess correctly. - He was good in Anyang.
This is easy.
- He was the best in Anyang. - I didn't play this game.
I told people to give me money.
(I told people to give me money.)
(He makes people want to give to him.)
Do you know what's amazing?
My guesses have been wrong all along.
He always called out the wrong guesses.
(He was always wrong.)
(When he called out even, it's odd.)
(When he called out odd, it's even.)
(His guess was always incorrect.)
- Odd. - It must be odd.
It must be even if Jae Seok chose odd.
- Should Jong Kook be wrong? - Odd.
- I should be right. - He should be right.
Odd.
(Will...)
(Jong Kook's answer be correct?)
(Even)
See? Jae Seok chose "odd". It means it's even.
Please stay out of this.
We're having fun.
You're not helping us.
- Just go home. - What's with you?
Go home, and wash yourself.
- You've been wrong every time. - Go home.
Go to bed early. We'll hang out by ourselves.
You know what?
It's Jae Seok's birthday today.
I'm sorry.
It's his birthday.
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
We just told him to go home.
- We were so harsh to him. - Happy birthday dear Jae Seok
I can't believe it.
My goodness.
How was I wrong every time?
All right. As it's Jae Seok's birthday today,
- One more chance? - if Jae Seok...
What if he has to be wrong every time?
If you're right 2 out of 3 times, we'll give you 10 dollars.
- All right. - That sounds good.
Is it a team competition?
If you're right 2 out of 3 times, you'll win 10 dollars.
Good luck.
You should overcome this.
Choose the opposite of what you think.
What if that's wrong too?
- It's your birthday. - I'll listen to you.
- What do you want to choose? - I want to choose "odd".
Even.
(Jae Seok chooses the opposite of his initial choice.)
(Will he be right this time?)
(Odd)
It's the opposite of what you say.
It's the opposite of your choice.
It's the opposite of your final decision.
- Don't do anything. - Not your first decision.
- Final decision. - The opposite of my final decision?
The opposite of your final decision.
- How can he be wrong again? - The opposite of my...
- final decision. - Final decision.
- The opposite of your answer. - Okay.
- Jae Seok. - Make up your mind first.
I have a strong hunch that it's even.
- I'd like to choose "even". - But you'd choose "odd".
- I'd choose "odd". - But it'd be even.
- My final decision... - In the end, it's odd.
would be "even".
It's odd then.
Odd.
(How will his second try turn out?)
This is hilarious.
(It's odd.)
(The opposite of Jae Seok's final decision)
This was it.
- This was it. - Try one more time.
- The opposite of your decision. - The opposite...
of my final decision.
- The opposite of my final decision. - Final decision.
I didn't know this game...
- was so mathematical. - Me neither.
- The opposite of my final decision. - Final decision.
(There is only one chance left.)
- What's your first thought? - What do you think?
I have a strong hunch that it's even.
Then you'd say, "odd".
- I'd say, "odd", but... - You'd say, "even".
I'd say, "even".
- Then you'd choose, "odd". - It's the opposite of that.
Then it should be odd.
- Then it should be the opposite. - It should be even.
- You should say, "even". - Hold on.
Just say your final decision.
My final decision is,
- "odd". - Then it's even.
- Then it's even. - Even.
Doesn't it mean that that's your final decision?
What am I supposed to do?
(There is no end to this.)
Then shout this.
"Odd, even". Then your choice is "even".
- "Odd but even" or "even but odd". - That's right.
It should be the opposite of your hunch.
My hunch is that it's odd.
- Then it's even. - Then it's even.
(Then it's even.)
- Shout it. - It's odd.
- The opposite is "odd". - Say, "even", but it'll be odd.
- It should be odd. - Don't listen.
- Even but odd. - You might win 10 dollars.
(Even but odd)
(It's the last chance. Is he right?)
(His final decision is "odd".)
- You might win 10 dollars. - Odd.
(Odd)
(Jae Seok has overcome his bad luck.)
Unbelievable.
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
(They congratulate him on winning 10 dollars.)
It's the opposite of my final decision.
That's how you overcome bad luck.
You can fight anything from now on.
- It's the opposite. - It's the opposite.
- I can overcome it. - This was...
the most exciting game today.
The opposite of your final decision.
- We're in front of the restaurant. - Okay.
You'll go in one by one and choose a dish.
Half and half.
- Is it that game again? - Half and half?
(Why would they go in one by one?)
(Last time, everyone had to choose a different dish.)
(Will they be able to settle their score today?)
- I want to eat. - Me too.
- I'll just choose what I want. - Me too.
Because you can plot...
- You go first. - Should I go first?
- I have no idea what this is. - See you.
(What mission will they be given here?)
Am I to choose between these?
(Fried rice and japchae rice, jjamppong and jajangmyeon)
I'll explain.
You can eat only if you find a partner.
The mission is called Eat with Your Half.
(Eat with Your Half)
Choose one dish.
(Choose 1 among the 4 dishes.)
If someone chooses the other half of the set you choose,
both of you can eat.
If you don't find a partner, you can't eat.
(To eat, they need a partner.)
I have to find a partner?
If you don't find a partner, you can't eat.
- I'll choose jjamppong. - Jjamppong.
- One more thing. - I love jjamppong.
If you choose jjamppong...
but more than one person chooses jajangmyeon,
- Does it become a competition? - you can...
choose one of them.
More people would choose jjamppong than jajangmyeon.
- Can I change my mind? - Yes.
I should choose something not many would choose.
That would raise my chance.
Okay. I choose japchae rice.
- You choose japchae rice. - Japchae rice.
- Please go upstairs. - Okay. Japchae rice.
Someone must choose fried rice.
(It's Ji Hyo's turn.)
Oh, my gosh.
(Why are you doing this to me?)
Why do you have to do this?
I choose jajangmyeon. I'm sure someone will...
choose jjamppong.
(Ji Hyo chooses jajangmyeon.)
If I choose jjamppong, I need someone who chooses jajangmyeon?
And If I choose fried rice, I need someone who chooses japchae rice?
My goodness.
I love this dish.
(He's in a dilemma.)
(But he doesn't want to choose what he doesn't like.)
(What will the Chinese food lover choose?)
I wanted to have jjamppong.
But I was sure someone else would choose it too.
I know. I hope someone chooses fried rice.
I'm sure there will be someone.
Please.
(Someone is coming.)
It's Jae Seok. What did he choose?
(I hope he chose fried rice.)
Did he already choose something?
(I hope he chose jjamppong.)
Fried rice...
- Did you choose japchae rice? - Yes.
(I chose japchae rice.)
(Did you choose japchae rice?)
(Disappointed)
Why? You chose japchae rice too?
- Why would you choose that? - Why would you choose japchae rice?
I like it.
Don't criticize my taste.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
As you said, I should have chosen the opposite of my decision.
- Why did I... - You have to choose the opposite.
We need two people to choose fried rice.
It's not easy.
I think Haha will choose fried rice.
- Then he has to choose between us. - Yes.
- I hope he'll choose me. - I'll be nice to him.
In the car, I said I wanted to have fried rice.
Someone might have heard...
and chosen...
I don't know.
Haha, please.
- Haha would... - Please choose fried rice.
Please.
Let's say I choose fried rice, and no one chooses japchae rice.
Then I'll get nothing.
(What will he choose?)
I chose this for Ji Hyo's sake
Is it rice or noodles?
- Why did you choose that? - I wanted soup.
I'll slap your face if you chose japchae rice.
(Please let it be fried rice.)
No way.
(We need fried rice.)
- We need fried rice. - Why would you slap me?
- Did you choose japchae rice? - What is it?
It's japchae rice.
(Why is he singing?)
(For Jae Seok's other half, Haha brings fried rice.)
Come here.
(He's proud of Haha.)
Were you about to slap me?
(He remembers what Jae Seok said.)
Seok Jin.
- Happy Birthday to you - Wait, Haha.
I'm going to eat
I'm going to eat no matter what
- He chose fried rice. - If there are three fried rice...
(It's time for Kwang Soo to choose.)
I should pick the other half of something others will choose.
Okay.
I choose fried rice.
- Fried rice? - Yes.
(He chooses fried rice.)
- May I change it? - Go ahead.
Jajangmyeon
(He chooses jajangmyeon instead.)
(Sighing)
Please don't make me choose.
(Kwang Soo struggles.)
Here he comes.
Which one is it?
- Kwang Soo. - It's this side.
(It's either jajangmyeon or jjamppong.)
(Did you choose the other half of jjamppong?)
(He brings jajangmyeon.)
It's jajangmyeon.
Goodness.
He has no choice but to fight with Jong Kook.
Gosh, this is tiring.
I'm already tired.
Can't I eat if someone brings...
- jjamppong? - Jong Kook will choose jjamppong.
It's difficult to eat.
I don't think Jong Kook will choose jjamppong.
Only one of you who chose jajangmyeon can eat.
The others can't eat.
- Really? - Yes.
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
I'll choose between jajangmyeon or jjamppong.
Please choose one.
I choose...
(Did he choose jjamppong?)
Look at that.
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
He chose jjamppong.
(They've waited for jjamppong.)
(My goodness.)
(Jong Kook has always chosen jjamppong for 7 years.)
(Did he choose jjamppong again?)
(What about today?)
I knew you'd choose jjamppong.
We discussed a lot on the bus.
That's why.
I thought many of you chose jajangmyeon.
- Jong Kook. - I chose jajangmyeon.
- Jajangmyeon... - Let's see what So Min brings.
This is annoying. There are four choices.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
I bet Haha chose fried rice.
Jae Seok chose japchae rice.
(He narrows down his choice.)
Kwang Soo probably chose jajangmyeon.
(What will Se Chan choose?)
Please go to the second floor.
Here's Se Chan.
Is he here?
(Please choose fried rice.)
It'd be incredible if he chose fried rice.
This is the only choice I have.
I'm sure of it.
Wish me luck.
(He should choose either fried rice or jjamppong.)
- I'm sure of it. - Which side is it?
Is it noodles or rice?
Many of you chose rice.
- Is it rice? - What is it?
(Se Chan gets flustered after looking at the others.)
(Did he choose either fried rice or jjamppong?)
I hope he chooses jjamppong.
(What did you choose?)
I have both rice and noodles.
- What do you mean? - He chose japchae rice.
Come here.
(Se Chan chose...)
It's japchae rice.
(His choice is japchae rice with rice and noodles.)
- Why did you choose japchae rice? - I didn't know.
(He joins the others.)
- Why did you choose that? - Have you lost your mind?
Why did you choose it when you don't usually eat it?
Why are you so tactless?
- I was so sure of it. - How much time do we have?
- I feel lonely. - I can't tell anymore.
- It's random. - Gosh.
Please choose jjamppong.
It's perfect if he chooses jjamppong.
Ji Hyo said she wanted jjamppong. Haha said he wanted fried rice.
I'll choose...
I'll choose what I want to eat.
(She decides to make a choice independently.)
- So Min. - She's here.
- So Min. - What did you bring?
It's perfect if she chooses jjamppong.
That's right.
(Then everyone can eat.)
- Is it fried rice? - Is it rice or noodles?
(If she chose fried rice, four members can eat.)
(She must be chosen if she chose either jajangmyeon or japchae rice.)
(She brings jajangmyeon.)
What did you choose?
It's the same situation for both.
(Only those who are chosen get to eat.)
- How is this possible? - Have a seat.
(It's also a mess at the other table.)
All right.
- It's unfortunate. - I don't have to think twice.
- Jong Kook. - It's the same.
What a terrible situation.
Our situation is also annoying.
Jong Kook chose jjamppong,
- and Haha chose fried rice. - This is horrible.
It depends on their choices. Choose only one.
Does Haha get to choose?
- The chosen ones can eat. - This is my second time playing.
Please let me eat once.
You're not allowed to eat yet.
This is confusing for me.
It's Jae Seok's birthday today. Se Chan started the show.
I pity Seok Jin.
(He explains why it's difficult to choose.)
I don't know how to choose.
Shall I pick someone by the length of the noodle?
- That sounds good. - The length of a noodle.
- Pick 1 noodle. - Pick 1.
- Okay. - That's a good idea.
The person who picks the longest noodle...
will eat with Haha.
Shouldn't you consider someone who has the most money?
- Money? - In regards to money,
I'll accept only a dollar for the participation fee.
(He will take a dollar for participation.)
What are you talking about?
I won't consider money.
- Won't you participate? - I'll pay the fee.
- Okay. - Here you go.
I'll only take participation fee.
You have five seconds.
- Four. - You won't eat?
3, 2.
2, 1.
(They all pay up.)
Three of you will participate.
This is making me angry.
Gosh, it's upsetting.
- Thank you for the fee. - He became the king.
You became the king for choosing fried rice.
Congratulations. The three of you will participate.
(He feels powerful.)
Do we do it at once?
- You should start. - I'll start.
- Let's see. This is it. - Grab one.
If it gets cut, you can't choose again.
Of course.
(He picks a noodle carefully.)
Gosh.
(It gets cut.)
(His noodle gets cut.)
It got cut.
My noodle got tangled with the others.
(It was too taut that it broke.)
Yes.
(Se Chan loses.)
He lost his chance.
I got it.
- The noodle was quite long. - Poor Se Chan.
It was quite long before.
You should have been careful.
We don't know yet.
- Okay. - You grabbed one.
(He expects to defeat Se Chan.)
(Extending)
You have to pull it out.
(Will unlucky Seok Jin get lucky?)
We don't know who will win yet.
(The noodle extends.)
(It suddenly gets cut.)
(He might get lucky.)
(Not today)
- Hold it. - We don't know yet.
(Jae Seok is ready to eat.)
- Thank goodness. - The problem is...
- Thank goodness. - It gets stuck.
Yours will get cut too. It'll be the same.
Hold it.
It'd be amazing if I win.
Gosh, I think mine is shorter.
(We'll compare their noodles later.)
I shouldn't get greedy.
Any noodle that I can see will be longer than those.
The noodles are tangled.
I should be careful.
He has to choose carefully.
It's similar to the claw machine.
- Is that it? - He picked one.
- Goodness. - He got it.
It's already longer than the others.
(It looks long and stable.)
He chose a good one.
- He got it. - It's coming out.
It's already long.
(Will Jae Seok get to eat japchae rice?)
- He got it. - Just pull it out.
(It gets cut.)
Okay!
(As long as he pulls it out...)
(However, it breaks.)
Stay still.
(I'm the one who will eat japchae rice.)
This is...
I grabbed it.
Jae Seok is never the final winner.
- He lost. - He grabbed it too hard.
May I do it again?
- This isn't fair. - You lost your chance.
It was funny.
- It wasn't funny. - It was very funny.
I dropped it.
Sit back down.
(Jae Seok is eliminated.)
- May I do it again? - Let's measure the noodles.
(Seok Jin and Se Chan compare theirs.)
Be accurate.
Wait, mine is longer. Don't pull it.
- I'm not. - It's the same.
We should play again if it's the same.
(He's shocked.)
(I get to play again too.)
- Do it one last time. - Look.
- No. - Seok Jin.
It's a little longer.
- No. - What are you doing?
You can't extend it.
It was a close game.
Pay two dollars to participate again.
(Pay 2 dollars to participate again.)
You may participate again.
- Two dollars. - I'll poke you.
- I'll poke you with this. - Seriously.
Don't you want to eat?
(Seok Jin wins the japchae rice in the end.)
Let's compete with noodles.
- Noodles are soggy. - Let's try.
- Pick from your own dish. - Yes.
Pick noodles from your own dish.
Then one person will win by default.
Please don't forget to pay the participation fee.
(Please don't forget to pay the participation fee.)
- How much is the participation fee? - Two dollars.
Is it two dollars?
- You should make it a dollar. - I only have a dollar.
- I only have a dollar. - Do you only have a dollar?
- Please bring down the price. - I will make it a dollar.
It's a dollar for the first round.
Who made these rules?
They are ridiculous.
Thick noodles aren't necessarily the best.
(So Min is doing something strange.)
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
I am making my strand of noodle cold.
She is unbelievable.
So Min, I acknowledge your effort.
You are doing your best.
(So Min uses the air conditioner to make the noodle taut.)
Let's decide on the matches with rock, paper, and scissors.
- Will someone win by default? - Of course.
Flip hands to decide.
Kwang Soo is putting his heart into this.
Flip hands.
(They decide to flip hands.)
Get ready.
Up or down? Flip your hands.
(Kwang Soo wins by default by showing the back of his hand.)
Okay!
That makes Kwang Soo the first to go.
(What?)
What are you talking about? Why am I the first to go?
- You are the first to go. - Don't be ridiculous.
They should compete against each other.
Both of them showed their palms.
Seriously.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - This is ridiculous.
- Okay. - That means...
you have been eliminated from the first game.
(I guess you didn't know.)
That's not how it works.
You have been eliminated.
- In one... - Hold the ends.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
So Min will win.
She is cutting his noodle.
(She attacks with the noodle she dried under the air conditioner.)
(So Min's noodle breaks.)
- Did you win? - I won.
- All right. - Okay.
That's right. Dry noodles break more easily.
(He soaks the noodle in soup for the final round.)
You can't use the same noodle. Pick a new strand.
You should continue using the one you have used.
Do you dislike me or something? What is your problem?
Do you hate the idea of me eating?
You shouldn't change the noodle.
- Are you jealous? - No, I am not.
"Are you jealous?"
Start.
(Ji Hyo versus Kwang Soo)
- Pull. In 1, 2, 3. - Pull, Kwang Soo.
- Pull. - The one who pulls will lose.
- Pull. - In 1, 2, 3.
(They tell each other to pull, but refuse to move an inch.)
Pull.
- Neither one of them is pulling. - In 1, 2, 3.
Kwang Soo, pull.
Neither is pulling.
- In 1, 2, 3. - Kwang Soo, pull.
- Pull. - The one who pulls will lose.
The one who pulls will lose.
They won't pull.
(The brave Ji Hyo attacks first.)
The one who pulls will lose.
(They are worried that Ji Hyo's noodle will break.)
Let's put them in the middle.
(Kwang Soo's noodle is out.)
- Yes! - Ji Hyo won.
Let's put them in the middle.
(Ji Hyo wins easily with a daring move.)
- Ji Hyo won. - Did Kwang Soo lose?
Ji Hyo won.
(The sauce tastes especially good today.)
(Spicy and chewy japchae rice and glossy fried rice)
(Soft jajangmyeon and spicy jjamppong)
(After the fierce matches, Ji Hyo, Jong Kook,)
It's tasty.
(Seok Jin, and Haha eat.)
A spoonful of japchae rice is a dollar.
- Really? - Shall we have a spoonful?
Let's do that.
Please give me a spoonful.
- So Min will go first. - It's a dollar for a spoonful.
- I will only take three people. - Me.
- You have 3 people. - 3 people.
(Se Chan tries a spoonful of japchae rice.)
- Come on. - Lift it up.
Isn't it hot?
- Be careful. - That's nice.
(He inhales a big spoonful of japchae rice.)
(It's a big spoonful.)
- You can't eat more. - It was on the spoon.
You can't eat more.
(She opens her mouth wide.)
What are you doing?
(She inhales the dish like a vacuum cleaner.)
- It was on the spoon. - You can't eat more.
(A japchae rice monster appears.)
What a delinquent.
- She ate all the japchae. - So Min.
Three dollars...
- will clear the dish. - There are no noodles left.
She will only leave rice behind.
- I still haven't had a spoonful. - It's one spoonful.
- It's 1 spoonful. - 1 spoonful.
(It's Jae Seok's turn to have a spoonful of japchae rice.)
Hey.
- This is my spoon. - For goodness' sake.
- This is my spoon. - He can use his own spoon.
- Why are you upset? - Pile on food.
I can't believe these delinquents.
For goodness' sake.
My nickname is "Ladle".
(Inhaling)
(A ladle monster appears.)
That's good. Okay.
For goodness' sake.
- I can't believe these delinquents. - Okay.
What is this?
We gave you three dollars.
I am really hungry.
I can't eat this.
Kwang Soo, you should borrow a dollar.
- Won't you eat the rice? - Kwang Soo.
If I lend you a dollar, can you pay back two dollars?
(I will lend you some money.)
Pay back two dollars later.
(A loan with a high interest rate and japchae rice call for him.)
This is your last chance to have a spoonful. Five.
- Okay. - Pay back two dollars later.
You are the witness. He needs to pay back two dollars.
I will buy a spoonful.
(Kwang Soo buys a spoonful of japchae rice.)
- What is this? - They ate japchae.
You inhaled the dish.
(What do you want me to eat?)
Haha, give me a spoonful.
I will use a regular spoon.
- I am serious. - I will lend you this for 50 cents.
Can I have another 50 cents?
(I want to borrow that ladle.)
- What? - I will pay back three dollars.
You will pay back three dollars?
No, pay back 4 dollars. I will give you 2 dollars.
I will give you two dollars.
I don't have 50 cents.
Then give me a dollar.
Pay back four dollars, okay?
- Okay. - He needs to pay back four dollars.
Shall I get you a new ladle?
No, it's okay.
What is this? Did you borrow a ladle?
I am not going to make this deal.
(I am sorry.)
I never agreed.
Did I hear you wrong?
(What is this ladle for?)
From this moment on, this ladle is yours.
(That's how it is.)
Here you go.
You need to pay back four dollars.
That ladle is yours.
I will use it to drink water.
Kwang Soo.
It has the faint smell of japchae rice.
(The water tastes bitter.)
Kwang Soo, the ladle is yours.
I strongly recommend this japchae rice.
- It's really tasty. - Let me have a taste.
(SBS Prism Tower at Sangam-dong)
I used up all of my money. I am broke.
I spent everything at the restaurant.
You need to pay back four dollars.
- Four dollars. - Okay.
Okay. I will give you real money.
No, I don't want that. Give me the game money.
- I don't have any game money. - Come on.
You promised me earlier.
- I don't have any game money. - There are witnesses.
What should I do? If he doesn't have any money,
- can he pay me back next week? - I will give you real money.
I don't want real money. I want game money.
- I will give you five dollars. - I don't want it.
If it's going to be real money, it's 50 dollars. No, 500 dollars.
Why would it be 500 dollars? I don't have any money.
Please tell me...
I can receive the game money next week.
I will give you real money.
I don't want real money. How many times...
do I have to tell you?
I don't like this atmosphere.
Stay here. You don't want to stay close to a fight.
You will get caught up in it if you are next to So Min.
Then I wouldn't have lent you two dollars earlier.
I will buy you a carton of cigarettes.
I don't want it. Shut it.
(I don't smoke.)
- You win if he buys you a carton. - That's right.
A pack of cigarettes is expensive.
(She fails to receive the money.)
All right.
- This is the final mission. - What is it?
The sum of the money you have collected is 135 dollars.
From the sum that is required to beat the staff,
- you are 65 dollars short. - We only need a little bit more.
The final mission, Money Talks, will provide a change...
to change the fate of the team and individuals.
(Money Talks)
- Money Talks. - Money Talks.
It will be a team game.
On the board are...
different amounts of money from a dollar to 20 dollars.
They are written behind the numbers at random.
- I see. - Randomly?
They are written at random.
(Different amounts of money are behind the numbers.)
Come up one by one, and pick a number.
(The members come up one by one and pick a number.)
Listen as the amount of money goes up by a dollar per second,
and say, "Stop" at the desired amount.
Then look at the amount you have picked.
If the amount you stopped at equals to or is smaller than...
the amount you picked, you get the money.
If it's bigger, you lose the money.
My goodness.
(If the amount you stopped at is bigger, you lose the money.)
(They must stop at the amount that is smaller.)
- I'll have to try first. - This sounds difficult.
How will I get it right?
We just need to refrain from being greedy.
Since each person gets a chance, you have eight chances in total.
You succeed if you acquire 65 dollars.
Then you get the prize money.
If you acquire less, you fail.
Then you don't get the prize money.
(Running Man versus Staff)
Decide on the order wisely.
The unlucky ones should go first.
You talk like you aren't one of them.
(Haha, aren't you unlucky?)
- He likes to rank the members. - You know,
you only seem lucky because you are among us.
- He is unlucky from head to toe. - Stop it.
Hey, go first.
What are you talking about?
(He is the unluckiest one.)
- Why should I go first? - He is a throw-away card.
No, I am not.
You should go first.
(Se Chan is the rookie of the unlucky ones, so he goes 1st.)
- Should I go first? - Yes, go ahead.
Let's go.
(He must pick a number that has a high amount on it.)
Which one do you pick?
- I pick 8. - 8?
(He picks number 8.)
I'm going to think that's 15 dollars.
- Stop at 14 dollars. - I'll do that.
(He has to get as close as he can to the written amount.)
Actually,
there are eight of us.
Are you doing the calculations? I thought about that too.
We need to earn nine dollars each.
If we all get it right, we'll earn 80 dollars.
If 2 people get it wrong, we'll earn 60 dollars.
Can we get started?
(When are you going to finish?)
We already knew all that.
You have to analyze.
But we already knew it.
- Shouldn't we analyze? - You're taking too long.
- We have to analyze. - Excuse me, Mr. Jee.
Let's aim for 65 dollars.
There's no point in getting 2 or 3 dollars.
- Mr. Jee. - We can't stop there.
I'm going to think this is 15 dollars,
- so I'll stop at 14 dollars. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - All right.
- Pay close attention. - Don't be too greedy.
I'll start counting.
One dollar.
(Remaining balance)
Two dollars.
Three dollars.
Four dollars.
- Really? - Five dollars.
(He was certain before, but now he feels pressured.)
Six dollars.
- This is tense. - Seven dollars.
Shouldn't you stop him soon?
- Eight dollars. - Just stop.
- Nine dollars. - Stop.
Good job.
- 9 dollars? - 9 dollars.
- Stop. - Good job.
(Se Chan stopped at 9 dollars unlike what he said before.)
Check the amount on the number, and if the amount you stopped at...
is equal or less than that, you earn the money.
You went too far though.
- It's okay. - In 1, 2...
(If the written amount is less than 9 dollars, he won't take the money.)
(This is their 1st attempt in accumulating 65 dollars.)
What is it?
You did it.
Good thing I stopped.
See?
- You did well. - Good thing I stopped.
I was going to stop at 14 dollars.
- Good thing you stopped me. - I know.
Thanks for stopping me.
- This is awesome. - You're only off by three dollars.
I wanted to change my mind for some reason.
- Good thing you stopped. - Good job.
That was pretty good.
(There is 56 dollars remaining. They have 7 more attempts left.)
Let's go, Sang Soon.
I don't look like him.
(He must be the owner of "Kwang Soo's Bed and Breakfast".)
- I look different. - You're Hyo Ri's husband.
It's Sang Soon.
The rest of you need to accumulate 56 more dollars.
Let's go, Kwang Soo.
I pick number 17.
- 17? - Yes.
I don't like that number.
What do you mean?
I won't ask for more than three dollars.
But we have to make 65 dollars.
Get set, go.
One dollar.
Two dollars.
- Three dollars. - Stop here.
- Four dollars. - I think you should stop.
- Five dollars. - Don't be greedy.
- Six dollars. - This is too much for you.
- Seven dollars. - We don't expect much from you.
- Eight dollars. - Stop it.
(He's hesitant.)
- Nine dollars. - You already passed it.
- 10 dollars. - Stop.
10 dollars?
It won't be higher than 4 dollars. I have a feeling.
- I hope it's 10 dollars. - In 1, 2...
(Nobody expects Kwang Soo to get 10 dollars.)
(What's the amount on number 17?)
(He gets 10 dollars.)
(People looked down on me. Are you watching this?)
Good thing you stopped.
You should have kept going.
You should have kept going. Why did you get scared?
(I earned 10 dollars for you.)
You should have stopped at 13 dollars.
- What a coward. - Come on.
- You should have kept going. - He's such a coward.
He's usually unlucky, so he did pretty well.
I earned 10 dollars, Jae Seok.
There are 6 of you left. You need to accumulate 46 dollars.
(There is 46 dollars remaining. They have 6 more attempts left.)
- What number? - What number?
(It's Seok Jin's turn with 46 dollars left to go.)
- Number 20. - Number 20?
- The last number. - You have chosen number 20.
It's not a bad number.
- 1 dollar. - I think it's around 5 dollars.
Two dollars.
- It's not a high number. - Right, he won't get a big amount.
Three dollars.
- Four dollars. - Stop it.
- Five dollars. - Stop.
(Stop trying to act like you're bold.)
- Six dollars. - Stop it.
He's about to pass it.
- Seven dollars. - Stop.
- He stopped at 7 dollars. - I stopped at 7 dollars.
(He calls it at 7 dollars which is a safe amount.)
- 7 dollars? - You stopped at 7 dollars.
Please let it be eight dollars.
(Is the amount on number 20 less or greater than 7 dollars?)
Why did you make me stop?
(He earns the money.)
- He got lucky. - I was going to stop later.
- I feel bad. - He's incredible.
- When did he stop? - I was being safe. I got seven.
We're getting lucky. We picked all the good numbers.
We did.
(There is 39 dollars remaining. They have 5 more attempts left.)
We picked all the high numbers.
- The five of you... - They're all high numbers.
accumulated 39 dollars.
They're all above 10 dollars.
So Min is next. What number?
- Number 19. - Number 19? Okay.
Come forward.
Get set, go.
One dollar.
Two dollars.
Three dollars.
- Four dollars. - No, no.
- Five dollars. - She has to stop soon.
- Six dollars. - Call it.
Seven dollars.
- 8 dollars. - There is 7 dollars left.
Nine dollars.
- 10 dollars. - You already passed it.
- I think she passed it. - 11 dollars.
- You passed it. - What are you doing?
- 12 dollars. - You're done.
- Why are you just standing there? - 13 dollars.
- 13 dollars. - Stop.
How much was that? 13 dollars?
She stopped at 13 dollars. It's number 19.
- That's not possible. - Everybody was...
- criticizing me. - In 1, 2...
- You stopped at 13 dollars. - She didn't get it.
See?
She fails.
(Is there a hiding spot somewhere here?)
- She wasn't even listening to us. - What was she thinking?
She never listens to other people.
Keep going. Go to 13 dollars.
- I'll go to 13 dollars. - 13 dollars.
- Stop. - All right.
Was it number 14?
(Jae Seok stops at the same amount as So Min.)
- Let's go. - Number 14. 13 dollars.
(He earns 13 dollars.)
All right.
- Really? - See?
- Number 11. - Number 11. Let's get started.
Eight dollars.
- Nine dollars. - Isn't it now?
- 10 dollars. - Stop.
- 10 dollars. - Number 11.
- Number 11. - It's here.
We already got too many numbers above 10 dollars.
- We got too many. - In 1, 2...
(He earns 10 dollars.)
- We're insane. - He should have kept going.
We don't have anything less than 10 dollars except So Min.
(There is 16 dollars remaining. They have 2 more attempts left.)
I feel so pressured.
- But you have to keep going. - There's one in this column.
(There are not many big amounts left.)
- It's one of those. - I don't agree.
Are you able to analyze this?
We can still try.
Just go. Let's get it.
Let's get it. Number 10.
- Try number 2. - Let's get it. Number 10.
Go against Jae Seok's suggestion.
If you listen to him, you always get unlucky.
He said number 10, so number 5 is half.
- Number 20 was taken. - 5 is half of 10.
- Okay, do that. - It was 2 times 7 before.
Ready. Get set,
- We picked too many high numbers. - go.
One dollar.
- Two dollars. - He doesn't get it.
Three dollars.
Four dollars.
Seven dollars.
- Stop it. - Eight dollars.
- Stop. - Good job.
I think he could have gone up to 10 dollars.
He should have.
(Haha aimed for half of what they needed.)
(What's the amount on number 5?)
In 1, 2, 3.
That was close.
- He failed. - That's right.
Let me do it again.
"Let me do it again?"
- Remember what I said? - "Let me do it again."
I told you it's not right. You should have chosen number 10.
It has to be over 16 dollars. For your reference,
there are 16, 19, or 20 dollars you can choose from.
- There are only 3 left? - You have to choose 16 dollars.
Just call a number, Ji Hyo.
Pick number two.
We have nowhere else to go.
Let's get it.
(Number 1 sounds good.)
- Do it. - He picks number one.
- Do something else. - Let's get it.
- Do this. - How does this sound, everybody?
If you collect money amongst yourselves...
and give me 10 dollars,
I'll get rid of 2 numbers that's under 10 dollars.
(It's a chance to erase 2 numbers under 10 dollars.)
- Okay. - Let's collect 10 dollars.
- There is no reason not to do it. - Let's collect the money.
I'll contribute two dollars.
This is a bonus for you.
- You won't lose anything. - We're fools if we don't do this.
I'm giving you this chance.
- Check number 7 and 10. - Number 7?
Let's see number seven.
(Number 7 and 10...)
(are the numbers Jae Seok recommended many times.)
(What are their amounts?)
(It's only 5 dollars.)
What was that?
(It's only 5 and 4 dollars.)
- We predicted this. - These are the ones he recommended.
- Let's get it. - Number 7 and 10.
- You're incredible. - You're unbelievable.
Why don't we do this?
- We won't touch the one he picks. - I'll exclude the one you pick.
You can have a look.
Don't choose number one. That's what he wanted you to choose.
He could have seen it.
Aren't you supposed to whisper that to her?
I'll cross out number one.
I'll cross it out.
(He crosses it out.)
What's next? Did you say number two?
(Let's see.)
- Go with your guts. - I think it's either of these.
- Cross both out. - Are you a fortuneteller or what?
Are you a fortuneteller?
- What do you do? - I'm speechless.
- Pick the next one. - You cross out everything I say?
You looked so cool.
- This is... - That was cool.
- You cross out everything I say? - This is a skill.
I think it's number one. Let's get it.
(Jae Seok consistently suggests number one.)
- It can't be. It's either 2 or 3. - Number 2 or 3.
- He kept on picking number one. - I'm confused.
- It can't be. - Let's get number one.
It's Jae Seok's birthday today, so I'll go with number one.
Number one?
Let's get started.
(Ji Hyo decides to trust Jae Seok's birthday luck.)
We'll just stop at 16 dollars. Can we just rip it?
13 dollars. 14 dollars.
15 dollars. 16 dollars.
- Stop. - All right.
Number one.
One...
(Ji Hyo trusted Jae Seok and picked number 1.)
- 2... - We need 16 dollars.
- Please. - We need 16 dollars or more.
(If number 1 is more than 16 dollars,)
(they get to go to Salar de Uyuni that Se Chan recommended.)
(If it's less than 16 dollars,)
(they'll ride New Zealand's Nevis Swing recommended by staff.)
(Is number 1 above 16 dollars?)
It starts with one.
- No. - It's one.
Mission failed.
(They fail the mission.)
Goodness.
Can I see what number 12 is?
Yes. You can look.
We should have picked number 12.
Why did we change our minds? It's because of Jae Seok.
- Number two. - That was it.
See? That's the one you picked.
- You kept on picking it. - He kept on saying, "Let's get it."
That's why we didn't pick it.
He kept on saying, "Let's get it."
- We didn't feel safe about it. - You kept on picking it.
Jong Kook and I kept recommending number two.
Number two?
- There were two good ones. - That's right.
You lost today,
so please put New Zealand's Nevis Swing...
on the board.
I hate this.
(Nevis Swing is the 1st potential place out of 4.)
And how much do you have right now, Haha?
I have 34 dollars.
Each name can be bought at 10 dollars.
Which names would you like to buy?
There are only two of mine, right?
Wait. Who wants to volunteer?
Hold on.
Remember during the I Go Race,
- you survived. - He did.
- When was that? - During the I Go Race.
When was I excluded?
- You were. - He wasn't even given the penalty.
I was a little hurt over that.
I'll buy one of Seok Jin's.
Why? Why would you buy mine?
Because during the I Go Race...
- What about it? - Come on.
- Good. - Can you bring the board back?
Please bring it back. I'll buy...
two names of the person who chooses the lowest number.
(He'll buy two name tags of the person who chooses the lowest.)
- Two? - That's a lot.
The lowest amount?
That person?
The person who picks the lowest?
I'll go.
It's eight dollars.
(Jong Kook picks 8 dollars.)
That's high.
Go ahead, So Min.
Two dollars?
Really?
(She picks 2 dollars.)
- Do we have to keep going? - Is it necessary?
Pick whatever.
- My gosh. - If somebody picks...
If somebody picks one dollar, that's too bad for them.
That's not possible.
- Somebody might pick one dollar. - That's not possible.
Are you going to get this?
Let's get number seven?
- Please let it be one dollar. - He loves that number.
- No way. - Let's get it.
It's one dollar.
Let's get...
(Let's get one dollar.)
(That's unbelievable.)
(They are both shocked and delighted.)
(They didn't think Jae Seok would actually pick it.)
Let me do it again.
(Jae Seok does the impossible again.)
Really?
This is impossible.
How did you do that?
Please give him a round of applause.
(Happy birthday, Jae Seok.)
(They're happy, cheerful, and delighted.)
- Happy birthday - I got goosebumps.
- Dear Jae Seok - People will think we made it up.
- No way. - People might think that.
- That's not possible. - Your problem is "Let's get it."
It's your birthday too. Today must be your day.
- This is such a weird feeling. - I just got chills.
- That was shocking. - I got goosebumps.
That's so cruel.
Whose names shall I cover?
Wait, Haha.
Remember the beginning?
Se Chan and I...
We were always so close to winning.
- Remember what we talked about? - What is it?
We said we won't pick each other.
- Haha. - Hey.
- That's different. - He picked somebody else.
- Haha. - Can you cover one of mine?
(He's miserable.)
Remember the sophora root tea?
Why would he do that?
- You have no sense of shame. - That's what I'm saying.
Stop it.
He's so shameless.
Just say, "Let's get it."
- Should I cover yours? - Please cover one of mine.
- What should I do? - Please.
I feel so bad.
Pick the person who gets the highest number.
- Let's do that. - Okay.
I'll go with the highest number. Okay.
It's over if somebody gets 20 dollars.
It'll be over.
We've been filming for too long.
- It's 12 dollars. That's high. - She got 12 dollars.
- Who was that? - Me.
- He might get 20 dollars. - Okay.
Keep going.
- 14 dollars. - That's the highest.
Okay. I got 14 dollars.
- Se Chan. - Okay.
18 dollars.
What was that? What did you do?
- That was unexpected. - I'm set.
20 dollars.
I'm set.
- What did you say? - "20 dollars".
"20 dollars".
I was pretty high.
(I'll show you all.)
Nine dollars.
(Ji Hyo and Jae Seok are left.)
- Go, Ji Hyo. - Me?
I think she'll get 20 dollars.
Kwang Soo might lose with 18 dollars.
Jae Seok is hopeful. What would Ji Hyo pick?
Me?
(She hits the jackpot with 20 dollars.)
(Ji Hyo picks the highest amount possible.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are both dejected.)
(It's Ji Hyo at the end.)
This is awesome. She's incredible.
Really?
(I thought today was my day.)
- Today's not his day. - He didn't even pick.
Kwang Soo was so close to winning.
(I wanted to be lucky today.)
(There were no surprises.)
So I'll cover Ji Hyo's name.
Okay.
Why do I feel like Seok Jin will be picked?
Why does it look like there are so many of mine?
There are four of mine, but it looks like Seok Jin has more.
- Why does it look that way? - This is weird.
(Whose name will be picked from this roulette?)
I'll let Jae Seok spin this...
because it's his birthday today.
What if you spin it, and it lands on your name?
It's be hilarious if he picks his own name.
- Let's get it. - Let's get it.
Pick your own name. The spirits will help you.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin have the highest possibilities.)
(The person who gets picked will be going on the Nevis Swing.)
Please.
Please save me.
- I have such bad luck today. - There are so many of mine.
There are so many.
We're almost there.
It's me.
- No. - It's Kwang Soo.
No way.
(Please)
(No way.)
(Who's the first person to go on Half and Half Tour?)
(Jae Seok, let's get it.)
No way.
(That's unbelievable.)
(Is this for real?)
(This must be a drama.)
(Everyone other than the birthday boy is happy.)
Let's get it.
- Let's get it. - Let's get it.
- Good job. - Happy birthday
(He'll remember his 45th birthday.)
(When did things start going bad?)
This is one of your unluckiest days.
(When he called even,)
(it was odd.)
(It's odd.)
(Jae Seok always guessed wrong.)
(Please don't do anything.)
(Just go home.)
(He was given all sorts of criticism,)
(but he hoped for a birthday miracle.)
Please put "Plus one" next to Jae Seok's name.
This is interesting. I'm amazed.
- This is unbelievable. - I understand how you must feel.
I can't go there.
How did that happen? I thought it was me.
Jae Seok.
(A series of mysterious events...)
(happen to Seok Jin.)
- Really? - Yes.
(Race of Wits: Deceive Seok Jin)
(Seok Jin is the only one who doesn't know.)
(He gets tricked...)
(and excluded.)
(It's a story of wits.)
(They have 7 years of experience dealing with Seok Jin.)
(I really have to poop.)
(The moment he lets his guard down, he'll get tricked.)
You're such crooks.
(Race of Wits: Deceive Seok Jin, Next Sunday at 4:50pm)