(2017 Running Man's 3rd Global Project)
(Half and Half Tour)
(Salar de Uyuni is nature's biggest and clearest mirror.)
(Bora Bora is Venus' island located in the South Pacific Ocean.)
(Rome is the eternal city that has the history of the Roman Empire.)
(Antelope Canyon is a sandstone formation created by rain and wind.)
(Alaska is the home of extreme sports and aurora.)
(Lake Hillier is a romantic lake that is made pink by plankton.)
(Bow River lets the visitors enjoy fly fishing in the Rocky Mountains.)
(Krabi is a fantastic vacation spot where the sky and sea connect.)
(Did you think there'd be only paradise ahead of you?)
(There are also hideous vacation places which the staff recommended.)
(8 recommendations from the members and 8 recommendations from the crew)
(Each week, the members have a match to put their names on the roulette.)
(First destination turned out to be the Nevis Swing in New Zealand.)
(Jae Seok, the icon of penalties, got Nevis Swing in New Zealand.)
(Second destination was...)
(Bora Bora, the fantastic vacation spot, which Haha recommended.)
I really want to go.
(So Min, the icon of luck, got Bora Bora.)
(Haha and Z Young won the third race.)
(Third destination came to be...)
(Rome, the city that holds the history and beauty of Ancient Rome.)
(Jae Seok became the lucky member to go on a trip to Rome.)
(And)
(The final race of Half and Half Project)
(Roulette Underworld)
(Their fates will be determined only by spinning roulettes.)
(The last match between the Running Man members and the staff)
(What will be the final destination, and who will be chosen to go there?)
(It'll be revealed today.)
(The final race of Half and Half Project)
All right, everyone. We'll start the final race.
You are currently stuck in the Roulette Underworld.
(Roulette Underworld?)
(The identity of this room is...)
(Roulette Underworld.)
You'll find roulettes on each wall.
(There are roulettes on each wall.)
All your decisions today will be determined by those roulettes.
- Is that so? - I see.
There are a total of four rounds.
You'll win the race...
if you secure 300 dollars until the race ends.
(The members will win if they keep 300 dollars.)
(In other words, they will get to win only if they retain the money.)
If it's less than 300 dollars, the staff will win the race.
(The last destination depends on the 300 dollars.)
You will escape from the room every time you clear each mission.
You'll be given a chance to obtain additional money.
(If they clear each mission, they get to obtain money.)
If you fail the mission, you must pay a 10-dollar fine.
(They have to pay 10 dollars per failure.)
(It's important for them to succeed each mission and raise more money.)
We need to get out of here first.
And the one with the most amount of money will be the winner.
- Yes. - That's right.
(Also, the member with the most amount of money will be the winner.)
This week again, the member who acquired the most amount of money...
will get to buy a name sticker and stick it on the roulette.
Among the four entries,
the winning team's destination will be placed on the three entries.
And the losing team's destination will be placed on the other entry.
You will choose 1 of those 4 entries to decide on the last destination.
Okay.
(What's written on the chosen entry will be the last destination.)
(Which vacation spot will be picked as the last destination?)
Before we begin the race, we'll draw the candidates.
I have a question. Will we have another tour project after this one?
I'll have to think about it.
Something like Die and Live Project.
(Die and Live Project)
- Go Crazy Project. - "Go Crazy Project".
Go Insane Project perhaps?
- Go Again Project. - I see.
- I Got Fooled Project. - Goodness.
You can't do another tour project similar to this.
- Please draw the balls. - Do I start?
- Okay. - From this one or that one?
You pick it.
(Draw it, Jae Seok.)
- Right, Jae Seok. - Good.
- Since I already have two slots. - Go ahead.
In this Half and Half Project, Jae Seok broke...
all the unlucky records Kwang Soo had made.
- He broke them all. - Right.
- I feel a bit upset. - Right.
He made so many good scenes.
- I always look far ahead. - Is that right?
He tends to deal with trivial things.
- What do you mean? - You really do.
- Listen, fellow. - What?
- I don't see anything different. - Goodness.
- Goodness. - You silly.
Plan big like I do.
(What's going to be his plan for today?)
I want to go to the Bow River in Canada.
Right, that sounds good.
I've never been to Canada before.
(The magnificent view of the Rocky Mountains)
(The visitors enjoy fly fishing in the great nature.)
- I didn't see it. - Gosh.
- There. - That's it.
- Please. - 1, 2, 3.
- Three. - Please. Let it be Canada.
(He's desperate.)
(Which vacation spot will be the destination candidate?)
- That's also a nice place. - This one's good too.
(Krabi in Thailand)
(Krabi is a fantastic vacation spot where the sky and sea connect.)
(It will become the last destination on the roulette if the members win.)
(I recommended this place.)
- It's close. - I recommended the place.
(All right. Let's win and put it up on the roulette.)
- It's Krabi. - This doesn't really matter.
(This isn't important.)
- That one's important. - It's no big deal.
- This one's important. - The staff's recommendation.
- This... - Take it out.
- Take it out. - Choose one.
- I took this ball out. - That's not the one.
- Choose the opposite one. - The opposite of what you decided.
(Did you forget already?)
The opposite one.
(What's this about?)
I choose even...
(A few weeks ago, Jae Seok managed to overcome his bad luck...)
(by choosing the opposite of his decision.)
(That's how he set his creed after 7 years.)
(Being careful)
The opposite...
of this ball.
(He follows his creed as it's important.)
The opposite. I'll draw the one at the corner.
- Do it again. - Draw the opposite of the opposite.
Jae Seok, how about you draw it with your left hand?
- Okay. - Good.
- That's a good move. - Left hand.
- Se Chan, you're good. - Use your left hand.
You know what's funny?
There's nothing good in here anyway.
(They're the staff's recommendations.)
- It's going to be bad anyway. - Still.
(Whatever they choose...)
(will be a fire pit like this anyway.)
Still, we need to avoid the worst. Something that involves...
- height. - Right.
(Touching)
- Height. - Right.
(Change your decision.)
(You're always unlucky.)
(Just draw again.)
(I know, right?)
Make a final decision.
Think as if it's the last choice which you can make.
Don't change it now.
Jae Seok. That's what you picked a second ago.
(Hold on a second.)
You picked the same ball.
- He's helpless. - Look, Jae Seok.
(They want to avoid the worst.)
Hit this hand.
How about you draw it with your mouth?
He can't put his head in there.
(After thinking hard,)
(he finally chooses one.)
- That's it. - Let's go with it.
- Let's go with it. - Right.
- I'll open it now. - Do it.
1, 2, 3.
(The staff's recommendation matters more to the members.)
(It should be better than the others.)
What is that?
(It's Cage of Death in Australia.)
(Frightening date with a cannibal crocodile)
(They must put up with the extreme fear in front of them.)
Is it about crocodiles? Australia?
(Sighing)
(The frightening Cage of Death is selected.)
- It's about crocodiles, right? - Well...
We'll be in a cage made with glass. Crocodiles can't come in.
Right?
Hit its nose if it comes in.
(Jae Seok, hit its nose.)
- It's possible for you. - So Jae Seok's going?
(Is Jae Seok going there?)
Why do you think I'll be going there?
I have this feeling that you'll go.
(It's because you already have the half of the roulette.)
This is it.
We haven't even gone to receive the penalties yet.
This is so stressful.
- I have to go next week. - Me too.
It's driving me crazy.
Do you realize how stressful it is?
- I feel like I'm being chased. - What did we do so wrong?
Don't choose us to go with you, all right?
- We're getting penalties anyway. - I know.
Today's theme is deciding on which place he'll go.
(It's going to be about deciding where he will go.)
Right.
Please don't choose us to go with you.
Everything will depend on you.
- Save us. - You never know.
You never know whose name will be written on the last slot.
It may be So Min or you. You never know.
I'm going to Indonesia.
We've done picking the destination candidates.
- Cage of Death. - All right.
The candidates are Krabi in Thailand...
and Cage of Death in Australia.
(Krabi versus Cage of Death)
We'll begin today's race now.
The first mission of Roulette Underworld is called...
Dreadful Hands.
(1st round of Roulette Underworld: Dreadful Hands)
- What is that? - Dreadful Hands.
(What is the mission about?)
The mascot of Running Man,
Mr. Kim Hyung Jun, please come on out.
(Mr. Kim Hyung Jun, please come on out.)
Mr. Kim Hyung Jun.
(Is he here again?)
My goodness, he's back.
- Hello. - Hello.
(The master of sports massage, Kim Hyung Jun)
(He is a sports massage therapist from the netherworld.)
(He stimulates the members' limbs with his electrifying hands.)
His thumbs became bigger.
- They became thicker. - His thumbs became thicker.
(He is back with upgraded weapons.)
Please take good care of our aching bodies.
I have a stiff shoulder.
If you withstand the massage for more than 10 seconds...
without making a sound, the mission is a success.
I can't do that.
Spin the roulette to decide on...
the number and members.
(Don't forget that this is Roulette Underworld.)
I will spin the roulette.
Haha is relatively lucky in this project.
- 1. is a good number. - 1.
- 1. - 1.
- Spin the roulette. - Please.
- One. - He spun it well.
I have a good feeling about this.
One.
(They lose 10 dollars if they fail the mission.)
(A small number gives them a higher chance of success.)
- It's one. - No.
It's one.
(If they get 1, only 1 member needs to succeed.)
- No, no. - It's one.
- No, no. - Hey, hey.
(To which number is the first roulette headed?)
This is crazy.
No.
I can't believe we got seven.
- Why did you spin the roulette? - I can't believe we got seven.
Seven members will participate in the mission.
This is unbelievable.
- That's everyone except for one. - Move out of the way.
Haha always sends people...
into peril.
- He only cares about himself. - You are a jerk.
- You are an utter jerk, too. - You are a jerk.
(Haha takes responsibility and tries the dreadful hands first.)
- I will go first. - What's the order?
- This can be the order. - Okay.
- I'll massage behind your head. - The back of his head.
Let me get a taste of it.
Get the most out of the massage.
It's very painful.
(He gets a taste of the massage.)
It's painful.
(My goodness.)
- It's painful. - Is that the massage?
I've gotten massaged there before. It hurts.
It's connected to your bones.
(Pressing)
- Wait a minute. - It relaxes your neck.
Will you use this much strength?
- No, I will use more strength. - He will use more strength.
- Give me a taste of your strength. - Should I use more strength?
How do you normally do it?
This is how I normally do it.
(Hitting)
(How dare you?)
Why did you attack him with your elbow?
(I am already worried.)
Let him massage the front of your shoulders.
I won't be able to withstand it.
- Try it anyway. - We need to succeed.
Where do you want to get the massage?
My hips.
Spin the roulette to decide whether you can get that massage.
(Let's spin and find out.)
Will it be the front of his shoulders?
It's a good tool.
It's a good tool for making a decision.
- There is no need for a fight. - You are right.
It will bring us closer.
What are we doing?
- O is the front of the shoulders. - O is the front of the shoulders.
- What about X? - X is the hips.
(He spins the roulette for the mission.)
Every household should have a roulette.
That's a good idea. It can help indecisive people.
It will eliminate fights in the family.
(Why am I spinning the roulette?)
(The roulette says yes.)
The front of the shoulders.
- Let's go. - The front of the shoulders.
I am warning you that I might fail.
You need to withstand the pain. You came this far.
You are the one who chose seven.
You are the one who got us into this mess.
- Ready... - Wait a minute.
Please let me bite down on something.
(Put something in my mouth.)
I am already in pain.
- All right. - That's a good idea.
- All right. - There we go.
- Get ready. - That's a good idea.
Set, go.
(Haha gets started with Dreadful Hands.)
It's okay. You can do this.
(Haha is silent so far thanks to his members.)
- 5, 6. - You can do this.
- Seven. - He is so ugly.
(He needs to remain silent for 10 seconds.)
Okay. You are almost done.
Okay.
(Haha succeeds.)
- You did a good job. - It's no joke, right?
(Screaming)
Everyone should get it on their shoulders.
- Who will go next? - Kwang Soo.
- You will die. - Kwang Soo should go next.
Go ahead. You saw me withstand it.
- I have weak shoulders. - I withstood the pain.
Let me get it on the back of my head.
The back of your head? Okay.
(Kwang Soo chooses the back of his head.)
- Get ready. - The back of the head.
May I go with my pelvis?
- The back of your head is fine. - Isn't this a vital point?
No, it isn't.
You need to loosen the muscles.
My mind is going hazy.
- Your head will clear. - My head will clear.
Yes.
Get ready. Set, go.
(Kwang Soo gets started.)
You are almost there.
- Kwang Soo. - You are almost there.
(The acupressure makes his head clear and his mind hazy.)
You are almost there.
(He has 3 seconds to go.)
(Whimpering)
- You are almost there. - You are almost there.
He made a sound.
- Did he make a sound? - He didn't make a sound.
Didn't you withstand the pain?
To be honest... Listen to me.
Kwang Soo, I was getting ready.
I can't believe you.
Give up 10 dollars.
- Give up your money. - Listen.
Let the roulette decide whether Kwang Soo should pay.
(Shall we spin the roulette again?)
Wait a minute.
Why can't I see well?
This is what we will do.
- Since this is Roulette Underworld, - How many people should pay?
let the roulette decide how many should pay.
Don't spin it in that direction.
Jae Seok, let the roulette decide who should spin it.
- Right. - That's ridiculous.
- It's only fair. - Ji Hyo is right.
- This is Roulette Underworld. - Ji Hyo, you are right.
- What are you talking about? - Let the roulette decide.
- We are a team. - In that case,
spin the roulette to decide who will spin it.
Let's first decide who will spin the roulette.
Spin this roulette to choose a member.
All of us should grab the board.
- Let's spin it together. - That's right.
Is there an end to this?
Think about why this is called Roulette Underworld.
One person can spin the roulette while we hold our hands.
Let's do that.
- This is ridiculous. - Spin the roulette.
We are connected.
There is no need for a fight. We will become closer.
(The roulette united the members.)
- I want to go in this direction. - I want to go in this direction.
Let's spin the OX roulette.
- O is left. - Spin the OX roulette.
O is left, and X is right.
- O is right. - O is right.
X is left.
Why do you get to spin it?
- We must let the roulette decide. - Come here.
- We must let the roulette decide. - That's right.
Go with it.
- No. - Go with it!
That's unfair.
- Right. - Right.
(They need to spin the roulette to the right.)
Why did he spin it?
- Hurry up, and hold hands. - It's this direction.
Why are we holding hands?
I don't understand why we are holding hands.
(Nevertheless, they hold hands to spin the roulette.)
(Jong Kook is chosen.)
- Jong Kook. - Shall I spin the roulette? Okay.
Were we choosing a member who would spin this roulette?
- Yes. - Get out of the way.
- Was it necessary? - Today,
the shoot will drag out.
Who should pay 10 dollars? Kwang Soo or us?
Let's settle the matter with the OX roulette.
That's so sudden.
What's the point of what we did so far?
(What was the use?)
Who should pay 10 dollars? Kwang Soo or the 6 members?
- Do I pay everything if we get O? - Yes.
What's the point of what we did so far?
- We should do this. - Kwang Soo pays if we get O.
- That's right. - You made a sound.
- Kwang Soo needs to pay. - What?
It's O.
(The roulette decides that Kwang Soo will pay 10 dollars.)
- Are you gangsters? - Don't say that.
- It was a fair decision. - We decided with a roulette.
We decided with a roulette.
- Do I really need to pay alone? - This is Roulette Underworld.
(Welcome to Roulette Underworld.)
- This is Roulette Underworld. - That's right.
- Come to your senses. - That's right.
- How could you forget? - You shouldn't learn from him...
when you have been on the show for seven years.
- Wait and see. - "Wait and see"?
- See what? - We are seeing.
- See what? - See what?
(Slapping)
Pay up.
This is Roulette Underworld.
(Roulette Underworld is terrible.)
Here is 10 dollars.
We are thinking about ordering...
- some food. - Okay.
- Who needs to use the toilet? - Me.
Choose one person who will go to the toilet.
(Choose one person who will go to the toilet with a roulette.)
- What? - Don't do that.
- You can't do that. - Give us diapers then.
- This is ridiculous. - Does that mean it's okay...
if we relieve ourselves in the studio?
I can pee here.
(Or else, I will pee here.)
So Min, don't do that.
- Please stop. - You are doing well.
That's my style. You are doing well.
- That's the way to go. - You can pee here.
It's good to take off your clothes and lay down on the floor.
Decide on the number of people who will go with the roulette.
We need to use the roulette to go to the toilet.
We aren't free to pee?
Will you blur the body parts if we pee in the studio?
- We will blur it. - Will you clean up after us?
May we use a bucket?
- I don't have a problem with it. - I don't mind...
- peeing in the studio. - That's the purpose of the layout.
We can go in there to pee.
Isn't that a prison?
Do you want us to go there?
Isn't this a detention center?
(Those who haven't been picked by the roulette, come.)
(There is an open-bathroom prepared at the corner of the Underworld.)
But we ought to pee where there are doors to close.
That's right.
We need to pee in a bathroom that has doors.
(This built-in bathroom protects your privacy.)
- That's right. That's nice. - Of course.
- There are doors. - We just need to get number eight.
- Did you spin it? - I really need to go.
(Come on. Hurry.)
I really have to go to the bathroom.
- I need to go too. - They shouldn't do this.
(So Min spins the roulette as she urgently has to go.)
- If we get 8, all of us can go. - 8?
(The roulette will choose the number of members who will get to pee.)
I really need to go to the bathroom.
(How many members will get to go to the bathroom?)
- So Min, why did you spin it? - Why did you spin the roulette?
- Only two of you will go. - So Min.
You cannot spin it again. Only two of you will go.
(2 members can go to the bathroom.)
- Let me go. - Only two will go.
- Will we spin the roulette again? - Hey, hey.
- We'll spin it to see who will go. - All right. Only two of us will go.
- But I really need to go. - You can't go yet.
I will spin it since I said I had to go to the bathroom first.
I've been holding it in since this morning.
- Only two of us will get to go. - Whoever is picked can go, right?
- Yes. - But I need to go.
(Even their chance of peeing depends on the roulette.)
(Most of the members have been holding it in.)
- Jong Kook. - He doesn't even need to go.
(Jong Kook, who doesn't even need to go, is selected.)
- He doesn't even need to go. - He doesn't have to go.
I don't have to go though.
I'll go since I'm selected.
- Can he sell the ticket? - You should sell the ticket to us.
- Then I will... - You may sell the ticket for money.
Then I will sell you the ticket to the bathroom.
We have to spin one more time for another member.
- We have to spin it again. - No, no. I should spin it.
- Please select my name. - All right.
(They lost a chance to Jong Kook who doesn't even need to pee.)
(Their names must be chosen for them to go to the bathroom.)
(So Min, who has to go most urgently, is chosen.)
It's So Min. So Min is picked.
Thank you. I'll be back.
So Min and Jong Kook can go to the bathroom. Wait, hold on.
(They are in despair as their bladders can't hold it in anymore.)
Jong Kook, what do you want to do?
- Will you give it to someone else? - I'm going to sell this.
- For how much? - For 10 dollars.
(The price is 10 dollars.)
10 dollars?
- It's 10 dollars. - I don't have 10 dollars.
- You're so greedy. - I ought to get 10 dollars for it.
Then people who don't have money can't go to the bathroom?
- This is too harsh. - That's why we have tickets.
Are you being serious right now?
We're going to pee on the walls.
Oh, no. I really have to...
(What on earth is she doing?)
(Undressing)
- Hey, hey. - Go. You should go!
(Gosh, just go already.)
(We knew she was crazy, but we didn't think she'd be that crazy.)
Hurry.
Did I see that right?
No, what you saw really happened.
She is...
too extreme.
- Hurry. - I'll be back.
(I had no choice. I really have to pee.)
Where is the bathroom? Where do I need to go?
Which way is to the bathroom? I have to go now.
(Where is the exit? She's in a hurry.)
Where is the entrance?
(We gave you a chance to go, but why can't you go to the bathroom?)
There isn't a bathroom here.
(She was about to return to the Underworld she just escaped from.)
Thank you.
The bathroom. I must go to the bathroom.
Oh, my. It's surrounded by...
It's so hard to go to the bathroom.
There's no way out of this place.
(She runs at full speed to the bathroom.)
Where is the bathroom?
Hello.
(She sees the bathroom at last!)
- The bathroom. - Hold on.
(Hold on.)
What? There's a fee?
(There's another roulette here? Why is this roulette here?)
(She can't just go to the bathroom.)
Before you go to the bathroom,
you must spin the roulette.
The roulette will decide whether it's free or not.
But you didn't tell us about this before the shoot.
Had you told me this earlier, I would've gone to the bathroom.
(She bites the bullet and spins the roulette.)
I need to go now.
(She has to pay in order to pee.)
(Don't mess with my bladder right now.)
Please give me a discount. Let me pay two dollars less.
That can't be done.
Unbelievable.
You just wait and see. Mark my words.
(I'm only going since I need to pee now.)
- Hey. - Give me six dollars.
Please give me a discount.
- How can I give you a discount? - Let me just pay three dollars.
Then don't go. I'll just go to the bathroom.
- If you don't want to pay. - But you don't have to go.
I'll just go for a walk then. It's stuffy in here.
You're going for a walk?
But right now, I have a big problem down here.
(His bladder is about to explode.)
If you do, you should just pay.
- Think about your health. Right? - We are in an underworld after all.
But seeing Jae Seok peeing his pants isn't a good sight.
(Just pay 10 dollars for it.)
What's wrong with that? I'll get a lot of attention.
(What's so bad about that?)
- You want to generate buzz? - These days...
That's great.
Come on. Go borrow money.
I'll pay you six dollars.
Then don't go. I'll go for a walk.
- Hold on. - Why?
- Let him just go for a walk. - Exactly. I'll just go.
Both of you should hold it in. That's fair.
- Hold it in. - To be honest, I need to poop.
(Please let me go. I have to poop.)
I'm serious.
- If so, you need to pay more. - In that case, pay me more money.
- It's at least 10 dollars then. - Why did you tell him that?
- You should pay more then. - What are you doing?
Okay. I won't go.
Let's see what happens.
(Kwang Soo gives up.)
- It's fine by me. - I'll pay you six dollars.
- Six dollars? I'm going then. - He's not going to bid now.
- Let me pay 6 dollars for it. - Pay 7 dollars.
- I have three dollars now. - Think about it.
- He lowered it to 7 dollars. - I gave you a discount.
- Okay. I'll pay you 7 dollars. - Okay. Pay me 7 dollars.
- It's surrounded like an island. - I'll be back.
Goodness. Which way is the exit?
- Have fun at the bathroom. - Jae Seok, good luck.
- I went to the bathroom. - Yes?
They want me to spin the roulette in front of the bathroom.
- What? - Seriously?
- Why? - To see if you'll pay a fee or not.
- Gosh. This is unbelievable. - You paid at the bathroom?
- I had to pay 5 dollars. - You paid 5 dollars?
- I should hold it in then. - They're such jerks.
(These jerks who call themselves the crew...)
The roulette will decide whether it's free or not.
- What on earth are you saying? - You may spin the roulette.
I already paid seven dollars to come here.
But you must spin the roulette.
But I already paid seven dollars.
(But you're in the Roulette Underworld.)
(Had I known, I would've peed my pants.)
For goodness' sake.
You want me to pay more after I paid Jong Kook seven dollars?
(He's dumbfounded.)
I can't believe this is happening.
(Since it's the rule, Jae Seok spins the roulette.)
Please.
(No way! Jae Seok gets to use the bathroom for free.)
(After much struggle, he manages to not cause a scene.)
(Jae Seok comes back with an empty bladder.)
Did you pay five dollars or not?
- What? - Did you pay?
- You spun the roulette, didn't you? - Of course I did.
- What did you get? - Did you pay?
I peed for free.
- Okay. - Great job.
Does this deserve an applause?
Jae Seok, I paid though.
- She paid 5 dollars. - I paid 5 dollars.
(Of course it's praiseworthy. I had to pay 5 dollars.)
(Kwang Soo paid 10 dollars since he failed the mission.)
(So Min paid 5 dollars to use the bathroom.)
(The current sum of their mission money is 285 dollars.)
You had a chance to go to the bathroom.
I feel so much better now.
We thought you'd be hungry by now. We'll order Chinese food.
(Gosh, I'm hungry. We have to eat.)
- Hold on. - We have to do this right.
- They won't just feed us for free. - Let's spin the roulette well.
Whatever happens, we must eat.
- I think they'll make us spin it. - I want jjamppong rice.
I want jjamppong.
I want two helpings of jajangmyeon.
- Two helpings of jajangmyeon. - I want...
seafood jjamppong rice.
- I want jajangmyeon in a tray. - Seafood jjamppong, please.
Let's order tangsuyuk.
- Under whose name will you order? - It's under Seok Jin's.
- It's under Seok Jin's. - No, no.
- Seok Jin will order it. - No, all of us are ordering it.
- Seok Jin will order it. - Everyone can order one dish.
Seok Jin, order it for us.
You want me to treat you all?
- I heard your stock price went up. - You ought to buy us a meal.
- You look great when you eat it. - I really want to eat it.
- It will be under my name, right? - First off...
- Yes. - Put it under my name.
You want tangsuyuk instead of jajangmyeon in a tray.
- All right. - Okay.
We'll continue with Lunch Roulette for your lunch mission.
(Lunch Roulette? Goodness, it never stops, does it?)
You'll spin the number roulette to decide how many of you will eat.
Don't you think you should just let us eat?
- We need number eight for this. - This is too cruel.
If we get number one, it'll be a big problem.
- We must spin it. Let's just do it. - We must be thorough with this.
Let's choose who will spin this by the roulette.
We need someone to blame.
I'll choose the name roulette then.
- Let Kwang Soo spin this. - Go ahead.
We're going to decide who will spin the number roulette, right?
(Their fate depends on the selected member.)
It's Jong Kook. No, it's me.
- Hold on. It's Jae Seok. - No, it can't be Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok, the unluckiest of the unluckiest, is selected.)
(Sighing)
- Jae Seok, spin it. It's okay. - This is driving me crazy.
Jae Seok. Someone has to spin it.
- I'll spin this. - Okay.
- That unlucky punk. - I'll pick number eight for us.
We must have the mindset that we can overcome this.
- Please, Jae Seok. - Jae Seok.
- In 1, 2. - Please pick a good one, Jae Seok.
We should at least eat.
(Their lunch depends on his hands.)
- We should at least eat. - Let's get number eight.
- This will throw them off. - Let's make the crew flustered..
It's going great. The speed is good.
- I have a good feeling about this. - It's going well.
(It's heading to higher numbers?)
- Stop! Stop! - Come on.
(They want everyone to eat. Will the wish come true?)
- It's not bad. - It's not bad.
- That's not a bad number. - Good job.
(6 members will get to have their lunch.)
It's not a bad number.
- Six of us will get to eat. - That's not a bad number at all.
- 6 of us will eat. 2 can't eat. - Only 2 of us can't eat.
- That's all right. - It's only two people.
Choose the two members who...
- won't get to eat by the roulette. - We'll choose who can't eat.
(The roulette will decide the 2 members.)
(We won't ever stop spinning the roulettes, will we?)
If you spin it and pick your name, I'm going to compliment you.
- Jae Seok, you should spin it. - Okay.
Okay. Choose your name. Do it for the greater good.
The member Jae Seok picks will spin next.
- Sure, sure. - Okay.
(Jae Seok will choose 2 members who can't eat Chinese food.)
This member can't eat his or her lunch.
- I wonder who it's going to be. - The roulette picks me too often.
Hopefully, it won't be me.
- Who is it? - Goodness.
- It's Seok Jin. - Seok Jin can't eat tangsuyuk.
- He can't eat it. - Spin the roulette, Seok Jin.
Spin it.
You're useless in my life.
I won't forget the two of you.
- The person I had in mind... - Don't jump.
got selected.
I hope it's one of you two.
(He selects the last person who won't be eating Chinese food.)
The person I had in mind got selected.
I hope it's one of you two. Let it be Jae Seok.
(Will it be either Jae Seok or Kwang Soo?)
- It won't work. - It's Haha.
- Is it Ji Hyo? - No way.
(Will it be Ji Hyo...)
(who won't be eating tangsuyuk?)
- Is it Ji Hyo? - No way.
- It's Kwang Soo. - It's him.
(Kwang Soo is selected.)
(Yes, I get to eat.)
Okay, this is great.
It was one of the two.
We won't order jajangmyeon for Kwang Soo.
- Aren't you grateful? - He was so excited.
- He was so excited. - He's such an annoying brat.
(He regrets being annoying.)
We'll order food except for the two.
Won't we get to eat?
- Is there an option to pay? - Again?
(He can't use the restroom or eat.)
(You don't look so good, Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo is breaking out into a cold sweat.
Does your stomach hurt, Kwang Soo?
I'll accept the challenge.
I wanted to treat everyone.
I really have to poop.
Pay the money and use the restroom.
I'll give you a dollar.
If I pay, can I use the restroom any time?
(Please let me go before it's too late.)
(Suddenly...)
(the lights go out.)
- What happened? - Did lights go out?
- I'm scared. - What's going on?
What's going on?
What's happening?
- I'm scared. - Come on.
- Don't do this. - What's going on?
- I can't see anything. - Why did the lights go out?
Is everyone leaving?
- Shall we go out? - What?
(While everyone discusses for a solution...)
(What?)
What are you doing?
What were you trying to do?
(What were you up to?)
(The lights turn on again.)
(They see him standing alone.)
I think he's on a mission.
(He makes it obvious.)
- Are you on a mission? - That must be it.
- That's not true. - Explain to us.
- I was... - What were you trying to do?
Since Haha has the most amount of money,
- To steal his money? - I was about to steal it.
(He was about to steal Haha's money.)
Are you admitting it?
I don't want you to think that I'm on a mission.
Why are you the only one standing?
I was about to steal Haha's money.
Sit back down.
From Seok Jin's mission money,
60 dollars were taken and given to the Designer.
(Given to the Designer?)
(Why was my mission money...)
(given to the Designer?)
Did you take away 60 dollars from me?
- 60 dollars? - I don't have 60 dollars.
- Why? - The Designer?
(What does it mean?)
From 33 dollars of Seok Jin's money,
60 dollars were taken.
- You have negative 27 dollars. - Negative?
- Did you take 60 dollars? - Yes.
- All at once? - The 60 dollars...
were given to the Designer.
Why is it 60 dollars?
- What's the reason? - Did you say something?
- What's the reason? - He must have said something.
The Designer who designed Roulette Underworld is sitting among you.
(One of us...)
(is the Designer.)
- I knew it. - One of us is the Designer.
My goodness.
(I knew something was wrong.)
Goodness.
(Someone wants to steal our mission money.)
Who is it?
If the Designer carries out the hidden mission,
he or she can take other members' mission money.
You must figure out the identity of the Designer...
and the hidden mission.
If you guess correctly,
the Designer fails the hidden mission.
All the money that the Designer has accumulated...
will be equally given out to the rest of the members.
(Members get an equal share.)
(It's a psychological battle...)
(between those who steal and those who protect their money.)
(The Designer versus Running Man)
- By the way... - I'm bad at guessing.
- Do we have to guess who? - I'm bad at guessing.
What did I do? It's Jae Seok.
Jae Seok suddenly became quiet.
- That's true. - Right.
Didn't he suddenly become quiet?
Here's what's funny.
The lights came back on too early.
He froze while standing up.
- He was the only one. - Goodness.
Kwang Soo is good at designing.
- He's good at pulling tricks. - In the past,
- I designed a maze. - Right.
It was a huge mess.
So Min, why do you look upset?
It's because...
when the lights went out,
I acted similarly to Jae Seok.
I moved my arm to steal someone's wallet,
but Kwang Soo wasn't in his seat.
- I was standing. - He was.
I extended my arm, but he wasn't there.
When the lights came back on, he was sitting here.
Is there one Designer?
There may be multiple.
There's only one Designer.
(There's only one Designer.)
Is there only one?
There are two members who aren't allowed to eat.
- Isn't that why it's 60 dollars? - That's right.
(As 6 members get to eat, the amount is 60 dollars.)
The arrow is pointing at six.
Six members get to eat.
It must be 10 dollars per person.
That's why it's 60 dollars.
- By the way... - This is it, everyone.
It's Seok Jin and number six.
- Does that mean... - He's right.
(The roulettes point at Seok Jin and number six.)
(Wait a minute.)
Why is it pointing at my name when it was Kwang Soo before?
Right?
(The roulette...)
(indicates a different member.)
(When Seok Jin spun the roulette,)
(Kwang Soo was selected.)
(When the lights came back on,)
(the target changed to Seok Jin.)
It means that Kwang Soo stood up...
- and spun the roulette. - I'm getting goosebumps.
- That makes no sense. - I'm getting goosebumps.
- That's right. - That's why...
he wasn't there when So Min moved her arm.
That's why 60 dollars were taken from Seok Jin.
Why would I spin it?
Jae Seok kept saying that he's the Designer.
It could be a method to trick us.
- He's capable of doing that. - Definitely.
He intentionally admits that it's him.
We narrowed down our choices. It's definitely one of them.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo seem suspicious.
Right.
(Is either Jae Seok or Kwang Soo the Designer?)
Here's the next mission.
It's called Dreadful Pirate.
- Pirate? - Are we playing it again?
It's so cute.
(It's a miniature pirate.)
There aren't many knives.
- There are eight. - There aren't many slots.
Spin the roulette to determine...
how many should succeed.
You must also decide...
how many knives to stick in.
This is amazing.
There are only eight slots.
You're eliminated automatically if you get number eight.
- Please spin the roulette. - Okay.
- Give it a try. - Go, Se Chan.
One person is good.
- 1 is the best. - 1 person is the best.
Let it be number one.
(The smallest number...)
(means the maximum amount of gain.)
- It looks good. - Keep spinning.
- No. - It's number one.
(Will it be a small number...)
(that all the members want?)
- It passed. - It's two people.
Two members is good.
(Two members are selected.)
(They gain additional mission money if two members succeed.)
It's possible for two members to succeed.
(She feels the need to do something.)
I'll spin next.
(What's going on?)
(What's with her enthusiasm?)
(Don't stop me. I feel lucky.)
So Min.
(Something seems suspicious.)
(Trust me.)
It might work.
(Will it be a small number?)
- Is it 5? - It's 4.
(She gets four.)
(They must stick in four knives.)
(If they succeed, they gain mission money.)
- Four knives? - I trust you, So Min.
Stay calm, So Min.
(She starts to stick the knives in.)
One.
- 2. - 2.
We're half way there.
- 3. - This is the last one.
(She sticks three in safely.)
(There's one remaining.)
(If So Min succeeds...)
You can do it, So Min.
(Only one more person has to succeed.)
You're doing well.
Okay.
(So Min succeeds.)
(Great job, So Min.)
(There's only one member left to go.)
Jong Kook wants to do it.
(I will...)
(put an end to this game.)
(If Jong Kook succeeds,)
(they can win additional mission money.)
(In order to succeed,)
Here I go.
(it must be a small number.)
- Come on. - Look.
- It's one. - That's it.
- Is it 1? - It's 2.
(Two is selected.)
(He must stick in two knives.)
(Great job, Jong Kook.)
- Good job. - If Jong Kook succeeds,
- we clear the mission. - Right.
Turn it once.
- Like this? - Yes.
Did it work?
(Is...)
(this...)
(real life?)
(The game ends...)
(in vain.)
Come on.
(How could he? They were so close.)
(Kicking)
Goodness.
Gosh.
- We were so close. - Kwang Soo.
Why did you have to ruin it?
What?
(They fail to gain additional mission money.)
(At that time,)
(the lights go out again.)
Here it is.
(The lights go out.)
(It means the Designer is on the move.)
- No. - Don't spin the roulette.
- Who was it before? - Where is it?
- Kwang Soo. - What's the number?
(The designer's plan is exposed.)
- Someone is here. - Who is this?
- Who is this? - Se Chan.
- There are so many in the front. - Who are you?
(What traces will the designer leave behind?)
- It's Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo.
(Meanwhile, on the other side where the roulette is placed...)
(What? Did he just move the roulette?)
- You're here. - Sorry?
(He's flustered.)
It's Kwang Soo.
(It looks like he has a lot to say.)
Why are you standing over there?
(Why are you there? You look suspicious.)
- What? You were all there. - You couldn't hear?
I couldn't even see.
- Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is the designer.
That's right. It is Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo, you were behind this? - Kwang Soo is the designer.
(The designer exposed himself just like that? That was too easy.)
(Is Kwang Soo, who seems too obvious, the designer?)
(A day before the shoot)
(Preliminary meeting with the crew)
(Is the designer Kwang Soo?)
(Yes, Kwang Soo...)
(is the designer...)
(as expected.)
(The designer who got exposed within 2 hours has entered.)
We had a meeting with the message...
you sent us before.
(What message?)
I didn't mean anything by it. I didn't know it'd be a big thing.
You had a meeting.
(Do I have to face the penalties? It will take me a year to do all.)
I faced every penalty.
I had to go to the Labyrinth and Indonesia to face the penalties.
I was never excluded from the penalty, not even once.
Just as you said, you're always chosen to face the penalty.
And for that, we do sympathize for your suffering.
So we have prepared a hidden mission for you.
(A hidden mission?)
Kwang Soo, tomorrow, you will be...
the designer who constructed the set for the Roulette Underworld.
(You will be the designer who built Roulette Underworld.)
In the set,
there are a number roulette and a name roulette.
During the shoot, when there are unexpected blackouts,
without getting caught,
you may adjust the name and number roulette to your liking.
You can earn mission money during the blackouts.
I will get to keep the money?
Yes. In other words, the rest of the members must uncover...
the designer and what the hidden mission is.
If they fail to do so, it's your win.
You will keep the mission money and be exempted from being chosen.
(He will earn money and be exempted.)
(I'll be exempted?)
(This is his last chance not to be chosen as the trip companion.)
- The members can't choose me? - No, they cannot.
If I win, I will not face the penalty.
Exactly.
(This is amazing.)
We are giving you a special opportunity...
- since you were always chosen. - Thank you.
We have high hopes for this project.
But there was one time I completely ruined the episode with the maze.
I mean...
(He's reminded of his past once again.)
(The crew had prepared a special for Kwang Soo with a high budget.)
(Are you the spy? Are you?)
(He was suspected from the start.)
(And he was punished gravely.)
(This was his opportunity to take his revenge.)
(Whenever the crew prepared a special episode for him,)
(he was the prime suspect and suffered greatly.)
(And during these episodes prepared for him,)
(he was always ruined.)
(His painful past refreshes his memory.)
I'm grateful, but could this work?
We're very worried now that you don't seem confident.
(This special is making us worry about you and ourselves as well.)
I don't think I can pull this off.
(Sir, I can't do this.)
I can't do this. This is giving me a lot of pressure.
This is such a big project.
(We did it since you asked.)
I just need to be careful of Jong Kook.
(He's worried about Jong Kook.)
Does he still have gout?
We'll see you tomorrow.
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
(He exited as he worries about all sorts of things.)
Do you want to sleep over at my house tonight?
I'm so nervous.
(He had shaky eyes. Why didn't we see this coming?)
(That this project was destined to fail in vain.)
(They saw.)
(They caught.)
(And they ended.)
(The crew is in a crisis.)
(He smiles as he pretends he's not.)
All right, Kwang Soo's mission money,
30 dollars, will go to the designer.
He's giving money to himself.
(Kwang Soo has been exposed. Will there be a twist?)
I was just informed that your lunch has arrived.
We'll give you your lunch.
What are you doing? Why are you putting your hand on me?
That didn't mean anything.
- His hand was on me for too long. - Who did that?
- Kwang Soo put his hand on me. - That's nothing.
Is there something on my name tag? Check.
He's worrying over nothing.
- I bet he's exhausted today. - Nothing is on it?
(I'm so tired.)
- I agree. It's hard for Kwang Soo. - He keeps...
(You little...)
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
(He slaps Jong Kook out of frustration.)
- Hey. - I was just imagining this.
- Go, and get yourself checked out. - I'm really sorry.
- I'm sorry. - He's unbelievable.
I'm sorry. I couldn't hold it in.
Can we eat now?
- You may eat now. - All right.
Turn the metal container around.
- What is this? - It's a roulette again.
(There's a roulette on this too?)
Goodness, this is too much.
(I'm sick of Roulette Underworld.)
- Let's spin it. - It's the roulette again.
- Let me spin it. I'm not greedy. - Give it a spin.
- I'm not greedy over food. - That's right. Spin it.
He should spin it. You can't do that. Stop it.
(Since he's not allowed to eat, won't he get lucky?)
I hope it's free.
(Charged)
- I'm sorry. - I knew he would be unlucky.
I'm sorry.
(He has committed a grave sin.)
- Each dish will cost... - Wait.
5 dollars, and since you have 6 dishes, we'll collect 30 dollars.
(Scowling)
You should just pay.
We have to choose who will pay.
(They have 255 dollars left.)
- Thank you for the food. - This is yours.
- I have jjamppong. - Here's the seafood jjamppong.
I ordered jjamppong rice.
- I ordered jajangmyeon. - That's mine.
- Thank you. - Gosh, that one has crabs.
Seok Jin and I can't eat, can we?
- Is there a chance for us to eat? - We can't eat it at all?
- That looks good. - I think we can eat that.
Jajangmyeon looks really tasty.
(Are jajangmyeon and jjamppong pies in the sky for them?)
- Jajangmyeon is tasty. - What are you talking about?
- Se Chan. - Stop it.
- I'll help you. - No, don't.
Just pay back what you owe me.
I will pay you back.
- You can eat when you pay back. - This is good.
- If I pay you back, I can eat this? - And pay a dollar for this.
(There always seems to be debts when Chinese food is involved.)
(He borrowed the money without thinking as he was hungry.)
(With the interest, 1 dollar became 4 dollars.)
(I'll buy you a carton of cigarettes.)
(He tried his best not to pay back his debt.)
You haven't paid me back in weeks.
Can we eat in peace? Why do you keep talking about debts?
I'm just a third party, but it's making me uncomfortable.
- That wasn't it. - Goodness.
- But it became four dollars. - Jae Seok is right.
(Mr. Lee with bad credit is hungry.)
We should eat in peace at least.
I'll give you four dollars right after I have a sip of the soup.
Do you have money?
What is this?
I don't want this. What is this?
Look at these!
(He gives her 4 dollars he had in his pocket.)
- You're horrible. - Stop bringing food to the table.
- What is this? - Real cash means nothing here.
- But this is money. - I need money from the game.
Forget them. I can't use them here.
Let me have a mouthful with a dollar.
(They have reached a compromise.)
Can I have some broth?
(He gets to have a mouthful.)
(This is his mouthful.)
Kwang Soo, this isn't right. I didn't even get to eat.
(As he picks up a lot of noodles,)
(the pitch-dark blackout has visited the members again.)
- Hold Kwang Soo. - Hold him.
- I got him. - Hold him.
- Get ahold of him. - I've been here all along.
- Yes? - Hey.
- Stop eating. - Jae Seok has to pay 40 dollars.
Stop eating it. It's mine.
(It's over anyway. Let me at least fill my stomach.)
He ate the whole thing.
(Oh, no.)
Give back my noodles!
(He chose food over the mission. The roulettes haven't changed.)
(I see. Since he's not moving,)
(there's no mention of the designer.)
(He's the culprit.)
I can't believe this.
(Can the mission proceed without a hitch?)
Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes. - Yes.
The mission is Dreadful Rock-Paper-Scissors.
(The 3rd mission is Dreadful Rock-Paper-Scissors.)
Everyone...
will choose 3 cards out of 10 cards...
as you each take a turn.
You will play rock-paper-scissors with me.
You must win the number of times the roulette chooses.
We should get one.
Kwang Soo should spin it since he's the architect of this project.
Because he's unlucky,
- he won't get what he wants. - I won't say anymore.
- There's another... - You can't take this back.
- Okay. - Of course.
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
- Someone else should spin it. - Let Ji Hyo spin it.
- Move aside. - You're unlucky.
- Are you serious? - You did well.
You're not lucky. Move away from it.
- Are you serious? - You did well. Now, come.
- Move when there's a blackout. - You have to move around.
(You should move when there's a blackout, not when it's bright.)
- You little... - What?
- You're done. - "You're done."
3 or 2 will be great for us.
- 1 is the best number. - 1?
2 isn't bad since we'll have 10 cards.
1 is the best, but 2 isn't bad.
1, 2, and 3 aren't bad numbers.
- This looks good. - Number four would be good.
- It's not bad. You did it. - It's number one.
- Great. - I knew it.
Ji Hyo is lucky, indeed.
- One of us... - Hey, Ji Hyo.
She gets lucky all the time.
- Three of us have to beat you. - Okay.
Let me go first.
- We'll accomplish this mission. - Of course, we will.
Just three of us have to win. Don't make us play.
(He's choosing the cards carefully.)
Why don't you finish this mission before Kwang Soo's turn?
We can't let Kwang Soo see the cards.
He's going to give signals to the crew when he sees our cards.
- He might wink at them. - Observe him.
- He might wink twice. - The wink means paper.
I bet he already made signals.
- Haha, you watched "Tazza". - This is not a team game.
Close your eyes. Turn around.
(Haha chose 3 cards.)
(The key to success is to use them at the right time.)
Go.
(Haha has 2 rocks and 1 paper.)
- Let's go at rock-paper-scissors. - Sure. Hold on.
I'm not going to see it.
- That's good. - That's a good idea.
You have to be smarter. Take a chance.
(Should I do paper or rock?)
(The director chooses scissors.)
Take a chance.
(If Haha chooses rock, he wins.)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(What did Haha choose?)
Paper
(Rock)
- Okay. - Okay.
(Running Man has 1 win with Haha's victory.)
- Good job. - Nice.
- Great job. - Good.
Mix them. I have a good feeling.
Let's finish at Se Chan.
(Ji Hyo is next.)
- I chose it with So Min. - All right.
Same positions?
Are they in the same positions?
(2 rocks and 1 paper)
(He's thirsty.)
Let's go.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo wins with paper.)
I won.
(Running Man wins 2 times in a row.)
- I won. - He's bad at games.
- Let's finish this off. - End it, Se Chan.
- I will. - Three cards.
(Se Chan is next, and Running Man has 2 wins.)
- Do I pick anything? - Yes.
(He's careful.)
If he wins, that's our win.
Yes. This is over.
(The director chose...)
(three rocks.)
(He's in trouble.)
(This won't do. Today is a bad day.)
I picked these.
(If Se Chan doesn't have scissors, he can't lose.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(The first match is a tie.)
All right.
Rock-paper-scissors
Scissors
(Se Chan wins with paper.)
I won?
I won.
(Running Man wins.)
- I won. - We won.
- I won. - Good job.
- Please pick. - I picked these.
(He picked 2 papers and 1 rock. He couldn't have lost.)
- Does he only have rocks? - He does.
- He only has rocks. - Why?
- He only has rocks. - How is that possible?
You know how we all stood up when we won?
Kwang Soo clenched his teeth.
- Is that right? - He clenched his bottom teeth.
- We won. - We won.
(I'm done today.)
He only has rocks.
- Is that right? - He clenched his bottom teeth.
- What? - His bottom teeth.
All right.
You're not going to high-five me, right?
Do we get more mission money?
One person will escape.
Please spin the roulette to find out who.
- That sounds good. - One person.
- They have to find it, right? - Let's get it.
(Who will have to go out and find mission money?)
- Back and forth. - It's Ji Hyo.
- Good. - This is good.
- Good. It's Ji Hyo. - Go.
- I'll go. - Ready.
(She gets 30 seconds.)
(They must get the lost mission money back.)
This is so messy.
The designer must have hid it well.
I should have went. I'm a ghost.
(Kwang Soo looks suspicious while everybody is not paying attention.)
(Why is he holding a tape and heading to the roulette?)
(Is he trying to change something?)
Kwang Soo is putting something on.
(Did you see that?)
Kwang Soo, why are you doing that to Jong Kook?
(What is it?)
(Sighing)
He's in trouble.
Why are you sighing?
I don't know anymore.
(He doesn't know what to do today.)
(We don't know either, Kwang Soo.)
I don't know anymore.
Whenever you say that,
it feels like something is not going right.
Is there something?
Look. Just look.
Jae Seok, there was one left.
- It must be 10 dollars. - It must be.
(There are 10 dollars in the envelope.)
It's 10 dollars.
She's always so lucky.
- How is she so good? - How much is that in total?
Again?
(It's dark again.)
- Hold him. - Hey.
Hold onto him.
(Kwang Soo is acting suspicious, so they hold onto him.)
- Who's this? - Me.
- What about this? - Me.
Hold onto him.
- I'm here. - That's So Min.
Seok Jin is on my right, and Kwang Soo is on my left.
- I'm holding Ji Hyo. - Kwang Soo.
- Our hands... - What happened?
- Nobody moved. I didn't move. - Let's see.
(Please trust me.)
Jae Seok's 60 dollars...
- was accrued by the designer. - What?
(Kwang Soo didn't move, but Jae Seok's money got stolen?)
Why is my name there?
(They held onto Kwang Soo, but the roulette is turned to Jae Seok.)
(The mission money roulette is turned towards 6.)
(Is Kwang Soo not the designer?)
- I didn't move. - No way.
- You know I didn't move, right? - It's not Kwang Soo.
(You know I didn't move, right?)
Didn't Se Chan sound far away?
No, he was next to me.
- Kwang Soo didn't move this time. - If it's not him...
(Kwang Soo is smiling. What just happened?)
When we play games, they always get suspicious of me.
They always pick me. I think...
I need an advantage.
So...
we have Plan B for you.
(Plan B?)
When you press on a member's name tag for five seconds...
and they touch the roulette, the money goes to the designer.
(Kwang Soo has to press down on the name tag.)
(Before the lights went out,)
(Kwang Soo touched Jong Kook's name tag for 5 seconds.)
(He got himself a proxy for spinning the roulette.)
Why are you doing this? Why is your hand on me?
- That was nothing. - You hand was on me for too long.
(When Ji Hyo went out to look for mission money,)
(he waited for Jong Kook to spin the roulette.)
(He spun it without knowing anything.)
(That's how the designer earned 60 dollars.)
- You know I didn't move, right? - It's not Kwang Soo.
But...
Kwang Soo breathed weirdly.
(Kwang Soo breathed weirdly.)
I held onto him,
and he asked who I was. I didn't say anything.
He asked again, and I said it was me.
Then he sighed like it was nonsense.
It was as if he was saying, "I'm done for."
You know what type of breath that was?
Okay. Do as you please.
- This is not a team game. - Hey!
What's on your back?
What?
(Somebody played around with his name.)
What? What is it?
Look at this punk. You're making it obvious.
- What is it? - Is this your mission?
(He turns from the designer into a fool.)
What's this?
- Is this the mission? - Who did this?
I have no idea.
(He's not under the radar anymore.)
(Plan B has begun. He has a chance to turn this around.)
(He has to earn the penalty exemption.)
(Jae Seok is his next target. He has to press his name for 5 seconds.)
(You made fun of me.)
This roulette mission is called Dreadful Marshmallow.
(Round 4 is Dreadful Marshmallow.)
Jong Kook said marshmallows last in your system for years.
Right.
(He starts pressing down on Jae Seok's name tag.)
(If I do this for 5 seconds, Jae Seok will come under me.)
(This is his only hope to turn the table around.)
You can roast it.
It's so good when you roast it.
(Chuckling)
(This secret mission is too obvious.)
(What's Kwang Soo doing now?)
(They exchange smiles.)
(He doesn't know what to do.)
What is it? What's going on?
That was too...
- Is he being too obvious? - It's too...
I felt it.
That was too...
(It's as if he's screaming out and saying he's the designer.)
(When he was trying Plan B on Jong Kook)
Why are you doing this? Why is your hand on me?
(That was so obvious.)
That was nothing.
- His hand was on me for too long. - Who?
Kwang Soo had his hand on my shoulder.
Is there something on my name tag? Check.
(He was nervous from the beginning.)
There's a disadvantage for Kwang Soo.
(We are sure Kwang Soo has a mission.)
I felt it.
(He's silent.)
I think there's something going on with him too.
(Please help me.)
(What should I do?)
Let's say Kwang Soo has a secret mission today.
How many times has he messed up?
Are we filming next week or not?
Tell me. I was planning a family trip.
This roulette mission is Dreadful Marshmallow.
I'm free next week.
(He calls himself out.)
(They give him credit for having the courage to say it.)
(Should we stop for today?)
Keep it up until the end.
This roulette mission is...
Dreadful Marshmallow.
In 30 seconds,
you must stack three marshmallows in a row.
Stack them?
(They have to win this final mission to get more mission money and win.)
You don't have to stack it like that.
(Jong Kook goes 1st and fails.)
(Ji Hyo goes 2nd and fails as well.)
No. That won't work.
- It doesn't work. - Fail.
(So Min fails, and they lose the mission.)
Half and Half Project Part 4, Roulette Underworld...
has concluded.
You have accumulated...
286 dollars.
- We have to go. - Running Man has lost.
(They couldn't keep 300 dollars.)
(They can already see the Cage of Death.)
I can't go to Australia.
However, since we won,
there are four exits.
3 exits lead to Cage of Death,
and one exit is for Krabi.
If you exit through the exit for Krabi,
that goes on the roulette.
(Whatever they choose will go on the roulette.)
There are three exits for Cage of Death.
- There's a 25-percent chance. - We get another chance.
Before that,
it's time to arrest the designer who confused you all.
He didn't confuse us.
(Everybody knows the culprit.)
We weren't confused at all.
Please come forward one at a time, and tell me who it was.
Also, tell me how they took your money. If you're accurate,
I'll approve.
The designer is Kwang Soo.
I pick Kwang Soo.
I think it's Kwang Soo.
The name tag he touches...
He put his hand on the name tag.
(They know Plan B exactly as well.)
He pressed down on my back.
(Snickering)
I think he was too nervous.
I'm sorry.
I'll see you next week.
Let me reveal the answer.
Today's designer...
was surprisingly...
("Surprisingly"?)
It wasn't him?
(Is there something unexpected about the designer?)
(Was it someone else other than Kwang Soo?)
- It was Kwang Soo. - Exactly.
(There's nothing unexpected at all.)
I thought it wasn't him. You scared me.
(I thought it wasn't him. You scared me.)
If it wasn't him, that would have been shocking.
- Gosh. - My heart skipped a beat.
"Surprisingly".
The person with the most mission money is Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is in 1st place.)
It was a dollar difference.
It's because she found the money.
- Really? - How much do I have?
(She won because she found 10 dollars during the mission.)
We'll have to go there.
- It's a bad place. - I can't go to Australia.
From a bird's-eye view,
this is a roulette as well.
(The set is a huge roulette.)
(It's truly Roulette Underworld.)
That must look cool.
(The designer didn't know either.)
(That must look cool.)
Is this the center?
- That's right. - It all connects...
and looks like a circle.
(She gives a thumbs up.)
This is awesome.
(Roulette Underworld)
Out of the four exits,
Krabi is one of them.
Cage of Death is on three of them.
(There are 3 bad exits and 1 good one.)
- Do we choose the exit first? - Yes, go ahead.
Shouldn't it be the door we always used?
- Exit 4? - I think it's Exit 2.
I think it's 2 or 4.
I think it's Exit 2 as well.
Let's spin the roulette and listen to that person.
All right. Kwang Soo, spin it.
- Jae Seok. - Designer, spin it.
- All right. - I got it wrong.
We listen to the person that the roulette lands on, right?
- That's right. - Yes.
(The chosen person gets to pick an exit.)
(Who will be the one to decide?)
It's me. It's Jong Kook.
Is it me?
(Is it me?)
- Which one? - Exit 4.
- Exit 4. - This one?
- Yes. - When you go out,
if there's a red sign that says Cage of Death, it's a penalty.
(If the floor is red, it's a penalty.)
If it's Krabi, it's a blue sign.
(Blue means paradise.)
Go with your instincts.
(We made the correct decision, right?)
- Please. - We want Thailand.
- If we get Thailand... - If it's Krabi...
(There's a door between paradise and the underworld.)
(There are 3 reds and 1 blue. Which one is Exit 4?)
Will Exit 4 be...
Krabi or Cage of Death?
If this is Krabi, that will be amazing.
It can't be.
(What will the last destination be?)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(The decision has been made.)
Two...
(Exit 4)
Three.
(Is it paradise or the underworld?)
(Cage of Death)
- It's three, right? - Cage of Death.
- Which one was it? - Two?
Krabi was Exit 1.
(Krabi was Exit 1.)
The final destination for Half and Half Tour...
is Australia's Cage of Death.
- Crocodiles like blood. - It'll be a pool of blood.
- I can't believe this. - I don't want to go.
- It depends on whom Ji Hyo picks. - Right.
Today's winner is Ji Hyo.
(She's the 4th winner of the project.)
- Song Ji Hyo! - Song Ji Hyo!
He's the designer.
- Please trust him. - No.
Please take the designer.
- How many can I buy? - You can buy four name tags.
- Four? - That's...
- a lot. - You have two each, right?
Please consider the designer.
Let me explain why Kwang Soo was the designer.
- He sent me a message. - What did he say?
Hold on. You can talk after we finish filming.
No, we have to hear it. What is it?
He said he always gets picked,
so if he succeeds the secret mission, he wanted an exemption.
(This is the actual message he sent.)
That's what he said.
- He wanted to save himself. - I wanted an exemption.
- So you wanted to save yourself. - It was more like...
(He's flustered.)
(That's what it sounds like to us.)
- That was well expressed. - Right?
That was a good one.
He wanted to save himself only. He's right.
It was more like...
Where is Kwang Soo's name?
- Here. - I have two.
I see.
He has two.
He's right next to Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is here.
- Let's do two first. - Let's do that.
- Let's do it. - I'll do two first.
- Ji Hyo. - Come on.
- I tried my best. - Let's do it.
- I'll do 2. - There's a 50-percent chance.
- I'll cover my name first. - Of course.
Of course, you should do that.
You're going for me.
- Ji Hyo, Jong Kook's name... - What if...
we put all Jae Seok's name?
(What if we do Jae Seok for the 2 that's left?)
It's up to me, so I'll erase So Min's name.
- Thank you. - It's up to you.
- I have one. - She's scared of crocodiles.
- I'm scared of them too. - Who isn't?
Who likes crocodiles?
I got bitten by one when I was young.
(Is he a pathological liar?)
The crocodile...
So Min is really scared.
He did this...
- to pay back at us. - I'll spin it.
- This is for buying a name tag. - He's so mean.
- Please spin it. - I agree.
Please.
(Who will get their names put on?)
No. It's Kwang Soo.
It's Haha. It's Seok Jin.
Is it me? No way.
It's Se Chan.
(Se Chan gets picked.)
Why do I get picked all day?
Let's spin to pick whose name tag you'll cover.
Let's do that.
- Okay. - You're spinning it again?
If it's me, you have to cover mine.
This is the Roulette Underworld.
- This is clean. - You're outstanding.
Please turn around before I spin.
I'll pick the person that the roulette lands on.
- Sure. - This is cruel.
(He's given up now.)
- I don't want to do this anymore. - I'll go.
I think we spun the roulette like 30 times.
I spun it really hard.
Can we look?
- No, no yet. - I'd be on "Show Me the Money".
This is too intense for me.
We can look, right?
(Which lucky person will get their name erased?)
I'm worried.
Who is it?
It's Haha.
- It's strange. - He's so lucky.
- He's really lucky. - This is incredible.
- Seriously, Haha. - It's strange.
- Thank you. - We must accept it.
Attach it to Haha's name.
Is it attaching name tag?
Haha is so lucky.
- Goodness. - In Haha's case,
he kept winning.
- It'd be fun to take him with us. - Really?
- Of course. - That's right.
- Admit that it'll be fun. - Why would I go?
You didn't do anything wrong.
The last is...
Cage of Death in Australia.
(One slot for punishment is empty.)
- It's Cage of Death. - It's time to spin the roulette.
This is very nerve-racking.
I'll spin it the opposite way.
- I'll spin it hard. - Push it really hard.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Who will be sent to the last destination?)
Goodness.
- I'm worried. - Four is many.
I might get selected...
even though Kwang Soo has many name tags.
- It passed my name. - No.
- It's not me. - It's Jong Kook.
- No, it's Kwang Soo. - Okay.
Keep moving.
(Will it be Kwang Soo?)
(Or will it be Jae Seok?)
(Who will be sent to Cage of Death?)
No.
(Kwang Soo will be sent to Cage of Death.)
(Kwang Soo is selected, and Jae Seok survives.)
- I knew it. - Goodness.
That was perfect.
It was really perfect.
(He's relieved.)
Wasn't your name here?
- It was Ji Hyo. - Yes, it was my name.
It was originally my name.
I thought it'd be Jae Seok.
(Why did he design Roulette Underworld?)
Something would be missing if Kwang Soo weren't selected.
- That's right. - Kwang Soo is necessary.
Jae Seok, Jae Seok, So Min, and Kwang Soo.
My goodness.
It was originally my name.
Thank you, Designer Kwang.
- It's such a relief. - I know.
- My goodness. - All right.
- What did I do wrong? - Long live the designer.
- Long live the designer. - Something feels strange.
Candidates for Half and Half Project have been determined.
Here are the four final destinations.
It's recommended by Haha.
Bora Bora in Polynesia...
is where So Min is selected to go.
(So Min will go to Bora Bora in Polynesia.)
It's recommended by the staff.
Jae Seok will go to Nevis Swing in New Zealand.
(Jae Seok will go to Nevis Swing in New Zealand.)
It's recommended by Seok Jin.
Jae Seok will go on a full tour in Rome, Italy.
(Jae Seok will go on a tour in Rome, Italy.)
Lastly,
Cage of Death in Australia is recommended by staff members.
It's where Kwang Soo will go.
(Kwang Soo will go to Cage of Death in Australia.)
Whenever we do this,
certain members always get selected.
- That's right. - There are a few.
- He's a new member. - Whatever we do,
it's always the same members.
Let me warn you.
I hope Nevis Swing won't get selected.
- What if it does? - However, I'll take...
one of you with me.
- One of us? - Yes.
- We're in trouble. - Ever since we started the project,
- I had someone in mind. - Really?
However,
his name tag started taking over the roulette.
It's my personal opinion.
- It was at first. - Right.
- That was my thought at first. - I understand.
The probability is 25 percent.
- Let's spin it. - Turn it clockwise.
Like this?
- Here we go. - It'll determine who.
- Don't push softly. - Don't.
- It's the last chance. - Right.
- We can't change the result. - Here we go.
2 destinations are good, and the other 2 are bad.
It's half and half.
(2 destinations are paradise, and the other 2 are dreadful.)
(Each has a 50-percent chance.)
(Who will go where?)
- Let's go. - I hope it won't be me.
- In 1, 2, 3. - Please.
(The roulette is turned for the final time.)
- Here it is. - It's the last chance.
- Please. - I'm serious.
- Anything but Nevis Swing. - We get one chance.
(The selected member must go.)
This is nerve-racking.
- It's Kwang Soo. - Let it be Kwang Soo.
It's Jae Seok.
- It's Kwang Soo. - It's Jae Seok.
- It's Kwang Soo. - Let it be Kwang Soo.
It's Jae Seok.
It's Kwang Soo.
- No. - It's Kwang Soo.
(If Kwang Soo is selected, he goes to a cage full of crocodiles.)
(If So Min is selected, she goes to Bora Bora.)
(What will be the result of the final spin?)
(Kwang Soo is selected.)
(Kwang Soo gets penalized as always.)
Let's get it.
(Kwang Soo gets the final penalty.)
This is incredible.
- I knew it. - See?
It's Kwang Soo.
- Goodness. - Jae Seok was the most excited.
- I don't know why. - Goodness.
Jae Seok has to go anyway.
That's right.
You got lucky.
- It's better than Nevis Swing. - We don't know...
- whom Kwang Soo will choose. - Right.
(We don't know whom Kwang Soo will choose.)
- Let's see. - The member is selected.
The result is...
No one is talking.
Wait a minute.
Everyone is avoiding eye contact with me.
I can't look at Kwang Soo.
- We're not avoiding. - Seriously.
For Half and Half Tour,
the final destination and member...
- are Cage of Death in Australia... - Who is his plus-one?
with Kwang Soo.
It's Cage of Death.
(Moving)
Wait a minute. Why did you switch places with me?
He must decide with whom he'll travel.
- I have no idea. - Why not?
- Will you choose now? - Does he get a choice?
(Kwang Soo will choose his plus-one.)
Or will you choose next week?
(Whom will Kwang Soo choose?)
It's a good idea to take some time.
He'll choose Jae Seok next week.
I haven't decided yet.
- Why not? - Really?
- You haven't decided? - Is it 9 against 1?
Many people stressed me out today.
They gave me a hard time.
I was slapped...
about eight times today.
(There are many whom he wants to take.)
There are so many.
Someone added my name twice.
Someone wished me bad luck at first.
- As soon as we started, right? - Right.
- Haha was terrible. - Seok Jin was mean too.
- Jae Seok as well. - Seok Jin was mean.
Seok Jin is always on my mind.
- That's not what he means. - What?
Seok Jin is always on his mind.
Is that how you interpret that?
Thank you, Kwang Soo. I understand.
Please say a few words, and we'll finish here.
- I'm jealous of you. - Let's hurry.
- The shoot is getting long. - Australia sounds nice.
You won't be jet-lagged there.
Let's hurry and go home.
- Did you say hurry up? - Yes.
Do you want to pick me? Go ahead.
- Choose him. - Go ahead.
- Pick Jong Kook. - Go ahead.
Pick me.
- You can choose me. I'm fine. - We'll switch places.
Pick him.
Let's have a good time in Australia.
Is that another penalty?
Let me think it over for one week.
Just one week.
I'll hold myself back today.
- Listen. - I'll hold myself back.
Let's hurry up.
(Do you remember 2 months ago?)
(So Min was selected for the final penalty during I Go Race.)
(Her destination is...)
(Indonesia's manual, wooden cable car.)
(Unfortunately, Kwang Soo is selected as her partner.)
(They finally go to Indonesia.)
(They're welcomed by many fans upon arrival.)
(However, the penalty wasn't forgiving.)
(Despite the terrible weather,)
(Kwang Soo and So Min get on the cable car.)
(The force of nature is uncontrollable.)
(The two members get penalized.)
(Their long journey starts now.)
I want to go back to Korea!
(Incheon International Airport on September 3 at 8am)
(A somber, black vehicle arrives.)
(Laughing)
Hello.
- Here's your microphone. - Okay.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
This is fun.
(He clenches his teeth.)
(He can't believe it the more he thinks about it.)
Am I dreaming?
The time and atmosphere...
(The time and atmosphere seem dreamy.)
What did I do wrong?
What did I do to deserve this?
(I haven't done anything wrong.)
It feels like a dream. What's going on?
You're going to Indonesia today...
in case you thought it was Australia.
(Goodness)
Why would I be mistaken?
We also have to go to Australia.
What's wrong with you?
I haven't done anything wrong.
How many places do I have to go?
My schedule next month is full of penalties.
(The same goes for his cameraman.)
(Another vehicle arrives.)
Hello.
(So Min arrives.)
Hi, So Min.
(She doesn't hear him.)
She must be in a terrible mood.
(He tries his best to stay calm.)
She is closing the door.
Hey.
For goodness' sake.
So Min closed the door.
All right. Thank you.
(She unloads the luggage as if nothing happened.)
Hello.
Ouch. Thank you.
- Hello. - Why do you have so much luggage?
One is for clothes.
Did you fit everything in one suitcase?
Yes, my suitcase is very heavy. Try lifting it.
- What's inside? - Clothes.
- You only brought one suitcase. - Yes.
Why do you have so much? Will you have a fashion show?
I won't have a fashion show.
I brought clothes and personal belongings.
I see that you don't have much experience with penalties.
That's understandable. I was like that at one time.
What do I need?
- There are many things you need. - Don't you only need clothes?
To be honest, I can't open my eyes.
Kwang Soo and I talked on the phone at 4am.
- Both of us stayed up. - I couldn't sleep.
I couldn't sleep.
I still can't believe this is happening.
Am I going? Am I really going?
Not even the worst criminal would receive such punishment.
Kwang Soo and So Min, you will go on a penalty tour...
for People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent.
You will go on Indonesia's manual, wooden cable car.
(They must go on a cable car that is made with wood and ropes.)
(Depending on the power of men makes you fear the nature.)
Why must I go with someone?
- What do you mean by that? - Why must I go with Kwang Soo?
- What are you talking about? - Look.
(Suddenly)
Do you remember this?
(The bracelet looks familiar.)
(3 months ago, on their way to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear)
(A cute bracelet caught So Min's attention.)
(Kwang Soo, please buy it for me.)
(Don't speak nonsense.)
(I guess I won't buy it.)
(So Min couldn't buy the bracelet since she didn't have enough money.)
(Handing over)
- Is it a present? - Kwang Soo.
(So Min was touched, and Kwang Soo was embarrassed.)
(Kwang Soo was cold outside but warm inside.)
(He acted like a big brother with a 10-dollar bracelet.)
- That's right. - I wore it. You remember, right?
You still have it.
Of course, I do. I wore it often during the summer.
Isn't it pretty?
It looks good.
(It looks good on your wrist.)
Remember these moments.
We prepared a special tour...
for the moths of Running Man, Kwang Soo and So Min.
It's called Indonesia's Tiger Moth Tour.
Tiger Moth Tour?
What kind of a name is that?
I have a question. Aren't we only receiving a penalty?
No, you aren't.
- Is there more? - It's Tiger Moth Tour.
- Just us two? - Yes.
For this tour,
the travel expenses are important.
Isn't this the main shoot for Running Man?
Where is everyone? Why are we by ourselves?
One of us will receive a penalty,
- right? - Is there another penalty?
(What are you talking about?)
Listen.
- You will... - Why are you attacking me?
I am here thanks to you.
I am grabbing you by the collar in Jae Seok's place.
What is this?
I don't know what is going on.
The travel expenses are expensive.
You can't use the money you brought with you.
For the two of you who are going on a penalty tour,
the six members sent you allowances.
That's incredible.
They are amazing.
For the three days of Tiger Moth Tour,
you can only use the allowances from the members.
The person who has more money upon arriving in Korea...
will receive an advantage during the next race.
- An advantage? - There is an advantage.
- Of course, there is an advantage. - Excuse me.
Is the next race similar to this one?
- All projects are over. - There will be another one.
- Will there be another one? - There will be another project.
Will we have more things like I Go Stickers?
You should tell us in advance.
Will there be more word plays?
If that's the case, I need to clear my schedule in advance.
Be quiet.
Stop it. Stop it.
You will now have a mission for the travel expenses...
called Money Sixth Sense.
Inside the six envelopes are allowances...
- ranging from zero... - Is there one with zero amount of money?
to 200 dollars.
Each one of you will choose three envelopes.
The amount of money inside them is your travel expense.
Aren't we a team?
- He and I should be friends. - Is this a competition?
(His eyes change.)
Must I compete against him again?
- The travel expenses... - Will one of us ride the cable car?
- are very important. - Will one of us ride the cable car?
It will be decided by the travel expenses.
Don't touch them.
(This is a competition.)
- I chose the envelopes. - No, this is ridiculous.
(Don't touch them.)
No, this is ridiculous.
- Hurry up, and give them to me. - Ji Hyo, Jae Seok, and Jong Kook.
The decision is final if you touch the envelopes.
- The decision is final. - Don't be ridiculous.
I am sorry.
- The decision is final. - Give them to me.
I am sorry. The decision is final.
You don't know how much money is inside.
- This is ridiculous. - I am sorry.
(Hitting)
That's not my stomach. What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
What is wrong with you?
My legs are long. Be careful.
(I can't spend 3 days with someone like him.)
What is wrong with you?
This is wrong. You can't do this to me.
Your envelopes might have more money.
No, they won't.
I know they won't. There is Seok Jin's envelope.
- There is nothing I can do. - Give me Ji Hyo's or Jong Kook's.
You must do that much.
(Which one should I give her?)
(What is Kwang Soo's choice?)
(He gives her Ji Hyo's envelope...)
(and receives Seok Jin's envelope.)
(Kwang Soo gets envelopes from Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and Seok Jin.)
(So Min gets envelopes from Haha, Ji Hyo, and Se Chan.)
Please reveal the amount.
Do we reveal the amount?
It doesn't matter.
It's a gift card for meat.
Haha is cool.
- It's from Haha, right? - It's not money.
(Wait a minute. It's not money.)
It's a gift card I can only use at a restaurant.
You can only use it at a restaurant.
(You can only use it at a restaurant in Hongdae.)
Is he picking a fight?
We asked him how much he would give if he were to give an allowance.
This was his answer.
- This is a competition, right? - Yes, it is.
The more money you have, the better it is.
- That's right. - This is...
- You can eat meat later. - My throat feels tight.
- I can't use it in Indonesia. - Of course not.
You can only use it at Hongdae.
(She checks the allowance from Ji Hyo.)
- Whose is it? - There is a lot of money.
My goodness, Ji Hyo.
There is a lot of money. She is the best.
She is cool.
50 dollars. Ji Hyo gave 50 dollars.
You should give me 20 dollars.
Don't be ridiculous. I bet Jong Kook gave 50 dollars.
Ji Hyo wanted you to remain confident abroad.
(I don't want them to be discouraged abroad.)
(She checks the allowance from Se Chan.)
What is this?
(My goodness.)
Which one is real money?
(Se Chan gave 200 dollars in game money.)
- Real money is real money. - What?
- Real money is real money. - This one doesn't count.
What is this?
(I am disappointed in Se Chan.)
Se Chan said that he will give 200 dollars...
in game money.
(Se Chan, how dare you?)
Yang Se Chan...
I will check Seok Jin's envelope.
You never know what Seok Jin will do.
He is a big spender.
- Seok Jin. - There is a lot of money.
There is a lot of money.
(It's a surprising 50 dollars.)
- Did he give 100 dollars? - 50 dollars.
That's the same amount as mine.
What about Jong Kook? You are so mean.
How could you let him keep the envelopes of his choice?
What a jerk!
(What a jerk!)
Whose is it?
Jong Kook's envelope is empty.
- He has issues. - Is it empty?
- It's empty. There is nothing. - Is it really empty?
- It's empty, right? - He said he won't give any money.
Thank goodness. How much did Jae Seok give?
(He feels betrayed.)
I got goosebumps from seeing the empty envelope.
- The last one is from Jae Seok. - Let's see.
- Jae Seok doesn't joke around. - No, he doesn't.
(There are 50 dollars inside the envelope.)
Give me 10 dollars.
You didn't pay back my four dollars.
Pay back with real money.
I have real money.
- Come on. - It's in my suitcase.
Give me four dollars.
Pay me back right now.
- You need to pay me back. - Wait a minute.
- She is like a moneylender. - Of course, I am.
I borrowed game money,
but she wants me to pay back with real money.
Do you think it makes sense?
Is this Blue Marble?
(Is game money real money?)
Give me 10 dollars.
- You really want that much. - Yes.
Your credit has been restored.
I will lend you more money. Ask me if you need money.
I have money.
Thank you.
- Take six dollars. - Thank you.
We will now leave for Indonesia.
(This is fun.)
This is fun. Smile.
- Shall we jump and teleport? - Let's do it.
- Never mind. - Let's do it this once.
- Shall we jump? - Yes.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Let's jump.)
(Sighing)
(Indonesia's Tiger Moth Tour begins.)
We are really going.
(My goodness.)
I can't believe this is happening.
Am I going to Indonesia or Australia?
There are so many people.
They must be going to Indonesia to receive a penalty.
What are you talking about? Come to your senses.
You should wash your face in the airplane.
(They are tired.)
(They are each other's penalty.)
(The 10-hour flight begins.)
(They take a 7-hour flight to Jakarta...)
(and an hour and 20 minutes flight to Yogyakarta.)
(September 3, 10pm, Adisutjipto International Airport)
(A cheerful country with various kinds of people)
(Indonesia has its unique taste and color.)
(What's this noise at the airport?)
(People are gathered to see him.)
(They welcome the Asian Prince.)
(Hello)
(They're excited to see Kwang Soo.)
(That's right.)
(Kwang Soo is the Prince of Asia.)
(He becomes all nice and friendly.)
(He's always teased by the members,)
(but in fact, he's popular all around the world.)
(They welcome the betrayer couple.)
It was true after all.
(It's shocking for So Min.)
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is so popular.
It's not something that we can witness in Korea.
Look at his unusual smile.
(They're grateful for the welcome.)
It still doesn't feel real.
(But they're here for the penalty.)
Why did you...
keep falling asleep?
- What? - It hurts.
I bumped my head.
(He's getting tired.)
Why did you keep falling asleep while I was talking?
(Asking a question again)
It's not that I fell asleep while you were talking.
You just kept on talking.
(Upset)
There's a timing for everything.
But you never stopped talking. What am I supposed to do?
I couldn't sleep either.
(We're on the same boat.)
You ate gimbap yesterday.
I'm going to sleep. I need to save my energy.
And you ate it again this morning.
- Do you like gimbap? - For breakfast?
Do you want to bet on who can read more?
The books, I mean.
How about we play this game?
We'll open a book randomly and find names.
All right, let's play.
The one who wins twice first will win.
- Find what? - The page with more people on it.
How many more games do we need to play?
- This is the last one. - I want to stop.
This will be our last game.
We've begun already.
I got a nosebleed while I was washing my face.
(Please cut me some slack.)
(Kwang Soo received an additional penalty while flying.)
This will be the last one.
I looked at you after talking, and you were asleep.
My ears bled when you fell asleep.
(Please stop.)
(The bus heads to the accommodation.)
It feels strange since it's just the two of us.
It feels empty, right?
- It kind of does. - Right.
We're really here.
We're here at last.
(They're a step closer to the penalty.)
I didn't know I'd actually come here.
(However, the trip hasn't even begun for real yet.)