- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - This place is really pretty.
- It was in "The Beauty Inside". - That's right.
It's the same cafe.
The owner of the cafe has my respect.
- Big respect. - Respect, respect.
So Min, you cut your bangs.
I cut my bangs to make myself look refresh without cutting my hair short.
- Why did you refresh yourself? - Did someone dump you?
- Did something happen? - Did someone break your heart?
- You and your boyfriend broke up. - No.
- You and your boyfriend broke up. - She is looking for another lover.
Ji Hyo, you never change your hairstyle.
- I don't have a change of heart. - I know.
- I always remain the same. - Seriously.
- You are amazing. - Ji Hyo is really like that.
- I always remain the same. - Ji Hyo remains calm...
while those around her suffer because of her.
Those around her suffer because of her.
- She is fine. - No matter what happens,
- she remains unaffected. - That's right.
- She is cool. - She remains unaffected.
- She is a strong woman. - She is incredible.
- Respect. - Big respect.
(Respect for a strong woman)
Se Chan, your face is very swollen today.
(By the way...)
(Why is his face puffy?)
I'm not swollen, I gained weight.
(He is stressed out.)
Both Se Chan and I binge eat these days.
- New Zealand changed us. - I eat my stress away.
- I can't stop thinking about it. - You look better.
My face is rounder, right?
Your mouth doesn't look as protruded.
I realized something during last week's shoot.
The members have a lot of moles on their necks.
- That's right. - They have moles on their necks.
- That's right. - I have a mole right here.
Haha, Jong Kook, and Jae Seok have them.
- Seok Jin, you don't have any. - No, I don't.
- You have a wart instead. - Doesn't he have a mole?
- What are you talking about? - You have a wart.
- A wart? - I don't have a wart.
- Don't grandpas get warts? - Don't say that.
You can get warts at any age.
Anyone can get warts.
- Scary grandpas get them. - The two of you are attacking me.
- I see a wart! - Get your hand off of me.
Don't cut in when we are talking.
(So Min and Seok Jin show off their chemistry from the start.)
For goodness' sake.
Thank you for working hard on various projects.
(Thank you for working hard on various projects.)
- It was nothing. - Why is he using such a warm tone?
- Seriously. - We must be done with the projects.
Only a few members worked hard.
That's right.
I gave Seok Jin the nickname of Sinsa-dong Mudfish.
- He slips away from penalties. - That's right.
- He is incredible. - Last week,
I did an amazing job of slipping away.
He's so good at it.
To soothe your tired body and mind with a fall vacation,
we prepared "Running Man, Do Whatever You Want".
(Running Man's fall vacation, Do Whatever You Want)
We are getting a vacation.
- Do Whatever You Want. - We are finally getting a prize.
Before you go,
please write down the vacation you recommend...
to the person to your left.
Jong Kook should have sat to your left.
Where do you want to send me?
Gosh, this is upsetting.
Let's recommend good places to each other.
- Let's write down what we want. - Okay.
One bad place will ruin everything.
- It will be a dog fight. - This isn't a penalty.
You are right. This is a vacation.
Kwang Soo, don't joke around with this.
I know what you've always wanted to do.
(Don't worry.)
This is for Seok Jin.
"From Seok Jin".
Sinsa-dong Mudfish.
(What does So Min want to do?)
I could have written down your nickname.
- Which one? - Anyang Hothead.
- Anyang Hothead. - Anyang Hothead?
Anyang Hothead.
Sinsa-dong Mudfish and Anyang Hothead.
Anyang Hothead. You must think it suits you.
Jong Kook likes his new nickname.
This is perfect for you.
- My goodness. - It's tailored to your needs.
- Really? - Yes.
- I don't want to do anything. - You don't want to do anything.
- No. - You will get your wish.
- My goodness. - That's right.
You won't do anything.
Wait a minute.
Keep writing without looking in my direction.
(Urgent)
- You look a bit like Han Hyo Joo. - Who?
(My goodness, he says I look like Han Hyo Joo.)
Thank you.
Jae Seok, why are you being annoying in the morning?
When she was looking down, she looked a bit like Han Hyo Joo.
- How annoying! - Don't spoil her.
(Anyang Hothead chimes in.)
- Seriously. - Don't say such a thing.
From this side, her eye is this big due to a sty.
(He reveals that she has a sty.)
Why won't it go away?
Do you have a sty? Gosh, I shook her hand earlier.
Why did you say that? Don't tell people.
That's right.
Kwang Soo recently hosted Kim Ki Bang's wedding.
- An acquaintance of mine was there. - Okay.
- How did Kwang Soo do? - I heard you did a terrible job.
I heard it was very boring.
It was my first time to get booed for hosting a wedding.
- How is that possible? - From afar,
I couldn't hear what the guests were saying, but they did this.
(That's wrong.)
- They did this. - Seriously.
You have no right to talk about hosting a wedding.
- Why do you say that? - At my sister's wedding,
you said my father's name instead of the groom's name.
(Seok Jin's father almost walked down the aisle twice.)
He said my father's name.
Why did you do that?
- Did you finish writing? - Yes.
Hand the envelope to the person to your left.
Here you go.
- It contains my sincerity. - I will see what you wrote.
It's something you like.
- Really? - Really.
- I can trust you, right? - Of course you can.
- You don't have to do anything. - Don't open it yet.
Please take turns to talk about with which thoughts...
- you recommended the plan. - Shall we do that?
- Let's start with Cunning Yang. - Shall I go first?
- Shall we start with Cunning Yang? - Cunning Yang.
- It's from Kwang Soo, right? - Yes, it is.
"Dear Se Chan. Se Chan, it's me, Kwang Soo."
"I am having many thoughts."
"What could be a vacation of your dreams?"
"I suddenly remembered..."
Why did you write a letter?
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
This is why you were terrible with hosting the wedding.
- For goodness' sake. - Why would you bring that up?
You shouldn't have made these unnecessary comments.
(Where is the actual recommendation?)
- Seriously. - This is excessive.
"I suddenly remembered something you always wanted to try."
- We still didn't get to the point. - This is ridiculous.
- For goodness' sake. - What is this?
It's waxing.
(What?)
(Waxing?)
What?
(Am I hearing things?)
Waxing!
"Satiate your curiosity and gain confidence..."
- "with waxing." - Waxing!
Isn't this a penalty?
Se Chan has talked about it.
He was curious about waxing.
How much hair do you want me to remove?
(There are different types of waxing.)
- What? - Everything?
Where do you want him to be waxed?
Are you referring to the Brazilian waxing?
- Come on. - Hey.
- Okay. Say that I got the waxing. - Well, I'm not the one getting it.
To whom should I show my waxed body?
Do I have to get naked in front of you and show you my body?
- That's right. - How could you feel shy about that?
(He's disappointed.)
- It's too much. Why would I get it? - Waxing?
- I wrote a good one compared to it. - Hey, this vacation is...
- You should've written a good one. - This is a penalty, not a vacation.
No, hear me out. Se Chan really talked about getting a waxing.
- Kwang Soo is so weird. - What's gotten into him?
- He's gotten strange. - Are you doing this on purpose...
- because Jong Kook likes me? - Why are you doing this?
That's right, you jerk.
(That's right, you jerk.)
So watch your back.
- But still, Kwang Soo. - Be grateful it was just waxing.
He got it in for me.
I was going to write shaving your head.
Anyway, since he wrote it, you must carry it out.
Whether it's your leg or some other part, you must do it.
- That's right. - Right.
But seriously, what is his deal with me?
(The first vacation spot gives them the chills.)
Gosh, Kwang Soo can be so scary.
- Compared to this, mine is great. - Kwang Soo...
I'll read what Se Chan wrote for me.
"To my hero, Haha."
"I think you've been stressed out lately because of Nevis Swing."
"Since you have to get on the ride as the penalty,"
"I hoped that you would familiarize yourself with the word, 'swing'."
- He's in trouble. He's doomed. - Poor Haha.
"Go to a dancing studio and learn how to swing dance."
I mean it, Haha.
- This is... - You have to get on that ride.
- I want you to get used to it. - Really?
You know swing dance?
- He can learn how to jive or rumba. - That's too harsh.
- Swing dance... - Actually, Haha and I learned...
- them on a show back in the days. - I learned the cha-cha dance.
- You'll be fine. - You have a knack for dancing.
- Get comfortable with it. - He must be cool to look good.
You'll look cool.
Goodness, what a bad move.
- So it just rhymed with "swing". - Right.
- It rhymes with Nevis Swing. - But that was witty, Se Chan.
- It was, wasn't it? - Yes, it was.
- Thank you. - Sure.
You like everything he says, don't you?
Well, waxing was good too.
What about Ji Hyo's?
Well, mine is...
Ji Hyo likes sleeping.
- My gosh. - She likes it.
- I guess it's a good one. - "To Ji Hyo, my neighbor."
"It seems like you can never get enough sleep."
"This place is perfect for you to take a long nap."
- "Go to a sleeping cafe." - Seriously? She's going to sleep?
- Haha really wrote that. - "Sleep tight and rest."
- That's such a great one. - Can she really do that though?
- It's good for her, - This week,
- but what about the show? - she won't get any air time.
- Do you not want her on the show? - Really?
- Is that what you want? - I'll be on the show for a second.
No. Imagine how funny it'd be if you were to have sleep paralysis.
But I never get sleep paralysis.
(This will be enough for your air time.)
- You just look silly like that. - He can write that?
- Goodness, this is... - But he really...
thought about Ji Hyo.
- You should sleep talk. - That's right.
- You're tired today. It's perfect. - That sounds like fun.
- Shall I read mine? - Yes.
- Isn't that a good one? - It is.
Ji Hyo wrote this, right?
- I did. - What is it?
Hold on. Gosh.
- What is it? - I bet it's ramyeon.
- Does he have to eat ramyeon? - No.
- If I were to write his... - I was serious about this.
- I wrote this for you. - That's a long letter.
Jong Kook, read it.
"Kim Jong Kook".
- My letter isn't affectionate. - Goodness.
She just wrote, "Kim Jong Kook".
- I like that. - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - Was she challenging him?
- "Kim Jong Kook". - But...
I like how plain it sounds. She just wrote his name.
- That's right. - I hate those endearments.
"To Jong Kook, the health promoter".
"I want you to eat sweet potatoes as they are in season now."
That's nice.
- You like sweet potatoes. - "Go to a sweet potato farm."
(Go to a sweet potato farm.)
"Dig sweet potatoes yourself."
- He likes healthy food. - That's right.
- You can work out while digging. - Hey, she's right.
- Get some fresh air. - I hate things like this.
You know what I mean?
I hate doing small stuff.
- I rather do something big. - Like trivial tasks?
- Hey. - Like trivial tasks?
- I really hate doing those. - When you grab the stem...
- I'll read what Jong Kook wrote. - Learning to swing dance is good.
"To Jae Seok. You love eating noodles."
- He does. - "Jae Seok."
- I was really thoughtful. - "You especially like ramyeon."
Go to a ramyeon buffet and eat as much ramyeon as you want.
"Let's get it!" I love this.
- There's a ramyeon buffet? - You want me to eat ramyeon?
- This place actually exists? - There's such place?
- This is it. This is a good one. - Jong Kook gave me a good one.
- I knew he likes eating noodles. - Thank you.
(This is how he takes care of Jae Seok.)
This is amazing.
I really want to visit that buffet.
- I'm really curious about it too. - I want to go there too.
Jong Kook is being so nice to Jae Seok.
Then I'll change mine to the ramyeon buffet too.
No, leave it.
(When have you ever seen me eating ramyeon?)
- It's time to read mine now. - I'm sure you'll like what I wrote.
- Jae Seok wrote it for you. - Jae Seok annoys me.
- I'm sure you'll like it. - I wonder what he wrote.
"To Seok Jin, Sinsa-dong Mudfish".
"Fishing..."
- You want me to go fishing? - Yes.
- I hate fishing. - What's wrong with him?
- I know that he hates fishing. - Hey.
There are tons of fish at Noryangjin Market.
- You should go fishing. - As soon as I heard it,
- I started yawning. - "Go fishing. Catch fresh seafood."
- "Cook seafood ramyeon." - That's right.
And this is his favorite part.
This is the best part of it.
"Lie down as you look up to the sky and hum."
It's a description of a mad man.
- Hey. - "Look up the sky"?
- Are you in your right mind? - This is what I'm talking about.
- He likes lying down. - That's true.
When he lies down, he starts humming.
(It's a personalized vacation for him.)
- Who knows? Kwang Soo... - All right.
I gave her a good one. Right before the shoot, she told me...
that she didn't want to do anything.
- Hey, read yours. - Shall we hear yours?
"To So Min".
"So Min, you always talk and chat like a parrot relentlessly."
- That sounds affectionate. - "I bet it's hard to always talk."
"So I found the perfect vacation for you to relax."
- This sounds caring. - "It's temple stay."
- That's nice. - Temple stay.
"Get yourself sorted out there."
- "Try the practice of silence." - She can go to the temple.
- That would be so hard for her. - "And declutter..."
- "your mind." - That will be so frustrating.
The letter just sounds caring,
but in the end, he told her to be quiet.
(The letter sounds caring, but in the end, he told her to be quiet.)
I guess two of our female members will be very quiet.
- That's right. - One of them will be sleeping.
- So Min wrote this letter. - I can't wait to hear this one.
"To Kwang Soo".
"Kwang Soo, you're working hard."
"I heard prawns are in season now."
He's going to catch prawns.
- You're making him catch prawns. - "I saw..."
"I saw that you really enjoyed eating shrimps in Indonesia."
"People are picking pen shells in the mudflat near the West Sea."
"Pick a lot of pen shells."
"And prawns and their shells are great for your joints."
"I hope you can enjoy your vacation as you eat the heads too."
- You have to eat the heads too. - What is he doing?
We'll get to see the mudflat. It's been a while.
He has to pick prawns.
She wants me to go to the mudflat and pick pen shells?
When you sprinkle the salt, they come up. You can pick them then.
Anyway, he can do that. I'm glad mine is great.
- Everyone will be on their own? - Will we be by ourselves?
- Put recommended vacation spots... - This is great.
back into the envelopes and hand over them to me.
You're not going to mix these letters, right?
I've never gotten such a good one.
I just got the chills.
- Se Chan. - Am I right?
- Why? - No way. They wouldn't do that.
- What is it? - What is it?
- They might mix those. - Can I eat temple food there?
- We might pick one of those? - But...
- what if Jong Kook... - If we do pick one...
What if Jong Kook picks the one with ramyeon buffet?
- That's feasible. - I really want to eat...
- ramyeon. - That's right.
If I do choose the ramyeon buffet, I'm doomed.
- This is good. Let's go! - It's a penalty for him.
Ramyeon buffet.
Now, I will...
tell you the rules of Do Whatever You Want, the fall vacation...
- for our Running Man's members. - What is it?
There are eight vacation spots that you recommended for each other.
(There are 8 vacation spots that you recommended for each other.)
Those are the vacation spots that all of you will...
- enjoy together. - I knew it.
- Didn't I tell you? - It was for the member next to me.
You said it was for the member sitting next to me.
Among these 8 vacation spots, you will draw 5 randomly.
(They will draw 5 vacation spots randomly.)
- This is crazy. - We're in trouble.
- What if we get the waxing? - Waxing? You little...
- Kwang Soo. - I didn't know we all would get it.
I don't like learning how to swing dance too.
You will have only eight hours to finish them.
(They only have 8 hours for their vacation.)
Within the given time, you can enjoy...
your vacation with the budget of 1,000 dollars.
- 1,000 dollars? - The sleeping cafe will be great.
That'd be awesome. We can eat everything there.
However, if you fail to enjoy five of your vacations in time...
or if you fail to spend all of the budget,
you must come up with 1,000 dollars and return the money to us.
(If they fail, they must return 1,000 dollars to the crew.)
We have to use up the money.
1,000 dollars won't be hard.
We have chance cards that will help you maximize your experience.
- What are those? - Please discuss among yourselves.
- And use them at critical moments. - We have chance cards?
We have the dividing card.
- Dividing card? - What is that?
8 of you can split into 2, and go to 2 vacation spots simultaneously.
(They can go to 2 vacation spots at once.)
We also have the deleting card.
- That's nice. - This is the best one.
And another one is the recommendation card.
You can call your acquaintance and change the vacation spot.
(Recommendation card)
And you have the dud card.
(They won't get anything from it.)
We'll get nothing from that.
- Choose one. - Okay. I'll get us a good one.
(Kwang Soo will choose the first vacation spot.)
Kwang Soo's choosing.
(Waxing, swing dance, sleeping cafe, picking sweet potatoes,)
(ramyeon buffet, temple stay, fishing, and catching shrimps)
- We never know... - I chose the middle one.
I rather go fishing.
Look at his face. Goodness.
- I guess it's a bad one. - What is it?
- I knew you'd pick a bad one. - Is it waxing?
Is it really waxing?
- What is it? - What is it?
Sweet potatoes...
(It's picking sweet potatoes.)
Sweet potatoes.
Goodness, what's wrong with that guy?
We have to pick them from the field.
- Se Chan, choose one. - Can I?
You picked the sweet potatoes.
- The five vacation spots... - Get the sleeping cafe or buffet.
- Just don't get the waxing. - Don't pick the waxing.
(Please let's just make sure we don't get waxing.)
- Hey, what is it? - Make sure it's not waxing.
You can't choose waxing.
(As he sighs, he sinks his head.)
(What is the vacation spot Se Chan has chosen?)
I'm sorry. My name is on this letter.
- What is it? - Is it the swing dance?
No, it's waxing.
(His name implies that they have a chance to get waxing.)
(We have to get our hair waxed together?)
Seriously?
- All of us have to do it. - How could you pick that one?
How could you pick that one? And why did you write that?
I don't have any hair to shave.
Let's use the chance for the waxing.
I have the perfect amount of hair right now.
(The one who recommended waxing committed the biggest crime.)
Exactly.
Once you start waxing, you have to get it regularly.
- What's the third one? - Let's use the chance card.
It's not that...
Why did you do that?
What is it?
(Did Ji Hyo pick a bad vacation spot too?)
- Ji Hyo, what is it? - Ji Hyo.
- It's Haha's. - I'm sorry, Haha.
- Is it the swing dance? - It's the swing dance.
(It's the swing dance.)
- This episode won't be any fun. - Goodness.
Jong Kook.
- Goodness. - I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
Let me pick one myself.
We've picked the worst options so far.
- Exactly. - We have the worst ones.
- Gosh. - It's the fourth choice.
Waxing is too much.
- I'll make sure to pick ramyeon. - Okay.
- Please. - Ramyeon.
- Please. - We need at least one good place.
(He reacts loudly after checking his choice.)
- What is it? - Is it ramyeon?
It's ramyeon buffet!
(Jae Seok chose the ramyeon buffet.)
- Yes! - Nice.
- Respect. - Good job.
- It's your turn now. - Respect!
- We respect Jae Seok. - Respect.
Let's go have some ramyeon.
- He's Superman. - I chose ramyeon.
- Thank goodness I picked this. - Goodness.
- It's like the oasis in a desert. - But Jong Kook doesn't like it.
What else do we have left? She shouldn't pick prawn fishing.
- It's vow of silence, right? - Are we going to ride a boat?
- What is it? - What should we do?
- What is it? - So it's prawn fishing.
(What's their last vacation spot?)
It's Sinsa-dong Mudfish, fishing.
(She has picked fishing.)
- How are we supposed to... - It's fishing?
- It's fishing? - Yes.
Do we have to have ramyeon again?
- You wrote that. - We have ramyeon buffet too.
- Let's go have some ramyeon first. - Good.
Please decide the order first before you start your vacation.
- Let's eat first. - Ramyeon.
Let's make waxing the last to do.
Let's use the chance card to get rid of it later.
- Let's get rid of it from the list. - Put the strange ones at the back.
That waxing is the worst to be honest.
- Right. - Why did you write that?
Let's go to the sweet potato farm first.
- Good idea. - All right.
Let's do a physical activity first and go to fill ourselves.
- Then the fishing. - Let's go fishing after.
Let's cross out swing dance and waxing from the list later on.
- We'll go pick sweet potatoes. - Right.
I'll search if there's any sweet potato farm in Incheon.
We'll help you find available places if you can't.
- Will there be any? - It should be located around here.
There's a farm that provides picking experiences for people.
- A sweet potato farm in Incheon. - I found one too.
- Where is it located? - It should be somewhere near here.
They aren't answering. Hello?
- Hello? - Is it the sweet potato farm?
- Yes. - Are you open today?
- From 1pm today. - From 1pm?
- Can we pick sweet potatoes? - It's too late.
- We should change schedule then. - Yes.
- We'll call you later. - Thank you.
- We have to use the GPS. - Bye.
But this place is open from 1pm. What time is it now?
- It's 10am. - That's...
- It's too late then. - We need to go right now.
And the sun will be high up in the sky around 1pm.
- It'll be hot. - It'll be extremely hot.
- We might get sunstroke. - It's better in the morning.
- I'll try calling them. - Try it.
Kwang Soo, try it.
(He tries calling another farm.)
You won't be able to host the wedding. Are you okay with that?
What?
- Can you tell them? - Sure.
The music.
The music is nice.
(She starts dancing.)
It goes well with the farm.
Goodness.
(They're impossible.)
Hello?
- Is this the sweet potato farm? - Yes.
- Are you open today? - Yes.
- From what time? - Ask him if we can go now.
From what time are you open?
We're open from the morning.
Can we go right now?
Ask him if it's okay to shoot there.
- Tell him we're Running Man. - Is it okay...
Hello, I'm Lee Kwang Soo of Running Man.
(The owner stays silent.)
It seems like he doesn't know who Kwang Soo is.
I don't think he knows you.
Hold on. I'll let you talk to the famous person.
Kwang Soo, you better work harder.
Hello, sir. I'm Yu Jae Seok of Running Man.
Oh, hello.
- See? He responded differently. - It's different.
- He recognized Jae Seok right away. - Goodness.
We're filming the show at the moment,
and we have to find a farm in which we can pick sweet potatoes.
Can we go with our filming crew?
Yes, of course.
Goodness, thank you. We'll head there right now then.
- Okay, call me when you're here. - Okay.
Thank you.
Good.
- We respect him. - He said okay right away.
- Respect. - Goodness.
- Respect! - Respect.
(Should I go pick sweet potatoes in Indonesia?)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Get it. - Let's get it.
- We'll pick sweet potatoes, right? - Yes.
Let's get it.
- I'm so excited to have ramyeon. - Me too.
I didn't know there was a buffet for ramyeon.
I might have ramyeon in a long time.
- Really? - Jong Kook.
I'll put chicken breast in your ramyeon.
(Will it be healthy food then?)
So Min, I'd love that.
(They're excited to be on their relaxing vacation.)
Join in.
(We're on our vacation today.)
By the way, waxing is too...
Kwang Soo wrote that.
(Who recommended waxing?)
That's too much.
Right. Or go do it alone.
We can use the chance card later.
- Get your body waxed. - Or we have to go together.
- What? - Goodness.
We have to spend all 1,000 dollars.
Shouldn't we buy a huge sack to put in sweet potatoes then?
- Right. - We should pick a lot of them.
We have to pick a lot of them.
I'm so curious to know by the way.
Why is this a relaxing vacation?
(He comes to wonder suddenly.)
- What is? - This.
Why is this a vacation?
I just don't get why she wrote that for me.
What do you mean? I wrote it for you.
Sweet potatoes...
I did a good job in writing fishing.
Hey, it takes much time to catch fish.
It's only a waste of time.
- I'm a master of fishing. - What are you talking about?
Don't lie, Jae Seok.
I'm like a fisherman.
They call me a fisherman in the field.
When we went to fishing, everyone caught fish except for you.
(3 years ago)
(The members caught big fish here and there.)
(Reeling)
(He failed to catch fish alone.)
(Jae Seok was the only one who couldn't catch anything.)
When will I get to catch something?
I'll show you this time.
I'll show you what fishing is.
- Shall we bring it on today? - Goodness.
I'll show you the difference between an amateur and an expert.
If you fail to catch at least one, you will get somewhere waxed.
- Deal? - Goodness.
Then it'll become a penalty. Let's go first and talk later.
Why are you stepping back?
- Are you not confident? - Why are you getting upset?
Goodness, get off.
This isn't your car.
- I'm driving, so get off. - This isn't your car.
It's not my car, but I'm driving this car, so get off.
Let him off at the crossroad over there.
- Right. - Drop him off there.
Take a taxi and come to the farm.
(They're on their way to the farm.)
We're here.
It feels like there's the sweet potato farm somewhere around here.
- We're here. - Goodness.
Here it is.
Let's pick sweet potatoes, and leave here quickly.
Let's pick them quickly, and get some ramyeon.
Let's not waste time here.
I've never picked sweet potatoes before.
(Try our delicious sweet potatoes.)
It's the first course of your vacation.
It's what Ji Hyo recommends to Jong Kook.
(The first course is the sweet potato farm.)
Before you start enjoying your vacation, there's one announcement.
Please come in.
- What? - What's coming in?
Perhaps, we have to choose tools.
- No way. - No way.
(They're getting suspicious.)
Gosh, it's a roulette again.
It's a roulette.
- Is it a roulette again? - What is it?
(They have a bad feeling about this.)
- What is this? - "Company credit card".
- What is this? - We might have to pay for this.
- We might have to pay for this. - Goodness.
You told us to use the 1,000 dollars. What is this now?
(What is this suspicious roulette for?)
All right, guys.
You have to use up 1,000 dollars throughout the five courses.
The roulette is fairly divided by your names and the company card.
After you finish enjoying each course, you'll spin the roulette,
and the chosen person will pay for the expenses.
(They'll spin the roulette to decide whom will pay for each course.)
- I mean... - What is this?
I thought we were going to have a relaxing vacation.
Isn't this a vacation?
If you don't wish to spin the roulette,
- do you see the box over there? - Yes.
It's the golden bell box.
(Golden bell box)
Until you fill this sack with sweet potatoes,
vote for one member whom you want to pay for the course.
(They'll write a member's name in secret and put it in the box.)
- In secret? - Any kind of paper is fine.
Write someone's name on a piece of paper and put it in the box.
That person will pay for the course.
If there are several pieces of paper inside the box...
That's why I was given a pen.
If it's one person, will that person pay for the course?
That's right. If there are several papers,
we'll draw one among them.
Let's just go for the company card.
- Right, let's hold hands. - The company card.
Right? Let's not write names.
Why are you trying to write a name already?
I just want to ask a question.
Is it okay to write a name on here?
- Don't do this. - Let's not write names.
Let's go for the company card.
Let's spin the roulette.
We'll leave the roulette and the box here.
Enjoy picking sweet potatoes.
(They shouldn't vote for anyone if they want to use the company card.)
- Let's go pick sweet potatoes. - Right.
We're going to the ramyeon buffet, so we shouldn't waste time here.
- Right. - Okay.
Let's go.
- Where do we get the tools? - We should eat ramyeon.
So Min.
- Goodness. - What are you doing?
It's nothing.
You guys are too much.
(Who will get to pay for the first course?)
- We're running out of time. - That's right.
We don't have much time.
Where should I dig? Here?
All right, guys. Look here.
You guys...
haven't picked sweet potatoes before, right?
Have you?
I'm experienced with everything.
I'm the master of fishing and picking sweet potatoes.
About 10 years ago from now...
Stop talking nonsense and just pick sweet potatoes.
Well...
Ji Hyo!
- There are so many here. - Where?
It's nice here.
(They have found a place with a lot of sweet potatoes.)
Se Chan, you're no joke.
Ji Hyo.
Check this out. It's long just like Kwang Soo.
- Come on. - It looks like Kwang Soo.
I don't look like that.
You look exactly like this.
Check this out. It's like Seok Jin.
It's like Seok Jin.
(Ta-da. Doesn't it look like Seok Jin?)
What? How does that look like me?
It sort of does.
Look over here.
(Their friendship grows through the experience.)
Hey.
Gosh, look at this.
It's easy to dig them out.
We're doing very well.
- This is great. - Isn't it?
- There's a lot. - Dig here, Se Chan.
I'll do it.
(He volunteers to help.)
I've done everything.
- Dig over here. - We're doing very well.
(The sweet potato expert shows off.)
- You're so good at shoveling. - I know.
Jae Seok is good at shoveling.
I've done it for 10 years.
(His talent is shoveling.)
(He conquers all the sweet potato fields.)
- There are no sweet potatoes. - Why not?
There aren't any over here.
- There aren't any. - Dig over here.
There aren't any where Jae Seok is digging.
- I found some. - Where?
(Is the expert finally showing off his skills?)
(Screaming in joy)
(That's tiny.)
It's so small.
(On the contrary, he finds a small sweet potato.)
What's that, Jae Seok?
I let them go because they're too small.
(It's not worth it.)
(The others find big ones.)
- I got lucky. - Goodness.
- They're here. It's so small. - I know.
Look how small it is,
but they found big ones.
It's this small.
(Look how small it is.)
They're so small.
Am I responsible for that?
No, but they found big ones over there.
(He gets discouraged.)
Why can't I find any here?
- It's strange. - There aren't any.
These are so small.
Goodness.
Guys, look at these. Jae Seok's are so tiny.
So Min, be careful what you say.
Be careful what you say.
The sweet potatoes that Jae Seok found...
(Make yourself clear.)
So Min, what are you saying?
Jae Seok's are so tiny.
So Min!
Are you out of your mind?
(Speak accurately.)
Hey.
- These are big. - I feel so proud.
There are only big ones.
Let me see.
(Why are they so small over here?)
Why are the sweet potatoes so tiny?
Look at this.
Isn't it cute?
Gosh, this is big.
- Good ones are over here. - Right.
Big ones are over here.
I'm quite experienced with digging sweet potatoes.
I'll show you my expertise in fishing.
I found more.
I want to go somewhere.
(Jae Seok dreams of traveling.)
Based on what Ji Hyo wrote,
you must steam the sweet potatoes.
Steaming them takes 20 minutes. 1 of you should take some.
I'll take them now.
- I'll do it. - I will.
- I will. - No, I will.
I'll do it since I'm the youngest.
- No, I should do it. - I will.
As a sweet potato veteran, I'll take them.
- I'll do it. - Do you have mythomania?
Why do you say that you're good at everything?
- Let's go. - This should be enough.
- Let's go together. This is enough. - Okay, let's go.
- We'll be back. - See you soon.
While I shovel,
- What are you doing? - someone should pick them.
I'll pick them.
Let's dig out big ones.
(He struggles for 10 minutes.)
- Seriously. - So Min, can you help me?
Gosh, look at these.
Hey, look how big they are.
Look over here.
So Min.
Didn't you ask me to pull it up?
I've been struggling to...
- take it off. - You asked to pull it up...
because you like it.
(It looks like a diaper.)
My goodness.
Gosh, I'm getting angry.
How does he find good ones?
Ji Hyo, look at this.
- Gosh. - That's huge.
(It's big like Jong Kook.)
Look at them.
There's another one here.
It's a great exercise.
That's right, Jong Kook.
(He finishes picking sweet potatoes.)
Sweet potatoes are being steamed on the other side.
You may go and eat them.
Are they done?
- Shall we open it? - It's been 20 minutes.
- I can smell them. - They look delicious.
Let's see.
(They look big and delicious.)
- These look amazing. - They look delicious.
- They're cooked. - They'd be good with milk.
- Shall we eat them? - They're ready to eat.
(He splits it open.)
- It's a pumpkin sweet potato. - It's golden.
- Take a bite. - It's golden.
- What color is it? - Be careful.
Gosh, look at this.
- How is it? - It's so good.
It's not necessary to peel it.
You can push out the inside.
- It's very sweet. - Now is the perfect time to eat.
- It's delicious. - They'll still be good tomorrow.
- Be careful of your hand. - We'll give you kimchi.
(Even its complementary dish kimchi is served.)
Let's get it, let's get it.
- Why are you being nice to us? - Get it.
Look. Put it on top.
That's exactly what I'm doing.
I know what to do.
That's right.
Crunchy cucumber field?
- Gosh. - I've never done this before.
Ji Hyo, this was a great idea.
It's therapeutic indeed.
Isn't it great?
- You deserve respect, Ji Hyo. - A lot of respect.
(Enjoy sweet potato picking this autumn.)
The drinks you have here cost a dollar each.
That's a good price.
The total cost is 106 dollars.
Running Man members deserve it.
It's 50 dollars' worth of sweet potatoes.
Let's spend more.
- Come on. - We have enough.
What about our crew members?
(Let's spend a lot.)
- Really? - My goodness.
(He suddenly cares about the crew members.)
Here's a drink for each of you.
It's because it's not his money.
Does anyone want some Coke?
Take it.
He's acting like he's never met them before.
It's okay as long as I don't pay.
(He hopes he doesn't get picked.)
(It's time to determine how they'll pay.)
If there are no names inside the box,
- Do we spin the roulette? - you'll spin the roulette.
If there is a name in the box, that person will pay.
Here we go.
Here I go.
Let's not put anyone's name in it.
- Let's trust each other. - Pay with the company card.
Right?
Here I go.
(There's something inside.)
It won't be necessary to carry that heavy roulette today.
I think a war is about to break.
It's a sweet potato.
Is there a name on it?
"Yu Jae Seok".
(The first candidate is Jae Seok.)
Whoever wrote it should be ashamed.
What is it?
What did you write?
Does it look like Yu Jae Seok?
Does it?
We have to write it.
- This is done. - Take it off.
All right.
Whoever wrote it should be ashamed.
Gosh, it's written on a sweet potato.
"Beloved Kim Jong Kook".
(The second candidate is Jong Kook.)
It's the same handwriting as the letter to Jong Kook.
- What? Let me see it. - What?
It's the same handwriting.
Was it Ji Hyo?
It must be Ji Hyo.
He'll know it's me if I refer to him as an older man.
(She erases it.)
I'd like Jong Kook to pay since I recommended this place.
(Ji Hyo targets Jong Kook.)
(Were you the one who wrote my name, Ji Hyo?)
Okay.
- "Lee Kwang Soo". - "Lee Kwang Soo".
Me?
- "Kim Jong Kook". - It's a variety of people.
"Yu Jae Seok".
He's picked twice.
"Jeon So Min".
There's So Min?
Yes. Next is "Lee Kwang Soo".
Is it me again?
- That's right. - Why is it me?
Is there one more?
- It's "Yu Jae Seok". - All right.
Jae Seok has the most votes.
- Luckily, I'm not a candidate. - He's popular.
- Kwang Soo got 2 votes. - 2 votes.
I have 3 votes. Jong Kook has 2 votes.
So Min has one vote.
How many people put a name in the box?
Eight people.
- Did everyone write? - Everyone did.
I didn't write any.
(Jong Kook says that he didn't write any.)
It's not that. I'm sorry.
- I thought I could write two names. - Who did you write?
(Whose name did you write?)
- Do I have to tell you? - I didn't write any.
(Why is she looking at me?)
There are two leaves.
Shall I say whom I want to exclude?
Whose names did you write?
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo.
How dare you?
- Did you write these? - So Min.
- I didn't write them. - So Min.
- Those aren't mine. - Did you write these?
I'll take out the stone.
(She takes out Kwang Soo's name.)
- Okay. - Look, I have three votes.
- I have 3 votes. - I only have 1 vote.
3 votes for Jae Seok, 2 votes for Jong Kook.
- Gosh, So Min. - 1 vote for So Min and Kwang Soo.
Okay.
The person with the most votes should pick.
It'd be funny if you pick yourself.
- No. - You only get one chance.
- You get one chance. - Really?
Pick one right away.
You might pick your own name.
(Jae Seok has the highest probability.)
(Who will pay for the costs at the sweet potato farm?)
Here's the name.
One.
(The total cost is 106 dollars.)
2, 3.
(Who will pay the vacation costs?)
It's Kim Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook must pay.)
(He didn't get chosen.)
Why are you doing this to me?
Jong Kook said that the members deserve it.
- Right. - Thank you for the food.
Thank you, Jong Kook.
- You're welcome. - Thank you.
All of us recognize this face.
He's going to start getting angry.
- Come on. - Anyang Hothead is coming soon.
Anyang Hothead.
(Before Jong Kook gets angry, sweet potato digging is finished.)
Let's do a chance card lottery.
Ji Hyo, you pick one.
You should do it.
Just pick one.
I hope we can divide into two groups.
Is it a dud?
- It's a dividing card! - It's a dividing card!
- A dividing card. - Unbelievable.
Respect.
Big respect.
One team will go fishing, and the other will take a dance class.
My goodness.
We'll leave the rest to chance.
It'll be chosen randomly.
All right.
I bet Kwang Soo will be taking a swing dance class.
Two, three.
(Swing dance, fishing, swing dance, fishing)
Let me see.
Kwang Soo will be taking a swing dance class.
Ji Hyo is taking a swing dance class.
- I'm a bad dancer. - It'll be so cringe worthy.
(They move to the second spot, expecting hardships.)
(Team Fishing, Team Swing Dance)
75 dollars is a lot.
Is that how much it usually costs?
Dance classes are expensive.
I see.
Let's go for company card.
- That sounds good. - Promise me.
- Company card. - We have no choice.
Promise me.
Put your hand here. Otherwise, you're not with us.
Let's shout, "Swing, swing, swing."
- Start. Swing, swing, swing. - Swing, swing, swing.
Okay.
- What's with your expression? - What?
(What's that face?)
Why were you smiling? Your eyes...
I'm not supposed to smile on a variety show?
- I can't believe this. - We're here to relax.
- Today's theme is relaxing. - I give up.
- Stop it. - I give up.
We have to go for company card.
(Will Team Swing Dance be all right?)
We have to pay 400 dollars.
Not everyone has to catch one.
No.
As soon as we catch one,
- we'll make ramyeon. - We'll make ramyeon with it.
Wink at that car.
- Why? - It's a beat-up car.
Gosh, she's making us wink at a beat-up car again.
I already winked.
I winked without realizing.
Why do you wink?
- It brings good luck. - It does?
We'll catch big fish today.
Really?
- We'll catch huge ones. - I winked too.
- Did you wink? - I did.
I have a good feeling.
(Team Fishing is feeling positive.)
- It's so blue. Look at the sea. - Look at that.
It's the ocean. The sea!
- Look at that. - Look at that.
- This place is great. - It's nice here.
- I didn't think it'd be this nice. - It's so nice.
- So Min, it's nice, right? - Yes, it is.
- I'll teach you how to fish. - It's so nice.
Hold on, captain!
- Hello. - Where are you?
- I'm here. - Hello.
- It looks so luxurious. - Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for welcoming us on a holiday.
- Nice to meet you. - Hello.
- How much do we have to pay? - How much do we have to pay?
It's my own boat.
So...
just pay me about 200 dollars for the fuel.
Thank you.
It's too cheap.
It's a holiday today.
- Be quiet. - We'll pay 300 dollars.
(That's not necessary.)
- Think about it. - Let's do that.
We can pay with the company card.
(Right, we can pay with the company card.)
Let us pay just 200 dollars.
200 dollars? That's just for the fuel.
We should pay him for his time too.
He's working on a holiday.
- Let's pay 300 dollars. - We should pay 300 dollars.
- We'll pay 300 dollars. - Sure.
Thank you.
He asked us for 200 dollars.
- He needs some profits. - He's right.
Don't write any names.
Of course. We'll pay with the company card.
Let's pay with the company card.
- Don't write any names. - We should pay him a bit more.
Let's do it that way.
It's nice. There's some shade too.
- It's nice. - Jae Seok.
- Show us. - Stop rolling your eyes, So Min.
(Will they spin the roulette?)
It's nice.
It's not so hard to catch webfoot octopuses.
I've caught some before.
I tried it five years ago.
- Webfoot octopuses? - You could catch one right away.
- I almost felt bad. - Hey.
If you're after webfoot octopuses, get on another boat.
This boat is for catching tuna.
- How is this a tuna boat? - What are you saying?
- It's for webfoot octopuses. - Look at my arms.
They're too nice for webfoot octopuses.
If you want tuna, Jong Kook can catch them with his fists.
(If you want tuna, Jong Kook can catch them with his fists.)
By the way,
I'll put this here.
(The box gets on board too.)
- We don't need it. - We don't need it.
(You didn't hear? We don't need it.)
- We're not going to use it. - Put it away.
We decided to be nice.
Let's stay this way to the end.
If you write someone's name now,
you're a jerk.
- Of course. - Let me tell you.
- After what you said... - Of course.
I won't forgive you.
- I don't think he will. - Seriously.
I already start to feel sick.
- No way. - Are you nervous?
(The boat departs.)
Look at the sea!
(They have been exhausted from all the missions and penalties.)
(The beautiful waves are relieving all their stress.)
(This is therapeutic.)
The sun on the waves looks beautiful.
It looks so beautiful.
Saving it in my heart.
I'll do Se Ho's version.
(Saving it in my eyes)
(Se Ho's version shocked everyone.)
What's with him?
Saving it in my eyes.
(Saving the view in my eyes)
(You guys look so happy.)
Stop it.
What is Jong Kook doing?
I'm getting all wet.
Me too.
- Look at this. - The water is spraying everywhere.
Come sit here.
The waves are so strong.
(Therapeutic, my foot.)
It's cold.
(They're getting sprayed by the waves.)
The waves are so strong.
(We're getting all wet.)
- It's cold. - I feel like I'm back in Indonesia.
(Memories of the Tiger Moth Tour)
(It looks as if they're being penalized.)
You're so wet.
I'm soaked.
Wherever I go, it's never easy.
This is not what I was expecting.
I didn't expect this.
(I didn't know it'd be so tough.)
Help!
So Min, stay seated.
- Help! - Goodness.
The sea is angry.
I can't...
- stay here any longer. - My pants are all wet.
We can't shoot in this situation.
Can we really shoot?
Sir, help!
Help!
Sir!
We'll have webfoot octopuses next time.
(We'll just buy some.)
We're here.
We finally made it.
It's time to fish.
- You've tried this before, right? - Yes.
- If somethings bites it... - Do we put it into the water?
- Can we start? - Yes.
Can we put it into the water now?
It has to touch the bottom.
The bait is so nice. I'm sure we'll catch some.
- We'll catch something. - Good luck.
We'll definitely catch something.
We have to.
Let's do it.
- Let's catch something. - Who will catch one first?
I want to beat you guys.
She wants to beat us.
If I can beat Jong Kook, I'll win.
(You wish.)
Let's try to catch fluke.
I'm a fluke expert.
That's absurd.
Gosh.
He denies everything I say.
(He denies everything I say.)
Just go to a sashimi place and eat some fluke.
You're fishing at a nice place thanks to me.
Be quite and be grateful.
Just eat some seafood ramyeon later.
(The fishing king says to thank him.)
(I'll see how many you catch.)
Okay.
Let me show you.
(Sea fishing starts.)
(Did something bite Seok Jin's bait?)
All I'm getting is seaweed.
(He was fooled by seaweed.)
They're not interested in the shrimp.
(Time is ticking away.)
Take a bite.
I said, "Take a bite."
(It's unbelievable quiet,)
(and there isn't a single webfoot octopus in sight.)
It's so quiet.
The water is so calm.
Be confident.
We'll catch something.
I'm sure we will.
I'll show you guys.
(Which of the two will break the calm?)
Reel it in.
Sir!
(So Min calls the captain hurriedly.)
(Nothing has happened to Jae Seok and Jong Kook's baits yet.)
Something ate the bait and left.
You should have reeled the line in when something nibbled at the bait.
(It ate just the body of the shrimp.)
It just left the head of the shrimp.
- It must have been a fluke. - It must have been a fluke.
- Really? - You should have caught it.
- What a shame. - I didn't feel anything.
- It's a shame. - You didn't notice.
- It's very subtle. - So Min...
is getting hooked on fishing.
I'm a fishing queen.
(I'm a fishing queen.)
It's fun.
- Fishing is fun. - It gets more and more fun.
Jae Seok is being so quiet.
Just wait and see.
He was so...
He was so confident.
Stop it. That's enough.
(I will show you soon.)
- He talked big. - Seriously.
(So Min's fishing rod bends again while the other members quarrel.)
(This is real!)
(Is the novice fisher, So Min fated to catch fish?)
For goodness' sake.
It swam away when I felt the bite and reeled in.
(The head of shrimp is gone this time.)
- It ate the head this time. - It ate cleanly.
That's too bad.
How did it eat the head?
(Don't people usually feel the bite if fish finishes the bait?)
Did it eat the shrimp again?
(Did it eat the shrimp again?)
This is driving me crazy. When did this happen?
I didn't feel anything.
So Min, you became well-known among the flukes.
I am like the owner of a restaurant.
You are known as someone who gives food for free.
(It's like a soup kitchen.)
I don't even feel a nibble.
Why won't fish eat my bait?
(Their baits are untouched.)
It lures the fish, but...
It's similar to my life.
Even though I can lure men, I can't make any one of them mine.
(Even though I can lure men, I can't make any one of them mine.)
(Not many men bite the bait even though I gave them so much.)
(My life is similar to fishing.)
(How is Team Swing Dance doing while So Min looks back on herself?)
(They arrive at the dance academy with the acclaimed instructors.)
They are dancing.
- Is this the right place? - Yes, it is.
They are the instructors.
That's swing dance.
- That's right. - Is that it?
It looks cool.
- Let's go. - Let's take our shoes off.
It looks difficult.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's nice to meet you. - Who spoke to us on the phone?
- I did. - You did. Hello.
- What brings you here? - We are here...
- to learn swing dance. - Swing dance.
What you did just now is swing dance, right?
Yes, I'm dancing it right now.
You need two people for it.
Have you heard of Nevis Swing?
Stop it.
We only have an experience with Nevis Swing.
That's why we are here.
We came here to get over Nevis Swing.
(They enter the world of swing dance.)
(The instructors give a swing dance performance.)
(Their facial expressions and steps make the onlookers dance.)
(They have the perfect teamwork.)
(They are so cool.)
There she goes.
(They are surprised by the endless difficult dance moves.)
(The passionate swing dance is bound to burn Running Man's vacation.)
Please stop.
(Is this what swing dance is like?)
- Please stop. - Is that how it normally goes?
- This is the easy version. - This is the easy one?
- Yes, it is. - We don't know anything about it.
I will do the man's part.
- I will do the man's part. - Me too.
(They show off their manliness.)
Everything that is related to swing is scary.
We need to partner up.
Since there are three men, someone must do the woman's part.
Please pick one of us.
- Should he do the woman's part? - Me?
(As soon as they finish asking,)
(she chooses Kwang Soo.)
- Should I do the woman's part? - Your face is the prettiest.
Really?
(If I do the woman's part, I must do this...)
(and that, right?)
(Why is it me?)
He has long hair.
His hair is as long as mine. He can wear a hair piece.
There is a hair piece.
(Now, he is Kwang Ja, not Kwang Soo.)
(The instructors finally reveal the dance routine they will learn.)
(Relaxed)
(Clumsy)
(Claps)
(The cheerful swing steps add to the swing rhythm.)
How do they do that?
(Even though it looks easy, they can only follow clumsily.)
(Lifting)
(They pull off difficult dance moves with a smile on.)
(Welcome to the world of swing dance.)
Bravo!
- It was cool. - Bravo!
Respect, respect.
(Swing dance deserves big respect.)
This isn't the dance routine we will learn, right?
- It is. - It is.
Would you please take out a few dance moves?
We don't know if we will be able to learn it.
- The basic steps will be enough. - That's right.
Your talent, skills, and facial expressions...
- will take care of everything. - Our bodies won't follow.
We need to learn the basic rules of swing dance.
We heard the lesson is 70 dollars per hour.
We should reach an agreement on the price.
We need to bargain.
- Let's bargain for the price. - 75 dollars per hour.
It's 75 dollars per hour for each person.
- 75 dollars. - Yes.
How about we agree on 300 dollars for everyone?
It's for an hour.
We dress casually for the lesson...
because it's a popular dance in the US.
Kwang Soo, I will do it for you.
It looks funny if it's at the front. Let's put it on the side.
Kwang Soo, it looks good on you.
- How pretty! - You look like a gypsy woman.
Look.
Doesn't he look beautiful?
You remind me a bit of Sol Bi.
(Surprised)
- Why would you bring up Sol Bi? - You remind me a bit of Sol Bi.
You remind me a bit of Sol Bi.
Kwang Soo, it looks good on you.
(Se Chan is wearing an item for men.)
(Laughing)
I feel like we are in "Rustic Period".
We are like the thugs in "Rustic Period".
- The two of you... - We are like the thugs.
- Breaking news! - That's right.
- Breaking news! - That's how it goes.
What does that make you?
(What does that make you?)
(A wild woman)
- Sol Bi. - Sol Bi.
- Stop it. - Seriously.
He isn't Sol Bi.
Isn't he a shaman?
Why don't you wear a wrap instead of a skirt?
- It's nice. - It's nice.
Would you please make your voice more feminine?
- We need to concentrate. - Kwang Ja.
We won't be able to learn anything.
(They divide into groups and begin training.)
(He teaches the steps one by one.)
(He gives them a lesson according to their capabilities.)
Backwards.
(Haha and Se Chan are doing pretty well.)
Good. Good job.
(You are doing a good job.)
Please go slowly.
Let's go.
(They keep missing the steps.)
That was incredible.
(She is in a daze.)
(These two are struggling with the basic steps.)
(They always show the same dance moves.)
(Ji Hyo and Kwang Soo have a dance they used for the past 7 years.)
Let's try this by ourselves.
- In 1, 2, 3, 4. - In 1, 2, 3, 4.
Wrong steps.
We forgot everything without her.
- I will move to the front. - Please show us again.
In 5, 6, 7, 8.
(The women need a lot of instructions.)
Good job.
(They are improving slowly.)
(I am starting to get it.)
(They train with passion.)
Stretch out your legs.
I'm exhausted.
You are exhausted, right? Let's take a short break.
No, I don't want to stop.
Go.
Please show me one more time.
- Kwang Soo, are you okay? - I'm okay.
Please don't stop me.
(No one can stop me.)
(She's praising him.)
(She praises Kwang Soo to stop him,)
(but his steps only get faster.)
- Is it good? - Yes, it's good.
Please teach us the next move.
- Shall we move on? - Yes.
Let's have one couple stand here, and the other one stand here.
- Now. - Stand here.
- Please take good care of me. - Please take good care of me.
A man and a woman, the leader and follower...
face each other.
Then cross while facing each other.
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(They have a good teamwork.)
- 5, 6, 7, 8. - 5, 6, 7, 8.
Return to your place.
Which foot goes first?
I'm sorry,
but my partner looks angry.
I'm not angry, but focused.
- He won't even look at me. - I'm focusing hard.
I'm very focused.
- I'm taking this seriously. - Since this is a partner dance,
you need to depend on and trust each other.
-You also need to have love... - Friendship.
- for one another. - You need an eye contact.
- An eye contact. - Let's go, Ji Hyo.
- I love you, Se Chan. - I love you, Ji Hyo.
- That's what it means to dance. - Let's love each other.
Love and cherish each other.
The facial expression is important.
(I love you.)
That's great.
(They are full of love.)
All right. Let's move on.
Let's try what we learned earlier.
I can't stop myself.
You look like you are in a good mood.
It's the feeling of swing dance.
- Good. - This part is for women.
The move where you turn your hips is called swivel.
We will walk forward as we swivel.
(Swivel adds beauty to the swing rhythm.)
It's something you are good at.
Do this quickly.
2, 3, 4, 5, 6. Women will go around men.
- What are you doing? - Did you lose your mind?
- Did you lose your mind? - Did I do it wrong?
- You look scary. - This is swing dance.
You are doing well.
- It was nice. - Kwang Soo is very scary.
Women need to turn fast in the count of eight.
- Fast? - Yes.
- Circle the man. - I need quick steps.
We used to go like this. 1, 2, 3, 4.
(They must move faster.)
6, 7, 8. That's right.
You are doing well.
That's good.
- Go faster. - That's good.
(I'm faster and more unique compared to the others.)
You are very fast.
May we remove the flower?
- He looks like a crazy person. - He is crazy for dance.
That flower makes him look like a crazy person.
You are doing well even though it's a bit scary.
- Let's try again. - Stand behind him.
(Short and Tall Couple continues to smile.)
- 5, 6, 7, 8. - Start to move forward.
Next.
- This is great. - The next movement is...
- It's Haha's favorite. - I did it a long time ago.
- It's too difficult for now. - Just do it.
(Do you mean this?)
He can do it.
Kwang Soo, it's for men.
It's the male dancer's part. It's not for women.
It's for male dancers.
Yours is moving the pelvis.
- Can I do it too? - No.
- It's almost the last part. - It's the highlight.
The male dancer lifts the female.
This is how you do it. The female dancer must jump.
- You must jump. - As she jumps,
go down and up like this.
(The man's strength and the woman's jumping are the key.)
- The man supports. In 5, 6, 7, 8. - In 5, 6, 7, 8.
- Step, down, up, down. - That's right.
- You did well. - Good job.
- We can do it. - Was it okay?
I'm too heavy.
- You're light. - You aren't heavy at all.
- You're very light. - May we try it?
(Can you take a look at us?)
We're confident.
- Okay. - I practiced a lot too.
- Go ahead. - We'll give it a try.
1, 2, 3, 4. Back, step, down.
That was great.
- How was it good? - It wasn't.
You didn't see Kwang Soo's face.
- His face was strange. - Really?
Fix his facial expression.
Let me take a look at the facial expression.
- Facial expression? Okay. - Yes.
- Get ready. - 1, 2, 3, 4. Back, step, down.
(It's the wrong smile of a swing dancer.)
Good job. You're doing very well.
I bet they can try this move.
Please follow our move.
5, 6, 7, 8. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
(He adds a kick.)
- That's so easy. - 5, 6, 7.
(Do you mean a kick between my legs?)
- Watch us carefully. - Let's go.
Try it, Kwang Soo.
- Watch carefully. - All right.
- Haha, give him the count. - You can do it.
- Get ready, set. - Wait.
- I'm not a real woman. - Start with the count.
1, 2, 3, 4, back, step, down.
(How could you?)
You must hold him up.
I did.
- Haha. - He let me go.
After you put down your partner,
you'll choreograph the next part.
For example, you may finish in this pose.
- You can finish like this. - Or...
do this.
(Swinging)
- You may finish in this pose. - Can you do that?
Let's try that.
- Show us how you did the last part. - Be creative.
Put your leg around the partner's waist.
- Lift her up. - Here's how you move.
Turn her around.
Separate the legs while you jump.
Three.
It doesn't work.
(Come on!)
Haha wanted to kick him.
How dare you?
(They're not fighting. They're creating the last part.)
Practice on your own.
Let's practice one last time while watching the teacher.
Okay.
Cross and turn. Watch the arms.
2, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo dance well together.)
One more time.
(They're very focused that they're not speaking.)
Gosh, what are we doing?
Please let me go eat ramyeon.
Try harder.
What is this?
(What's this on my head?)
What are we doing?
(What do you mean? It's swing dance.)
(Their surprising swing dance performance is coming up soon.)
- We don't have much time. - We must hurry.
We can't stay here long.
Fishing is not about catching fish. It's about catching time.
(They haven't caught any fish for 1 hour.)
I didn't catch anything.
Bite, bite.
(They even get aggressive.)
Can anyone catch just one fish?
Let's try to catch at least one.
What happened? Come on, Jae Seok.
There aren't any fish, So Min.
(He has no idea what's going on.)
(Jong Kook's fishing rod moves.)
Didn't something get caught? Take a look.
(It's tight.)
- He caught something. - He did.
(Did Jong Kook catch something after an hour?)
What's going on?
(Will Jong Kook catch first?)
(Will Jong Kook fill the containers with fish?)
I caught it. I caught a webfoot octopus.
- Hurry up. - It's a webfoot octopus.
(Did he catch a webfoot octopus?)
He caught a webfoot octopus.
(Jong Kook catches a large webfoot octopus.)
It's a webfoot octopus.
(After 1 hour, they finally catch something.)
- He caught one. - I caught a webfoot octopus.
- Gosh. - May I touch the head?
Yes, take it off.
- Take it off. - Goodness.
Gosh, it's interesting.
You can eat it raw.
The webfoot octopus bit the bait. It's so cute.
I should have caught it.
You don't know anything about fishing.
Gosh, this is so frustrating. It's so annoying.
I bet the webfoot octopus that he caught is all we're catching today.
That's how I feel.
- It's a webfoot octopus. - I caught one.
I caught a webfoot octopus.
(They catch the second one.)
- It's big. - Goodness.
I almost lost it.
He caught another one.
- It's really big. - It's so big.
(This is what fishing is like.)
Fish recognize the bait of a professional fisherman.
- Goodness. - He insisted on fishing...
even though he's not good at it.
Is something wrong with my bait? Why can't I catch any?
I'm in a lonely fight.
I'm fighting against the sea, fishing, and the fish.
(It's a saying of the king of fishing.)
No fish falls for my bait.
(Jae Seok hasn't caught any.)
I felt something.
Is something wrong with my bait? Why can't I catch any?
(He's at risk of losing his title.)
(Will he recover his damaged reputation?)
Did you feel something?
(Something bites the bait.)
He got something.
(Those who looked down on me, just watch what I got.)
(He calls himself the king of fishing. Will he prove himself?)
The fishing rod got bent.
(He catches a tiny webfoot octopus.)
- Come on. - Okay.
- This is great. - It's a small webfoot octopus.
Okay, this is great.
Okay, nice.
(It's a small webfoot octopus.)
- Finally, - I'm going to catch one myself.
they're reacting to my professional fishing bait.
You caught such a small one.
Be quiet, So Min.
I'm on the fishing channel.
Did you catch it on camera?
(Yu Jae Seok, the webfoot octopus expert)
You missed such an important moment.
The smallest octopus in the container is Jae Seok's.
- It's the smallest. - It's a baby.
His sweet potatoes and webfoot octopus are small.
(Everything he gets is small.)
(Is Jae Seok's expertise in small things?)
He's Small Jae Seok.
(He gets a new nickname, "Small Jae Seok".)
My goodness.
(He gets a new nickname, "Small Jae Seok").
It'd be great if I catch one fluke.
(No one catches any fluke.)
What if the fish want us to stop fishing?
Stop fishing.
It's time for us to leave.
(They caught one webfoot octopus each.)
Wait a minute. I think I caught something.
(Wait a minute. I think I caught something.)
- It's fluke. - I caught something.
- He caught it. - What is it?
(He feels a different type of bite.)
I caught it.
- It's fluke. - What is it? It's not fluke.
What is it?
(What type of fish is it?)
- What is it? - It's flathead.
(Jong Kook catches huge flathead.)
It's flathead.
He caught something.
(He caught a great one.)
That's amazing.
- Jong Kook is amazing. - Jong Kook caught it.
How did you catch it?
I had a feeling that I got lucky.
Can we eat this fish, sir?
You can eat it raw, but it's perfect for stew.
Maybe not for ramyeon.
I just felt it.
- Its mouth... - Congratulations.
Why can't I catch anything like that?
(Jong Kook proved his class.)
We have enough webfoot octopuses to make ramyeon.
Something ate the shrimp and left.
This is the first thing I caught.
(A small webfoot octopus)
- I'm sorry. - Look at that.
It's interesting.
- Put them in one by one. - Okay.
Yes, like that.
I'm sorry, but...
- stop saying that at the back. - You're doing a good job.
Look at that soup.
They have so much ink.
It's webfoot octopus ink ramyeon.
The soup...
(This is the real vacation.)
This is making me eat a lot.
(Jae Seok puts a webfoot octopus in his mouth.)
- It tastes so good. - It tastes really good.
- It tastes fantastic. - With webfoot octopuses...
(Even Jong Kook enjoys ramyeon today.)
It tastes much better.
Dear ramyeon advertisers...
(This is my chance.)
(So Min is good at describing flavors.)
(She'll make people's mouths water.)
(Dear advertisers, what do you think of me?)
You look too ambitious. Stop it.
(They're trying to protect her.)
(Disappointed)
You should hum now.
(The last task is humming.)
Just me? Shouldn't everyone do it?
How do you hum?
(Humming)
Like this.
(I'm happy when you smile)
Isn't this humming?
That's just a nasal sound.
(I thought I was humming.)
- One song comes to my mind. - Which one?
("Meeting" by Noh Sa Yeon)
(Seok Jin likes it.)
(To get over it)
(It's too...)
Judging from the way she sings,
she must have been born before 1965.
(So Min sounds old.)
(They all start to sing together.)
(She hits the high notes.)
I love you
(They sing together despite the age gap.)
(Relaxing tour, I love you)
- Harmony. - What's with you?
I want to be good at singing.
(After accomplishing all tasks, they're back.)
Good work, everybody.
Thank you, Captain.
I'm so happy to finally land.
- It was exhausting. - I felt sick.
It wasn't easy.
(Jae Seok goes back onto the boat.)
I'm happy to land.
Give me some paper.
(While everyone is getting off the boat,)
(Jae Seok writes down a name.)
Here.
What are you doing?
- What? - What are you doing?
- I'm taking this thing off. - What?
(Whose name did he write?)
The total cost of your tour was...
- 300 dollars. - 300 dollars? Okay.
(They have to pay 300 dollars.)
If the box is empty, we'll turn the wheel.
I see my name.
(Unbelievable)
- Who did it? - Who did it?
(Seok Jin is a candidate.)
It's Jae Seok's handwriting.
I recognize his handwriting.
It's definitely his.
I can't believe this. Wait.
(There's something more in the box.)
Someone wrote a name on a towel.
A towel?
Oh, my.
(Jae Seok's name is written on a towel.)
Do you have a pen?
(While they were moving to the fishing spot...)
(While Jae Seok was hiding from the waves,)
(Seok Jin wrote his name on a towel.)
(He didn't see it, did he?)
- There's something more. - What's that?
- It's an oil control film. - Is there a name on it?
- There is. - It says, "Kim Jong Kook".
It's written clearly.
(While Jong Kook was covering his face...)
She's writing his name when he's covering his face.
(So Min is taking the chance.)
(So Min wrote Jong Kook's name.)
I can't believe you.
The whole time, I was...
I shouldn't have trusted you.
There are three balls.
So Min will pick one.
- So Min will pick one. - Yes.
Pull it out at once.
Just do it.
The one who gets chosen...
- will pay. - Should I pick this one?
I can spend this much for the members.
Pick Jae Seok.
Go after Sinsa-dong Mudfish.
Just pick one at once.
Who is it?
(Who did she pick?)
The total cost of your tour was...
300 dollars.
(The one who gets chosen has to pay 300 dollars.)
Who is it?
(Seok Jin will pay for the fishing.)
Really?
(Annoyed)
(Thank you for everything, Seok Jin.)
I'm so happy.
So Min, that little...
I should have written her name.
Something is being printed.
It's a receipt.
(Seok Jin pays 300 dollars.)
I recommended this activity for Seok Jin.
- He should pay. - Thank you for the good time.
(Team Fishing is finished.)
Let's do this.
- Is it our turn? - Do we go first?
Be confident and bright.
I'm getting nervous now.
We're more serious than ever.
This is not a competition.
We're here to enjoy ourselves.
(They learned swing dance for an hour.)
- Good! - Nice.
(Will they be able to pull it off?)
Play the music.
(The music starts.)
(They're getting into the rhythm.)
(They make an eye contact.)
(They're pulling off the steps perfectly.)
(She's back to her confident self.)
(Perfect teamwork)
(They're perfectly in sync.)
(They even look relaxed.)
(Ji Hyo is doing a great job.)
(They spent only an hour to prepare for this performance.)
(It's the most difficult part.)
(They perfectly manage it.)
(Ji Hyo has changed.)
They're so calm.
She is doing so well.
I'm exhausted.
(It's time to jump.)
(Jump)
(Freestyle dance of each team)
(The name of this dance is "Floundering in the sea of swing".)
(They finish it off nicely.)
(Bravo)
Great job.
- We did it! - It was perfect.
Nevis Swing.
Respect, respect.
(Respect)
Good teamwork.
As soon as the music started,
both of you looked like different people.
They changed at once.
- They're talented. - Totally.
I didn't expect such great teamwork.
- It was amazing. - You did a fantastic job.
Great teamwork.
It was definitely therapeutic.
We're taking a day off today.
All right. Next...
- You win. - Give it a try.
- Just try. - I don't remember a thing.
- They did it at one go. - Next team.
Let's welcome the next team.
Haha and...
- Kwang Soo. - Let's go.
Let's go.
Haha looks great.
Take a pose.
(Haha looks like a newsboy.)
Are you ready?
Let's get it.
(Let's get it.)
(Warming up)
(They look too excited.)
Are we paying with a company card?
Let's do that.
Swing.
- Swing, swing, swing. - Way to go!
(Their steps are energetic.)
(Their facial expressions are priceless.)
(Great teamwork between the tallest and the shortest)
(They're perfectly in sync.)
Nice facial expression.
(They're natural-born swing dancers.)
(The audience looks somewhat uncomfortable.)
Nice! Way to go!
(It's time to jump.)
Look at him.
(Success)
(How will they finish it off?)
(Shorty's freeze)
(Fantastic collaboration of swing dance and B-boying)
Respect!
(Haha and Kwang Soo's performance is finished.)
I want to cry for some reason.
Let's give them a big hand.
(Swing dance class for Haha is over.)
The amount of money you spent for this activity...
- is 320 dollars in total. - Okay.
(It was for registering for the class and buying props.)
Before we calculate the balance,
let's check the golden bell box.
We probably won't have anybody.
- Won't they spin the roulette? - We'll use the company card.
(If there's nobody, they'll use the company card.)
Let's use the company card.
(A few hours ago on their way to the swing dance class)
Let's say swing, swing.
(This team decides to use the company card.)
(In a moment)
Is she in a sleeping cafe? I thought we didn't pick that one.
I know, right?
(She makes her own sleeping cafe.)
Isn't this cheating?
She's not allowed to this.
She's in her own sleeping cafe. This doesn't make sense.
(They want to betray her.)
(They unite without Ji Hyo who's sleeping.)
(They decide to write Ji Hyo's name.)
Ji Hyo?
(They all vote for Ji Hyo.)
- There are names inside. - Please pick a name.
- Please call it out for us. - You can open it like this.
- You can pick whichever. - They are all in there.
- You can read all of them. - All of them.
(It's from me, Haha, and Se Chan.)
There are four names.
(Ji Hyo won't just watch. She betrays them as well.)
(They unite over their betrayal for each other.)
- Four? - We all put it in? When?
(Who will ring the golden bell?)
Lee Kwang Soo.
(Did Ji Hyo write my name?)
(It's him again.)
(He got two votes?)
Song Ji Hyo. It's all Song Ji Hyo.
I got two for Song Ji Hyo.
I got 2 for Lee Kwang Soo. It's 2 on 2.
- My goodness. - What happened?
- Who did that? - Somebody bent their promise.
Who did you write?
(Which of you is it?)
- Who is it? - Hold on.
- Ji Hyo, I wanted to stop. - Who is it?
That's not the problem right now.
It's 100 percent certain you wrote my name and I wrote yours.
This is obvious.
- I can't write my own name. - Right.
- That's right. - I'm getting goosebumps.
- It's either one of us. - Let's clean this up later.
Please pick one.
- Just 1? - Yes, you just need to pick 1.
If it's against Ji Hyo...
(Is it Kwang Soo or Ji Hyo?)
Make sure nobody sees it.
(What's that supposed to mean?)
I think this person has a connection with me.
- Who is it? - Who is it?
(Who will pay for everything?)
(It's Kwang Soo.)
It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo has to pay 320 dollars with his personal credit card.)
Ji Hyo got lucky again.
- Thanks. This was therapeutic. - I know. Thanks.
- Please turn on some music. - Thanks so much.
- Isn't this a party? - Let's go party.
Let's go.
(He dances as soon as the music comes on.)
(This is a party. Thanks, Kwang Soo!)
(Swing dance is scary, everybody.)
(The swing dance was therapeutic for their body and soul.)
(I'm happy as long as you are.)
(Kwang Soo pays 320 dollars, and the swing dance is over.)
Thank you, Kwang Soo.
- Thank you. - That was very therapeutic.
I paid for it, and it was great.
I know Ji Hyo wrote my name.
Who was the other one?
It's already over so there's no point talking.
- Wasn't it you? - It wasn't me.
(Trust me.)
- Did you write my name? - I didn't.
I guess I wrote my own name.
I think you're mistaken.
I guess I did.
When you were sleeping, Kwang Soo said to pick you.
- That's not it. - So...
- I thought we were doing that. - Look at you.
You are such a jerk.
Watch this on TV.
He wanted to make you pay 500 dollars.
Anyway, he wanted to make you pay.
- Gosh. - I'm serious.
He wanted to make you pay 500 dollars.
Haha, let's go for some ramyeon.
There's one nearby.
(He's searching for a ramyeon buffet.)
- Ramyeon... - Really?
(He tries calling them.)
- I hope... - How long would it take?
- Hello? - Hello.
Is this the ramyeon buffet?
- Yes, it is. - Are you open today?
- Yes, we are. - Really?
- Really? - I guess they're not closed.
This is Yang Se Chan from Running Man.
- Okay. Hello. - Hello.
Can the eight of us come and eat now?
Yes, it's possible.
Thank you. We'll be on our way.
- Yes, thank you. - Thank you.
I've never been to such place.
I'm going to make it good.
(He's planning to fill himself up with good ramyeon.)
(There's 1 hour and 30 minutes left until the mission is over.)
Is this the famous...
- Yes. - Have you been here?
- Is this a snack stand? - It's like a convenience store.
- Look at all the ramyeon. - I know.
- Amazing. - I didn't know this place existed.
There's tteokbokki too.
This is like a department store.
- Look. - You can pick your toppings.
This is perfect for me.
This is perfect for Jae Seok.
It's therapeutic for him.
- They have jjajang tteokbokki too. - They do.
- Do they have what I want? - I want this.
(They choose according to preference.)
Should I put in eggs now?
No, not yet. It has to boil first.
I didn't know this place existed.
- It's cool that you can make it. - Right?
Jong Kook, this is a great gift for me.
- This is awesome. - Right?
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you for the meal.
(They start gulping it down.)
(It finally seems like they're on vacation.)
(Jong Kook tries the first frozen tteokbokki of his life.)
This is like real tteokbokki.
I didn't know you'd eat this.
(He's eating fast food.)
That's great.
- Were you sitting here, Kwang Soo? - Go ahead.
(Spurting)
(She spurts spicy sauce towards Haha.)
Look what So Min did to me.
(Thanks, So Min.)
- Look what she did to me. - I'm sorry, Haha.
It's okay.
You are kind of scary.
Put it in.
I have to use the sauce. What do I do?
This is spicy, So Min.
I don't have the sauce.
Do you have scissors?
(She spurts the sauce and collects it back.)
(She swallows it without biting the noodles off.)
This is awesome.
(We bought quite a lot.)
(Who's going to pay here?)
Let's spin the roulette.
Let's do that.
We can stop people from getting near it.
I shouldn't do it. I'm not doing this.
(He reflects on himself.)
- What is it? - Somebody did it, right?
Do what?
(Do what?)
So Min did, right?
It doesn't even cost a lot. Let's spin the roulette.
(This is their chance to unite.)
We finished the cheese.
Can we have more cheese?
- Do you want that? - Yes, I do.
Where are you going, Kwang Soo?
(He got caught.)
I'm going to the bathroom.
- Kwang Soo - Where did you go?
- Kwang Soo. - Let's stop.
He's addicted.
It's a disease.
Everybody,
you used 78 dollars in total here.
We can't use it all.
- We can't use 200 dollars. - We give up.
- There are 192 dollars left. - We can't use it.
- We didn't use enough. - We have to do waxing.
We spent less than 10 dollars per person.
Let's open the golden bell box.
Did anyone put a name in it?
I didn't do it this time.
(They wanted to use the company card this time.)
Should we eat more of this?
So many people have participated.
Really?
- Really? - There are so many.
(Jae Seok went to the bathroom 20 minutes ago.)
Where's the bathroom?
(He recommends Seok Jin.)
(We were thinking the same.)
It's full.
I'll pay for these two.
(They've been doing this for 8 years.)
Don't you have the other kind?
(They don't trust each other.)
Oh, gosh.
We did this again?
I just hope I don't get picked.
There's Se Chan, Kwang Soo, and Haha.
- Who wants to pick? - I will.
- There are so many of Seok Jin. - I'll pick.
Can he practice?
- He can't. - No?
It's 50-50 chance.
I have 50 percent chance.
- I picked one. - The cost...
Show it.
(He already paid 300 dollars earlier and Kwang Soo paid a lot too.)
(Who will end up paying the most?)
(It's on me.)
Let's see.
(My gosh)
- Thank you, Seok Jin. - Thank you.
Why does this happen?
Where do we go for the last one?
Let's go for waxing.
Since Kwang Soo recommended it, he has to do it.
But is that the rule? He must do it?
Se Chan got recommended, so he has to do it too.
The person who suggested it has to do it.
Then we'll do it,
- and we'll pick one more person. - Sure.
How much money do we have left?
It's 192 dollars.
If it's 30 dollars each...
Should we look into it?
- You should look into it first. - That's important.
Call a place nearby.
We have to get the price right too.
We can figure it out when we get there.
(The waxing service has to be exactly 192 dollars.)
Yes, this is the waxing shop.
Hello, is this the waxing shop?
- Yes. - Are you open today?
- We are. - I see.
How are the prices like?
(How are the prices here?)
What parts are you getting it done?
Excuse me.
We need to spend 192 dollars.
I'm sorry. I know this is an odd situation.
We might need to film us waxing.
Are you getting the Brazilian waxing?
- No, no. - No, no.
(Do you want to get the Brazilian waxing?)
- No, no. - No.
I'm sorry.
Why would we get Brazilian and film it?
No.
It would be dangerous to film it.
- It has to be on TV. - Not that type of filming.
- It has to be appropriate. - This is SBS.
It's on TV.
If not Brazilian...
- Everything but that. - Legs or...
We can do any other part.
If we want to use 192 dollars, how many people should we have?
- It's all men. - It's for men.
You can get your legs done.
- Three people? - Legs?
Okay.
- I'll send you our address. - Okay, thank you.
- Thank you. - We can check it there.
(The waxing shop is their final stop.)
(Will they be able to succeed in their mission within 35 minutes?)
Men and women?
- Yes, it's for both. - Hello.
It's separate.
It's for three men. Does it hurt a lot?
Well, the pain is inevitable.
If it's 192 dollars, what parts are they doing it?
2 people on their legs and 1 person on a single leg.
(1 person will get a single leg done.)
No way.
We have to match the price.
- It's his first time. - The price doesn't work out.
Can we do this then? The person who will get one leg done...
- 1 of 3? - Yes, it'll be 1 out of 3 of you.
Can we get three changes of clothes?
- Sure. - You can come over here.
This is so painful. Every week is so bad.
Please. I can't get waxing done.
I think Seok Jin is a good candidate.
You have 30 minutes left.
We have to hurry.
Let's pick one.
We won't waste time.
When you all put down your heads, we'll throw this on top.
- I have to tell this to my wife. - Please hurry up.
I'll remember this.
(This person will join Kwang Soo and Se Chan.)
- Just a moment please. - Make up your mind.
Just a moment.
- Don't do that. You scared me. - Put your head down.
- Please put your head down. - Please.
I have to go somewhere with Dream.
Stop mumbling.
- Okay. - Please join us...
Please, sir.
Which member will join us?
We'll pick now. One.
Put your head down. Two.
(Who did Kwang Soo and Se Chan pick?)
Two.
(Seok Jin got picked.)
It worked.
It's not me.
Thank you. Thank you so much!
- Respect. - Respect.
Respect.
He wanted to do it.
- He wasn't even nervous. - He thinks it's obviously not him.
What do you mean? My heart was beating fast.
Should we do rock-paper-scissors?
Let's do rock-paper-scissors for one leg.
Do rock-paper-scissors and decide who it'll be.
Is it the loser or the winner?
The loser.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Se Chan wins.)
- Okay. - This is driving me nuts.
Thank you.
I won.
Do rock-paper-scissors. We have no time.
- There are 15 minutes left. - I don't want to do just 1 side.
I really don't want that.
We have 15 minutes. Hurry.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(This is between the two people who paid the most today.)
(Who will get one leg waxed and pay the fees?)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(It's Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin gets to have one leg waxed and pay the fees.)
(The Sinsa-dong Mudfish is completely ruined today.)
- This is... - This is how it feels like.
It's so nice. It'll be quick.
I guess people film here. I had no idea.
We only have 20 minutes left. Let's hurry.
- Let's hurry. - Hurry.
- We have no time. - Hug the stuffed animal.
What's this?
- Is it that bad? - It won't hurt that much.
There's a stuffed animal to hug?
- I don't want to do it. - I have no hair.
- It'll be very painful. - Is it really bad?
I think it will.
Kwang Soo, it'll be worst for you.
That must be painful. His hair looks like ivy.
They are tangled up.
That looks like a rifle.
(Are you ready?)
What's this?
He put it on. I'm done. I have to do it.
He's going to rip it now.
(He keeps on talking.)
This is driving me crazy. What did I do wrong?
That hurts already.
You have the most amount of hair.
Hold on, sir.
Hold on.
Are you doing it already? Sir.
(He starts without warning since they have no time.)
(Look at all that hair.)
Wait. Wait a minute.
(It's clean.)
(That really hurts.)
It really hurts.
I'm serious.
Does it really hurt?
(This is not the vacation I had in mind.)
(He wrote waxing this morning...)
(only to tease Se Chan.)
(You're lucky I stopped with waxing!)
(I was going to make you shave your head.)
(He thought only Se Chan would have to do it.)
(This is what he gets for his actions.)
(Look at his face.)
Get his hands.
- Does it hurt? - Please slow down.
Slow down.
(That was unexpected.)
Excuse me. How could you?
(They never had such rude customers.)
That hurts.
We only have five minutes.
If we don't finish, do we fail?
Flip over.
They have no mercy.
They really have no mercy.
That's how you are supposed to do it.
That's my flesh. You just pinched me.
No, it's not.
- I think it's my flesh. - My gosh.
Look. Kwang Soo's legs are so pretty.
His legs are really pretty.
I'm worried about Seok Jin. What is he going to do with the other leg?
You should pay now.
- Pay now. - We are in trouble.
(They are almost done waxing with 3 minutes left.)
Why did you write this down, Kwang Soo?
(He's losing it.)
You are done. I'll hold you, Se Chan.
It's clean.
Thank you for the good work.
Kwang Soo, look at your legs. They're so smooth.
Yours look better that way.
(It's much cleaner.)
It's clean. It's nice.
They turned like this?
(They were hairy men.)
(Now, they are hairless.)
You have successfully completed all the missions.
(Do Whatever You Want race is finally over.)
We are finally done.
- Good job - Good job
- Good work - Good work
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you for the food.
(Running Man members will run even harder next week.)
- Let's go. - Yes, sir.
(They are...)
You can't run a restaurant here. Where's your boss?
(They are united over their comedic skills.)
Are you here by yourself?
Who are you?
(The best in Korea)
(Mungdol Gang, the beautiful criminals)
(Yuchen Gang, the worst-looking gangsters)
(Ma Jong Kook, the squad detectives)
(Kang Daniel, every lady's heartthrob)
(Jo Se Ho, also known as Jo Daniel)
(Ha Yeon Soo, every guy's heartthrob)
(Noh Sa Yeon, the godmother of the entertainment business)
(Kang Daniel...)
(versus Kwang Daniel)
(The crazy war has started.)
(City of Crime, next Sunday at 4:50pm)