(7 years ago,)
(the members' paths collided...)
(for the show.)
(359 greetings...)
(and countless laughter and memories)
(Running Man has run for 7 years.)
(For 7 years, the 7 members completed various missions.)
(For 7 years, the 7 members created legends.)
(For 7 years, numerous friends joined them.)
(Then the new family was born.)
(Is he for real? The shameless man, Yang Se Chan)
(She has foolish charms. The magnet, Jeon So Min)
(Fear?)
(Embarrassment?)
(Difficulty?)
(Nothing scared them because they ran together.)
(Now comes the special vacation to celebrate the 7th anniversary.)
(J hanok hotel in Yeoncheon, Gyeonggi Province)
(Hantan River and waterfall make Yeoncheon a nice vacation spot.)
(This is a place for Running Man's 7th year anniversary vacation.)
(The gifts from South American fans decorate the place.)
(Why is it raining?)
(Heavy rain watch has been issued. There will be 100mm of rain.)
(The heaviest rain falls on the day of the shoot.)
(The production crew moves out from the original location.)
- It's raining too hard. - Let's move.
We are moving out.
(The staff becomes busy.)
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
- Hello. - What is this?
It's rice.
Latin American fans sent it to the lobby of SBS building.
(Latin American fans sent rice for the 7th year anniversary.)
From faraway countries,
- our fans sent gifts. - We are very grateful.
Thank you very much. We will work hard.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- The 7th year anniversary. - The 7th year anniversary.
I love the seventh year anniversary.
- Seven years have passed. - Already.
- Seven years have passed. - Time flew by so fast.
- That's incredible. - This year,
So Min and Se Chan have joined us,
- and we're working hard together. - Right.
We'll keep on doing our best as well.
- Great! - Let's do our best!
- Congratulations. - Goodness.
You're our lucky charms.
Goodness.
Jong Kook is unusually nice to Se Chan today.
Two days after the shooting last week,
Se Chan asked me if I'm feeling better.
- I was worried. - Really?
He texted me to check my condition.
But Kwang Soo didn't send me a single text until today.
- I... - He didn't even ask me how I was.
I stayed up for three nights to pray for your health.
I don't make it obvious like him.
I get touched by small stuff like this.
I was worried a lot.
- I'm fine now. - It's good to hear.
- I got much better. - I always check your condition...
by meeting your acquaintances. I worry if you eat well.
He's lying.
Do you know the meaning of the word written on your shirt?
It means to shut your mouth.
- Stay silent. - Don't say anything.
"Don't say anything."
Congratulations, Kwang Soo.
- By the way... - For what?
(What is he talking about all of a sudden?)
You have one more person to serve.
What do you mean?
(He will have to serve Hye Kyo as well as his master, Joong Ki.)
He'll have to serve her as well once they get married.
If the two get married,
are you going to move into their house?
- What are you talking about? - As their butler.
I have my own house.
- You have to be always around them. - Look at him.
You know there are maids who reside in their masters' house.
So that's not how it works.
There isn't such a system like that.
You should demand a salary now that you're serving two people.
- What are you talking about? - You need to get paid.
You'll be the first-class butler though.
- Right. - Indeed.
By the way, is Jong Kook not going to wear his outfit today?
What do you mean?
- That's his outfit? - I'm all ready.
I can even see his ribs from here.
Because people all have their ribs.
This one's better, I guess.
He usually wears something that comes down to here.
That's only when I work out.
- Gosh, seriously. - Those are my workout clothes.
I happen to put my hands inside that shirt whenever I wear it.
(It happens whenever I wear that shirt.)
(He can reach his underwear directly.)
Today, we've prepared a special race to do with your friends.
- It's called Summer Race. - Okay.
I'm sure you all invited one of your friends to join today's race.
- Sure. - I did.
Today's guests are on standby...
in the room next to here.
- Really? - I'm excited to meet them!
(The invited friends are waiting next door.)
We'll move to the room and start our race.
(Let's go meet their friends who are here to join the race.)
Let's go!
(The rain pours down as if it's celebrating the 7th anniversary.)
(Running Man members' friends are waiting inside.)
There are a lot of them.
There are many of them.
Your friends are waiting behind these blinds.
(Come meet us.)
We'll get right into your first mission...
to acquire 10 dollars which will play a big role in today's race.
(Succeed the mission for 10 dollars.)
- It's about mission money. - 10 dollars is a lot.
10 dollars in Running Man is worth 1,000 dollars.
(They start guessing their guests.)
Let's start the first mission in finding your guests.
We don't know whom each of us invited, right?
- No. - I have no idea.
- Except for my guest. - But So Min...
is wearing a t-shirt that says "older sister" on it.
(Your older sister is here.)
I guess it's someone younger than her.
- I think the same way. - I think so too.
It could be...
your family member for real...
or someone who's like your family.
- Family. - It could be someone really close.
- Like we're so close to each other. - Yes, we're like family.
- He and I are like family. - Se Chan and I.
- Family. - What about Kwang Soo?
(Three of us are like family.)
- Not him anymore. - Not him?
Not anymore.
(He attacks Jong Kook's weak spot.)
- Why would you do that? - Goodness.
For goodness' sake.
We're not sure whom each of us invited,
but we'll say hello to them first.
We'll start from number one.
- Hello. - Hello.
- It's a guy. - It's a guy.
His fake voice sounds like a man.
You can't tell who invited you, can you?
No.
- That was short. - He sounds...
Did you wait long?
- Yes. - What was that?
Are you annoyed because you had to wait so long?
A little.
You're annoyed a little?
He's talking so casually to us.
I think he's quite close with us.
I think it's Seok Jin's friend.
- Isn't he one of your club members? - Is he?
(What's the identity of number 1?)
Let's try talking to number four now. Hello.
Hello.
(Nervous)
I can sense right away...
that it's your first time on television.
Not at all.
- Is it a woman? - Is it a woman?
Is it a man or a woman?
What's your job, a singer?
Have you joined Running Man before?
- No. - It's your first time?
- It's your first time? - Yes.
Did you appear on any other programs?
Yes.
Why do you keep laughing?
(Laughing)
- What's wrong with you? - Have you lost your mind?
- She's scary. - What's wrong with you?
Is it a man or a woman?
That person sounds like a professional.
Let's try talking to number six this time. Hello.
Hello.
- What? - It's a girl!
She has a very thin voice.
That sounded cute.
Her voice sounds pretty.
It's either a girl or Jong Kook to have that kind of voice.
- Hey. - I mean...
- Since it's not you, it's a girl. - What are you talking about?
Because it's not you.
Next up is number seven. Hello.
Hello.
Number seven.
You don't sound like...
you're used to being on television. Am I right?
Have you been on many TV programs?
It's my first time.
- It's her first time. - It's her first time.
It's your first time on television?
- She's never been on TV before. - Then she must be a family member.
- She's a family member. - It's possible.
- By the way, So Min. - Yes?
Why do you look so nervous? Whom did you invite?
- She's acting strange. - Why are you sweating so much?
- She's so quiet too. - Is she a spy?
- What's wrong with you? - You tend to be...
nervous when your family comes out as a guest.
He's right.
By the way, why are you pressing down on their shoulders?
(They've become his armrest.)
- I think... - What's this?
I think I'll get a heat rash here, but I'm letting him be.
I'm enduring the pain in my back too.
I think I'm getting a heat rash.
- Can't you put your arms down? - If I put them down,
we'll feel more uncomfortable since there isn't much room here.
You're the only one who's feeling comfortable now though.
- We like it this way. - Right?
(They're done greeting their guests. It's time to guess who they are.)
We've said hi to them briefly.
We'll now talk more in detail with them.
Please answer yes or no to our questions.
Here's the first question.
"I have one thing which I'd like my friend not to do."
Please answer yes or no.
1, 2, 3.
(What will be their answers?)
- They all have it. - They all answered yes.
- Except number 1. - Number 1 answered no.
- I guess their friends are perfect. - 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, and 8 answered yes.
(They all answered yes except for number 1 and 6.)
Number four.
What would you like for your friend not to do?
I like everything about my friend...
except for the drinking habits.
- Drinking habits? - Drinking habits?
(Drinking habits)
(How are number four's friend's drinking habits?)
- Drinking habits? - Drinking habits?
- It must be Kwang Soo. - Can you explain more in detail?
My friend won't let me go home or sleep.
- It's Ji Hyo. - By any chance...
Can you tell us an example?
My friend splashes water.
- Splashes water? - What?
I do it once in a while.
It might be Kwang Soo's friend.
What about you, Ji Hyo?
I do that sometimes.
She splashes water on cigarettes when they don't get put out.
Only when they don't get put out.
Splashing water is much easier, you know.
She used to do it with her saliva before,
- but not these days. - Because we can't smoke indoors.
- We have to smoke outdoors. - So she uses water.
(Those slanderers.)
How far can your friend go?
Does that person catch you when you try to sneak out?
Right, when I try to leave,
that person acts pathetic all of a sudden.
- Pathetic? - Goodness.
- It's not me then. - It's Kwang Soo.
- It's Kwang Soo. - No?
- It's Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo.
- It's Kwang Soo. - She rather follows the other.
Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and I had a drink the other day.
Jong Kook and I pretended to go home and went alone to talk in private.
But she kept following us in secret by her manager's car.
We tried to send her home,
but she followed us in secret.
They kept going somewhere else without me.
We almost thought there was a tracker installed in our car.
There was no way she could run into us.
(You can't escape from her until morning once you drink with her.)
That startled us.
- It must be Kwang Soo. - It must be Ji Hyo.
- Number five. - Yes?
What do you want your friend to not do?
Personality is one thing,
but I think the biggest thing is the drinking.
- Drinking? - Alcohol again?
The person must drink a lot.
Does your friend drink too much?
It's beyond your imagination.
How does your friend act when drunk?
My friend becomes a complete mess.
- A complete mess? - Yes.
Whenever I try to go home,
my friend uses violence and splashes water.
Sometimes, my friend hits me and kicks my bottom too.
- It's Ji Hyo! - They like to tease people.
It's you for certain.
- It's Ji Hyo. - This is...
- Right, splashing water. - I have to dance...
to the same song for two hours. Only then, my friend falls asleep.
- Hold on. - So Min looks serious.
So Min.
Why are you being so quiet and careful all of a sudden?
- What's wrong with you? - Apologize already.
I don't dance.
- I don't dance. - It's not So Min.
Have you danced for two hours before?
- I do that every time. - Every time?
- It's her. - I didn't know she danced.
- Do you dance? - I love to dance.
It's just that I'm not good at it.
- I love to dance. - Is that so?
Is it you?
(It's Ji Hyo's younger brother, Chun Sung Moon.)
(They were both good-looking since they were young.)
(He kicked Ji Hyo on behalf of all the younger brothers in Korea.)
(He's now an actor following his sister's footsteps.)
Number six, why did you answer no to the question?
So far,
this person has nothing to work on.
- So far, there's nothing. - So far?
- I see. - What if they are not close?
Could it be that you're not interested in this person?
I don't even know their phone number.
- You don't have the number? - You don't have it?
Why did you decide to star on our show today?
- Why are you here? - Hold on.
I don't know.
- You don't know? - By any chance,
did you regret coming here today even for a second?
Well, yes. Right now, I feel...
You're regretting it now?
- Now? - She's regretting it now.
- She said she regrets it now. - Among other things...
(Number 6 who keeps the members on their toes, is...)
(Son Na Eun, Se Chan's pick, whom he wants as his family member.)
(She didn't do anything, but managed to steal Se Chan's heart.)
(The crew invited her since Se Chan wanted to talk to her more.)
So do you wish to know this person's number?
(If we meet only once, it's a coincidence,)
(but if we meet twice, it's fate.)
Well... Sure.
(Everyone can see it's a definite rejection.)
- Hey, you! Go home! - I bet it's her.
Get out of here!
Before you hurt my feelings even more, leave!
Go before you hurt me more.
(I've experienced this many times before.)
- I won't ask for you anymore. - Could it really be her?
- This is really happening. - No way.
- Se Chan. - Could it really be Na Eun?
- It can't be her. - Is it really her?
(What is the ending of his one-sided romance?)
What about you, Number Three?
You answered yes to the question.
I want this person to talk less.
- He wants this person to talk less. - It's you, Jae Seok.
- Did you invite two people? - Is it So Min?
(Is it Jae Seok, the talkative one?)
Is it So Min? Could it be her?
- That's right. It's So Min. - She talks a lot too.
- He was referring to her. - It's So Min.
He wants her to talk less.
- So Min... - I bet she talks a lot at home too.
She is truly talkative.
(Is Number 3 my brother?)
Does this member tell you to work on something?
Definitely.
- Please give us an example. - Is he talking about me?
This person tells me to work out.
(They nag him to work out the most.)
- He's talking about Jong Kook! - True.
(If he's into fitness, it's Jong Kook.)
- It has to be him. - He's talking about me.
- Jong Myung! - Hey, Jong Myung.
Aren't you Kim Jong Myung?
You came here today, and didn't go to your clinic, did you?
Jong Myung, it's you, isn't it?
(He's a legendary figure who scolded Jong Kook and bossed him around.)
(Left: Jong Kook, Right: Jong Myung)
(Jong Myung is Jong Kook's proud brother who is a plastic surgeon.)
- Okay. I got it. - It's his brother.
- Life is important, not money. - It has to be his brother.
You ought to work out.
Okay. Number Eight, you're up.
What do you want your friend to work on?
This friend of mine...
isn't like this anymore,
but my friend used to fall in love too easily.
- He's a hopeless romantic. - It has to be Kwang Soo then.
- It's definitely Kwang Soo. - It's him.
- Then... - It ought to be him.
- But he still falls in love easily. - It's Kwang Soo's friend.
- He does fall in love quickly. - But the thing is,
- he doesn't do that anymore. - Your friend doesn't now?
He's not like that now.
Then it's not you.
To be frank, I still fall in love quickly.
Can you give us an example when you thought he fell in love too quickly?
One time, I saw him fall in love with someone from the audience.
(He once fell in love with an audience member.)
- Someone from the audience? - What?
- Can this air? - Hey!
Can you talk about this on TV?
Is he talking about you?
- Was that you? - Well...
- Did you really fall in love? - I'm sure it's Seok Jin...
- because... - Next week...
(The identity of Number 8 who threw off Seok Jin is...)
(Kim Soo Yong, a member of Big Mouth and a friend of 30 years.)
I wasn't flirting with someone from the audience.
- Don't get the wrong idea. - Why?
- Did he mean you? - She happened to be there.
That wasn't her job.
- You weren't trying to seduce her. - No way.
- Don't use that expression. - That wasn't it.
- But it's true. - Why do you say I picked her up?
- At that time, it was serious. - But you did pick her up.
- It was a serious relationship. - It's all in the past.
Hey, go easy on me.
Okay.
Here's the next question.
This will tell us everything.
Have you ever heard of your family member badmouthing...
members of Running Man?
(Have they ever talked badly about one of their members?)
- This is a sensitive one. - Goodness, this question...
If this gets out, it will be a mess.
Hey, but this...
Don't talk. Don't talk, okay?
Don't tell them.
Everyone, you must clearly raise your answer boards.
A lot of you can't laugh at ease.
I see.
(He smiles awkwardly.)
In 1, 2, 3.
- O, O, O. - Many of them answered no.
(Only numbers 1, 7, and 8 answer yes.)
Number One said she did hear the member badmouth.
Number One, please tell us briefly what this person talked about.
This person badmouths quite often.
- Quite often? - Quite often?
(Can I tell them?)
- That person badmouthed often. - Really?
- Whom does he badmouth the most? - Who is it?
- Whom does he talk about the most? - Whom does he badmouth the most?
- I just got goose bumps. - Who is it?
Can you give us an example?
He said that he's going to beat up Jong Kook one day.
(The mysterious member plans to get back at Jong Kook one day.)
- It's Haha. - I never said that.
- It's either you or him. - No, it's not me.
- I didn't say that. - It's one of them.
- I swear I've never said that. - It has to be you.
- It's one of you. - Then my friend must be lying.
- Jong Kook. - Why would I say such a thing?
- It's possible. - He's friends with one of you.
- It's either Haha or Kwang Soo. - Why do you think it could be me?
- You hurt my feelings. - Nothing's confirmed yet.
So what did your friend say?
He asked for my help.
It has to be Haha.
(He asked for my help to beat up Jong Kook.)
- It has to be Haha. - Haha.
It's him. It's him.
- He asked for help? - No, it's Kwang Soo.
- He wanted to outnumber you. - It's Kwang Soo.
I have never imagined attacking you.
- He said he'd win if it's 2 to 1. - 2 to 1?
- I have a feeling it's Kwang Soo. - I wouldn't dare to think of it.
Hey, you told me that yourself.
- He told me this when he got drunk. - Calm down.
- He said he wanted to join forces. - Give us another example.
It's about Kwang Soo.
(Another example concerns Kwang Soo.)
- It's about Kwang Soo. - It's about Kwang Soo?
- What did he say? - What is it?
Then it must be Haha.
He said that Kwang Soo wants to copy...
every fashion sense he has.
What?
(What do you mean I want to copy you?)
- What? What do you mean? - I'm right, and you know it.
- Whenever I buy something, - That was...
- you wear it the next day. - Wait, you...
- talked about it behind my back? - Hold on a second.
- It's certain now. - I think he is my friend.
(Number 1 might have attacked Jong Kook 2 to 1.)
(He is Park Geun Sik, Haha's friend of 20 years.)
I like this guy.
(Haha's best friend whose friendship began from school days until now)
(Geun Sik is a loyal friend, and wants to do everything with Haha.)
Number Two, you answered no.
Your friend didn't badmouth anyone?
He's not the type who badmouths other people behind their backs.
He tends to badmouth them directly.
(He talks badly in front of the person.)
He's talking about Jae Seok. It's him!
- It's you. - I'm 100 percent certain.
(He's known for badmouthing someone so openly.)
- That's right. I do that. - You're right.
- You do. - Right.
Was there a time he talked about you when you were present?
There were countless times.
- What did he say to you? - What did he say recently?
Recently, what I heard the most from him was that...
I'm arrogant.
- You're arrogant? - I see.
I told him I was at home when he asked,
and he told me that I was arrogant.
What is so arrogant about being at home? Why is he arrogant?
- Why is that? - Wait.
He told me that I have to go out and socialize at times like this.
One time, when I was out,
I got a phone call.
When he asked where I was, I told him I was out.
He told me again that I was arrogant.
Where is this guest supposed to stay then?
(Just hearing this annoys them.)
Where should he be then?
He told me to go home and work on myself.
I think I know who this is.
- Number Two. - Yes?
So you've never talked about him behind his back?
I have.
What did you say about him?
I said that he made me feel horrible.
You felt horrible when he nagged you?
(It's Cho Sae Ho.)
All right.
- Next up is Number Four. - Yes.
You answered no. This person never badmouthed members of the show?
It's actually the contrary. I heard this person complimenting...
members of Running Man.
- This person complimented us? - Please give us an example.
I heard this person say that you are loyal, kind, and diligent.
- We are diligent? - That person is nice.
- Diligent? - It must be a family member.
- I don't know who that is, but... - This person didn't badmouth us,
but considering the frequencies of the compliments,
which member received the least number of compliments?
(Chuckling)
- The guest is laughing. - Exactly.
It's Ji Hyo.
Who is it?
- Who is it? - Who can that be?
(You don't have to be so honest.)
- Who is it? - Sit down.
Kwang Soo.
- It must be Kwang Soo. - It's Kwang Soo!
- He doesn't badmouth us. - What's happening?
I only compliment. I don't talk behind their backs.
- So... - What just happened?
He just doesn't compliment her. That's all.
(Tae Hang Ho, Kwang Soo's actor friend, shares opinions bluntly.)
(He demonstrated a unique performance...)
(from "It's Okay, That's Love", and the two became friends.)
- Number Five, you're up. - Okay.
- This person doesn't badmouth us? - No.
- There wasn't a single time? - No.
Have you heard of this person complimenting...
- members of Running Man? - Yes.
- Who was it? - Whom did this person compliment?
This person said the members were nice and took care of this person.
- That's it. - Who is it?
- Who took care of this person? - Who was it?
- It's Kwang Soo. - I see.
(My friend, Kwang Soo)
(Whose family member is that? Who complimented me?)
Kwang Soo does take good care of us in general.
- It's likely that So Min said that. - It could be So Min.
If it's not So Min...
- Wait. No. It's Ji Hyo's family. - It's Ji Hyo.
- Is it Ji Hyo? - He said that person kicked him.
- That's right. - She drinks a lot too.
- It's Ji Hyo. It is her brother. - Is it Ji Hyo?
(Number 5's family member who complimented me...)
(is Ji Hyo?)
- Wait. This means... - My brother hits me, actually.
Number Four.
Doesn't your friend compliment Ji Hyo?
- Just think about it. - Hey, cut it out.
(You brat.)
(Hitting)
(Ji Hyo becomes aggressive.)
She's back.
- Ji Hyo. - She's back.
- It could have been worse. - She's angry.
Be quiet.
(The big sister's love)
All right. "I think..."
"the family member is ugly."
1, 2, 3. Please show us your answer.
Three. Please show us your answer.
X, X, O, O...
(Three of them think their family member is ugly.)
There are 3 O'x and 5 X's.
It must be Seok Jin, Kwang Soo,
and Se Chan.
(It must be Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, and Se Chan's family members.)
- And Se Chan. - What?
- The last one is for you. - What are you talking about?
The last one is for you.
- Jae Seok, Se Chan... - You're wrong.
This is frustrating.
Those who showed an X must be real family members.
- Let's ask them. - They must be family members.
Number one.
- Yes. - You don't think...
the family member is ugly?
- No. - What do you think?
Which part is the most handsome?
(Sighing)
- He sighed. - He can't say anything.
He can't find an answer.
Shouldn't you have chosen O then?
(Flipping)
He changed his answer.
- He changed it. - He's so funny.
He must be a celebrity. He's not just a family member.
- He changed his answer. - He changed it.
- Is it Geun Sik? - Haha's friend...
Do you love your friend?
I don't exactly love him.
(Let's see... Well...)
(Angry)
(Here you go.)
What are you doing?
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
- It might be someone else. - What if it's someone else?
Then I'll apologize.
It might be someone else's family member.
- I'm so disappointed. - Goodness.
All right. Number seven.
Can you rank your family member according to looks?
Fourth.
(4th)
- Fourth? - It's in the middle.
- That's not bad. - It might be me.
It's quite high.
Have you seen all the guests' faces?
Yes.
How high do you rank?
(Haha asks an extra question.)
(Well...)
I rank first.
You rank first?
(He's So Min's little brother, Jeon Wook Min.)
(Both the sister and brother are attractive.)
(So Min's brother works as a personal trainer.)
- I rank 1st. - You rank 1st?
If I may,
can I ask you who ranks lowest?
Say a number.
Who ranks lowest?
Number two.
(Number 2)
- Number 2? - Number 2?
(Me?)
- Number two is the ugliest? - Who is it?
Number two...
Are you there?
He might be hurt.
I'm very surprised.
(It's so funny.)
This is very unexpected. I'm very surprised.
Who would you rank lowest?
Well...
Number eight.
- Number 8? - Number 8?
- Who is that? - Who is that?
It must be a very close competition.
- Number eight. - Yes?
Which do you think looks better, number two or you?
- Number two? - Yes.
That's ridiculous. Number two looks like garbage.
Number two looks like garbage.
(He fails to choose the right word.)
(They must be neck and neck.)
They must know each other.
Number two, are you okay?
Are you okay?
- Number two... - Go back to your seats.
Number two looks like garbage?
- Goodness. - It's so fierce.
- They must know each other. - They know each other.
That's why he can say that.
That's why he can joke.
They know each other.
All right.
Among the guests...
It's easy.
The one you think is your family member...
- Do we stick this? - It's clear now.
Put it on the booth.
Shall we?
Do you think number seven is yours?
Yes.
There's no confusion.
It's nice.
Let's meet Haha's family member.
Please come out.
- We might be wrong. - I'm sure.
- Who is it? - It's Geun Sik.
- Geun Sik. - Geun Sik.
(Haha and Geun Sik)
My brother!
Let's meet my family member.
My arrogant friend.
Hello.
Welcome.
Shouldn't he be seeing his patients?
Poor guy.
- Sung Moon. - Sung Moon.
Let's meet Se Chan's family member.
It's Na Eun.
She's so kind.
This way, my lady.
- This way, my lady. - Na Eun.
- It must be her brother. - Right.
(Jeon So Min and Jeon Wook Min)
- Hi. - Hi.
(Jee Seok Jin and Kim Soo Yong)
Finally, let's meet Kwang Soo's family member.
Please come out.
It's Hang Ho.
(Shy)
Oh, my.
You look even scarier now.
- Hang Ho. - Hang Ho.
I know him.
This is the first time I've seen him in real life.
What happened to your hair?
I've seen him so many times on TV.
- Me too. - When you came out,
you looked so wild.
(I'm wild.)
Right?
He looks like Go Chang Suk.
- Right. - I was...
- a bit confused. - Right.
- He looks like Jo Jung Lin too. - Jo Jung Lin.
Jo Jung Lin.
He really looks like her.
He looks like her.
He looks like Miranda Kerr too.
- That's right. - Miranda Kerr.
(He surprisingly looks like Miranda Kerr too.)
- He looks like Miranda Kerr. - He's amazing.
- I see the resemblance. - How many people does he look like?
He has a thousand faces.
- He does look like Miranda Kerr. - He does.
- He really looks like her. - Yes.
Excuse me, can you get out of my way?
What?
I can't see Sung Moon.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Aren't you Lee Jae Po?
No, I'm not.
He's my family member.
- He's my family member. - He's Lee Jae Po.
- Aren't you Lee Jae Po? - He's my family member.
- It's okay. - I'll talk to him.
I'll talk to him.
- I'll talk to him. - It's okay.
He's my family member.
He looks familiar.
He acts like him,
- and sounds like him too. - Stop it.
I'm...
(Blind Mission Fees)
(The rain doesn't stop as if to celebrate their anniversary.)
Our family members are here today.
(Welcome)
We're a family.
We are the world!
A summer vacation with family members,
Dangerous Family Crisis.
(Dangerous Family Crisis)
You'll team up with your family member.
The team with the most money at the end will win.
The winners will win a prize and be exempted from penalties.
The team with the least money can choose one team...
to receive the penalty together.
Is it an ice shower?
- The losers can choose one team? - Yes.
After each mission,
two teams with the highest scores...
will be given the chance to change their family members.
(2 top teams can change their family members.)
Change family members?
(Should I find a new family so that I can win?)
Each family's fate can change all the time.
You look happy.
Even if your family member changes,
you can keep your money.
That's why you should divide the money wisely.
(The amount of money is important.)
(Stuck indoors, they become more and more aggressive.)
(Protect your money to avoid an ice shower, and save the family.)
(Who will win this battle among families?)
Let's do...
- some more interviews... - Sure.
before we start the game.
- Sae Ho. - Yes.
I invited him.
He's one of...
- my closest friends. - Right.
Sae Ho, I'll see you later.
(I'll see you later.)
(Is that it?)
I'll see you later.
(They're too close.)
As I said,
Sae Ho is so busy these days.
He's receiving so much love.
Luckily, he had time today.
Thank you so much for coming.
- Thank you. - All right then.
(All right then.)
You can find out about me...
on other shows.
But...
He's our guest.
I want to know more about him.
- Later... - Ask him a few basic questions.
Ask him a question.
When I invited you,
you were doubtful.
I wasn't exactly doubtful.
I always wanted to be close with Jae Seok,
but he never showed any response.
(I wanted to know if we were close.)
What he just said gave me too big of a burden.
Jae Seok is like that.
I feel too burdened.
Jae Seok doesn't like it when people approach him quickly.
I've known him for more than 10 years.
- You're too hasty. - Now...
- Am I? - You need at least 15 years.
- 15 years? - 15 years.
- You're almost there. - Yes.
It took me 22 years.
22 years?
I'll ask this question to the other guests too.
In a word,
what kind of a person am I to you?
(Flustered)
In one word.
That's an unexpected question.
(His mind goes blank.)
It's hard.
- It's hard. - Can't you improvise?
- Sure, you can. - Why do you say it's difficult?
Soo Yong.
How would you describe Seok Jin in one word?
- Seok Jin is fickle. - Fickle?
- Is it time for him to leave? - That's great.
It means that he's easily persuaded.
- Don't say that. - He's not going to die.
That's not what I mean.
- He's easily persuaded. - How could he say that?
Don't misunderstand.
My goodness.
How about you, Sung Moon?
(Did he call him Sung Moon?)
How would you describe Jong Kook in one word?
He is Jong Myung.
- Sung Moon is over there. - Jong Myung.
Jong Myung, how would you describe him?
He's Mother Bear.
- Pardon me? - Mother Bear.
- Mother Bear? Why? - Yes.
He nags a lot.
(He's like a mother bear at home.)
What does he nag about these days?
"Exercise."
"Only do things that are healthy."
"Don't do unhealthy things."
"Quit smoking."
Aren't you suffering from gout?
- You really are. - What about my gout?
- He can't walk well. - Yes, I have gout.
It's not caused by something unhealthy.
(He thinks it's unfair.)
Pardon me for asking,
but do you have any illnesses?
No, I don't.
- You don't, right? - No.
It happened while I was trying to be healthy.
- He always has a cold in summer. - That's right.
- Take care of your body. - What?
You're a celebrity. You should take care of yourself.
Move on, move on.
(Go on while I'm being nice.)
- He should take care of himself. - Next is Hang Ho.
How would you describe...
Kwang Soo in one word?
He doesn't know him well enough.
- He does. - What comes to mind?
(They don't seem very close.)
- What comes to mind? - In one word.
- He's a great actor. - A great actor?
(He describes Kwang Soo as a great actor.)
- What makes you say that? - Kwang Soo?
People usually say that when...
they don't know each other well.
(It's a common way to describe a stranger.)
Do you know each other well?
Otherwise, he wouldn't say that.
I don't think they're very close.
They're not close at all.
Hang Ho doesn't describe people as "great actors".
To be honest,
most people were...
too busy.
They're getting married.
They have shoots.
Is that why he's here today?
He's the closest among the rest.
I consider him as family.
- Is that why he's here? - Yes.
Thank you very much for coming.
Kwang Soo.
How would you describe Hang Ho in one word?
When I'm with him,
I stand out more.
(He thinks he stands out when he's with Hang Ho.)
- Is that why you invited him? - No.
- Is that why you invited him? - No, I swear.
- You shouldn't do that. - That's not why.
Of course, that's not why.
I'm being honest.
Kwang Soo is so harsh.
How could you say that after inviting him?
Hang Ho described Kwang Soo...
in a positive way.
I don't feel so good.
- Goodness. - I see.
I'd like to ask Wook Min next.
(Wook Min is So Min's handsome brother.)
Gosh, he's so handsome.
He's charming.
He's a real man.
Wook Min is handsome.
How would you describe her?
Parrot and Frog.
As she's too talkative at home, your father calls her Parrot.
Is that true?
(While her brother is handsome, So Min is talkative.)
(Is she also talkative at home?)
In general, our family members are talkative.
- Is that so? - Are you also talkative?
When we're in the elevator,
we must press the button to get to a certain floor.
No one presses it.
- Are you too busy talking? - Yes.
They're too busy talking.
- Do you keep talking instead? - Right.
(Their family is always too busy talking.)
Usually, people converse when they're in the car.
We talk over each other.
No one listens.
We're like radios.
(The family is busy talking about themselves.)
So Min is like that.
- That's exactly like So Min. - Right.
- She talks a lot about herself. - She does.
Our father is also talkative.
- He's very amicable. - He keeps talking.
(Kwang Soo spent a night listening to So Min's father.)
Could you talk about So Min?
(He tells another story.)
Before we go out,
she only brushes her teeth.
- She doesn't put on makeup? - No.
Does she wash her face?
I don't think so.
(So Min is a little embarrassed.)
- Is that embarrassing for you? - Yes.
She wears crumpled caps.
He hates that.
- Why? - Crumpled caps?
We went out for some beer recently.
He talked about her cap for a long time.
"Why do you wear caps like that?"
Why are you meddling in their family business?
(Hold on. Why are you involved?)
What's wrong with you?
You have more to say about them than Hang Ho.
I just remembered it.
Let's talk about Kwang Soo.
It's not true, and it's unlikely in the future.
What if Kwang Soo and So Min get into a relationship?
- What if? - Right.
- What if it happens? - What if?
How would you feel?
(As her younger brother...)
I'll be happy if she's happy.
(He's happy as long as she's happy.)
(Smiling)
Look at Kwang Soo.
Why do you look so happy?
(Why is he reacting this way to his response?)
- It's not because I'm happy. - Why do you look so happy?
That's not why.
It's nice to be complimented.
Compliments are nice.
How about you, Na Eun?
- I'm really curious about her. - How would you...
describe Se Chan in one word?
(It's the most difficult question for Na Eun.)
(Na Eun doesn't even know Se Chan's phone number.)
(She doesn't know why she's invited as his family.)
(How will she describe Se Chan in one word?)
Say that he's a burden.
He's someone I want to get to know.
(She wants to get to know him.)
- That's not bad. - Is that true?
That's not bad.
Accept what she said. She wants to get to know me.
Why do you keep buttoning and unbuttoning the shirt?
I don't know which looks better.
I'm trying to do what she prefers.
- It doesn't matter. - Is that so?
It's too much.
Na Eun doesn't care about that. Just unbutton it.
You're just a friend.
(Can't you see?)
She could meet up with you and her boyfriend.
Pardon me, but you aren't in the camera frame.
(Haha, you aren't in the camera frame.)
Come in.
What will you do?
The film set ends here.
Come in.
Come in, Geun Sik.
During the OX Quiz a moment ago,
there's a question I didn't ask.
Does your family member brag too much?
Geun Sik, what do you think about Haha?
He doesn't brag.
- He doesn't? - No.
- It sounds like you're lying. - I don't.
He has nothing to brag about.
(He doesn't brag because he has nothing to brag about.)
(He has a headache.)
(Geun Sik's answer is genuine.)
- He has nothing to brag about. - Not at all?
Not at all.
Since he was in school?
It was worse back then.
(He had less to brag about back then.)
- Was he worse than before? - He was worse.
He had nothing to brag about.
Now that he's on TV, he has something.
(He had things to brag about when he started being on TV.)
I'm disappointed.
- I feel very disappointed. - All right then.
- You run a business together. - That's right.
Jae Seok, while you're interviewing other people,
Sae Ho is very anxious.
He's wondering...
if you'll ask him any questions.
Will he just skip me?
(It was a moment ago.)
- Sae Ho. - Is it my turn again?
Yes, it is.
How would you describe me in one word?
I'll just say that...
you're like iced coffee.
- Why do you say that? - That's my final word.
Why am I like iced coffee?
I really like iced coffee.
- Is it because you also like me? - Yes.
That's it?
What's wrong with you?
This is one of my weaknesses.
I have strengths,
but I can't describe people in one word.
He gets flustered by unexpected questions.
The number of words I can use per day is limited to 100.
Otherwise, it gets difficult.
- I really like you. - By the way,
I heard that you prepared something...
for today's show.
- Did I? - Didn't you?
I...
I heard Sae Ho knows the dance choreography to "New Face".
It's because Na Eun is also invited to the show.
- The dance is popular these days. - You're right.
I like the dance.
The video of Na Eun's dance to "New Face" was viewed...
by almost a million.
(Her video has been viewed by 700,000 people.)
Can you dance to "New Face", Sae Ho?
Let's see Cho's Face.
- Cho's Face. - Be careful how you pronounce it.
- Cho's Face. - Say, "New Face".
Should I say, "New Face"?
- Let's call it Ho's Face. - Ho's Face.
Can you show us the dance?
Why are you suddenly making me dance?
(He's surprised by their request.)
We were having a serious talk.
- We're family. - I can dance.
- It's because we're family. - It's so sudden.
- Can you dance? - Yes.
- It's just a dance that I like. - I see.
- I never... - He's really going to dance.
volunteered to dance.
You said you'd dance to "New Face".
- I did? - Yes.
(He's confused.)
Look here.
"Cho Sae Ho, New Face".
- I don't... - Am I wrong?
- You debuted 17 years ago, right? - Yes.
- Through SBS's sixth recruitment? - Yes.
- You appear on "Happy Together". - Yes.
Below that, it says, "New Face".
I don't think so.
(That's odd.)
(Only Jae Seok can see it.)
Why do you make him dance instead of asking him questions?
He can't talk well today.
Me?
(He's surprised once again.)
- I've been doing well. - No.
You're not talking very well.
- These days... - You're not doing well.
- I can talk. - Today,
just dance, play games, and go home.
My specialty is talking.
You're not talking very well.
- You're not doing well. - I have to dance?
Can you play some music?
Do you need it?
(Do you really need it?)
Do I have to dance without music?
"New Face" dance moves without any music?
All right. We'll play music.
You should have asked us.
I was just...
Sae Ho will dance to "New Face".
- Play the music. - Okay.
(Sae Ho's New Face)
(Breathing)
(Let me release...)
(the Psy-like vibes that I've been hiding inside me.)
(His face is dancing too.)
Yes!
(You said you weren't prepared.)
(Flapping)
(Yes, I want some Ho's Face)
(He dances with his whole body.)
(Broken)
(Ho's Face)
(He looks exactly like Psy.)
(Bouncing)
(He finishes off by bouncing his belly.)
(This is Ho's Face.)
- Nice! - That was amazing.
(His dance skills are better than ever.)
Great job.
That was amazing.
- You looked like you were in pain. - Really?
(You looked like you were in pain. )
Yes.
(Me?)
(His face contorted as if he was in pain.)
(I dance when I'm in pain.)
Na Eun, what did you think?
- It was great. - It was amazing.
There is another person who wanted to dance.
Let's see Hang Ho dance to "New Face".
- Did you want to do it? - No.
- "New Face"? - Hold on.
(You wanted to dance to "New Face"?)
- Hold on. - It says your name too.
He's ambitious.
- Here. - I love it.
"Hang Ho, New Face".
Do you see it?
You debuted nine years ago, right?
- Well... Yes. - Right?
(He gives up.)
I thought I was going to dance with you.
You'll dance alone.
- Alone? - Yes.
He's very shy.
He's very shy and feminine.
Kwang Soo, show some support.
Hang Ho.
You already look funny.
(Giggling)
Just move your hips.
All right.
Hang Ho.
Give us some music.
(How will Hang Ho dance?)
(What's that?)
He's so cute.
(Wriggling)
(Cute)
(He's too cute.)
He's so cute.
(So Min likes it.)
(The guys can't stand it.)
Miss.
This is hilarious.
(He dances even more prettily than Na Eun did.)
This is amazing!
This is amazing.
He's so cute.
Go back to your seat.
Hold on.
It was so feminine.
He's very feminine.
That was amazing.
He's so lovely.
- That was great. All right. - He's so lovely.
There is another person who wanted to dance to "New Face".
Can you do it?
- No. - I think he can.
- He can. - He can.
- He can do it. - Stand up.
Just a quick one.
- Suddenly... - You can do it.
- You can do it. - It's war.
(You can do it.)
- Be confident. - I don't know the song.
- Sorry? - I don't know the song.
The song? You just saw the others do it.
- You can mimic them. - Just mimic them.
Give us some music.
(How will this quiet guy dance?)
- 1, 2, 3, 4. - 1, 2, 3, 4.
(Hesitating)
(You can do it.)
(What is that?)
(Inappropriate)
(It's not appropriate for the show.)
(Why did he close his eyes?)
(The moves were not suitable for children.)
(My brother...)
What did you do?
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Sit down.
Sit down.
You said you weren't prepared.
(Thank you for showing off your sexy charms.)
Let's see Na Eun dance.
(It's Na Eun's turn.)
Her dance moves are so controlled.
You know her, right?
She's the originator.
(The originator steps onto the stage.)
She's so passionate.
She's beautiful.
Music, please.
(Enjoy the originator's vibes.)
(Excited)
(This is the original.)
(After smiling shyly,)
(she shows off her charms using her whole body.)
(I love you.)
(Look at...)
(how sexy she is.)
(All the guys' hearts are on fire.)
(Let me show you the original moves.)
(Fatal charms)
(Na Eun is the definition of love.)
Na Eun is the best.
Na Eun, thank you.
You're the best.
Thank you.
(Despite their enthusiasm,)
(the heavy rain doesn't stop.)
(They won't be able to go outside.)
It's still raining a lot.
We won't be able to do any outdoor missions.
(The next mission will be carried out indoors too.)
Everyone, are your bodies warmed up now?
Too much. Our muscles have no energy left.
All right. Let's start the games now.
(Let's start the games now.)
- Was this just the opening? - Yes.
- Up until now? - Yes.
(For two hours?)
It was just the opening.
Unbelievable.
All right. All family members,
welcome. Let's start the next mission.
Family Contest.
(Family Contest)
(Dancing)
(The siblings dance together.)
(Laughing)
(He shows off his charms.)
Please sit down.
A member will introduce his or her family member's specialty.
If you think you or your family member...
can outdo the person, participate in the game.
- Okay. - It's a competition between teams.
Only one person can participate from each team.
The winning team will be...
given 10 dollars.
10 dollars is big.
- It is. - It is.
Jae Seok will...
announce Sae Ho's...
specialty.
Sae Ho's specialty is keeping balance.
- Keeping balance? - Keeping balance?
(Sae Ho's specialty: Keeping balance)
After turning 20 times,
- That's hard. - without faltering,
- I can walk straight. - Really?
I can put ink on my partner's nose.
- Really? - Is that possible?
20 times?
20 times.
- He'll turn 20 times. - 20 times.
That must be hard.
We can't even turn five times. We've done it.
(In the Thief Race,)
(they had a hard time keeping balance after turning.)
(Turning 5 times was hard.)
(How will he turn 20 times?)
It's going to be hard.
You do it.
Can't you do it?
Sae Ho, can you really do it?
I do it often.
- Really? - Yes.
(I do it often.)
Why do you do it often?
Some people never become dizzy.
- It improves your sense of balance. - Right.
Let's see. Ready.
(I do it often.)
Turn 20 times. Start.
(Turning 20 times is no problem.)
(How well will he do it?)
- 1, 2... - He's so fast.
(His heavy body turns fast.)
(He's turned 10 times already.)
- I think he's dizzy. - 8, 9...
- He's not going to make it. - 14, 15,
- 16... - He's not going to make it.
(Sae Ho is becoming unstable.)
- Just 2 more times. - Last 1.
- 20. - Go.
(He's turned 20 times.)
(He has to walk straight now.)
(Jae Seok,)
(here I come.)
(Without wobbling)
(Will Sae Ho be able to put the ink on Jae Seok's nose?)
(Accurate)
(Sae Ho succeeds.)
Really?
(Unbelievable)
- It's... - That must be hard.
He didn't even wobble.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I got it.
Next up is someone who volunteered to do it.
- Who is it? - It's Sung Moon.
(Ji Hyo's brother gives it a try.)
- Sung Moon exercises a lot. - That's right.
I'll start.
(By the way...)
Are you okay, Sae Ho?
Yes, don't worry about me.
He shouldn't have done it.
I just need to catch my breath.
You're sweating so much.
I'm very hot right now.
I'm very hot.
I exerted too much energy.
- Your face is very red. - Right.
You look sick, Sae Ho.
Get ready, Sung Moon.
You can do it, Sung Moon.
(Unlike Sae Ho,)
(he'll walk towards her quickly.)
- Start. - You can do it.
That looks great.
(Ji Hyo, I'm coming.)
He's doing well.
- He turns easily. - You're doing well.
If Sung Moon succeeds...
- Okay. - 16.
- He'll make it. - 17.
- He turns quickly. - He's so fast.
You're doing well.
- That's great. - He'll make it.
- He's done. - Go.
Let's go.
(Now,)
(he starts walking.)
(He goes to touch her nose.)
Here he goes.
(He falls down.)
(He falls on the floor instead of going toward Ji Hyo.)
My goodness.
Are you okay, Sung Moon.
- Sung Moon. - You wanted to touch her face.
You wanted to touch her face.
(My poor brother)
He collapsed.
He wanted to touch your nose.
His look was so determined.
I felt it in his look.
(Sung Moon fails.)
I bet Hang Ho can do it.
- Do you want to try? - I bet he can.
He's very sensitive.
I bet he can do well.
I think he'll turn in a pretty way.
He'll be elegant.
He's very elegant.
I have a bad sense of balance.
If you succeed, you win 10 dollars.
(In that case,)
(I'll try my best.)
He's determined.
He can be cute.
Start. One.
- He's quick. - Two.
3, 4.
- 5, 6. - He turns like a ballerina.
(He looks like a dancer in Swan Lake.)
- You have 10 turns left. - 1.
- Two. - He's got it.
- Sir. - Nine.
- Go. - He's done.
- Go. - Sir.
(After making 20 turns, it's time to spread his wings.)
Sir! Oh my, I'm so dizzy.
(He remains elegant even when he's dizzy.)
(He's so adorable.)
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, Hang Ho.
You did a good job.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
- I'm really sorry. - Hang Ho.
- I'm sorry, Hang Ho. - I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.
Give it a try.
- No. - Try it now.
- I can't. - Do it now!
I get dizzy easily.
I understand. Just do it.
- You could win. - Let's go, Geun Sik.
- It's your chance. - It can be dizzy.
I get dizzy easily.
You should concentrate.
"You should concentrate"?
- Come on, Haha. - Tell us if you can't continue.
- Hold on. - Turn 20 times.
Be confident.
- What? - Is this it?
(He must grab his nose before turning.)
How do I do it?
This isn't very difficult.
- I got confused. - Come on, you can do it.
I'm ready.
Start.
Wait a minute.
(He stops.)
- 1, 2. Start. - Here I go.
That's right.
- 2. - 2.
- 3. - 3.
(Haha is nervous.)
Eight.
- Nine. - That's right.
- 11. - 11.
- He's too dizzy. - Wait.
(He falls down.)
(He can't lift his head.)
Wait a minute.
- Wait a minute. - He turned red.
Give me some time.
Wait a minute.
Come on, Geun Sik.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Give me some time.
- Stay seated. - I'm sorry.
The shoot isn't over yet.
(Why is Haha embarrassed?)
You'll have more chances.
(Jae Seok and Sae Ho win 10 dollars.)
Next is Hang Ho and Kwang Soo. What is it?
My family member is good at making high-pitched sounds.
(High-pitched sounds)
(Hang Ho is the best at making high-pitched sounds.)
Are you doing that in front of Jong Kook?
(It's a competition.)
Let's hear him.
I forgot about Jong Kook.
I had no idea.
Let's hear him. My voice is in a bad condition as I drank recently.
Hang Ho's mission is a competition of...
making high-pitched sounds. It's called Hello, Cleopatra.
Read while raising an octave for every given sentence.
Hello, Cleopatra
The best potato chips in the world
- The next person says... - Hello, Cleopatra
Yes, that's it.
He can sing an entire song in one female tone.
I'm confident that he can compete with women.
Who would like to compete with him?
- Na Eun? - Yes.
- Na Eun will try. - Okay.
Who else?
So Min.
(So Min volunteers.)
Geun Sik will do it.
- Geun Sik? That sounds good. - Yes.
I'll do it.
- Jong Kook? - How about you?
- I'll do it. - You will?
- Please stand up. - Does everyone stand up?
Stand in line.
Based on our objective judgment, we'll eliminate you...
if the tone is too low.
Here we go.
(Family members with high tones come together.)
Let's get started already.
(Will Hang Ho be able to win?)
Here we go.
Hello, Cleopatra
The best potato chips in the world
(She raises the tone by one octave.)
- Hello, Cleopatra - That's right. She raised it.
(Let's raise the tone.)
- It's going up. - The best potato chips in the world
Hello, Cleopatra
(He wants to fight with Cleopatra.)
(His voice sounds tough as if he'd steal potato chips.)
(He gets competitive.)
(Seok Jin struggles to raise the tone.)
Hello, Cleopatra
(She raises her tone with her nose.)
- Hello, Cleopatra - He sounds like a mosquito.
(He sounds like a flying potato chip.)
- There it is. - Best potato chips in the world
(Will Hang Ho raise one more octave?)
(It's an explosion of high-pitched sounds.)
He raised it.
(His high tone is unexpected.)
That's it.
(Will So Min continue to raise the tone?)
(Her eyes widen as she sings.)
(Good job, So Min.)
(Will Na Eun raise one more octave?)
(She raises many octaves.)
(Her voice is as high as a dolphin.)
(Hello)
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
(Goodbye, Cleopatra)
(He wanted to win.)
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
Goodbye.
(His voice isn't high at all.)
- He's so unlucky. - That was good.
Geun Sik was cute,
but he's very unlucky today.
The order is important.
(The order is a factor.)
(They get competitive with their high tones.)
- Hello - Wasn't that it?
(Welcome to the jungle of high-pitched sounds.)
- Sae Ho? - Yes?
Get ready, set, go.
(He makes a face.)
(Sae Ho barely succeeds.)
(Hello)
- Let's see. - He's eliminated.
(Goodbye until the next mission.)
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
He's definitely eliminated.
You're eliminated. Have a seat.
(Seok Jin is eliminated.)
(She sings in a high tone.)
That sounds good.
- Jong Kook is next. - This is...
- too difficult. - It's too hard.
(Ji Hyo's tone makes him nervous.)
I can't do it.
(Men can't compete with women.)
I can't.
(He can't go any higher.)
Next is Hang Ho.
Shall I pinch you?
Raise my voice.
- Shall I pinch you? - Harder, harder
That's right.
(He bites him.)
Cleopatra
(His pinching is very effective.)
(The best potato chips in the world)
You made it.
- He made it. - You made it.
You really made it.
- He did it. - You did it, Hang Ho.
Do it one more time.
So Min?
(Singing nonsense)
I can't make out the words.
You are eliminated.
(It was impossible to understand her.)
You were incredible.
Did it hurt?
Na Eun.
Let's go.
(How will Na Eun do?)
(I can easily hit the high notes.)
(The diva makes everyone speechless.)
The best potato chips in the world
(Her voice goes beyond Yeoncheon, and moves the universe.)
(The universal diva's potato chip music)
(Sae Ho is determined to perform as well as her.)
(Singing nonsense)
(He is eliminated without a word.)
- I raised my voice high enough. - You are eliminated.
You are eliminated.
This is incredible.
We will see an end to this.
(The last 3 people)
Na Eun, Ji Hyo,
- and Hang Ho. - Why don't we have them sing...
- in the highest pitch in turns? - That's a good idea.
Let's begin.
Since all of you are very good at this,
you will be eliminated right away if you sing in the same pitch.
Hang Ho, you need to do well.
Let's start with Ji Hyo.
Hello, Cleopatra
- Hello - That's wrong.
- You are out. - You are out.
I can't do it.
Ji Hyo, you are out.
Two people remain.
- Beat one more person. - Na Eun and Hang Ho.
- Beat Na Eun. - Two people remain.
We need 10 dollars.
(10 dollars and their pride are on the line.)
Let's start with Hang Ho. Please begin.
(They go back and forth.)
(I can't back down.)
Hello, Cleopatra
(Her vocal cords know no limits.)
(Approaching)
If you fail, you will be eliminated.
(Hang Ho's muse, Kwang Soo, is on standby.)
(A musical motif enters my mind...)
(now that my muse, Kwang Soo, is protecting me.)
Hello
(This is the moment I hit high notes like magic.)
(He knows when to stop his muse.)
You did it.
- His voice went higher. - Do it one more time.
- His voice went higher. - That's it.
- His voice went higher. Na Eun. - Hang Ho.
You can do it, Na Eun.
Unleash your voice.
(She does it again.)
(I can't make my voice go higher.)
She sounded like a dolphin.
- She sounded like a dolphin. - A dolphin.
- This is the last round. - How did she do that?
Hang Ho.
If you fail, you will be eliminated.
(This artist refuses to lose to a petite girl.)
(Both the artist and the muse want to win.)
(Screaming)
(Hello, hey, Kwang Soo!)
(Like a dolphin at the sea, Hang Ho sings of freedom.)
Hey, Kwang Soo!
(He taps out because of the pain.)
He sang in the same pitch. It was the same.
- Na Eun won. - Na Eun won.
(Na Eun wins 10 dollars.)
Now, Seok Jin will announce his family member's specialty.
I will announce his specialty.
My family member, Soo Yong,
- can't feel pain. - You are lying.
I am serious.
(Soo Yong's specialty is withstanding pain.)
We will test his ability to withstand pain...
with sideburn-pulling.
Sideburn-pulling.
Why don't you stand up and have a sideburn-pulling match?
- Jae Seok, do you want to go first? - Shall I go first?
- Sure. - Will you be okay?
- You can't withstand pain well. - Yes, I can.
It's my specialty.
Didn't you know?
You look like you are in pain already.
I am not.
- You should give up. - I withstand pain very well.
Tell them about the car accident.
A car that was going 40km per hour hit me once.
(What kind of a story will it be?)
- What happened? - I brushed myself off.
(What is he talking about?)
You didn't feel pain.
You withstood the pain.
(He brushed himself off, and said, "I am fine, thank you, and you?")
You withstood pain.
You should have gone...
- to a hospital. - The car suffered...
12,000 dollars' worth of damage.
- Soo Yong was fine. - Really?
I paid for the damage.
- You weren't like that in the past. - Did you pay for the damage?
You didn't feel pain.
I can withstand any level of pain.
(Is the legend about Soo Yong true?)
Get ready. Set.
- Go. - Beat at least five people.
That's right.
(Is it true that Soo Yong can't feel pain?)
(Screaming)
He can really withstand pain.
It was true.
He hurt my feelings.
(He really doesn't feel pain.)
His facial expression didn't change.
Who wants to go next?
Geun Sik will go.
Geun Sik can withstand pain well.
- He can withstand it very well. - Isn't he too strong?
Isn't he the one who couldn't touch your nose?
- He is very patient. - That's good.
I think he will win.
(It's a real match this time.)
(He is determined to restore his pride.)
I think he will win.
Excuse me. Is this a fight?
(It's not a fight.)
- Don't do that. - This isn't a fight.
- Don't do that. - Make sure you pull lightly.
Don't lift him up by his sideburns.
(I don't know what pain is.)
- Grab what you can. - It's painful.
(The man who doesn't feel pain, Kim Soo Yong)
Let's get 10 dollars.
(The man with patience, Park Geun Sik)
10 dollars matter, Soo Yong.
(The two men have a showdown for their pride.)
Go.
Wait a minute.
I pulled out his hair. What should I do?
(Pulling out)
(Soo Yong remains calm.)
(Flustered)
You pulled out his hair.
(Soo Yong's hair sends everyone into a frenzy.)
What should we do? What should we do?
- You lost. - What should we do?
(Soo Yong wins thanks to Geun Sik's foul play.)
You lost.
(Why do we feel bad for him even though he earned 10 dollars?)
(The rain doesn't subside.)
Next up are...
Se Chan and Na Eun.
Okay.
My wannabe family member's specialty is...
Drawing Quiz.
(Na Eun's specialty is Drawing Quiz.)
We will test Na Eun's skills...
by playing Drawing Quiz within the time limit of 100 seconds.
The team that gets the most number of answers will win.
- Okay. - All right.
They will go first.
I will pick a theme.
Let's take a look. What did you pick, Na Eun?
(The theme is profession.)
- Number 7. - Number 7.
- Get ready. - Let's go, Na Eun.
Set,
go.
(Nurse)
(She draws without hesitation.)
Doctor. Nurse.
Correct.
All right.
She draws the most important things.
Baseball player.
- Correct. - Baseball player.
- She is good. - I can see it from here.
(He gets the answers right away.)
- Basketball player. - Correct.
She draws very quickly.
She can draw very well.
(Na Eun's drawings are simple and straightforward.)
- Teacher. - Good.
Time's up.
(100 seconds are up.)
(Se Chan and Na Eun get 4 questions right.)
We didn't win once.
I will do my best.
(Let's win this time.)
- We lost so many times. - Number one.
- Get ready. - What's the theme?
The theme is proverbs.
- What? - Proverbs are hard.
(Why does it have to be proverbs?)
(Will they be able to draw the proverbs?)
Set. Go.
(He who steals a needle will steal an ox.)
(Look at the needle.)
A needle...
(Yes, it's a needle. Give me the answer.)
"A needle makes a treasure."
(He is confident.)
(He combines different proverbs.)
Isn't it "beads"?
"A needle makes a treasure."
(There is a similar proverb.)
Isn't it "beads"?
"Beads make a treasure."
Move onto the next question.
What a fool! I am sorry.
For goodness' sake.
It is about a needle.
"It's hard to go through the eye of a needle."
(I think this one is the answer.)
(It's hard to go through the eye of a needle.)
(It's hard indeed.)
This is hilarious.
- Pass. - Pass.
Here comes the next one.
This is driving me crazy.
(Birds listen during the day, and mice listen during the night.)
This is hilarious.
You are doing well.
Shout out your guesses. Don't sit still.
(This proverb is easy to draw.)
He will get this one right.
Mice listen during the day, and birds listen during the night.
(He switches the subjects.)
My goodness.
Please be quiet.
(You are almost there. Just switch the subjects.)
(Birds come out during the day.)
(I get it.)
The sun and a bird.
(The sun and a bird)
(The sun and a bird?)
(It is a sun and a bird indeed.)
Pass. Just move on.
- Pass. - Pass it.
Pass. It's not a sun and a bird.
(Geun Sik makes up a new proverb.)
There.
Go ahead.
It's not a sun and a bird.
He's awesome.
Go. Good.
Share every last bit.
That's not it.
"Share every last bit."
Why?
(You spray it on the rice.)
The rice...
(He got it.)
(You rain...)
Seasoning with rice.
(What on earth are you talking about?)
(Geun Sik thinks the seasoning goes great with rice.)
Go back.
- I... - Seasoning...
- I don't know any proverbs. - It's all right.
I don't know any.
We can do this.
(It looks like legs and arms.)
I don't know what this is. A dining table?
He loves eating, doesn't he?
Is he hungry?
He loves to eat.
Those are legs.
Say it.
Don't put your legs on the table.
What's that?
(He gives a life lesson instead of guessing a proverb.)
That's it.
(Haha and Geun Sik run out of time.)
- Geun Sik. - Today,
he mentioned the sun and the bird...
and seasoning with rice.
Give them a round of applause.
(Geun Sik is eternally respected.)
- He's a nice guy. - He's very nice.
- He's an angel. - He really is.
- There are only movies left. - These are movies.
Really? Movies?
- Movies? - Yes.
Ready. Go.
("Spider Man")
This one's relatively easy.
It's easy.
(It's easy if you draw the right things.)
What is that?
Sae Ho is very bad at drawing.
Look at his drawing.
What's that? A waffle?
It looks delicious.
No?
(Why don't you get this?)
- Please be quiet. - Pass.
- What? - Why don't you get this?
- I don't know. - How can you not get this?
Pass. Why don't you get it?
I don't know.
(The next question is...)
- "The Little Mermaid". - This one is hard.
(What's the next question?)
It's scary.
It is.
(It's scary.)
(What's that? A horror movie?)
I made eye contact with it.
(The Beauty looks very troubled.)
- "Hellraiser". - I made eye contacts with it too.
- Pass. - "Hellraiser".
- You don't know this? - What are you doing?
- Hurry. - Does one team...
Hurry, Sae Ho.
- What's that? - What is that?
(What's this now?)
(You haven't seen this before, right?)
I made eye contact with it again.
Please.
(What is that ugly thing?)
It keeps on glaring at me.
- Turn it around. - It's glaring at me.
Don't make it scary.
Make it look happier.
(Sae Ho doesn't get why Jae Seok is not getting it.)
Pass. Why doesn't he know this?
("The Man from Nowhere")
Hurry, Sae Ho.
You don't have to be so detailed.
Sae Ho...
- What's that? - What is that?
What's this?
(He keeps on drawing ugly pictures.)
What are you doing?
That's...
- What's that? - Pass.
(They didn't get anything right before running out of time.)
What's this?
- What movie was that? - It was "The Man from Nowhere".
- Wait. - Wait. How's this the same movie?
Don't you know the scene...
where Won Bin was sick?
(Don't you know the scene where Won Bin was sick?)
(They don't look alike at all.)
You should have drawn the hair trimmer.
You were supposed to draw the hair trimmer.
Look at what he drew before that.
- What's this? - Try to guess.
- It's easy. - What's this?
It's obviously "200 Pound Beauty".
(He's so confident.)
- It's obvious. - I guess that's Kim A Joong.
(She looks like she's in a lot of pain.)
If I drew it, you would have gotten it right away.
Try drawing this then.
This is easy.
You don't need to take your time with it.
- It's "200 Pound Beauty". - My gosh.
"200 Pound Beauty".
(It looks exactly like "200 Pound Beauty".)
I think it's "200 Pound Beauty".
That's "200 Pound Beauty".
("200 Pound Beauty")
- "200 Pound Beauty". - I'll guess. "200 Pound Beauty".
- What about "Ju-On"? - What?
That one's too easy.
- You need somebody crying. - It's scary.
("Ju-On" doesn't take much effort.)
It's Toshio.
- That looks like "Ju-On". - Exactly.
(It's like looking at a poster.)
(I guess this is how you draw.)
I'm sorry then.
(You're supposed to draw like me.)
- I should have drawn. - I'm sorry.
It's all right, Sae Ho.
Too bad.
(Se Chan and Na Eun win 10 dollars.)
This time, let's go with Ji Hyo's family.
Sung Moon.
Sung Moon says...
he's good at kicking.
- Kicking? - Yes, I...
- Kicking? - Did you play soccer?
- He was a soccer player. - He was.
He went abroad for it.
(Sung Moon is number 1 in kicking.)
- The machine. - I know this one.
(It's a soccer game.)
There's a machine for this.
(The person with the highest score wins.)
- Let's see Sung Moon first. - Sure.
- He's different from amateurs. - Exactly.
Let's go, Sung Moon.
I bet he's good.
Ready.
- Sung Moon. - Let's go.
(4 months ago in Mapo-gu)
(He kicked his sister on the streets.)
(You have to do the same, brother.)
Set. Go.
(He only gets one chance.)
(He gathers up every ounce of energy he has.)
(It's a powerful kick.)
(The score keeps on going up.)
- My goodness. - That was amazing.
(What's his score?)
He broke the record.
(It's the best score.)
This is the best score on the machine.
- He kicked it well. - It's the best score.
He got 605 points.
(Sung Moon gets 605 points.)
Who would like to try?
- Jong Kook would. - Let's see how good he is.
(He doesn't look like an easy opponent.)
His phone dropped.
He's getting excited.
Like this.
(If you get kicked by him, you'll die.)
All right. He plays recreational soccer a lot.
- You've played a lot. - Right.
He's not good, but he loves it.
I'll do this.
- Be careful. - Okay.
- You never know. - I'll give it a try.
(He looks very threatening.)
(Will he get a higher score than Sung Moon?)
(He kicks it.)
He's going to break the machine.
(They are in awe.)
He's strong.
My body didn't go forward.
It should have. My body didn't go forward.
(Sung Moon is currently in 1st place.)
(Will he be able to keep his spot?)
I should have gone forward.
(Jong Kook gets 595 points. He doesn't beat Sung Moon.)
Sung Moon won.
If you can't get past 605 points, Sung Moon and his sister...
will take 10 dollars. Who'd like to try next?
(I'll break the record.)
It's finally Wook Min's turn.
He's strong.
- I... - I have a feeling he'll win.
- I had surgery on my right leg. - What?
- I had surgery on my right leg. - Can you use your left leg?
- I will. - Be careful.
- I will use my left leg. - Sure.
- Do you play soccer? - No.
- You don't? - No.
- By the way, he's very handsome. - He is.
I think he's the most handsome out of everybody here.
He looks better than celebrities.
I feel kind of...
sad about it.
He's the most handsome here.
I mean it.
He's the best one here.
- I feel like his left is strong. - Can I go?
- Let's get that 10 dollars. - 10 dollars?
- You like money. - Please go ahead.
(Would his leg muscles be as good as his face?)
(Kicking)
(He smashes it with his left leg.)
That was good.
He went over.
He did.
(Would it be higher than 605 points?)
(Wook Min gets 641 points.)
(He's in 1st place.)
It's his left leg.
(He got such a high score with his left leg.)
- I'm right-footed. - And he even used his left foot.
This is unbelievable.
He put his weight on it.
(He's currently on top.)
The Black Shadow Geun Sik is next.
I think you can do it.
- You can. - Geun Sik.
- Can you pull up your pants? - No.
Up to now, he's... Wait.
(Hey, hold on.)
- That's it. - What's wrong?
- Wasn't I supposed to kick? - It's high.
- Go again. - Listen to him first.
- You don't play soccer, do you? - No.
- I've never played soccer. - All right.
Are you feeling confident?
- This is my first time. - Really?
He's never used this machine before,
but within our group of friends,
- he's the king of foot volleyball. - Is that right?
His nickname is Foot Volleyball.
Because he's good at it?
He's really good. I'm serious.
- Are you Park Foot Volleyball? - Yes, that's me.
- All right. - It looks good.
Be serious. Hey, let's make this one look cool.
(He bets his name on it.)
(He's going for it!)
(Roaring)
(What's his score?)
- It was good. - His weight wasn't on it.
- It wasn't. - Same here.
Too bad.
You aren't good.
(He gets 590 points.)
(It looked cool, but he doesn't get 1st place.)
So...
- So... - You're so sexy.
Thank you.
He's very sexy today.
I agree.
Wook Min is starting to show off now.
"I even kicked with my left foot."
(He copies Wook Min.)
"I got surgery on my right leg."
He kept on showing off.
- It was good before that. - He says things like that.
He's the best right now.
(Today's guests are competitive.)
- This... - It isn't easy.
- This isn't easy to beat. - I don't know how to feel about it.
Next is So Min's family.
- My brother is good at... - What is it?
arm wrestling.
(Wook Min is number 1 in arm wrestling.)
(He looks like he's good.)
He looks like he's really good.
Let's not try.
Hang Ho's never lost in arm wrestling.
Really?
I'm right.
It's because I've never done it before.
I'm serious. He won't show off.
- He's just modest. - I'm not.
Sae Ho has a family of strong men too.
- My family? - Yes.
- My family has strong men? - Yes.
His family is. It runs in his family.
How did you know that?
Geun Sik is confident about this one.
- He's strong too. - He is.
Should we do a tournament within the group?
- We should. - That would be better.
Wook Min hurt his right hand, so he'll use his left.
- His left? - Yes.
- Then, - It's okay.
use your left hand in the final round.
For the preliminary, use whatever hand you prefer.
It's okay.
Let's do this, Geun Sik.
- I'm not sure. - I'm certain.
I can't.
Let's start the first round.
It's between Se Chan and Soo Yong.
(It's between Soo Yong and Se Chan.)
Go, Se Chan.
I'm bad at arm wrestling.
- Ready. - He has a big hand.
Look at him.
Ready.
Se Chan is pretty strong.
It might be a surprise.
- Se Chan is strong. - This is a preliminary.
He's too strong.
Ready.
You have to win, Soo Yong.
(Who will be the winner?)
Set. Go.
Se Chan wins.
(He wins right away.)
(She's impressed.)
- He's strong. - Look at Soo Yong.
Next... Na Eun is across from you.
He's much stronger with her across from him.
Am I doing okay, Na Eun?
(I can keep winning for you.)
Next is Hang Ho and Sae Ho.
As I mentioned, he has a family of strong men.
Hang Ho has never lost before.
- Really? - Yes.
All right. Ready.
(It's a legendary match up.)
Good.
- Look at his grip. It's different. - Ready.
Set.
Set...
(Hang Ho has never lost before,)
(and Sae Ho is from a family of strong men.)
(Who will win?)
Go.
(That was quick.)
(Who's the winner?)
He's so strong.
I thought you won.
It sounded like you won.
Is it over?
(Is this really over?)
Set. Go.
(Shouting)
(It ends in 1 second.)
I don't think the match started yet.
It's between Sung Moon and Geun Sik.
He's got the strongest bones in Mapo-gu.
- Is that right? - He has strong bones.
- Ready. - Would you be all right?
Sung Moon is an athlete.
- He used to be. - Ready.
Let's cheer for them.
Let's go.
(It's between the soccer player and the king of foot volleyball.)
- Ready. - It'll be great if Sung Moon wins.
(Will it be Sung Moon in his 20s...)
(or the invincible Geun Sik?)
(What will be the result of the 3rd match?)
Go.
He's so good.
(Geun Sik wins in a second.)
- Geun Sik wins. - That was fast.
(Haha and Geun Sik take their first win.)
This is the first time I won something here.
Next is Se Chan...
(It's between Se Chan...)
(and Jong Kook.)
You never know.
Show him, Se Chan.
If you win this one... Na Eun is watching you.
- All right? - The table might get lifted.
Na Eun.
Ready.
Hold on. Wait, Jong Kook.
What's wrong?
(His grip is already strong.)
Show him the strength of a comedian.
- Let's win. - Look at his arm.
These are not vessels. They're electrical wires.
They are wires.
Set.
He's different. He's a rock.
We can do it.
- Let's go. - Se Chan...
(Let's go, Se Chan.)
(Na Eun is watching.)
Set. Go.
Goodness.
That hurts, Jong Kook.
(Too much confidence might give you pain sometimes.)
That hurts. You knew I wasn't strong.
- He was too strong. - You knew from the start.
I wanted to end it fast.
- You knew I was weak. - Right now...
I'm sorry.
- Jong Kook wins. - I didn't know it would hurt.
- I'm sorry. - That was a good one.
- I'm sorry. - He's a rock.
- Next is... - He's really strong, right?
- He is. - Geun Sik...
and Hang Ho.
(It's between Hang Ho and Geun Sik.)
You never know.
- Jong Kook is so strong. - Hang Ho.
I'm serious.
He's a natural.
- In what? - In using strength.
- Is he? - He is.
He's a strong guy.
(Hang Ho hasn't lost so far.)
- This is intense. - This is intense.
I can feel their energy.
(They're both on a winning streak.)
You never know.
(Who will win?)
Set. Go.
(Did Geun Sik defend himself...)
(from Hang Ho's surprise attack?)
(Groaning)
(Hang Ho wins again.)
What happened?
Okay.
- Why did you lose? - He's strong.
(What do you mean why?)
He's really strong.
I only win once.
Hang Ho wins.
(Hang Ho wins twice in a row.)
You never know how it'll turn out.
Why are you so good?
Before we get to the finals,
it'll be between Hang Ho and Jong Kook.
(It's between Jong Kook and Hang Ho.)
If he beats Jong Kook, it'll be insane.
He doesn't exercise,
and he's worked out for over 20 years.
There's no correlation between working out and arm wrestling.
This is incredible.
He's so firm.
He's soft.
(Hang Ho is soft.)
He's a soft tofu.
His vessels are like water pipes.
- This is incredible. - Right? He has water pipes.
This was unexpected.
He's chubby.
- How's that possible? - Ready.
- He's incredible. - Like Jong Kook said,
arm wrestling is unpredictable.
We came this far, Hang Ho.
- Hang Ho. - We can't lose now.
(The winner of this match...)
(face the champion in the last match.)
Go.
(Groaning)
(Jong Kook is...)
(on another level.)
(Jong Kook defeats Hang Ho.)
Jong Kook wins.
- Good job, Hang Ho. - I can't face him.
This is the final match.
- Now, - This is the real deal.
- it's the final match. - It is.
(They're both strong.)
(This is the big match.)
(Will it be Jong Kook, the tiger of Running Man?)
This is like an international match.
Look at these two.
(Or will it be muscular Wook Min?)
They're both professionals.
(It's tense around here.)
Look at his hip.
Look. Look at his hip.
- He's strong. - Look.
(There's tension between them.)
- This... - They're so strong.
- Ready. - They're like beasts.
(What will be the result of the legendary match?)
(They focus all their energy.)
(It's a counterattack from the families.)
(You can never stop them.)
(It's not over until it's over?)
(You'll survive if you unite...)
(and die if you split up.)
(It's the 2nd episode of the 7th anniversary special.)
(When in Running Man,)
(do as Running Man members do.)
(It's unbelievable and extraordinary.)
(This is as good as a variety show can get.)
(Family Outing)