(This is Running Man's global project of 2017.)
(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by bloggers)
(Shark cage, USA)
(Cage of Death, Australia)
(Fly Toledo, Spain)
(Active volcano in Mount Bromo and Mount Ijen, Indonesia)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan)
(Nevis Swing, New Zealand)
(Insano water slide, Brazil)
(Three Tour Stickers will earn them a trip to the tourist attraction.)
Haha and Se Chan!
(The war of Tour Stickers gets fiercer and fiercer.)
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo are piling up the stickers.)
(Today, even more Tour Stickers will pour out.)
(Who will be sent on the dangerous trip?)
(Ulsan is an important port for the Korean industry...)
(and is a hot place for whale-watching.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(10am, Jangsaengpo Port﻿, Ulsan)
- We're in Ulsan. - Yes.
This is the second part of...
Global Project Part Five, Dangerous Choices.
(By the way,)
(where are Seok Jin and Kwang Soo?)
Before they got on the ferry, Seok Jin and Kwang Soo...
did something in relation to today's mission.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo received a mission?)
They had to guess whether they'd spot dolphins or not.
(They had to guess.)
That was it.
If their choice was right,
they'll be given five dollars.
(If Seok Jin and Kwang Soo's choice is right, they get 5 dollars.)
They get five dollars?
I'll provide you the same situation.
Choose if Seok Jin and Kwang Soo got to watch the dolphins or not.
(Did they get to watch the dolphins or not?)
(5 hours before the shoot at Jangsaengpo Port)
(It's the beginning of their mission to watch dolphins.)
Good morning.
Hi. Hello.
What did Kwang Soo do to deserve this?
(He's here only because Seok Jin chose him.)
Currently, Seok Jin already has three Tour Stickers.
- Already? - Right.
Kwang Soo, you have two.
It's not fair for me.
- I came here because of you. - I'm sorry.
I may end up getting a penalty because of you.
- You're ruining my life now. - Hey.
Before we move on, let's guess how the results will turn out.
If you succeed in guessing, you get five dollars.
- Whether we'll see dolphins? - Yes.
We won't be able to.
(What?)
We need to be realistic on this.
- I choose that we'll be able to. - If it happens, I'll get...
- the money and the penalty too. - Look.
(He'll be getting the penalty.)
(Even if he sees dolphins, his life seems so miserable.)
- What's good for me then? - You...
It'll be just taking the ship for no reason.
- If we don't get to see dolphins... - I'm pretty sure we won't.
I'll just choose that we'll see them.
- Both of you did your bet. - All right.
I need to see them no matter what.
(After 1 hour)
- There are the dolphins! - Yes!
(They face a pod of dolphins.)
- Look. - Come back!
- They're right in front of us. - Hey!
(The miracle of nature made them forget about the mission.)
My gosh, it's amazing.
- It doesn't make sense. - It's crazy.
(Dance with the dolphins.)
- My gosh. - This is really happening now.
It's real.
(The dolphins don't seem to care at all about their going crazy.)
- Don't shoot me! - There they are!
You need to capture them with your cameras!
- Hey, film them! - Not me! I'm just a mere person.
- They're right in front of us! - They're following us!
- You can't remain calm about this. - Everyone!
I'm witnessing the horrible... I mean,
- the magnificent moment now! - It's happening now.
Due to the time limit, we will finish the tour here...
and move back to the port now.
- What? - No way!
- What? - Not a chance!
(They said goodbye to the dolphins and moved back to the port.)
I'm pretty sure I was a dolphin in my past life.
(I'll be back, my dolphin friends.)
- I'll announce the results now. - Okay!
Seok Jin and Kwang Soo.
You saw the dolphins despite the low possibility.
(They came, they watched, and they completed the mission.)
Our hard work paid off.
- Right! - Dolphins!
You each acquired the No Tour Card...
and five dollars for the mission.
(They acquired 5 dollars each along with the No Tour Card.)
You need to keep this to yourselves when you join the members.
(Now, it's time for the members to guess what happened.)
How should I fix my face expression? Should I be upset?
You can't look disappointed, you know.
Let's just be expressionless.
(They need to fool the other members.)
What do you plan to do?
I...
(They're known to be horrible actors.)
I should just stare into the abyss like this.
- How about we just be all excited? - What?
(If you're not confident in acting, just be yourself.)
That'd be weird too.
- Either way would be weird. - Well...
- I can't just lie. - You know,
we're just not good at...
fooling others.
I'll bet my five dollars on not being able to fool them.
I'll bet my entire fortune on it.
They'll find out for certain.
- I'm sure. - I'll bet my Tour Sticker on it.
(The duo arrives, being certain of failing the mission.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
From now on, you need to do whatever it takes...
to fool them.
- How does my face look now? - Your face?
(I do...)
(have a secret.)
You're making it too obvious.
(I'm sorry, but everyone will know you're acting.)
- Is it okay? - You look like you're acting.
You're making it too obvious.
Should I be natural?
That's it. That's the right look.
- There they are. - They're...
(Will they successfully fool the others?)
(At the same time)
Choose if Seok Jin and Kwang Soo got to watch the dolphins or not.
We'll provide you with five dollars each if your decision is correct.
(They get 5 dollars for guessing it right.)
- I think the dolphins came out. - Me too.
But it was too early. Dolphins sleep at night too.
(Will they be able to acquire the money?)
They're here.
(The dolphin duo is back, pretending not to know.)
- What happened? - Did you see them?
- They must've gone through much. - They seem bright.
I don't think they got a Sticker. I think they saw the dolphins.
Am I being natural now?
(We're not being obvious, right?)
- Right? - We're natural enough.
They're walking confidently.
They must have seen them.
Seok Jin's footsteps are light.
You'll say you saw them, right?
Yes, I will.
- What happened? - Did you see them?
- They don't look bright. - They look depressed.
- We saw them. - What?
- We did. - We saw them.
You're lying.
- We really did. - Don't lie.
Did you take pictures?
You need to prove us.
- Of course, we did. - Is that right?
That was an amazing experience.
- What was? - We took pictures.
(They sound like they saw the dolphins, but they look awkward.)
How did the dolphins look?
- They're unbelievable. - You wouldn't believe it.
- They were long. - As long as that ship.
You wouldn't have been able to see their whole body.
They jumped.
- They jumped? - So you didn't see them.
Were they bouncing on a trampoline or what?
- I did. - I saw at least 3,000 of them.
No way.
Your acting is awful now.
(You must've forgotten, but I'm an actor.)
You must be...
- in good condition today. - I actually am.
(Right when Kwang Soo's acting skills are brought up...)
What color were they?
(All of a sudden)
(They all have the same color.)
Are you sure your question was sharp?
So Min is stressing us out.
I've been watching her until now,
and she keeps having suspicions on everything.
(In alert)
(20 minutes before the shoot)
(Tap)
(Glancing)
(Is there a secret mission?)
I guess you're tapping me for a reason.
- Is it not? - Are you suspicious?
(On guard)
(She's focused too much on Running Man.)
I tried to help her with the mic, and she went like this.
(Here's another tip-off.)
- Yesterday as well. - While I was on the phone...
with Se Chan, she suddenly cut in and suspected if it was me.
"I think you're not." And I said I'm Kwang Soo.
- And she wanted me to swear. - She wanted to talk to him.
- She told me to swear. - Why would you want him to swear?
(I said I'm right!)
Then she asked why I swore at her.
But she told me to swear.
- It really happened. - It's true.
- Really. - So Min is weird.
- She is not ordinary. - You're right.
I don't understand her.
Well, is our opening going to be longer today?
- Why? - I'm a bit tired.
- Make sure you prepare... - I'm exhausted.
a stretcher to carry him.
I'm going crazy now.
His mouth is going very dry.
(Pale)
I was fortunate to watch those dolphins though.
(Very unnatural)
(What is he saying?)
I was fortunate to watch those dolphins though.
- That is strange. - So you didn't see them.
(They become sure that they didn't get to see the dolphins.)
(Is he trying to pull a trick?)
- He saw it. - He did.
- He did. - He's just making it not natural.
- They did. - Was it too obvious?
(I'm sorry.)
He shouldn't have said things like that.
(This guy is such a trouble maker.)
Was it obvious?
How should we decide?
Just take turns in saying you choose whether they saw or not.
For your information, the money is very important for today's mission.
(The money will be an important variable for today's race.)
I'll go first. They saw the dolphins!
I know Seok Jin and Kwang Soo too much.
I choose they didn't succeed.
- They succeeded. - They did.
I knew from the beginning.
- What? - They succeeded.
- They didn't. - The two women chose differently.
- All men chose... - They chose that the two saw it.
(They have finished choosing whether the two succeeded in the mission.)
I'll reveal the answer now.
We got aboard the ship at 5am.
The captain commented they might see the dolphins...
as the weather and the waves were nice.
In fact, the possibility was only 20 percent, so we took an hour...
- to wait for the dolphins. - Can I change?
You can change your decision.
- Can you change now? - Let's have a final time to think.
Okay, this is your last chance.
(It's their last chance to choose.)
- Will you change? - Will you?
- You should change. - Do it.
(Thinking carefully, I realized the possibility is very low.)
Change it while you're at it.
(What is Jae Seok's decision?)
They succeeded.
- What? - What was all that for?
- What's wrong? - It's such a waste of time.
Why would you waste the tapes?
- You spoiled the mood. - Seriously.
Why don't you go further? Spoil it even more.
- What was that for? - It took us an hour.
I don't care what you choose. Just finish it quickly.
(I can't stand this anymore.)
Did you sing at a karaoke room last night?
Tell us whether you saw the dolphins or not.
(Well)
I'll give you one last chance.
- That makes us certain. - That's it.
- There we go. - They saw it.
(That made us clear.)
I told you they're bad at acting.
I'm now 100 percent sure of it.
I will tell you.
They saw the dolphins.
(The two girls failed in guessing.)
- Okay. - I told you.
- Yes. - We were right.
(They're envious.)
- It was just amazing. - So you saw the dolphins.
I shouted too much that my voice is gone.
(They still can't believe they encountered them.)
- I'm so jealous. - It wasn't just one dolphin.
Thus, except for So Min and Ji Hyo,
the members will take five dollars each.
(The male members gain 5 dollars.)
If Kwang Soo didn't say the last thing,
- I fell for Jae Seok's trick. - I was going to change my guess.
Right.
Here are the rules for today.
Today's race is called Dangerous Choices Part Two.
The project for choosing a dangerous tourist attraction...
that you want to go to before you die will be over today.
- We just need to survive today. - Is that so?
Let's do a lot today.
As the last day, many Tour Stickers will be given out today.
My goodness.
Who wants to come with me?
- You should go over there. - I must go.
- Kwang Soo should go too. - Not me.
- You have two stickers. - Jae Seok should go too.
I only have one. We don't know how it will turn out.
- Haha is at risk. - I only have one.
Seok Jin is definitely going, right?
He should get some rest instead.
(He tries to be considerate.)
- We'll call him later. - Right.
However, we don't know what will happen.
He might go on two tours.
During each mission,
you may gain or lose the mission fee depending on your choice.
With the final mission fee you have,
you may buy Tour Stickers or Reflecting Cards.
(It's possible to buy these two.)
(Will that be a chance to turn the tables?)
You can put the Sticker on another member to change their final fate.
(You can stick it on another member.)
You can give it to someone.
- After buying it? - You can give it to someone.
(Who will get the last laugh?)
(Gain mission fees to have the power to change who goes to the tour.)
(With more money, you can buy more Tour Stickers and Reflecting Cards.)
I will make it happen.
(Buy Tour Stickers and send others on a dangerous tour.)
Here's the first mission where you can earn your mission fee.
It's called Dangerous Wallets.
- What's that? - Do we choose wallets?
Among Running Man staff members,
pick one person who you think has the most cash.
Ask for his or her wallet.
We'll give you the same amount of money as the amount of cash...
- in the wallet. - Is Director Park Chan Hee here?
I choose Director Ha.
(They look for rich-looking staff.)
- By the way, - I choose Director Ha.
people don't carry much cash these days.
(It won't be easy to find cash.)
(Who will have the most cash in their wallet?)
Wait a minute.
Director Ha, do you only have your card?
I bet that's the case.
Do cameramen have cash on them?
- I don't think so. - I'm just asking.
Cameramen could easily drop their wallets.
- They wouldn't carry cash. - That's true.
I bet they only have their cards.
Kwon Ryeol doesn't bring any cash on the day of the shoot.
Gi Jin, do you have cash?
I've seen him carry cash before.
Do you have some cash?
(Who has the most cash?)
Do you have cash?
Everyone looks so poor today.
(Everyone seems broke.)
Goodness.
Everyone seems broke today.
How about you?
Do you have cash? I know who.
Wait, who is managing the production fee?
Here he is.
Ju Yong.
(The manager of production fee must have a lot of cash.)
(Lee Ju Yong)
I picked him.
There he is.
Ju Yong should have a lot of cash.
Gosh, I see many 50-dollar bills.
Hyung Min, do you have your wallet?
May I borrow it?
(Park Hyung Min)
Director Ha, give it to me.
- It's thick. I'll give it back. - He only has cards.
Give it to me, please.
- That bag is expensive. - No.
Give me your bag.
- May I borrow your wallet? - You'll regret it.
That's fine.
It's okay. This is good enough.
May I borrow your wallet?
(Se Chan takes an assistant director's wallet.)
I must find a good one.
(Jae Seok takes time.)
People don't carry cash these days.
What about Yu Ri?
This is difficult.
I don't know what to do.
Someone unexpected may have a lot of cash.
(He ponders as he walks around.)
Wait a minute.
(While he's still confused...)
What?
(A staff member hands him his wallet.)
Were you waiting to give it to me?
(Is this a trap?)
(He voluntarily hands him his wallet.)
(Jae Seok is confused.)
Really?
(Is this a trap?)
He's telling me to trust him.
Okay, I choose this wallet.
This is crucial.
Let's check Haha's first.
- Let's take a look. - You never know.
The wallet looks empty.
(Show us your power, Director Ha.)
My goodness.
(How much cash is in the wallet?)
(Haha screams.)
(It's full of cash.)
(Director Ha is rich after all.)
He has a lot.
You're the most successful man in the Ha family.
(Haha is impressed.)
That's a lot.
That's amazing.
I never expected it.
Do you carry all of your money?
You do, don't you?
- He carries all of his money. - It's 16,
- 17, 18, 19, and 20. - Wait.
- 21, 22, 23, and 24. - No way.
- 1, 2, and 3. - I knew it.
Older people carry more cash.
(Haha gets 247 dollars.)
- This is... - That's unfair.
the power of the Ha family!
(This is the power of the Ha family.)
Next up is Se Chan.
- He picked So Yeon's wallet. - I have So Yeon's wallet.
(He takes a look inside her wallet.)
The wallet looks expensive.
- Wait. - It's expensive.
She often shops at department stores.
- Does she have many cards? - It's an expensive brand.
It's an expensive brand.
- She has no cash. - No.
(Is there any cash at all?)
Is there any cash?
She doesn't even have 10 cents.
It's completely empty.
This is the worst.
It's the last leaf.
(Empty wallets look sophisticated.)
Se Chan gets zero mission fee.
Whose wallet do you have?
- He's so unlucky. - I have...
- Writer Yu Ri's wallet. - Yu Ri?
She has 30 dollars.
- It's 30 dollars. - It's something at least.
- How about So Min? - Whose wallet do you have?
I have Ju Yong's wallet.
He always pays for our meals.
- It's 17 and 18. - Gosh, So Min.
- I finally have a match. - It's 1, 2, 3,
- and four. - Let's spend a lot today.
It's 184 dollars.
- I have a cameraman's wallet. - Who is it?
- Gi Jin. - Gi Jin.
He has a lot of cash.
- I didn't expect much. - How much does he have?
There's a 50-dollar bill.
It's 80 dollars.
(Jong Kook gets 80 dollars.)
Everyone knows who she is.
She is the beauty among our staff members.
- She's in charge of marketing. - Right.
I have her wallet.
That's a nice wallet.
It's a wallet you'd find in Gangnam.
Usually, long wallets have cash in them.
This wallet is the best one of all.
- This has to have cash in it. - Absolutely.
I have high hopes.
I hope it only has cards.
I'm nervous.
What's wrong? Is it thin?
- Is it just the leather? - First of all,
I saw something yellow which was a parking ticket.
(He saw something yellow which was a parking ticket.)
- That means she drives her car. - Are there checks?
She drives a car.
- Hurry up. - Is there anything on the back?
How dare she...
(Seok Jin gets angry.)
(He feels bitter and betrayed.)
Let me see.
There's no cash.
- There's no cash at all? - No.
- Wait. - There's nothing at all?
- How about on the back? - Take a look.
(It's a point card.)
The wallet is the only thing that is fancy.
(Today's lesson is empty wallets only look fancy.)
She looked so sophisticated.
How could you have no cash?
Seok Jin gets zero mission fee.
Are there any 10-dollar bills?
- He gets nothing. - Goodness.
- I can't believe there's no cash. - He's unlucky after all.
- Gosh. - He's you in 10 years.
- Seriously. - He's me in 10 years?
- I can't believe there's no cash. - He's unlucky after all.
- How about you, Kwang Soo? - I'm quite hopeful.
He's working as a manager,
- but he has his own business. - Business?
It's Hyung Min, Seok Jin's manager.
- Why him? - You can't choose his manager.
He's one of the staff members.
Hyung Min's main occupation isn't being Seok Jin's manager.
- This is his part-time job. - That's right.
Seok Jin's manager has more money than Seok Jin.
- Let's see. - Okay.
Here's his wallet.
The wallet looks like it belongs to someone poor.
- There's some cash in it. - There it is.
- There's a lot. - It's a lot.
You got lucky, Kwang Soo.
That's so little cash for someone who has his own business.
It's not 10 but 9 dollars.
(He finds 9 dollars.)
- Wait. - Is that his wallet?
Isn't this yours?
It's my wallet.
Why did you give me poor Seok Jin's wallet instead of yours?
(Why did you give me someone else's wallet?)
- Where did he go? - It's my wallet.
It turned out to be my wallet.
Finally, it's me.
He voluntarily offered his wallet to me.
That's crazy.
(A man offered his wallet to Jae Seok without being asked.)
(Jae Seok took the wallet.)
(He also offered his wallet to other members.)
(Was he simply being generous?)
Is there a lot of cash?
- Are they any? - That's not fair.
(The Pandora's box is opened.)
- That's a lot of cash. - No way.
- It's a lot of cash. - That's unfair.
Goodness. There are a lot. How much is this?
- This... - Look.
- This is getting annoying now. - Give it to me.
Oh, my.
You can't do that.
- Poor Se Chan. - Se Chan.
- This is so annoying. I mean it. - 50, 60, 70,
80, 90, and 100.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18,
- It's 191 dollars. - It's 190 dollars.
- 191 dollars. - What was it?
(I'm sorry that I have doubted you.)
(Status of mission fees)
Before we start our mission,
please freely make 2 teams of 4.
(Freely?)
- Freely? - Form your teams freely.
- People with money, come here. - All right. Wait.
(Trotting)
People who have money should be in my team.
At least one of you should come to our team.
- Hey, let me join your team. - We should...
(Everyone is trying to get the rich members into their team.)
- Seok Jin, how much do you have? - Me?
I have five dollars.
- How much do you have? - I have 180 dollars.
- She has 180 dollars. - I have 14 dollars.
- Haha. So Min! - So Min!
- So Min, come here. - So Min, come here.
- So Min, come here. - So Min, come. This is your team.
- So Min. - Come here.
- I really mean it. So Min. - They are unlucky. Come!
(Look out! They are unlucky.)
- Come here quickly! - Then let me join you.
- No. Come quickly! - You will be unlucky too.
- Then let me join you. - No.
No, we don't want you.
- Jae Seok, don't come to us. - Are you crazy?
- Hey! I have a lot of money. - Go away.
- You will be unlucky too. - That was too harsh.
- Come before you get unlucky too. - How can you say that?
- What's wrong with you? - Let go.
- What a harsh thing to say. - Let me join you.
- So Min. Hurry! Don't be unlucky. - Don't join them!
(It's best to avoid any unlucky members.)
- I can join your team. - No.
- No, go away. - I have 10 more dollars.
We don't want you. Don't touch us.
- We were the team... - Come here.
who'd survive the apocalypse.
(Don't you remember?)
(The team that will survive the apocalypse?)
(Last time, it was confirmed that they were the chosen team.)
(The remaining members were like cockroaches.)
When we're together, don't we look like a tribe?
(The members of the tribe meet again unexpectedly.)
(The tribe of the squids is reunited again.)
- Hold on a second. - Couples surviving the destruction.
- This is going to be my team? - How much do you have?
I have some money.
- I really do have some money. - Hey.
Don't you know me?
- Wait. They don't have any money. - Do you have money?
- Don't you know how much I have? - Hey, forget it.
Hey, don't regret later.
- So Min. - You called us unlucky.
- Seok Jin. Forget them. - Whatever.
- Fine. You, go ahead. - We will go then.
- Go! - What about you, Jae Seok?
(What? What about you?)
- I'll be here. - Come here. Come, Jae Seok.
- You'd better come here. - Hey, I belong in that team.
- We don't have money. - Let go of me.
- This is still an individual game. - Yes, at the end, it will be.
- Can we switch teams later on? - Of course.
- It can change. - All right.
I will take these poor members with me.
I am not poor. I am sort of in the middle.
- What? You have 19 dollars. - 19 dollar.
- It's basically nothing. - What's wrong with 19 dollars?
So have you formed your teams?
For now, yes.
The thing is that kids who have nothing to lose are scarier.
(Kids who have nothing to lose?)
- Nothing to lose? - Kids?
- Did you call us kids? - What?
It's just an expression.
Let me start now.
This mission is Dangerous 10 Seconds.
(The 2nd round is Dangerous 10 Seconds.)
What is this now?
It's a 4-against-4 quiz. Please pick a member who will figure out...
the answer after listening to only the first sentence of the quiz.
- Only the first sentence? - I am good at solving quizzes.
Only the first sentence?
I can't. I am not that fast.
When you figure out the correct answer, you'll receive 30 dollars.
(The reward will be 30 dollars?)
- Let's do this. - This is our chance.
- What a twist. - All the smart ones are here.
The member who gets the right answer can choose either...
to end the mission after having the money to themselves...
(The member can choose to end the mission and keep the money?)
- Or they can share with... - This can't be right.
This is over. We are in the clear.
(It's the best betraying environment.)
In my team, they are all traitors.
- My team... - No, don't say that.
- Is it every man for himself? - Hey, don't be like that.
The rule is that we are supposed to have the money to ourselves.
- Is that it? - That team won't survive.
(This is a game to keep the money to him or herself.)
Look who's talking. When So Min is picked, you are doomed as well.
Be quiet, you unlucky ones.
Stop. That's enough.
My team won't get past the first question.
- They are in a pit of fire. - How many questions are there?
You will have to make your decision within 10 seconds...
whether you will keep it or share it. You must decide on...
the amount as well. Say that you earned 30 dollars.
You must distribute the money. You can split it however you want.
If the member's answer is wrong,
the representative member will have to pay 20 dollars as a penalty.
Whoever answered the question?
If you're wrong, you pay 20 dollars.
We have to pay 20 dollars if we don't get the correct answer?
What about the members who don't have enough money?
- Some members have no money. - Right.
I have 19 dollars. Cut me some slack.
There is a special loan plan for the ones who have no money.
- A loan? - Hold on.
You will receive 50 dollars for 1 Tour Sticker.
(If they receive 1 Tour Sticker, they will receive 50 dollars?)
You want me to go on that trip, don't you?
- Kwang Soo and I have to go then. - I...
- With one more, I have to go. - Come on.
(It's a cruel system for Kwang Soo and Se Chan.)
Gosh, they are good.
- I am done with one more Sticker. - Goodness.
- This can't be right. - What a horrible producer.
- This doesn't make sense. - You gave up since it's over soon.
- I will have to sell my body. - For 50 dollars?
I will get 50 dollars for my body?
- You can go on that trip. - It's not 500,000 dollars.
Would we risk our lives for 50 dollars?
- If I have one more dollar... - Just go on that trip.
Please pick your representatives carefully.
Goodness, they are so cruel.
Can I pay back the loan?
If you can, you can pay it back.
- We can do that? - Yes.
If I give you 50 dollars, can you get rid of the Sticker?
- That's not possible. - It's not?
Seok Jin, don't try to get out of it. You're bound to go.
No, I heard something is there for me.
- The producer told me so. - No, just go on that trip.
He told me that there will be something.
- Seok Jin, compare the prices... - No, I don't need to.
online and look for the cheapest flight.
- He said something good will occur. - Besides,
you like researching online.
- I told you that won't happen. - Let's cheer up.
Shouldn't a member with money try the mission?
That's right. We don't have money. So Min has some.
- Right. Haha, you should try. - Will Haha try the mission?
I am not good at solving quizzes.
I will tell you the first sentence.
The quiz is about sports.
- Sports? - Michael Jordan is...
- Haha. - Go for it.
(He raises his hand immediately.)
He is considered the best basketball player in the history of 120 years.
- Okay. Haha. - Who would like to answer this?
Me.
(Haha is Running Man's official basketball genius.)
(In order to solve this quiz, he has been practicing basketball.)
- Haha will definitely get this. - He's going to get this right.
Haha, here comes the question.
He is considered the best basketball player in the history of 120 years.
If so,
- tell me five people whose names... - 1980...
have "Michael" in them.
(Who has Michael in their names?)
- Michael Jackson, Michael Bolton, - In 5, 4,
- 3, 2, 1. - Michael Jonathan.
(Michael Jonathan?)
- Who is Michael Jonathan? - Who is Michael Jonathan?
- Search it online. - Who is Michael Jonathan?
(There might be someone by that name.)
- Go back to your spot. - Haha.
- Hurry. - Hey.
- Pay 20 dollars. - Give him 20 dollars.
- Don't be so petty. - Let go of me.
- Pay him 20 dollars. - Let me go.
There aren't that many celebrities whose name is Michael.
Michael Jonathan is such a nice guy.
What does he do for a living?
Is that important?
Since you have money, spend some.
All right. Why don't you go and buy yourself something delicious.
You too. You're working hard.
All right. Pay them.
Mr. Ha.
(I love you, Mr. Ha, the source of my wealth.)
I don't think I should solve the quiz. It's hard.
- We can do this! - We can do this!
- In 1, 2, 3. Let's go! - In 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
All right, Team Unlucky.
Look at Kwang Soo. His attitude has changed.
If I know the question...
(I am going to figure this one out.)
- If I know it, I'll do it. - Me too.
(I need to make some money.)
- It's every man for himself. - I'm going to get it.
In an International A Match,
the referee decides the offense and defense with a coin of FIFA.
Hey!
(He's pushed out.)
- Jae Seok. - Hey.
You have to get this right.
- You can do it. - He'll ask FIFA's abbreviation.
(Jae Seok is selected against his will.)
It wasn't my intention to move forward.
In an International A Match,
the referee decides the offense and defense with a coin of FIFA.
If I throw a coin now, will it be heads or tails?
- Will it be heads or tails? - I knew it, Jae Seok!
- Jae Seok. - You never know.
(This is a draw of luck.)
- This is a 50-50 chance. - Seriously?
I think he might be able to get this one right.
- This is 50 to 50. - But Jae Seok won't be able to.
Don't you think so? Jae Seok...
- He is really unlucky. - If you choose, that's it.
(Heads or tails?)
Here it goes.
(That is the question.)
(If the picture is shown, it's heads.)
(If the number is shown, it's tails.)
Heads!
- It's heads! - It's heads.
- Hold on. - He'll open it like this.
(What will Jae Seok's decision be?)
- Wait. - It's heads.
(It's heads!)
It's heads. I saw it, Jae Seok. I saw it.
- I saw it, but it's tails. - Will it be heads or tails?
(He makes his decision in the midst of their trickery.)
It is...
heads!
(Jae Seok chooses heads.)
(The result is tails.)
What is it? It's tails.
(He can't even win a 50-50 chance.)
(How can you get that wrong?)
(How could you get that wrong?)
Goodness. I told you so.
- It was so close. - You are the unlucky one.
He's really horrible at judging things.
This was so close.
(Jae Seok fails to solve the quiz and pays 20 dollars.)
Here is the question. Se Chan...
earned the nickname Strawberry Yang after the last shoot.
Strawberry Yang.
- Strawberry Yang? - Se Chan, go. Money's at stake.
If I get a loan, get some money, and pay it back,
- the Sticker will disappear? - Of course.
Hold on. If I get it right, I will earn 30 dollars.
I just need 20 more dollars.
You don't want to share it with others?
I don't have the slightest intention.
(Keeping it is the only way to survive.)
I don't care about the people here.
Challenge!
(He has only 5 dollars. He can't afford a fine.)
(If he says the wrong answer, he'll be sent on the trip.)
Last week, Se Chan got the nickname Strawberry Yang.
How do you spell "strawberry" in English?
You have five seconds.
- You have five seconds. - It's an easy one.
He'll get it right.
- Hey. - It's "strawberry", right?
- Four, three, - S, T...
- Straw... S, T, O, R... - two,
one.
- S, T, O, R... - One.
Are you trying to spell "story"?
What story are you talking about?
Even I know this one.
- It's S, T, R. - You really don't know?
Are you serious?
Kwang Soo seems to know. He'll try.
- I know it. - What is it?
Try it.
- S, T... - All right.
- R... L? R. - Go on.
- A... - Come on.
R, A? Isn't it S, T, R, O?
- It's A. - W.
I'm not the only stupid one.
I want you to know. None of us know it.
Viewers,
please post the right spelling on our website.
- We'll memorize it. - We'll study hard.
Se Chan is officially going on the trip.
Se Chan will go on the Dangerous Trip.
(He has to take a loan and receives one more Sticker.)
I can pay back when I earn money, right?
Yes, then we'll take away the Sticker.
If he fails to pay back...
- He'll be sent on the trip. - I see.
(If he fails to earn 80 dollars, he'll be sent on the trip.)
Is it this team's turn now?
Yes. Let's go.
"Mamma Mia!" is a musical...
loved by many people around the world.
- Jong Kook, try. - I won't.
I think the question will be about the songs...
in the musical.
The answer will be "ABBA".
So Min, go. The answer will be "ABBA".
I know only one song by them.
Ji Hyo, go.
- I don't have enough money. - I'm sure it's something funny.
You guys can decide who should try.
Let's decide by rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Rock-paper-scissors)
(Ji Hyo and Jong Kook lose.)
Those two haven't tried yet.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Rock-paper-scissors)
(Jong Kook is trying.)
I have a feeling it's something I don't know.
Then be penalized.
"Mamma Mia!" is a musical loved by many people around the world.
What does "Mamma Mia" mean in Italian?
- I know this. - Really?
- I know this. - A: I'm happy.
B: Oh my. C: Excuse me.
- D: I'm delighted. - I know this one.
(I don't know this.)
- It's confusing. - Five, four,
- What was D? - three...
- I can say it right away. - Was it "Excuse me"?
- Two... - B: Oh my.
(He picks.)
B: Oh My.
(Is it the right answer?)
No way. I got it right?
("Oh my" was the right answer.)
- I got it right? - You were right.
Decide how you'll divide up 30 dollars in 10 seconds.
(He has to decide how to divide up 30 dollars.)
You can decide to have everything to yourself and finish the mission.
- You can also divide it up and... - This is it.
This is it.
- Please decide in 10 seconds. - Really?
I'll take everything.
(He doesn't hesitate.)
I'll take everything. I will.
Why would I divide it up?
- What are you doing? - What?
Don't you even have to think?
- We decided by rock-paper-scissors. - The mission is completed.
Why did we play rock-paper-scissors?
(Their mission is completed.)
With Jong Kook taking 30 dollars, you guys are done with the mission.
- It's over. Go now. - Go home.
- You're so mean. - What?
Divide it up and do some more quizzes.
Why would I do that?
- Jong Kook. - I should have done it.
- What's the point? - How can you do this?
Why did you make me do it? I didn't want to.
He has a point.
- You lost rock-paper-scissors. - Right? It wasn't my choice.
- What are you, Bao Zheng? - Yes.
I accepted the challenge despite my mental stress.
Think of the mental stress you gave to your team members.
Can you not think about that?
(He's giving mental stress to his team members.)
Let's start.
Here we go.
April 28 is General Yi Sun Sin's birthday.
- I know. - I can't do this anymore.
I can't do this anymore.
(Pushing)
Now...
(Kwang Soo will try this time.)
(I think someone pushed him.)
Kwang Soo, you're here.
That was nice.
You'll have to take a loan.
Wait. This is unfair.
I have 19 dollars. Please lend me one dollar.
Cheol Min, please.
I'm not talking to my producer.
Cheol Min, we're friends. Can't you lend me a dollar?
(I'll make sure to pay you back.)
I have 19 dollars.
You might get the question right.
- You might. - I can't.
(You know I can't.)
You know I can't.
(Kwang Soo will be one step closer to the Dangerous Trip.)
April 28 is General Yi Sun Sin's birthday.
I'll toss this coin General Yi Sun Sin is depicted in.
Will it be heads or tails?
You can do this.
You have a 50-percent chance.
You wanted to do this.
- Okay. - Go for tails.
You usually get the same one repeatedly.
(The coin is tossed.)
Kwang Soo, it's heads.
- It's heads. - The number side is tails, right?
- It's heads. - It's heads.
(All his team members say it's heads.)
If you borrow 50 dollars, you get one Sticker.
(If he gets it wrong, he'll be sent on the trip.)
(What will Kwang Soo say?)
Heads.
(He listens to his team.)
It was tails.
(Tails)
You guys...
(You guys...)
(I won't forgive you.)
He's taking a loan.
(Together, they become super unlucky.)
My goodness.
He's taking a loan.
It's because of that brat.
Kwang Soo is going on the trip, right?
Hey. Kwang Soo.
(He shouldn't have trusted his team.)
By the way,
we really are unlucky.
Calm down.
We're so unlucky.
I just need one dollar.
One dollar.
I'll do anything for you. Please give me one dollar.
Please give me one dollar.
- 1 dollar. - I'll give you 20 dollars less.
I'll pay you back 10 dollars.
Kwang Soo is going on the trip.
(Kwang Soo will be sent on the trip.)
This time, it'll be Jae Seok.
I'm sure.
It'll be Jae Seok this time. Be careful.
- Three on our team... - Three of us...
are going on the Dangerous Trip.
(Three on his team are being sent on the trip.)
We could just...
send the whole team.
I can't believe this.
Actor Kim Myung Min won the Grand Prize...
for his role in "Beethoven Virus".
"You piece of garbage."
(It's his famous line from the drama.)
Why me?
Why?
Why me? Why?
Go ahead.
He'll have to take a loan too.
My goodness.
Actor Kim Myung Min appeared in "Beethoven Virus".
What is Beethoven's full name?
A: Franz Beethoven. B: Ludwig van Beethoven.
Wolfgang Amadeus Beethoven.
C: Wolfgang Amadeus Beethoven.
D: Johann Sebastian Beethoven.
- He's amazing. - C?
- He already said his answer. - Don't try to make it funny.
It's Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart,
now that I think of it.
(You're amazing.)
You're incredible.
Seok Jin, choose D.
- It's definitely Johann. - Choose D.
Michael Jonathan Batman.
Batman?
(They're trying to confuse him.)
Michael Jonathan Batman.
- What? - Batman?
- Batman? - Do you choose B?
Yes, B.
(Seok Jin chooses B.)
- Do you choose B? - Yes, B.
(Is Seok Jin right?)
B: Ludwig van Beethoven.
(B: Ludwig van Beethoven)
(Correct)
You have 10 seconds.
- Divide it up. - Divide it up.
- You should divide it up. - Divide it up.
- Hey. - Divide it up.
(Give it all to me.)
(Seok Jin chooses to have 30 dollars to himself.)
You and I saw dolphins together.
Seok Jin.
Think of why I've ended up this way.
Who ruined my life?
I'll have everything to myself.
- You can't trust anybody. - Okay.
We just finished the first round,
and already three people have received three Tour Stickers.
Can't we wrap up now?
Anyway,
- if you pay your debt, - You can lose your sticker?
- a Sticker will be taken away. - All right.
I have a debt of 80 dollars.
I'm faced with danger because of one dollar.
Because of one dollar.
Why did you choose heads?
(You little...)
(Laughing)
We'll move to a place where Round Two will take place.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(Global Race)
- Dolphins. - That's so cool.
We saw them in person.
- We saw them. - We did.
We saw 500 of them.
(This place shows the history of Ulsan.)
Will the teams be the same?
It's a team competition again.
You can form new teams.
(They can form new teams.)
(New teams?)
- All right. - We'll form new teams?
I guess it doesn't matter.
Those who took the prize money to themselves...
should team up.
Fine, come here.
- It doesn't matter. - It'll change again.
- I'll stay here. - This is a liberal democracy.
- They're cool. - I earned my prize.
So Min, can you help us this time?
- Please. - Okay.
We need your help.
If you're cool, come here.
- Hey, come here. - If you're cool.
You said you wanted to team up with me.
- If you're cool, come here. - We're done.
- It's perfect. - Come here.
- Okay. - I like it.
We're cool people.
(The teams have been formed.)
The next mission is called...
It's called Your Dangerous Choices.
(Round 3 of Dangerous Choices is called Your Dangerous Choices.)
- Your choices? - Yes, your choices.
Your choices.
First, discuss with your team members how much you will bet...
on a total of four missions with different levels.
You will have 4 missions and 4 choices of betting money.
The other team will randomly choose your mission and betting money.
- This is difficult. - It's hard.
Your team's mission is Shouting Speed Quiz.
You have to guess the answer right within the time limit, 100 seconds.
The distance between the examiner and the rest of you...
will be among 1cm, 5m, 50m, or 100m.
(Shouting Speed Quiz)
(It is best for them that they choose 1cm.)
Your mission is called...
Spin and Kick.
- "Spin and Kick"? - Yes.
- That sounds like dolphins. - I see.
Spin 10 times in place first...
and throw your shoe to hit the doll.
The number of members that need to succeed is among 1, 2, 3, or 4.
(It's best for them to choose 1.)
So they will choose how many members we need to succeed, right?
- We can pull some tricks here? - Yes, you're right.
- This is worth five dollars. - Right.
- Let's make this four people. - Good.
(They arrange the numbers so the other team picks the easiest one.)
It's predictable though.
- We can't help it. - Okay.
- How about we make this into one? - You can also...
Hey, So Min.
(The spy appears.)
- So Min, you... - So Min.
- Seriously. - You learned only the bad stuff.
(Spy So Min fails to get a clue.)
What did you say?
They're so aggressive.
(Careful)
They will know by looking at how our hands move.
Where are you going?
- Where are you going? - Gosh.
- Where are you heading? - It won't give you a clue.
(The original spy fails as well.)
(They've finished preparing for Your Dangerous Choices.)
- We're done. - They did it that way.
Which team should we start with?
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do that.
- Let's do something else. - What then?
- Upgraded rock-paper-scissors. - Get hit on the back of your hand,
and if you don't make a noise, you win.
I'll go first against Seok Jin.
I'll do this with Seok Jin.
Why should I go first?
If you hold it in, you get to hit me next.
You just made a noise.
(Groaning)
(Oh, no. You made a noise.)
I'm sorry, but you're out.
It was like that of dolphins.
I think I heard it this morning.
- Did you follow me here? - Oh, gosh.
- Yes, I did. - I forgot about you for a second.
(Sigh)
(Team Jae Seok gets to choose the other team's mission first.)
Choose, and we'll reveal what it is.
- I go for 3. - Let's choose 3 then.
(Their expressions are mysterious.)
And for the amount, we choose two.
We choose 3 for the difficulty level and 2 for the amount.
- Gosh. - Show us the amount first.
- Good. - Show us.
(It's best for them if the betting money turns out to be 50 dollars.)
(But if their difficulty level turns out to be 4 people,)
(their possibility to lose money will go up.)
- That was perfect. - It's 50 dollars.
(Their betting money is 50 dollars.)
(They have a nice start.)
- Okay. - 50 dollars is nice.
- What number was for the level? - It was three.
- Okay. - One...
(Having fewer number of people to succeed will be advantageous.)
- 2, 3. - My goodness.
It's 4 people.
(They get the hardest level.)
- So 4 people must succeed? - 4 people?
So why did you listen to Kwang Soo?
Wait.
(Wait)
So why did you tell us to choose number three?
- Right. - Wait.
- This mission is for their team. - What?
- What? - My gosh.
(That's why it's called Your Dangerous Choices.)
So Team Jong Kook's betting money is 50 dollars with the hardest level.
What we did is good, right?
- Right. - I did well too.
I mean, they blame me for anything first.
So they choose the mission for us.
- It's ours? - It's ours.
Goodness.
- So I did well. - Good job.
- Good job. - Compliment me then.
- We're busy filming so how can we? - I mean...
- We're busy. Can't you see? - So...
They need to hurry home after work too.
We don't have time to compliment you.
Just make a new segment for yourself and do it there.
- I'm working on it. - Okay.
All right. It's for Team Jae Seok now.
- Let's do number 4. - 4?
- Four is a good number. - Okay.
- Let's go with 4 and 4. - Okay.
- 4 and 4. - 4 and 4.
The amount is...
(It's best for Team Jae Seok to have 1cm and 50 dollars.)
(It's the worst for them if they get 100m and 50 dollars.)
- 50 dollars! - 50 dollars.
(It's the hardest level for them as well.)
- It's 100m. - Our choice was perfect.
- I knew this would happen. - We have nothing to lose then.
I told you to mix the numbers up.
(It's the worst for both teams. How will the mission turn out to be?)
(Your Dangerous Choices)
- Let's head down now. - Okay.
(Spin and Kick, Shouting Speed Quiz)
They decorated things like a traditional village.
It's like an experience center.
(Ulsan natives used to live with dolphins.)
It's so well-built.
Ulsan has been the city of rich people since long time ago.
(The past is brought back in Jangsaengpo Village.)
It says the village was so wealthy...
that even dogs were carrying 10-dollar bills.
(That is why we cast puppies with 10-dollar bills for today's guests.)
Team Jong Kook will start with the mission first.
- Okay. - Okay.
Spin 5 times and throw your shoe targeting 1 of these dolls.
(It's a success if they spin 5 times and hit the doll with their shoe.)
Since all of you need to succeed,
if anyone of you fails the mission...
- It won't be that difficult. - Right.
(If they fail, they lose 50 dollars.)
The thing is, I didn't get enough sleep.
Stop it already.
Stop making a fuss and focus.
- Be positive. We can do this. - Okay.
Se Chan, how do you feel about being in this team?
It's depressing.
Whenever we try to get things done, one person stops us all.
- So stop complaining. - I'm not that bad.
- He always brings us down. - It's okay.
(It's a rough start for them. Will they be all right?)
Let's do this.
You'll try out one by one.
- If you fail, the mission ends. - Right away?
- Can we do some practice? - I'll go last.
Let us practice once.
No way.
We need to get the grip on how our shoes fly.
- What grip? - Don't you think so?
Just do it.
(He looks at the ground while shouting.)
(He shouts in a very polite way.)
- Whom were you talking to? - What was that?
- Where were you looking? - I'm right here.
- What? - Whom did you talk to?
- Why would you look at the ground? - Be confident.
- He's such a coward. - Why would he...
I just told them to start.
- Let us practice. - What?
As a practice?
- Will you start? - Yes.
Ready.
We don't have a time limit.
(Spinning fast)
(Their mission will be put to an end as soon as one of them fails.)
- Five. - Now throw.
(Dizzy)
Hurry and throw.
- There isn't a time limit. - You can't let them do that.
I'll go.
(He dragged time unusually. How will the result be?)
- Okay. - That's it.
- That's it. - That's our Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
- He hit it right. - That's it.
This is harder than you think.
- This is hard. - Okay.
- Haha. - Okay, one of you succeeded.
Why don't you just let them go home, come back, and throw?
- This isn't fair. - You can't do that.
- It doesn't make sense. - Count to 10 then.
Counting to 10 is still too much.
(He's looking at the ground again.)
Do it yourself then.
Where exactly are you looking?
- What was that again? - That's funny.
How I did was reasonable.
I'll give you 3 seconds after your 5 spins.
I'll go.
(Haha starts.)
- Don't spin too fast. - Three.
- Four. - Spin here.
- 5. That's it. - 5.
(He finishes with his spins.)
- Slowly. - Three.
(Their mission ends if he fails.)
(Will they lose money or double the amount?)
- Seriously. - Okay!
(That was a clear miss.)
Okay! They fail the mission.
(Pay 50 dollars. The deal is closed.)
(Did I fail? I'm still dizzy.)
- You try it. - Three counts won't do it.
- That's too soon. - Give us five seconds.
(They agreed on giving the team 5 seconds after the spins.)
- Otherwise, you can never do it. - Give them five seconds.
- I can do this. - This is too hard.
And you punk!
(The tiger is angry.)
Focus.
Seniority is dead in our team.
Use your foot more wisely. Look.
Do you not have the right to speak?
- Why... - We follow the American style here.
We're all friends.
You do it all by yourself, so how is that American style?
- We're in the Western age. - Sure.
You get shot if you don't follow.
- I'll go. - Okay.
(Haha goes off again.)
Ready, set, and go.
(He spins slowly this time.)
Gosh, seriously.
We won't give you another chance if you're being like this.
Or he'll teach me a lesson.
If I spin fast, he'll scold me.
(Do you have any idea?)
- So what should I do? - It's all right.
It's all right.
Mamma mia!
- Haha, take it easy. - All right.
- That's enough. - It's better to be scolded by you.
(They're so happy not to be in that team.)
Just spin at an ambiguous speed. You know what I'm saying.
Okay? Now, spin.
(This time, he does it seriously.)
- That's it. - 1, 2, 3...
A little bit faster!
(His whipping continues.)
(It seems uneasy this time as well.)
- It'd be hard even without spins. - Five seconds now.
- Do it. - 2, 3.
Throw!
(He throws.)
(Sorry, Haha.)
Oh, come on.
- Let's stop. - Hey.
(In despair)
(That little punk can't do it.)
- Let Seok Jin try it. - This isn't right.
(I clearly told you to spin at an ambiguous speed.)
Can I have a break for two weeks?
I can't go on like this.
Look at him.
(He's about to explode.)
I'm begging you.
Please.
(Haha gets another chance.)
My target is the stuffed dog in the middle.
Hit any one of them.
- Get ready. - Don't make a mistake.
(What is he doing?)
(He makes a creative pose.)
What kind of pose is that?
- It's up to me. - What's this?
He looks like an elephant with two trunks.
- These are two trunks. - It's more comfortable that way.
Each neighborhood does it differently.
I used to hold the nose and the chin.
(What kind of elephant is that?)
Get ready.
- Start. - Turn.
- 1 and 2. - You're doing well.
- Three. - Am I doing well?
- That's enough. - That's good.
That's good so far.
Find your balance first.
(He tries to find balance.)
(He falls to the ground.)
- He got it. - Okay.
(His shoe hits the stuffed dog.)
- It worked. - Did I make it?
(What he did counts as a score.)
- Did it work? - It hit the stuffed dog.
- It doesn't have to fall. - It's fine as long as it hits it.
- It counts. - It works as long as it touches it.
The rule of the game is to hit the target with a shoe.
- Right. - You don't have to knock it down.
Yes, the rule was to knock down the target.
Is it hitting or knocking down the target?
(What will the producer say?)
- Isn't it hitting? - I told you to hit the target.
- Wasn't I right? - Wait a minute.
(Move out of the way.)
- He hit me. - Wasn't I right?
Did you just hit me?
- Stop it. - How dare you?
(Why is he blocking Seok Jin's eye?)
Listen.
(Seok Jin gets attacked instead.)
What are you doing?
(Ji Hyo turns violent.)
- It's okay, Ji Hyo. - What happened?
Good job, Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin has matured a lot.)
We beat Seok Jin the most.
(I'm sorry, Seok Jin.)
(While everyone else was involved in the fight,)
(So Min concentrated on counting the money.)
(She's in a world that's different from everyone else.)
A fight broke out while I was counting money.
Don't worry.
Let's see Se Chan's potential.
- It's a success if he hits it. - Come on, Se Chan.
Start.
(He does his best.)
- That's a good speed. - Three.
That's a great speed.
Calm down before you throw the shoe.
(They clear the mission if Se Chan succeeds.)
(Jong Kook's eyes sparkle in hope.)
(Will Se Chan succeed?)
He made it.
(The stuffed dog is knocked down.)
(It's a definite success.)
Look, Jong Kook.
- I knew you could do it. - It's possible.
- It's definitely possible. - He made it.
We clear the mission if Haha succeeds.
Haha, you're the abnormal one.
(Did he call me abnormal?)
He called Haha abnormal.
This isn't a big deal.
- It's possible. - Am I the last one?
- Give it a try. - Do you want another chance?
- Do you want to try? - Does he get another chance?
You should pay us.
(You should pay us.)
We'll also give you another chance.
- Of course. - We should keep the promise.
If they give us another chance,
- we'll also give them a chance. - They must pay for it.
So Min, don't hesitate so much.
- I see you. - It's give and take.
Make them pay 30 dollars.
(They finish discussing.)
Pay us 30 dollars for another chance.
We had a discussion.
(Pay us 30 dollars in advance.)
Instead of paying, we'll give you a chance if you fail.
- No, we'll pay for it. - Isn't that better? No way.
- Let's pay 20 dollars. - Give us a discount.
- Just pay 20 dollars. - Let's do it.
- It's your mistake. - You should pay them.
Come on.
They're bullying me, aren't they?
- Come here. - Listen.
It'll be strange if I pay them, so you should pay them.
You should pay them.
(Jong Kook is careful about saving his face.)
Shouldn't I report them?
Please say something, SBS!
Come here, Haha. I'll make a comment.
(Jong Kook directs Haha.)
Say this.
"I'll pay 20 dollars because it was my mistake."
- Tell them. - Wait here.
- Listen. - It should be edited.
Please give him a chance.
- Pardon me? - Give him a chance.
- Then pay us 20 dollars. - 20 dollars?
Why are you playing along?
- You're not on his team. - He asked us.
(Do whatever you want.)
We'll get five dollars each.
- They're asking for 20 dollars. - What should we do?
- We don't have money. - Only Haha made a mistake.
That's true.
What Seok Jin did doesn't count.
- Let's ask him for 10 dollars. - Right.
- It wasn't proper. - Pay 10 dollars.
- I hit it. - It wasn't knocked down.
It got moved.
You didn't knock it down.
- Tell him. - Listen to me, everyone.
(Pushing)
(Jae Seok screams.)
- Look. - Did he hit you?
Did you hit Jae Seok?
- No. - Did you hit him?
Did you hit him with your finger?
(Haha's 20 dollars leads to a fight.)
I'll just pay 20 dollars.
(Haha gives in.)
Stop fighting.
Give us 20 dollars.
Is this a gangster show?
- Give it to me. - Give us 20 dollars.
(Haha gets another chance in the end.)
It's Haha's last chance.
Haha paid 20 dollars for it.
Get ready.
- Set, go. - It's for 50 dollars.
- 1, 2, 3. - That's great.
- He's doing well. - Four.
- That's the last turn. - Five.
Focus.
- Take your time. - One,
- 2, 3. - He got it.
(Their fate depends on Haha's shoe.)
(If he fails, they must pay 50 dollars.)
(He fails.)
There's something wrong with my foot.
(Did he fail again?)
- Goodness. - My foot was wrong.
Haha is terrible.
(What should I do with him?)
Team Jong Kook failed.
Pay 50 dollars to the other team.
The team that chose Shouting Speed Quiz...
must answer 10 questions in 100 seconds.
- How many questions? - 100m isn't a short distance.
Get ready.
It's three people including Seok Jin and Jae Seok.
We can't hear you.
- It has four syllables. - Unlucky ones?
- What's this? - What is your name?
- It's a movie starring Emma Watson. - What is it?
We can't hear you.
(They fail the mission.)
The time is up.
Let's go to the next location.
It's time to eat.
(Mission fees that members currently have)
What's this?
(O Restaurant in Ulsan)
(It's a feast.)
- Does everyone get to eat it? - Gosh.
(It's Eonyang bulgogi, a specialty dish in Ulsan.)
I want this one.
(It's finely minced beef cooked in savory sauce.)
Does everyone get to eat it?
(What's going on there?)
I'll sit here.
(Simple meals are set up in one corner.)
What's going on?
It doesn't matter where you sit.
- Okay. - Pardon me?
Take a seat first. We'll eat based on the game result.
Here's the mission where you get a chance...
to taste Ulsan's specialty, Eonyang bulgogi.
The other team will decide how much you can spend.
You can select the menu according to the amount.
It's the same rule as before.
The other team decides how much you can spend.
You eat according to the amount.
(The other team determines the amount you can spend.)
- We must be careful. - You're right.
Give it to us.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Don't think too much.
It's more upsetting if things turn out bad after thinking hard.
Let's do it.
Just follow our intuition.
Let's do it separately.
- There's no strategy for this. - Okay.
- It's one. - Let's put them randomly.
Leave it up to the expert.
That's right.
Don't show me the other chart.
Which team would like to choose first?
- The other team. - The other team.
Let's make them eat a bowl of rice.
Which number do you choose for the amount?
- Is the amount for us? - Which number do you choose?
(Which number?)
We don't know which one.
We can't react, right?
- Let's go for number four. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo trusts So Min's choice.)
We choose number four for the amount.
- Number four? - Show us the amount first.
- Shall we? - What's the amount?
Let it be 50 dollars.
(They're desperate.)
- How much is it? - Goodness.
What is it?
(Team Jong Kook has to pay the amount.)
(How much will they have to pay?)
- What is it? - It's 50 dollars.
(They pick the maximum amount.)
Okay!
That's unlike you, Kwang Soo.
(It was So Min's idea.)
- It's okay. - Who picked number four?
We can eat Eonyang bulgogi.
Which number do you choose for the menu?
So Min?
Number one?
- Number 1? - Number 1 for the menu?
- Yes. - We choose number one.
- Okay. - Is that it?
It's number one.
(Which menu will Team Jong Kook get?)
What is it?
What is it? No way.
(Will it be crispy Eonyang bulgogi?)
(Or will it be rice with dried laver?)
(We can't tell by his face.)
- It's not bad. - It's doenjang noodles.
It's doenjang noodles for four.
(We can't eat bulgogi?)
Doenjang noodles?
(Team Jong Kook gets doenjang noodles and pays 50 dollars.)
(They can't eat bulgogi.)
- That's not bad. - No.
(They'll be having noodles at a bulgogi restaurant.)
How about us?
Let's have them pay 50 dollars for rice.
Okay.
There's always the worst.
We chose number four twice last time.
- How about 1 for both? - Number 1?
- Food is very important. - Let's pick number one.
(They choose number 1.)
- Number 1? - Number 1 for the amount.
(How much was it?)
The amount is...
(How much did Team Jae Seok bet for number 1?)
Go ahead.
- It's 50 dollars. - Goodness.
(They're all happy.)
(50 dollars...)
Is it really 50 dollars?
(They're great at wishing each other bad luck.)
I got goose bumps.
Let's just go with number one.
- Let's go with number 1. - Number 1?
His face didn't look good when we kept saying number one.
- Let's do number 1. - Number 1.
(Earlier, they were deciding to choose number 1,)
(and he looked very worried.)
- His face didn't look good. - Number one.
- Number 1. - Number 1.
(Are they flustered?)
(Or are they acting?)
(There's Ulsan's Eonyang bulgogi in front of them.)
(Number 1 is...)
(What did Team Jong Kook choose?)
Please.
His face didn't look good...
- when we kept saying number 1. - Number 1.
- Number 1. - Number 1.
(Jae Seok's face is unreadable.)
(They might only get rice at an Eonyang bulgogi restaurant.)
(What will happen to Team Jae Seok?)
Please.
Let's eat together.
(4 more doenjang noodles please.)
- We get the same. - This is perfect.
Let's pay for it.
This is war.
- Okay, this is war. - Can you take everything else?
This is war. It's war.
- Fine. - This is war.
Can you take everything but doenjang noodles?
I'm just happy to see that they're not happy.
We have to pay 50 dollars for doenjang noodles?
- It's too expensive. - Good.
We're at an Eonyang bulgogi place,
and we can't even have meat.
I really wanted it.
I want some bulgogi.
Gosh. We almost had it.
(They're all depressed.)
I had instant noodles and now I'm having this.
(Slurping)
It's good.
(Their attitude change.)
(Slurping)
(It's good.)
It's good.
- It's really good. - It suits my appetite.
(They're satisfied with just doenjang noodles.)
How did we end up choosing the same?
At least I feel better that we're eating the same thing.
- We're not jealous. - I know.
Can I have 50 dollars from each team?
Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
Can you exclude me? I have too little money left.
Hey, I don't have much either.
- How much do you have? - We can't do that.
Se Chan, I gave you 10 dollars earlier.
Let's do this then.
We'll split 2 to 1 to 1 to 1.
- 2 to 1 to 1 to 1. - Okay.
(They listen to Jong Kook right away.)
- Rock... - Only one person will pay more.
- Rock, paper, scissors - Rock, paper, scissors
(Haha gets to pay 20 dollars.)
Okay.
That's 20 dollars. We pay 10 dollars.
- Put it here. - I can still survive.
It's good because the person with more money keeps on paying.
We're very democratic.
We're very...
This is peace.
(He glances at Jong Kook.)
Does this look like democracy to you?
- Of course. - We're very democratic.
(It sounds more like Jong Kook's words are the law.)
Jae Seok, democracy is when its citizens are satisfied.
That sounds nice.
(You are great.)
(Democracy is great.)
Let's do rock, paper, scissors and have two people pay.
What do you say? Let's do rock, paper, scissors...
- and save two people. - But we have so little.
I just need 11 dollars to escape.
I'll start living a new life.
Jae Seok,
- I'll work harder. - Then...
Then can you two...
pay 10 dollars together?
(So Min and he will pay 40 dollars.)
- 10 dollars? - Yes.
I can afford 10 dollars,
but if I can get 11 dollars, I can pay back my loan.
I...
I wasn't going to say this, but...
my mom became a victim of a spam call not long ago.
(This is a true story.)
- I wasn't going to mention this. - We should pay for him.
I'll pay.
(We should pay for him.)
(I'll pay.)
(He's touched.)
I'll only pay 10 dollars.
What are you doing?
You're only paying 10 dollars?
Let's pay 25 dollars each.
- 25 dollars? - Yes.
You're paying half each, So Min.
(That was a very fair suggestion.)
Why do you sound...
Hold on. Did I do something wrong? I was actually thinking about it.
- What's wrong? - Even I...
- Why did she sound surprised? - I thought...
I made a difficult suggestion.
Can we do rock, paper, scissors and have one person pay?
(So Min makes a daring suggestion.)
- That's intense. - That's good.
Good one, So Min.
She's good in this.
- That's what I like about her. - Me too.
- So Min. - Okay.
What are you going to do?
- I can't tell. - What are you going to do?
I can't say.
She gets too scary when it comes to money.
Even last time, Kwang Soo and she...
(She abandoned Kwang Soo because he didn't have any money.)
But I have some.
- You do? - You have money?
- How much do you have? - I lied...
to you earlier.
You... Hey.
(So Min lied to Kwang Soo before.)
It's one round.
(Her opponent is Jae Seok this time.)
Wait a second.
That thing...
- Don't open it. - Okay.
Number of grains?
Whoever picks the bowl with more grains left wins, okay?
Okay. We'll count the number of grains left.
- The one with more grains wins. - Okay.
I'll give them to you as is.
- Don't touch it. - Okay.
Okay. Right or left?
- I choose right. - This?
(So Min chooses the right bowl.)
(Kwang Soo emptied the 1st bowl in his noodles,)
(and he emptied the 2nd bowl into So Min's noodles.)
- This one? - This is mine.
All right. That one.
(This is quite intense.)
- It's by the number of grains. - Yes, it is.
- Including the lid, okay? - Okay.
The person with more grains wins, right?
One, two, three.
(The winner won't have to pay,)
(and the loser has to pay 50 dollars.)
(Who is going to pay today?)
One, two, three.
(So Min is the winner.)
(She has a bunch.)
Thank you for the food, Jae Seok.
- Thank you for the food. - This isn't it.
(Thank you for the food.)
This isn't it.
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors. - No way.
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors. - Then...
give me 10 dollars. I'll do rock, paper, scissors.
(Give me 10 dollars, and I'll do you a favor.)
(That was a good one.)
She learns very fast.
(She gets scarier and scarier.)
She's too scary.
(She is controlling Jae Seok.)
- Jeon So Min... - Stop being like that, So Min.
(So Min adapts very quickly.)
Hold on. So Min...
She's no joke, right?
Good job, So Min. Take all his money.
I'll do rock, paper, scissors if you pay me 10 dollars.
(He gives her 10 dollars to get another try.)
I don't know if I'm doing the right thing.
- You can win this time. - It's a single round.
Yes, that's right. It's a single round.
Yes.
(I can't get swayed.)
(He faces her with his own strategy.)
So Min is strong.
Rock, paper, scissors!
(They're true enemies.)
(Jae Seok and So Min are trying to make each other pay.)
(Who will win this time?)
Rock, paper, scissors!
(So Min was going to win anyways.)
(Lunch is on Jae Seok today.)
- Jeon So Min. - Jeon So Min.
(You should live life like her.)
- This is beautiful. - She's starting to...
(Boiling)
This is getting interesting.
Here's 50 dollars.
Thank you for the food.
So Min, you won't get away with this.
(How will this rivalry between Jae Seok and So Min end?)
She's no joke.
This is war, So Min.
Jeon So Min.
- You're dead, So Min. - This is war.
You don't know how he is. You're dead.
- Jong Kook. - He keeps his words.
- Let's form an alliance. - He keeps his words.
- It's okay. - So Min.
I need to bring So Min with me.
We'll get a few losers in a row.
(Gimhae Theme Park)
(Gimhae is known for its rich heritage.)
Where are we?
This is fascinating.
Silla and Gaya...
(It still has remnants of the Gaya confederacy.)
Baekje...
Aren't you giving out more Tour Stickers?
We might give out a lot at the end.
This is unfair for people with no money.
People like me. Me and Seok Jin.
- Yes, I have nothing. - Me neither.
So we have a special mission.
It's the Be Irrelevant game.
(Be Irrelevant game...)
(is where you provide irrelevant answers to questions.)
(How do you decompress?)
(Waterproof device)
(What is your nickname?)
(Strict measures will be taken against smoking within the studio.)
(What is the biggest lie you want to say?)
(Fire hydrant)
(This is correct.)
(What do you want to eat right now?)
(If your answer makes sense, you're wrong.)
(What do you call your wife?)
(Oh Jung Tae)
(It stirs up many controversies so reporters pay attention to it.)
This is hard.
It's different. It's been upgraded.
You can bet anything from 10 to 50 dollars.
If you win, we'll give you the amount you win.
If you lose, you'll get that much deducted.
Seok Jin is the worst at this game.
- I'll bet 10 dollars. - That's all-in.
Set, go.
What are you most interested in these days?
Toad.
(With his loss, the real game starts.)
Be Irrelevant is so hard.
He has no money now.
It actually makes sense.
- Is it Kwang Soo next? - Yes.
- I'll bet 10 dollars. - 10 dollars.
Hey.
Double the amount. It's okay.
Bet 22 dollars.
- You'll be debt free. - That's right.
- Bet 22 dollars. - Do it.
I will.
Fine, I'll do it.
- You have to be smart. - I'll do it.
- You must be fair though. - Okay.
If you win this time, you can pay off your loan.
Ready, set, go.
What did you dream about yesterday?
Don't worry.
- How do you feel right now? - Kimchi.
- Few words for your mom? - I love you.
(I love you, Mom.)
(He's a good son.)
You're a good son.
Go again.
- He's a good son. - He is.
This is your last chance. It's fine.
I'll bet money and play two more times.
If I lose, I'm done.
This is how you become bankrupt, right?
Ready, set, go.
What do you want to say to our viewers?
Emergency department.
What did you dream about yesterday?
Green.
What do you want to lie about?
Mimi.
What's that?
- Mimi. - What's that?
Mimi.
It's the name of the cat I had as a child.
- You took too long. - I know.
You took too long.
- You took too long. - That's right.
Hey, watch me.
Bet everything.
Who'll take the xylophone?
I will. Who will?
How much are you going to bet?
- I'll bet 5 dollars. - Okay, it's 5 dollars.
Ready,
set, go. What's in your bag right now?
What do you know?
What do you want to say to your wife?
(What do you want to say to your wife?)
(He can't answer it this time either.)
- What's wrong? - What's the problem?
- Why are you pausing? - It's always his wife.
- Were you thinking about poop? - Yes.
- I knew it. - Hey.
I was thinking about poop. Why would you ask that?
- You should have said it. - This time,
I bet 11 dollars.
- 11 dollars. - He's wasting it all.
- Cue. - Ready, set,
go. What do you tell your angry wife?
81.
You can say that.
(You can say that to your wife.)
- 81... - It's an irrelevant answer.
- It's irrelevant. - It's true.
- See? He can't do it. I told you. - Let go.
- Give it back. - It's my fault.
(He's mad.)
Jae Seok, he's not mad at you.
He's mad at himself.
(Boiling)
- Is that right? - I'm just mad at myself.
Okay, that makes sense.
It's like I'm asking, "Why did I do that?"
- Don't be so strict on yourself. - Don't.
You weren't mad at me, right?
Why would I be mad at you? You didn't do anything wrong.
That was entirely my fault.
- All right. Stop being mad. - I'm good.
You have to do better.
- Do three in a row. - Okay.
Ready, set,
go. How old were you when you had your first kiss?
How could you abandon me?
How do you comfort your mad wife?
58.
Isn't this wrong?
No, keep going.
What's wrong with you?
Why do you keep interrupting?
- Stop doing that. - What's wrong?
- What's wrong with you? - Hold on.
- Hold on. Give me a second. - What's wrong with him?
- And Jae Seok. - Yes?
- When his wife gets mad... - Don't say anything.
(Can you stop talking?)
(He gets ordered around by somebody 11 years younger than him.)
- Why? - I...
I can't even...
- I'm sorry. - What was that?
He's the oldest of us all.
He's not the youngest.
- He's not. - I'm sorry.
- He... - That's not it.
I said that because Jae Seok...
kept stalling...
- and tries to earn time. - I didn't.
Then here's your question.
- Is this my last chance? - It's a mental game this time.
- Is this my last chance? - Yes, here it is. Ready,
set, go. Can you say something long to me?
All right.
Something short?
What's that?
- He knows he's wrong. - My gosh.
- This is driving me crazy. - He's so nice.
- He actually said something short. - My gosh.
- Who's next? - It's So Min's turn.
I'll bet 20 dollars.
- Really? - Yes.
Ready, set, go.
What is your favorite number?
Shipping and pick up.
What do you want to say to Kwang Soo?
You...
(Kwang Soo, you...)
- No... - Hey.
- Hey. - That was wrong.
- This... - Come on.
That sounds unpleasant.
I'll bet 12 dollars.
- Haha bets 12 dollars. - Okay.
Ready, set, go.
- What do you want to lie about? - 23.
- What is your favorite number? - You're so funny.
What do you want to say to Dream?
Crying like a baby. Who are you?
(What are you doing, Haha?)
Come on.
(Who are you, Dream?)
How can you say that to your child?
It's your child.
He was trying to stall.
He was saying, "Crying like a baby," to stall.
(It's a perfect answer for Dream's age.)
He was saying it to Dream.
Hey, don't you dare.
Don't talk about my family.
- Stop mentioning our family. - Why would you do that?
"Crying like a baby. Who are you?"
"Who are you?"
I thought he was imitating a comedian.
- Nature's great, right? - It's wonderful.
It makes my eyes open wide.
This is different.
I feel healthy.
You should always try to enjoy the nature.
(What mission awaits them in this spring weather?)
Everybody, welcome to Gimhae.
(Welcome to Gimhae.)
We're in Gimhae.
The palace behind you is a replica of Gaya Royal Palace...
where King Kim Su Ro lived 2,000 years ago.
(It's a replica of the palace King Kim Su Ro lived in.)
Our last race of Dangerous Choices will be in this historical place.
You have your mission fee, right?
Of course.
You can earn more mission fees with Dangerous Shoe Throw.
(Dangerous Shoe Throw?)
Steal another member's shoe...
and throw it on the large board with their names on it.
(There are 3 boards scattered around.)
The member whose shoe is thrown on the board is out.
(If your shoe is on the board, you're out.)
(You'll be remotely eliminated.)
You can steal half the money that the person has.
Wait. That's a bit too much.
Half? We have none.
- What if you have none? - We have none.
If you have none, then that's that.
It's always a gain for us.
(If you eliminate a person with no money, you don't gain anything.)
However, you shouldn't be happy because you have no money.
If your shoe lands on the space that reads, "Dud",
you must pay 30 dollars as a penalty and try again.
- 30 dollars? - Yes. If you have no money,
you must get a loan.
There's also a space that reads, "Winner".
If your shoe lands on that spot,
that's the end of the race.
You get 100 dollars as prize money.
100 dollars?
- We can pay our loans back. - We can do it.
It'll be hard to steal each other's shoes.
Since...
it won't be easy,
we also hid three shoes somewhere around this area.
- We have to find it? - Those shoes count too.
What are you doing? You're already tying your shoelaces?
(Untying)
Come on, So Min.
Look at her. She's untying my shoelaces.
What is she doing?
Please separate yourselves and start the mission.
(Who's going to be the ultimate winner?)
It won't be easy to steal people's shoes.
I should look for the hidden shoes.
(Steal or find the hidden shoes.)
- I think they'll come off easily. - These?
They have to touch it in the first place.
(That's frightening.)
Do we start here?
(So Min is a rookie.)
I'm worried. What do I do?
(She's half-worried and half-curious.)
Do we get slippers?
If you get your shoes stolen, we'll give you a pair.
I shouldn't hide my shoes, right? It'll be unfair.
I'm going to get mine stolen quickly.
(She already knows how to cheat.)
I just want to steal one shoe.
I'll lose to Ji Hyo, right?
Ji Hyo is a woman,
so I can steal hers.
(Is that right?)
I'll count down.
They're all nearby.
Kwang Soo is right next to me.
(He's right next to Jong Kook.)
(Roaring)
(Goodness)
Three,
- 2, - 2,
One. Start race.
(Kwang Soo runs for his life.)
Look at Kwang Soo run.
He's so fast.
(He's very fast.)
(I can't catch him.)
Wait. Where are the shoes?
I shouldn't let the others find it. I should catch them first.
(What are the other members doing?)
Seok Jin.
The two of us...
Let's switch shoes...
with each other and throw them.
(That's an idea.)
- Should we? - Yes.
The others are going to steal ours anyways.
(Haha thinks of ideas so that he can win.)
- That's a good idea. - Right? Hurry.
Mine usually don't come off.
I know but Seok Jin...
We should both throw them?
Yes, let's throw both of them.
- That's actually great. - Yes, it is.
- If we do this... - Why don't we steal others' first?
Seok Jin.
What's up? Are you two a team?
No, should we form a team?
- Do you want to be a team? - First of all,
the four of us should be a team.
- I don't have anything. - How does that sound?
- I don't have anything either. - Okay.
- The thing is... - Then let's attack Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook? - Yes.
- Let's get rid of him first. - No, let's finish Jae Seok first.
Let's work together after we get rid of Jong Kook.
- Actually, we should do that first. - That's right.
- We all know how he is. - Okay. We are a team now.
We are one.
I'm getting tired of this.
Let's go at him hard!
We all don't have any money and you are aware of it, right?
Of course.
- That's right. - I have nothing to lose.
(Person in 1st place is moving with the low ranks.)
- You have money though, right? - Yes, money doesn't matter though.
If you go around by yourselves, it's not good for you.
But who is going to attack Jong Kook first when we see him?
- It will be Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo will try first.
Let me see.
There will be shoes?
(He opens his eyes wide and starts hurting for shoes.)
I think it should be somewhere around here.
(Shoes or members, where are you?)
There's a shoe.
(He finds 1 out of 3 hidden shoes.)
I got it. Let's go. Hurry.
Jong Kook found something.
(He goes to kick the shoe.)
Jae Seok's coming. It'd be great if I can eliminate him.
Hey.
- There he is. - There's Jong Kook.
(Everyone pays attention to his first try.)
Kick it to the right block. Kick for Kwang Soo.
Go into Jae Seok block!
(The owner of the block where the shoe falls will be eliminated.)
(What will the decision of Jong Kook's shoe be?)
Go into Jae Seok block!
(Seok Jin who has no money is eliminated.)
Darn it. He doesn't have any money.
(At this moment, Seok Jin shows up.)
What happened? I just saw it.
Hey, what are you doing?
- You have no money. - He started off the race.
(Am I eliminated already?)
Is it over for me?
- He's right there. - Let the race...
start.
Goodness. What is this?
We just started.
What is it? Doesn't he have to do two?
Hey, Jong Kook. Why me? Wait.
No way. Seriously. Let me go.
- I am in a hurry. - You're making me sad.
I don't have time.
I will do exactly what you want.
(Haha fails to escape from this crisis.)
(Jong Kook throws Haha on to the ground.)
(He gives up.)
I'm sorry, let me have the right foot shoe since I'm taking yours.
(I'm sorry, let me have the right foot shoe since I'm taking yours.)
(I can't believe you.)
(He runs at a full speed to kick the shoe again.)
I can't be eliminated.
No one can eliminate me. I have to hurry.
This is so embarrassing.
I am a man too. Hold on.
(Jong Kook tries for the second time.)
(Flying)
(What will Jong Kook's shoe decide for the second time?)
- Kim Jong Kook. - He picked himself!
(Jong Kook is eliminated.)
(This is how scary a decision of the shoe can be.)
(Good for you.)
He eliminated himself.
(Jong Kook ends the race with 90 dollars.)
Come here. You are eliminated too, right?
Yes, the thing is...
if I were eliminated by Jae Seok, it would have made me so angry.
Exactly. Your money would have been transferred.
I should've been eliminated after I got Haha.
Then I would have had a lot of money.
(But at least you got to do something.)
This is unbelievable. I came here without doing a thing.
How could it fall into your block?
That's my point. How is that possible?
(His legend as the race starter will continue.)
(Meanwhile)
(Ji Hyo is trying her best to find the hidden shoes.)
Shoes. Shoes! Where are they?
(And a woman is targeting Ji Hyo.)
(She is tailing Ji Hyo from afar.)
(From the start, So Min targeted Ji Hyo.)
Where is Ji Hyo?
Where would Ji Hyo be?
(After she spotted Ji Hyo,)
(she starts tailing Ji Hyo right away.)
Where are the shoes?
(This is my grand opportunity.)
(I will attack her when she's distracted.)
Why are you following me now?
No, I am not.
Why are you following me?
(You shouldn't get caught if you are tailing me!)
Ji Hyo, I am not after your shoes.
It's Se Chan.
(At this moment, Se Chan appears.)
What is it?
(He attacks So Min.)
This isn't how you play this. No!
(So Min tries to reciprocate.)
(She sits down thinking she won't win against him.)
You are so annoying. Let me have your shoes.
Hey, we shouldn't attack each other.
- We should... - What?
We joined the show on the same day.
Kwang Soo! I got So Min! Come here!
I will give you money.
- You are done. - No, that's not true. No!
- What is this? - Kwang Soo, I got her.
(Kwang Soo, save me!)
- Kwang Soo, let's not do this. - Kwang Soo, stop it.
Kwang Soo.
What a jerk!
(He's a jerk in disguise of a giraffe.)
- How can he... - I knew it. How can you trust him?
I am going to win it this time.
(Kwang Soo came to kick the shoe.)
(Right now, I might be dirt poor.)
Challenge.
(With this shoe, I plan to flip my life.)
(What will Kwang Soo's shoe choose?)
(What? This is...)
(Will he win at his first try?)
(Will he be able to turn the race around?)
The race is over!
(The final race is over.)
Let me settle everyone's money.
(He's proud.)
So Min, you have 169 dollars.
Jong Kook, since you eliminated yourself,
- you have 90 dollars. - Okay.
Ji Hyo, you have 40 dollars.
Haha, you were eliminated by Kwang Soo.
Sorry?
(Haha was eliminated...)
(by Kwang Soo?)
(A little while ago)
(The shoe that Kwang Soo kicked with all his might...)
(fell into...)
(the winning block at once.)
Haha.
(And it flung back to Haha's block.)
(Kwang Soo eliminated Haha and acquired half of Haha's money.)
- So... - How much do I have?
Haha, you have 85 dollars.
- Kwang Soo, you have the same. - Yes!
(From 0 dollar, he managed to earn 85 dollars.)
- I was eliminated? - Yes, at the end.
(Then who won the race?)
(5 minutes before the race ended)
Here it is.
I found it. I found it!
(Jae Seok spotted a hidden shoe rather dramatically.)
(It was Jae Seok's first try kicking the shoe.)
Please. Please.
Did someone find the shoe?
If I land this shoe in the winning block, then I win, right?
(What will Jae Seok's shoe choose?)
(Flying)
(Victory)
That's crazy.
(Is this really happening?)
- Jae Seok, you won. - It felt into the winning block.
- Hey, I won! - How can you do this?
(No way.)
I am the winner!
(He manages to kick the shoe right inside the winning block.)
How could this have happened?
(Am I dreaming or is this real?)
- No way! - I won!
(She feels surreal even though she saw it with her own eyes.)
- This is amazing. - No way.
Jae Seok, you won.
(Jae Seok wins the final race.)
What a lucky break!
(He acquires 100 dollars.)
Since you won, you received 100 dollars...
and you have a total of 200 dollars combining the money you had before.
That's amazing. He just turned rich.
I have to be in Jae Seok's graces.
(The 5th round of Dangerous Choices Part 2)
With my 80 dollars, I'd like to get rid of one Tour Sticker.
Why don't you listen to the whole script?
- All right. - Okay.
- What is happening? - We will open a Store of Fate now.
Excuse me?
(Store of Fate?)
You can buy 1 Tour Sticker for 50 dollars.
You are unbelievable.
For 100 dollars, you can buy 1 Reflecting Card.
- Reflecting Card? - This is driving me crazy.
(Jong Kook can't buy it since he needs 10 more dollars.)
I am doomed.
Haha has only 85 dollars and you have only 90 dollars, right?
That means both of you can't buy it then.
Kwang Soo, you have to decide. You must either buy a Tour Sticker...
or pay 80 dollars and get rid of your Tour Sticker.
Will it make a difference?
(He will end up going on the trip anyway.)
I think it might be better for you to hold on to the money.
- Keep the money. - Okay, let's go.
- You will end up going anyway. - Saving the money will do no good.
Take at least one person with you.
You should pay your debt first.
- That's the right thing to do. - You're right.
- You should pay your debt. - You're right.
I'll pay my debt.
You've made a choice.
As he's paying back 80 dollars,
we'll take one of his stickers away.
Okay. I have two now.
- Okay. - Please move to the store.
(They move to the Store of Fate.)
(Tour Sticker, Reflecting Card)
(People who chose the Tour Stickers.)
(So Min has 169 dollars.)
(People who consider getting the Reflecting Cards.)
(And...)
(all their choices can be reversed...)
(by this one person.)
(What will he choose?)
(It's a war from now on.)
(The brutal decisions are made in risk of the Dangerous Trip.)
(Twist after twist)
(Who will be sent on the Dangerous Trip?)
(And...)
(the Dangerous Tourist Attraction is decided.)
(Where Will Fate Lead Running Man?)