(The winter festival of the world, )
(2018 Pyeongchang Winter Olympics)
(The members begin their field training for the games.)
(However, )
(the biggest cold wave hits Korea.)
(Running Man's winter games...)
(may seem slightly simple and nasty, )
(but they play games of loyalty.)
(What are the missions they will play at the end of 2017?)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hi. - Hello.
- It's really winter. It's cold. - It's freezing.
- It's so cold. - It's freezing cold.
- Seriously. - But I don't see the ladies.
I bet we are having female guests today.
Is So Min going to be a spy again? Is she a spy?
- Kwang Soo, when I saw you earlier, - Yes?
The light reflected on your jacket. It almost fooled me.
- What do you mean? - I thought it was a fly.
(His jacket is sleek like his bottom.)
- What are you talking about? - That does look like a fly.
- It's khaki. - I can see that,
- Kwang Soo, rub your hands. - but the light reflected on it.
- Do it. - Come on. Just do it for us.
Why would I rub my hands?
- Don't dress up only for dramas. - Hey, do it here.
- Unbelievable. - Kwang Soo, just copy me.
- My gosh. - Dress up for variety shows too.
- I've never heard that before. - Wait.
When the sun reflected, I really thought he was a fly.
How could you mistake me for it?
(He's treated like a fly.)
I can see that everyone tried to look presentable including Se Chan.
Don't you think my outfits look quite nice these days?
- Sure. They improved a lot. - They improved a lot.
- Right? - "Y".
- It stands for "Yang". - Actually, I...
- I was shocked. - What do you mean?
It happened on the elevators. Many neighbors are fans of the show.
We even shot an episode at my house. A kid...
told me that he enjoyed watching the show.
He asked me why my outfits looked ugly.
(A kid asked him why his outfits looked ugly.)
- A kid asked you that? - Yes, I was surprised.
- Not everyone has nice outfits. - So I asked...
if mine looked the ugliest, but it wasn't.
- Who had the ugliest outfit? - He picked Jong Kook's.
(Jong Kook's outfits are the ugliest.)
- He said Jong Kook's is the same. - Well, it's just that...
Jong Kook, it's such a waste of money.
- Jae Seok. - I...
I was shooting a show yesterday,
but I had some spare time, so I went shopping there.
- I bought it since it was warm, - So what we mean is that...
but you know what's surprising?
They forgot to remove the security tag.
- Seriously? - Yes.
(The security tag is still on as if he had stolen the vest.)
- They didn't take it off? - I...
- Someone might think I stole it. - Hey!
- Hey. - What if people think I'm a thief?
Hey, Jong Kook. How could you...
- Jae Seok. - You know that you shouldn't steal.
- You even dressed up like a thief. - I bought it in Ilsan.
I announced it on TV. I didn't steal this vest.
I paid for this.
(Don't think I stole it!)
- Everyone. - Yes?
The day after this episode airs, it will be January 1.
- Really? - It will be New Year's Day.
In celebration of Pyeongchang Winter Olympics which will be held soon,
you will depart for the field training with us.
(Members of Running Man will leave for the training as well!)
- Field training? - Why would we?
- New Year and that aren't related. - We aren't athletes.
Why would we go on training? We aren't athletes.
Guests including So Min and Ji Hyo...
who will join you on the training...
are on the train bound for Pyeongchang.
- They are in 3 different carts. - 3 carts?
(2 teams of guests are waiting.)
2 sisters of Running Man take up 1 cart.
- Female guests take up another. - Okay!
And male guests take up the other coach.
No, not them.
I already feel uncomfortable.
- I already feel uneasy. - So...
- the best pair is the female pair. - Exactly.
I wonder who will pick them.
There are two female guests.
- Partner up with another member. - I'm serious about this.
Make a pair, and choose a coach.
Then you will make a team with the guests in the coach you've chosen.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Yes, let's do that.
Those who play the same hand are a team.
- All right. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo play scissors.)
- The two of you played scissors. - You are a team.
- Let's do it again. - Why are you ignoring each other?
- The two of you are a team. - Why are you ignoring each other?
The two of you are a team.
- Front or back - Front or back.
(Jong Kook and Haha, Jae Seok and Se Chan are teams.)
- My goodness. - This is good.
The ones with protruding mouths became a team.
- Both of us have protruding mouths. - We are a team.
Team Ugly.
Speak for yourself.
(The partners are set.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Okay. I am serious.
- The middle one will be the best. - Let's choose the middle one.
I want the coach with So Min and Ji Hyo.
It's a train to Gangneung.
- It goes to Pyeongchang. - It only takes an hour and half.
An hour and half? That's fast.
- Let's choose the middle one. - Coach number four.
- Okay. - Coach number four?
- Shall we go? - Let's board the train.
(Which team awaits them?)
(In the three coaches are Team Ji Hyo and So Min, )
(Team Female Guests, )
(and Team Male Guests.)
(We want Team Female Guests.)
Hold on. For goodness' sake.
Did we pick the wrong one?
This is upsetting.
- I can already tell who they are. - For goodness' sake.
The beanie gives away her identity.
The guests wouldn't wear that kind of a beanie.
- The guests would go to a salon. - Seriously.
I knew it.
This is upsetting.
- Hello. - Hello, Haha.
- Hello, Haha. - Hello.
Let's work hard today.
(Jong Kook, Haha, Ji Hyo, and So Min form a team.)
- Why don't we take the front? - Let's do that.
Let's take the front.
- Which coach is left? - The middle one.
- Okay. Coach number six. - We pick coach number five.
- It's the middle one. - Let's go.
(Team Female Guests and Team Male Guests remain.)
- Let's see. - Let's see.
(They have a 50-percent chance of meeting Team Female Guests.)
I don't think this is the right coach.
(Which coach are they in?)
Is it this one?
Are they men or women?
I think they are women.
- They are women. - We picked the right coach!
(My goodness, there are women.)
They are women.
- They are the guests. - They are the guests.
- I can tell from the back... - They are the guests.
That they are the guests.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo are excited to meet the female guests.)
I think we chose the wrong coach.
There are too many people.
- Why are there too many people? - Aren't there two female guests?
We chose the wrong coach.
(There are 5 men with broad backs.)
The right choice is always the opposite of your choice.
Their hats look gloomy.
Look at those hats.
They look old.
Who are they?
Honey.
(Honey.)
(The one who calls him "Honey" in a gravelly voice is...)
(Sechs Kies.)
- It's Sechs Kies. - Honey.
(Honey, you are late.)
- For goodness' sake. - Hello.
- Hello. - Have you been well?
Sechs Kies.
It's nice.
Shake that booty!
Hello.
(Who are the guests with beautiful backs?)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - My goodness, Soyou.
(The healthy beauty, Soyou)
Who is she?
(She is...)
Elijah, you are back!
(The innocent actress, Lee Elijah)
- My goodness. - Hey.
Elisa?
It's Elijah.
- Elijah. - Are you kidding me?
Elijah.
Elijah, you are back.
- Are you the only ones here? - What?
- Are you the only ones here? - We split up into groups.
- Are you the only ones here? - It's just the two of us.
- I repeated myself so many times. - It's disappointing.
- Are you disappointed? - What are you talking about?
I am happy to see you.
- You should be happy to see us. - I am happy to see you.
This is incredible. We chose the right coach.
(The production crew took Korail's safety education.)
The teams have 4, 4, and 7 members respectively.
For today's race, 3 teams of 5 members are needed.
- From the team with seven members, - Perfect!
Two members must move to the other teams.
(2 members must move to the other teams.)
- Come on. - That's good.
- Can Jae Seok and I move? - Yes, you can.
- Anyone can move. - Can we move, too?
- Anyone can move. - My goodness.
You can't go.
- Don't even think about it. - Ji Won became serious.
- Don't even think about it. - He became serious.
Here is what we will do.
Why don't the teams with four members decide...
- which member they want? - Will the first choices move?
That's right. The first choices will move to the other teams.
Tell me which member you want.
(Whispering)
- Su Won. - Really?
So Min wants...
- Su Won. - Su Won.
Seok Jin wants Ji Won.
He isn't the only name you know, right?
What are you talking about?
Then give me their names. Who is he?
Stop it.
(He becomes angry.)
For goodness' sake.
Of course, I know their names!
- What is wrong with you? - You are ridiculous.
My goodness.
- It's a reasonable question. - Tell me.
- Stop it. - I mean...
Why wouldn't I know the names of the six crystals?
Who is he?
Stop it.
- Come on. - Don't be disappointed.
- He doesn't know. - That's not true.
Now, it looks like I really don't know their names.
Su Won will go to So Min's team.
- Yes. - Yes. Come on.
It's Jong Kook's team.
Su Won, this is great. Welcome.
This is amazing.
Kicking out the member who lose in rock-paper-scissors...
would be a better way.
All right. Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The one who loses will join our team.
Seok Jin is looking up Sechs Kies.
I am serious. Seok Jin is looking up Sechs Kies.
- Stop it. - Seok Jin is looking up Sechs Kies.
That's not true.
- Hold on. - Let's win.
- The winner moves. - The winner moves.
- It's a single-round match. - Let's go, Sung Hoon.
(Seok Jin suddenly roots for Sung Hoon.)
- Why are you suddenly doing that? - He began to use their names.
He began to use their names after looking them up.
Sung Hoon, don't lose.
Kang Sung Hoon.
"Kang" means "Strong".
"Sung" means "Achievement".
"Hoon" means "Handsome".
(Team White, Team Gray, and Team Black)
You will have a race to celebrate Pyeongchang Winter Olympics...
with the 1,000-dollar prize money and the water bomb penalty.
- It's freezing outside. - Water bomb?
If you get hit with the water bomb today...
- This is bad. - The water will freeze instantly.
This is Running Man's Loyal Pick, Race of Discontentment.
Someone will be discontent.
Each round has Fire Stickers for the prize money...
and Ice Stickers for the penalty on the line.
The team that places 1st gets 10 Fire Stickers.
The team that places last gets 10 Ice Stickers.
- That's a lot. - Then the team chooses an order...
to play the Loyalty Game.
In the chosen order, the members take as many stickers as they want.
It will make you distrustful.
The one with the most number of Fire Stickers wins...
- and acquires the prize money. - There's only one winner?
The one with the most number of Ice Stickers loses.
The loser and his or her pick gets...
- the water bomb penalty. - Does the loser get to pick one?
- We must be nice to the loser. - Now,
you will have the first mission for the stickers.
The first mission is...
Zombie Game, Train to Pyeongchang.
(Zombie Game, Train to Pyeongchang)
You have three minutes.
The team with the most number of survivors...
who avoid the zombies and cross the finish line wins.
One team will wear blindfolds...
and attack the other team as zombies.
- Two teams will move over. - Let's go.
(Team Offensive versus Team Defensive)
It will be very difficult to go through them.
There is nowhere to go.
One person should continue to make noises.
He or she should do this...
to draw the zombies.
Zombies, please wear blindfolds.
This is scary.
Kwang Soo really looks like a zombie.
(Come, my preys.)
Look at his arms.
(He is serious.)
(Kwang Soo, the zombie, is ready.)
Let's go as a group.
- Jae Duck. - Yes?
Tell me if the people are on your left or right.
- You will be able to sense them. - Okay.
We only need to hold them out for three minutes.
Three minutes is too short.
Let's get started. Get ready.
(Can Jae Seok's team move past the zombies and survive?)
Set.
(The 1st round of Zombie Game starts.)
- Let's go. - Here.
- They went to the right. - The right?
(The zombie bites the bait.)
The right.
(The first obstacle is Soyou, the zombie.)
(She swings her long arms.)
(Careful)
- I didn't feel them. - Where are they?
I don't know.
Did they get past you? Soyou.
No, no one got past me.
Did they get past you?
- Did they get past you? - No one got past me.
- Go to the left. - No one got past you, right?
I will go this way.
(He carefully takes the upper route.)
(Grabbing)
There you are.
(She grabs him.)
(Soyou, the zombie, catches a prey.)
I got one.
- Did you get one? - I got one.
(This is my chance.)
(Ji Won wriggles his way...)
(to the 3rd obstacle.)
Did you get one?
(Moving)
- Someone is passing by. - Where?
Someone is passing by.
(He faces the biggest crisis.)
(The zombies close in on him.)
(Can Ji Won survive?)
I got one!
(Cheerful)
It's me!
- I got one! - It's me!
(He averts the crisis thanks to the zombies' confusion.)
- Why would you grab me? - I am sorry.
(How nice!)
Elijah.
(Ji Won manages to survive by diving to the floor.)
Did he get past me?
Where is he?
I think someone just passed me by.
Someone passed by.
(The scared three can't go forward.)
I think someone just passed me by.
(Jae Jin plucks up his courage and starts moving.)
Where are they? I can't believe this.
- Where are they? - No one has come here yet.
- No? - I don't think they've moved far.
Maybe they're moving slowly on purpose.
Quiet.
Here...
I caught one.
(Soyou reaches her long arms out with an animal instinct.)
- I caught one! - I caught one!
I caught one!
(This is my chance.)
(They try to move while the zombies are distracted by Jae Seok.)
(Ji Won moves past Elijah.)
- I caught one. - Come here.
(Ji Won moves past the last zombie, Kwang Soo.)
(He enters the safe zone.)
(Ji Won survived.)
I caught one.
One minute left.
(There's 1 minute left.)
(Sung Hoon and Se Chan are left.)
Okay.
(Will they survive?)
There's one over here.
(You're hiding there.)
I caught one!
(Jae Duck is about to catch Se Chan.)
Where did he go? I caught one!
(Se Chan gets down on the floor.)
- Hold on. - I caught one!
- I caught one. - I caught one.
I caught one.
This part is difficult.
(Sung Hoon moves forward.)
I caught one!
(I caught one!)
I'm a staff member.
You're a staff member?
(It's easy to deceive a zombie.)
There's only one minute left.
No one has succeeded yet.
(We've succeeded.)
(Team Jae Seok's Ji Won and Sung Hoon survive.)
- Did you catch them all? - Two survived.
Really?
- Two survived. - How did you do it?
Two survived?
How could you not catch any?
- When did Sung Hoon pass by? - When did you pass by?
(Offense: Seok Jin, Kwang Soo, Elijah Soyou, and Jae Duck)
(Defense: Ji Hyo, So Min, Jong Kook, Haha, and Su Won)
We have to pass by Jong Kook.
They have Jong Kook.
What should we do?
Wouldn't you pass out if you get hit by him?
Is it really okay?
Is it okay?
We have to catch them, right?
Gosh.
(The 3rd zombie is very muscular.)
Ready.
And...
(Will Team Seok Jin survive the zombies?)
(The 2nd round of the zombie game begins.)
Let's go!
- Here we go! - There's one here.
(The 1st zombie is Haha.)
(Careful)
Here we go!
Someone is passing by.
I just felt something.
(Soyou was able to dodge Haha.)
I caught one!
(I caught one!)
- I caught one. - It's my arm.
(It's my arm.)
Hold on.
- It was Haha. - The cameraman is here.
I caught one.
(Elijah tries to go past the 1st zombie.)
Someone is passing by. Someone's here.
- Where? - Hair?
- Someone's passing by. - I caught one.
- I caught one. - Where?
Someone's passing by again. I caught one.
(Elijah goes past So Min too.)
(Soyou starts to move.)
I hear a sound from the left side.
- Here. - Who is it?
- It's me. - Someone is here.
Something touched my leg. Someone is here.
Something touched my leg.
Something just passed on the right.
(The male members have yet to start moving.)
Someone's passing by again.
(Distracted)
Someone is here.
Something touched my leg.
Something is touching my right leg.
Something just passed by on my right side.
(Gosh)
- I caught one! - You caught one?
I caught one.
- I caught one. - I caught one.
(Let me try.)
I caught one. It's Seok Jin.
Where?
- I caught one. - I caught one.
I caught one.
(It's my turn.)
(Jae Duck and Kwang Soo are stuck at the 2nd hurdle.)
Hey!
Someone is on the left side.
On the left side?
(I have to break through.)
(Jae Duck escapes.)
You caught one? Keep him.
- Who is it? - Who is it?
(Kwang Soo fights with a zombie.)
Who is it?
It must be Kwang Soo. Over here.
(Kwang Soo makes a strategic retreat.)
Someone is on the left side.
(He has to hide his pain.)
Someone is here.
Where?
(No one has succeeded yet.)
(We don't have much time left.)
- Who is it? - It's me.
(We can't wait any longer. Move forward, Elijah!)
Soyou is a bait.
- I'll keep Soyou. - Okay.
Soyou!
Get her!
Soyou.
Hold on. Soyou.
(Nice teamwork.)
I'm sorry, Ji Hyo.
- I love you. - I'll keep Soyou.
I can't move.
I love you.
(Escaping)
Someone is here!
(Jae Duck has been spotted by Ji Hyo.)
Su Won, someone is here!
(Will he be able to escape?)
Someone just passed by.
On the left side.
(Will Jae Duck escape with his agility?)
Jae Duck!
(This is my chance.)
(Approaching)
Su Won, to the right. To the left.
(Thanks to Soyou, Jae Duck enters the safe zone.)
(Jae Duck survives.)
Elijah escaped.
To the left.
(Kwang Soo is the only one left.)
I have to keep Seok Jin, right?
I'm keeping him.
- Someone is breathing very heavily. - Someone is passing by.
Who is it? It's me. Why do you touch my chest?
(She accidentally touches Jong Kook's chest.)
So Min!
(Oh, was it your chest?)
(She was working too hard.)
- I can't see anything. I'm sorry. - I chose the wrong outfit.
Who is it? Someone is here.
Someone is here.
I caught one!
(Hitting)
(He struggles to survive, )
(but the time is over.)
- Hey, come here. - Jong Kook.
I didn't mean to.
- You hit my head. - I thought you were a zombie.
I couldn't move past here.
- Elijah was so fast. - She's good.
Me?
- It's a tie. - It's 2 to 2.
(Offense: Ji Hyo, So Min, Jong Kook, Haha, and Su Won)
(Defense: Jae Seok, Se Chan, Sung Hoon, Ji Won, and Jae Jin)
The zombies are coming.
If I catch Jong Kook, I'll use my strength.
Be my guest.
No, I won't. Just pass me by.
Tap me on the shoulder twice, and I'll move to the right.
Tap me on the shoulder, and I'll...
"Go, Jong Kook."
It looks so dense.
He'll hit you.
- They look so strong. - They're all guys.
They look robust.
Let's get it.
Here we go. You have three minutes. Start when I blow the whistle.
Ready, and...
(The 3rd round of the zombie game starts.)
(Come on.)
(Jae Jin waves his arms.)
One person is coming.
(Team Jong Kook is trying to distract the zombies with sounds.)
Someone is coming.
(Guys, )
(let's go.)
(Jong Kook confronts the zombie.)
(The others move forward.)
Jong Kook, it hurts!
(What is this human being doing?)
(Do you remember those muscular guys in zombie movies?)
It hurts! Hold on.
(They fight the zombies with bare hands.)
Hold on.
Wait. Let go of me.
(Jong Kook is sacrificing himself for the team.)
- Wait! - What are you doing?
(All zombies, come to me.)
Hold on, Jong Kook...
What is this?
(Let go of me.)
What is he doing?
Get him!
He's a zombie.
Hey, get them!
Jong Kook got us.
He's a zombie!
- What are you doing? - Gosh.
I caught one.
(So Min is out.)
(The zombies are distracted by So Min.)
Wait. Where are you grabbing?
(Su Won manages to escape.)
I caught one.
(Su Won survives.)
- I caught one. - Hurry.
Gosh!
Someone is over here.
Someone is here.
Where?
Here. I got him.
- I got him. - You got him?
(All the zombies are on the right side.)
(Ji Hyo tries to move forward on the left side.)
(The last zombie is waiting.)
(Ji Hyo, please survive.)
Who is it?
(So Min sacrifices herself.)
(Ji Hyo enters the safe zone.)
- Who is it? - We caught one.
We caught one.
It's over.
Su Won survived.
Isn't he the only one?
There are more.
(Why are there two?)
- Ji Hyo survived. - My goodness.
How did you miss them?
If I were in the front, I would've probably caught three.
Our scores are tied.
They're all tied.
(We used an empty coach to film the show.)
We have the results.
- Okay. - Okay.
Two members from each team survived.
- What about duration? - Based on the duration...
(Determine the winner by the duration of survival.)
- We were fast. - That means my team won.
- Duration of survival? - The winning team is...
It's our team.
(Which team...)
(will win 10 Fire Stickers?)
Soyou and Lee Elijah.
(Team Seok Jin wins.)
I didn't expect that.
- Why? - Why did they win?
They were caught the latest after 2 minutes 59 seconds.
Goodness.
We won.
Who came second place?
The second place winner...
is Team Jong Kook.
Good job.
They had an advantage.
We were so close. We did well.
We were so close.
We were caught too quickly by Jong Kook.
The winning team gets 10 Fire Stickers.
(Team Seok Jin wins 10 Fire Stickers.)
10 is a lot.
The losing team gets 10 Ice Stickers.
What about the team in second place?
You have a chance to guess the member who took...
the one with the most Fire Stickers and the one with the least Ice Stickers.
If you guess correctly,
Fire Stickers get switched with Ice Stickers.
That's a big twist.
If you guess the member with the least number of Ice Stickers,
the member will get additional Ice Stickers to match the maximum.
If the team guesses correctly,
each member will receive a Fire Sticker.
If you guess incorrectly, each member will receive an Ice Sticker.
It's complicated.
Shall we play rock-paper-scissors?
Or shall we go in the order of age?
(Seok Jin makes a sudden suggestion.)
- It's because... - Shall the youngest go first?
- Shall the youngest go first? - Shall the oldest go first?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors instead.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo, Jae Duck, and Elijah win.)
- Okay. - Okay.
We'll take two each.
- Kwang Soo can't be the 1st. - He can't be the 1st.
- You must win. - Jae Duck won.
No, we'll take two each.
I keep my word.
- Let's play. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- You must win no matter what. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo and Elijah win.)
It's over for them.
- I still have a chance. - Kwang Soo must lose.
- It has to be over six. - I have a chance.
Please win.
If Kwang Soo wins, it's over for them.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Elijah wins.)
Thank goodness.
Kwang Soo must be sad.
Okay, please start.
Go, Elijah.
Which one should I choose?
If they select me, do mine turn into Ice Stickers?
- If you have the most. - Right.
Elijah is competitive too.
(She ponders for a while.)
(Which one will she choose?)
You don't need to think so hard.
He won't make it.
He's taking a long time.
He's taking long to count.
Winning a lot right now is pointless.
- Let's see. - Elijah.
Listen.
What?
- Who's next? - Who's next?
How many will it be?
Indicate the number with your fingers.
Is it good to take many?
(What's going on?)
What happened?
What?
(There are none left.)
He's still deciding.
How many should I take?
- Can I take all? - Of course.
- All of them? - Yes.
- You can take all. - Take up to half.
(The two took all 10.)
He'll make a guess.
- Who's next? - It's me.
(Seok Jin takes a look.)
(He doesn't know what to do.)
(He pretends as if some stickers remain.)
People were conscientious.
Seok Jin has nothing.
Nothing was left for him.
He definitely doesn't have any.
They were conscientious.
- What? - Seok Jin.
Take all the rest.
Soyou, take all the rest.
That's why...
Listen.
If a member on your team is annoying,
- you'd want to guess him. - Goodness.
If you guess correctly who has the most Fire Stickers...
among those who have them,
each member gets a Fire Sticker.
The stickers of the one who had the most will switch to Ice.
That's incredible.
I hope Kwang Soo gets them.
- He will. - If you guess incorrectly,
each member will get an Ice Sticker.
The answer is obvious if Kwang Soo went first,
but it could be Elijah.
Look carefully into Elijah's eyes. She could be cunning.
(She may be a trickster.)
- No. - She's like us.
It's possible.
They recognize each other.
Doesn't So Min recognize it?
- Can you check? - Isn't she a trickster?
- Can you check? - She definitely is.
- She is. - See?
(So Min confirms it.)
She's definitely a trickster.
Whom do you guess?
It's 1 of the 2.
(Is it Elijah or Kwang Soo?)
I pick Elijah. I want to try something new today.
Shout in the count of three.
In 3, 2, 1.
- Elijah. - Elijah.
(Everyone guesses Elijah.)
(Did Elijah take the most number of Fire Stickers?)
- Elijah... - Please.
Did not take the most...
(Did she take the most number of stickers?)
- Fire Stickers. - Isn't that obvious?
- Come on. - It must be Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo is acting again. - The number of stickers she took...
- How many? - is three.
She took a lot.
Three is a lot.
(She was afraid of her stickers turning into Ice Stickers.)
(She took 3 stickers.)
(She took 3 instead of 2.)
(Kwang Soo checked the remaining stickers.)
Seven.
(He takes all.)
(It's not surprising.)
Each member on the team receives an Ice Sticker.
(Each gets one Ice Sticker.)
- She didn't take the most. - We all got it.
(How could he take 7?)
It's because...
Stop pretending.
- Is it you after me? - Yes.
They might guess me.
Go on.
(I'm sorry. You'll get used to it.)
That's it for Fire Stickers.
It's time for Ice Stickers.
Jae Seok will take more than one.
(The one who takes the most gets penalized.)
I don't want to take any.
(After pondering, )
(they make a decision.)
- It's your turn. - I knew it.
Next up is Se Chan.
- You'll be penalized. - I'm the last.
- Yes, it's automatic. - What do you think?
It was impressive.
(My goodness)
(There are 5 stickers left.)
You'll take at least six.
- Seriously. - He'll take at least six.
(5 stickers remain.)
- Look at him. - How could you?
All of you surprise me.
One of you betrayed.
Someone didn't take any.
Someone pulled a trick.
- It's someone wearing a beanie. - My guess is...
My guess is Jae Seok.
- Let's pick Ji Won. - Okay.
- I think it's Jae Jin. - Who?
- Jae Jin? - I think it's him.
He's suspicious because he's not talking much.
- Right. - Jae Jin is blushing too.
- Let's do it. - Take a guess.
1, 2, 3.
- Jae Jin. - Jae Jin.
I'm curious.
Here's the answer.
Did Jae Jin take the least number of Ice Stickers?
(Did he take the least number of stickers?)
That's correct.
(He took the least number of stickers.)
- Wasn't I right? - It was right.
Wasn't I right?
Jae Jin didn't take any Ice Stickers.
(He took 0.)
I knew it was Jae Jin.
Can I take nothing?
- It's possible. - I won't take any.
(He played selfishly.)
(He didn't know.)
How could he take nothing?
Jae Jin will get the same number of Ice Stickers...
as the member who has the most.
- Does he get as many as me? - Yes.
That serves you right.
I knew it when you pulled a trick. It serves you right.
Gosh, what a relief.
(Number of Fire and Ice Stickers per member)
It's snow.
It's very high.
Look at that.
(It's very high.)
(They arrive where the Olympics will be held.)
That's impressive.
Amazing.
Do we get penalized here?
It's so cold.
This looks intense.
(He gets attacked.)
(So Min throws snow at Kwang Soo.)
I knew they'd cause trouble.
That looks terrible.
- I agree. - Right?
(This is so much fun.)
(Kwang Soo counterattacks.)
Jong Kook!
(She runs for help.)
Why do you always look for me when he's after you?
You're the strongest.
Did it hit you?
(Please scold Kwang Soo.)
Are you okay?
Kwang Soo.
Stop bothering So Min.
(Punching)
(He takes her to the ground.)
(Wait a minute.)
Goodness.
(This scene looks familiar.)
(They look friendly as they play in the snow.)
(It's the exact scene from "Love Story".)
(Look at the snow, So Min.)
(Catch me if you can.)
No.
(What are they doing?)
Stop it.
Snow got inside my clothes.
- Are you okay? - I'm not okay, you punk.
(She curses at him.)
Hey.
- Stop it, you two. - You guys should never date.
- Don't ever date each other. - You are not meant to be.
Hey, come back here.
(Their love story ends with a fight again.)
Hey, it's...
- It's... - Yes?
Snowing a lot here. The snow built up here.
- Everyone is feeling sentimental. - I know, right?
- Elijah was singing. - She was singing?
(A while ago)
(Promise me, even if I might not be perfect)
- Which song did you sing? - Sing it. Start.
(She sang "In Summer"?)
That's not the song you sang.
(The skies are open towards us)
- That's "In Summer". - Sing the song you sang earlier.
Why did she sing that song in winter?
The skies are open toward us!
This is what I mean about actors and actresses.
They do a good job at presenting themselves.
(Look at her.)
They do market themselves a lot.
So many actresses are weird like her.
(Elijah does show some signs of being slightly different.)
(As soon as she sings the song, a snow storm engulfs them.)
(What's the mission they'll play in the winter kingdom at minus 13C?)
- It's cold. Let me speed it up. - Okay.
Your mission is...
Shivering Ski Jumping.
(Their mission is Shivering Ski Jumping.)
- I'm shivering in this weather. - It's freezing.
The weather does make me shiver.
Within the time limit, 100 seconds, 2 representatives of each team...
will do the skiing and jumping poses on the side.
They can only mimic sounds and do gestures to explain the problems.
The team that answers more questions in a relay will win.
Choose your two representatives.
The theme will be movies.
- Movies. - All right then.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay. Let's do that.
- Okay. Let's do that. Ji Hyo. - Let's play that.
- Me? - Elijah, you should do it.
- No, no. This is a lot of pressure. - Just play it. Do it.
- This comes with a lot of pressure. - You don't have to win.
- Elijah. - Yes?
You should either wear the hat or take it off.
(I'm sorry to point this out, but do something with the hat.)
(It's placed awkwardly.)
Put it on.
(Even her hat is clumsy.)
- That's better. That's much better. - Just put it on.
- All right. Rock-paper... - Don't be nervous.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Su Won and Elijah win.)
- Okay. - What is it?
- She won. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Elijah wins Su Won.)
- The winner will go first! - No way!
- Your team must go 1st. - The losing team will go 1st.
- You must go first. You wanted it. - No, we didn't.
- The winning team must go 1st. - No, the losing team must go 1st.
No, my gloves!
- You punk. - No, my gloves!
(Elijah's gloves get stuck on Seok Jin's name tag.)
- "No, my gloves!" - What a mess!
She said, "No, my gloves."
My gloves.
(She is fighting for her gloves while others fight each other.)
- The losing team should go first. - I agree.
- Hurry. - Do rock-paper-scissors for it.
This is for foreign films, and this is for Korean films. Got it?
- This is for foreign films. - We've been brainwashed.
- That's cheating. - It's for the number of syllables.
Look at them. They are making signs.
I can't believe they are making signals.
You shouldn't allow that!
How could they do that?
The number of syllables for the title.
- It's not right! Tell him! - What do you mean?
- What are you talking about? - You're doing that again?
- He can't do that. - What?
- You can't give out signs. - You should've done it too.
Hey.
If we don't follow his order, he scolds us.
(I don't want to do it either, but he scolds us.)
- I get that. - Seriously.
- Okay. - You're right.
He scolds us if we don't.
Okay!
(Haha will mimic sounds, and So Min will do gestures.)
- We are starting now. - Jong Kook,
I'm sorry, but can you not block the keyword?
(Please don't block the keyword.)
Oh, I see. Where is it? Okay.
My gosh, you've got some guts.
(I'm Jong Kook's trainer.)
- Hey, Jong Kook. Move aside. - Let me go first.
(The 1st keyword is given.)
(He gives out the 1st onomatopoeic word.)
(She kneels down and throws her hands up.)
What's that? What was the title?
- What's that? I know that! - That was...
(Mumbling)
(Kneeling down)
I want to go back!
Is he Maeng Gu? Did he turn into Maeng Gu?
He looks like Maeng Gu.
(He somewhat resembles Maeng Gu.)
(It's the famous scene from "Peppermint Candy".)
- How could they not get it? - The title. I must say the title.
- "Peppermint Candy". - Okay!
(Ji Hyo answers it correctly.)
(The next up is Su Won.)
(The keyword is "Titanic".)
"Titanic". It's "Titanic".
(It's Jong Kook's turn.)
That one was a giveaway.
(Gosh, this is a difficult one.)
Why do I always get the hard ones?
(Is he crying?)
(So Min throws something while sitting down.)
What is this one?
- Gosh, So Min. - "Memories of Murder".
"Memories of Murder"?
Gosh, So Min did such a good job.
(Her gesture is just like the one from the film.)
(Haha is wailing, and So Min is throwing something.)
(It's this scene from "The Wailing".)
(Jong Kook's still lost.)
- She's throwing a stone. - "The Lord of the Rings"?
That's a Korean film. You're throwing a stone?
(Their teammates haven't even gotten close to the answer.)
(So Min is tired of throwing stones.)
(Okay. It's time for me to take charge now.)
- A joint film of Korea and Japan. - Stop it. Don't talk.
(Enunciating)
- Haha just spoke. - Hey.
- That's enough. - Okay, okay.
He just spoke a phrase.
Thank you.
- Don't talk! - Hey.
- Hey, you can't talk! - Stop talking.
- Why are you talking? - You're not supposed to talk!
- The film... - Is that what matters now?
I know that. I can't remember the title. What is it?
- That one doesn't count. - It's "The Wailing".
- It was "The Wailing". - Gosh.
I knew the film, but I just couldn't remember the title.
How am I supposed to do this?
(This is it. Ta-da!)
(It's the most famous pose of Elsa from "Frozen".)
"La La Land"?
My gosh, we are at a "frozen" world.
(He starts talking again.)
- Hey! - Enough.
- Haha. - He cheated.
- What are you doing? - Okay, I'll stop.
I'll be serious now.
- We can't count this again. - Okay.
- I'll pass. - It's hard! How should I do this?
Move back. Back up now.
("The Exorcist")
What should I do?
(It's a difficult keyword.)
(Lying down)
(They must know this famous scene, right?)
- This is... - What is she doing?
What's that?
(He mimics the sounds the ghost makes perfectly.)
(They seem quite peculiar, but it looks like a horror film.)
- "The Exorcist". "The Exorcist". - "The Exorcist".
- What's that? - "The Exorcist"?
- Is that something else? - "The Exorcist"?
("Spider-Man")
It's "Spider-Man".
(They were so close, but time is up.)
- My gosh, it was so hard. - We got three questions?
- You answered three questions. - How could you not know the titles?
Hey, to be honest,
- So Min did well for "The Wailing". - Hey.
- So Min did a great job. - She was just like that actress.
- Even her expression was the same. - "A joint film".
(So Min and Haha's hard work was evident.)
(Soyou mimics sounds, and Elijah does gestures next.)
(Team Female Guests comes 1st after answering 5 questions.)
(Jae Jin and Se Chan's great teamwork puts them in 2nd place.)
(Team Male Guests is in 2nd place after answering 4 questions.)
We were so close.
So Team Female Guests takes first place.
- Okay! - They won again.
Team Male Guests takes second place.
We're better than the other team. We are in second place at least.
Gosh, you guys just wait.
- The winning team. - We are last.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Okay.
(They will decide the order to choose the stickers.)
You know what? It's a war now.
- I can't trust you. I won't! - No, no.
- We'll reveal them again, right? - Yes.
- Then let's each take two. - All right.
- Let's take two each. - I'm serious this time.
- Let's take two. - They are going to reveal them.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
(The order is Elijah, Jae Duck, )
(Kwang Soo, Seok Jin, and Soyou.)
Come, please.
(Don't forget to take just 2.)
Point the ones you want in the briefcase.
(After thinking hard about it, )
(Elijah takes 3 Fire Stickers.)
(Let me take one more.)
How many did you take?
- You should go. - It's my turn.
All right. Next member, please come.
Let me know how many you want with your fingers.
(There are three empty spots.)
(Come on, Elijah. I knew you'd do this.)
Elijah went first, right?
It's really hard to decide.
(Their plan is already a bust.)
(Jae Duck thinks hard about it. How many will he take?)
- Jae Duck might take a lot. - Let one person take them all.
I thought the same thing. He went second.
Kwang Soo.
Use your fingers to tell me how many you want.
(I see. This is what it has come to.)
Kwang Soo will take everything if there's anything left. I'm sure.
Isn't...
Isn't today about our love for our team?
I...
I will not take any.
(Does he mean that he won't take any stickers?)
Everyone, gather around.
It's time for Team Male Guests to choose.
I don't think Kwang Soo took all the remaining stickers...
since he took seven stickers from the previous mission.
I bet he probably took two if he took any.
I thought about it objectively.
Right now, I have the most stickers.
If 1 of these 2 guests win,
they probably are in first place.
I'm certain Elijah took the most.
Excuse me.
Your words just slurred.
It's because I'm cold.
- Are you okay? - That's what I think.
- Yes, I'm okay. - Don't accuse me.
- Are you all right? - Jae Duck took a lot too,
- but Elijah took the most. - Wait.
- Don't say such a thing. - I'm vulnerable to cold weathers.
(His mouth is frozen.)
I think it must be either Elijah or Jae Duck.
Elijah might get greedy about this mission.
I'm sure she took either 3 or 4.
This is hard even in terms of probability.
- We have no choice. It's Elijah. - I'm sure she took them.
- Let's go with Elijah. - No.
No, I think it's Jae Duck. What about you?
- Okay. Let's go with Jae Duck then. - I think...
When he wanted to take the stickers,
he couldn't take any because Kwang Soo took all of it.
- Okay. Let's go with Jae Duck. - I think so too.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- It's Jae Duck. - It's Jae Duck.
All right. Jae Duck is the member...
(If Team White is right, all the members will get 1 Fire Sticker, )
(and Jae Duck's Fire Stickers will be switched with Ice Stickers.)
He has the most Fire Stickers.
(Team White was right.)
We were right!
(How did they know?)
(There were 7 Fire Stickers.)
(He took them all.)
Jae Duck took seven Fire Stickers.
You took seven?
All of them will be switched with Ice Stickers.
(All of his 7 Fire Stickers will be switched with Ice Stickers.)
Ji Hyo.
Just do what you want.
(Haha is thinking.)
Ice Stickers are difficult.
(Haha takes 2.)
I'll take...
(Jong Kook takes 2.)
(There are 5 Ice Stickers left.)
(Su Won wants to take all 5?)
(So Min has nothing to take.)
(Empty)
I'm so...
That's not important.
This is...
Team White.
Team White, please make a decision.
Let's choose Haha.
- How many did he take? - One.
- He took one. - Haha.
(If they're right, all the members will get one Fire Sticker.)
1, 2, 3.
- Haha. - Haha.
Haha would give one back.
Haha is not the member who has the least Ice Stickers.
He isn't?
- Aren't I amazing? - You are.
I'm like a mom these days.
I'm so generous.
- Who is it then? - Haha has...
- two. - So Min must have nothing.
The member with the least Ice Stickers is...
So Min, who has none.
We're amazing.
Wasn't she the last member?
- Yes. - That's right.
Su Won took a lot.
- He took a lot. - Su Won, you're amazing.
- Su Won... Hold on. - He's amazing.
Is there something going on?
(What's going on?)
Hey.
(So Min wanted Su Won on her team.)
(Me?)
(There was something going on from the morning.)
- Right now... - Don't start this.
- Oh, really? - It's not too late. Do you want it?
No. I'm fine.
(Nothing is going on.)
As a result, all the members of Team White...
will get 1 Fire Sticker and 1 Ice Sticker.
Let's go to the next place to have lunch.
(The members of Team White get 1 Fire Sticker and 1 Ice Sticker.)
(Ski Jumping Sticker Results)
(A beef place in Pyeongchang)
- I see something. - What's that?
Oh, my.
- What's that? - Hello.
What's that?
Look at all the beef.
I want tenderloin.
I love yukhoe.
- Look it's rib-eye. - Rib-eye.
- That's the best part. - It's crazy.
- Can we eat them? - Chuck flap tail.
We could share them.
Look at the marbling. It looks amazing.
(They're impressed.)
There's ramyeon too.
Nurungji ramyeon?
(Nurungji ramyeon)
- To be honest, ramyeon is the best. - No, it isn't.
- What? - Here?
- Are you serious? - You should eat beef.
- You should eat beef. - You want to eat ramyeon...
- at a beef place? - We don't want to.
- That rib-eye looks great. - Rib eye.
Can we eat this too?
So Min.
I want to eat them.
(Pyeongchang's specialty, gummy worms)
Why are there fish-shaped buns?
- Why are there fish-shaped buns? - There's beef jerky too.
You'll decide what to have for lunch yourself.
We slide the stones?
- Do you see the curling board? - Yes.
(It's a mini curling board.)
They're rice bowls.
(They'll use rice bowls as stones.)
You'll compete for food and Chance Cards.
Each rice bowl has a name on it.
You'll have to slide it into the target.
Depending on where your stone ends up,
you're lunch menu will be determined.
If someone's stone ends up on the center of the target,
he or she can choose what to eat...
and switch his or her bag with someone else's.
You can switch your bag with someone else's?
- Kwang Soo, be careful. - Chance Cards...
I have just one more sticker.
Elijah and Kwang Soo...
You're our targets.
(Elijah and Kwang Soo, we'll take your stickers away.)
Gummy worms are the worst.
- We have to push others' away. - Gummy worms...
Cheongyang chili and kimchi are the worst.
What a weird combination.
- Yukhoe would be fine too. - I like yukhoe.
Beef jerky... I'm not sure.
Doenjang jjigae is fine too.
Garlic and green onion salad is the worst.
I just want to eat something.
(I wouldn't mind any food.)
We should practice.
It's harder than you think.
It's not slippery.
It doesn't slide well.
- It's not so easy. - It doesn't slide well.
You have to use a lot of force.
- Control your strength. - You have to slide it far.
It might rebound too.
I want rib-eye.
I can only reach ramyeon.
(Rubbing)
(Please slide far.)
I'll win the tenderloin.
(So Min is determined.)
Rib-eye.
(Let me show you something.)
(Ji Won can hit any target he wants.)
That's how you do it.
I can hit anything.
(What's this?)
(He hits it again.)
I can hit anything.
Hey, look at this.
(He could even be on the national curling team.)
- Look at this. - Gosh.
(He can hit anything.)
I can hit anything I want.
Ji Won can hit anything he wants.
I can hit anything.
You have only one chance. If it escapes, you don't get a menu.
- You don't get a menu? - Goodness.
It's better to go later.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
The teams will take turns.
- We'll take turns. - One member from each team...
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Let's do that.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay. Ji Won.
Ji Won.
(I have a good feeling.)
Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Yes. - Nice.
- It doesn't matter. - Ji Hyo wins every time.
She always wins.
Let's go.
Go, Ji Hyo.
Number five is not good.
Take it easy.
- Use a lot of force. - Slide it far.
Use a lot of force.
(What will Ji Hyo hit?)
- Nice. - Nice.
We don't know yet.
(Nurungji ramyeon)
- Someone will push mine anyway. - Yes.
- Jae Duck. - Second person.
Ji Hyo will...
Someone will probably push hers forward.
It's the perfect spot.
I don't have to push Ji Hyo's, right?
No.
Don't push hers.
Let's see.
- Hit the side like pool. - I want a Chance Card.
Aim for right in front of the camera.
- Just do it. - It's okay.
(His stone slides towards the center.)
- A Chance Card? - Rib-eye?
(Rib-eye)
(He can already taste the rib-eye.)
(Team White's Ji Won)
I'll hit Jae Duck's.
Push Jae Duck's away.
(Ji Won shows off amazing skills during practice.)
- Ji Won is amazing. - I can hit anything.
(Let me aim for the rib-eye.)
I'll hit Jae Duck's.
Push Jae Duck's away.
Hit both Ji Hyo's and Jae Duck's.
- Hit them both. - No.
Like when you play pool.
I think he'll do a good job.
(Like a sniper, Ji Won aims for the rib-eye.)
(He slides his stone carefully.)
(Will his stone hit the rib-eye?)
- Out! - Out!
(It did hit Ji Hyo's stone, )
(but it went out of the board.)
(He used too much power.)
(His stone flies over Pyeongchang.)
(The rice bowl lid has been launched successfully.)
It's out.
- He was too greedy. - Ji Won's out.
- What should he do? - He was too greedy.
- Whose turn is it? - Good luck.
It's my turn. It doesn't slide well.
Aim for chuck flap tail.
Come here.
(He can hear the beef grilling.)
- Nice. - No!
- Yukhoe. - Yukhoe.
I prefer grilled beef.
(I want grilled beef.)
- Grill your yukhoe. - You can grill it.
Jae Duck still has the rib-eye.
- Nice. - Good luck.
- Soyou. - Here we go.
- Just slide it. - Aim for beef.
- Rib-eye and a Chance Card. - Tenderloin.
Yukhoe is nice.
Don't distract her.
(They're distracting her by singing her song.)
(The beef will be as soft as her voice.)
Gosh! Ramyeon.
- I like it. - I like it.
- Ramyeon. - That's nice.
(She sounds like Jeon In Kwon.)
I didn't know Soyou could sound like that.
I was so shocked.
(Screaming)
(Embarrassed)
Let's give up on food.
Let's just push all the stones away.
I can't push them away well.
(It's Jae Seok's turn.)
It's hard.
They're blocking the way.
They're in the way.
(Trusting the other members, )
(he wants to push away all the other team's stones.)
(Will Ji Won and Jae Seok's teamwork bring success?)
- Gosh. - What have you done?
(He gets garlic and seasoned spring onions.)
All right. Good job.
What have you done?
(At least it's red like meat.)
- Seasoned spring onions? - I'm jealous.
Wait a minute.
- Listen to me. - This would have been better.
- How could you? - When you eat...
When you eat meat, you need garlic and seasoned spring onions.
- We didn't win meat. - We'll win.
This is humiliating. An out is better than this.
It'd be perfect if Se Chan gets Cheongyang chili.
We'll get a stomachache if we eat this.
We'll die.
You should win meat.
- We should try to get gummy worms. - Is it our turn?
- Go ahead. - Let's go.
- If So Min pushes the others... - We'd lose.
- Good luck. - Do well. That's right.
Here she goes.
(Her lid approaches.)
(She wins a bowl of ramyeon.)
Why is everyone blocking?
- It's blocked. - That's good.
- That's a relief. - It could have been better.
Is everyone helping out Jae Duck?
The next person should get garlic and seasoned spring onions.
- Next is Kwang Soo. - Go.
Okay.
(Next up is Kwang Soo.)
- Don't move ours, okay? - Okay.
Kwang Soo, you should hit Soyou's.
- I want to eat at least a piece. - You should hit Soyou's.
You can't go in the field.
Wait a minute.
Don't go in the field.
Think of this as the Olympics. We're in Pyeongchang after all.
(He becomes speechless.)
- Goodness. - He's really upset.
He was being serious.
It's impossible to win meat.
- Kwang Soo. - You should approach here.
Will it bounce off?
You should get doenjang jjigae.
- Kwang Soo, hit Soyou's. - Go this way.
- If not... - If you hit Soyou's,
you can win a Chance Card and the rib-eye.
You should hit Soyou's. Don't you want to be a star?
A star?
I'll make you a star.
Hit all three of them out.
We're on the same team.
Let's share some rib-eye.
We can eat some at least.
- Think carefully, Kwang Soo. - No.
- You should win. - This is right.
Do what best suits you.
It's best to hit Soyou's.
(He's more serious than ever.)
(He concentrates like a national athlete.)
(While everyone's attention is on him...)
- Push toward the left. - How about this?
Can I approach the middle and win a Chance Card?
- It's hard to get through. - You should stay in the circle.
- It might bounce off. - It's completely possible.
- Is it? - Did you take your turn?
- Didn't you take your turn? - What?
(There's no such thing as practice.)
- He already went. - He did it.
- Didn't he go? - Didn't he?
- That was short. - He went.
- Come on. - You already went.
- It's over. - He already went.
- No way. - Get out of the way.
- Get out of the way. - How is this possible?
(Sighing)
- I didn't. - He had his chance.
That doesn't count.
- It does count. - As soon as you let it go.
- Good job. - Where are we?
- We're in Pyeongchang. - Right.
We must play fair.
You must play fair.
I forgot that we're in Pyeongchang. I'm so silly.
You're silly.
Who's next?
- Is it the end? - Yes.
Pyeongchang is all about being fair.
(Lost for words)
- We're in Pyeongchang. - Good job.
- That's it. - We're next.
Remember that we get no practice. Play right away.
- It's Sung Hoon. - Sung Hoon.
- Is he next? - Come, Sung Hoon.
It's over once you let it go.
He'll do well.
- Sung Hoon is good. - Give it a try.
- This is rather difficult. - He's not bad.
- Give it a try. - Push it hard.
My goodness.
(Gummy worms)
(They win garlic, seasoned spring onions, and gummy worms.)
- It's gummy worms. - He blocked it.
- It's completely blocked. - He blocked it.
(He helped block the rib-eye.)
It's blocked.
- That was good. - We should hit it this way.
How can we get through?
What should we do?
I bet Su Won will get through.
- Look. - It was too short.
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
- Good job. - Are you okay?
Did you get hurt?
- Next is Elijah. - It's Elijah.
- Let's go. - Her pose looks professional?
What will it be?
- Look at her pose. - What is it?
(It went too far.)
That's a home run.
What happened? Where did you aim?
- I don't know. - She was too greedy.
I should hit the others.
- Try to hit them. - No way.
- If you cross... - He let it go.
- He let it go. - Okay.
- Everyone is so sensitive. - It doesn't count.
- Everyone is sensitive. - You could lose your chance.
- I understand. - It's over...
- if it goes up. - Okay.
- Good job. - Don't be so nasty.
- 8, 7. - Stop counting.
- It makes me nervous. Stop it. - 6, 5.
- 4, 3, 2, 1. - 4, 3, 2, 1.
- He gets gummy worms. - It's gummy worms.
Eating gummy worms in this cold weather will break our jaw.
(They get two bags of gummy worms and seasoned spring onions.)
My goodness.
- We're almost there. - My goodness.
Come on.
(Jong Kook is next.)
- Please win meat, Jong Kook. - Win meat.
(Jong Kook, please win meat.)
- Please win meat, Jong Kook. - 5, 4.
(Yukhoe and ramyeon are only side dishes.)
(Let's win some grilled meat.)
Two.
(Get through the other lids.)
(His strength made something bounce off.)
(Jong Kook is out.)
(Sung Hoon moves to the rib-eye instead.)
(Jae Duck moves from the rib-eye to beef jerky.)
Did Jae Duck land on the Chance Card?
- What happened? - It's beef jerky.
- It moved to the beef jerky. - It's beef jerky.
It's beef jerky.
- Sung Hoon. - No way.
(He lost the rib-eye and ends up with beef jerky.)
(Team White wins the rib-eye.)
- We got the rib-eye. - My goodness.
- What happened? - We got it.
Am I out?
- Look. - Am I out?
- Rib-eye, rib-eye. - Rib-eye, rib-eye.
That was so accurate.
- Jong Kook did it. - This is crazy.
- It's because of Jong Kook. - Jong Kook.
(There's loss and victory.)
- We got rib-eye. - Rib-eye?
- I can't believe it. - I'm jealous.
Garlic and seasoned spring onions will be useful in the end.
I just need a Chance Card.
- It won't be easy. - This is sad.
- It's possible. - It is.
- Go on. - Try it.
- This is incredible. - Give it a try.
It'd be incredible if he hits mine into tenderloin.
- Where did it land? - It'd be incredible...
if he hits mine into tenderloin.
(It hits Jae Seok's and lands on tenderloin.)
Is it tenderloin?
It's tenderloin.
- Where did it land? - It's tenderloin.
(Seok Jin wins tenderloin and becomes a hero.)
He won tenderloin.
Our team is so lucky today.
I knew it was possible.
- Is Jae Jin the last player? - Yes.
Just avoid moving the rib-eye anywhere.
It should land here.
Jae Jin won't go easy.
He'll turn the tables.
He'll make it fun.
Do your best, Jae Jin.
(Where will his unpredictable lid land?)
(He hits Jae Seok's out of garlic and seasoned spring onions.)
- My goodness. - Yes.
(He pushes out Seok Jin's and takes tenderloin.)
(Team White wins rib-eye, tenderloin, and spring onions.)
That was amazing.
- We won. - What happened?
He got lettuce and ssamjang.
He did it!
Lettuce and ssamjang.
It happened as they said.
- It happened as they said. - We still have the flap steak.
We only won beef jerky.
We won tenderloin, rib-eye, and seasoned spring onions.
Seasoned spring onions was a good choice.
It happened as they hoped.
- It's a miracle. - It is.
Team White wins garlic, seasoned spring onions,
- Gummy worms. - tenderloin, rib-eye,
- And gummy worms. - and gummy worms.
We won tenderloin too.
- Team Black wins seasoned raw beef. - Seasoned raw beef?
- We get two ramyeons. - That's right.
That's unfortunate.
- Team Grey wins beef jerky, - Beef jerky.
- Lettuce and ssamjang. - lettuce, ssamjang, and ramyeon.
Let's add lettuce, ssamjang, and beef jerky in the ramyeon.
Let's do that.
We'll bring the food accordingly.
(They move to the table.)
- The color is beautiful. - It smells amazing.
Eat it with seasoned spring onions.
Let's eat.
(A bite of Korean beef and seasoned spring onions)
The ramyeon looks delicious.
That team...
Even the ssamjang is good.
(She's imagining that it's good.)
He had some.
I'll give this to Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, here's some tendon.
(He takes care of Kwang Soo.)
(Give it to me.)
(He's upset.)
What is wrong with you?
What's this?
It's garlic.
It was for Kwang Soo. Why did you eat it?
(It was garlic for Kwang Soo.)
(A second ago, he was dipping the garlic in sauce.)
(Jae Seok took the bait instead.)
I dipped garlic in sauce for Kwang Soo.
Why did you eat it?
He took that from him.
- Goodness. - You shouldn't be so greedy.
- Was I being greedy? - It was...
just a piece of tendon.
You took it from me. It smells.
(You can't cheat in Pyeongchang.)
(The final mission will be held in a resort in Gangwon Province.)
(What is the final mission here?)
(Sixth Sense Board of Fate)
- What's this? - Is there a chance to win?
(Running Man's Loyal Pick)
- All right. The final mission... - Yes.
Is Sixth Sense Board of Fate.
Sixth Sense Board of Fate?
Sixth Sense?
- Gosh. - What's that?
"All pass", "all consistent", "all inconsistent".
Each team gets to choose one category...
from "all pass", "all consistent", or "all inconsistent".
Once you check the mission, you can bet up to 10 stickers.
If you win, you get the number of Fire Stickers you bet,
and if you lose, you get Ice Stickers.
The stickers you win go on the boxes of the Sixth Sense Board of Fate.
You can discuss amongst your team and see if you will distribute...
the stickers in one box or over multiple boxes.
The opposing team will put the stickers on the boxes randomly.
(The opposing team will put the distributed stickers as they want.)
Once that's been done, each person chooses a number...
and obtain the stickers in that box.
Why are there six boxes?
Why do we need six?
For example, if you want two stickers in each box,
- one box will be empty. - Right.
We gave you six boxes so that you can choose wisely.
For example, what happens if you put all stickers in box five?
The person who chooses five gets all the stickers.
We get to choose.
We choose a number from here.
- This game is not team-based. - I get it.
- We get a chance to win. - We should put it in one box.
This is scary.
(Anybody can win, and anybody can lose.)
(Team Gray chooses "all pass", Black chooses "all inconsistent", )
(and Team White chooses "all consistent".)
- Let's start with Team Gray. - Okay.
"All pass". Let's see.
I think this is okay.
(What is Team Gray's mission?)
(Group jump rope)
- Okay. - Yes.
- We can do this. - We've done this.
- We can do this. - How many?
- I'll hold the rope. - I'm confident.
Everybody, there are two versions...
- you can choose from. - Okay.
If our referees hold the rope, the 5 of you have to jump 30 times.
If you want to hold the rope, the 3 of you have to jump 50 times.
- 50? It's a lot. - No.
Let's have the referees hold the rope and do 30.
No, no.
Seok Jin can't jump more than 20 times.
(We can't do that.)
Is that right? Then should 2 people hold the rope and 3 jump?
You have to do five people.
30 times with 5 people is perfect.
- Let's do that. Let's go, Seok Jin. - There you go.
- Because... - Don't listen to him.
50 is too many.
- You should do 30 times. - And...
Seok Jin can't spin the rope 50 times.
(They'll bet 10 stickers and skip the rope 30 times.)
- Ready. - We are ready.
Ready.
- You all have to pass. - Can we practice?
No, you can't. It's 30 times.
- Please be good to us. - Set,
- go. - Soyou is going first?
(The counting starts once all five of them are in.)
(Soyou has a lot of pressure because she's going first.)
Good job.
(She admires Soyou.)
- We don't know yet. - She's good.
- It's fast. - It's too fast.
Go in, Jae Duck.
(Jae Duck is very agile.)
Move up. You have to move up.
It's looking good.
- They're good. - They can do 30.
(At this rate, 30 is not a problem.)
They can do 30.
- What happened? - What happened?
(Kwang Soo...)
(did it again.)
- Hold on. - No, this...
- Let's laugh. - I didn't mean to.
(Let's play some music.)
It's over.
- You're so unathletic. - I didn't mean to.
- I got the timing wrong. - I'm so tired.
- I'm serious. - 50 is hard.
- Okay, everybody. - Sir.
Please give us another chance.
- Let's give them another chance. - Thank you.
One more chance.
Go in once the rope hits the floor.
- Okay. - Go in after it hits the floor.
As long as you get in, it's fine.
He's really unathletic.
Okay, let's go.
Turn the rope. I'll try going in.
- You can't practice. - There's no practice.
- You can't practice. - You can't.
It's because he's tall. We want to see if he fits.
- We want to see if it's okay. - This is your second chance.
I can't even try?
Come closer.
If you're too tall,
you can duck down and jump.
- You don't have to jump like this. - We just wanted to check.
You can jump like this from the first place.
Ji Won has been on many variety shows.
- How humiliating. We have to win. - Yes. Let's go.
- We're going to succeed. - You can do it.
Hey.
Go in once the rope hits the floor.
- Go in once it hits the floor. - You're too tall?
This is tall enough for Seo Jang Hoon.
- When do I go in? - Once it hits the floor.
- Go. - Do I go first?
- Go in. - Go now.
(Go in now.)
Go in. Just do it.
Run to it. Go.
- Go. - It hit the floor.
(He's about to go.)
Go in once it hits the floor.
- It hit the floor. - Go.
- He's late. - Good job. You got it.
- Go in once it hits the floor. - Go.
- Good job. - Where are you going?
- Move up. - Where are you going?
(He's moving up by a tiny bit.)
Hurry up.
- Hurry up. - Go.
Good job.
(She's in right away.)
This is good.
We're not counting down yet.
Seok Jin is next.
- We can count on him. - It's Seok Jin's turn.
- Kwang Soo is tired already. - Go in.
Go.
- You have to go. - You go.
- It hit the floor. You go first. - You have to go.
(Seok Jin can't jump too many times, so he makes Elijah go.)
- Elijah. - Go.
(What? She gets caught in the rope.)
(She stumbles and falls.)
(It slaps him.)
(It's 2017's last slapstick comedy.)
- Elijah. - What now?
What now? It doesn't look pretty.
- Everybody is laughing. - None of you...
None of you are athletic.
- I'm sorry. - It didn't look pretty.
- It didn't look nice. - Excuse me.
- I... - It didn't look pretty.
I'm sorry.
- My bad. - This is too funny, Elijah.
- That was too funny. - The three of them...
- What do I do? - That was funny though.
That didn't look pretty.
You were as funny as you can be here.
He got slapped, she got caught on the rope and fell.
- She got caught on the rope. - Is that what you wanted?
You got slapped by the rope.
(That should ward off all the misfortune in 2018.)
That was so funny.
So...
- It hit me. - Team Gray fails.
They get 10 Ice Stickers.
(Team Gray gets 10 Ice Stickers.)
- Team Black is next. - Okay.
- Team Black. - They're "all inconsistent".
- "All inconsistent". - That's right.
It's the "all inconsistent" mission.
What's "inconsistent choice"?
Inconsistent Choice.
If you're inconsistent with each other, you win.
(If they're all inconsistent, they win.)
How many stickers would you like to bet?
- If we win, - 10 is good.
We should give it to one person.
- Okay. - If we lose, distribute it.
- Okay. 10 it is. - Let's do that.
- 10 stickers. - Here's the question.
(They have to listen to the question and write different answers.)
None of you should have the same answer.
Including Sechs Kies and the two female guests,
we have seven guests today. Write one of their names.
(From Sechs Kies and 2 female guests, write 1 name down.)
- 1 person? - Write 1 name down.
(This is difficult.)
They have to remember the guests' names.
There will be repeats.
- You can't talk. - Okay.
- You can't. - This is difficult.
- This is difficult. - Write one name.
- This is so hard. - It is.
There will be same answers.
- This is hard. - If you hesitate, you'll fail.
You have to write down whatever.
(It's hard not to think about it.)
(Will Team Black all write different answers?)
Let's start with So Min.
- So Min. In 1, 2, 3. - So Min first.
(They have to be inconsistent with each other.)
(She has to start it off well.)
Jang Su Won.
(She wrote Su Won's name.)
- Oh, my goodness. - Jang Su Won.
(What?)
Why did you write his name?
Why did you do that?
- Come on. - She shouldn't have done that.
Are you stupid?
Jong Kook.
- All right. - What's going on?
- I'm here. - He's in our team.
- I should write my name down. - Goodness.
(They match, so they failed.)
- Okay, they wrote the same. - Yes.
- They matched. - Yes.
- They matched. - What a fool
I knew she was going to do that.
There are other guests,
so I thought they would choose from here.
Su Won and So Min wrote the same answer, so you fail.
What a fool.
So Min is a fool.
If she wrote somebody else's name...
(They almost got it.)
- If she wrote somebody else... - Really?
I thought you would choose from here, not from the same team.
- Why did she write Su Won? - No, it was good.
I think So Min will drink tonight.
I'm sorry, but can I have some soju?
- Why did she do that? - The red one.
It's hard to believe.
(Team Black earns 10 Ice Stickers.)
We'll bet nine stickers. We might still win.
Let's keep one to be safe.
Please open it.
- It's "all consistent", right? - It's one or the other.
You can't smell it.
- This is the steamed bun mission. - This is hard.
One of the buns has red bean in it, and the other one doesn't.
(They must choose one and match in order to win.)
- This is so hard. - How do you pick?
(It's hard to match, but it's also up to luck.)
- This is hard too. - Choose...
and once I count down, break the bun in half and show it.
- This is so hard. - It's red bean or no red bean.
You can't smell it.
You won't know by looking either. You just have to choose.
We'll know if we look.
- I'm not sure. - They'll know if they look.
- They all have to choose the same. - Right. They have to match.
- You can't discuss. - It's hard to match.
They all have to choose the red bean or no red bean.
What do we do then? The red bean or no red bean?
- All right. - You can't discuss.
You can't discuss.
- Remember what I said earlier. - Just go.
One,
- two, - Hold on.
- three. - Oh, gosh.
(Team White chooses their buns.)
Choose it and break it in half.
(Did they all choose the same one?)
You can open it one by one.
- I... - I think they got it.
Hold on.
What?
- Oh, dear. - It's all red bean.
Did they match?
Did we match?
(Jae Seok got red bean as well.)
(If Jae Jin picked red bean, Team White wins.)
(Goodness)
(There is...)
(no red bean.)
What happened?
Did we get it? What?
- Did we match? - What?
Did we?
(What?)
He didn't match.
Why?
This is what I'm talking about.
He didn't match.
Jae Jin helped us.
Jae Jin, why did you choose this?
- Only one person didn't match. - That was close.
They almost won.
Did you say you'd know if you looked at it?
What do you know?
This is obviously the red bean one.
Since Jae Jin picked a different one...
We almost had it.
That was unbelievable.
I'm not even shocked. He always does something different.
(He's not shocked anymore.)
- I'm not shocked anymore. - I see.
(Team White gets 9 Ice Stickers.)
We have the results now.
- You all failed your missions, - Right.
So you'll get 10, 10, and 9 Ice Stickers.
So naturally, today's winner is...
- It's Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo with seven Fire Sticker.
This is unbelievable.
(Kwang Soo wins with 7 Fire Stickers.)
(He's a fiery man.)
Can we give it to a guest?
(They can't be happy for him, because he betrayed them.)
Again? He won again?
But he can also get a penalty.
- Right. - If he gets nine stickers.
- We have 10. - He can lose.
(Anybody can lose if they get all the Ice Stickers.)
(Even if you have many Ice Stickers, you can turn this around.)
Team Gray can decide...
how to distribute the nine stickers.
- Let's not put it in one box. - Let's not.
- Maybe... - We don't want to lose.
Split it by two.
You can have three.
It's dangerous for Jae Duck. He's still in our team.
- We should protect him. - How can we protect him?
- We have to put it in one box. - That's right.
Let's put eight in one box then.
I'm sorry, but why should I help Jae Duck?
(I have to look after myself.)
- I might get the penalty. - I'm thinking the same.
You're in first place.
Let's show our teamwork in the end.
- Okay, let's do this. - Let's just split it up.
- Su Won and Se Chan... - 2 and 8?
Have 6 too. They're only 1 less than me.
- That's true. - Yes, we can do that.
- So we... - Should we do 2 and 8?
- That sounds good. - Let's do that.
- We'll do 2 and 8. - 2 and 8?
You said 2 and 8.
- Team Black can place them. - We can?
As long as I don't pick the box with eight stickers.
That's true. Two is fine.
(Jae Duck has 7 Ice Stickers, so he has to go for no stickers.)
We're trying to be loyal to Jae Duck, so we're doing eight.
2 and 8?
What if Kwang Soo takes all of them?
It'll be great if he gets the penalty and donates too.
- All right. Shall we start? - All right.
Let's go.
Please choose a number each.
- Soyou, you're up. - Me?
- I choose number 1. - Number 1. Please put her name.
Okay, this is Soyou.
Next is Kwang Soo.
(Next up is Kwang Soo, who's the winner.)
- Number 2. - Number 2. All right.
- Okay. - Elijah.
(If you choose 8 Ice Stickers, you're likely to lose.)
- Number 4. - Number 4.
I choose three then.
I choose three.
Seok Jin is number three.
And Jae Duck?
It's 5 or 6.
- 5? - 6.
Six? Sounds good.
We'll give you a chance to switch.
(These are the current placements.)
(We'll give you a chance to switch.)
- No, I don't want to switch. - Which one's left?
- 5 is left. - 5 is left.
I want to switch.
To which one?
I'll go to five.
(Soyou switches from number 1 to 5.)
- Number 5? - Soyou moves from 1 to 5.
Can I go to number one?
- Okay. - You can if you want.
Kwang Soo goes to number one. That's good.
Number two is free.
Who wants number two?
(They hesitate.)
- Should I do number 2? - Number 2 is free.
- I'll stay in five. - All right.
(Team Gray finishes and leaves number 2 blank.)
All right. Let's go.
In 1, 2...
(If they avoid 8 stickers, everyone but Jae Duck is safe.)
Two...
Three.
(Jae Duck has to avoid the Ice Stickers.)
(Kwang Soo gets 8 stickers.)
This is unbelievable.
- 2, 3. - It doesn't matter.
(What?)
(Everybody is shocked by how unlucky Kwang Soo is.)
This is unbelievable.
See? That's what I said.
- This is unbelievable. - Kwang Soo, that's what I said.
This is fate, Kwang Soo.
The spirit of Pyeongchang.
- Kwang Soo. - This is fate.
(Their fates changed after Soyou switched.)
He did it himself.
Kwang Soo chose number five...
- He switched. - He did.
So Kwang Soo has the most Ice Stickers with eight.
I can't believe he moved to number one. It's incredible.
It's so interesting. He has a feeling.
The spirits are with you.
Next team will start betting now.
(Team Black's Ice Sticker count)
If Su Won doesn't get one, he's in last place.
Please choose your numbers.
- I choose 2. - 2.
- I choose 3. - 3.
So Min said four?
If Su Won gets more than 0 or 1, he's done.
- In 1, 2, 3. - I'll survive.
(Su Won survives with 1 Ice Sticker.)
- You survived. - This is incredible.
Kwang Soo is still in last place with eight stickers.
(Team White's Ice Sticker count)
We'll do...
1, 1, 1, 1, and 5.
- 4 1's and a single 5? - Yes.
The stickers will be placed by Team Gray.
- 4 1's and a single 5. - How many stickers do they have?
Se Chan has six,
and Jae Jin also has six.
Ji Won has four.
Sung Hoon and I have two each.
I got four against my will.
If we get more than five,
we'll have more than Kwang Soo.
For example, Se Chan, Jae Jin,
and Ji Won will have more, so Kwang Soo won't be last.
That's right. Se Chan, Ji Won, and Jae Jin.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Let's do this.
We all have the same thing in mind. Let's try our best.
We are all thinking the same, so let's try our best.
We can do this.
Let's get the energy of Pyeongchang.
Okay, let's go.
(Who will receive the final penalty of 2017?)
For your information, Kwang Soo placed them.
- We followed his opinion. - And...
you get no chance to switch.
Once you say it, it's done.
- Se Chan, - Jae Jin?
And Jae Jin should go first.
- Go, Jae Jin. - Jae Jin.
I pick one.
Number one.
I pick two.
- Sorry? - Who's two?
- We're important in this. - I pick two.
- Number two? - Yes.
- Ji Won. - He likes one.
- Go in a row. - Do that.
- 3. - 3?
They're going in a row.
I pick number four.
(Jae Seok picks number 4. He has no chance of losing.)
- Sung Hoon? - Wait.
- Wait. They're smiling. - Number five.
(His lips twitch.)
I think we dodged the worst.
I think we did. Look at his face.
We dodged it.
(I don't think we're last.)
(What is Kwang Soo going to do?)
- It looks like... - Let's open it.
- We dodged it. - We did.
Keep a straight face.
- It's okay. - Can they switch?
- They can. - Once.
- We don't want to switch. - I thought we can't.
- You said we can't switch. - We don't want to switch.
After Sung Hoon and I chose our numbers,
he said we can't switch and now...
What would you like to do?
- We won't switch. - Look at his face.
You don't want to switch? We'll give you one last chance.
I pick six.
(Punching)
(When I'm trying to do you a favor, take it.)
Kwang Soo hit him really hard.
It's serious here.
If Ji Won, Jae Jin,
or Se Chan...
gets five stickers, the results change.
We are not switching?
I'll give you three seconds.
- If you don't switch... - I think it's best...
for you not to speak.
- I choose number 6. - You have 3 seconds.
- Number 6? okay. - Jae Jin chooses 6.
(Jae Jin changes to 6 in the last second.)
(Whispering)
(Kwang Soo and Seok Jin smile.)
(Sechs Kies members start laughing as well.)
(I think somebody lost.)
- 1... - 1...
(Kwang Soo is currently in last place.)
- 2... - 2...
(Jae Jin, Se Chan, or Ji Won can be last.)
- 3. - 3.
(If one of them gets 5 Ice Stickers, Kwang Soo won't lose.)
(What is the final result?)
Gosh, you passed.
(Kwang Soo is in last place.)
- It was Sung Hoon. - Goodness.
- Sung Hoon got it. - Look at that, Se Chan.
(Kwang Soo is in last place with 8 stickers.)
Hold on.
(Turn off the camera.)
So today's...
You are not getting the penalty.
- Is this over? - You have the spotlight.
Is this over?
- Kwang Soo is the loser... - Is this over?
Kwang Soo is the loser with eight Ice Stickers.
- But who is the winner? - Kwang Soo is also the winner...
with seven Fire Stickers.
(Kwang Soo is both the loser and winner.)
I knew he would win.
Congratulations.
You are incredible.
- You are incredible, Kwang Soo. - Respect, respect.
Big respect, big respect, Superman, Superman, Superman.
- Also... - Avatar, Avatar, Avatar.
I choose him to take the penalty with me.
(I choose him to take the penalty with me.)
- What are you doing? - What?
- What are you doing? - I get to choose one person, right?
Think it over.
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, please choose a member...
who will take the penalty with you.
I can't believe it happened this way.
(Who is he planning to choose as his partner?)
Please say a few words to me.
Keep it simple.
- All of us? - Keep it simple and short.
I don't want a long speech. Ji Won, say a few words.
Congratulations on your victory.
Okay.
I have nothing to say.
You are the first one in the history...
of Running Man to win and lose at the same time.
- Respect. - This is...
Big respect.
- Okay. - He was being sarcastic.
- He was being sarcastic. - He was totally being sarcastic.
All right.
Okay.
I am sticking my tongue out.
(I am sticking my tongue out.)
What was that?
He said, "I am sticking my tongue out."
I am sticking my tongue out.
(What is his intention?)
Jae Seok, what was that?
- My goodness. - I mean...
Why did he do that?
- Why did he do that? - Jae Jin is like that.
- What? - Jae Jin is like that.
Why did he do that?
- Jae Jin is like that. - I don't understand.
Jae Jin is like that.
I am already in the worst mood.
Why did he do that?
I will choose.
- Okay. - You know,
Sechs Kies should experience it.
"I am sticking my tongue out" was too strong.
The guests get too much special treatment.
(Who is the one to stand next to Kwang Soo?)
- Let's see it. - Okay.
(It's time to check the result.)
Would you throw out those you didn't pick?
- I will go in order. - Please do that.
Leave three pieces behind.
It's Sung Hoon.
Congratulations.
- It's Jae Jin. - Jae Jin.
- You didn't pick Jae Jin. - I was very tempted.
- He stuck his tongue out. - I was very tempted.
- Unbelievable. - He stuck his tongue out.
I was very tempted,
but another member pulled at my heart.
It's incredible that you didn't pick Jae Jin.
If you didn't pick Jae Jin...
I am sure you are beginning to get nervous.
- Se Chan is out. - Okay!
This is incredible.
(Jong Kook, Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and So Min remain.)
I will be good to you.
Let's draw the curtain now.
(I am dying to know.)
- I will leave out one more person. - Please do that.
- Seok Jin is out. - Why?
(Screaming)
- Why didn't you leave me out? - Congratulations.
Why didn't you leave me out?
My goodness.
- Why? - What?
Why didn't you leave me out?
(They are the ones who pulled Kwang Soo's heart.)
Why me?
The three of you.
- Why? - I didn't do anything today.
I remained innocent.
- Why me? - Let's take a look.
Jong Kook might get chosen.
(Who gets the penalty with Kwang Soo?)
- One... - Maybe it's So Min.
- Two. - I didn't do anything today.
(It's time to reveal who is inside Kwang Soo's heart.)
(Who is the one to get hit by the water bomb?)
(Jong Kook is chosen.)
Is it Jong Kook?
(For goodness' sake.)
Really?
Bye.
This is scary.
Jong Kook said that he caught a cold.
Earlier,
he said he would prefer suffering the penalty today.
- Hold on. - Let me think.
- He said... - May I look at the cameras?
- May I look at the cameras? - Hold on.
I didn't do anything to Kwang Soo today.
He usually wants to get picked. For the first time today,
- he really didn't want to get picked. - Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on.
- Today... - He didn't want to get picked.
Today, I didn't do anything to Kwang Soo.
- What did I do? - He has always welcomed...
- the penalties. - Hold on.
However, he hated the idea today.
- Is that it? - Yes.
- You chose me for that reason. - I knew it was my chance.
A chance like this might never come again.
All right. Okay. All right.
It came back alive.
My passion for Running Man came alive.
(Thank you for awakening my passion.)
That's good.
- That's good. - Seriously.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
(Congratulations on the prize money as well as the water bomb.)
Money doesn't necessarily bring happiness.
Let's move to the location of the water bomb.
It's going to be cold.
Jong Kook.
He chose me.
- Everyone is here, right? - Yes.
It's time to get started with the penalty.
We had heated up the water.
However, as you can see,
the water is freezing right away.
(The cold weather freezes the hot water as soon as it drips.)
I want to receive the penalty today.
If you get hit with the water,
you will bleed.
He will bleed anyway.
(He will bleed anyway.)
- What are you talking about? - He will bleed anyway.
- What are you talking about? - It's nothing.
- Why would I bleed? - Please don't say that.
- What is wrong with you? - I mean...
Since he will bleed anyway,
wouldn't it be better to receive the penalty?
- Let's bleed. - All right.
(What is wrong with them?)
Anyway, Kwang Soo and Jong Kook,
you will receive the penalty the next time.
(The penalty gets pushed back.)
We should do it when the water melts.
This will weigh on my mind every day.
- "When will it happen?" - Before it ends...
For a year, the production crew and the members...
of Running Man ran hard.
The viewers told us that the show is fun...
and sent us their support.
- It gave us energy. - That's right.
Next year, we will run even harder.
- Happy New Year! - Happy New Year!
Happy New Year!
(Happy New Year!)
(It's time.)
(The year of 2018)
(Everyone, )
(do you want to know the future?)
(The best fortune comes together.)
(The worst fortune comes together.)
(The Fortune)
(Are they compatible enough...)
(to get married?)
They might live together.
While you have a handsome face,
you have a perverted disposition.
(His fortune for 2018 is terrible.)
(Who called me unlucky?)
(Look at how I have changed.)
(The former lucky ones leave...)
(and the new lucky ones emerge.)
(The New Year Fortune)