(2017 Running Man's Second Global Project)
People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent.
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(The member with 3 I Go Stickers will go to a place for 1 percent...)
(with a member they choose to go with.)
(Their fates depend on the die that the victor throws.)
(Haha and So Min received one Sticker each.)
(As a result of the second race,)
(Seok Jin received a Sticker.)
(As a result of the third race, Suspicious Partner,)
(Haha is in the lead with 2 I Go Stickers.)
(Will someone be selected for the trip today?)
- Hello. - Hi.
- What are we doing today? - Hello.
Hi.
- Hello. - Hi.
(They start with the status report on I Go Stickers today again.)
- Hello. - Haha is in trouble.
- He is. - Good grief.
Haha, if you get another Sticker, it's over.
I think Haha will go on that trip.
(If Haha gets 1 more Sticker, with 1 member, he will go on the trip.)
Congratulations.
All right. Whom shall I take?
Who's going to join me?
(Hugging)
It's Jae Seok.
(Haha, I like you a lot.)
- You know I didn't say anything. - Goodness, look at you guys.
- They clapped, - Whom shall I take?
- but I didn't say anything. - All right.
Who wants to go with me?
- Don't give up hope until the end. - Thank you!
Before we start the mission,
we will reveal a new recommendation from the viewers.
We are still getting recommendations.
We have a new travel destination.
It's the place I will have to go.
(The 4 proposed places that were revealed the last time)
(The mysterious underground ossuaries in the heart of Paris)
- Where is this place? - The ossuaries.
My goodness.
- It will be too scary. - That place has ghosts.
- They have real ghosts. - It's another scary place.
Are those bones?
- That's ridiculous. - Those are human bones.
(A shocking collaboration between a valley and a cliff.)
Where is this place?
That's a foreigner.
That's no joke.
My goodness.
I want to try it.
- Really? - What?
Do you want to try it?
It's a swing.
Look at that.
Why would anyone ride it?
It will be impossible to go on it.
(It's the legendary swing even the architect rode only once.)
(The scary flight on the cliff, Giant Canyon Swing)
(If you find a diamond, it will be yours.)
- Let's go to this place. - I wouldn't mind this place.
This place has diamonds.
It will be nice to go there.
(2 places were added)
(Who knew such a charming activity existed in Indonesia?)
(You will be surprised when you go there.)
(There are hammocks between the peaks.)
Which activity is it?
What is that?
- Are those hammocks? - Hammocks?
No way!
That's impossible.
I don't use hammocks on the ground because they are scary.
(Try flying across the ocean!)
(I want Running Man to have this thrilling experience.)
This one involves the sea. This will be nice.
- What is this? - Look at those waves.
What is this?
It's in Indonesia.
Don't people catch shrimp here?
(A cable car flies across the sea.)
- How is that possible? - I can do it.
(This small machine is the only way to brave the waves.)
It's manually run.
Who gets the I Go Sticker is very important.
From the start,
- I will bet I Go Stickers. - That's fast.
People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent,
Defend the Stickers.
(Defend the Stickers)
I will first bid two I Go Stickers...
(2 I Go Stickers)
- for the auction. - Two Stickers?
- This one will be important. - Two Stickers will end you.
Two Stickers?
(Two Stickers will be given at once.)
(Two Stickers can send Haha, Seok Jin, or So Min on a trip.)
Wait a minute.
It will be game over if So Min or I get two Stickers.
(I don't want to go on a trip.)
- Can I distribute the Stickers? - Of course.
I see.
The person who gets the Stickers...
- can distribute them. - I see.
You can give them out after you win them.
(That's a relief.)
Inside the safe on the left are two I Go Stickers.
The person who wins the bid...
can put two Stickers under anyone's name.
We will have...
a blind auction with Slap the Forehead as the bids.
(Slap the Forehead is the specialty of Running Man.)
The person with the highest number from 1 to 10 will win the bid.
That person will get his forehead slapped...
by the bidder with the second highest number,
and take the two Stickers.
Bidders with overlapping numbers...
will be dropped out.
(Bidders with overlapping numbers will be dropped out.)
- That's an important rule. - No overlapping numbers.
Moths,
you need to think carefully.
- I am warning you. - Don't be so extreme.
Our skulls might crack during the shoot.
(I don't want to get my forehead slapped by the 2nd highest bidder.)
(They begin to write down the number.)
If I win the bid, I won't have three I Go Stickers.
Are we allowed to give 2 Stickers to 1 person?
- Of course. - Oh, my goodness.
(The rookie moth, So Min, finishes writing down a number.)
Send me on a trip.
I wrote down a number.
She is a moth.
If you are done, please turn it in.
- I knew which number to write. - Really?
- Did you write a number to win? - Me?
I don't know...
- what she is thinking. - Can I give myself the Stickers?
Look at her.
(She turns in the number.)
She has ruined my plan so many times.
I am ready to have my skull cracked today.
(I am ready to have my skull cracked today.)
Why would your skull crack?
(Which number did So Min write down?)
So Min, you scare me.
I need to use my brain.
I am so confused.
What should I do?
People may not write 10 down. I will write 10 down.
- Our numbers might overlap. - I will write 10 down.
- I will write it down as well. - I will write 10 down.
(It looks like they will write 10 down.)
(In that case,)
(I will write 3 down.)
Kwang Soo, I bet you will write three down.
(I have a feeling.)
It's not that small a number.
- I bet you will write three down. - It's not that small a number.
(How did they know? I will erase it.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
You erased three, right?
(You punk.)
(No, I didn't.)
You need to think hard.
(They write down numbers in a fierce war of nerves.)
Okay.
I am done.
(Jae Seok finishes writing down a number.)
I didn't know Jae Seok would do that.
(I saw his number.)
Seriously.
(I hope my number doesn't overlap.)
The future is uncertain.
They say the scariest people have nothing to lose.
I became scary.
(They turn in the numbers for Slap the Forehead.)
I will announce the result.
Is the result interesting?
- Yes, it is. - Really?
One was written by...
- Did someone write down one? - No way.
- Did someone write down one? - Really?
- Who did that? - Who wrote down one?
That's too much.
(Did Kwang Soo write down 1 after erasing 3?)
For goodness' sake.
No one wrote it.
No one did that.
We would have slapped the person who did it.
- 3 was written by... - 3? Is it Kwang Soo?
It's not me.
(People suspected Kwang Soo to write down 3.)
(Which number did he write after erasing 3?)
Three was written by...
- Three? Is it Kwang Soo? - It's not me.
No one.
You must have erased it.
All right.
- The bid of 4 slaps... - 4 slaps.
- The bid of four slaps was made... - Someone made the bid, right?
Someone made the bid, right?
- Did someone write down four? - The bid of four slaps was made...
(Who made a bid of four slaps?)
by Haha.
(Haha wrote 4.)
Come on.
- Who said, "Come on"? - Haha.
- It was Seok Jin. - It wasn't me.
(Surprised)
(If you mess with me, I will take you on the trip.)
Five was written by...
(5 slaps)
Jae Seok and Ji Hyo.
For goodness' sake, Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo are dropped out of the auction.)
Why did you do that?
I thought six would be the highest number.
(They fell into the trap of overlapping numbers.)
- Did you write down five? - Yes, I did.
For goodness' sake.
Six was written by...
- Seok Jin. - Yes!
(My number didn't overlap.)
I might win with six.
If the higher numbers overlap, I will win.
I almost wrote six.
I am glad I didn't do that.
I didn't write six.
It's possible to win with six.
I will win if the higher numbers overlap.
Seven was written by...
(Will Seok Jin's plans come true?)
(The thing is,)
(Jong Kook wrote 7.)
(If no one else wrote 7, Jong Kook will take the 1st place.)
Seven was written by...
Jong Kook.
- What? - Am I the only one who did that?
(Jong Kook takes the 1st place.)
Am I the only one who did that?
- Wait a minute. - Seok Jin is in second.
Then I will get to slap him, right?
Me, Kwang Soo, and So Min remain.
- Jong Kook will slap hard. - That's right.
If their numbers overlap, Jong Kook will win.
Kwang Soo, did you write 10?
(There could be a winner among Kwang Soo, Se Chan, and So Min.)
Eight was written by...
Whoever gets slapped by me will die.
(Will Jong Kook win? Will there be a new winner?)
Se Chan alone.
Wait a minute.
(It's good to take the 1st place, but he will get slapped.)
- Wait a minute. - Are you the only one?
Who will slap me?
Jong Kook will.
I am going to die.
I hope the numbers overlap.
Wait a minute, that would be bad.
I hope the numbers don't overlap.
The remaining numbers are 9 and 10.
(If the numbers overlap, Jong Kook will slap Se Chan.)
I hope someone wrote nine so that I can slap them.
The remaining members are So Min and Kwang Soo.
The remaining numbers are 9 and 10.
(The remaining numbers are 9 and 10.)
Nine was written by...
Please.
Please don't let the numbers overlap.
(Let me keep my skull in one piece.)
Maybe someone else will take the 1st place.
(I want to massage Se Chan's forehead.)
Nine was written by...
(9 slaps)
Kwang Soo and So Min.
(Kwang Soo and So Min)
(Kwang Soo and So Min are dropped out of the auction.)
You are the winner.
(Congratulations on winning the bid of death.)
The first place is Se Chan,
and the second place is Jong Kook. Congratulations.
My goodness, Se Chan.
Congratulations.
I am so excited.
My goodness.
- I am so excited. - I should have written eight.
Se Chan, congratulations on winning the bid with eight slaps.
Please take your eight slaps.
(Se Chan exchanged his life for 2 I Go Stickers.)
Se Chan, you will get the Stickers.
That's true.
I don't mind going on a trip.
I like traveling abroad.
We can take the easy way.
I like traveling abroad. Give me the Stickers.
You can't negotiate with him.
You are so stubborn. Indeed.
- In every way, he's inflexible. - All right.
- He drives me crazy. - Sit down.
For your information, Jong Kook is the type...
to hit hard without making it funny.
(They were surprised by his powerful slap that was not funny at all.)
It's going to hurt a lot.
(Jong Kook tends to hit them in their eyes.)
(The game is about slapping one's forehead,)
(but he likes to slap them in their eyes.)
I'm the type that makes oneself in trouble.
(You understand me, right?)
He's the most annoying type.
- All right. - Don't do that.
Slap me lightly first so that I can grasp how it'll be.
- Okay. - Lightly.
I'll slap harder little by little.
(Slap)
(It's like there's an earthquake in his brain.)
(It's just as I heard.)
No, I didn't put much strength into it.
He's in pain, but it's not funny at all.
What's going on? It's not funny at all.
- All of a sudden, - It's even boring.
I couldn't control my temper.
- Sit down already. - Goodness.
You got slapped only once.
You won first place though.
(Se Chan has 7 times more to be slapped left.)
(Slap)
Jong Kook, hold on.
(Merciless)
- It's just beating him up. - Hold on.
Make it interesting, will you?
- What is going on? - He's really beating him up.
This is too much.
- Remember it'll be aired. - My goodness.
- He's committing violence. - This isn't right.
- It's no joke. - He clenched his teeth.
(He's tearing up.)
- Come here. - He's crying.
Hold on.
Wait.
- Se Chan. - I just got slapped twice, right?
(I'm not this kind of person, but I can't stop crying.)
I'm telling you the truth that I didn't put my strength at all.
If you're on Se Chan's side, you should take one slap for him.
- Right. - Right.
If anyone gets slapped on behalf of me, I'll repay for their kindness.
- Sure. - I'll take one.
- I'll take one too. - I think I'm sick.
- I'm dizzy now. - Guys, I'm the first in line.
Give me one slap.
Tell me who'll go first so I can remember.
- Me! - I'll go first.
- I'm the first in line. - So Min, you too?
- Yes. - So Min too?
I can't slap a girl.
Please slap me.
Okay, that's the spirit, So Min.
(Please don't mind me and just slap.)
Take one slap.
Still, you're a girl. It's not right.
Then I'll slap her on behalf of you.
(If you think it's not right, let me slap her.)
(What is he saying?)
I know you can't hit girls.
I'll slap her with my dirty hand.
- Let me slap her. - My hands are tainted already.
- Yes. - Really?
- You have to think carefully. - Ji Hyo.
It'll hurt more than you think.
(How do I know? Because I took a slap like you,)
(and faced incredible pain before.)
I'll slap her.
So Min, you have to stay still.
- I won't slap hard. - She must not have seen...
Ji Hyo get slapped then.
(Since you're my friend, I won't slap hard.)
(You mean it, right? I'll trust you.)
(Of course, So Min. Trust me.)
(Slap)
Gosh, hey.
(High five)
(She's a fool to be deceived again.)
- Goodness. - That was too hard.
You slapped too hard.
- Goodness. - This isn't right.
This shouldn't be aired.
- Kwang Soo, how could you... - Look at her forehead.
- Are you okay? - Are you okay?
- Magnet Lady, are you okay? - Are you okay?
I'm sorry, So Min.
(He didn't know it'd be this hard.)
That's not it.
- Hey, you. - Next, please come forward.
- So Min. - Don't forget about me.
- I won't. - Remember me.
It's the fourth slap now.
- So Min. - Let me slap him.
Sure, do that.
(She's been waiting for his turn to come.)
You have to slap him hard though.
- You can't make her do that. - Slap him hard.
- This isn't right. - With my palm, right?
(That's my girl, So Min.)
- Close your eyes. - It doesn't matter where she slaps.
(Slap)
Nice.
(Today's lesson: Nice slaps for nice slaps)
That wasn't too hard.
That was the fourth slap.
Se Chan acquired the right to give out...
two I Go Stickers.
Please open the strongbox and take the Stickers.
All right.
It doesn't matter even if you give one to me.
Okay.
In the strongbox on your left,
there are two I Go Stickers.
(Se Chan gets to give one to whomever he wants.)
Who didn't volunteer to help me out just before?
Was it Seok Jin and Jae Seok?
What?
The member with three I Go Stickers will...
choose one member to go on the trip with.
- It's done for Haha if he gets one. - It's for certain he'll go.
(Will he give all 2 Stickers to Seok Jin or So Min?)
Can he give all 2 Stickers to 1 person?
- Sure. - My goodness.
(Any 1 of the 3 will have to go if they get 2 Stickers.)
I'm nervous.
It's making me nervous to press the buttons.
(Everything is up to Se Chan now.)
(What will his choice be?)
It's not there?
(But)
- It's not there. - Was it a lie?
- What's this? - It's a prank?
(The Stickers...)
(aren't there.)
It must be hilarious if it was a lie.
- They're not there? - What's going on?
(The Stickers aren't there?)
- They must have lied to us. - It was a lie.
- They're not there? - They're not in here.
- What? - Really?
The real race for today is...
- What? - What's going on?
(Was there a hidden race behind today's mission?)
- The real race for today is... - What?
Defend the Stickers, Thieves Among Us.
(Today's real race is Thieves Among Us.)
(What did he just say?)
My goodness.
Let me slap him just once.
(Is this really happening?)
You went too far.
(Don't you see my red forehead?)
- What are you trying to pull? - This is ridiculous.
- Excuse me. - What's going on?
You're not the one to be worked up.
- What was all that we did today? - Se Chan...
- My goodness. - You shouldn't be the one.
- Se Chan... - So this is how you do it.
- Se Chan... - What are you doing?
You made me get slapped from the start.
What does it make Se Chan?
(He's still in pain.)
Se Chan's two I Go Stickers...
have been stolen by someone among the Running Man members.
- Among us? - Who is it?
Among you, there are two thieves...
who stole the Stickers, five civilians,
and one sheriff who is on the civilians' side.
The civilians will win the race if all two thieves are caught...
before the race ends.
The stolen Stickers will be given to the two thieves.
However, if the sheriff on the civilians' side is taken out,
the thieves will win today's race,
and the Stickers will be given to whomever they want.
I'll provide the first hint for catching the thieves...
to Se Chan who was supposed to have the right to give out the Stickers.
(Se Chan's provided a hint.)
- That's worth being slapped. - Yes, after all.
Se Chan could be the thief.
- I got slapped for something. - It could be him.
- You did. - It's not me.
I wouldn't tell you even if I was the thief.
It's really not me.
You can either share the hint with the others or not.
But you should be careful since you don't know who the thieves are.
All right. 30 seconds have passed. Please destroy the hint.
- Goodness. - Let's share it.
I read the first hint,
and I think I can share this with you because it's too broad.
We need to guess by looking at each hint 1 by 1.
Why are you sweating so much?
There are two thieves.
- One is... - It's a woman, right?
- No. - Then?
One is married.
- I'm married. - That's a big hint.
- It can't be me. - All right.
- Listen to me. - It's them two.
Have you seen me this calm before?
(The married members deny first.)
- Look. - 1 among those 3 is the thief.
Let me clear things out.
So Min and Jae Seok.
- They're likely to be the thieves. - It's not me.
- Think about it. - I...
Se Chan may be lying.
- All right. - For today's mission,
you'll change into uniforms and move to another place.
Let's go.
(1 of the 2 thieves is married.)
(They move to another location.)
So far, I have...
Jae Seok and So Min as the thieves in mind.
It's similar to my guess.
Shut it, you punk.
- What did you say? - You punk.
You know nothing, so don't be cheeky.
(They act up drastically.)
- My goodness. - You punk.
But So Min is unusually quiet today.
Trust me. It's really not me.
- She's not talkative today. - I promise.
(Ji Hyo is quiet too.)
All right, everyone.
You'll start your mission to acquire...
the second hint.
My goodness.
(They go onto their mission with suspicions.)
This mission is called...
Song Relay.
(The mission is called Song Relay.)
- Oh, this. - It's difficult.
I'll sing a song first.
The next person will sing another song...
that starts with the last word of my lyrics.
(They'll acquire a hint if they succeed.)
All right, we'll now start...
- Song Relay. - The last word.
- Let's do this. - Watch each other closely.
I'll go first.
("I'm Sorry" by Kim Gun Mo)
- That's the last word. - A song that starts with it.
Excuse me, is someone out there?
- Is someone out there? - There.
(He's flustered.)
There...
(Jong Kook fails.)
- You're suspicious. - Hey.
I swear.
- Hold on. - Think of one.
- There, there - You just heard him say it.
Try it.
- I love you - See? You can't think of one.
- Jong Kook, don't be so worked up. - Try it!
I mean, it doesn't make sense. I can't think of anything.
I swear.
- Hold on. - I swear.
Why is he so worked up when he got it wrong?
What's wrong with you?
- It's not that we made a mistake. - Why are you so mad at us?
But it's so difficult.
I'm not sure what his identity is, but he's so mad at us.
- Think about it. - We can't say anything to you.
You're...
You're either a thief, the sheriff, or a psychopath.
Hey.
If you can't control your temper like this...
He isn't just a civilian.
You'll cause a big mess at this rate.
(He may be a psychopathic civilian.)
- He's strange. - Just suspect me. I don't care.
- He's suspicious. - But I really can't do this.
I really can't do this. Seriously.
Gosh.
(We've done nothing so far.)
- What are you doing? - If you can't do it,
get off this bus.
(They're now criticizing him instead of suspecting him.)
Leave.
I can't play Name Tag Elimination either.
I've never seen a member like him before.
By the way,
can we play a different game?
How about you recite...
the time tables?
Okay, that sounds good.
Let's start with Jong Kook.
- Give us something easy. - Our pride is on the line.
(They succeed if all members answer correctly.)
- 5 times 3? - 15.
- 6 times 3? - 18.
7 times 3?
21.
- 2 times 5? - 10.
- 6 times 4? - 24.
- 6 times 5? - 15.
(Her answer to 6 times 5 is 15.)
That's wrong, Ji Hyo.
Come on. Let's do it again.
- What did you say? - Ji Hyo.
(How can she answer incorrectly so naturally?)
I'm suspicious of you.
- Why did you do that? - She's strange.
Are you a thief?
(They get no hints due to Ji Hyo and Jong Kook's mistakes.)
- I'm sorry. - Are you a thief?
- No, I'm not. - I think she is.
- No. - Aren't you a thief?
You will not be given the hint related to the thief.
I wish I had memorized the multiplication tables.
I know that 6 times 5 is 30.
Of course you do.
(A gymnasium at D University)
What's going on?
(They must identify the thieves.)
(Is this where the missions are?)
One-person Mission.
(What are these missions?)
I know what it is.
(He recalls the missions.)
- What is it? - It's my favorite.
- I remember this game. - I used to play it a lot.
Rock-paper-scissors. I lost.
That's right, Kwang Soo.
All right. For this mission,
you'll play as a team.
It's called Relaying with the Thieves.
(Relaying with the Thieves)
(Relaying with the Thieves?)
You succeed if you finish the five courses...
in relay within the time limit.
Randomly pick a member's name from the box.
That person is the player.
It's not about your skills.
- This is difficult. - Ji Hyo...
must pick the name since she's lucky.
You don't know what will happen.
Do you see the tank filled with ink?
- Yes. - Come on.
There are three hints related to the thieves inside the tank.
The ink fills up as time passes.
All hints are gone after 10 minutes.
Okay.
The thieves will try to stop us.
It will become more obvious.
It definitely will be obvious.
(While members try to clear the missions to obtain hints,)
(the thieves will try to stop them from clearing the mission.)
It'll be very obvious.
Here's a short explanation. The first course is...
kicking a jegi 5 times after 5 elephant nose turns.
- Kicking a jegi is hard. - I can't kick a jegi...
- even without turning. - The second course...
- involves two people. They must... - Don't try so hard.
touch their index fingers after 5 elephant turns.
It's more difficult than you think.
- It's hard. - You're right.
(It's rather difficult.)
The third course is a game from the past.
Rock-paper-scissors.
The game is based on luck.
I'm confident about playing rock-paper-scissors.
For the 4th course, 3 people must say words that start...
- with the given consonant. - The first consonant?
It involves thinking.
Here's the last course.
It's shooting the basketball into the hoop.
Haha should play basketball.
- Haha? - I'm good at it.
If Haha gets picked...
He's good at basketball.
Don't the thieves have too much of a disadvantage?
Why do you say that?
Are you at a disadvantage?
(Flustered)
- Yes. - Why do you say that?
I saw you swallow.
(His throat trembles.)
Why do you say that?
The thieves are at a disadvantage.
- Are you... - It will be difficult.
Are you thinking from the thieves' perspective?
- That's right. - Right?
We didn't think that way.
- Let's find out if it is. - It's disadvantageous.
It's easy to clear the mission.
Let's do it.
(Will the thieves succeed?)
- Right? - I can't do it.
- You have to kick harder. - Jae Seok is good at it.
The jegi seems strange.
It's a good jegi.
Jae Seok is good.
- It's difficult. - Try it, Seok Jin.
It's difficult.
It's hard to kick it without turning.
- Okay. - Hey.
We must suspect those who say that they can't do it.
(Haha starts playing detective.)
(Thieves will pretend that they can't kick the jegi.)
I've never been good at it.
Give it to me.
Wait in line.
It's loose.
Look, this is how to do it.
- It's loose. - Look.
(Goodness)
Seok Jin is really annoyed.
It's better to do it loose.
(Jae Seok takes it away.)
(How dare you?)
He took it away.
It might be better to play it loose.
(Did you trust me?)
It may be better to play it loose.
It's frustrating.
Let me try it.
Let's do a cheer.
Come together.
- In 3, 2, 1. Let's go. - Let's go.
- We're good at playing as a team. - Right.
Get ready.
(The time limit is 10 minutes. The countdown starts.)
Haha.
(The first player is Haha.)
- Do it now. - Start turning.
- Hurry. - Turn now.
- Start. - You should turn first.
- 2, 3, 4, 5. - That's good.
Kick it five times. Start.
- 1, 2. - That's good.
- 3, 4. - Come on.
(Haha only kicks it 3 times.)
- What happened? - That's not right.
- I was so close. - So Min.
- It's So Min. - Hurry up.
The next player is up.
- 1, 2. - 1, 2.
(She can't even hold her nose.)
- 3, 4. - We don't have time.
Turn quickly. Here you go.
Don't try so hard.
She seems suspicious.
- Get out. - She seems suspicious.
(Get out.)
Hurry, we don't have time.
Next is Se Chan.
(Se Chan is up next.)
He'll definitely succeed.
It's strange if he fails.
- 3, 4. - It's 4.
- Five. - Go ahead.
- 1, 2. - He'll make it.
- He got it. - Five.
Let's go.
(He somehow completes the first course.)
- Let's go. - Great.
I'll pick the names.
- Okay. - Let's see.
- Jae Seok. - Pick another one.
Pick another one.
Pick one more name.
- Gosh, it's me. - Turn.
- Get ready, set, go. - Go.
- 1, 2. - 1, 2.
- 3, 4. - 3, 4.
- Will they succeed? - Touch the finger.
Do it in one go.
They're dizzy.
Try it again.
(They fail to touch.)
(They're pathetic.)
(If they fail, they must start again from the beginning.)
We have to start again.
(They're at the risk of losing one hint.)
- Jong Kook. - He'll make it.
We'll succeed.
1, 2... 5.
- He got it. - Hurry.
- Concentrate. - You must concentrate.
- 1, 2. - He got it.
- 3, 4. - Let's go.
- He made it. - Let's go.
(He's proud of himself.)
- Pick two names. - Ji Hyo and Jae Seok.
- Hurry up. - Jae Seok.
- Turn. - One.
Jae Seok is bad at turning.
You're doing well.
Come on.
- Hurry up. - Start.
(They successfully come in contact.)
- We did it. - They made it.
Move to the next one.
- Hurry up. - It's rock-paper-scissors.
Who is it?
- Se Chan. - I'm good at it.
(He's confident.)
(From the start,)
(he expressed his confidence about the game.)
Se Chan is good.
(Will he defeat the machine?)
(He loses in 1 second.)
I lost.
(Flustered)
Come on.
(Everyone is annoyed.)
You said you were confident.
- Did he lose? - Is that all?
- Wait. - You said you're good.
You said you're good at it.
Do we go back?
- Let's start again. - Pick a name.
- Pick a name now. - I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Pick a name.
The hints are getting erased.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
Seok Jin is up.
- It's Seok Jin. - I don't think...
- he'll make it. - One.
2, 3.
- Four. - You must succeed.
(He turns one more time.)
He turned six times.
(We don't have time to waste.)
- What is he doing? - 1, 2.
Did he get it?
He seems suspicious.
(Seok Jin is suspicious.)
He's also strange.
- Wasn't Seok Jin good at it? - No.
- It's strange. - It's Seok Jin.
1, 2.
- 3, 4. - This is too difficult.
- Okay. - Turn one more time.
- Give me the jegi. - Turn one more time.
(He doesn't know what he's doing.)
Here you go, Seok Jin.
One.
(He falls already.)
(Unnatural behavior and strange reaction)
Wasn't Seok Jin good at kicking jegis?
(Wasn't he good at it before?)
(He moved smoothly during practice.)
(However, he suddenly loses balance.)
It'll be strange if he's a thief.
I can't turn anymore.
I'm not.
- It makes you dizzy. - You can't fail now.
Gosh, I'm dizzy.
- Darn it. - Kwang Soo.
I can't kick a jegi.
That's good.
- We don't have time. - He's ready.
- Good luck. - Concentrate.
It's okay. Just concentrate.
(He misses it.)
- Goodness. - I can't kick a jegi.
- I feel dizzy. - I feel too dizzy to do it.
Keep turning. Turn more quickly.
You're too slow.
So Min, you turned more than five times.
Turn one more time.
- Go and touch his finger. - Come here.
- Wait, come here. - I'm too dizzy.
Come on, Jae Seok.
(He's very suspicious.)
- Wait. - Come on.
- Jae Seok is suspicious. - Pick a name now.
Isn't Jae Seok suspicious?
I'm suspicious of him.
(A thief could be Jae Seok.)
Next is rock-paper-scissors.
Kwang Soo is doing well.
- Slow down. - Don't turn too many times.
Why did you turn so quickly?
- It makes you dizzy. - Go, Jong Kook.
(They trusted Jong Kook.)
Go.
- Get closer. - They made it.
We made it.
- What's next? - Next is rock-paper-scissors.
- Se Chan. - I'm sorry.
(He's the best at this game.)
There he is.
(He lost the game which was humiliating for him.)
I have a good feeling about it.
(I'm going to earn my respect as the representative of the humankind.)
- I won! - He won!
(I'm the king of games in Dongducheon.)
- I won. - He won.
Hurry and draw the names.
(3 members must present a word that has given syllables.)
They are Se Chan, Jong Kook,
- and Seok Jin. - It's me?
- They are our key players. - I'm about to throw up.
- I'm a key player? - Who is up first?
It's "E" and "N".
- Wife. - Today.
Today.
Hi. Day.
(He gives an absurd answer.)
- Start from the beginning. - What was that?
What kind of a word is that?
Hey, let's take a breath.
Let us take a moment.
You could've said, "Hello."
- Jong Kook, Jae Seok, - Jae Seok.
- What is it? - and So Min.
Get ready. Start.
"P" and "P".
Waterfall.
(She fails.)
Do it again from the top.
- We have to do it again? - It was hard getting this far.
- Let's go. - What's wrong with you?
(They only have less than 2 minutes.)
- We are in trouble. - What is it?
I bet the thieves are happy now.
We lost two hints.
- We did it. - It's here.
This game is holding us back.
- Let's succeed for once. - This is the problem.
- So Min. - It's So Min.
(The first match of the artificial intelligence and the magnetic human)
- You won. - We won.
(So Min wins.)
Everyone, come.
(This is So Min's first assist in the win.)
- Kwang Soo, - Kwang Soo.
- Se Chan, - This is the hard one.
- and Ji Hyo. - I'll be the last.
- Hold on. - "K" and "S".
- Hardship. - Gratitude.
- Kwang Soo. - Great.
(They pass the problematic 4th course at last.)
- That works. - It's the free throw.
- It's my turn. - Do it at once.
- Please pick me. - Pick Haha.
- Ji Hyo, pick my name. - Just pick anyone.
- Please pick me. - Let it be Haha.
- Please. - Please.
Pick me.
(I'm the king of basketball.)
(My left hand merely helps.)
(To get the last hint, they are desperate for a basketball hero.)
- Don't do that. - Just pick one.
- It's Kwang Soo. - He's good.
(Kwang Soo steps up to the line.)
Kwang Soo, take a breath.
You have to make a big parabola.
- I'll see if you're a thief or not. - Go back to your spot.
- We don't know what will happen. - I'll keep an eye on you.
(The fates of the citizens depend on Kwang Soo's free throw.)
(Will Kwang Soo be able to make the free throw?)
He did it.
Nice!
(The ball goes in!)
He did it.
(Of course I did it! I am a genius.)
He did that on his first try.
That was great.
- It was amazing. - You did it.
(With 50 seconds left, they accomplished their mission.)
He's not the thief.
Everyone,
- you may take the last hint. - What is it?
- Let's read it together. - Let's do that.
- Let's see. - The thieves...
(It's a happy moment for everyone except for the thieves.)
- Here it is. - What is it?
- What is it? - It's long.
"One of the thieves is unlucky."
"I'm not sure about the other one."
(One of the thieves is unlucky. I'm not sure about the other one.)
- It's Kwang Soo. - Unlucky ones, please gather.
- It's Kwang Soo. - There are four.
- You should stay. - Wait, I am...
- I am not unlucky. - You are unlucky too.
- Hey. - Kwang Soo must be the thief.
- He's single too. - I am luckier than you guys.
Everyone, the thief is out.
- So Min, you need to join us. - The hints tell us it's Jae Seok.
- That's right. - It must be him.
- It's Jae Seok. - He's married and unlucky.
The other one isn't married and unlucky. It must be one of the rest.
We can speculate that the thieves are So Min and Jae Seok.
(So Min and Jae Seok become the leading candidates.)
Who is someone that is married and unlucky?
- It's Jae Seok. - It must be Jae Seok.
- You are married and unlucky too. - The description fits you too.
(Are you introducing yourself?)
- When I was kicking the jegi... - You all know me.
- I don't look suspicious today. - Actually, Seok Jin...
- failed a lot of missions. - I'm myself today.
- I suspected him a few times. - No, you don't.
(At this moment, So Min takes a step back and observes.)
(Se Chan clearly said one of the thieves was married.)
- I think it's Jong Kook. - That was out of nowhere.
Really?
Unlucky member who is single is Kwang Soo. They're the thieves.
I am not married.
(I am not married.)
- Hey. - Oh, right.
(She suspects a bachelor as a married thief.)
- Oh, right. - I'm single.
- What's up with her? - I'm about to lose it.
Shouldn't you feel disappointed?
Hey, let's know the facts before we pick a thief.
- You should know he's single. - Hey, I am...
Who is my wife?
- Look him up online. - I got mixed up.
- Why do you say I'm married? - I made a mistake.
Is it so wrong that he is still single?
You think he got married when he filmed "X-Man".
- "X-Man"? - I'm telling her that you didn't.
He didn't get married then.
- I'm sorry. - Poor Jong Kook.
- We'll solve it with one more hint. - We can solve it then.
Is there another one in it?
We can't read anyway because of the ink.
There might be people who aren't sad about losing the hints.
- Check their reactions. - I was very sad.
He didn't look sad.
- Haha. - You looked relieved.
Haha, think about what I did in the beginning.
If you think I'm one of the thieves...
- Se Chan did well kicking the jegi. - Isn't Haha weird?
- You say others are the thieves. - He's acting strangely.
- You are... - He does that because it's him.
You are leading the investigation today.
- I am? - Yes.
All right, everyone. You will move to the next place.
When you are moving to the next place, you won't go all together.
You will split into 2 groups of 4 and go.
We are isolating the thieves?
Everyone, let us get going.
- Thieves will try to ride together. - Let's go.
They know each other. So they will try to ride together.
You think you are certain that I am the thief.
Yes, I just wanted to ride with a thief.
I wonder what you will do.
- I think two thieves are in here. - Goodness.
What I'm certain about is that...
The one thing we learned from the game we just played...
- What is it? - The truth is...
(Sneezing)
I was talking about something important.
(I felt nervous about hearing this important clue.)
What is it?
I don't think Se Chan is the thief.
- He's not it. - Hey, I am...
- You can see I'm not one either. - But...
- before... - I am not certain about that.
What I'm suspicious about is...
when you played the second course, you were a bit weird.
You don't know how dizzy I was.
- Isn't Jae Seok the sheriff? - Really?
- No, he is the thief. - I think he's the sheriff.
(I bet he is a thief.)
- We all agree he is a thief. - He has to be the thief.
- I think he is the thief. - Is the other one So Min?
I do believe it's Jae Seok.
Look at this. So Min is talkative.
- She talks a lot before the shoot. - That's right.
- She didn't talk during the shoot. - That's true.
- What's up with that? - That's a bit odd.
How do you feel being pegged as the thief?
Jae Seok, who do you think is the thief?
- What do you think? - What's your opinion?
I get the feeling...
that it could be Haha.
- Haha? - Yes.
It's because...
(Guys, listen up.)
They should have a reason to steal the Stickers.
- Then he has the perfect motive. - That's a valid point.
Why does he have to steal them?
- He has two Stickers already. - That's right.
(Is it because he felt he would go on the trip?)
He is going to catch the sheriff.
- That's right. Exactly. - He can give out the Stickers?
That's true.
- Now that I heard that... - Think rationally.
(Can Haha be one of the thieves since he has the motive?)
Anyway, I am not completely certain.
That's my opinion.
Then who is the sheriff?
Actually...
I can't figure this out.
Se Chan, I'm actually the sheriff.
(Se Chan, I'm actually the sheriff.)
You are?
(So Min is the sheriff?)
(30 minutes before the opening segment)
(A mysterious figure came to the crew's office before the shoot.)
Hello.
(Someone visited the crew?)
(Why is Se Chan here?)
What is it?
(What is the identity of Se Chan?)
Please sit down.
Why did you call me here alone in secret?
Se Chan,
you are the sheriff who is on the civilians' side.
I'm the sheriff and on the civilians' side?
The sheriff and the civilians must find the thieves.
When you eliminate the thieves at the last race, you will win.
(He feels a lot of pressure.)
Really?
If the sheriff is eliminated,
the victory will go to the thieves right away,
and the race will end.
As a sheriff, do everything in your power to conceal your identity.
Catching the thieves without exposing yourself is the key.
Soon, there will be an auction, and you will bid for I Go Stickers.
Two I Go Stickers have already been stolen by the thieves.
The one with the winning bid of this auction...
will receive a hint about the thieves instead of the Stickers.
In order to uncover the identities of the thieves,
it's in your best interest to get the hint since you are the sheriff.
I will look forward to your performance today.
(Numerous fates of the civilians are on his shoulders.)
If Jae Seok is the thief...
- and choose you, it's over. - That's right.
I think everyone here isn't the thief.
- The three civilians... - I am the sheriff.
I don't believe you.
Look! I think Kwang Soo is the sheriff.
- He must be the sheriff. - You're the sheriff, Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo, are you the sheriff? - No, I am not.
(What is So Min's identity who is sounding him out?)
Gosh, a delicious meal is prepared for us.
(At a wrap restaurant in Seoul,)
(there's an abundance of delicious meat and fresh vegetables.)
There's meat. Meat!
(Why are they here?)
- This is nice. - There's pork belly meat.
This is one healthy meal.
(Who is the thief?)
You all chose your own seats.
This mission is Ssam My Way.
(This mission is Ssam My Way.)
(Ssam My Way?)
- Ssam My Way? - Ssam My Way?
This is an individual match.
A member who fails the mission is eliminated right away.
Only the final victor of the mission will receive the hint.
If a civilian wins, the hint will be about the thieves.
If a thief wins, the hint will be about the sheriff.
(If a thief wins, the hint will be about the sheriff and vice versa.)
(I have to win this game by all means.)
This is an important mission.
The first round of Ssam My Way is...
Ssam Relay.
It's similar to when you play When I Go To a Market.
An ingredient will be added as you take turns...
in making a ssam in the same order. If you get the order wrong...
or put in a different ingredient, you'll be out.
You'll also have to eat all the ssam you've made until then.
- All of them? - Okay.
(If you fail the mission, you have to eat all the ssam.)
We'll start from So Min then.
Take lettuce or sesame leaf.
Should it be lettuce or sesame leaf?
- It must be lettuce. - Lettuce.
Let's take one of each.
- Okay. - I'll just take lettuce.
- Let's take both. - I don't like having them together.
Seriously.
- Okay? - Add it as an ingredient.
- I'll do that. - Okay.
- Okay. - It'll be my first ingredient.
Whatever the role may be, I don't want to do it with you.
(Speechless)
All right. Let's get it started. So Min is the first to go.
- Okay. - Ready,
set, go.
- When I make a ssam - All right.
I put a pickled radish on top
(What's next?)
I put a grilled onion on top
A pickled radish, grilled onion
And a piece of pork belly on top
When I make a ssam, I put a pickled radish on top
(What was next?)
- You can't remember? - I do.
- Already? - You can't go on like this.
- Grilled... - She's suspicious.
- A grilled onion - She's really suspicious.
- Already? - A piece of pork belly
Already?
- It's actually... - Did you understand the rule?
We can't actually say she's the thief or not...
- by this game. - I'm thinking what to put next.
- She's just not good at memorizing. - I'm thinking about...
- what to put on top next. - It's strange not to suspect her.
A grilled clove of garlic will do.
- A grilled clove of garlic on top - There you go.
- Okay, when I make a ssam... - Gosh, it's scary.
(Confident)
- A radish... Grilled onions. - Okay.
A piece of pork belly.
- Next is grilled garlic. - Okay.
- And I'll put a sesame leaf on top. - My goodness.
(He can't believe Jong Kook put a sesame leaf on top.)
Why would you...
When I make a ssam
I put a pickled radish
A grilled onion
I'll put a piece of pork belly on top
Next is grilled garlic
- I don't want to put a sesame leaf - My favorite sesame leaf
- But I have to - It's my favorite
Jae Seok hates it, but he has to put it on top
(Shall I make a wrap with him?)
- A sesame leaf on top - He has to put it on top
- And... - It's great
- I'll put gochujang on top - Gochujang!
(He adds gochujang to it.)
I'll make a ssam
I'll put a pickled radish
Grilled onions
He sounds like those typical, old men.
"Let me see"
- A piece of pork belly - All right
- Like grannies. - Shall I put grilled garlic on top?
And...
Gochujang sounds delicious.
I can't put them on my ssam yet?
No, you can't.
(Putting them back)
(You have to do it when your turn comes back.)
(So Min, please understand the rules clearly.)
(Smiling brightly)
- A sesame leaf. - Don't let them know from now on.
After putting a sesame leaf on top
Ssamjang
(He's so sure.)
(Not gochujang?)
- You haven't put mine yet. - Okay!
(He fails the mission.)
It's not ssamjang?
- It's not ssamjang? - Yes!
It's gochujang
Seok Jin is out.
- You can have your ssam now. - It's gochujang
Why don't you play cards more often?
You should use your brain more.
- Do I just eat it? - Yes.
It looks delicious.
- You'll go from the start. - Right.
- Please have... - Do I get to eat it too?
- You can. - Do we have it too?
- Sure, you can. - Okay.
- Can I add other ingredients? - Can we?
- Can we add others on top? - Can we add other ingredients?
No, just have what you've made.
Are you telling me to eat only the radish and onion?
(There's nothing much inside.)
- She gets to have only the radish. - Yes, have it.
- I have meat inside. - And you're enjoying it.
You can't put anything else.
(They're forced to practice non-possession.)
Let me put at least a piece of meat.
Seok Jin is out, and let's move onto another round.
- Let's start. - Why did I get it wrong?
Let's start from Haha.
So Min will be next after Haha.
(2nd round of Ssam Relay)
When I make a ssam
I put three pieces of jeyuk bokkeum
Three pieces of jeyuk bokkeum.
(After jeyuk bokkeum)
I'll put a whole pepper.
(A whole pepper on top)
- What did you say? - What?
- What's wrong with you? - What are you doing?
(I like it spicy.)
Are you saying this whole pepper?
(Of course.)
Why would she put this in her ssam?
Can't we make it delicious?
When I make a ssam
I put three pieces of jeyuk bokkeum
A whole pepper
Are you sure about this?
I'll put another lettuce on top
(He adds another lettuce on top.)
This is crazy. I think I'll get it wrong again.
(What?)
When I make a ssam
(I'm sorry, but you're out.)
I put three pieces of jeyuk bokkeum
- And - Three pieces of this...
(He doesn't understand the rule and memorizes hard.)
A whole pepper on top
A whole pepper...
And
- Lettuce on top - Lettuce on top
- What will go on top? - And...
You should add grilled garlic
No, I'll put another whole chili pepper on top
(A whole chili pepper is a must for ssam.)
I'm not going to eat this.
It's fine as long as I don't get it wrong.
(What should I do if I get it wrong?)
They're two whole chili peppers, right? After lettuce...
- Three pieces of jeyuk bokkeum. - I think you're out.
- What? - You're out.
- I'm out? - You're out.
I'm out?
Oh, I see.
(Please use your brain.)
Why are you making a ssam?
It's better to be the first to be out.
When I make a ssam
Another lettuce on top
- It goes on top - Goes on top
Another whole chili pepper
It goes on top
And I'll place one more chili on top
What's this?
(This ssam is all about chili peppers.)
Could you give us about eight more peppers, please?
Let's see how it goes.
When I make a ssam, I'll put three pieces of jeyuk bokkeum
And!
I'll put a sesame leaf on top
Stop with that sesame leaf already!
(They're sick of it now.)
You really like sesame leaves, don't you?
I love the smell of perilla leaves
Some strange punk puts a sesame leaf on top
- It's my favorite - And
It's my turn now
I'm not going to have this anyway
So I'll put three slices of raw onions
Are you kidding me?
(Jae Seok adds 3 slices of raw onions.)
Should I put a bowl of rice on top?
(The race is going fierce.)
Calm down. We have to make it edible at least.
We can't miss out garlic
One clove of raw garlic
(He adds a clove of raw garlic to it.)
I'll put a clove of raw garlic
On top
I'll put
1, 2, 3 napa cabbage leaves
- Are you serious? - On top
That's definitely for cows.
That's not for humans.
I'll put ssamjang on top
I'll put six pieces of jeyuk bokkeum
I'll take six pieces of jeyuk bokkeum.
Lettuce... Gosh, I'm so nervous.
- You are? - I'm so nervous.
- When I make a ssam - All right.
When I make a ssam
You have to hurry.
Don't take time trying to remember.
- You're running out of time. - When I make a ssam
Chili pepper
When I make a ssam, I put a chili pepper first
- Wrong. - You got it wrong.
(She's out.)
It was three pieces of jeyuk bokkeum.
(Her love for chili peppers caused her trouble.)
It finally came to an end.
(I'm so glad it's not me.)
It's amazing.
I was so nervous.
All right, So Min. You need to have that ssam now.
How can she eat that?
She can't eat it. It's huge like a sandwich.
(It's a sandwich for cows, not a ssam for So Min.)
I...
(So Min's reaping what she sowed.)
I'm reaping what I sowed.
It'll even make a bear turn into a human.
I love how passionate you are.
Is it good?
It must be tasty.
(How about a well-being, ssam burger as a snack for today?)
She eats it well.
She fails the mission.
(So Min is out.)
The second round of Ssam My Way is called Ssam Says.
Ready, go.
Grab a lettuce,
and put a perilla leaf and chicory on top.
Make a nice ssam with ingredients except for raw garlic.
Show me the ingredients I've mentioned in your ssam.
- All right. - Lettuce, perilla leaf...
(Will Se Chan win first place and acquire a hint?)
- It's difficult. - I don't have it.
- I only have two of them. - She's out.
Then Se Chan is the only one to clear the mission.
Okay!
(Sheriff Se Chan wins first place.)
It's amazing.
It was grilled onions, not garlic.
(He gets to receive a hint.)
It'd be the best if he's the sheriff.
(Anxious)
Think about what I've done so far.
- Can I have it now? - He might be the thief.
- You can't share it with us, right? - He can't.
Let us know though.
- What? - Share it with us.
Share it with someone you can really trust.
Can I read it now?
It has to be destroyed 30 seconds after you read it.
My goodness.
(The hint will be destroyed 30 seconds after he reads it.)
(Se Chan knows all the hints which came out so far.)
Se Chan, you're awesome.
It's strange how Se Chan gets all the hints.
(He can't share the hint because no one can be trusted.)
I'll read it at the back.
It was so close.
It was the chance to win first place.
(What's the last hint about?)
(Thieves are very talkative.)
(He also obtained another hint.)
(One of the thieves...)
(is married.)
One of them is married.
One of them.
(Is it Jae Seok or Haha?)
(If the other thief is not married,)
(is it Kwang Soo or So Min who are both talkative?)
(It's been narrowed down. Thieves, you'll be caught soon.)
(Place for the last race)
What's in here?
What's this?
(It's a courtroom.)
What's going on?
Is it about telling the truth?
- It's a courtroom. - It is.
It looks amazing.
It's a trial.
This mission...
is the last chance to identify the thieves.
It's called Judgment Day.
(Judgment Day)
(It's Judgment Day?)
Inside this building,
hints related to the thieves and the sheriff are hidden.
Find the hints...
and figure out who the thieves and the sheriff may be.
There will be a trial every 30 minutes...
during which you can identify the thieves.
We must find proof.
The civilians should work together.
(He claps.)
What was that?
- Wait a minute. - Why are you putting on an act?
May I suspect someone before we start?
He's so strange.
(Why are you so awkward?)
You're so cute today, Jae Seok.
I know you feel impatient.
- Wait a little longer. - If you get identified so quickly,
wouldn't the other thief be nervous?
So Min will start to get nervous.
(Jae Seok looks suspicious.)
(Is he really a thief?)
Let's start. We'll figure it out when we get the hints.
You'll start at different places.
- Please go to your places. - Let's go.
Let's eliminate Seok Jin first.
- We'll start with you. - No.
(Who will be on trial 30 minutes later?)
Are you not a thief?
Are you really not?
- I'm not. - I think it's you.
Why?
- Is it because you're a thief? - It can't be Seok Jin.
- Is that why? - No.
- Listen to her. - What did she say?
She suspects that I'm a thief.
- So Min does? - Yes.
- She suspected everyone. - Do you know why?
It's because she's a thief.
I think she is.
I'm the sheriff.
- It's unfortunate. - What?
- I'm the sheriff. - That also sounds strange.
- It sounds strange. - Are you the sheriff?
- That makes no sense. - If you are, you must tell us.
- Yes, I'm the sheriff. - We have to protect you.
We have to protect her.
This isn't Name Tag Elimination.
We have to find the hints.
Once we find them, we'll figure out together.
We must remember this.
The civilians must...
come together to identify the thieves.
Protect me since I'm the sheriff.
- I'm also a civilian. - I'm sure.
I'm quite sure.
- Here's a thief. - What is this?
(Running)
- It's a thief. - Come on.
(They exclude the prime suspect.)
- Go away. - We won't include you.
We won't include you.
Brave civilians.
(Let's come together.)
(That includes me.)
Civilians, do not be confused.
(The civilians disperse.)
Honestly speaking,
- Haha is suspicious. - Please press three.
Haha is suspicious.
- He's also suspicious. - It's difficult.
- It's difficult. - He really is.
It's strange.
He's too suspicious.
This isn't Name Tag Elimination.
Third floor.
- We have to get off. - Second floor.
We're having an important conversation.
I don't believe this.
- Kwang Soo. - I was saying...
- Get off the elevator. - Get off.
- Get off. So Min. - I'm getting off.
- See you later, So Min. - See you later.
- See you. - I'm a civilian.
You said you're the sheriff earlier.
- Civilian. - You said you're the sheriff.
Haha is suspicious.
- He is. - He really is.
- I'm a civilian. - He overreacts.
- You know? - Yes.
The phone call at the restaurant was too much.
Do you realize that I'm not a thief?
- You could be the sheriff. - I'm not sure.
- I'll protect you. - You...
- I'll protect you. - have to be protected.
(He suspects So Min.)
Don't do anything to me if you're a thief.
Don't do anything to me.
I'll be disappointed if you do.
(The real sheriff appears.)
Are you filming me?
What's going on?
(A moving camera follows him.)
(He feels happy to be the sheriff.)
Here are the rules.
This is how the sheriff can eliminate others secretly.
(How the sheriff can eliminate others secretly)
You may eliminate others...
(Dear Sheriff)
with a water gun.
A water gun?
(Shoot the water gun.)
(The water gun is loaded with blue paint.)
Shoot the water gun at the member's name tag.
Then rip off the name tag to eliminate him or her.
(He must shoot and take off the name tag.)
This'll be hard.
(Arrest the thieves by shooting blue paint water gun.)
(Sheriff)
This is amazing. Put it on neatly.
When someone asks who the sheriff is,
I'll appear all of a sudden.
(I'm the sheriff.)
I'm nervous as I'm given an important task.
(This is Sheriff Yang who will protect the civilians.)
I'm nervous since I'm in the spotlight today.
I'm nervous.
(Rest assured, Civilians.)
The game will be boring since Jae Seok is acting too obvious.
Everyone in my car suspected Jae Seok.
He'll give up soon.
The unlucky thief may be single.
It could be Kwang Soo.
Could the unlucky thief be Haha?
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo is suspicious.
How can she say 6 times 5 is 15?
(He calculates the probability.)
Whatever.
I don't know what I'm doing right now.
I don't know. It's not me anyway.
I'm just a good civilian.
(Seok Jin is a civilian.)
See? I'm a civilian.
Jae Seok is definitely a thief.
It could also be So Min.
(So Min?)
I think it may be Se Chan.
I have no idea who the sheriff is.
I'm definitely a civilian.
I'm bad at multiplication tables.
I made a mistake.
(That's a misunderstanding.)
I'm sorry. My mind was somewhere else.
(Ji Hyo is also a civilian.)
(The suspects are narrowed down to 5 people.)
I'm sure Se Chan is a civilian.
I think Seok Jin is also a civilian.
So Min is...
(However, So Min is...)
I have no idea who she is.
I don't understand her as a person.
The more I get to know her, the less I understand.
(Who is she?)
(So Min is...)
(moving about.)
Why do you keep filming me?
(She likes to avoid the camera.)
Are the hints in an envelope?
Or is it a flag?
(Where are they?)
They aren't easily visible, are they?
Are they hard to find?
(They must be hidden well.)
(What is the identity of So Min?)
The race will start now.
Five.
4, 3, 2, 1.
The race starts.
All right. Let's go.
Okay.
I have to find the hints.
(Looking through)
Where are they?
(They must find the hints first.)
Goodness. This race...
Let's get it over with.
I can't do it any longer.
- Se Chan. - Where are you going?
- Did you find anything? - I'm still looking.
(Haha appears.)
I'm looking.
(They look at each other.)
(He senses something.)
- Se Chan, what are you doing? - What?
What's wrong?
Stop it. I'm looking.
Your facial expression.
- Haha. - Your behavior.
- What are you? - Listen.
We'll protect you since you're a civilian.
Tell me who the thieves are. Just name one.
I know one of them.
Jae Seok?
Who protects Jae Seok the most?
Who is the one that protects Jae Seok the most?
You'll find out soon.
Who could it be?
- Good luck. - Thank you.
If you're the sheriff...
(If you're the sheriff...)
(If I'm the sheriff?)
I'll still protect you.
(I'll still protect you.)
(He'll still protect me?)
What are you?
(What are you?)
Who are you?
- Who are you to protect me? - Me?
- Who are you? - Se Chan.
You punk.
I said I'll protect you.
You're the sheriff of Mapo.
- What? - I'll protect you.
Who am I?
- Who are you to protect me? - Didn't I sound cool?
You did at first, but now that I think of it,
who are you to protect me?
(Who are you, Haha?)
See you later.
Something amazing will happen in 30 minutes.
We will get so much air time this week.
- Just wait and see. - I don't know what Haha is.
I don't.
"What are you?"
I got flustered.
Haha...
I'm bothered by him.
This is funny.
(Does Haha really know something?)
- Hello, Seok Jin. - So Min.
You're in danger right now.
Why?
You'll be mentioned at the trial.
- Me? - Yes, I'm giving you information.
I'm a civilian.
Who do you think it is then?
Me?
(She approaches Seok Jin.)
I think it's Jong Kook.
(She slides in.)
I didn't find anything. I'm clean.
What are you doing?
You look so natural.
- What are you doing? - Let me see it once.
There's nothing in it.
You wrote something down.
- Just once. - There's nothing.
- What are you doing, by the way? - You wrote something down.
Can you show it to me?
You're not supposed to show it to each other.
- Can you show it to me once? - I found it.
I looked everywhere and found nothing.
I'll tell you.
"There is a big difference in height."
(He just says something random.)
- Height? Between two people? - Yes.
- Between two people? - Their height is largely different.
It's Kwang Soo.
It's Kwang Soo and Haha.
It has to be Kwang Soo and Haha.
(Does she really believe me?)
Don't they look like the thieves from "Home Alone"?
Yes, It's Kwang Soo and Haha.
(Thieves Among Us)
Kwang Soo.
What is it? What were you laughing about?
It's nothing. It was just funny.
(They bump into each other in a secluded area.)
- I should try here. - What?
- I should look here. - I think...
it's you and Jong Kook, or Jong Kook and Jae Seok.
I think it's Jae Seok too.
Jae Seok and Jong Kook.
- Let's look some more. - What if we do Jong Kook first?
- I like that idea. - Me too. I made up my mind.
I think it's Jong Kook.
- I think the culprit... - Civilian Song Ji Hyo is out.
Civilian Song Ji Hyo is out.
(Ji Hyo is out?)
The thief eliminated an innocent civilian.
(You can get eliminated from this game?)
Civilian Song Ji Hyo is out.
What?
(They are in panic mode over the announcement.)
The thief eliminated an innocent civilian.
Here's a hint about the thief.
(How, when, and who eliminated a civilian?)
(A hint is released about the thief for killing a civilian.)
- A hint about the thief? - They're giving us a hint.
- What is it? - It's a hint. Hold up.
Listen carefully.
Here's a hint about the thief.
Thief A has the letter S in their name.
(Here's the hint.)
Thief A has the letter S in the name?
Lee Kwang Soo.
Jee Seok Jin.
(Jee Seok Jin?)
(Is it you?)
Hold on.
The fact that she's out means...
How do you eliminate somebody?
Why did she get eliminated all of a sudden?
I'm scared right now. Don't come near me.
- Don't come near me. - I'm scared of your eyes.
No. Why are you coming closer?
Why are you coming closer? Don't come.
The trial will begin in one minute.
- Please assemble. - It's hot.
(Will the truth be revealed at the court?)
She's so scary.
I'm getting scared of him.
There's an S?
(Thinking)
There's an S. So Min,
Jae Seok,
Seok Jin...
(He lists all the S's.)
Kwang Soo...
I don't think you rip off the name tag.
- What? - I don't think it's the name tags.
I don't think so either.
- What? - What is it?
What?
(Why is he surprised at Seok Jin?)
- What is this? - What?
(What's going on with Seok Jin?)
What's wrong?
What is it?
Hold on.
- What? - You got shot by a water gun.
(He got shot by a water gun?)
(I got shot by a water gun?)
- I did? - Yes.
What color is it?
It's pink.
(There's a pink stain on Seok Jin's name tag.)
(It's different from Se Chan's blue paint.)
I got shot by a water gun?
I think you're out.
I'll get going.
I have to survive. I'm sorry.
- I have to go. I'm sorry. - I mean...
- I might get infected. - Is there a mirror?
- Who shot the water gun? - It's a water gun.
Did you do it?
- How's that possible? - You were here for a while.
- Let me check. Be honest. - I don't have anything.
- Didn't you shoot it? - I can't get infected.
- Kwang Soo. - You've been infected.
- It could have been you. - It's not me.
Who did you meet before me?
(Who did he meet before Kwang Soo?)
So Min,
Jae Seok...
- Did you find something? - Did you find anything?
There's nothing.
Tell me what's going on. I have no idea.
I'm looking for a hint, but there aren't any.
(Hold on.)
I just saw it.
I have a good eye.
I think Jae Seok has a water gun too.
(He's 200 percent sure.)
(A short while ago, in front of the elevator)
Are you going down?
(Jae Seok was spotted by Sheriff Yang.)
- I'm going to check downstairs. - Okay.
(Wait. What's that?)
(Is that a pink stain on Jae Seok's shirt?)
(Everything is pointing towards Jae Seok.)
All right.
(He's onto Jae Seok.)
I'll go around.
I'll go around. There's no hint here.
Jae Seok, gosh.
(Jae Seok has been acting strange all day.)
(He's going to meet him.)
Here's an announcement.
- Please listen up. - What were they saying earlier?
(This looks like a natural encounter.)
- What? - What letter was it?
An S?
I didn't find anything.
- Did you find anything? - Nothing.
How long is a minute?
(He looks for a good timing...)
(and spots Jae Seok's back.)
We didn't see here.
- Should we look here? - Okay.
(He makes it look like he's looking for a hint.)
(He loads the blue water gun.)
(Spraying)
(Jae Seok is shot.)
- We didn't look here. - Exactly.
(He just has to rip off Jae Seok's name tag now.)
I have to hide it again.
Time is up. Please head towards the court.
(He hides the evidence.)
(He finally did it.)
Did you see that? That looked cool.
(30 minutes have passed. The 1st race is over.)
(This is where the trial will be held.)
Seok Jin. So Min is pink.
I'm right. It's her.
I'm going to say it.
(Even her shirt is pink.)
- It's not me. - You got shot.
I'm going to the restroom.
The water gun... Why are you going to the restroom?
- Where are you going? - I'll be right back.
Are you filling up your water gun?
Are you hiding it?
We'll treat you to something nice after this.
I'm going to the restroom.
This is not fair. Where's the restroom?
It's not me.
Se Chan has it too.
Se Chan, you got shot too.
What?
(Why does Se Chan have a pink stain too?)
- Come here. - You got shot too.
Me?
(If the sheriff is out, the thief wins. Se Chan is in danger.)
(When did he get attacked?)
(During the past 30 minutes, Se Chan bumped into many people.)
(There's a thief among them.)
Did I get shot?
(Will Sheriff Yang be able to catch the thieves?)
(It's the first trial.)
- I can't trust you. - You can.
- I'm being honest. - The thieves can lie.
I think you two will be eliminated soon.
(They both have water gun stains.)
- Can you leave a long testament? - Why?
- No, look. - I think they'll be gone soon.
- He got shot. - Jae Seok, let me see your back.
- Let me see you. - Let's see.
- He has 2. - There are 2.
(There are two?)
- Let me see you. - Let's see.
- He has 2. - There are 2.
(He got shot twice?)
(There's the blue paint from Se Chan, and what's the other one?)
(Who shot the pink one?)
(Was it the thief? Then, Jae Seok is...)
- I got shot too? - You did.
You're a target too. This is getting confusing.
- I'm getting goosebumps. - I had no idea.
(Everything is still a mystery. First trial begins.)
Let me speak first.
So Min,
you tried to look.
You spun it around and tried to look at it.
Then, Kwang Soo was surprised by my name tag. Why?
I got shot by the water gun.
(Did So Min do that?)
What is the color of your shirt?
- It's pink. - What's this color?
It's pink. But it's not...
How long were you around me?
- Around 5 minutes? - It was around 5 minutes.
That's enough time.
That's it, everybody.
So Min...
(Seok Jin suspects So Min and she doesn't have an alibi.)
I bumped into So Min on the seventh floor.
With a blushed face, she said,
"Haha, I'm a civilian."
I instinctively turned my back towards the wall.
It was an instinct.
And then, I heard the announcement.
It was about the trial being held in one minute.
Suddenly, without thinking...
Without thinking, she asked the staff members.
"There's no name tag ripping on the way to the court, right?"
(1 minute before the trial, on the 7th floor hallway)
She's so scary.
Go first.
You can't rip it off here, right?
(You can't rip it off here, right?)
What? You're supposed to rip off name tags?
- Just in case. - How do you know that?
- I mean, earlier... - What do you mean?
You knew it was about ripping the name tag.
- Right now... - The civilians had no idea.
Don't only the thieves know about it?
(Isn't Running Man about ripping name tags?)
- If you think I'm a thief... - Everyone, let's save So Min...
from this suffering.
It's not me.
- I never thought it was her. - It's not me.
It's not really me.
- Who do you think the thief is? - Mention one name.
I think it's Jong Kook. He's my first pick.
- Why? Why is it me? - Earlier...
- You were acting strange. - Look into my eyes.
What did you find strange?
You were really angry today.
Aren't you way too close? Don't you think?
You were really angry,
and you are usually good in games.
- I was good today. - You were...
But you were being too angry.
- That's normal of me. - Especially today, right?
If he's not the thief, and if he's still this angry,
he should go see a counselor.
(He should go see a counselor.)
- I think strongly of this. - Hold on.
It's not time to look for a thief if you're not one.
I don't feel different.
I don't think you can control your emotions.
I'm not bothered by it.
I'm totally fine.
Let's commence the trial.
Starting from Haha,
please state who you'd like to put on trial.
(The person who gets picked will be eliminated with the majority vote.)
- I don't know. - Everybody.
Please trust my instinct as the Mapo Sheriff.
Let's put So Min to ease.
- It's not me. - Kwang Soo is next.
- So Min. - It's not me.
Se Chan?
I pick...
(He takes his time.)
(He's careful.)
(He thought it was Jae Seok before going into the court.)
(He shot Jae Seok and waited to eliminate him.)
(There has been a twist in the story.)
(Jae Seok got shot by the thief?)
- I got shot too? - You got shot.
(If Jae Seok is not the thief,)
(the only potential suspect is...)
You'll get punished. It's not me.
(The only potential suspect is...)
So Min.
(He picks So Min after some thought.)
(Sheriff Yang picks So Min after some thought.)
- So Min. - This is done.
Then, a majority has been reached,
so we'll have So Min stand on the R mark.
It's not me.
I was always weird.
- I think it might be her. - I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything.
You can change your mind now. It's not me.
So Min's identity is...
(So Min is the first defendant.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Her identity is written inside her name tag.)
If you're a civilian, I'll treat you to dinner.
(She was always weird,)
(but she was weirder today.)
(Se Chan, I'm actually the sheriff.)
(She impersonated the sheriff in front of a real one.)
(Was it because she was the thief?)
(Or was she always weird?)
(So Min, please rest now.)
(What is her identity?)
(It's unbelievable.)
(The first defendant, So Min, is...)
I told you it's not me.
(She is an innocent civilian.)
(She's the first victim.)
It's not her. I can't watch this.
(I need to break out of jail.)
I'm so mad.
Why did Haha say that?
- What happened? - I told you.
I didn't suspect So Min.
I told you it's not me.
Everybody, we should suspect Haha.
(Haha becomes the main suspect for accusing So Min.)
It's not me.
He's strange. He accused So Min.
An innocent civilian died,
so the race resumes now.
Please move back to your original positions.
(Haha, Kwang Soo, Jong Kook, and Jae Seok are the candidates.)
I think Kwang Soo is the sheriff.
I have to find something to make progress.
(They can't trust each other, so they must find the hints.)
Hey, are you the sheriff?
- I'm not. - You're not?
- I'm not. - Are you the thief?
I'm not. Jae Seok,
I think you'll be eliminated soon.
If you have some hints, please share it with me.
I have none.
You got shot twice.
You're a living dead.
Tell me everything and die in honor.
I don't know who shot me.
Try guessing who shot you.
I met you,
Se Chan...
(He met everybody.)
- I met Seok Jin... - Twice...
What's that?
Your sock...
(Your sock...)
What's that?
(Kwon Ryeol's sock?)
(Why is there pink paint?)
(Hold on.)
Look at him. Hey.
(It's the paint they saw earlier.)
(It was on Seok Jin...)
(and Se Chan's backs.)
(Why is Kwon Ryeol's sock soaked with it?)
Did you shoot?
(No way. Is it...)
(Is it him?)
(This morning, 30 minutes before the start of filming)
(Jae Seok and another thief are here.)
(Jae Seok is Thief A.)
Today's special is Defend the Stickers.
Thieves Among Us.
- Is that right? - The two of you...
are thieves who stole the I Go Stickers.
Us?
The rest of the members are civilians.
(These are innocent civilians who must reveal the thieves.)
And one of them...
is the sheriff, who is on the civilians' side.
You must find the sheriff...
and eliminate him or her to win.
On the other hand, if you get eliminated, the civilians win.
(They'll try to eliminate each other to win.)
(So that's how Jae Seok started.)
- Your fingers. - Do it in one shot.
(He interfered with the missions so that they can't get hints.)
- Hold on. - So Min.
- Jae Seok. - He did that on purpose.
You're one of the thieves, Jae Seok.
Oh, gosh.
- Here's something special. - What is it?
The thieves and the sheriff...
can kill each other...
during the 30 minutes of the race.
You can kill the sheriff or the civilians by...
- What is it? - What are you known for?
The water gun. Do I shoot it?
(Jae Seok makes his return with the water gun as the thief.)
This water gun is important...
because once you shoot at a civilian's name tag,
he must rip the name tag to eliminate the civilian.
This is difficult.
(If he eliminates a civilian, a hint will be released about him.)
- Why are you drinking that? - It's open.
(Spraying)
(Jae Seok shot at everybody...)
(he suspected to be the sheriff.)
(He planned it out so that they will be eliminated quickly.)
- Okay. - I'm getting goosebumps.
(He also approached Se Chan.)
Why is he doing that?
(He shot at the sheriff without incurring any suspicion.)
Me? Why me?
(Why did he turn away on his way to the court?)
Can you shoot at me too?
(Kwon Ryeol, shoot at me too.)
(He shoots at his own back too.)
(He avoided everybody's suspicion.)
- I got shot too? - You got shot.
(Everything was going perfect for him,)
(and Kwon Ryeol's sock might give him away.)
Kwang Soo, I don't know anything.
It's not me. Kwang Soo...
(That's what it is.)
Hey, how can you do this? My gosh.
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo sprints away.)
Jong Kook!
My goodness.
It's not me. My gosh.
(Kwang Soo ran off without the cameraman.)
Your cameraman is back there.
- Where was he? - He was looking for you.
- Jong Kook. - What is it?
- This is so shocking. - Why?
(His heart is still pounding.)
What's going on? What is it?
- Tell me what's going on. - I was talking to Jae Seok.
I don't know if I should tell you this.
Why not?
I thought it was Jae Seok for sure.
I was talking to him, and I was looking around.
Okay.
Kwon Ryeol was wearing a pink sock and a white sock.
- What? - I thought...
that was strange, and I looked.
His sock was soaked with pink paint.
- Really? - Yes, it was Kwon Ryeol.
I'm right. It's Jae Seok. I'm certain.
I don't think it's something to be surprised about.
(Is that all?)
I gave you an important information.
It's not something to consider lightly.
We kind of suspected him from the beginning.
Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok joins them.)
Hey, you... Listen to me.
(He runs away as soon as he sees the thief.)
- Don't come near. Talk there. - What did he say?
- Hey, Kwang Soo. - Hey...
What are we supposed to do?
No... Hold on.
- Hold on. Don't tell Jong Kook. - Are you the sheriff?
You're not the sheriff.
(If you're the sheriff,)
(you shouldn't run away from the thief.)
You're not the sheriff.
(He starts a mission of his own.)
You're not the sheriff, so you can't go around talking about me.
I'll be in trouble.
Be careful, Kwang Soo.
I'm the sheriff.
Are you planning to spoil everything?
(Keep my identity a secret.)
You told Jong Kook I was acting strange, right?
Be careful, Kwang Soo.
(I didn't know you were the sheriff.)
You can't go around saying that.
Be quiet.
(It's fun lying to Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo knows about the water gun so Jae Seok gets ready to shoot.)
(Spraying)
(Kwang Soo's name tag is ready to be ripped off.)
You need to think.
(If you are a civilian, you should protect the sheriff.)
What are you going to do if I am the sheriff?
Kwon Ryeol, change socks with me.
For goodness' sake.
You need to think.
You are the sheriff.
Of course, I am.
- For goodness' sake. - You are the sheriff.
Don't tell anyone.
(Keep my identity a secret.)
You aren't the sheriff.
Then keep quiet.
(He checks until the end.)
(Jae Seok acquires a dependable ally.)
(The real sheriff is looking for the thieves.)
- Did you find the thieves? - Kwang Soo.
- Did you find the thieves? - No, I didn't.
(Who are the thieves?)
- Where is Haha? - I don't know. Tell me.
- I have no idea. - Jae Seok,
it's showing.
(His water gun is showing.)
(The person who has a water gun...)
(other than the sheriff is...)
(the thief.)
Wait a minute.
Catch him.
I am not a thief.
Wait a minute.
(Jae Seok's name tag has been sprayed.)
(Removing the name tag will eliminate him.)
(Slipping)
You are mistaken.
He could be the sheriff.
- No, he isn't. Catch him. - He could be the sheriff.
- Catch him. - Come to your senses.
(Jae Seok is the sheriff.)
- No, he isn't. - Come to your senses.
- Come to your senses. - Think.
What's going on?
(The members gather.)
Who is the sheriff?
What's going on?
- He is the sheriff. - Kwang Soo, come here.
- Jae Seok, come here. - Who is the sheriff?
- Who is the sheriff? - Come here.
- Who is the sheriff? - What's going on?
I will finish everyone off.
There is no need to think. He is the thief.
I need to be alone.
Let me go over my thoughts.
(Get out. I need to be alone.)
Come here.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, Jae Seok escapes.)
(It's all thanks to Kwang Soo that I lost Jae Seok.)
(Jae Seok has Kwang Soo fooled.)
Haha.
(Finding hints is the way to go.)
Have you been sprayed?
You haven't been sprayed yet, right?
I have been sprayed.
- You have? - Yes.
(Have you been sprayed?)
I must find hints, and deduce the answer...
without talking to anyone.
I don't know whom to trust.
You just need to remove the name tag.
Just eliminate him.
(Why do I feel...)
(a sense of foreboding?)
Civilian Lee Kwang Soo is out.
(Since a civilian is out, it's time to get a hint on the thieves.)
Kwang Soo was a civilian. This is bad.
Thief B didn't go into Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
(Thief B didn't go into Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(Haha and Jong Kook are the only ones.)
(Is one of them Thief B?)
(Since Jae Seok had already sprayed Kwang Soo's name tag,)
(the other thief only had to remove it.)
(Who is the other thief?)
Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
You are the thief. Jong Kook.
(Ripping)
- Jong Kook. - Stay down.
(Kwang Soo is out.)
All right.
(Kwang Soo, are you surprised?)
(This morning, 30 minutes before the shoot)
(Two thieves gathered to receive a secret order.)
(Thief B, Kim Jong Kook)
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook hadn't worked together recently.)
For goodness' sake.
We are in...
the opposing teams.
Listen.
We aren't meant to sit together like this.
This is frustrating.
- How frustrating. - Give us the mission. What is it?
Let us finish it, and leave.
It's stifling to be in the same room as Jong Kook.
I can't breathe.
Today, we will have Defend the Stickers,
Thieves Among Us.
Really?
Will he be the thief?
- For goodness' sake. - Will I catch him?
Both of us will be thieves.
But you know, since Jae Seok is sloppy,
I am a bit worried.
How frustrating.
He should be the thief, and I, the sheriff.
That's the relationship we have.
If one of us gets caught,
- can the other play the game? - Will it end the game?
Thieves will win if only one survives and catches the sheriff.
- Really? - I see.
- In that case, - That's nice.
I can use him as bait.
What are you talking about?
That will be nice.
If you do that, I will destroy everything.
(Try me.)
- You know what I am like, right? - Don't be that way.
- I won't die alone. - For goodness' sake.
You know what Kwang Soo and I are like, right?
- We are moths. - I know.
- We fly into the flame. - I know.
All right.
For goodness' sake.
My goodness.
(As soon as the other members suspected Jae Seok,)
(Jong Kook cast him as bait.)
(He lead the suspicion on Jae Seok,)
(and avoided getting suspected himself.)
The doors are closing.
For goodness' sake.
- You need to work properly. - You need to work properly.
You need to work properly.
What in the world are you doing?
- I have never seen anyone... - Do you want me to self-destruct?
- who is worse at this. - Do you want me to self-destruct?
Do you want to ruin everything?
- What choice did I have? - How dare you throw me to them?
Had I defended you,
we would have fallen under everyone's suspicion.
- Let's catch the sheriff. - All right.
Work properly.
Hold on. I have a plan.
- Did you find the hints? - They are hard to find.
- You didn't find anything? - No, I didn't.
Jae Seok, aren't you busy?
- What? - Do you have time to play around?
(Let's go, Jae Seok.)
We should finish her off.
It's a water gun!
Ji Hyo, be quiet. Be quiet.
- Remove the name tag. - Come here.
Hurry up, and remove it.
(Jae Seok sprayed the name tag, and Jong Kook removed it.)
(That's how Ji Hyo got eliminated first.)
Since there is glass everywhere, we should talk at a distance.
Listen to what I have to say from over there.
I will spray Kwang Soo's name tag.
- Spray Kwang Soo's name tag. - Even if I die,
- you need to finish the rest. - I will take care of them.
- Okay? - Okay.
Be careful.
I bet the sheriff has something he can use on us.
Okay.
(Jae Seok followed the plan, and sprayed Kwang Soo's name tag.)
(Afterwards, Jong Kook finished him off.)
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo, are you okay?)
(Kwang Soo still believes Jae Seok is the sheriff.)
You have been eliminated.
Kwang Soo.
What happened?
This is driving me crazy.
Who is the sheriff?
(Come here, you thief.)
(Kwang Soo, thank you for saving me earlier.)
(Kwon Ryeol, give me back my socks.)
Civilian Lee Kwang Soo is out.
The thieves eliminated an innocent civilian.
Thief B didn't go into Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
It's Jong Kook.
(People become certain that Jong Kook is the thief.)
(If they have a trial, Jong Kook will be eliminated.)
It's Jong Kook.
It's certain.
You have three minutes until the trial.
(The thieves have no time.)
Let's talk.
Jae Seok, shall we out everyone?
Hold on.
Either Seok Jin or Se Chan is the sheriff.
- Really? - The hint I found said...
the sheriff's name contains the letter S.
(A moment ago)
(Jae Seok found a hint by pure luck.)
Please let it be a hint on the sheriff.
(The sheriff's name contains the letter S.)
- Let's find and eliminate them. - That's right.
Don't worry about Haha.
- Let's find Seok Jin or Se Chan. - Are you sure it's one of them?
Remove their name tags as soon as you see them.
(Se Chan is their number 1 target.)
He isn't here.
It must be Se Chan.
(They must catch Se Chan before the trial.)
Should I go here?
Where could he be?
(Se Chan's target is Jae Seok.)
Where could Jae Seok be?
Hurry up and find him.
(The sheriff and the two thieves chase each other.)
- You have a minute until the trial. - We must catch him.
Otherwise, we will die.
(At that moment,)
(Jong Kook finds Se Chan.)
All right.
Come here.
Don't do that.
(He only needs to hold out for 20 seconds to catch them.)
- Se Chan. - Don't do that.
Se Chan.
It's okay.
- Se Chan. - Wait a minute.
Jae Seok.
(The sheriff is out 15 seconds before the trial.)
- Are you the sheriff? - Are you the sheriff?
He is the sheriff.
Really?
(Sheriff)
My goodness.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
The winners are the thieves.
Here comes the board.
The 2 thieves will take 2 I Go Stickers.
(The stolen I Go Stickers become theirs.)
This is the most important part.
Jong Kook and Jae Seok, discuss among yourselves,
and put the I Go Stickers on the board.
Will they put the Stickers without rolling a die?
That's right.
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook's Stickers...)
(will decide who goes on the trip.)
Congratulations.
(Congratulations.)
Thieves. Thieves.
Your eloquent words had me fooled.
We can't do anything when someone tries to con us.
- I... - You weren't feeling well, right?
There was no way we could have beaten you.
- Go, Jong Kook! - Today...
If we give one to this guy...
- Isn't that so sudden? - That's great.
- Hear me out. - This is fun.
We don't have to give one to this guy...
because he will be chosen by the member with three Stickers anyway.
(He will accompany the member.)
(He's bound to go.)
You didn't have to say that.
Why do you jump to conclusions?
Whoever gets three Stickers will choose him.
(It will be Kwang Soo.)
We can conclude he will go.
Why would we waste one Sticker on him?
I have no I Go Stickers.
(Will he continue to go on the trip?)
Is there something you want to say, So Min?
- I will do my best. - Wait.
- Should we give you one? - No.
(Will you do your best there?)
We will stand in the back and you can put the Stickers.
- Let's do that. - Okay.
- Let's have a close match. - Turn around and face the back.
This is intense.
- I think we can choose this member. - Okay.
- Please. - Should we put it here?
- I agree with you. - Okay.
- This member will go next week. - Consider it done.
(This is a place for 1 percent which is full of extreme experiences.)
(Haha is about to go on the trip and Seok Jin and So Min are close too.)
Everyone, on my count of three, turn around and see the result.
In 1, 2, 3.
What? Goodness.
Three.
(I didn't get the Sticker.)
- Is someone going? - Oh, no.
(Seok Jin and So Min get 1 Sticker each.)
(Seok Jin, So Min, and Haha all have 2 Stickers.)
- This is a three-way race. - It is.
- Kwang Soo. - Why?
- You survived. - Of course.
The number of Stickers for him doesn't matter.
(What are you talking about?)
In my opinion, Kwang Soo...
should start packing this week.
Why would I pack now?
- You can start now. - It won't be me.
- Next week, someone will be picked. - I agree.
- I'm certain of it. - That's right.
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Are you okay going on the trip?
- Me? - Yes.
Who put this on here?
I am going to go with that person.
I don't know who it is. I will watch the episode.
- I'll pick that person. - Look.
- It will be a new world next week. - That's right.
(Next week, there will be a whole new world.)
(A Place for 1 Percent, the Final Race)
(The ones who want to be exempted from the trip...)
(must avoid being the unlucky one.)
(This is only a taste of the real trip.)
(There are no enemies...)
(or comrades.)
(This is a series of mistrust and betrayals.)
(No one can...)
(make any prediction.)
(This is the ultimate race of the twists.)
(If you can't avoid it, enjoy it.)
(Final Race for 1 Percent)
(Running Man)