It's Running Man Member's Week.
(The seventh and the last member is...)
(Lee Kwang Soo.)
(I get lonely often.)
(I am lonely all day long, but it gets worse at night.)
(I want a travel plan for myself as I live alone.)
(I'd like a night tour to fill in my loneliness.)
(And...)
(there has to be a penalty this week.)
(I am always the one to be doubted first. I'm sick of it.)
(Maybe there could be a twist...)
(so that the members won't be suspicious of me.)
You can make some kind of system.
(If you fail this time,)
(I will be fighting against the staff.)
(I look forward to my Member's Week.)
(That's how Kwang Soo's Week started.)
Hello, members of Running Man!
I will give you a mission.
Until midnight,
think about a trip we can take at night for me.
Then come to the place where we film our opening segment.
(However)
Don't wear any makeup.
Don't do your hair.
Don't bring your manager or your stylist.
Running Man members, don't forget to come at 12am.
Viewers, during my week,
I will bet everything I have and make sure...
I will absolutely make sure...
that I succeed this time.
Thank you!
(This is how Kwang Soo disclosed his surprise mission.)
(That night at 11:52pm...)
(Mokdong SBS)
(Somehow, they look grubby.)
Why?
(They're not dressed up.)
It's midnight.
(They have minimalist looks.)
Put your microphones on.
Why did you wear a long, padding coat?
It might get cold.
- Why not? - How can you wear that to a shoot?
It's because I had to wear my own clothes.
(He's wearing clothes he'd wear to a shop nearby.)
(Someone arrives in a taxi without his manager.)
Thank you.
(Haha is full of annoyance.)
So why did you call me all of a sudden?
What are we doing now?
I came as soon as I finished another shoot.
This is my second shooting today.
What are we doing in the middle of the night?
Haha is here.
He looks shabby.
What's with those blue pants?
Are you going to a morning soccer club?
Are you playing soccer?
- You deserve a penalty. - It's fashion.
- It's fashion. - Just don't say anything.
(His fashion is friendly and stylish.)
- Oh, my. - People will go crazy over this.
- They might go mad. - You're sometimes so out of style.
- It's Ji Hyo. - Are you all right?
- Well... - Why did he call us at night?
He's here. He's here.
- Jong Kook. - He's here.
I worked out my legs today because I thought I'd have no shooting.
I can't even walk well.
Why do you exercise until you can't walk?
Why would you?
- How much do you exercise? - This is bad.
You only worked out your legs?
- What is that? - What is that?
(The scum is here.)
- I don't want to see him again. - What is he doing?
(Because the day was good, because the day was bad,)
(because it was just right. It's a good day for a Member's Week.)
Hello.
(Goblin Kwang enters.)
What is this?
- Why aren't you in your clothes? - Why aren't you dressed casually?
(Why are you dressed up?)
- Are you wearing your own clothes? - Yes.
- Did you put makeup on? - You're wearing makeup.
- I did. - Why did you?
(I'm the main character.)
By the way, I have to sleep now.
- Why did you call me at midnight? - Jae Seok.
- I'm sleepy. - Even the weather is bad today.
- Why is it raining today? - I know, it's raining.
It's your week. Do as you want.
It better be fun. I'll be watching.
How can I do anything about it?
Calling me at midnight is okay. But I'll be watching you.
All right.
It's 12am now.
We will start Kwang Soo's Week.
Please give a big hand.
(Kwang Soo's Week begins.)
I will if you say so.
(Annoyed)
You have to introduce one by one your night tour course...
that you've thought of.
Kwang Soo will choose four according to his preference.
- That's right. - After completing all the trips,
if you return to SBS by 6am, it will be considered as a success.
- Really? - If you fail to return in time,
- there will be a terrible penalty. - A terrible penalty?
So please try to be punctual.
(This terrifying punishment is...)
It is the tallest in Korea.
(The tallest bungee jump scared Haha and Jae Seok to death.)
(We will escort you to another one this morning.)
(If they fail, they will be sent straight to do bungee jumping.)
(As soon as their trip starts, the countdown will begin.)
(However, the members are not aware of this fact.)
Is that all?
Today,
as we told you previously, we are going to...
have a night tour.
A night tour?
Is this all?
The members always doubted and suspected me.
I wanted some tricks to get even. Aren't there any?
Of course, we have prepared a hidden rule.
A hidden rule?
(This element of surprise will catch them off guard.)
(What can this hidden rule be?)
Moreover, the members whose trips are selected...
will receive a special benefit.
The key point is to make sure the trip is to Kwang Soo's liking.
This is true.
- He has to approve of the trip. - So...
Kwang Soo has to like the trip.
You should have behaved like this long before.
We will select the first course.
If I choose one,
there will be added points.
Kwang Soo only likes specific things.
(A throne is brought out for him to sit.)
You probably already know. Thank you.
- You're desperate to become a king. - Thank you. Goodness.
I haven't seen this for a while.
This is my week, and there will be extra points.
- Kwang Soo has to like it. - We have to please you?
I had a lot of possible destinations in mind.
I decided on Kwang Soo's home at the end.
- I bet you will place last. - I didn't know about this.
- He didn't want to stay at home. - You're right.
- Did you really decide on my home? - No, I didn't.
I also thought of his house.
(To be honest, Kwang Soo has a bad memory regarding his house.)
(In May, 2015, they forcefully let themselves in.)
(Screaming)
(He had no choice but to reveal his privacy during the shoot.)
Why are you doing this to me?
Did everyone...
They were lazy.
Hey.
Why did you pick my house?
- Hey, your house... - Don't bring my house into this.
- By the way... - Don't come to my house anymore.
You don't know what Kwang Soo likes.
- You are clueless. - I can take away points.
Kwang Soo, aren't you feeling a bit hungry?
- I was feeling slightly hungry. - I knew it.
- Are you planning to... - Do you want some tteokbokki?
(It is the perfect late-night snack for Kwang Soo.)
(Kwang Soo, I will show you the paradise for snack bar food.)
- I do like snack bar food. - You do?
- Kwang Soo does like them. - It's too late...
- to eat that. - He almost won me over, too.
- I have a place in mind, too. - Where is it?
I went there a while ago and had so much fun.
- It's the fish market. - It's Noryangjin...
Hey, I'm supposed to tell him.
- He told me. We went together. - I should be telling him.
- Fish market. - There, we can see raw fish.
- We can pick fish and eat it. - Raw fish is great.
- This will be great. - I know Kwang Soo well.
It's amazing.
- You don't know him at all. - Why?
- He likes raw fish. - At this hour, raw fish isn't good.
- Kwang Soo. - No, it's the perfect time for it.
- I am not sure. - It's all protein.
It's great. He likes raw fish.
So far, we have snack bar and fish market.
Let's go for meat.
(Haha suggests meat.)
(Hold on. Did you just say meat?)
(Raw fish? Tteokbokki? Forget it.)
- I will buy you beef. - Beef?
- Did you say beef? - Hey.
I will buy you doenjang jjigae with beef brisket.
- We have three choices so far. - The time's perfect.
I heard this place is popular these days.
I heard rooftop bars are trending.
(Would you like to have a dance party at a trendy place?)
I heard G-Dragon often visits that bar.
- Don't say things like that. - Then let's not go there.
- You will ruin the mood at the bar. - G-Dragon...
- What are you talking about? - Let G-Dragon enjoy it.
- What are you implying? - You aren't good enough for it.
- That's right. - You can't go there.
Let's just go to the fish market.
It suits us. Let's go and have some delicious food.
- Let's go to the fish market. - Let's head to Dongdaemun.
- I know an incredible place. - Let's go shopping.
- Eat something nutritious. - Think about a fish this big.
Imagine having a raw fish sliced.
The chef with 30 years of experience is slicing the raw fish.
- How about snow crabs? - Snow crabs?
There are snow crabs, too?
- There are all kinds of seafood. - Of course.
Besides, you know what?
It takes a while to cook snow crabs.
- No, it takes 15 minutes. - They have it cooked already.
- It takes 15 minutes? - Yes, it does.
- It's edible undercooked. - Besides...
Tteokbokki is served right away.
- Tteokbokki sounds good. - I asked you that.
What is your decision?
(Let me think.)
(The 1st possible place is Seok Jin's fish market.)
(The 2nd possible place is Jae Seok's snack bar.)
(The 3rd possible place is Ji Hyo's rooftop bar.)
(The 4th possible place is Haha's meat restaurant.)
(It's a dilemma. What's his decision?)
It's Noryangjin fish market!
(Seok Jin's fish market has been selected.)
- Great. - That's it.
- This is good. - This isn't bad.
- This is... - That will be the first course.
- We are wasting time. - Right. Let's eat first.
- We have three more places. - Exactly.
(Remaining time)
(They must rush to Noryangjin.)
- We have to be back by 6am? - Let's go to nearby places.
- That's right. - You have booked the place, right?
I am going to book it.
You don't have to do anything. I will take care of everything.
If you don't want raw fish, we have other options.
I can also introduce you to the tasty world of seashells.
You won't regret this.
- It's chewy when it's cooked. - It sounds delicious.
Indeed, it is delicious.
(The seafood paradise is still bright at night.)
(Noryangjin's fish market is full of night air and fresh scent of sea.)
All right. I am introducing you to this fish market.
Kwang Soo, please come this way.
Hello.
(He tries to book a seafood restaurant.)
- Nice to meet you. - Hello. Nice to meet you.
- We must have steamed seashells. - Right. With steamed seashells...
I am in charge of this area today.
- Do you serve steamed seashells? - Of course.
Aren't they delicious around this time?
- How about steamed snow crabs? - We serve that, too.
(It will be a shame to only eat seashells and snow crabs.)
The scallops look so tasty.
- Steamed scallops are good, too. - That's fine.
You should choose since you are the host of this week.
Even though we are tight on time, we'll include...
snow crabs!
- All three of them. - Great!
- Let's go. - Let's go now.
- I can't wait. - Add the seashells.
I did. Thank you.
- Let's go. - Gosh.
Sir, try this.
- Imagine you are... - What did you say?
Imagine you are having this with seafood noodles, sir.
- Why are you flattering him? - Kwang Soo.
Try some.
- Why are you... - I should've done this for my week.
- He likes to be flattered. - Look at this.
- That's true. I do like it. - He likes to be treated well.
But still...
It's nice to be here though, right?
- We are eating altogether. - Until when do we have to wait?
- Please manage your time well. - All right.
- I don't know who will be next. - I should manage the time.
- You're right. - We have to eat fast.
During the shoot,
if you want to play games, let's go to an arcade.
It won't take long to get there.
- In Hongdae... - I have...
- We can go play table tennis. - Excuse me.
- Sir. - How about table tennis?
(He tries to convince Kwang Soo.)
- What are you doing here? - Hey, Jae Seok.
- Stop cheating. - Can we switch seats?
(Haha wants to switch seats.)
How can we convince you when he's next to you?
(This is why everyone wanted their week so badly.)
(Steamed seashells are served.)
All right. Here's the first mission.
- What? - What?
(Hold on. What mission?)
(The first mission is introduced out of the blue.)
- What's happening? - Is there only one plate?
- You will get one plate. - I see.
- Can we eat? - We can eat, right?
- Dip it in chojang, everyone. - Should I?
I don't have any.
Here it is.
Gosh. This is delicious.
- It's tasty. - It is, isn't it?
- Try other dishes, too. - This is good.
- I can put this here and... - How delicious.
- It's good. - Isn't it?
- Have this, sir. - Who made it possible to eat this?
- You should have this and... - Kwang Soo made it possible.
- It's all thanks to Kwang Soo. - I made this happen.
- Who thought of this idea? - But I...
came up with the idea of this week for you to have this idea.
Can we have more seashells?
- You have failed the first mission. - What?
(What on earth is this mission that we failed?)
- We will start the second mission. - What did you say?
(Starting the second mission, a plate of seashells is served.)
(There is another mission?)
- Does Kwang Soo have to eat first? - No. Eating together isn't it.
(It sounds about right.)
- Hold on. He has to eat that part? - That's right. Feed him.
(Let Kwang Soo eat first.)
- I guess we have to eat that part. - No. They can't predict that.
Wait. Perhaps, we have a time limit to finish eating.
- He's looking at his clock. Hurry. - Let's hurry.
- What did you say? - Is that it?
We ate this before.
(They come up with various guesses.)
- What is that? - We are done.
(They finish eating quickly.)
We are done eating.
We will start the third mission.
(They've failed the third mission. They are bewildered.)
If you can't accomplish the mission, you can't go to the next place.
- Those snow crabs... - What could the mission be?
This is an escaping game.
They are purposely trying to delay us.
But what is the mission?
Is this a hint?
(A hint is given.)
"Hashtag, Lee Kwang Soo".
(The hint is Lee Kwang Soo.)
(The mission has to be about me.)
Could it be his feeding us?
- Kwang Soo. - What if it's swallowing after him?
- Or maybe he needs to eat first. - Maybe he needs to feed himself.
Maybe he needs to feed us.
- Maybe he has to eat all of it. - Or he has to feed us all.
- First of all, we should... - Kwang Soo.
How can you be in the dark if you came up with this idea?
- Don't let them drag you around. - I didn't plan this part.
(This hidden mission which the host isn't even aware of is...)
(If Kwang Soo has the last bite, the mission is accomplished.)
- Don't be a pushover. - Is this your revenge?
Is this your revenge?
- No, I'm not. - Are you trying to stop us...
from clearing the mission?
- I thought about taking revenge. - He must be a spy.
I've done it so much, so I decided not to.
Jong Kook is starting to get upset.
That doesn't make sense.
I don't understand, so help us understand.
This is my Member's Week.
Do you want to be kicked out without clothes on?
- Can you do that? - Yes.
- You can do whatever you want. - Right.
Here's the mission for the third time.
Here's the king crab.
We get to eat because of Kwang Soo.
Thank him and enjoy it.
- Thank you. - Give everyone a leg each.
How many legs are there?
- There are 6. - I'll give 1 each.
- Thank you. - I'll give one each.
- Thank you. - Give everyone a leg. Thank you.
I think that's the mission.
(Despite being nervous, they enjoy the king crab.)
You're penalized if you can't remove the shell.
What if Kwang Soo has to feed us?
(Did they clear the mission?)
- Did we clear the mission? - We did.
- Did you finish? - Yes.
See? We cleared the mission.
Here's the next hint.
- Okay, that wasn't it. - Come on.
I told you that wasn't it.
Should I be the only one eating?
Here's an important hint.
- Is there another one? - We need the hint.
- "Yield". - "Yield".
(The second hint is yield.)
- We must yield to Kwang Soo. - He should yield to us.
- I yield to you? - You shouldn't eat.
- You shouldn't eat. - Only the rest of us eat.
Kwang Soo shouldn't eat.
I'll be furious if this is the mission.
- You can't eat, Kwang Soo. - Don't eat.
You shouldn't eat.
Everything we ordered is what I wanted to eat.
- That's right. - That's the mission.
- This is it. - Right.
I guess it is.
Everyone knows that Kwang Soo yields.
- He's impressive. - He's so generous and caring.
- He's amazing. - I agree.
- Right? - It's true.
We ordered what I wanted.
The mission is ordering the dishes you like.
- You share with others. - You share with other members.
- That's what yielding is. - He's so generous.
- What do you mean? - You're an angel without wings.
He's loving like a mother.
It's good to hear that.
He's like a mother who yields food to her children.
Did you finish the dish?
- Will rice be served after? - We finished.
- Did you finish the dish? - We finished.
- Did you finish the dish? - Did you finish?
You're very close to clearing the mission.
- See? - What did we do?
(What did he do?)
(Kwang Soo took the last piece of the crab.)
- Kwang Soo has to eat the last. - He has to eat the last piece.
We understand.
We'll give him the leftovers.
- We just give him the leftovers. - That's right.
Okay.
- It's fried rice with crab meat. - Goodness.
It looks delicious.
- Let's do it. - Okay.
Leave this much for Kwang Soo.
- It's his last bite. - He gets the last bite.
I really like that dish.
(Thanks to Kwang Soo, they enjoy a seafood course meal.)
It's delicious.
(Kwang Soo's week is the best.)
I really like that dish.
Leave some for Kwang Soo.
Are these the leftovers? Do I get to finish?
- Go ahead. - You should eat it.
The leftovers are for you. I must say it out loud.
Finish everything.
He's doing a good job of finishing it.
- It's delicious. - Take the last bite.
(He eats the last bite perfectly with some kimchi.)
(Time passed as they failed to clear the mission.)
(They still have three courses left.)
The mission is cleared.
(They barely clear the 1st hidden mission.)
- Shall we go? - We cleared the mission.
The first course...
was selected by Seok Jin.
As I mentioned, you get a benefit when your suggestion is chosen.
Only you can read it.
Don't share it with others.
(Kwang Soo prepared it.)
The benefit is very special, so please keep it with you.
(What is the special benefit Seok Jin received?)
- You can throw it away. - Can we read it?
- I can't throw it away. - What is it, Seok Jin?
I can't tell you.
- Show us. - I can't.
Show us if you can't tell us.
Do you think I'm a pushover?
(How dare you say that?)
- Really? - Goodness.
- Please sit. Don't attack him. - Stop it.
- What's wrong with you? - Calm down.
- What's the matter with you? - How can I calm down?
- I'm getting upset. - You're acting strange.
- I'm so upset. - What's wrong?
- His face is flushed. - How could you say that?
Now that we ate, let's go and exercise.
How about a baseball field?
- How about a baseball field? - We mentioned it before.
How about playing baseball on the screen?
- A shooting range. - Let's play table tennis.
- A shooting range in Hongdae. - How about an arcade?
We can eat again when we get hungry after playing games.
Kwang Soo, how about a shooting range in Hongdae?
- It's really fun. - A shooting range.
I'll decide.
We should do what Kwang Soo can play well.
- It should be what I like. - Shooting is really fun.
It's very popular because you can win big dolls.
- He won 100-dollar worth of dolls. - You can win dolls.
Hurry up.
(The clock is ticking.)
It's really fun.
(There are 4 candidates.)
- Choose my suggestion. - I choose the arcade.
(He takes Jae Seok's suggestion.)
- We should play... - This is awesome.
- the claw crane. - We should play that.
- Let's go. - We don't have time.
- Take my suggestion next time. - Let's go.
(Second course is the arcade.)
Listen, Kwang Soo.
We're making great memories.
- I know. - They'll be unforgettable.
- Thank you. - It's an early morning trip.
- Yes. - That's right.
We're doing something when everyone else is sleeping.
Everyone else is sleeping right now.
It's like a secret trip.
- That's right. - After everyone falls asleep
- I will love you - I will love you
- You're such an old generation. - Without anyone knowing
(They sing an old song by Kim Won Jun.)
- Gosh. - We all know the lyrics.
The song was released in early 90s.
It's 1:45am.
We'll leave the arcade by 2:30am.
- Then we'll have patbingsu. - That sounds delicious.
That will be perfect.
How about foot massage, Kwang Soo?
I like foot massages too.
- I like foot massages too. - I can give you one now.
How about a foot massage in warm water?
- Let's do that. - You're trying so hard, Haha.
Let's find an arcade in Hongdae.
Do you know a place?
- We can play claw crane here. - Here it is.
- Let's go there. - It's also deserted.
- Even on Sunday, it's crowded. - It's full of people.
- It's so busy here. - What's going on here?
- Is it a club? - They're waiting in line for a bar.
- It's too crowded here. - Right?
- Let's go to the last one. - Shall we?
- Let's do that. - It wasn't crowded there.
- How about here? - It looks great.
- Isn't this great? - This part of Hongdae is empty.
- Is it claw crane? - No one is working there.
- Let's go. - This is a great place.
- Okay. - This is good.
It's a great place.
It's nice and empty. There's no one here.
Here's the mission for the second course.
Kwang Soo, please step up.
- Only me? - Yes.
What is it?
Here's your secret mission.
If you disclose this mission,
your penalty will double.
- It must be a mission for us. - I think so.
You must clear it in secret.
(What's the mission for Kwang Soo?)
(Each member has to do something for Kwang Soo.)
Gosh, it's not easy at all.
(He must choose wisely to save time.)
Your success...
depends on Kwang Soo.
What is it?
- Kwang Soo. - Is it guessing the order?
It's either probability or order.
I think he decides the order in which we play claw crane.
(Please think before talking.)
- Is it the number of dolls? - We must clear...
- the mission quickly. - Kwang Soo.
- This is our second course. - Jae Seok is good at it.
I'm not bad either.
I love Pink Panther.
It's ugly.
(He finishes the list.)
- These aren't random. - Kwang Soo.
They're based on their habits and what happened today.
(Jae Seok has to win a doll for me.)
(Seok Jin has to kiss me on the cheek.)
(Jong Kook has to lend me a mask. Haha has to give me a foot massage.)
(Ji Hyo has to wipe off when I spill water.)
The mission starts now.
What should we do, Kwang Soo?
Just start because I can't tell you anything.
- Just start? - Yes.
- I can't tell you. - If you win the game, you pass.
I'm addicted to playing claw crane these days.
- Give me some money. - Right.
- What? - Give me some money.
- Give me some money. - Give us two dollars each.
- Were you keeping 50 dollars? - Give me some.
Give us two dollars each.
- Give me 10 dollars. - Give me some.
Just give us 10 dollars each.
- Why are you so greedy? - Goodness.
Please start playing.
- Can I start? - Yes.
- Act freely. - I'll start.
- Okay. - Jae Seok.
- I'll get the white one. - Here I go.
Let's go, Jae Seok.
- I'm good at this. - Please win a doll.
He's cheering for Jae Seok for a reason.
Jae Seok has to clear the mission.
(He cheers for Jae Seok who's good at playing claw crane.)
(Jae Seok has to win a doll for me.)
- Please get it. - He's close.
- He got it. - I should do that.
(Jae Seok is amazing at playing claw crane.)
I'm addicted to playing claw crane these days.
Let me get one for Kwang Soo. That's right. I got you.
(Will he clear the mission easily?)
You almost got it.
(Dropping)
No way.
You have more chances left.
That was the second attempt.
- I spent a lot of money. - There we go.
I caught one.
That's right.
(He drops it.)
It's driving me crazy.
(It's not as easy as he thought.)
(Kwang Soo watches Haha.)
Here I go.
- My goodness. - Haha.
- That's right. - Haha.
Let's continue our conversation we had in the car.
The next course is very important.
(Do you remember?)
(Haha has to give me a foot massage.)
(A conversation took place in the car.)
- I like foot massages too. - I can give you one now.
(Let's eat patbingsu as I recommended.)
(Remember your promise?)
- I'll be honest with you. - Okay.
- I have two things in mind. - That's right!
- Patbingsu or foot massage. - All right.
Let's go with patbingsu.
(Is it that simple?)
It's important where we go.
Let's go with patbingsu. It's right next door.
- But I really want a foot massage. - Great job.
- Don't go with foot massage. - All right.
- I don't need any hot water... - Foot massage...
I'll do it for you.
- That's it. - Really?
- That wasn't fair. - Do I have to do it now?
- I want to know how good you are. - This is driving me nuts.
I can do it but we have to focus on this game now.
(He doesn't understand.)
- I'll do it now. - Can you?
(Kwang Soo keeps on being bossy,)
(so Haha agrees.)
You volunteered to do it.
Great job.
(Punching)
(Haha tries to impress Kwang Soo.)
You get to play twice, dummy.
- I can always do it for you. - That's good.
- I know. - There you go.
(Kwang Soo completes his mission with Haha.)
I kept on using my coins.
(Who's next?)
That worked.
(He spots Ji Hyo.)
(Ji Hyo has to wipe off when I spill water.)
(She's a nice person.)
- So... - I got it.
(He starts spilling water on himself.)
(Spilling)
(She starts wiping water off.)
(He completes his mission with Ji Hyo right away.)
- No, Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
(She always takes care of him.)
Kwang Soo.
- I won something. - This is a hint.
- I won something. - You won this?
- Yes. - I didn't get one yet.
(Seok Jin has to kiss him on the cheek.)
- Did you win this? - I did.
(Seok Jin is proud.)
I did.
- Seok Jin. - I'm serious.
(Kwang Soo acts like he's touched.)
(Smacking)
(Seok Jin has to return the kiss.)
Thank you.
(He's satisfied.)
(Was that good, Kwang Soo?)
You can't lie.
- I'm so happy right now. - Really?
(Seok Jin is happy.)
- Okay. Should I go for a big one? - I got three.
(He completed his missions with Seok Jin, Haha, and Ji Hyo.)
(There are 3 hours and 45 minutes left for Jae Seok and Jong Kook.)
(Jae Seok keeps on missing.)
I almost had two.
(Let me go with Jong Kook first.)
(Coughing)
- All right. - I keep coughing.
I'm getting worried.
I think I'm catching a cold.
Kwang Soo is coughing. That's strange. What's going on?
(I told you I'm feeling sick.)
It's not working.
(Look at me.)
Do you have any more change?
(Are you going to keep ignoring me?)
(Jae Seok stares in his direction.)
Can you give me some change?
(Stop coughing and give me change.)
Get some change.
- He wants to take my money. - I'll get you some change.
(He tries to borrow Jong Kook's mask by saying he caught a cold.)
- I'll be back. - That's not it.
- Jong Kook. - Get me some change, Kwang Soo.
- I'll be back. - Sure.
Should I just go?
(I need something warm, Jong Kook.)
Go.
(Just go.)
(This won't work.)
(He plans to borrow the mask to disguise himself.)
Hurry up, Kwang Soo.
There are a lot of people. Would I be okay?
(He doesn't care.)
- I need a cap or a mask. - That's right.
(I need that thing...)
(on your chin.)
Hey.
(Take my cap.)
(You're kind only at times like this.)
Kwang Soo.
(They're so clueless.)
Okay.
(He heads to a convenience store to get change.)
Hello.
Do you have masks by any chance?
(He'll get it himself and make Jong Kook hand it over to him.)
I can give it to him...
and make him give it back, right?
Kwang Soo.
(Time is ticking and he still has two missions to complete.)
- Did you see how it dropped? - I don't have too much change.
(How do I hand this over to him?)
Here's your change.
- Why are you giving this to me? - I got it.
- Why? - I don't have too much change.
It worked.
- Am I not supposed to talk? - Sorry?
What does this mean?
(He doesn't understand what Kwang Soo is doing.)
If this doesn't work...
(Do you get what I want?)
It's 2. I won 2.
Stop doing this.
- Focus on me. - Pardon?
- It's my Member's Week. - So?
(Coughing)
You're coughing too hard.
(Does he get it now?)
(Is this my mission?)
You...
(You never disappoint me.)
(He completes Jong Kook's mission. There's only Jae Seok left.)
It's my first time winning something ever.
- Really? - It's my first time.
(They are impressed over their wins.)
I won two puppies.
Kwang Soo, wait for me. I'll win something for you.
How long do I have to wait? It's been over an hour.
- Look at me. I won 2. - Jae Seok.
- What's wrong with you today? - This one's good.
This one will work. That was so difficult.
That was so difficult.
That's right.
(You're more than just clueless.)
I'll win you something. Don't worry.
Kwang Soo. I won something again.
(Praise me, Kwang Soo.)
(Congratulations)
You're on a roll.
(Am I 1st place right now?)
- Kwang Soo. - I'm so happy.
(I'll give you a peck. You can take some rest.)
- Let's do this. - Thank you.
This will work.
(Jae Seok is unsuccessful again.)
Can you get me some change, Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo. - Did you win again?
- What's up with you? - I'm so good at this.
Why are you so good?
- You can stop. - This is insane.
(I won three this time.)
(Please stop.)
(He gives him a peck for the 4th time.)
Okay.
- Kwang Soo. - I must be really bad at this.
Kwang Soo.
- There you go. - Shut your mouth.
What's wrong? I won eight.
Do you know how much money I used on this?
You're the only one who didn't win anything.
Exactly. I'm trying to win it for you.
Try a different machine.
I'm so close with this one.
This is how you go broke.
- Stop losing it. - Hey.
Don't you like Pink Panther?
- I do... - Hold on then.
- We have 3 hours and 30 minutes. - Fine.
We have two more places to go.
I won, Kwang Soo.
Come to your senses. Please come to your senses.
Don't you know what the penalty is?
(Something is waiting for us in Inje.)
- You can catch that one. - Get the blue one.
Let's do it.
(He's focused.)
- Yu Jae Seok. - Yu Jae Seok.
This one's for certain.
You got it.
(Would he succeed this time?)
(Please)
- You got it. - You got it.
- You got it. - Yes.
(He succeeds.)
(He finally did it.)
(He didn't know it was going to take this long.)
Aren't you happy?
(They're this happy over a stuffed animal.)
- Let's move on. - Is that good?
- Jae Seok. - You completed the mission.
(That concludes the missions at the arcade.)
(There are three and a half hours left.)
Jae Seok, your suggestion was chosen as the second place,
so you win a hint. It's just for you.
- Look at it by yourself. - It's just for you.
(What's this?)
Do we choose the next place?
- The third place... - Let's go for tteokbokki.
(Let's go for tteokbokki.)
- Okay. - Tteokbokki?
- Tteokbokki is first on the list. - Let's go for tteokbokki.
- Very tasty waffles... - No.
- and patbingsu. - Waffles and patbingsu?
And ice cream.
- What about udon? - Udon.
(That sounds good.)
- I'm craving for udon. - What was that?
- Let's get udon at a food stall. - Why udon all of a sudden?
I choose udon.
(Ji Hyo is the host for the next round.)
I swear I was going to call tteokbokki.
- Jong Kook, I was going to do it. - I'm sorry.
- Did you see Ji Hyo's face? - It's because of the rain.
- I was going to say tteokbokki too. - She surprised me.
Do you have a place in mind, Ji Hyo?
Do you know a good place?
Yes, I do. Turn right at the next traffic light.
All the food stalls there are gone.
- Really? - Yes.
They're all gone.
(That's an unexpected situation.)
You're talking about the one across from the hospital, right?
- They're all gone. - Kwang Soo,
if we went for tteokbokki, it would have been next door.
That's not good.
- There it is. It's next to the cab. - Is it?
- Where? - There it is.
(She finds a food stall.)
- It's there. - It is.
- There it is. - They have udon.
(This is what they had in mind.)
- They would have it for certain. - There it is.
I hope they have udon.
Please.
- Hello, ma'am. - Hello. Do you have udon?
We don't.
You don't?
- What about just noodles? - We don't.
What now?
(They don't have udon. What now?)
- They don't have udon. - Let's go for any udon.
Hold on.
You said udon at a food stall.
We can go to a different food stall.
You don't have to be so inflexible.
(We're not doing this because we're afraid of the penalty.)
This happens. It could be difficult to find things at late night,
so we prepared to give you a chance.
- I see. - We were mistaken. We're sorry.
- We really like udon. - You're a nice person.
Many places are closed on Sunday nights.
- That's right. - So we're giving you a chance.
Choose 1 of the 2 cards.
- Do I pick one? - Kwang Soo does?
It's a special chance.
(There are two cards.)
Choose the one at the bottom.
There's a reason it's at the bottom.
(They have to be very careful about it.)
This is up to what's written inside, not my will.
(There are many restrictions due to the time.)
(This card is supposed to help them at situations like this.)
(What did Kwang Soo pick?)
Friend Card.
- Friend Card? - If there's anyone still up,
you can ask that person for an udon place.
(They have to go to an udon place Kwang Soo's friend recommends.)
(At this hour?)
The thing is,
we're awake because we're on a trip.
- But it's 3am now. - Everyone's asleep.
It's Sunday, too.
- Exactly. - It'd be rude of me to call.
Aren't we Kwang Soo's friends?
We're his friends.
I'm your friend.
Seok Jin is your friend.
He is.
Are you my friend?
Yes, I am.
Mapo Station is right around the corner.
Can we exchange cards?
I'll give you this.
It's what I got.
Do you want to...
- switch to another card? - Yes.
It must be a difficult one.
(What's the other card?)
- Night Bus Card? - What's that?
(Are we taking a bus at this hour?)
Have you heard of night buses?
- Yes. - No.
(There are buses that run only late at night.)
- Take any night bus. - And then?
Throw a dice. The number you get will be the number of stops...
you have to move. You'll have to find an udon place there.
We'll take the Friend Card.
- Give it back. - You can't do that.
Give it back to us.
That's what we picked.
Take this and give us the card.
Take this.
We picked the Friend Card.
Wake someone up.
Whom should I call?
We have to go somewhere near here. We don't have much time.
All stores are closed, and everyone's asleep.
- Send a text first. - Wait.
Bo Young seems to be awake.
- Who? - Park Bo Young.
(Are you talking about the one and only Park Bo Young?)
(Is this cute woman awake at this hour?)
- Try calling. - All right.
- Let's call her. - Does she have your number?
- Text her. - Tell her to say Hapjeong-dong.
Say that Mapo has the best udon.
And then call her.
If she says Gangnam, we'll have to go there.
- Text, "Mapo has the best udon." - Do that.
- I'll call her. - Call her.
Put it on speaker.
(Bo Young, please pick up if you can hear me.)
- Hello? - Bo Young.
(Bo Young picked up.)
Where are you?
I'm in Paju.
Are you shooting?
- In this cold? - It's late.
- Hi, Bo Young. - It must be cold.
- Hi. - I miss you.
- Hi. - We're shooting, too.
We're shooting Running Man.
- Did you read my message? - No.
- Read it. - Read it.
I'm sure you don't want to read Kwang Soo's message.
Why didn't you read it before taking the call?
- Just ask her. - Bo Young.
Bo Young. Udon...
(Bo Young, about that udon...)
(Their night depends on Bo Young's answer.)
(Will they have to cross the Han River or not?)
(What does udon mean to her?)
The best udon is in Mapo.
(You know your udon well.)
Exactly.
- My question wasn't finished. - Bo Young.
- Thank you so much. - The best udon is...
- in Mapo. - In Mapo.
It must be very cold there.
It must be cold there, too.
Still, where's the best udon?
In Mapo.
(The best udon is in Mapo.)
Thank you.
- Thank you, Bo Young. - Bye.
- Goodbye. - Let's hurry.
We should send a picture of us having udon to Bo Young.
Let's get it done and go home.
Are we going to Mapo?
(They set off to try udon in Mapo.)
It's possible. We can do it.
Don't worry. I'll make it.
There's not much time left.
I'm worried.
It must be this way.
Look to the left.
- Does it have to be a cart bar? - Wait.
I found it.
Go straight.
Do you remember something?
Right there.
- It's there! - Right there!
(Did they find an udon place?)
- It's open! - It is!
We found it.
(They find an udon place.)
(They arrive at an udon place in Mapo.)
Let me show you.
Cameramen,
please take a close-up shot of the word "udon".
Right there.
(We need to take this.)
- Good luck. - Good luck.
Hello.
(Ji Hyo asks them for help.)
We're shooting Running Man.
We have a mission to have udon.
Please.
I really want to have it.
- We have to have it. - I'm going crazy.
If the owner doesn't allow us, let's shoot outside.
- We have to have it. - We'll have takeout.
We could eat outside. Did it work?
Well...
The owner is not here.
As long as we don't shoot the employees, we can shoot here.
Thank you. It's done.
Thank you.
Thank you. We're sorry.
- Thank you. - We're sorry to bother you.
- We're sorry. - We're sorry.
We'll keep quiet.
This place has a nice feeling.
(They enter the restaurant.)
They close at 4am. We could have missed it.
- They close at 4am. - We could have been late.
The mission at this restaurant...
- is extremely simple. - What is it?
Turn this roulette.
The chosen ones will have udon, and that's it.
- Really? - Will it be only one person?
You'll see soon.
What?
(How does the roulette look?)
It's Kwang Soo versus the other five.
- It's either Kwang Soo or us. - It's either him or us.
(Kwang Soo or the other five? That is the question.)
This is crazy.
I mean...
Kwang Soo.
Wait. Why are you doing this? It's my week.
Shouldn't there be all of our names?
- Let's just do it. - Let's do it.
They need to take customers.
- Let's do it. - They need to take customers.
I'll do it...
- Ready. - really seriously.
- We have to eat it. - Turn it hard.
(This whole tour must have started for this udon.)
(They're all desperate.)
Turn it hard.
(It's turned.)
(Their fate changes every 0.1 second.)
(Please let me eat udon.)
(It's a cruel game.)
(Who will have a warm bowl of udon?)
Yes!
(It is Kwang Soo.)
- Do it again. - You didn't say, "Start."
- You didn't turn it properly. - It was a bit...
Turn it hard.
(What is going on?)
(Everyone is his enemy.)
- You should say, "Start." - Turn it this hard.
- Turn it hard. - Okay.
Say, "Start."
Start.
- I said it, okay? - All right.
I think I'm going to cry.
Do it.
Turn it hard.
(It's real this time.)
(Kwang Soo turns it hard.)
(No mistake is allowed.)
(The fierce udon game is on.)
(Chewy noodles in warm soup)
(Who will get to taste it?)
Yes!
(The other 5 are chosen.)
(What a twist of fate!)
(I'm going to cry.)
All right. Give us udon.
4 fish cake udon and 1 udon with rice.
(We respect Kwang Soo's opinion.)
Kwang Soo, I knew it.
(Teary-eyed)
Let's change places.
(He is hurt.)
Kwang Soo, where are you going?
(Are you upset?)
I'm...
- going home. - Home?
Try some of ours.
- I don't eat much these days. - We'll share it with you.
I mean...
We'll share it.
- That's right. - We'll do that.
- If all of us give you a little... - Right.
Is that allowed?
Kwang Soo, can you go outside for a moment?
- Why? - I'll announce a rule.
Is he not allowed to see us eat?
Is there something?
Are they having a meeting?
- Did something go wrong? - There must be something.
We're probably supposed to do something.
No. I'll give you a rule.
- I'll give you a rule. - What is it?
Here's the mission at this restaurant.
When the udon is served,
you'll offer some to Kwang Soo. If he refuses...
(They'll be given extra 30 minutes.)
(And Kwang Soo will get a bowl of udon.)
What should we do?
I feel sorry for him.
(Kwang Soo has no idea.)
This restaurant is completely soundproof.
I mean...
This building is very well-built.
I've never seen such a soundproof udon place.
(Now that I think of it...)
Why am I left out? This is my week.
What's that?
- It looks so tasty. - It's here.
- Look at that. - I can smell the green onions.
It looks so tasty.
(It looks so appetizing.)
It looks amazing.
It costs only 4 dollars and 50 cents.
(Even the price is perfect.)
(Slurping)
This udon tastes like the one I had in high school.
(You've never tasted anything like this.)
It tastes amazing, right?
(Kwang Soo returns.)
I love anchovy stock.
Let me remind you. Kwang Soo can't have any of it.
Why not?
According to the roulette, you're not allowed to eat.
That's the rule.
(Slurping)
(The sound is torturing Kwang Soo.)
I'm going crazy.
It tastes so good.
- I want to give up everything. - It's been 10 years for Seok Jin.
We used to have this after chatting until late at night.
(It tastes just like 10 years ago.)
- Kwang Soo, do you want a bite? - Have a bite.
(This is the 1st time they've asked.)
Have a bite.
(He looks at the staff.)
Try it.
Do you want it or not?
(It's a temptation.)
(The noodles are irresistible.)
This is perfect for when you're hungry.
(Is that so?)
- The fish cakes are delicious. - They're chewy, too.
(The slurping sounds make Kwang Soo's mouth water.)
It's especially delicious today.
Do you want some or not?
I'm glad I didn't eat the noodles.
(What will Kwang Soo do?)
(He successfully overcomes the 1st temptation.)
(They're impressed by his determination.)
(How about this, Kwang Soo?)
- I'm glad I didn't eat the noodles. - Me, too.
(Jjajangmyeon looks too good.)
What's this?
(Jae Seok acts cautiously.)
- How about some jjajangmyeon? - Try some of this.
Can I have some jjajangmyeon?
Of course not.
It's against the result of the roulette.
Why should I listen to you?
(Kwang Soo doesn't care about his future.)
(Kwang Soo will give in soon.)
(He stares at the udon.)
Do you want some?
(Haha offers some.)
(This is the 2nd temptation.)
- Can I eat it? - Why not?
What's wrong with that?
The fish cakes are delicious.
They aren't high-quality,
and it's made with a lot of flour.
It's more delicious.
Try some. Hurry up so I can eat.
It's made with a lot of flour.
(He slowly approaches.)
(He takes the bait.)
That's right.
(He hesitates.)
(He's indecisive.)
(Jae Seok is surprised.)
Have some, Kwang Soo.
(It's okay, Kwang Soo.)
- Here, have some. - I'll eat some.
(He's close to taking a bite.)
(Will Kwang Soo overcome the 2nd temptation?)
(Will he lose after a bite, or will he resist and win?)
(What will Kwang Soo choose?)
(He stops suddenly.)
Don't eat it.
(He overcomes the 2nd temptation.)
(We're proud of you.)
- It's good. - The fish cakes are delicious.
I was surprised by the wasabi.
Forget it.
(He gives in.)
(He can't resist any longer.)
Forget it.
(Kwang Soo fails.)
You shouldn't have eaten it.
- Why did you eat it? - Why?
(He lost the chance to win 30 minutes and a bowl of udon.)
(Kwang Soo is taken away.)
You shouldn't have eaten it.
- Why did you eat it? - Why?
Wait a minute.
My goodness, Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is taken away for eating udon.)
Let me go. Let go!
(This is so unfair.)
It's so delicious.
It's very delicious.
(He hasn't even swallowed the noodles.)
If he didn't take the bite, he would've gotten the udon.
I thought he would make it.
I know.
When Kwang Soo took a bite, dark shadows appeared.
(He's angry and hungry.)
(At times like this...)
(He gets out of the car.)
(He can't resist anymore.)
(Kwang Soo escapes and goes back to the restaurant.)
- Kwang Soo. - I want to eat.
(He wants to eat it all.)
- What's going on? - Eat this one.
- Eat this one, Kwang Soo. - What?
What's going on?
(That's all Kwang Soo gets.)
What?
(He flaps to get away.)
(Let me go.)
Let me go!
Hey, let me go.
(He's the Korean Jean Valjean.)
Let me go now.
Let go of me.
(He has the right to eat.)
(He feels ashamed for what he's done.)
One bite of it can make you crazy.
- I completely understand. - It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
It was really good.
My goodness.
(Udon on a rainy day is perfect.)
Udon is perfect for this weather. I'm about to lose it.
(What can he do to win a bowl of udon?)
(At times like this,)
(he needs his ultimate weapon.)
Excuse me.
(He attempts to bribe.)
This is my favorite doll.
It's my favorite.
Please, I'll be right back.
I'll be back soon.
(Everyone deserves a nice doll.)
It was difficult to win this.
Sorry?
(Go back in.)
What?
Wait...
(There's no negotiation.)
(How dare he try to bribe them?)
Wait, hear me out.
Give me back my doll.
Hello?
(He worked hard to win the doll.)
Hold on.
How... How could you do this?
I gave him my doll.
He took my doll without letting me go.
(That's what Kwang Soo deserves for trying to bribe.)
(Even the security men can't be trusted.)
What can I do?
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - It was amazing.
(Everyone else is full and happy.)
- Here comes Kwang Soo. - Come here, Kwang Soo.
If you didn't take the bite, you would've won a bowl of udon.
Did you know about that?
- Of course. - Everyone knew.
You did that when you knew?
- We tried to help you. - We were being intentional.
You're going to hit me, right?
You're such a know-it-all.
You can see the future.
We knew but pretended not to know.
(We forgot it was your week.)
- We knew about it. - We have one last course.
- Yes. - We have one last course.
- Let's discuss. - Tell me your thoughts.
Iced coffee, sandwiches,
- cake, and tiramisu sound good. - That's a good idea.
All right. What else?
- You couldn't eat udon. - Right.
Let's go eat tteokbokki.
Let's go get some tteokbokki and fish cakes.
We ate, but you have not.
- You should go and eat. - I feel his love.
You deserve to eat, too.
I'm too full, so I'm going home.
(He doesn't care about Kwang Soo.)
Do I have money for taxi?
We can have ice cream after he eats tteokbokki.
He wasted all his money on the claw crane.
- How will you go home? - I don't have enough.
How will you go home?
- He can't go home. - Just get off at Sinsa Station.
You need to wait at a PC room until the first train arrives.
- I don't know what to do. - It's not enough for a PC room.
Make your choice, Kwang Soo.
- Can I do whatever I want? - Of course.
(Will it be cake?)
(Will it be spicy tteokbokki?)
I choose tteokbokki.
(He chooses Jong Kook's tteokbokki.)
That's right. You should eat.
- You must be hungry. - I shouldn't stay hungry.
- Why should I? - Of course not.
- Okay, let's go. - He wants to eat.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- We can walk there. - Let's go.
(They head to a tteokbokki restaurant.)
(The last course is a snack bar.)
I don't remember. I should ask.
Thankfully, no one is here.
- Is it closed? - I hope it's open.
I think it's closed.
- It says naengmyeon... - Tteokbokki is on the menu.
- It's on the menu. - It is.
Tteokbokki is on the menu.
- This is great. - Is it open?
- Excuse me. - They have everything here.
- We're shooting a TV show. - We'll stay in one corner.
Thank you.
- Come in. They sell everything. - Thank you.
- Everything's on the menu. - There's even sundae.
- There's everything. - This is the original restaurant.
Right.
Let's order tteokbokki and sundae.
- The roulette's here again. - I'm scared.
Here's the mission.
You'll turn the roulette again.
- Come on. - Turn the roulette.
- Please. - Let him eat.
The roulette chooses who will eat.
- You must eat this time. - For Kwang Soo,
we increased the probability twofold.
- Let him eat. - We definitely should.
- You should eat. - You will eat.
- You can do it. - You should eat.
- Turn the roulette. - I don't believe this.
- Go on. - Turn the roulette.
- Turn it hard. - Do it in one go.
He'll get to eat.
He'll get to eat. He can't be that unlucky.
- Go ahead. - Don't feel pressured.
- He got it. - Okay!
(Kwang Soo is picked.)
- Okay! - That's great.
It's a happy ending.
It is.
- This is what I wanted. - Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
- Kwang Soo, you can start eating. - It's a lot of food.
- Try it. It's delicious. - This restaurant is the original.
The mandu...
- is very good here. - Try it.
They are delicious.
They're very delicious.
Here comes the tteokbokki.
(Here's the best snack food.)
Here you go.
- Dip sundae in it. - It's gukmul tteokbokki.
- Gosh. - I can finish the whole bowl.
- Of course. - That's easy.
I'm sure he can eat them all.
- Kwang Soo. - I'm full,
- but it still looks good. - I want a bite.
- Don't you want a bite or two? - I want to try the mandu.
This is amazing.
- Dip this in the tteokbokki sauce. - Are they wheat cakes?
I was thinking about the same thing.
I was thinking about dipping mandu in the sauce.
- Try it. - These days,
there are many one-man shows.
This is what it reminds me of.
That's what I wanted them to try.
Dip the sundae in the sauce.
Dip the sundae in the sauce...
- but put it on your spoon. - That sounds good.
That's right.
- No, pick up the sundae first. - Put it on your spoon first.
- Sundae first. - Put it on your spoon first...
and then dip it.
If you look here, there's carrot filling.
That's unnecessary information. Don't talk about that.
People don't like it when you talk too much.
- That's it. - Submerge it. Oh my.
That looks so good.
It must be good.
Let me try some.
- People don't say that these days. - Do they not?
- They don't. - Just smell it.
Talk about how it tastes.
(- Ji Hyo looks beautiful. - She looks hungry as well.)
- It must be good. - Is it good?
- It's good, right? - Try more sauce.
- Right away. - One more time.
Slurp it.
(- That sounds amazing. - The sauce is a must.)
Listen to that sound.
- How was it? - It has to be good.
- It's insane. - Really?
- It must be really good. - I can't stop eating.
Is it that good?
- I want some. - Udon was good, but this is great.
(1 hour and 59 minutes remain.)
- Are you enjoying your meal? - Yes.
Can Kwang Soo stay and the rest of you come out?
Don't make me lonely.
- Are you assigning them missions? - Yes, I am.
(The 5 members go outside to hear their missions.)
- Is it good? - I wonder what it is.
Everything's so good today.
- Here's the rule. - What is it?
Kwang Soo is eating inside, right?
- You have an option. - What is it?
You can all leave now...
and finish early.
Or you can wait for Kwang Soo to finish eating...
and complete another mission before going home.
That's harsh.
If we wait for him, we have to complete another mission?
- What time is it? - We don't know when it'll finish.
If we leave now...
Are you sure this is Kwang Soo's Week?
What are we supposed to do?
(That sounds really tempting.)
(Will they stay together or leave Kwang Soo alone?)
It's 4am right now.
I'm sleepy.
- There's no traffic right now. - You're right. We can leave.
- Look at his eyes. - It'll only take 30 minutes.
(Jong Kook is trying to avoid rush hour.)
Look at his face.
- He made up his mind. - Come on.
- We'll see him again next week. - You made up your mind.
(He's anxious for some reason.)
I think we should go home because of Jong Kook.
That's important. We are one.
He lives far.
- I live far. - He lives in Anyang.
- You're falling asleep, too. - I am.
- But she lives close-by. - And Kwang Soo...
must be getting full now, so we should decide quickly.
- I agree. - Sure.
What do you think?
Everybody agrees.
(Do I have to say it?)
(They all agree.)
- That was funny. - All right.
- I agree. - Your face was funny.
You can look through the window...
- and say bye. - I feel bad for him.
This is what we should do.
Haha, can you move a few steps forward?
(They're not plotting anything, right?)
Crawl. Go lower.
(Let's go home now.)
(They run away before Kwang Soo notices.)
Go.
Kwang Soo is still eating.
(Enjoy the night eating alone, Kwang Soo.)
- That's not the right car. - It's at the front.
(He glances around.)
Can you get Jae Seok's autograph?
(They're running away outside.)
- What about me? - I'm not sure.
(You should care about me, too.)
Your granddaughter might like me, too.
I'm not sure. I don't know your name.
I'm on this show as well.
(I should work harder.)
(The other members are running away while Kwang Soo is distracted.)
(They must leave quickly.)
What if he tries to get revenge?
Here it is.
(They steal the one and only car.)
Let's go.
(If they return before the end of the race, they get to go home.)
Your Member's Week is supposed to be bad for you.
(He is this week's victim.)
Are you holding me hostage?
- I feel sorry for Kwang Soo. - Same here.
This is actually for him.
It's his week.
(The 5 escapees head back.)
I feel sorry for him.
(He starts getting lonely.)
Why aren't they coming back?
(He finishes his food while the others run away.)
Did I clear the mission? I'm done.
- Did you finish? - Yes.
The others have left for the final place already.
(This is supposed to be my week.)
Isn't this my week?
They left me here?
This is how your week is supposed to be.
(The host always goes through some hardship.)
- I was a victim once, too. - Me, too.
You know what happened to me, right?
(He gets furious.)
They took the car,
so you can take a taxi.
(Am I supposed to take a taxi alone at this hour?)
(1 hour and 47 minutes remain.)
We'll make it on time.
You would've been on the Gangbyeon Expressway.
(If they're caught, they can't leave early.)
- Turn back and go straight. - Should he take a U-turn?
They were saying how it's Monday, and the traffic will be crazy.
Is that why they left?
My gosh.
(Did they leave me because of the traffic?)
This isn't nice.
(I can't let you go home early.)
I'm in a hurry, so can you please go a little bit faster?
(Will the others manage to go home early?)
What if we get punished for betraying him?
I thought about it.
What if this is a test?
- That's what I'm saying. - What if it backfires?
(They start getting suspicious.)
I think that might be it.
- I doubt it. - I was wondering about it.
(Is this a part of Kwang Soo's plan?)
(During the pre-meeting)
(He wanted to test the members' loyalty.)
What if this is a test?
(Is this Kwang Soo's plan?)
(They get back with 1 hour and 45 minutes left.)
- The lights are on. - We have to go the other way.
- Let's finish it up and go. - The lights are on.
Really?
Is there a penalty?
- I doubt it. - I don't think there is.
Just in case.
- This might be a trap. - Let's not think that way.
- Kwang Soo's plan? - His scheme?
Is this part of his plan to test our friendship?
He probably thought we'd betray him.
Let's not think negatively.
(A mysterious truck appears in front of them.)
What's this? What's that?
- What's that? - Why is there a sprinkler truck?
(This doesn't look good.)
What's that? It's from Running Man.
- It's a sprinkler truck. - Let's get off first.
(Will they go home early or fall into Kwang Soo's trap?)
- Hold on. - We can't take it back.
- What is it? - Let's get out.
(Thank to their betraying Kwang Soo, they return on time.)
There's a polling station.
I didn't feel so good about this.
(There's a polling station.)
(You thought it was over, right?)
We didn't have to do this,
but it's for the excitement of the show.
We did it for the show.
- That's right. - Please take it that way.
Here's the final mission for Night Tour Course.
(Final mission?)
We started Member's Week with an ice shower,
so we'll end with...
an ice shower for a fresh start.
There's only one member...
who will get the shower.
(Only one of them will be penalized.)
Through a voting process, the person who gets the most votes...
will take the shower today.
Each member gets to vote once.
If your course was chosen today,
you receive an extra vote.
We'll start...
voting now.
How could you...
It's so cold today.
Please hand out the ballots.
(They must choose a person to punish.)
How are we supposed to do this?
Look at his face.
Is this why we came back early?
Where's Kwang Soo?
I'm in a hurry, so can you please go a little bit faster?
7012?
(7012, my foot.)
(Enraged, he almost arrives.)
- This makes us uncomfortable. - Why would you do this?
Why would we do this?
You said it'd be over once we get here.
(Who will they vote?)
- Please vote. - You know whom this is for.
(Kwang Soo is the host.)
You're so cruel.
You know whose week this is.
(They're in this together.)
Which one of us didn't get the ice shower?
- Did you get it? - I did.
- Did you? - It started off with me.
- You didn't get it. - Did you?
You didn't get it either.
- I did. - When did you?
- It wasn't aired. - What are you talking about?
- Haha and I dived into ice water. - We all did it.
It almost killed me.
- We all did it except Kwang Soo. - It almost killed me.
- He didn't do it. - He didn't?
- That's right. - My gosh.
We're not trying to make things up. It's just strange.
(They all settle on Kwang Soo.)
Let's get this over with, everybody.
Sure.
- I don't even know. - We can't do anything else.
(They try to finish before they feel more guilty.)
- There's a reason. - We can't do much else.
Let's just do it.
(It's supposed to be Kwang Soo's Week anyways.)
Thank you.
(He arrives late.)
(Stop it, you punks.)
Kwang Soo is here.
He's here.
(He's in tatters.)
Hey.
- You can't do this to me. - Kwang Soo.
(We're just helping you stand out.)
- Come here. - I'm sorry.
Isn't this too harsh?
- You're mistaken. - We did it for you.
(Here comes our main host.)
You have to understand. We were trying to make it funny.
We couldn't do anything else. Look at the big picture.
- You would have done the same. - Look at the big picture.
- Are you serious? - Tell me this.
If you were in our shoes, wouldn't you've done the same?
(Be honest with us.)
- I would have left too, but... - Exactly.
Kwang Soo, here's the rule for the final mission.
You get to vote...
who gets the ice shower.
(That person will play the tragic, lead character.)
That person will get the ice shower.
(He panics.)
Why are you avoiding me?
Why aren't you looking at me?
All right. They have already voted.
You are the last one to vote.
They finished voting?
Behind you...
- They are done voting? - Yes, they are.
- Hey. - This is my week though.
- I guess this is the fate of hosts. - Hurry up.
- I mean... - Vote first.
- You should vote. - Go and vote.
- We all have the right to vote. - It's all the same.
- The conditions are all the same. - Go and exercise your right.
This is a strange omen.
I'm sorry, but can I go first?
(The king of variety shows is too cruel.)
- I feel really bad. - We mustn't watch it happen.
- I feel so bad. - I feel so horrible.
- There's no need for us to watch. - I can't look at him.
- Isn't it better if we just go? - I can't face him.
If he faces the punishment by himself...
- He has to face it alone. - We feel really bad.
- We feel sorry. - Aren't you being too harsh?
- It's because we are sorry. - Let's announce.
You can announce the result from far away.
- Why would you do it here? - Just let us know the result.
- Post it on the social media. - Call us to inform the result.
- We can all be in the car. - How about this?
We can get on our own car and head out.
- Whoever it is can come back. - That's right.
- We will begin counting the votes. - Don't call it out one by one.
- We will start. - Hey, by the way...
- We can see it from here. - "Lee Kwang Soo".
Kwang Soo gets one vote.
You won't tell me who voted for me?
Kwang Soo has two votes so far.
(He's in a daze.)
Kwang Soo has three votes so far.
Three votes? Did you say three?
This is the fourth vote for Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is bound to be the star.)
"Lee Kwang Soo". "Lee Kwang Soo".
Are you serious?
- Everyone voted for me? - It was an unanimous decision.
Every single one voted for me?
The ballot has been closed.
I'm not lying. I have goosebumps.
(Their friendship gives him goosebumps.)
- I'm serious. - By the way...
- We have our reasons. - I really did get the goosebumps.
- Look. I have them right here. - You haven't had that shower.
- You are the last one. - You're the only one left.
Excluding Kwang Soo, everyone voted for Kwang Soo.
Does he really have face that shower?
Kwang Soo...
accomplished his hidden mission.
(He accomplished a hidden mission?)
- What's happening? - I knew it.
Was there another mission?
(Laughing)
This Member's Week is so much fun.
Hidden mission?
(1 hour before the shoot)
(He had a secret rendezvous with a producer.)
(Kwang Soo is always suspected.)
(This is why the staff prepared a revenge race after 7 years.)
(A hidden rule was a bonus.)
(I do like hidden rules.)
A hidden rule?
If you are voted...
to receive the punishment...
I am 99 percent positive it will be me.
The members who voted for you will receive the punishment.
(It's a boomerang effect.)
- Only the members who voted for me? - That's correct.
What if all five of them vote for me?
All five of them will face the ice shower.
(Everyone will have the ice shower?)
What if I am not chosen?
If that happens,
you will face the shower by yourself since you doubted their loyalty.
It doesn't sound right, but this is a fact.
There hasn't been a single incident that they didn't betray me.
I am not sure if I should be happy or sad. I don't know.
I wasn't going to write his name.
- What's going to happen? - However,
- there is alway a hope. - You're right.
Since Kwang Soo is generous...
No, I am not.
(I don't know what generosity is.)
What should I be?
- Let me try it again. - Everyone here voted for me.
- They were ready to leave me. - Kwang Soo.
You will...
pick only one member to face the punishment with your own hands.
- That's too mean. - I have to?
We thought it might be too hard for you to choose one.
We have prepared a dart board.
- We will write the names and spin. - This is unbelievable.
The board is split into 12 parts.
Kwang Soo can write names however he wants.
Since I feel bad, I will write my own name in one blank spot.
- Are you serious? - Really?
- Hey. - I will write it once. Can I?
- You can. - In one blank spot?
- Even if you might get it? - Really?
- I can do that? - Yes, you can.
How can you agree so easily in times like this? Are you certain?
Since you are the host, you can do whatever you want.
- You can write anyone. - Write the staff members' names.
- Both of our names will be on it. - He had udon by himself before.
- I am fine with that. - That's right. Write his name too.
Why don't you write everyone's name at least once? It's confusing.
First, let's write everyone's name at least once.
Hold on.
- You put my names in one area. - That's true.
(That part has become my area.)
Your handwriting is so neat.
- You write so well. - How about writing Seok Jin again?
You wrote Haha's name only once.
- That's right. - Haha.
You were a bit annoying today.
- He lives so close from here. - Before...
Who fed you the noodles?
(Right. It was you.)
- I ate the noodles on my own. - It was him.
- You can write his name once more. - I did it for the mission.
- Why don't you write down his name? - You should write it again.
- It was to complete the mission. - Write his name again.
I only ate so that we could complete the mission.
(He smacks the back of Kwang Soo's head.)
Help him erase the names.
- Give me a new one. - All right. I am sorry.
I got it. I'm sorry.
- You should write his name. - I think you should.
- There's no need to think about. - Great.
- Are you done writing? - Yes, I am.
- I have one more than others. - You have the most.
- Ji Hyo has one less than us. - Right.
- Haha does have one more. - Right.
- Ready. - You only get to spin it once.
- He gets to spin it once. - Yes, only once.
- You can't complain afterwards. - Okay.
- Please. - Goodness.
- My names are clustered together. - Why is my name on three spaces?
(Only one member will face the ice shower.)
(The roulette is spinning.)
(As long as it's not me, it's fine.)
(Please don't let it be my name.)
(The roulette slows down between Jae Seok and Jong Kook's names.)
- My name is written twice. - So is mine.
It's the same with my name.
(Who will be the one to face the ice shower?)
(If it continues, it might be either Jae Seok or Jong Kook.)
(Moving back and forth)
(Yu Jae Seok is chosen.)
(It's Jae Seok.)
(Sighing)
(Yes! We can go home dry.)
I thought it would be me. I really thought so.
- I thought I was going to get it. - It's Jae Seok.
(They are so annoying.)
(For what did I rush today?)
- He got it. - Look at him.
(I don't have a change of clothes or my manager with me.)
- I thought I was going to die. - How can this be?
- This is unbelievable. - How can this happen?
Let's get going.
(A splendid finale of Member's Week is Jae Seok's ice shower.)
Hurry.
Goodness. I love you, Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok, I love you. - Okay.
Somehow, he always gets this sort of punishment.
Anyway, this is the last week of Member's Week.
Let's work harder starting next week.
- Let's work harder. - Let's do that.
- I can't watch this. - I'm sorry, Jae Seok.
We love you.
(The ice shower will be colder than the coldness at dawn.)
(I think I might freeze from watching him.)
(Splashing)
- Jae Seok. - I'm freezing.
- Goodness. Are you okay? - You'll be okay.
This isn't as bad as I thought.
I thought it would be worse.
I'm fine, Kwang Soo.
(Member's Week is a complete success.)
- Great work, Kwang Soo. - You too. Jae Seok.
We are indeed unlucky.
- Go home. - Good job, Jae Seok.
I'm sorry. I love you.
I love you.
(He's gone, right?)
(Jae Seok deserves it. It serves him right.)
(They are acting silly.)
I really thought it was my name.
(They can't hold in the excitement.)
(Member's Week reaches an end.)
We haven't seen that for a while.
(We will start afresh with warm breeze of spring.)
(This is the most dangerous deal in Running Man's history.)
(Resting Place)
If Running Man members win the battle against the staff,
we will provide you a resting place.
However, if the staff wins,
one of the members have to provide their house as the resting place.
- No way. - This won't happen.
We have to win no matter what.
(Have we ever been this competitive?)
(And)
(How will our fates turn?)
Don't come!
(Next week on Running Man, A Dangerous Deal)