- Hello. - These cars are awesome.
(Studio in Goyang, Gyeonggi Province)
- Here is the theme of today's race. - Go ahead.
Everything will be carried out based on advanced bookings.
- Advanced bookings? - It's called Booking Race.
- Booking Race? - What is that?
(What? What would we book out of the blue?)
Three guests will be the team leaders today and choose...
- two members to start the race. - Is that so?
- They will play an important role. - I'll introduce three team leaders.
- Please come on out. - Where are they?
(They can't wait to see them. Who on earth are they?)
(Sandara Park, a famous idol singer who now became the hottest actor)
Hey, Sandara.
(Being a famous idol singer wasn't enough!)
(She transformed into the hottest actor.)
(Now she's here to rule the variety shows too.)
- Hello. - Hi, Sandara.
- Sandara. - I haven't seen you for a while.
My goodness. It's been so long, Sandara.
(Wait. He is...)
(Do you remember him? Han Jae Suk was the very first youth star.)
(He is at his prime again! He's in his golden days.)
(Han Jae Suk, a dignified, handsome middle-aged gentleman, is back.)
I think I should take care of him.
(He's laid back.)
- Hello. - Goodness. Nice to meet you.
(They are saying hello.)
(Meanwhile, who is this guy now?)
(Yoon Bak, an actor with unexpected charms)
It's Yoon Bak.
(When he's acting, he is the most good-looking actor in this world.)
(When he's on a variety show, he's the funniest guy.)
(3 team leaders are done making their appearances.)
- It's been a while. - Oh, my.
We have these three guests joining us today. It's nice to meet you.
- Sandara and Bak joined us before. - That's right.
- It's a surprise to see Jae Suk. - I was surprised to see him.
- It's his first time joining us. - I wonder what brings him here.
I haven't seen him on variety shows for a while.
How was "The Law of Jungle"?
- It was very fun. - Was it?
- What was so fun about it? - Well...
- It was an escape from reality. - An escape? I see.
He's talking about an escape from reality. We just started filming.
It's nothing special, but it sounds so cool.
- An escape? - Oh, right. He married Park Sol Mi.
It could have been great if she also joined us with you.
She had to take care of the children.
(Gentle laughs)
- He laughs like an actor too. - He does indeed.
I've heard someone laugh like this, but Jae Suk laughs like this.
(Laughing)
We can literally write down the sound of his laughter.
- We have the same name. - That's right.
- But you two are so different. - But you are not the same.
- You two are completely different. - I didn't realize it until now.
He's the Jae Suk among the actors.
I'm sorry, but he should've approved of your name beforehand.
- Did you get that? - I was born before he was.
- Really? - You were born in 1973, right?
- See? I was born first. - I can't believe...
you two were born in the same country.
- He's handsome. - He looks handsome next to you.
- You look really pretty, Sandara. - Oh, right.
- Your names are similar too. - My name is Yoon Bak.
- Her name is Sandara Park. - It's her last name.
- Her last name is Park. - His first name is Bak.
Right. That's exactly my point.
- You were wrong. - You had it wrong.
- Admit that you were wrong. - Accept that you made a mistake.
- How was I wrong? - You can't mess up their names.
- Their names sound similar anyway. - Her last name is Park.
It must be hard for Jae Seok. He has no common grounds with them.
- Let's just agree with him. - Goodness.
- Are they strings on your outfit? - Don't pick a fight with me.
- Don't tease me for no reason. - Let me see. They're coming out.
- Sorry, but let me have them. - I can pull them off.
- Stop. It's hard to put them back. - Can they be pulled out?
- What on earth are these? - If you pull them out...
- Can we pull out presents from it? - All of them are pulled out!
What happened to this? Where did it go?
How will I put them back? It will take forever. He's so annoying.
- Over fitted outfit is trendy now. - Haha. It won't take long.
- Over fitted outfit? - I will do this for you.
- People often wear it like that. - Don't you worry.
There's no need for you to worry. Long time ago, my mom...
- did this for me. - Sandara. Please talk to him.
I'm about to lose my mind. He always wears shorts except during winter.
He wears a t-shirt with jeans. They know nothing about fashion.
- That's fashionable. - What on earth is this?
- Hey, you should tie your earrings. - Oh, sure.
- Stop it. - She can't leave them dragging.
- She looks fine. - This is driving me crazy.
- Sandara. You are... Goodness. - Yes?
What? She is what?
- "Goodness." - I guess you have nothing to say.
- Finish what you were saying. - Recently, she shot a film.
She sent me a trailer for that.
- Really? - So she's an actress now.
She is all over the entertainment industry.
- Can I ask the roles you played? - Can we?
- I played the role of a songwriter. - What?
You played the role of a musician.
My role used to be a famous songwriter.
Well... Then he was burned out.
When he can't create new songs, he meets...
- a genius songwriter. - He meets a genius songwriter.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but you speak so slowly.
- At this time, we're supposed to... - Please let him finish.
- finish at least two interviews. - I see.
I think it's funnier than your tying his clothes.
(With his low voice, he says what is on his mind.)
(He targets Jae Seok from the start.)
- Jae Suk. - Great job.
- What? It wasn't meant for you. - It wasn't?
(This is a piece of cake.)
- All of you are wearing badges. - Right.
(What are these badges?)
Let me explain about the badges. Before your arrival,
the team leaders have already booked the prize for the winning team.
(They already booked the prize.)
Hello.
Today, you guys will be reserving...
all the missions in advance.
It's called Booking Race.
The 3 of you need to choose 2 other team members.
- Then you'll do the race as a team. - Okay.
Is there anyone you'd like to choose in advance?
I'd like to have Jong Kook on my team.
He's mine.
I'll just choose whoever's left after they choose their members.
(Relaxed)
I'd like to...
choose Seok Jin. I feel comfortable around him.
(His choice goes well with him.)
Before starting the actual race,
let's start with the first booking.
You'll each need to choose the final winning award.
- It's ginseng. - Look. It's wild ginseng.
- It's ginseng. - I see.
There's also a ticket for an overseas trip.
- Is that real gold? - Yes.
That's too small.
I want to go abroad, so I choose the ticket for an overseas trip.
As for me,
(Jae Suk chooses...)
I choose the ginseng.
(the premium ginseng set.)
I want the ginseng set too.
You're still young. Why don't you choose this?
Then I'll choose...
the gold.
(They finish choosing their winning awards.)
- Where are we going abroad? - I want to go abroad.
- The location is what's important. - Are you okay with just ginseng?
They're getting gold and a ticket to go abroad.
Ginseng is a more realistic choice for me.
- Really? - Yes.
- He's so honest. - I'm sorry to say this,
but the way you talk right now...
makes it sound like you were forced to come here.
- Am I right? - No.
He keeps sighing like this.
Exactly. You just sounded like him.
- I know. - Okay.
So what's happening? Do we choose teams now?
All six members of Running Man will choose...
- a car each and sit inside it. - One person per car?
Once you're waiting inside the car,
the three team leaders will dance to the music...
and sit beside a member they'd like to choose.
If you like that team leader,
you just have to get off together.
If not, you can just stay in your seat.
- Then let's each choose a car. - Yes, go ahead.
- Can we choose any car? - Yes.
- I'm going to choose that one. - Do we just get on?
- You know how much I like that car. - I want to get on the truck too.
(I need to choose a pretty car so I can stand out.)
It's spacious.
(Excited)
"Transformer Optimus Prime".
- Are you ready? - Yes.
(Everyone's ready to get booked.)
(Let the booking begin.)
What's the music?
- What? - My gosh.
- What's this? - What's going on?
(Who will get chosen first?)
- He's coming. - I'm nervous.
- Come on. - He's coming here.
Hey, Bak!
(Dancing)
Hey, Bak.
(He goes straight to Seok Jin.)
Would you like to join me?
- Do you want to be on my team? - Of course.
(Is Bak seriously choosing Seok Jin?)
- Would you like to be on my team? - Of course.
- Will you join me? - Of course, Bak.
Why is he sitting on his lap?
- We're on the same team. - We are?
- Yes. - Really?
- Okay, let's do this! - Yes!
- Yes! This is great. - Whom else should we choose?
Let's see.
We need someone who's better than us at something.
- You think so? - They should either be smarter...
or stronger than us.
- What do you think about Kwang Soo? - Kwang Soo?
- Let's go together. - What?
Let's go get him together.
(They head to their next target.)
Did Seok Jin get chosen?
He got chosen first?
That truck is really high.
How can we go up there?
- They're coming this way. - Why aren't you looking at us?
(Why are you avoiding us?)
Hey, stop avoiding us.
- Hey. - I just might choose you.
- Excuse me. - I'm going to choose you.
Look to your left.
(We're not meant to be.)
- This isn't going to work. - Hey.
I'm going to choose you.
This won't work. We can't force him.
Let's go.
Are they coming here?
(Nervous)
(Are they coming for me?)
Hey.
(They surround Kwang Soo from each side.)
Hey, Bak.
- Hello. - Hey.
What brings you here?
We should get together...
- and show them. - No.
We should show them what we can do.
- Wait. Wait. - Hey.
- Bak really wants you on our team. - Come on.
With our teamwork,
we can take the winning prize.
- He's older than us. - So you think we can win?
- Shall we give it a go? - Let's do it.
- Shall we? - Yes.
- Let's do it! - Really?
- Let's show them! - Okay!
(Okay, let's go!)
(That was a lie.)
(He tries to open the door.)
No. I don't want to!
- Come on. - No!
Sandara...
- I want to be on Sandara's team! - How can you do this?
How can you betray me?
- I don't want to! - You already said yes.
How does this lock?
How can I lock the door?
Come on.
You got off, so you're on their team.
(What did you say?)
Okay.
He came out on his own.
- That's it? - Congratulations.
Can you play Sting's song?
(Do you mean this song?)
My gosh, that was funny.
- How funny. - Bye!
(Bak chooses Seok Jin and Kwang Soo.)
I should leave the door open now.
Sandara, please proceed.
(It's Sandara's turn to choose.)
"I Am the Best".
- It's Sandara's turn. - "I Am the Best".
- Sandara, look here! - Sandara, come on!
- Sandara! - Come on, Sandara!
- Sandara! - She's on her way!
You're the best!
(I'm the queen of booking.)
I am the best
- You're the best! - I am the best
Sandara, come on!
(She looks around.)
Look at Haha.
(She starts warming up by dancing.)
(She expresses her interest towards her target.)
- She's going for Jae Seok. - Hey!
- It's Jae Seok. - Stop!
She's going straight to Jae Seok.
I'll be the team leader this time.
- Sure. - Will you be on my team?
Okay!
- That's so unfair. - Okay!
They're so annoying.
We also need...
- someone strong. - Is that so?
(We know who it is.)
(It's Kim Jong Kook.)
(Are they coming for me?)
They're going for Jong Kook.
I can't believe this.
- He really likes it. - Isn't that unfair?
(Before choosing, she elevates the mood by dancing.)
That's not fair. She can't do that.
Hey, Sandara. Do you choose Jong Kook?
Do you want Jong Kook?
(Entering)
My goodness. Would you like to join us?
Of course. I'd love to.
Let's do this.
(Sandara chooses Jae Seok and Jong Kook.)
- I am the best - She didn't choose you.
- She chose Jong Kook? - She didn't...
You chose Jong Kook?
Things can still change.
- The game's already over. - What is this?
What's happening today?
- Things can still change. - It's game over.
- Hey, we're... - I am the best
We have the best team.
Are we a team now?
- Yes, we're a team. - This is so unfair.
Let's get off.
It's not set yet.
You guys might not get chosen.
Hey, you might have to live in that truck forever!
They're allowed to steal people.
- Jae Suk might not choose you two. - You guys might not get chosen.
(It's the last team leader's turn to choose.)
- My gosh. - Let's go Jae Suk.
This music is...
(What's this old song?)
(Dancing)
Look at him dance.
(He dances like everyone used to in the past.)
That doesn't look cool at all.
(Let's go back to the 90s.)
- He dances well. - My goodness.
- That's an old dance. - It's a very old dance.
He's a great dancer.
- He must've gone to a lot of clubs. - Look at him.
- It's this dance. - How does he do that?
How does he do this so well?
(Everyone's attracted to Jae Suk.)
How can he dance like this?
(Jae Suk chooses Haha.)
You got chosen?
- Come on. - Jae Suk!
(They dance as a couple.)
- My goodness. - Really?
- He's... - He must've danced a lot.
(He chooses Ji Hyo as his second team member.)
I'm sure he went to a lot of clubs.
We're a team.
They're all wearing jeans.
They look good together.
You really know how to dance.
Look at him.
You're a good dancer.
(Everybody starts dancing like Jae Suk.)
(All team leaders successfully chose their team members.)
Jae Suk.
Jae Suk's really handsome, but he dances like Seok Jin.
Whom are you talking about?
The good-looking Jae Suk.
(I'm talking about the good-looking Jae Suk.)
He's incredible.
Are you all satisfied with your team members?
- I'm satisfied. - Me too.
This is new. I'm just not so excited about getting ginseng.
- Do we get to go abroad? - Yes.
- Wasn't that us? - We get the gold.
Right, we get the gold.
- Your prize is gold? - I like going abroad.
I'll explain the overall rule.
The team that wins each mission...
will get a VIP ticket that will help them win the final race.
The team that wins the final race...
will be able to take the prize that was chosen by their leader.
I've installed a water bomb over there.
(A water bomb?)
I've installed a water bomb.
- What? - But there's just one bomb.
- I see. - There's just one water bomb.
There's just one. Now, please get changed into your team uniforms...
- and gather back here. - Okay.
Let's do this.
(What will be the result of this race?)
(Booking Race)
(Now, let's begin the Booking Race.)
This is the first match.
Round One is "Booking Quiz".
("Booking Quiz")
- It's a quiz. - Yes.
All of you will play at the same time.
The first sentence and the score will appear on the screen.
Ride the mini car all the way here.
Grab the phone and book the member to take the quiz.
If you want to take the quiz, say your name.
- Can we call someone else? - If it's too difficult,
you can say someone else's name.
The first team to score 100 points wins.
If you answer incorrectly,
we'll throw flour at you.
(It's a flour bomb.)
There are two holes in my team.
Haha doesn't know anything.
- We have no hope... - It's a big tunnel.
- for Haha. - Haha has no idea.
We hope two holes are all we need, but let's see how Jae Suk does.
- That's true. - You never know.
You'll reach a limit.
(He chuckles nervously.)
(We look forward to his performance.)
(Booking Race)
Are you ready?
- Yes. - I was born ready.
- What will be the question? - I depend on you, Kwang Soo.
- Shall we go? - Yes.
What's going on?
(The 1st question relates to Sandara for 20 points.)
(As "Celebrity Siblings", Sandara and her brother work together.)
(Everyone starts to race.)
What's going on?
(Sandara wants to answer the question.)
What's going on? It's stuck.
I was wondering why mine wasn't moving.
(Jong Kook can't start.)
(Sandara, Haha, and Ji Hyo race forward.)
(They reach for the phone.)
(Haha grabs the phone first.)
Why couldn't I move faster?
Whom will you book?
- Whom will you book? - Haha.
Haha?
(Haha books himself.)
- Will you answer it? - Everyone knows the answer.
The answer is obvious.
The question is very easy. I know the answer.
- It's a difficult question for you. - I definitely know the answer.
(Once he sits, the whole question is revealed.)
The question is difficult.
(The answer is too obvious.)
(What's the name of Sandara's brother?)
- The answer is obvious. - Come on.
(He knows the answer.)
The answer is obvious.
It's too easy.
- I know a lot about celebrities. - That's right.
- What's the answer? - Byeo Rak.
It's number three, Cheon Dung.
(Haha earns 20 points.)
Let's answer all of them.
- Everyone knows the answer. - My legs hurt.
Good job.
I can answer anything about celebrities.
Gosh, we missed it.
- Sandara. - Yes?
It was about your brother. You should have answered it.
I won't miss the next one.
Let's answer all questions about celebrities.
Gosh, we missed it.
Here's the second question.
(It's the second question.)
- It's for 40 points. - Hey.
(The 2nd question relates to Haha for 40 points.)
He's so fast.
(Everyone races forward to book.)
(It's my question. Move out of the way.)
- It's mine. - He's so fast.
(Bak grabs the phone.)
- He's so fast. - Goodness.
- You should answer it. - Let Jae Suk answer it.
(The question seems difficult.)
(Will he answer it himself?)
You answer it.
I'll answer it.
- Okay. - You can do it.
- You're smart. - I know the answer.
The question is somewhat difficult.
"When did the Berlin Wall..."
- What? - I don't know the answer.
Wait a minute.
It's too difficult.
Was it 1990? I'm confused.
I don't know the answer.
- Is it number one? - What's the answer?
Is it 1988?
- Take a guess. - Number three.
(He answers the year 1989.)
(He gets a question about history. Will Bak's answer be correct?)
(Bak earns 40 points.)
(He's surprisingly smart.)
He's so smart.
You're very sexy.
He's so cool.
- He answered correctly. - How did you know?
Our score is zero.
The Berlin Wall was demolished in 1989.
Here's the next question.
(It's related to Han Jae Suk.)
What is it?
(The 3rd question relates to Jae Suk for 50 points.)
Come on.
Good job.
(He's in a daze.)
What's this?
(Is it Sol Mi?)
(Everyone moves forward.)
(One old man stays behind.)
(Young people are good at riding mini cars these days.)
(Sol Mi, being on variety shows isn't easy.)
(I'm sorry, honey. I'm not good at this game.)
Goodness.
(Right, you aren't very good.)
(Kwang Soo gets his chance to book.)
Good job.
I was too flustered to move.
This is too difficult. Book Sandara.
It's difficult.
(The score is too high.)
(He suspects that he won't know the answer.)
- Sandara. - That's right.
You can do it.
- You can guess. - She won't know.
- You must answer correctly. - I didn't see the question.
(What's the question?)
Read the question.
What?
- I knew it'd be difficult. - What is it?
Man Deok is known as a savior of this place.
The question is too easy.
(She has no idea.)
(Kwang Soo teases her.)
Man Deok?
- I'd be impressed. - Which place is it?
Just take a guess.
What's the answer?
- It's a place he saved. - Wait, no.
Sandara.
- Answer it. - Take a guess.
- Take a guess. - Number three, Ulleung Island.
- Good job. - I think it's correct.
(Did Kwang Soo choose the right person?)
Good job.
- It's incorrect. - Gosh.
(She gets a flour bomb.)
(It's shocking to look at.)
- Gosh. - That's how it works.
Gosh.
I had no idea.
I didn't know this would happen. I'm sorry.
Sandara.
That was cruel.
I didn't know this would happen. I'm sorry.
Sandara.
You look pretty right now.
(Sandara turns white.)
She looks like a Japanese doll.
Jae Suk knew the answer.
(Team Yoon Bak has the highest score.)
(In the movie "Battlefield Heroes"...)
(The 4th question relates to Kwang Soo for 30 points.)
No!
(It seems difficult.)
No! Hold on!
(She doesn't care if the question is difficult.)
- Come on, Kwang Soo. - Sandara.
(Bak and Sandara arrive simultaneously.)
Sandara.
(Reach for the phone.)
(Sandara gets her chance to book.)
Stay calm.
- Bak moves so fast. - How is it possible?
The person I'll book is...
(Whom will she book?)
(Remember Jae Suk who stayed behind?)
- It's Jae Suk. - That's right.
(Sandara books Jae Suk.)
- You can do it. - He'll answer it.
- Good job, Sandara. - Good job.
(Kwang Soo hopes for a difficult question.)
- Good job. - Let's see.
(Is this the flour bomb?)
- It's difficult. - Will he answer correctly?
Jae Suk, it's so easy.
(It's a question about history.)
- Is it a multiple-choice question? - Yes.
It is.
(Jae Suk's fear starts to grow.)
The Three Kingdoms of Korea.
- What is it? - Joseon?
It's the name of a kingdom.
- Isn't it Silla? - What is it?
(What will be his answer?)
It's Goguryeo.
(Will Jae Suk's reputation change to a smart team leader?)
(Jae Suk earns 30 points.)
(He's smart after all.)
He's good.
Is it Goguryeo?
This is what Kwang Soo said.
He appeared in the movie and said that the answer was Silla.
- He said Silla. - No, I didn't.
I was lying on purpose.
Gosh, I'm relieved.
Goodness.
That was great.
- Our team is the best. - We're amazing.
Ji Hyo, you should go quickly and book.
- I'll go and book. - Sandara is quick.
I hope no one calls my name anymore.
Everyone, get ready.
(Team Jae Suk takes the lead.)
(Jae Suk played a lead in a drama called "Jazz".)
(The 5th question relates to Jae Suk for 20 points.)
(Jae Suk moves forward.)
Why didn't you stop Ji Hyo?
(There's heavy traffic.)
(He stops to look at the fight.)
(Ji Hyo gets through the traffic and races forward.)
The person I'll book is...
Call out Jae Suk.
(They trust Jae Suk.)
- Jae Suk. - Call him.
(Ji Hyo books Jae Suk.)
- Did someone stop you? - Yes.
Answering your own question incorrectly is funny.
Let's go, Jae Suk.
- "He was born in 1900." - It's difficult.
"He's called the father of jazz. Who is he?"
(The question relates to jazz this time.)
What is this?
What?
(Why is the question so difficult?)
What's the answer?
Louis Armstrong.
(It's another difficult question.)
(Will Jae Suk create a miracle?)
It's a difficult one.
(Jae Suk earns 20 points.)
(Who is that man?)
Jae Suk is good at quizzes.
(Call Jae Suk for quizzes.)
Jae Suk is amazing.
- My goodness. - He's such a smart man.
- How did you know the answer? - He's so sexy.
- Our team is the best, Ji Hyo. - I know.
Here's the next question.
Is that it?
(Seok Jin debuted as a singer in 1992.)
(The 6th question relates to Seok Jin for 60 points.)
(Bak races ahead the quickest.)
Bak is so quick.
Hello?
- Call out Seok Jin. - Okay.
- Call me. - Hurry.
- Seok Jin. - Okay!
(Bak books Seok Jin.)
I think he knows the answer.
- It's a question about himself. - "I Know"?
- I hope he gets it wrong. - It's about "I Know".
- What? - It's so hard.
(Seok Jin debuted as a singer in 1992.)
(Which of the following words does not appear in "I Know"?)
(Eyes, Lips, Breath, Happiness)
(Worried)
- What? - It's so hard.
We're doomed.
(Exactly)
- 5, 4, 3... - 4, 3...
(It's going to be hilarious.)
- I'll answer. - One.
- 3, 2, 1. - I'll answer.
Number three, "happiness".
(Will he be covered with flour?)
(Or does he correctly remember his 26-year-old song?)
(Team Yoon Bak wins 60 points.)
It was correct.
(I'm so proud of you.)
- You remember it. - I just took a guess.
(Seok Jin's legendary debut song)
- I took a guess. - You remember your song.
Let's go, Bak.
This question is worth 100 points.
(This question will determine the 2nd and 3rd places.)
(The 7th question is about Yoon Bak and worth 100 points.)
(Yoon Bak recently appeared in "The Law of Jungle".)
- Hey! - Go away!
(It's a great chance for Team Sandara.)
- Mine doesn't move. - I know.
(Relaxed)
(They race as fast as they can.)
(Ji Hyo gets the chance.)
- Why is it... - Let's do this.
I'll book Haha.
I was telling you to do it yourself.
(You're booked anyway.)
- Haha. - There should be minus points.
(All right, here I come.)
There should have been minus points.
(It's fun to watch.)
(Where did Bak visit for "The Law of Jungle"?)
- What's that? - It's hard.
- It's too hard. - I should have done it.
- They went to the same place. - We went to the same place.
I participated in the 1st half, and he the 2nd.
- Let's continue. - What's your answer?
Brazil.
(Why are Jae Suk and Bak laughing?)
(Wrong)
This is frustrating.
(Aren't there jungles in Brazil too?)
(The correct answer is New Caledonia.)
(Both Bak and Jae Suk visited a jungle in New Caledonia.)
(The 2nd place and the 3rd place compete again.)
This will be the last question.
(The 8th question is about Sandara and worth 100 points.)
- Ji Hyo, go! - Hurry.
(Make way for me.)
(Which team will get the chance?)
- Sandara, book Jong Kook. - You know, right?
- I'll book... - Sandara, book Jong Kook.
I'll book Jong Kook.
There you go.
(What's the question?)
(Which of the following has never hosted "Inkigayo"?)
(Song Ji Hyo, Song Hye Kyo, Han Hyo Joo, Han Ye Seul)
You have to get it right.
- Please. - I'll answer.
(If he gets it right, Team Sandara will be second place.)
- Let's take turns. - Why am I not sure?
I'm not sure either.
- Number two, "Song Hye Kyo". - It's confusing.
- There you go. - That's wrong.
(There's only one VIP ticket left now.)
(Will Team Sandara win the VIP ticket?)
(Team Sandara wins 2nd place.)
(The booking turns out to be successful.)
- It was correct. - He got it right.
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Han Hyo Joo)
(Han Ye Seul)
(Song Hye Kyo was a reporter, not a host.)
(Jae Suk's team finishes in 3rd place.)
- We did it. - Gosh.
Team Yoon Bak wins two VIP tickets.
(Team Sandara wins one, and Team Jae Suk none.)
- For the second game, - Go ahead.
we'll have "Talent Quiz".
Three missions will be shown on the screen.
Pick one person for each mission and move to the designated places.
Okay.
(The missions are revealed.)
"A mission for movie lovers"...
(A mission for movie lovers)
(A mission for music lovers)
(A mission for good guessers)
What if the guessing game is meant for unlucky people?
I'll do it then.
- I'll just continue to be unlucky. - We'll have to try.
Those three will do the music mission.
Bak and Jong Kook will do the movie mission.
The four of you will do the guessing mission.
Except Ji Hyo, we're all unlucky.
- We're so unlucky. - If we're unlucky today too...
- We're two. - Exactly.
(Booking Race)
(The members for the guessing mission arrive at the place.)
- What's that? - They look like airbags.
- Some of them must burst. - We might have to guess.
- We have advantages. - It's going to be fun.
There are 90 airbags here.
Seven of them burst when you touch them.
- Seven of them. - I'm confident.
- Ji Hyo... - My gut feeling is...
- usually right. - Don't be ridiculous.
(Don't be ridiculous.)
- No, it isn't. - That's nonsense.
(Jae Seok doesn't seem to know.)
I'm confident. My gut feeling is usually right.
I figured out what this game is about right away.
Are there seven?
2 are on that side, and 5 are on this side.
- Determine the order. - Rock-paper-scissors is boring.
Let's squeeze each other's hands. The one who screams first loses.
(It's not that important who goes first.)
- Let's do that. - Start.
(They're addicted to games.)
(When did it start? Maybe 7 years ago?)
(They used to be ordinary people.)
(After 8 years on Running Man, they can't live without games.)
(They need your love and care.)
(Game addiction hotline)
(Gosh)
(Jae Seok will go last.)
(Screaming)
- He'll go last. - There are teeth marks.
- It's 2 to 1 now. - It's 2 to 1.
- We have no choice. - Ji Hyo, please win.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo versus Ji Hyo)
(Although Ji Hyo is always lucky,)
(we're two people.)
Let's start.
Hey, why are you...
(Severe pain)
- Why do you attack me? - I'm sorry.
(Kwang Soo can't control his attacking instinct.)
- Hey! - I'm really sorry.
It's over now.
- Why did you attack me? - I'm sorry.
Look at the color of our t-shirts!
- I attacked both sides. - Let's play another game.
We hit each other's forehead, and the one who falls backward loses.
- Okay. - If Ji Hyo falls and I stay...
- Okay. - Stay where you are.
- Don't fall. - You have to sit like this.
I won't fall.
1, 2, 3.
Three.
(The sound is very cheerful.)
(Kwang Soo's forehead is so nice to hit.)
- It's Ji Hyo's turn. - Come here.
Kwang Soo will have to choose Seok Jin.
Ji Hyo, I have no choice.
- Did you wash your hands? - I couldn't help but fall.
(It's so funny.)
- "Did you wash your hands?" - 1, 2, 3.
(Ji Hyo falls.)
(Bye, Ji Hyo.)
(There's no winner.)
It's a tie.
- Ji Hyo. - Let's do something else.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors. - Let's do that.
We could have done it from the beginning.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Ji Hyo wins.)
What a disappointment.
We could have done this from the beginning.
We should have done that.
(While they are deciding the order...)
For the music-lovers,
- we prepared a music game. - I like it.
The sticks move up and down according to your moves.
Some sticks have a letter on them.
You'll have to come up with song titles by combining those letters.
(The one who finds 2 song titles 1st wins.)
After ringing the bell and saying your answer,
sing one phrase of the song.
I'm at the wrong place.
(The music game starts.)
- Is this the place? - Wait.
It's moving.
(As Sandara dances,)
(the sticks start to move.)
I see "come".
(The sticks are dancing.)
- We have to find song titles. - I see something.
(They're surprised at the speed.)
I don't see any.
- It's hard. - Did you see "new"?
There must be something.
(The sticks are teasing Sandara.)
(Sandara saw "love".)
(She runs to the microphone.)
"Love Rain" by Kim Tae Woo.
- Sing a phrase. - I don't know that song well.
(She has to sing a phrase to win one point.)
(Will she sing it right?)
My goodness.
Love rain falls
When it falls
(Wrong)
- Why? - I'll give you one more chance.
I don't know the lyrics.
- What's happening? - Go away.
(I smell something.)
When my love falls on me
- The love comes back - Okay.
(Thanks for the information.)
- Gosh, the lyrics. - "Love Rain" by Kim Tae Woo.
(When your love falls on my eyes)
When your love
(Wrong)
(Doesn't it count?)
(That's a relief.)
(Jae Suk gives a try.)
- "Come Back to Busan Port". - By who?
- Cho Yong Pil. - Sing a phrase now.
(Jae Suk managed to find a long title.)
(With this momentum, will he be able to succeed at once?)
Please sing the phrase.
Flowers are blooming
On Dongbaek Island
Spring has come
All right!
(Jae Suk is the first one to succeed.)
Great. I got another one.
It's "Tatata" by Kim Guk Hwan.
(Haha tries to sing "Tatata".)
What a choice. All right.
(This impressive song has gemlike lyrics and is sung with laughter.)
(How will I know you?)
(Laughing)
- I only have sing one line, right? - Right.
Why?
- Did you start? - He laughs for eight measures.
You can't do this.
This is in the lyrics.
That is not how he laughs in the song.
Fine.
I'll sing "Tatata" by Kim Guk Hwan.
(Laughing)
(That's incorrect.)
That's not it.
(He laughs again, but he gets it wrong.)
Hey. Let me see. Give it to me.
You might have the wrong lyrics.
This is so frustrating.
I can't get it right even if I know the song.
(He falls into a trap of the song.)
This is for movie lovers.
During the film,
you will hear the keyword...
and guess the title that starts with the keyword.
- All right. - Okay.
I'm scared of rides since I can't ride them well.
All right. Let's do this for the VIP ticket.
(Surprised)
(He's starting to be overly dramatic.)
Was this a mistake to choose this?
I don't know a lot about movies.
(However, the quiz has already started.)
(From the start, it's already bumpy ride.)
This is amazing.
(He clutches tightly.)
(Fear versus curiosity)
(Their reactions are polar opposites.)
I'm in trouble.
(Get ready for 4D Racing!)
- We are... - Goodness.
- I'm getting dizzy. - The first keyword is...
"public".
- I have the answer! - Jong Kook.
The answer is "Public Enemy".
That's correct.
What am I going to do?
- Hey. Look at that. - It's starting now.
It's ready. Here we go.
(The race starts now!)
The second keyword is "north".
- Jong Kook! - Yes, Jong Kook?
- "North Korean Guys". - That's correct.
Okay!
(Jong Kook gets the second question too.)
(He's in despair.)
I have the answer.
It's "Asura".
- Correct! It's the last question. - All right.
- Here's the keyword. - Jong Kook!
It's "The Harmonium in My Memory".
- That's correct. - Okay.
(Jong Kook wins the match.)
(He ends up only watching the films.)
That's correct.
(Bak is a true fan of films.)
How can you guess them right away?
There are so many film titles.
- I can't believe him. - By the way...
This isn't a set up, right?
When he gave you the keyword, you knew right away.
- How can you be so fast? - Of course I can.
There are so many movie titles.
(I can't compete against Jong Kook.)
Is this it?
- Did I lose? - This is fun.
- Ji Hyo. Go first. - You should go first.
- Ji Hyo. You can start. - Me?
- I'm nervous. - Goodness. This is...
- By the way, - I'll show you I have a hunch too.
Having a good hunch and being lucky are two different things.
- I will show you that! - I'm more serious than ever.
Me too. I'm serious too.
Only 7 will pop out of 90.
(Ji Hyo starts first.)
(Ji Hyo is known to be the lucky one among the members.)
(These unlucky ones are hoping that she will fail.)
- All right. - What a surprise.
(Did the airbag pop?)
(The universe has taken their side.)
- You are out. - Okay.
(This is gratifying indeed!)
All right. Ji Hyo, you are out.
You are done, Ji Hyo.
- It's your turn, Kwang Soo. - Okay.
I don't want to lose to you two.
- It's Kwang Soo's turn. - I don't want to lose to you!
- I want to win too. - Okay!
- I'll chose this one. - All right.
(Ji Hyo couldn't avoid picking the false airbag.)
(Will Kwang Soo get lucky?)
- Okay! - You did it!
(He succeeds.)
- It's your turn, Seok Jin. - Okay.
I'll choose the one below Kwang Soo's.
(Can he succeed too after receiving Kwang Soo's lucky energy?)
- Okay! - You did it!
(Seok Jin succeeds too.)
I can't let those two win.
Probability-wise, we have the upper hand.
(It's a rare scene where these two unlucky ones are feeling confident.)
- All right! I'm pushing. - You chose one.
(If Jae Seok fails, Team Yoon Bak wins.)
(The airbag deflates.)
(There was no twist.)
(Jae Seok fails.)
(Okay! The victory is ours!)
- The victory goes to... - To us, right?
Team Yoon Bak.
(They acquire one VIP ticket.)
- Cross! - Cross!
It was a close one.
Right. It was a close one.
- We're doing well today. - It's our day today.
- I have a good feeling about this. - I find this amazing.
We have to win today.
This is driving me crazy. How can't I know the lyrics?
I don't know who I am
There's no way that I am wrong.
That was one of my favorite songs, but I can't recall the lyrics now.
I'll sing "Tatata" by Kim Guk Hwan.
If you don't know who I am
How will you know who I am?
(He is just flat out wrong.)
(He begins to talk nonsense.)
(He is confused who doesn't know whom.)
(It has to be right this time.)
How will you know me?
I won't do this anymore.
Gosh!
(Meanwhile, Sandara is struggling to fight off Jae Suk and Haha.)
(I just need to sing one more song right.)
(She's on the brink as she tries to sing a song.)
I'll sing "Eyes, Nose, Lips" by Tae Yang.
Please sing one line.
(She tries to keep up with them with Tae Yang's song.)
(They share the same agency. She won't be wrong, right?)
Please sing one line.
(She's confident)
(She even dances confidently.)
Even all of your small nails
(She easily succeeds.)
- That's correct. Sandara. - Yes! This is great.
Can I use the same word twice?
- Yes, you can. - I can use the same word again?
I think that will work, Jae Suk.
Will it work? I ought to ask.
(He's not certain.)
I came here to ask a question.
Can I use one character twice?
It doesn't matter if you do.
I will sing "Strangers" by Choi Sung Soo.
- Can I sing that? - Please sing the song.
(He succeeds in differentiating his strategy by guessing an old song.)
(Will he...)
(be able to head straight to the victory?)
- Can I sing that? - Please sing the song.
(Thinking)
(No way. He can't succeed.)
I have loved her wholeheartedly
She left my side tonight
(If he sings the song correctly, Team Jae Suk will win.)
Tonight
(They win the game by guessing two songs correctly.)
What is it? Which song did you sing?
- I sang "Strangers". - Really?
It's great to play this game with someone with an old soul.
- This isn't over, Jae Suk. - Is it over?
- It is over now. - Oh, is it?
- It's over. - Okay.
(Team Jae Suk acquires one VIP ticket.)
Why don't you laugh in the front?
(Laughing)
You are the best.
(The score is 1 to 1 to 1.)
Now, it's time for a meal.
- Really? - Goodness.
This looks delicious.
- Can we eat? - Yes, you can.
You can eat now.
Thank you for the food.
- The steak looks delicious. - It looks tasty.
- Isn't the spaghetti delicious? - It is.
(Eating)
The food here is amazing.
- It's really good. - The food here is delicious indeed.
(The best quality food pleases their palate and eyes.)
This is delicious.
Listen up while you enjoy your food. We have one last final mission.
- Really? - Already?
We have one last final mission.
(We will do our last final mission already?)
In the final race,
each team will do a different mission which will be determined...
by the prize each team leader chose.
- Goodness. - How are the missions different?
The missions are related to the selected prize.
(What kind of race will they face?)
(The fate of the final race has already been chosen.)
Bak. Calm down.
Goodness.
- I got too excited. - Bak.
(Find, run, and solve if you want to change your fate.)
Where is he?
- He's right there! - Open it!
(Part 2 of Running Man is coming up next.)
(End of Running Man Part 1)
- Here is your final mission. - All right.
Missions are all different?
- What is that? - That's the passport.
(They are given luggage and passports.)
(Sandara has chosen the Trip Abroad Gift.)
- I like traveling overseas. - I want to win it too.
I will explain the mission.
The mission which will allow...
you to win the Trip Abroad Gift is...
- "Pass Through Immigration". - What?
(Did he say we have to pass through immigration?)
Immigration?
In this building,
six different nations' immigration checkpoints are hidden.
(They are all over the building.)
Find the immigration checkpoints.
Pass through immigration and get six stamps to succeed.
This is great. We can use the books to answer questions.
Here's the mission to win the prize of your choice, Ginseng Set.
It's called "Find the Supercar".
Here's the hint related to how you can find it.
Starting with the first hint, find the additional five hints.
Locate the Supercar accordingly.
Jae Suk is great at quizzes.
I'm not good at finding.
Ji Hyo is amazing at finding things.
- Is it best to find it quickly? - Yes.
What will be the mission?
Which prize have you won recently on Running Man?
I can't remember.
Today will be the day.
- Today is our day. - Right.
I'm being serious.
Here's your mission.
I'm curious.
(Team Yoon Bak is determined.)
(What will be their final mission?)
It's "Name Tag Elimination".
(It's "Name Tag Elimination".)
Is that it?
("Name Tag Elimination"?)
(We get to eliminate name tags.)
(Let's eliminate all the name tags today.)
(The other members are history.)
(They jump around in happiness.)
I'm so excited.
Wait.
I haven't felt so excited in a long time.
I'm excited.
What about out VIP ticket?
The number of VIP tickets determines the number...
of immigrations you don't have to pass through.
Team Sandara earned two VIP tickets.
You only need to get four stamps.
I'll tell you where the first hint is hidden.
That's for one VIP ticket.
- There were many cars downstairs. - Right.
- The first hint is in the blue one. - I see.
Each VIP ticket shows the location of the members.
(VIP tickets provide locations.)
If you have two VIP tickets, you get a Clone Card.
What should we do?
Let's use one for location. Then get Clone Card.
- We can eliminate one team. - Right.
- That's better. - What should we do?
There are only two clones for the Clone Card.
We need at least eight of them to fight Jong Kook.
(Try me if you can.)
For three VIP tickets...
(For three VIP tickets...)
(They receive a tremendous benefit with three VIP tickets.)
Here you go.
(3 VIP tickets cause a ripple effect.)
(Bak's fast and furious chase starts.)
(How will the others handle the power of three VIP tickets?)
Let's jump around.
We finally get our chance today.
- What should we do? - Listen.
We must eliminate Jong Kook before the rumor spreads.
Once Jong Kook is eliminated,
everyone else will get scared.
It won't be so easy.
I understand.
Let's search the trunk first.
- Open it. - Let's search.
Things are usually hidden here in Hollywood movies.
It was hidden here in "The Terminator".
- Ta-da. - No way.
I already knew it.
I sensed it right away.
I knew where it was hidden.
- Gosh, Haha. - We're so good.
- You're so observant. - We're a great team.
"The hint is hidden in the same color as this car."
- Haha. - We have to look in the car.
No, it's with the airbags.
The airbags were blue.
- Let's go over there. - You're right.
Ji Hyo, you're the best.
Where are they?
- We have to climb up and down. - I see.
- Isn't our mission too easy? - I have no idea.
- This is incredible. - Look...
Look for anything blue as we walk.
Blue? I got it.
(They're glowing with excitement.)
Gosh, this is so thrilling.
(They're absolutely thrilled.)
(Eliminating name tags was never so fun.)
- Seriously. - This is so much fun.
- It's so much fun. - We'll make it today.
(Team Yoon Bak starts the search.)
I can't control my excitement.
- Nothing is difficult today. - Right.
We have all the energy from the universe.
(They gather energy from the universe.)
We'll eliminate the name tags starting with Jong Kook.
We'll eliminate the name tags including Jong Kook's.
- You should calm down. - Right.
You're too excited right now.
I'm too excited.
- I bet there's something nearby. - Here?
Do we have to find the immigration?
Maybe there's something downstairs.
- Let's check downstairs. - Okay.
- I bet there's something here. - I agree.
- Check over there. I'll check here. - Thank you.
I'll check the other side.
- Okay. - Okay.
Be careful, Sandara.
Are we separating now? What should I do?
I was just here.
(Sandara is lost.)
(She hurries.)
(Where is the immigration?)
I want to be the heroine.
I want to survive until the end.
(She wants to make her teammates proud.)
I want to make them proud.
It should be around here.
Gosh.
(Instead of the immigration, he finds a gorgeous car.)
It looks great.
(He stops to look at it.)
Gosh, what's this?
(He's intrigued.)
I don't think it's here, Sandara.
We must depart soon.
- Here we are. - Is this the right floor?
Good luck.
(He hears the voice of another team.)
(What kind of mission are they on?)
There's someone.
(Team Yoon Bak is here.)
(He runs away first.)
Come on, let's go.
(Team Yoon Bak approaches Team Sandara.)
What's going on?
They're staff members.
They're over there.
There's Jong Kook.
They're carrying a suitcase.
(What are they doing?)
It's Kwang Soo.
They're carrying a suitcase.
What's going on?
What should we do?
Come on, Sandara.
(Unfortunately, Jong Kook isn't with them.)
We shouldn't separate.
(Stop right there.)
(The teams don't know each other's missions.)
(However, Team Yoon Bak chases after Team Sandara.)
- What's going on? - What are they doing?
- What are you doing? - What's this suitcase?
It's not mine.
- What's in the suitcase? - There's nothing in it.
There's nothing in it.
- We're leaving the country. - It's nothing.
- Where are you going? - Where are you going?
- What are you doing? - Wait.
- What's in this? - Wait.
Is there something in it?
- Where's Jong Kook? - In the suitcase?
(Where is Jong Kook?)
(They planned to eliminate Jong Kook before the rumor spreads.)
(Where did he go?)
(Are they looking for Jong Kook?)
- May I see it? - No.
You have no right to look inside.
(Sandara and Jae Seok are stopped.)
Are you delivering them somewhere?
Do you have to go somewhere?
I can't tell you.
You're making it difficult.
Why are you stopping us?
Let's go, Sandara.
Wait.
(They let them go since Jong Kook isn't around.)
We must eliminate Jong Kook first.
Once the rumor spreads, it's over.
- Where did Jong Kook go? - This is such a mess.
Where's immigration?
(He can't find anything.)
There must be a reason why the doors are open.
Shouldn't there be a reason?
(Jong Kook searches alone.)
(What's this?)
Is this immigration?
(He finds immigration.)
Hello, I'm Kim Jong Kook.
(He speaks in Chinese.)
(Hello)
Do you speak Chinese?
(What's the question?)
How much cash are you carrying?
Gosh.
What did he say?
Hold on, please.
(Will he get through immigration with the help from the book?)
(He searches...)
(and searches.)
Okay.
(Did he tell me to buy a lottery ticket?)
(He finds something.)
(What will be his answer?)
I have about 116 dollars.
(I have about 116 dollars.)
- You passed. - I passed.
(Jong Kook succeeds.)
Did I pass?
(His lonely search paid off.)
I can't believe it.
(He passes the Chinese immigration.)
Thank you.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
(He has three more to go.)
I passed.
I see something blue over there.
- Gosh, this looks amazing. - It's really cool.
It can also lift a chair.
(Is it hidden among the robots?)
I see something blue.
- There it is. - I see it too.
- This is blue too. - We can't go inside.
Is this it?
It's blue.
- Let's paint it. - Paint it blue.
(They press various buttons.)
(He steps away.)
I don't think it's here.
(He's shy with machines.)
- I bet it's in here. - I think so too.
Why is it so difficult?
(Jae Suk complains.)
- Jae Suk. - Here it is.
(Haha finds it.)
(Find the Secret Room.)
Secret Room?
We should go down that way.
Secret Room? That's too hard to find.
Something blue is coming.
(Team Yoon Bak approaches secretly.)
- They got something. - I know.
- What's going on? - Something seems strange.
- Let's kill them. - Kill them?
(We aren't easy anymore.)
What are you doing?
- Something seems strange. - They're cornering us.
Go over there.
(They start to corner them.)
What's going on? Bak?
- What? - What are you doing?
- We should stay together. - We should?
What's wrong?
(It's time.)
Kwang Soo, you look so suspicious.
(Does it show?)
- What are you talking about? - Why do you look out the window?
- My goodness. - Are you after our name tags?
- That's absurd. - No way.
(It's obvious that they're after their name tags.)
- What are you doing? - Give me your hand.
- Why? - My heart is pounding.
- We haven't found any hints yet. - Right.
- We have nothing. - We're looking for them now.
- Find Jong Kook's team. - Where are they?
(Team Jae Suk escapes the crisis.)
We'll see you later, okay?
My determination faltered.
Hey. My goodness.
We're doomed, right?
(Our mission just got revealed, right?)
Hey, look.
- This is crazy. - Why were you doing this?
- What do you think I'm doing? - Gosh.
(It's your fault.)
(There are no secrets in this world.)
Seriously. What's wrong with him?
- What does this look like? - Come to your senses.
- Let me tell you. We're doomed. - When you ran to them,
- they turned their backs. - This is going to fail.
(Three fools in blue)
- We're in trouble. - Why did you do that?
- Don't act suspicious. - I'm sorry.
Roll down your sleeves.
- Why did you roll them up? - It's hot.
(He's advertising that he's aiming for name tags.)
(I should pull myself together.)
We blew it.
Sandara, come on.
Okay.
(Let's leave this country.)
They're not running after our name tags yet.
Some of them must be after our name tags.
(Worried)
(Sandara looks back.)
(Is anyone following us?)
My goodness.
(Sandara looks around.)
(Sandara is worried.)
You look like someone who's fleeing at night.
- I'm worried someone's following. - I mean...
(Here we come.)
What are they doing?
- What's their mission? - I have no idea.
- We have to succeed before them. - We have to get it done.
There should be six of them, and why is it so hard to find them?
Exactly.
Where are they?
Team Yoon Bak is approaching.
- They are? - Yes.
(Let's run.)
(Running)
(Fast)
- They're nowhere. - They disappeared.
- Hurry. - They're running.
- I'll get them. - They're running.
(Bak has found his target.)
(Bak starts to rush.)
- Where are you going? - I want to stop them.
Stop running.
Bak, calm down. What's with him?
- Gosh. - Bak.
(What's that?)
It's so obvious he's after their name tags.
(Something's strange. Let's run.)
Let's go.
Calm down, Bak.
What's with you? Calm down.
- I'm so worked up. - Calm down.
- Pull yourself together. - You're obviously after name tags.
Hey, be quiet.
(Be quiet.)
Are you out of your mind?
(They're the same.)
Calm yourselves down, you fools.
- My heart is pounding. - Are you okay?
- Shouldn't you lie down? - It's so funny.
I'll be right back.
- What? - I'll do it.
- What do you mean? - I'll remove the name tags.
Just go outside and run for a while.
Bak, you should calm down. What's with you?
- We don't have much time. - Your face is so red.
(It's time for a full-scale attack.)
Let's go. That's Jong Kook. Why is he on his own?
What is he doing?
(They unexpectedly find Jong Kook.)
Hey!
Why are you running alone?
I completed one mission.
- Where? - China.
- Did you pass? - Yes.
(Jong Kook got a stamp.)
- He was hiding in the corner. - Are they hiding?
Have you run into the others?
Yes. But they didn't try to remove our name tags.
My goodness. I wish our mission was eliminating name tags too.
- It would have been over by now. - My goodness.
(Will they succeed in completing their mission?)
Let's go.
Have you looked in there?
(He goes closer.)
(He finds the second checkpoint right away.)
(What will be the question?)
(Speaking in foreign language)
(He takes out the books.)
French, Arabic...
(Don't you get it?)
(Let me see.)
(What will be the answer?)
Wait.
(Which language do you think it is?)
- It's not it? - No, it isn't.
Let me hear it again.
(What language is it?)
(Where are you from?)
Listening doesn't help. Look it up in the books.
- It sounds like... - This...
(It sounds a bit like French.)
(He stares at the book.)
Try to find out...
(Trying out)
- I studied French in high school. - Cut it out.
- I did. - I'm from Nantes.
(I'm from Nantes.)
I got this.
(Jong Kook is already answering the question.)
- Stop it. - I already found it.
I'm from Nantes. I'm from Korea.
- Correct. - What was it?
(Pass)
It was right. It means, "Where are you from?"
I'm from Anyang.
(Jong Kook is a great help.)
There you go.
(They've already won 2 stamps.)
Are we going somewhere else now?
- We just need two more now. - Exactly.
(Let's get it done.)
I think something must be here somewhere.
I didn't see anyone here before.
I didn't look here earlier.
(Is someone hiding here?)
- I found someone. - They're somewhere like this.
- Good job. - Which country is it now?
I don't think we'll understand it.
(Speaking in foreign language)
Do you have your passport with you?
It's definitely Arabic.
- It's definitely Arabic. - It's too long.
(This one seems hard.)
- What was it again? - Hey.
(Do you have your passport with you?)
(Will they able to pass this time too?)
- I have no idea. - Check the airport part.
(Will Jong Kook find the answer this time too?)
(Will Sandara find it?)
(They're desperate to pass through immigration.)
Yes, here's my passport. I'll show it to you.
Here's my passport.
(He seems to have found the answer.)
(Jong Kook hands over his passport.)
(Is the answer correct?)
- Is it correct? - Yes.
(Pass)
Jong Kook is a great help.
It's so easy to pass through immigration.
(They only need one more stamp now.)
(Booking Race Status)
- We've earned 3 stamps. - We only need 1 more.
We should be careful.
We should check every wall.
(They have to find a door to the secret room.)
- It'll take long. - What's this?
(Is this the place?)
I don't think this is the place.
How are we going to do it?
(Team Yoon Bak hasn't eliminated anyone yet.)
We haven't checked here.
We keep running into her.
(We can't run around forever.)
(We have to eliminate the name tags now.)
- What? - Come here.
(She tries to run away from the suspicious trio.)
Isn't this too much?
You guys keep winning the games.
(Bak is acting very suspicious.)
(Why is he following us?)
(It's time to remove your name tag.)
(Here comes Bak.)
- Bak! - Bak!
(What's wrong with him?)
(Ripping)
(Ji Hyo removes Bak's name tag, but Bak is not eliminated.)
- Bak! - What's with you?
- Who did it? - Hold on!
Don't do that!
- Please listen to me. - You come here.
(Ji Hyo and Haha are eliminated.)
Give him some water.
(Jae Suk runs away.)
Tell the other team.
We should start from Jong Kook.
Weren't we trying to remove their name tags?
What do you think we've been doing?
- We should start from Jong Kook. - We could have...
eliminated Jae Seok and Sandara.
We'll have to attack everyone we see from now on.
When Bak was attacking them, I could only see the whites of his eyes.
- I lost control. - You completely lost control.
(Team Yoon Bak's cover is almost blown.)
We need to find the Philippines.
(They need only 1 more stamp.)
- Will we be finished then? - Something's strange.
- Ji Hyo and Haha are out. - What?
- We have to hurry. - We were right about that team.
(Team Yoon Bak must be after our name tags.)
Guys.
(In the hallway right next to them...)
(is Team Yoon Bak.)
At the end.
(They can sense somebody coming.)
Not there.
At the end.
- We have no other choice. - Who's there?
(Should we check it out?)
(They're about to run into Team Sandara.)
Let's get on the elevator. Hurry.
Hurry up. Let's go.
(They get on the elevator.)
Let's go.
- Get on the elevator. - Come.
(Can you help us complete our mission?)
(Dashing)
- Hurry. Go. - Let's go.
- Go. Go first. - Let's go.
Go. Go first.
- Go down. - Hey.
Go. You have to go.
Go in the elevator.
- Go, Sandara. - Don't let her go.
(Go, Sandara.)
- Help me. - He's out.
- Hey. - What's this about?
- Go down. - This doesn't make sense.
- Bak. - Go down.
Hurry, Kwang Soo!
(She's anxious.)
What do I do?
I got separated from my team again.
(I'll get my revenge.)
I have to survive.
We must get rid of...
- these villains. - Kwang Soo.
We're the villains. We're the villains.
- How could you? - Go away.
- You villains. - Hey.
- You villains. - We're the good people.
We're the good people.
- We're the good people. - What's going on?
Why didn't you rip Sandara's name tag?
- Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
There's Sandara and Jae Suk left.
(Only Sandara and Jae Suk are left.)
Come here, Bak!
(Now, everybody knows Team Yoon Bak's mission.)
Bak.
Use it. Hurry. Where's the Death Note?
Where's the Death Note?
(Death Note?)
If you use all of them,
you get a Death Note.
(They get a Death Note for three VIP tickets.)
(They obtained the Death Note.)
There you go.
- Why aren't you taking it? - Please take it.
Let's rip Jong Kook's name tag...
and keep this for later.
(They planned to get rid of Jong Kook first.)
I'm getting goosebumps.
I can't help but smile while I'm saying this.
What's going on with me?
Use it. Hurry up.
- Where's the Death Note? - Seok Jin has it.
- Seok Jin... - Seok Jin.
Seok Jin.
Seok Jin!
Where is he?
- What is it? - Use it!
(They finally find him.)
- Hey. - Seok Jin!
Hey.
Sandara...
is about to win.
- Do you remember the stamp? - Use it.
- They're trying to do something. - Sandara... Listen.
Jong Kook and Jae Seok...
- helped Sandara escape. - Right.
They were so calm.
Right, they were.
- Let's use it. - Write her name.
- Sandara. - Do we write her name?
I have no idea where she is.
(They decide to get rid of Sandara.)
We can't even see her.
I wrote her name.
Eliminate her.
Sandara Park is out. Sandara Park is out.
Sandara Park is out.
(What? I'm out?)
- We just have to eliminate Jae Suk. - I'm so tired.
We just have to eliminate him.
(He's looking for the Secret Room.)
Hold on.
(He finds a suspicious emergency exit.)
(Peeking)
(He finally finds it.)
(What hint does he find?)
"A car that cries and twinkles".
I think I've seen this before.
Should we split?
- Should we? - It doesn't matter, right?
Let's split and look for him.
- Sure. - Let's go.
This place is too big to stay together.
- I'll check out that side... - Sure.
where the airbags are.
(Where could he be?)
Where can he be?
(Sliding)
Be quiet.
(He's in this alone.)
(I will survive until the end.)
(He darts in and out of places.)
I have no idea where he is.
"A car that cries and twinkles".
What can that be?
(What on earth is it?)
(What's over there?)
(Roaring)
(Fourth hint spot: a car that cries and twinkles)
Twinkling...
and crying.
(He starts searching the car.)
Okay.
(He finds the hint.)
(What does the last hint say?)
(The true Supercar is outside.)
(It's outside?)
Outside.
Is this the key to the Supercar?
(He takes the mini key...)
(and heads outside to look for the true Supercar.)
Supercar.
(He's almost there.)
First floor.
(Will he be able to find it?)
- Let's go. - He's done.
It's so big. We can't find him.
Where's Jae Suk? How do we find him?
What's this?
(What's this on the floor?)
"The true Supercar..."
(They find the hint that was left behind.)
(What if this is Team Jae Suk's hint?)
- What's this? - Someone left it behind.
Maybe they're running away on the supercar.
He's outside.
- He's outside. - Let's go.
- Bak, go outside. - Outside.
Let's go outside.
(Bak sprints outside.)
(Gazing)
(There's nobody here, right?)
(Who's there?)
Who's that?
Seok Jin!
(Their last target, Jae Suk, is spotted.)
(They win if they rip his name tag.)
Seok Jin!
(Their prey is in front of them.)
- Why did you come here? - Seok Jin.
Why did you come here?
(Why is Jae Suk so fast?)
(He slips away.)
There must be a way.
Seok Jin!
Kwang Soo.
Hey, how do we go outside?
(Jae Suk reaches outside without getting caught.)
- Go outside. - There he is.
(Every second makes a difference.)
(Will he get the hint first?)
- What are you doing? - Wait.
(Or will they get his name tag?)
Catch him.
(Ripping)
(Jae Suk is out.)
I'm sorry.
- Have we completed our mission? - We're done.
You did all the running, Bak.
(Team Yoon Bak completes their mission.)
We ripped everybody's name tag.
- We did. - We did.
- Did you rip everybody's name tags? - Yes.
Team Yoon Bak is the winner.
- And then? - However...
"However"?
Team Sandara also wins.
What's going on?
(But we eliminated everybody.)
(While Sandara was looking for her last mission,)
(Team Yoon Bak was looking for Seok Jin to use the Death Note.)
Seok Jin.
(Thanks to Seok Jin's absence,)
(Sandara completed her mission first.)
(This must be a dream.)
You were the villain.
You found the ginseng before you were eliminated,
- right? - Yes.
You found the ginseng before you were eliminated, right?
Yes.
You have completed your mission.
(Team Jae Suk was eliminated, but they still completed their mission.)
- My goodness. - My gosh.
What about us?
(While Team Yoon Bak was looking for Jae Suk)
Kwang Soo.
Hey, how do we go outside?
(Jae Suk found the Supercar first.)
I have to open this.
(Team Jae Suk completed their mission.)
(Jackpot)
(He's happy.)
- What? - It's over.
- What's over? - It's over.
You finished last...
after Jae Suk completed his mission.
(They came in last.)
So...
We're in last place?
We have to pick one person from your team.
Kwang Soo told me this earlier.
- He did. - He's never had...
a water bomb.
That's why...
- I recommend him. - I'll survive.
- I'll survive. - Really?
I think he'll get the water bomb for the first time.
- Kwang Soo. - Let's go. What?
- No, don't listen to him. - He's never done it before.
- Let's go. - It's one try.
It's one try.
(The roulette is spinning.)
(This is the worst that can happen for Team Yoon Bak.)
Please...
(Who'll be the unlucky person to receive the water bomb?)
(It's Bak.)
(Bak saved us.)
This is unbelievable.
How could it be?
It's Bak. He's so unlucky.
- Thank you. - He ripped everybody's name tags.
(Bak will receive the penalty today.)
I feel so bad for him.
- He ended up in the wrong team. - Exactly.
He worked so hard.
I think the universe was on my side.
- I had a great time. - We were so close.
Remember what I said? Bak always tries his best,
- but other teams don't like him. - He's slightly...
- annoying. - I agree.
Look at him.
Look at him. That's what I'm talking about.
Let's go!
- Is he in the center? - Yes.
(The water bomb is ready.)
I hate it.
It's coming.
(The water bomb goes off.)
It makes you bow, right?
(That would get rid of all the fine dust.)
(He's still got so much energy left in him.)
- Excellent. - We had...
Sandara, Jae Suk, and Bak join us today.
Thank you for trying your best and enjoying your time here.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Let us introduce two new Running Man members.)
(Next week, Jeon So Min and Yang Se Chan will join Running Man.)
(3 days before the article was published)
(The staff hid cameras for the interview.)
(Here's camera 1.)
(This is camera 2.)
(Moments later)
- Hello. - Hello.
(This new member must be a fashionista.)
- Sorry for asking to meet so early. - It's okay.
I'm happy...
about eating.
(So Min is the 1st new member.)
What do you think about joining us?
Can I join if I want to?
Your opinion matters the most. If you say no, we'll just eat.
When I first got the call,
I said yes...
and asked, "How many candidates are ahead of me?"
I had to move up the line...
so...
female candidates would have to either get married or be pregnant.
I was wondering how far I was on the list.
(She can't believe she's being asked to join.)
I'm worried because I'm not good at anything.
I'm not smart.
I've never done a sit-up in my life.
- Not even 1? - I can't even do 1.
I run 100m in 21 seconds.
That's slow.
I'm sorry to say this but that's fast for me.
I can sense how innocent you are.
Thank you, but I'm not that innocent.
I am actually quite dirty.
(She makes a surprising confession.)
- Right? - Are you like that?
(When was her first kiss?)
(It was at a bus station when I was 21.)
(That's so romantic.)
(It was after the last bus left. Her first kiss was unexpected.)
(It was her first kiss so how was it?)
(It was my first kiss. I thought I'd hear bells ringing.)
(I only remember the smell of his saliva.)
(You were supposed to talk about the kiss, not the saliva.)
(So Min is honest and random.)
I'm not very...
(She confesses.)
I'm not very comfortable being on variety shows.
I find it difficult.
(She finds variety shows difficult?)
(They play a game to find out about each other's preferences.)
(When I'm in a relationship, I'm the one who usually gets dumped.)
(Kwang Soo says no?)
(Does he usually dump girls then?)
(We know you always get dumped.)
(My ex-girlfriend was cheating on me so I asked her to break up.)
(That's getting dumped.)
(You got dumped.)
(How's that getting dumped?)
(You were betrayed from the beginning.)
(I dumped her!)
(How many times has So Min dated?)
(3 times)
(How many times were you dumped?)
(2 times)
(Why is everybody so quiet?)
(Sorry for asking about your breakups.)
(Did you dump the last one?)
(He cheated on her but she refused to break up with him.)
(Stop it.)
(She got dumped 2 times, and the last one cheated on her.)
(You told Kwang Soo being cheated on was getting dumped.)
(You got dumped all three times.)
(He's the female version of Kwang Soo.)
(We both got kicked around.)
(I asked him to come back to me, and he said no.)
(I tried that too, and she told me to get lost.)
(Kwang Soo's spot in Running Man is being threatened.)
(And...)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Here's the other new member.)
(It's Se Chan.)
What are you good at?
I rarely lose when playing games.
You know arcade games?
I can beat every celebrity.
I heard Jae Seok is the king of ddakji,
but I'm also pretty good.
Can you beat Jong Kook in games?
Of course.
I can beat him as long as it doesn't require strength.
(He's beyond Jong Kook when it comes to games.)
(Here's a sneak peek of his skills.)
(You must provide irrelevant answers to the questions.)
(What do you want to say to your new girlfriend?)
(Southern ape)
(Dear girlfriend. It's nice to meet you, Southern ape.)
(You can't call your girlfriend so.)
(How's this irrelevant?)
(He might end up meeting a woman who looks primitive.)
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
(I'll show you how to play this game.)
- Where do you itch? - My knee hurts.
- What is your nickname? - Strawberry.
(His official nickname is strawberry.)
(He said he was good at games. He's Strawberry Yang.)
(He's embarrassed.)
(You are the same as your brother.)
(The Yang brothers are all talk.)
(Your brother lost in everything on Saturday.)
(Don't make fun of my brother. He's good at games.)
(Don't make fun of my brother.)
(The Yang brothers have a close bond.)
(Somebody unexpected shows up.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(His brother, Se Hyung, shows up.)
(He calls his brother to see his reaction.)
- Hello? - It's me.
- Where are you? - I'm on a radio show.
I'm in SBS for a short meeting.
Can you come by when you're done?
Sure. I'll come over when I'm done.
- Is this confirmed? - Yes.
(That's incredible.)
- Really? - Yes.
My brother is better than me in many things.
He's funnier than me,
so I knew he'll get lucky like me...
but I didn't know it'd be this fast.
(He's embarrassed.)
You're already working with Jae Seok and Haha,
so is there anything you'd like to tell your brother about them?
I don't know exactly either,
but from what I feel,
Jae Seok...
always goes around and asks each person a question.
Make sure you think of an answer beforehand.
If you can't think of one...
Let's say you're Jae Seok and I'm you.
If you can't think of anything,
then do this.
"What do you think? I see."
(He looks away.)
I don't think he'll like that.
I looked in his direction...
(Pretend like Jae Seok is Medusa.)
- Then he won't ask. - He won't?
- When you're not ready? - Yes, he knows.
But if you're ready to answer his question...
"Let me ask you a question."
(Staring)
- "Would you like to say something?" - "I..."
(Make eye contact with Jae Seok.)
Look at him when I'm ready...
- and when I'm not... - Look away.
- It works. - Really?
On the other hand, Haha...
is very fashionable.
So if there's a cap,
ask, "What's this?"
(Look interested.)
- Then he starts explaining. - Like where it came from?
(Keep fidgeting with it.)
If you say it's pretty and look in the mirror,
- he asks if you want one. - Really?
You have to say no.
Then he'll buy you one.
(He'll buy you one if you say no.)
(It's so easy getting gifts from Haha.)
- I got it. - It's a secret.
That's a great tip.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- Thank you. - No problem.
(His lecture finishes.)
I'll try my best and run to the best of my ability.
I'll stomp everyone who gets in my way.
(My determination)
I don't know. Variety shows are scary for me.
"Would this be funny?"
"I've seen this a lot."
"Can I try again?"
My goodness.
Thank you for recruiting me.
(So Min and Se Chan are coming soon.)
(And next week)
(It's a dangerous tourist spot you must visit before you die.)
(Global Race)
(New experience)
(New chemistry)
(Next week, the new Running Man will be coming.)