(Spring is here.)
(Hangang Park is filled with the scent of flowers.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - It's a carpet.
(The 6 members are as bright as the weather.)
- Hello. - What is this?
- Each stool has a name on it. - Okay.
- Please sit on your stool. - Okay.
- They do have names on them. - It looks luxurious.
(The members are welcomed by five kinds of bite-size food.)
I've been feeling hungry.
- It's eel and small octopus. - It's eel.
- I love small octopus. - It's braised spicy chicken.
- Which one? - The second one.
- Is this chicken? - I love braised spicy chicken.
Last week, we asked you to recommend...
your favorite restaurants that would perk up your appetite.
What each of you is seeing on your table is...
food from the restaurants recommended by the other members.
Try them all...
and pick your three favorites.
- Three? - After trying them all?
It's a blind test. Put aside your favorites quietly.
- Are we supposed to remain quiet? - Is it a blind test?
- Try them all and pick three? - Right now?
One is spicy, and the other is salty.
- It tastes good. - I'm done.
- Pick three? - It has potatoes too.
- It's very spicy. - I've picked three.
I have to choose this one.
- I've picked three. - This one has to be included.
- I'm done. - I'm done.
(The blind test is over.)
It tasted very good.
Is the food really from the restaurants?
- Yes. - From the restaurants?
I'm sure mine will be popular.
- 4 restaurants have been chosen. - 4?
Two restaurants share the first place.
(Which restaurants won the most votes?)
They're Seok Jin and Haha's picks.
- See? - Which ones are they?
(Seok Jin's place offers Korean soul food, braised spicy chicken.)
(Haha's place offers spicy and sweet stir-fried small octopus.)
- I knew it. - I loved the sauce.
And Jong Kook and Kwang Soo share the second place.
Yes!
(Jong Kook's place offers health food, roasted eel.)
(Kwang Soo's place offers bulgogi stew.)
- We'll visit these four. - Okay.
Today's race is called Running Man's Food Guide.
- What? - "Running Man's Food Guide"?
- It sounds nice. - "Running Man's Food Guide"?
It'd be so nice to have good food in the spring.
Running Man's Food Guide starts now.
The food you'll get to try has...
some secrets in it.
(The food has secrets in it.)
- What secrets? - Secrets?
The team who finds out the secrets first will win.
(What's the delicious secret?)
Today, two guests who specialize in food shows...
will join the game.
- Do we have guests? - Where are they?
- Guests, please come in. - Who are they?
(The guests will join the members on the gourmet tour.)
- Bo Mi. - Min Yong.
- What's with your sunglasses? - It's been so long.
- Hello. - What are you doing here?
(Let us introduce today's guests to you.)
(They appear on shows just to eat.)
(They've been waiting for this moment.)
(They're perfect guests for the gourmet tour.)
(Food shows are their specialty.)
- Hello. - Hello.
SBS, Seoul Broadcasting System...
(Seoul Broadcasting System?)
As I'm on Running Man today, I'm wearing running shoes.
I thought I'd be running around. I'm wearing a comfortable outfit.
Haha rediscovered you, right?
I don't know what he did, but that's not true.
I'd like to put this straight.
Haha didn't rediscover me. I was just worried about him,
so I made a comeback after a 10-year break.
(15 years ago)
(Haha and Min Yong appeared in a comedy together.)
- Haha, you've got mail. - Mail?
(Min Yong made Haha a star.)
Haha could become a star...
- thanks to Min Yong. - What are you talking about?
- He's like your mother. - I passed the audition.
Min Yong gave birth to Haha,
and I raised him.
I created him.
- What about my parents? - Jae Seok...
- My parents raised me with love. - I'm talking right now.
- I'm talking. - Right, you're our guest today.
In addition to Min Yong, Bo Mi is here.
It's been so long.
- I'm here to eat. - Really?
- You lost so much weight. - I'm gaining some back.
- It's time to gain some back. - Is it an off-season?
- Yes, it is. - I see.
She's the first female singer who showed off her double chin.
- That's right. - Look at that.
- A lot of it has disappeared. - That's true.
- It's a shame a lot of it is gone. - You look like a toad.
- I'll come back when I have more. - I love Bo Mi.
Min Yong, have you ever met Bo Mi before?
No. This is the first time.
(This is the first time.)
What?
- Nice to meet you. - Are you serious?
Wouldn't "Flaming Youth" suit Min Yong better?
I'll appear on that one soon too.
(He's set for that too.)
- Really? - Are you serious?
- He sounds like an old man. - He's like a hermit.
- He lived in a mountain. - Really?
He was like this even when he was young.
I still look young. I've only just started.
I think it'll be an extraordinary episode.
Are we going to be divided into two teams?
The guests will be given...
very useful hints for the final mission.
- Really? - The guests are given hints.
Let's play a game to decide the teams.
The guests will eat something behind a blind. You have to guess...
- what they're eating. - Is that possible?
- And the guest will be ours? - I love both.
Bo Mi loves food.
It's possible for one team to take both guests.
- Really? - Really?
That's nice.
(Which team will win?)
(Team Jae Seok and Team Jong Kook)
Min Yong will go in...
and eat the food.
The team that guesses it right will take him.
Min Yong's outfit is not appropriate for the show.
Min Yong, aren't your pants too short?
- What? - Aren't your pants too short?
- Aren't they shorts? - They're capri pants.
Park Jin Young wore them when he sang, "I Have a Girl".
Ready.
(The games starts.)
- I can see something. - I can't see anything.
Oh, my.
- Is it something tasty? - It looks tasty.
Is it one of the dishes we tried?
This is too heavy to have in the morning.
(Gimbap)
(With various kinds of vegetables, gimbap is very nutritious.)
I know what food he likes.
- Try it. - Try it.
- It's very fresh. - Okay.
You can find this at the fish market.
(Gimbap at the fish market?)
- Really? - It's lobster.
- Wrong. - It's crab.
- Wrong. - It's seafood stew.
- What are you doing? - It's sashimi.
- Wrong. - He's supposed to eat it.
- You should show us. - Open your mouth.
- Open your mouth. - You should show us.
- Eat it. - Good.
(She continuously opens it.)
- Does it taste good? - His mouth is full.
It's very delicious.
- It's absolutely delicious. - Ji Hyo, don't you see it?
I can't see anything.
- Give me a piggyback. - Don't leave it open for too long.
(Jae Seok is on Seok Jin's back.)
- At the Grand Canyon, - Grand Canyon?
- I ate this on the trail. - I've never been there.
- Grand Canyon? - Show us the food.
I'm eating it right now.
- How much does it cost? - What?
Whatever you call is the price.
- I know. - The price must fluctuate.
What do you mean the price is up to the seller?
It's steamed snow crab.
(Your answer is far off.)
- Haha, you're wrong. - I have the answer!
It's ray sea bream.
- What? - What did you say?
There's no such fish named that. You meant black sea bream.
- It's black sea bream. - Let him have it.
- The answer is black sea bream. - Hey.
- How could you say that? - The answer is shark's fin.
- Shark's fin? - Yes, it's shark's fin.
(They are far from the correct answer.)
In fact, you can consider this to be one of our national food.
- Really? - His mouth is full with that food.
The answer is gimbap.
- That's correct. - Is it really gimbap?
(Kwang Soo gets the right answer.)
You're telling me that people sell gimbap at Grand Canyon?
- Seriously? - How did you know it was gimbap?
- You said it's from a fish market! - How did you figure it out?
- Yes! - No way.
(The answer is gimbap.)
- The red thing was carrot. - I see.
- It was gimbap. - I can't believe it.
- I did have gimbap at Grand Canyon. - Really?
Min Yong, you can join Team Jong Kook.
(Min Yong joins Team Jong Kook after all.)
- I feel like I just got an old man. - We should've gotten him.
- We were supposed to recruit him. - Right. We were supposed to.
Can we take the guest from the other team?
- We have to bring Bo Mi now. - That's right.
- We can also recruit Bo Mi too. - The second...
- Hey, we ought to bring Bo Mi. - You shouldn't be so greedy.
Jae Seok. We must recruit Bo Mi. We really have to get her.
- We have to get this one right. - Let's do this.
- Let's get this right. - All right.
Please reveal the second dish that Bo Mi will eat.
- Bo Mi. - Let us see your reaction to it.
- Bo Mi. - This looks delicious.
- Talk to us. - Stay quiet.
- If you join Jong Kook's team... - You must join our team, Bo Mi.
- I haven't had this for a while. - What?
- Really? - Do you like this dish?
- Min Yong, let us see her. - Do female idol singers eat that?
- Who? - Female idol singers.
- Can they eat that? - Well...
It must be this if she hasn't had if for a while.
- I haven't had this for a while. - This isn't on her diet then.
You can eat this with your hands.
It's similar to Indian food.
- There he goes again. - He's lying again.
Why are you lying?
I had this in Mumbai.
Min Yong. Let us see her a bit.
- A bit more. - This is your hint.
I will give you another hint.
It's called white food.
- What did you say? - I said this is white food.
- Did you say "white" or "fight"? - I said "white".
I have the answer!
- It's dumpling. - That's incorrect.
- He said it's white. - That was close.
- I have the answer! - I got it!
- I yelled first. - It's dim sum.
- Goodness. - Dim sum.
- He said it first. - Yes!
What is your answer, Haha?
- It's dim sum. - It wasn't his turn.
It was my turn.
- He said it first. - The answer is dim sum.
- It's dim sum. - No, Haha yelled out first.
- I really did call out first. - It's spelled...
(You're so greedy. Why are you doing this to us?)
- Do rock-paper-scissors to settle. - He said, "dim sum".
- He said, "dim sum". - All right. Then...
- Let's do rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors?
- The winning team can answer first. - But we were first.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - All right. He won.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - I lost.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - I won!
What is the answer?
(Seok Jin earns the opportunity to say his answer first.)
- It's dim sum. - That's incorrect.
(Incorrect!)
What are you doing? It's not dim sum?
(It wasn't correct?)
- What did you say? - What did you make us play then?
- Hey. - He's doing his job well.
Why did you do that? I'm so annoyed.
Pulling pranks is my area of expertise.
- You're making me mad. - I will give you a crucial hint.
There are two kinds of this food.
You have to be fast for this.
- Fertilized and unfertilized. - I have the answer!
I know the answer! I got it.
- I figured it out. - What is it?
Be quiet.
What are you doing?
- Stop that. - Go over there.
- Why? Tell us. - Go and stay there.
- Tell us the answer. - What is it?
- What is the answer? - Get lost.
It's boiled egg.
(Ji Hyo's answer is boiled egg.)
That's correct!
(Ji Hyo gets it right.)
- That's it. Bo Mi. Come to us. - Come on.
Why would you eat this in Mumbai though?
- Boiled eggs are sold in India too. - Let's switch.
- Is there a chance to switch him? - In Mumbai...
Can you give us a chance to switch him out?
- Let us switch. - Please let us!
- No, you can't! - I can't work with him.
I'm not going to be in this then!
- Let us change the guests. - He's really unhappy about that.
- Let us switch. - You can't do that.
- I can't work with him. - It's not that we don't like him.
- We just want to work with Bo Mi. - If you insist...
- You can't do that. - What about us then?
- I'm begging you. Just this once. - I won't work if you don't let us!
- I will take care of Jong Kook. - We are happy with Bo Mi.
- I will do whatever you want. - We are happy with Bo Mi.
How can I handle Jong Kook and Min Yong together?
- Switch guests! - This isn't right.
- We like Min Yong. - Right. Min Yong is great.
- How about this? Let's do this. - All right.
- Let Bo Mi choose her team. - Right. Let her pick.
- She can join the team she wants. - All right.
Will she want a younger or older team?
Can we do that?
(Bo Mi, join the younger team.)
What do you want to do?
- Choose one team. - Well...
- Bo Mi. Do you want to stay or go? - We starred on a show together.
- Bo Mi. - We have our own chat room.
- We really do, Bo Mi. - Which team do you want?
- Me? - Bo Mi, everyone here is young.
- I like both teams. - All right.
- Come to our team, Bo Mi! - Will you be okay?
- Bo Mi! - I'll switch since they're younger.
That's right!
(They complete trading the guests.)
- Come here. - Welcome, Min Yong.
(Laughing)
It doesn't matter if we lose now.
That's it.
In our team, you can play the role of Kwang Soo.
- Did you get that? - You are tall too.
- And... - He's tall too.
- Ji Hyo can play Bo Mi's role. - I'm excited.
Just because I'm tall, I don't act like him.
"Like him"?
- What do you mean by that? - He's complicated.
(Being tall and unlucky at the same time is complicated.)
- Unbelievable. - He's tall indeed.
Today, you'll visit restaurants recommended by the members.
You will have to unravel the secrets along the way.
A team game will decide the winning and losing team at each restaurant.
The winning team will earn benefits as well as hints.
We will start "Running Man's Food Guide" now. Let us begin!
(They set out to dig up the secrets.)
This is nice.
(They'll try braised spicy chicken, small octopus, eel, and bulgogi.)
What should we eat first?
- I picked this restaurant. - Where?
- Is this one in Samseong-dong? - It's bulgogi.
This is bulgogi, but this isn't your regular bulgogi.
(It's a classy transformation of bulgogi.)
We can grill it on this.
This is similar to shabu shabu.
Look. That looks delicious.
- This looks tasty. - Bulgogi...
Kwang Soo often goes to this restaurant.
- He takes girls there on a date. - Look at that.
- That's how he knows... - What are you saying?
- a lot of good restaurants. - No, I just like delicious food.
The girls who went there with him must feel betrayed...
- What are you saying? - when they watch this.
- How many girls did you take there? - I bet there are at least four...
- girls who went there with him. - It's not true. Don't be mistaken.
- Don't be mistaken. - I got my hair done at a salon.
What?
(What did you say that out of the blue?)
- I mean... - Let me tell you about him.
- He only thinks about himself. - He was touching my hair.
- Does he have his own show? - He only thinks about himself.
This camera is filming Bo Mi and me together.
I thought we could have our own conversation.
I haven't seen anyone pull up the collar since my school teacher.
Really. Not that many people do this.
People pull up their collar not to get the back of their neck tanned.
That's why gym teachers do this...
- since they stay outdoor a lot. - He even curled it a bit.
- He was a gym teacher on a sitcom. - There's a reason why we have this.
He does look like a PE teacher though.
- He played a role of a gym teacher. - Right, he does look like one.
- I can't stop playing that role. - He was...
You can't stop playing it? Stop exaggerating.
He's still in the process of assimilating into the present.
(They are on the way to the first course.)
(Kwang Soo's choice in Samseong-dong, Gangnam)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Look at this. - Hello.
(It's the perfect pair of vegetables and beef.)
- Hello. - This is similar to shabu shabu.
- This is shabu shabu. - Goodness.
- What is this? - This looks great.
(The first restaurant of the tour guide)
- It's bulgogi. - This looks delicious.
- This bulgogi looks different. - It will be so tasty.
- They won't give it to all of us. - Is that it?
The first restaurant of "Running Man's Food Guide" is...
a bulgogi stew restaurant...
- recommended by Kwang Soo. - This is excellent.
It is the restaurant that Kwang Soo came with the lady he was dating.
No, it's not true. I didn't.
- The owner will know. - It's not that.
This place is famous for beef soup...
- and bulgogi as well. - Beef soup?
The bulgogi meat is like a round ball.
I think this is very unique.
You can pop it into your mouth at once.
I am going to be impartial when I review the food.
I'm confident about the food.
The winning team of the game will only...
(Only the winning team will eat.)
eat the food.
The game you will play at this restaurant is...
that I will show you an enlarged picture of a dish...
- We have to guess the dish, right? - Right. You have to guess it.
- It's a dish? - Yes.
- It won't be easy. - I am an expert.
There is a special buzzer for this game.
To ring the buzzer, you have to get the other team to talk.
(The buzzer is the opponent's voice.)
Can I hit their vocal cord?
How could you say that?
The opponent's voice will be the buzzer.
(The team that wins 2 rounds out of 3 will win the game.)
Please select one player from each team.
Whom should we pick?
We must show our strength in the first round. You must play.
- No. - Should Bo Mi go first?
- Me? - Why don't you go first, Bo Mi?
Bo Mi is first?
(Bo Mi will play first.)
Then Seok Jin will play.
- Seriously? - Why are you doing that to us?
- He doesn't go easy on women. - I won't go easy on you.
- It's so big. - He only...
- He only cares about winning. - I won't go easy on you.
I don't know anything about Apink.
(Round 1, Bo Mi versus Seok Jin)
- Here is the first question. - All right.
(What is this dish?)
- What is this? - Can't you recognize it right away?
(What is that red thing?)
- Shall I give you a hint? - Please do so.
The hint is kimchi.
- Get ready. - There are a lot of sesame.
- Start! - Really?
(Pinching hard)
(Their passion to ring the buzzer is tremendous.)
Look. Seok Jin is clenching his teeth.
(Pulling)
(They will answer the question first when the opponent makes a sound.)
- Bo Mi is really trying too. - She is.
Both of them are playing this wholeheartedly.
Bo Mi is no joke too.
(She doesn't go easy on him.)
(Pinching)
(He targets her lower jaw which is her weak spot.)
Bo Mi, show your taekwondo moves.
Bo Mi, kick him!
- Kick him. - That's right.
Attack him.
(They struggle.)
(Let go of my hair.)
(She pulls out a chunk of his hair.)
(Each strand of hair is precious at his age.)
Bo Mi pulled out his hair.
(Seok Jin cries without a sound.)
What happened?
- You pulled out so much. - Bo Mi.
(It's not like she can implant the hair back.)
Go and wash your hands. What's this?
(Seok Jin can't take back his hair.)
- Bo Mi's hands are dirty. - Bo Mi.
- Her hands are dirty. - That's a lot of hair.
(Her hands are dirty.)
Go and wash your hands.
- Use wet tissue. - Do you have wet tissue?
- Did her hands get dirty? - Yes.
(She exposed his scalp by force.)
(I still didn't make any sound.)
- Bo Mi, use taekwondo. - Kick him.
Just kick him.
You can do it, Bo Mi.
- Let's take turns. - Take turns?
- You can do it, Bo Mi. - Let's take turns.
- Okay. - Take turns in hitting.
(Don't worry.)
- Okay. - What?
(She kicks him hard.)
(She attacks him with her leg.)
(Everyone gives a standing ovation.)
(He's completely embarrassed.)
Bo Mi gets her turn first.
- She goes first. - Good job.
(Bo Mi is good at taekwondo.)
(They all feel pity on him.)
- She goes first. - Good job.
(Seok Jin loses.)
She's good at kicking.
- Go ahead. - She's charming.
- Go, Bo Mi. - She's awesome.
(He gives in.)
- It's Bo Mi's turn. - Go ahead.
It's your turn, Bo Mi.
(What could it be?)
- Do you know the answer? - In 5, 4...
Kimchi is the hint.
(It's a dish made with kimchi.)
It's kimchi jeon.
(Is it a photo of kimchi jeon?)
That's correct.
(Bo Mi is correct.)
Is that kimchi jeon?
Good job.
- Really? - It's kimchi jeon.
- Right. - It looks like stew.
- Bo Mi. - It's oily.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Are you sure? I'm sorry.
Next up is Min Yong.
- I'm okay. - Come on, Min Yong.
Haha is up next.
(It's a match between Min Yong and Haha.)
(Round 2, Haha versus Min Yong)
Here's the photo.
(It's the second question.)
(What kind of dish is this?)
Hey.
(He reaches out.)
(Haha suddenly attacks Min Yong's private part.)
What are you doing?
(The two old men play like children.)
It'll be blurred on TV.
(They can't help but look.)
(He locks his head angrily.)
(Haha laughs.)
- Haha made a sound. - I heard it.
It's Min Yong's turn.
I endured it for too long.
My goodness.
Go ahead, Min Yong.
(His best friend has given him unspeakable pain.)
How could he endure that?
Min Yong, are you okay?
(He doesn't know how to explain the pain he's in.)
- Are you okay? - Min Yong.
- Min Yong, are you okay? - How did you endure it?
It looked too painful to stay silent.
Are you okay? You look pale.
I'm not even married yet.
Gosh, how did he endure the pain?
I pinched it hard.
You look exactly like your mother.
Long time no see.
- I hope all goes well. - Ma'am?
You look exactly like her.
(Min Yong gets his turn.)
- What's the answer? - Let me take a break.
- I can't calm down. - Go.
- Just answer it. - I almost got it.
That's easy.
- My answer is raw octopus. - That's right.
- Raw octopus? - Yes.
(Is it correct?)
(He's correct.)
That's correct.
- That was easy. - It was.
It was too easy.
- It's too bad. - The answer was obvious.
Are you okay?
I need to use the restroom.
- Are you bleeding? - I think so.
(It feels warm in his pants.)
(Next is Jong Kook versus Jae Seok.)
- Jae Seok. - This is the final round.
- Is it the final round? - You can do it.
I bet it'll be difficult.
Here's the photo.
(It's the third question.)
(What kind of dish is this?)
(Jae Seok attacks.)
(He bites.)
(Jong Kook starts to warm up.)
He's in trouble.
(Jong Kook throws him.)
- The real fight starts now. - Hey.
He made a sound.
Come on. You can't do this.
He can't throw me against the wall.
What is it?
Aren't they rice cakes?
(Can they be rice cakes?)
It's incorrect.
(Jae Seok is happy.)
(Did you step on my foot?)
(He laughs out loud.)
(Jong Kook gets his turn again.)
Gosh, I don't believe it.
(What could it be?)
Just answer it since it'll always be your turn.
- That's right. - This is annoying.
Is it mandu?
(It's something white and mysterious.)
(Can it be mandu instead of rice cakes?)
- That's correct. - What?
(Jong Kook gets it right.)
- How can it be mandu? - We won.
(Jong Kook answers the most difficult question.)
- It's mandu. - Goodness.
- We won. - It's obviously mandu.
I thought it was rice.
(This is the actual photo.)
(Jong Kook's team gets to taste the bulgogi.)
- Shall we start? - Is it ready to eat?
- Yes. - Thank you.
(Boiling broth and moist meat create the best harmony.)
That's how you eat it.
It's quite unique.
(What's the secret hidden in this dish?)
(Blowing)
(She opens her mouth wide.)
Don't pretend to be considerate.
- Thank you. - Help yourselves.
(Isn't it delicious?)
Is that rice?
(He tastes some seasoned raw beef.)
It's really delicious.
Don't be disappointed that you can't eat it.
(He makes fun of the others.)
My goodness.
Gosh.
(Is it delicious?)
It smells so good.
Here you go.
What's this?
It's an avocado.
Isn't that an avocado?
(Why is there an avocado?)
- Do we share it? - Yes.
Take a bite each.
It's like butter from a tree.
- Is that so? - Yes.
(Avocado is a soft fruit with a lot of vitamins.)
(They can't help but look at the bulgogi.)
May I get a bite after Bo Mi kicks me again?
Sure, go ahead.
(Do I have to kick him again?)
Jae Seok, take a bite.
(He offers a bite to Jae Seok.)
(Her kick could even break your leg.)
Bo Mi.
(Is getting a kick worth it to taste some bulgogi?)
You can get two pieces.
Really? That sounds good.
(Everyone wants to get kicked.)
What are you doing?
My legs can't function properly today anyway.
(He's already given up on his lower body.)
You'll find out after getting kicked.
Do you promise to give us two pieces?
- How about this side? - Yes, two pieces.
She's smart.
(She takes her pose.)
I have red belt in taekwondo.
(She kicks.)
(She kicks him hard.)
(Min Yong's determination for bulgogi deserves respect.)
- I'm really sorry. - Min Yong is in pain.
You can eat now.
- Bo Mi can kick. - Please eat.
Think about something else.
Bo Mi's kicks are impressive.
Jae Seok seems nervous.
- To be honest, I'm scared. - Go ahead.
- He looks scared. - Try it.
She moves forward as she kicks.
(Thud)
(Enjoy your bulgogi.)
(He lies down immediately.)
(He trembles in pain.)
(He feels it in his whole body.)
Good job, Bo Mi.
I'll eat Jae Seok's bulgogi.
Goodness.
(Isn't that mine?)
- Why are you eating mine? - It's gone.
Why are you eating?
(You can't taste this bulgogi anywhere else.)
Team Jong Kook wins the first round.
(Team Jong Kook wins.)
Here are the two items related to Food Guide's secret.
You ate rice and barley.
Here are rice and barley.
Are these hints?
Team Jae Seok lost.
- You had an avocado. - Yes.
Here's another avocado.
- The number of items is important. - Really?
(Is the number of items important?)
(Team Jae Seok gets an avocado. Team Jong Kook gets rice and barley.)
Bo Mi.
You must be feeling good since you ate tasty food and relieved stress.
- Yes. - Did you relieve stress?
Bo Mi, you look better.
- You look much better. - You really do.
Was it painful?
I can't walk properly.
(Seok Jin is the most impressed.)
I've never kicked someone so hard.
This can't be your first time.
- No, it really is. - Are you sure?
Are we going to eat again?
I thought she said she'd kick again.
- I misheard her. - He's traumatized.
"Shall I kick you again?"
I think she'll kick you four times minimum.
Bo Mi is making me upset.
- She is. - I like Bo Mi.
(It's a new side of her.)
I like her more than before.
(Which restaurant did Haha recommend?)
Come on, we can win.
(Next is a small octopus restaurant.)
(Haha's choice in Sinsa-dong, Gangnam)
- We've been here a lot. - It was such a long time ago.
- It's been a long time. - The food is delicious.
- There was a long line before. - I've only tried the squid.
- Was there a long wait before? - Yes.
This restaurant is recommended by Haha.
It's the second restaurant for "Running Man's Food Guide".
It's famous for small octopuses.
(It's famous for spicy small octopuses with 28 years of history.)
(It's sweet and spicy small octopus bulgogi.)
This place...
- has been here since the 90s. - It's legendary.
I came here often before.
I used to come here and the sausage stew restaurant often.
People came here a lot.
This time, you first need to enjoy all the bulgogi in front of you.
- Really? - My goodness.
(There's no mission?)
(You're going to let us eat this with no strings attached?)
(It's too good to be true.)
- Can we get some rice? - This goes great with rice.
(They soon forget about being suspicious.)
- Do you know what this is? - This tastes great.
- The sauce tastes great. - It's been so long.
- I haven't had this for so long. - Yes.
- I came here often with Haha. - That's right.
We used to come here with good friends.
I didn't know Min Yong would join us today. I used to eat here with him.
(They were poor, but they were best friends.)
We didn't have enough money to visit anywhere else. It was still fun.
(It's an unforgettable taste.)
- I ran into Jae Seok here a lot. - That's right.
Are you guys going to eat fried rice?
- The sauce tastes incredible. - I agree.
- I love this. - It tastes amazing.
(The sauce tastes spicy at first, but it leaves behind a sweet taste.)
It tastes different from the usual stir-fried squid.
Look. That one's a killer. It's deep-fried squid.
(Here's a dish that will calm down the spiciness.)
I used to eat this a lot too.
My gosh, this deep-fried squid tastes incredible.
(Deep-fried squid is another signature menu of this restaurant.)
I really love this.
(The savory deep-fried squid makes you crave spiciness again.)
But is it really okay for us to eat so carelessly like this?
- Of course. - I'm not trying to be suspicious.
(They finally finish their meal.)
- Did you enjoy your meal? - Yes.
It was amazing.
Then let's start the mission right away.
(We got fooled. There was no way they'd let us eat this for nothing.)
The name of this mission is called, "Consume Your Calories".
- We ate a lot. - "Consume Your Calories".
You can exit this place only after you finish...
burning up all the calories you've absorbed.
(Stir-fried small octopus: 366kcal, Deep-fried squid: 378kcal,)
(Side dishes: 100kcal, Total: 844kcal)
- Okay. - Is that even possible?
(I'm doomed.)
Three people will have to turn on their phones...
by using a manual phone charger.
Then you need to take a selfie with your team members and send it to me.
- Get ready. - Okay.
(Start consuming your calories.)
Ji Hyo, mine will turn on quickly.
(Everyone is busy turning the handle.)
(Powerful)
I'm scared that this will fall off if I turn it too aggressively.
(Their hands are almost invisible.)
Is this charging? Can you check if this is working?
- Mine turned on. - It's working.
(Excited)
- Hurry. - Calm down and keep going.
- It's working. - It turned on.
(Ji Hyo is in charge of calming the whiners.)
- Ji Hyo, this is killing me. - Keep going.
- We only need to turn on one phone. - My gosh, this is so hard.
- My gosh. - We need to take a selfie.
(I can feel...)
(my second ego entering my body.)
(Phone, can you hear me?)
(Just like how Toruk Makto communicates,)
(please hurry up and brighten your screens!)
(Will Kwang Soo be able to awaken the sleeping phones?)
- Keep going. - It's on!
(The phone is on.)
- Hurry. - In 1, 2, 3.
(They need to take a photo and send it to complete their mission.)
(Jong Kook's team succeeds with the first phone.)
- I got one from Jong Kook's team. - I sent it.
- Let's do this. - Keep going.
Hey, look at the camera while you're at it.
- We're almost done. - Everyone, let's take a picture.
(They don't have enough battery.)
- It's on. - My gosh, we need more battery.
(They fail to take a picture.)
- Hurry up. - Give it a try.
- Come on. - Do it with mine.
- No. - Try it now.
(Ji Hyo is suffering because of the whiners.)
(Let's try it with another phone.)
Hurry. Come here.
- Why is it only one percent? - What?
- Hurry up! - We can still take a photo.
(The other phones only have 1 percent battery life.)
(They seem exhausted.)
- Shouldn't it have more battery? - It's weird.
(Is it my turn to show my power?)
(Endless power)
(He's like a human motor.)
(It finally turns on.)
(They even succeed in turning on the camera.)
- It worked! Hurry! - Haha, look here!
In 1, 2, 3.
(Jong Kook's team succeeds again with their second phone.)
(The current score is 2 to 0.)
- Hurry. - We don't have enough battery.
Come on. Turn it faster.
(Did you not see what that team has already achieved?)
- Keep going, you guys. - Ji Hyo, this is really killing me.
Wait.
(He's too exhausted to even sit down properly.)
- This is so hard. - Just a second.
(This team is a group of weaklings.)
(It's on!)
My phone turned on. Hurry up. Min Yong, come here.
(For the first time, they finally turn on the camera.)
- Jae Seok's team sent me one too. - Nice work.
(The current score is 2 to 1.)
- Let's go. - Hurry up.
(Jong Kook's team only has 1 more phone to turn on.)
- Look here. In 1, 2, 3. - Hurry up.
(They pose for victory.)
- We need more battery. - Let's try again.
(This gives Jae Seok's team a golden opportunity.)
- We need more battery. - You guys are really close.
- Hurry up! - I can't do this.
(Use the energy you used to eat the stir-fried small octopus.)
- Take a photo with mine. - No, wait.
- Try it with mine. - Hurry up.
Okay.
(She turns on Seok Jin's camera.)
(They take a photo.)
- We did it. - Hurry up and send it.
(They successfully send their second photo.)
(The current score is 2 to 2.)
- This is driving me crazy. - This is so hard.
(They need to hurry up to beat the other team.)
(They're already done consuming their calories.)
- Hurry up! - My arm hurts!
- Hey, let's just try this. - Screen capture?
(Whispering)
- Be quiet. - Try it.
- Let's send this. - Hurry up.
(Can they successfully take a screen shot?)
- In 1, 2, 3. - How are they taking a picture?
(What are they doing?)
(You won't know even if you see it.)
How do you take a screen shot?
(What is Bo Mi trying to screen shot?)
You just need to press that button.
(They're trying to take a screen shot of a video call screen.)
(You can take a video call even with just one percent battery life.)
Send it. We did it, right?
Let's try...
(Jong Kook's team wins.)
- Bo Mi's so smart. - I'm so happy.
- My goodness. - How did you think of that?
Did they send a photo from another phone?
- No, that's not it. - Is it a different number?
Jong Kook's team screen captured a video call screen and sent it.
(Ta-da)
The video call worked. We captured that.
- She's so smart. - Bo Mi.
- How incredible. - You're so smart, Bo Mi.
Here's something for Jong Kook's team who won.
(Jong Kook's team gets 1 item.)
- This is your second hint. - This is a small octopus.
- The second hint is... - Seafood!
It's alive.
(Rice, barley, and seafood are three very different items.)
- We ate small octopus. - It's alive.
The next place is...
recommended by Jong Kook. It's a restaurant that sells eel.
- I love eel. - Let's go.
("Running Man's Food Guide")
(Braised spicy chicken, eel, small octopus, bulgogi)
(Jong Kook's favorite restaurant is located in Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul.)
(It's a restaurant where you can taste fiery eel.)
I'm looking forward to this dish.
It's different.
- Is it good? - Yes.
(They serve spicy grilled eel and salted grilled eel.)
We will be going to the restaurant recommended by Jong Kook.
The restaurant that sells grilled eel.
The team that gets to the place through public transportation...
- first will be the winner. - Really?
You just need to get there first. You can use the bus or the subway.
- First you need to... - I guess we need to choose.
- My goodness. - Why are you guys picking first?
- But at this hour, the subway... - Let's choose.
(They can only use the transportation they've picked.)
- Yes, we got the subway. - The subway's way better.
- We can let them win at least once. - Sure.
Taking the bus doesn't mean that we'll lose either.
- You can go now. - Let's have a fair start.
- The subway is better right now. - The subway is faster.
- See you later. - Bye.
(They all head to the place recommended by Jong Kook.)
- It's here. - We just need to transfer once.
(They need to check the route first.)
Taking a bus is really comfortable.
We need to find a bus that goes to Yeouido.
(Let's take a bus that goes to Yeouido when we're not sure.)
- I found it. Bus number 362. - Let's take that bus.
Where do we get off?
We need to get off at Yeouido and head to Yeongdeungpo from there.
- Really? - I know you.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I watch your show a lot. - Thank you.
- You even had a cute second child. - Yes, thank you.
(He's embarrassed and grateful.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- The bus is here! - Bus number 362!
- Get on. - It goes to Yeouido, right?
- We need to get to Yeouido first. - Four people?
- We have four people. - Yes.
Thank you.
(We'll soon be there to greet you guys.)
Go to the back.
(The bus departs.)
(Let's be quiet and not cause trouble to others.)
- How many stations should we go? - Just a few stops.
I'm going to give you guys a mission right now.
- In here? - Yes.
(The mission is rock-paper-scissors.)
(After throwing a dice, they need to win the equivalent amount of...)
(games of rock-paper-scissors in a row.)
(If they win, they'll be given a chance to choose a chance card.)
- There are some chance cards. - Okay.
Among the cards, there's a card where you can take the taxi.
(There's a taxi card which will allow them to get there faster.)
- And? - The others are...
two Push-Out Cards and a dud.
(Two Push-Out Cards and a dud)
If you pick a Push-Out Card, the other team has to get off.
Does that mean we might have to get off the bus too?
(It's important to avoid the dud.)
Let's hurry.
(The subway team starts from Apgujeong Station.)
- We're finally running. - Ji Hyo.
Hurry. We don't have much time.
We should go that way.
- We have to go to Chungmuro. - It's this way.
It'll open.
(They'll transfer at Jongno 3-ga.)
I haven't been on the subway in a long time.
- It's coming. - It's coming.
- Do you know where we're going? - Of course.
- Let's get on. - Let's get on.
- How many stops? - Please excuse us.
- It's five stops. - There are many senior citizens.
- Let's keep our voices down. - Hello.
(The subway team heads for their third spot.)
Are we going to do it here?
Let's do it here.
- Ji Hyo. - Who should do it?
(We lost twice in a row. We have only one to rely on.)
Min Yong, do you want to try?
We need one.
- Do we need 1? - Yes, avoid 6.
- This is my first time. - Say, "challenge".
Challenge.
I'll start.
One!
(He throws the die nonchalantly.)
One.
(Is Min Yong lucky or unlucky?)
It's a two.
(They get 2.)
(See?)
- Good. That was amazing. - We got two.
You're very good.
I ranked number two in the forgotten celebrity survey.
- Who was number one? - Goo Bon Seung.
(Goo Bon Seung was number one.)
- We need to win just twice. - He did a great job.
If you win twice in a row, you'll get to pick a card.
- I'll try it as I threw the die. - You try.
You should.
Can you play rock-paper-scissors with him?
What are you going to show?
(The woman happily accepts the challenge.)
- Please. - I'm a man.
(I'm a man, and you know what that means.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Then I'll give you paper.)
(Min Yong fails right away.)
She wants to win of course.
(He underestimated her.)
We should try once again.
- It'll be all right. - Throw the die first.
- I'll throw the die. - We need a one.
(Will a miracle happen?)
- It's a 2. - It's a 2.
Go over there.
Could you play rock-paper-scissors with me?
(The man is puzzled.)
Rock-paper-scissors. Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Jin wins.)
He won.
Thank you.
(Seok Jin is sneaky.)
Can we play rock-paper-scissors?
(He needs to win just one more time.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Will they get to take a taxi to Yeongdeungpo?)
(Will they get to push the other team out of the bus?)
(Will Seok Jin unexpectedly bring victory to his team?)
(Seok Jin wins.)
Nice! You did it!
(Be quiet.)
(They're celebrating silently.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The angels gave Seok Jin hope.)
- I can't believe this. - It's unbelievable.
That was amazing.
- That really was. - Everyone.
As you completed the mission, you get to pick a card.
Min Yong, go ahead.
(Min Yong does not hesitate.)
Min Yong, do a good job. We want a taxi.
(This is his chance to make up for his failure.)
We want a taxi.
(He picks a card without hesitation.)
It's okay as long as it's not a dud.
(There's a 25-percent chance it'll be the taxi.)
(Will Min Yong prove himself?)
(Sighing)
(Dud)
You're unbelievable.
You're so unlucky.
(He's as unlucky as Kwang Soo.)
My goodness.
(Min Yong reminds them of Kwang Soo.)
My goodness. I can't believe this.
(In our team, you can play the role of Kwang Soo.)
(He followed Jae Seok's order too precisely.)
(Is someone talking about me?)
You have to win as many times in a row as the number you get.
Okay.
One, two, three.
(Bo Mi throws the die on behalf of the other members.)
(It's a 2.)
(Good job, Bo Mi.)
Could you play rock-paper-scissors with me?
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Will Kwang Soo be unlucky today too?)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Unexpectedly, Kwang Soo wins.)
Did you win?
Miss.
- Thank you. - Excuse me.
We need to win one more time.
(They spot two beautiful girls.)
Beautiful ladies.
- Hello. - Kwang Soo usually...
wins against beautiful girls.
- Kwang Soo. - Hello.
Could you play rock-paper-scissors with me?
Hello. Could you play rock-paper scissors with me?
Thank you.
Here we go.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo usually wins against beautiful girls.)
(Will he win this time too?)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo wins.)
(The bus team completes the mission.)
He won.
Thank you.
Kwang Soo is strong against beautiful girls.
(They celebrate silently.)
(They have to pick 1 card out of the 4.)
Each of you take one, and I'll take the one left.
That sounds good. Kwang Soo, you're unlucky. You go first.
Take one away.
I'll take one too.
(There's only one left.)
This one is your choice.
(This card is their choice.)
Open your cards one by one.
(Kwang Soo opens his card.)
(Kwang Soo chose the Taxi Card.)
Gosh, he's so unlucky.
I think you have a dud.
I think it's a dud.
(If one of them has a dud, it means Bo Mi has the Push-Out Card.)
(It's a dud.)
(Excited)
(It means...)
(Bo Mi picked the Push-Out Card.)
The Taxi Card would've been great.
(The other team will be forced off the subway.)
The other team just completed the mission.
You will be forced out of the subway.
- What happens now? - You'll get off at the next stop.
Wait for the next train there.
(They'll have to wait for the next train at Euljiro 3-ga.)
Min Yong, you're so unlucky.
You're so unlucky.
I wish we could go just one more stop.
(It's one stop before the transfer station.)
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Is it one stop before the transfer station?
Nothing is going our way.
(What is wrong with us?)
Usually, Ji Hyo's team is good at these kinds of games,
but we're so unlucky.
The next train won't be here soon.
The train is approaching Chungmuro Station.
We're so...
We've been waiting for about 10 minutes now.
I mean...
How is this humanely possible?
So many things went wrong.
We're so unlucky today.
- We're not a good team. - We aren't.
I wish I could team up with Ji Hyo and Bo Mi.
It's your fault that we were forced off the train.
I wish I could team up with Ji Hyo and Bo Mi too.
Same here.
We all feel the same.
(What is Bo Mi, the girl everyone wants, doing?)
We're so lucky.
(They're relaxed.)
Be quiet.
(Blowing)
Your hair is flying in the wind. You're looking great.
That looks cool.
(The wind blows in my heart too.)
(Uncomfortable)
Bo Mi, what do you think of guys like him?
- He's handsome. - Do you think so?
(Thank you, cute lady.)
I hope those two end up together.
Then we could hang out all together.
Let's play a game, Team White versus Team Black.
(Bo Mi, give me five.)
It's a game where you hold each other's hand.
Right. It's a couple game.
(Will you give it a try?)
It's a couple game.
(We should follow the rules.)
(Bo Mi...)
Hold each other's hand.
(We need to follow the rules.)
(Kwang Soo is happy.)
(It's so funny.)
(Kwang Soo gazes at his hand.)
(I think spring is here.)
(What is with him?)
(I won't wash my hands.)
This time, our faces should touch.
(Their faces should touch.)
We shouldn't lose.
(These guys are hilarious.)
(Come on.)
(Ready)
(Bo Mi, this is just a game. We need to do our best.)
(Slapping)
(Wake up.)
(What did I do wrong?)
What?
What did I do wrong?
You guys look so cute together.
(Kwang Soo and Bo Mi look cute together.)
(Kwang Soo feels shy.)
(National Assembly Station)
(They need to transfer here.)
Let's do this.
Bye. Thank you.
(They thank the passengers.)
(They need to transfer to a bus for Yeongdeungpo.)
- It's here! - That's our bus!
- Really? - Let's get on!
- Is this our bus? - We're so lucky.
My goodness.
(They're so lucky.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Hello. - Hello.
(How can they be this lucky?)
(The bus team already transferred.)
(The subway team is about to transfer.)
- Are we taking Line Five? - Yes.
I haven't transferred at Jongno 3-ga Station in forever.
The platform is very far.
Jae Seok, we have to hurry.
Right. I know.
Is this it?
(They can't give up now.)
We have to go to Yeongdeungpo Market Station.
- We have to get on this. - Yeongdeungpo Market Station?
We have to start now.
Let's go.
(In order to rescue his team as the team captain,)
(he takes the initiative and leads as an example.)
(Will this throw save his team from this critical situation?)
I can't believe this.
(He throws the highest number as the team captain.)
You are truly unlucky.
- You have to get smacked by us. - Hold on.
(His unluckiness is beyond their expectations.)
- How can you get six? - Let me try.
Who knows? If you succeed, it's a miracle.
- It's not easy though. - He's really unlucky.
Excuse me, I have to play rock-paper-scissors with six people.
How could he get six?
(He's one of a kind.)
Can you play rock-paper-scissors with me? Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok, cheer up with this 1st win.)
She let him win.
(He happily wins 2 times in a row.)
(He has to win 4 more times.)
(Somehow, he manages to win 3 times in a row.)
(They allow themselves to get their hopes up.)
Can you play rock-paper-scissors with me? Rock-paper-scissors.
(He miraculously wins 4 times in a row!)
Jae Seok.
- You have two more left. - Just think you just started.
- Just think that. - Can you play rock-paper-scissors?
(She seems to be ready to play.)
(The fifth citizen doesn't seem ordinary.)
(Will he be able to continue his miracle?)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(What a surprise! At this point, it's getting a bit scary.)
- Jae Seok. - You have to win just one more.
- Just this once. - I only have one person left.
(He led an unlucky life.)
Please.
(A miracle on Line 5 is granted to Jae Seok.)
(No one had hopes for this sixth match.)
(What will Jae Seok's fate be?)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(He wins 6 times in a row!)
He did it!
(The universe is on his side.)
- I'm sorry. Are you all right? - I'm okay.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
He beat six people.
- I'm sorry. Are you okay? - How did he do this?
- This is amazing. - It's unbelievable.
- This is all thanks to you all. - This is awesome.
- Thank you all. - You did it, Jae Seok!
- You are the best. - How did you manage that?
- You did it. - You are so cool.
You are really cool.
Is it time now?
- We have to get 1 Push-Out Card. - There are 2 Push-Out Cards.
If you draw the Taxi Card, you are unlucky again.
If you choose the Taxi Card, you're ruined.
If that's the case, we are doomed.
(A Push-Out Card is their only hope to have a chance at winning.)
- Jae Seok. - I can't look.
- I'll look. - Please.
(So far, they failed all the missions.)
(They must win this mission by all means.)
It's a Push-Out Card!
(They are over the moon.)
Be quiet.
- This is amazing. - I picked the right one.
(Get off now.)
What is your ideal type?
- Are you asking Kwang Soo? - It's you.
It's you.
My ideal type is...
(The type of girl I like is...)
Please get off now.
- Wait. - They were talking.
We were talking about my ideal type.
Do we have to get off?
The other team utilized the Push-Out Card.
(They were about to arrive at the restaurant.)
- They got the Push-Out Card? - Really?
(Do we really have to get off?)
You must get off now.
- Let's get off. - All right. Let's get off first.
- Excuse us. - I'm sorry.
Another bus will come soon, right?
- We can get on the same one, right? - Right.
(Both teams are heading to a restaurant chosen by Jong Kook.)
The other team was only two stops away and was forced to get off.
- They were two stops away? - They are waiting for the bus?
- They are that close? - They are waiting for the bus?
They are only two stops away? It's really close.
There might be a traffic jam in Yeongdeungpo.
That's possible. There are a lot of cars in that area.
We should win at least once.
- That's my point too. - We must win at least once.
- It's frustrating. - They took all the hints.
(Team Jae Seok strikes a blow at Team Jong Kook.)
- This isn't the bus? - It won't go to Yeongdeungpo.
How about this?
- It's Bus 650! - I think it goes to Yeongdeungpo.
Get on.
It goes to Yeongdeungpo. Thank you.
The driver told me so.
(Could they have gotten close?)
This stop is Yeongdeungpo Market Station.
Hey, we have to run.
(They arrive at Yeongdeungpo Market Station.)
- Thank you for your help. - Is this the eel restaurant?
- Thank you. Have a good day. - From exit 3,
- how far... - We're running.
Can we just go straight?
It's exit 3.
(Just run.)
(They also arrive at their destination.)
We have to hurry.
Jae Seok, we have to rush.
Seok Jin, which way do we go?
We have to find the parking lot.
- Did the other team arrive yet? - Should we hurry?
(On the 3rd course, a secret item and roasted eel are at stake.)
(It's not over until it's over.)
- Let us go in now. - Hold on.
It must be somewhere around here.
(Which team will arrive first?)
The secrets of Running Man's Food Guide are...
(Chocolate, rice, barley, avocado)
It can't be.
(7 items stir up an incredible twist.)
(No one can predict the end.)
We don't have time.
(Who will win?)
(The third restaurant of Running Man's Food Guide)
(It's chewy.)
(It's also cost-appropriate.)
- Let us go in now. - Hold on.
It must be somewhere around here.
There it is!
- I found it. - There it is. Hello.
I got it.
There it is. It's over there!
(They must arrive before the other team does.)
(They arrive at their destination without taking a breather.)
(Team Jae Seok finally enters the eel restaurant.)
- You're here. - Hey, you are here.
(They are at ease.)
(Those jerks...)
- Thank you. - My goodness.
Leave it.
(It's a famous eel restaurant in Yeongdeungpo for its soft texture.)
(This roasted eel goes...)
- It's tasty. - I can't believe it.
(to these people.)
This is it.
(What a letdown. Give us some water.)
- Please give us some water. - This is delicious.
They only drank water today.
- This is your hint for this round. - All right.
(The winning team is also provided with peanuts.)
- We got peanuts. - Peanuts.
We have peanuts here too.
Thank you for the food.
Why can't we win at least once? This is frustrating.
- I'm full. Thank you for the meal. - Thank you for the food.
(They head to the fourth restaurant.)
(Running Man's Food Guide)
(Braised spicy chicken, eel, octopus, and bulgogi restaurants.)
(Current status on items obtained by each team)
- Hello. - I've been here a lot.
I had so many take-outs.
- There are outdoor tables. - I didn't know about this place.
Bo Mi, this is a famous restaurant.
- I've never been here. - A lot of people buy this dish.
Seok Jin chose this place, right?
I also come here often.
- You do? - Yes.
- I'm glad. - This place is really popular.
This place is known for having big chicken drumsticks.
Whenever I come to this area for a shoot,
- I always get takeout. - You do?
- Of course. - This is delicious.
- What's wrong, Jae Seok? - If we lost again...
- What's up? - He's mad.
- I'm so mad. - You are not in a good mood.
I ran so much that I lost my appetite.
Can I go to the hair salon?
- Why? - I think my hair got messy.
- He's really neat. - Were you in a bad mood like this?
Were you bickering at each other?
It's not that your team is good. We analyzed about your team.
Kwang Soo. Haha. What is your job in your team?
(He takes a shot at these two incompetent members.)
Me? Were you referring to me?
- Bo Mi... - Hold on.
- To be honest, Bo Mi... - Bo Mi...
and Jong Kook. Hold on.
Jong Kook and Bo Mi are facing the same problem.
- I can't believe this. - Bo Mi. You should tell him.
They radiate positive energy.
- They help us a lot. - You don't have to be nice here.
The last course of Running Man's Food Guide...
recommended by the members is...
a famous braised spicy chicken restaurant. It was Seok Jin's pick.
You will find out what the game is once you finish...
braised spicy chicken placed in front of you.
- Really? - You can enjoy the food first.
- The spice stings your tongue. - It does.
- It feels like that. - We will eat this with rice.
(Braised spicy chicken tastes best when it's eaten with rice.)
(It suits Min Yong's taste perfectly.)
- Isn't this delicious? - It's good.
Bo Mi. Try this.
- This is the delicious part. - Thank you.
Let's stir-fry the rice.
(She turns into an eater.)
This is tasty.
I'm glad we're finishing up with spicy food.
I think I ate the non-spicy one before.
You probably did.
Bo Mi can eat.
(She's on another level.)
She slowly eats everything.
We ate all the ingredients from land, sea, and air.
The highlight of braised spicy chicken is...
- fried rice. - It's fried rice!
Of course.
- It's very delicious. - It's great.
We will bring in fried rice.
This place is also famous for cooked glutinous rice.
- Gosh. - That's it.
(Is there a chopstick in the middle of the fried rice?)
- We'll play the game with this. - You guys.
- I am good at this. - Are you?
- I used to do this with soil a lot. - That's right.
- Our team will win this game. - Are you serious?
Ji Hyo, don't you worry. I mean it.
All right then.
The rule is simple.
Players from each team will take turns...
to scoop out a spoonful of fried rice.
Whichever team tips over the chopstick will lose.
We have to eat what we scoop out, right?
- You must eat what you scoop out. - Of course. That's obvious.
- Let's begin. - Can I go first?
You have to eat what you spoon out.
(It's a generous amount.)
- You have a voracious appetite. - She does.
- She can eat. - We just started.
I'll spoon out a lot since it's only the start.
Right. We just began.
She looks great when she eats.
- Look at that. - Goodness.
She knows how to eat.
(The way she eats brings good luck.)
(She's a fairy who knows how to eat.)
- Is it tasty? - Look at her eyes. She likes it.
- Min Yong is next. - Are we alternating?
- I played this a lot with soil. - You did?
He said he was good at this.
Min Yong. You have to eat what you spoon out.
(He penetrates into the middle.)
It's steaming.
Why did you scoop out the inner part?
- It's warm inside. - This looks awkward now.
- Kwang Soo, you are up. - All right.
I think it needs some sesame oil.
It's only the beginning.
(He deeply breaks into the inner part.)
(He opens his mouth wide.)
- Kwang Soo has a huge mouth. - He's like a crocodile.
- He's like a crocodile. - He is.
- I'm not like a crocodile. - He's a snake.
(They have to be careful. How would Seok Jin do it?)
- It's so good. - Take more.
(He scrapes a little bit.)
- That's so cheap. Take some more. - It's good.
- It's up to me. This is a lot. - My goodness.
- You're barely licking it. - You have to do what you promised.
It's good but I'm full.
(The real game starts now.)
You have to take this much at least.
(Gobbling)
That looks messy.
(I'll win and fill my belly too.)
- Good job. - It's sticky so it won't fall.
(She must digest fast.)
Take more.
(The rice tower gradually gets smaller.)
(The chopstick is not stable now.)
It tastes even better now.
- Can you eat this much, Bo Mi? - You eat a lot.
(The game will end soon.)
(It's Bo Mi's turn again.)
You eat a lot.
(A small movement may decide who loses the game.)
(She has to focus on the spoon...)
(and save the chopstick in the middle.)
- She's so good. - You can't say anything to her.
- Why? She's so good. - We don't have anything to say.
- What should we say? - She's good.
(Bo Mi is saved.)
(She takes a big spoon and makes it tough for the next person.)
(Let's see her eat.)
What's wrong?
(It's Bo Mi's eating time.)
- Good job. - Thank you.
(It's about to topple over.)
(Don't you like what I did?)
(It's Min Yong's turn.)
Why would you compete over this?
Hey, hey.
(Pushing)
- Keep going. It's okay. - Do it.
(Keep going, Min Yong.)
- Keep going. - Do it.
(He doesn't know anymore.)
- Good. - It's okay.
(He's bold like when he's shoveling.)
(How would this long game end?)
- Good job. - Hey.
(Falling)
(The tower falls apart.)
(What did you do?)
(He messed up.)
You said you were good.
(Team Jong Kook wins all the games.)
You barely scraped it.
(I want to turn back time.)
I'm sick of this now.
- I'm good at this. - Really?
(He said he's good in shoveling.)
(He was all talk.)
(He made his team lose with just two turns.)
(Isn't he a spy?)
(They're sick of winning now.)
- You said you were good. - He's really bad.
(He was all talk and he messed up.)
- Are you a spy? - He must be.
(I want to go back home.)
We're going to head to the giant claw crane in SBS lobby.
- Claw crane. - I saw it.
(Team Jong Kook gets 2 tries for winning and Team Jae Seok gets 1.)
- We'll win this one for sure. - Are you sure?
It's not just any ordinary claw crane.
You can put a name tag of a person inside the claw crane...
and if you pick the stuffed toy with their name on it,
they come to your team.
- We have to pick Bo Mi then. - We do.
- She has the hint. - We need to get Min Yong.
(1 hour ago on their way to have braised spicy chicken)
I'm the guest here but I don't know what the hint is.
(They're supposed to know something.)
- Do you know what it is? - No, I don't.
- You do know. - It must be hidden somewhere.
- You might not know it yet. - Do I...
- What are you doing? - Do I...
(Coffee Min Yong)
(This is a real situation.)
- What are you doing? - I ripped to check. It's a hint.
(That's what it was.)
(It's better to have guests on their teams.)
- That startled me. - Then we...
(I need to win so that I take Bo Mi's item as well.)
- I have a claw crane at home. - Forget it.
(I have a claw crane at home.)
(That hurt him.)
- Stop it. - It's about time.
- He's persistent. He keeps going. - He's flustered.
- I know you now. - How shameless.
- Is it the claw type? - We have to get Bo Mi.
- It is. - Okay. Let's go.
(That's a piece of cake.)
You saw it, right? I have one at home.
- I have the same one at home. - It's small though.
It's the same principle.
(He keeps on flaunting.)
He flaunts. He flaunts so much.
What does the rice tower have to do with a sand tower?
Rice and sand are very different. I didn't realize.
Rice is stickier.
(He's not appreciated by his team.)
Let's get going first.
Fine. Go.
I'm lonely, Haha.
He's lonely.
(Their last mission will be held in SBS.)
- This is it. - It's huge.
(Have you seen a gigantic claw crane before?)
(It's made of a huge box that's 4m tall.)
I haven't seen one this big.
It's huge.
- This looks so difficult. - It looks fun.
I have a problem. It's not the one I have at home.
(He's scared by how big it is.)
I have this small one at home.
Come on, Min Yong.
All right. I'll explain the rules.
Jong Kook will start.
There's a name tag on each stuffed toy.
It has Min Yong's name. If you win the stuffed toy,
he comes to your team.
The name tag will change to Bo Mi's after.
- Then the other team can go. - Okay.
Go ahead, Jong Kook.
- Who's going to go? - Each person can go once.
- Should we? - Do the one that's closest to you.
It's not easy.
(They take their time to pick the target.)
- Is this better? - Yes, it is.
(Jong Kook's 1st attempt)
- There's a time limit. - Does this even work?
(Let's look around.)
This is so huge.
- He won't be able to do it. - This is impossible.
- It's impossible. - There's seven seconds left.
- You have 6 seconds. - 5. Go right.
(He gets ready to press the button.)
- It's a fail. - I got it.
It won't work. Where are you aiming it?
(Will they get Min Yong or not? That is the question.)
(Will Jong Kook succeed?)
- I got it. - It won't work.
- Please. - It needs to be positioned well.
(Min Yong is nervous as well.)
- It won't work. - Okay.
(He got it.)
(It has to reach the hole.)
(Where would Min Yong end up?)
- Please. - You have to get the legs.
- Okay. - He got it.
It didn't work.
(It falls within a second.)
(It's not easy to succeed at once.)
- That's right. - Go for that one.
(Last try goes to Kwang Soo.)
Didn't you see that? I told you to move back a bit.
- You should have moved it. - Worry about yourselves.
(Let's see how good you are.)
- Are you mad? - It was just too close.
We just need Bo Mi.
- Bo Mi! - Wait for us.
(It's their last chance to get Min Yong on their team.)
- In 8, 7, 6... - Why?
(The counting down makes him nervous.)
- You have enough time. - They're done.
- It won't work. - It's not easy.
(Time is now.)
- Please. - He's in a perfect position.
- It's a good position. - It's perfect.
(I have a good feeling.)
- You got it. - Looking good.
(He may be unlucky but this looks perfect.)
It's difficult to win in a few tries.
(Will they get the stuffed toy with Min Yong's name on it?)
It's going to work.
- He got it. - It's difficult to win.
It's going up!
(He picks it up.)
- He got it. - Please.
(Would he be lucky just for today?)
(Please hold on until the stuffed toy gets released.)
(What would be the result of this game?)
Please.
(Slipping)
(Collapsing)
(The claw is unlucky like Kwang Soo.)
(His bad luck will last forever.)
It's difficult to win in a few tries.
(Team Jong Kook fails.)
- Okay. - It's difficult with two tries.
- We are done now. - Do you want to give it a try?
- Should I? It has to be standing. - I'll look for you.
Let's go for the one at the front. We don't have much options.
- Do you want to go for that one? - How much time do I have? This one.
(He finds his target.)
Okay!
- This one? - Yes.
- Should I go forward? - You're good on this side.
(He presses the button.)
(It goes down for Bo Mi's name.)
(What will happen to her?)
- Good. - It dodged.
- Good. - It's a perfect grip.
(He has a good feeling.)
(It's a perfect grip.)
I have a good feeling about this.
- Good. - I think we are done.
(It starts to move.)
(It just has to reach the hole.)
(They only have one chance to bring Bo Mi to their team.)
(His heart is thumping.)
- Okay! - Please.
(This claw crane will decide the two teams' fates.)
(Please hold on.)
(Her heart is racing.)
- Please. - No, Bo Mi.
(That's the exit hole.)
- Okay. - No way.
(Sliding)
(Team Jong Kook tries to protect Bo Mi,)
(and Team Jae Seok tries to steal her. This is the last game.)
Please, Ji Hyo.
(The team with the guests have the upper hand for the last mission.)
(Who will win this game?)
- No, Bo Mi. - You can't take her.
- Please, Ji Hyo. - We got it.
No, Bo Mi.
(Dropping)
(They got it.)
(Team Jae Seok gets Bo Mi in one try.)
(This turns the game around.)
- We did it. - We got it.
(Bo Mi gets transferred to Team Jae Seok.)
- What just happened? - Come here, Bo Mi.
- Sure. - Come here.
(They have both Min Yong and Bo Mi.)
(How would this race end?)
- We're in the same team now. - You look so happy, Bo Mi.
Give her a jacket.
Give her our pink jacket.
Bo Mi joins our team at last.
Here are the guest members' secrets.
Take off the guests' name tags.
Can we do it in the open?
(He takes it off.)
"Chocolate Bo Mi"?
- "Coffee Min Yong". - "Coffee Min Yong".
- Chocolate Bo Mi, Coffee Min Yong. - What's this?
You'll play Hide and Seek to obtain ingredients you need.
Hide and Seek?
That sounds fun.
The teams will take turns with the time limit of five minutes.
The team must seek the other team that's hiding.
If you take off a name tag, you obtain the ingredient written on it.
How many ingredients can one person attach?
- It's up to you. - Really?
The perimeter is limited to the first floor lobby.
- Is it here? - It's in the lobby.
- Where can we hide? - Is there a place to hide?
Determine the order.
What should we do?
- We have to be strategic. - How?
It's not about running away. It's important to hide well.
Let's put all the ingredients on Ji Hyo and Bo Mi.
- All of them? - Yes.
Isn't it better to have one each?
Two is better.
Will it be dangerous?
- How about Min Yong? - Do you want one?
It's better to have one each.
- Do I have to hide? - Let's get one each.
You can hide amongst the stuffed animals.
The other team will definitely consider it.
There aren't good places to hide.
(Kwang Soo has a hard time hiding.)
How about above the claw crane?
Can I climb up?
What's that behind?
There's a ladder.
We can climb up if there's a ladder.
Look.
We can fold the ladder after climbing up.
(Remove the ladder after using it.)
Attach everything on me.
No one can climb up without the ladder.
- Okay. - Should I take the ladder?
(Hide and Seek Round One starts.)
- Can you carry the ladder? - Once...
we remove their name tags, we can win.
Remove all their name tags.
Try to finish the game in round one.
We have more members, so we have an advantage.
(The hiding team has two minutes.)
It'll be fun.
- Do we start? - Yes.
Will you be okay?
- Hold it tight. - Okay, I will.
(Haha is bolder than before.)
Can you do it?
- There's a hole. - In the ladder?
- Move more to the side. - There's a hole.
(It's a big hole.)
What should we do?
(We're doomed.)
- What do we do? - Isn't it too high?
What should we do?
How about that coffee shop?
- Should we lift it up? - We can go inside for a while.
Thank you.
Should we go inside?
(They enter the coffee shop.)
(He finds a space to hide.)
I'll hide in here.
(Haha finishes hiding.)
No one will find you here.
Should we split the items?
Let's split them.
(They split the ingredients.)
Rice.
(Jong Kook, Haha, and Kwang Soo each get ingredients.)
You have one minute.
Please hide within one minute.
(1 minute remains.)
(Kwang Soo finds something behind the coffee shop.)
(He finds a podium.)
(He carries it with ease.)
(He passes the staff members and places the podium...)
(at an awkward place.)
Please start now. Hurry.
(Jong Kook finishes hiding Haha.)
Make sure no one can see me.
Okay.
(Haha's recording)
(Surprisingly, Haha is hiding in here.)
(He's fully hidden.)
(He has 15 seconds left.)
(Jong Kook's physique is difficult to hide.)
(He hides in front of the elevator.)
(The hiding team is ready.)
Please start now. Hurry.
Is everyone hiding?
The hiding team should be hidden by now.
Let's finish in one round.
- Do we have 5 minutes? - Let's finish in 1 go.
Let's do that.
In 5, 4, 3,
- 2... - Finish it in 1 go.
(The seeking team starts.)
(Ji Hyo moves towards Kwang Soo.)
We have five minutes.
(She knows Kwang Soo usually hides behind staff members.)
(Please don't come here.)
(Will Ji Hyo spot Kwang Soo?)
(She turns around.)
Act naturally.
We have five minutes.
(The seeking team speeds up.)
(Min Yong searches the claw crane.)
No one is here.
(Where is everyone?)
I can't find anyone.
(Jae Seok approaches where Jong Kook is hiding.)
(He searches near the reception desk.)
(He suddenly turns around.)
(Is he heading towards where Jong Kook is hiding?)
He's right here.
- I found you. Here he is. - I knew it.
I got Jong Kook and rice.
I got rice. I found Jong Kook.
Catch him.
We don't have time.
He caught Jong Kook.
Where are the others?
Catch him.
We don't have time.
(Kwang Soo is right here.)
(He turns around again.)
(Is someone else hiding behind the podium?)
(Kwang Soo is at risk of being found.)
(What will happen to Kwang Soo with barley?)
Here's Kwang Soo.
(He finds Kwang Soo.)
- I found him. - How did you know?
- We just need to find Haha. - How did you find me?
We need to find Haha.
- I got barley. - He's good at finding people.
- We need to find Haha. - We only need to find Haha.
It's over once we find Haha.
You have two minutes left.
We only need to find Haha.
(They won't find where Haha is hiding.)
How did he find me?
(Haha is struggling inside a trash bag.)
(The game is over once Haha is found.)
Here are the staff members.
He's too small to find.
(He gets anxious.)
Where's Haha?
It's hard to find him.
Haha should have kept all the ingredients.
Bo Mi.
Check inside the women's restroom.
It's difficult to find where Haha is hiding.
He should have kept them all.
(It's challenging to find Haha.)
Where did he go?
(They looked almost everywhere.)
(Jae Seok senses something and approaches the coffee shop.)
(Is that Seok Jin?)
I'm sorry.
May I take a look?
(No way.)
I'm sorry.
(Haha is in trouble.)
May I take a look?
(Seok Jin is in front of Haha.)
(Once Haha is found, Team Jong Kook loses.)
(What will happen to him?)
He's not here.
(He gives up quickly.)
(Haha is relieved.)
(They have 10 seconds left.)
In 9, 8...
Have you seen Haha?
(Min Yong gets desperate.)
(He's frustrated.)
Where is he?
I can't check inside the claw crane.
(Time is up.)
I can't find him.
I couldn't find him.
Okay.
(Haha survives.)
(He returns in glory.)
I did it.
(Team Jong Kook wins seafood and peanuts.)
Haha should have kept all the items.
That was amazing.
We'll keep one each.
Each person keeps two.
You keep it.
I found a place that's hard to find.
- You should hide there. - All right.
- Aren't you keeping one? - No, I won't.
- Shouldn't we keep one each? - I'll disappoint them.
- Really? - They'll get exhausted too.
They'll be disappointed to find that I have nothing.
- Let's find all of them. - Will we win?
We have to find them all.
- Let's hide. - They won't find me.
We can do it.
Bo Mi, Ji Hyo, hide well.
This is where I was talking about.
- This podium? - No, this one.
What's this?
It's a big stuffed animal.
- It's easy to look past it. - You're right.
- Do you want to hide here? - Yes.
- Wait a minute. - Can you film?
- Yes. - Wait.
It doesn't look obvious.
I'm good.
I'm good now.
(She's completely hidden.)
It's difficult.
(Where will the other members hide?)
- Is anyone in here? - Min Yong.
- Can you go inside? - Let me try it.
- Just go in there. - I know.
Gosh.
(He struggles to fit inside.)
(Seok Jin hides carefully as he has two items.)
Give that to me.
- The camera? - Give me that.
- Which one? - That one.
I'll hide here.
(Where did Jae Seok choose?)
I'll hide right here.
(He enters the claw crane.)
(Where will Bo Mi decide to hide?)
Where should I hide?
Can I hide inside?
Thank you.
May I hide behind the trash can?
Was Haha here?
(He hid there.)
Did he hide here?
(He hid there before.)
Really? He'll definitely find me here.
Wait.
This is where he was.
My goodness.
Can you switch your uniform with me?
- Me? - I'm really sorry. It's just once.
(She pretends like she's a barista.)
(She changes her clothes instead of hiding.)
May I borrow your glasses?
I'm really sorry. Thank you.
It's okay.
(She's meticulous.)
(Find me if you can.)
Where was that spot?
Is there nowhere for me to hide?
(Min Yong hesitates until the end.)
You have 10 seconds.
I'll just stand naturally.
I'll greet them naturally.
(They're done hiding.)
- In 4, - There's nowhere to hide.
- Right? - 3, 2,
(They have to collect all 7 items in 5 minutes.)
- This is first floor, right? - Yes.
(Where could they be?)
(Make sure you hide well. Your hair might get ripped off.)
(Does Kwang Soo head straight for the bathroom?)
(Would he greet him naturally?)
(Seok Jin is hiding in here.)
Give me that.
- This? - Yes.
(Seok Jin is hiding in here.)
(How did Kwang Soo know right away?)
Okay.
I was going to hide here but decided not to.
- Check it out. - Should I?
(Team Jong Kook was hiding 15 minutes ago.)
I can go in here.
(They already found this spot.)
This is good.
I was going to hide here but decided not to.
This is tall.
(I shouldn't have done that.)
There must be...
There's somebody here.
(Did he get caught?)
Seok Jin!
Seok Jin! I found him.
- Seok Jin. - How did you know?
I don't have to rip his name tag, right?
My goodness.
How did you know?
I was going to hide here earlier but decided not to.
I guess it looked different before.
Chocolate and rice.
Why did he give it to me?
(Kwang Soo turns around.)
(Did Min Yong get caught?)
(Dashing)
(That radio booth looks fishy.)
(Why won't he come here?)
(This is too intense.)
(3 minutes 30 seconds left until this round is over.)
(The coffee shop looks fishy.)
(Would someone be in Haha's hiding place?)
(She looks somewhat like Bo Mi but maybe not.)
- Bo Mi? - Yes.
(Peekaboo)
Let's go, Bo Mi.
This wasn't supposed to be it.
Get changed, Bo Mi.
I got caught right away.
(Team Jae Seok has 2 items left.)
Who's here?
How do you go inside the claw crane?
(Jong Kook heads towards the claw crane.)
(Is his intuition right?)
How do you go inside the claw crane?
(My goodness)
(Someone is probably hiding in here.)
(Banging)
How do you open this?
(The situation is imminent.)
How do you get in?
(What would happen to Jae Seok?)
Like this?
Here he is.
(Here he is.)
(He gets caught right away.)
- My gosh. - Hurry up.
Come out.
My gosh.
- Why? - Come out.
What's wrong with you?
(He doesn't have anything.)
He doesn't have anything.
Did you get caught? I did too.
I had a great hiding spot.
(Min Yong and Ji Hyo are still hiding.)
Who's still missing?
(There's 1 minute and 30 seconds left.)
They're nowhere.
Let's see.
We only need one chance.
That's all we need.
This won't open.
It won't open.
I found Jae Seok in the claw crane.
(He's right by Ji Hyo's hiding place.)
(Shuddering)
(Does he have a hunch?)
Who's missing?
(Kicking)
(That was a big impact.)
(Is this a giant doll?)
There's someone in here.
It's here.
Who's this?
There's someone in here.
It's here. Who's this?
(Ji Hyo stays quiet and doesn't move.)
Hold on. Isn't this it?
It must be a person. She has long hair. It's Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo. Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo?
Come out, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
She's out.
Who's left now?
- Whom did you find? - Ji Hyo.
- You found her? - Yes.
How much time do they have?
We're missing Min Yong.
It's just him?
It's just you! Hold on!
Why are you standing like this? You should have done this earlier.
(They don't think he's in an obvious spot like the bathroom.)
It's long.
It's eerie.
What about the bathroom?
(He heads to the bathroom.)
(There's only 10 seconds left. What would happen?)
What about the bathroom?
(He looks at the mirror by the door.)
It's just you! Hold on!
(Just a little bit more, Min Yong.)
He scared me.
(He finds Min Yong with a few seconds left.)
Why did you scare me?
You scared me.
- Did he get caught? - He got caught.
- He got caught. - Did you find him?
Everybody got caught. It's over.
- Really? - I found Min Yong.
(Team Jae Seok is out.)
Today's winning team...
is Team Jong Kook.
(Team Jong Kook is the winner of Running Man's Food Guide.)
- That was close. - Bo Mi.
- We have you in our hearts. - That was close.
- We consider you one of us. - That's right.
The secret to...
Running Man's Food Guide...
had to do with food that might disappear.
(It had to do with food that might disappear.)
- What? - Why?
The Daily Mirror, a British national tabloid newspaper,
announced eight food items that'll go extinct due to climate change.
- No way. - Seven of them are...
- in front of you. - No way.
We can't live without rice.
- Chocolate will disappear? - Peanuts too?
- Barely too? - Coffee.
You must be interested and invested...
in order to enjoy these items for a longer time.
Team Jong Kook won today's race,
so they get...
these seven items as a prize.
- That's so meaningful. - I agree.
Can Min Yong and Bo Mi...
say something?
- Something simple? - Yes.
I feel bad.
I was happy to have met Bo Mi.
What about you, Bo Mi?
I had so much fun...
and I realized the importance of positive energy.
- Really? - I'll come back...
- when I'm skinnier. - You're pretty already.
- Stop it. - Please stop.
- You're already pretty. - Please, Bo Mi.
We'll be back next week. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you Min Yong and Bo Mi for joining us.)
Today is Booking King Race.
Booking?
(We have invited booking kings for today's race.)
He's so sexy.
- Would you like to join me? - Of course.
Who booked for me?
(They must become booking kings of this territory.)
- What is the booker's name? - Sandara Park.
(And)
(A man with another goal.)
- Keep going. - Go.
- Does this make any sense? - What was that?
He's there.
Hey.
- Jae Seok is acting by himself. - I wonder what the mission is.