(2017 Running Man's Second Global Project)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(Travel destinations for 1 percent pour in from around the world.)
(Running Man will visit the place only 1 percent recommended.)
(The member with 3 I Go Stickers will go to a place for the 1 percent.)
(Avoid I Go Sticker to avoid going on an adventure.)
(The 1st Place Tour in Tokyo)
(Jae Seok dreamt of being a king.)
(Haha and So Min followed him.)
(Jae Seok rose above his bad luck and took the throne.)
(He was given the right to assign the members to the sides of a dice.)
(King, please look over us.)
I will assign my team mates to six.
(Jae Seok ends up giving Haha and So Min I Go Stickers.)
- Viewers, look at what... - You jerk!
(Today, )
(a suspicious race will unfold.)
(A suspicious member)
(A suspicious mission)
(And a suspicious...)
(reaction)
(A suspicious dance...)
(and a suspicious charm)
(A very suspicious race will unfold today.)
(They spent the spring of 2017 with Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
(The refreshing summer approaches.)
You know,
it's still early in the morning.
I am still recuperating from Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
I am serious. What is going on?
(Where are the other members?)
(Annoyed)
Gosh, I can't believe Jae Seok.
(Resentful)
I made him the king.
(He repaid me with an I Go Sticker.)
I will be likely to go if I get another I Go Sticker.
This is a race for I Go Stickers, right?
You are right.
(What could be today's race for I Go Sticker?)
(This place looks familiar.)
(It's Se Chan's place.)
(The producer aims to make a surprise visit.)
My goodness.
(Who is he?)
Gosh, you startled me.
- My goodness. - You startled me.
Hello.
I am here to see Se Chan.
He will be out shortly.
Okay. I am sorry.
It's okay.
I startled you.
(The person they were looking for comes out.)
For goodness' sake. What is it this time?
You met my brother, right?
We surprised each other.
(After the surprise visit, )
(they go to where actresses doll up, Chungdam-dong shop.)
(Which muse will we meet here? Ji Hyo or So Min?)
(Kwang Soo appears mid-transformation.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(His eyes are puffy.)
What are you doing?
(I can't believe you followed me to the beauty shop.)
- Please take this. - Okay.
We are starting the race separately.
Yes. Today, the race...
- starts here. - Does it start here?
Yes, it does.
Where are the members? Why am I getting this alone?
What is this?
It's a mission.
A Mission for the Acquisition of Money.
"A Propitious Place for 1 Percent".
"At exits 1 through 8 of Seoul's elevated park..."
"are different amounts of money for the mission."
"Exit 1, 40 dollars. Exit 2, 3, and 4, 50 dollars."
"Exit 5, 6, and 7, 70 dollars. Exit 8, 100 dollars."
"Among exits 1 through 8,"
"choose a number of your liking and gather around by 9:30am."
"However, the money will be divided among the members at the exit."
The money will be divided?
(If it overlaps?)
If two members come to the same exit...
The money will be divided.
(If the exits overlap, the money will be divided.)
(It's a battle of psychology.)
The money you acquire...
will play a big role on the outcome of today's race.
- Really? - Choose an exit and let us know...
five minutes prior to your arrival.
(Today's race will take place at Seoul-Ro.)
(The money will be divided if other members show up.)
(To avoid getting I Go Stickers, choose an exit no one will go to.)
(40 dollars)
(50 dollars, 70 dollars, 100 dollars)
(To avoid sharing, keep the others from coming to your exit.)
I will kill you if you come.
(A shallow, psychological warfare and the clumsy tactics fill...)
(A War for the Money, A Propitious Place for 1 Percent)
(Who will emerge victorious?)
"The money will be divided"?
Wait a minute.
That means everyone might go to exit eight.
How many members are there?
(Let me think.)
There are nine members, right?
(She counts with her fingers in a unique way.)
- There are eight members. - I am sorry.
Since there are 8 members, 100 dollars will be...
- divided by eight. - Yes.
Then...
(100,000 divided by 8 is...)
(Well, )
(let me think.)
Why don't you do it on the road?
- May I decide on my way there? - Yes.
Let's go. Let's go.
They want us to use our brains again.
The money will be divided.
(He acts like he has used his brain before.)
Exit one won't be a bad choice.
Maybe I should choose among exits 5, 6, and 7.
There are members who are bound to aim for 100 dollars.
Wouldn't it be best to go to exit eight?
An idea hit my head like a lightning.
It occurred to me that I should go to exit eight no matter what.
It's an instinct.
Everyone else might go for exits 5, 6, and 7,
but I have this strong feeling that I must choose exit eight.
Kwang Soo and Jae Seok will choose exit eight for certain.
They're like moths attracted to flames.
It is for certain that So Min,
Jae Seok, and Kwang Soo will go for exit eight.
These moths are hard to deal with.
I should carry a bug spray and exterminate them.
(How will these moths' choices turn out?)
(Jae Seok is calling someone.)
Hi, Jae Seok.
- Hi, Kwang Soo. - Hey.
Where are you?
I'm on my way to exit one now.
- You're going to exit one? - Yes.
I guess you're thinking of choosing exit eight.
You'll head there first and size the situation up, right?
(They know each other too well.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
I'll tell you flat out honest. I'm going for 100 dollars.
(Disappointed)
So don't come.
I'm warning you not to come.
Jae Seok, we're thinking exactly the same way.
- Jae Seok. - Kwang Soo.
I know several of us are like moths attracted to flames.
Go ahead and come if you want.
We'll have to split the amount, just so you know.
Let's meet up at exit eight then.
Sure, let's do it.
I'm on my way now.
- Okay. - All right, see you there.
- Hey, let's hurry to exit eight. - Hurry there.
- I'll see you there soon. - Okay.
(They act confidently.)
Is he going for certain?
(He feels intimidated as soon as he hangs up.)
(He calls another member.)
- Hi, Kwang Soo. - Hey.
Where will you go?
I'm on my way to exit six for now.
Gosh, whatever.
Stop acting because it's not working.
I'm not acting.
I only said I'm on my way to exit six. Where are you now?
You're going for exit eight, right?
(Gulping)
- Hello? - Well...
Why do you think so?
I know you're heading there too.
Of course, I'm going there.
I'm going there too, but don't come.
I'm telling you now. Don't come.
I'm going no matter what.
(Sighing)
- You sound so sure. - Let's hang up for now.
- Jae Seok's calling me. - Okay.
Hi, Jae Seok.
- Hi, So Min. - Where are you going?
I'm warning you not to come to exit eight because I'm going there now.
I'll see you at exit eight.
(She ignores his warning.)
- What did you say? - I'll see you there.
I just told you I'm on my way there.
- All right, see you soon. - So Min.
- What? - Will you keep doing this?
- What do you mean? - I said I'm going there.
Okay, I'll see you there.
My goodness. She's not listening to me.
- Why aren't you listening to me? - Anyway,
I'll see you later.
All right, come then.
(So Min will be there for certain.)
(Ji Hyo tries to call So Min who never listens to others.)
Hi, So Min.
Ji Hyo, where are you going?
(Straightforward)
What about you?
I'm going to exit eight now.
(She's going to exit eight.)
Gosh,
you're just going there even if you can't earn any, right?
- Hi, Seok Jin. - Hi, Ji Hyo.
Where are you now?
I'm on my way to exit eight now.
(Seok Jin is also going to exit 8.)
(Laughing)
Have you decided on it already?
- Hi, Ji Hyo. - Hi, Jong Kook.
So are you going to exit eight too?
You know I don't make risky choices.
- Which exit are you headed to? - Exit five.
Exit five?
Okay, I'll never go to exit five.
- Don't come for certain. - All right, I promise.
I'll kill you if you come.
How could you say that?
You have so many other expressions, but how could you say you'd kill me?
Isn't that inappropriate for TV shows?
You could've said, "I won't forgive you," or something like that.
- I won't forgive you. - "I won't forgive you if you come."
But "I'll kill you" is just inappropriate.
I won't forgive you.
(Anyway, I won't forgive you.)
- Hello? - Hey, Se Chan.
Hi, Haha.
Be honest and tell me where you're headed.
I'm going for exit five.
- Exit five? - Yes.
(Haha and Se Chan share strong faith in each other.)
(They went fishing together early in the morning in Russia.)
(I'm proud of you, Se Chan!)
(They grew a strong bond by catching pollack that day.)
(Haha is willing to share important information with Se Chan.)
Just keep in mind that many of our members are going for exit eight.
Really? I see, so that place is like a rest stop.
Are you going there though? That's what's important.
Choose among exits 5, 6, or 7.
- Exits 5, 6, or 7? - I'll be in exits 2, 3, or 4.
This is what I like about you. Your leadership.
You're going through a lot today.
Not at all. It's you who are going through a lot.
Gosh, our super rookie.
(He's proud of Se Chan.)
Haha, let's not run into each other.
- All right. - Bye!
- Wasn't it suspicious? - I could sense he would betray me.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
Whenever I talk to someone like him on the phone,
I don't feel like I had a conversation.
(He tries calling another member like Se Chan.)
Kwang Soo.
- Hi, Haha. - Hi.
His voice is so scary.
- Seriously. - What are you talking about?
So say what you want to say.
I'll go for exit eight.
I don't intend to avoid running into you.
How about we all gather at exit eight then?
Look at him. He's playing for high stakes now.
Are you trying to instigate me from the morning?
- Hi, Jae Seok. - Hi, Haha.
Thanks for the Sticker last week.
Goodness, Haha.
From early in the morning,
I'm very much motivated.
Listen to my determined voice.
Are you saying you'll go for exit eight?
What?
(He only cares about which exit Haha will choose to go.)
(Why is everyone talking about exit 8?)
You guys are so suffocating.
I made my decision...
as soon as I received the mission for today.
- Do you get it? - Gosh, seriously.
You know me.
You know me, right?
You know what happens if I go crazy about something.
Hold on.
Okay, I get it.
I don't think we need to talk any further.
- Okay. - Okay.
Is he serious or what?
What on earth is going on?
(He's frustrated.)
I should call So Min.
(He'll decide after calling So Min.)
- Hi, Haha. - Good to hear your bright voice.
Thanks, are you on your way to exit eight?
(Out of the blue)
It's so tiring.
Gosh, this is just so tiring.
So Min.
- It's exit eight, right? - So Min.
I'm so tired.
Okay, I'll see you at exit eight then.
(Please stop now.)
See you soon.
Five of us will get to split the money.
Gosh, she's giving me goosebumps.
- Se Chan, Jae Seok, Kwang Soo, - Gosh, I'm getting goosebumps.
- Seok Jin, and me. - So Min, I'm so tired now.
So Min, I can't stand this anymore.
Okay, I'll see you there.
So Min!
They all have the same thing in mind.
You can even switch So Min's brain with Kwang Soo's.
They think the same.
(They refuse to make strategies.)
(These moths are attracted to a large amount of money.)
They're all coming to exit eight. What should I do?
But I'm not going to exit eight actually.
It's highly likely that So Min will not go to exit eight.
I'm almost there.
I'll choose among exits 2, 3, or 4. I plan to take just 50 dollars.
I think that's the best choice.
Then go to exit 5. I'll go to exit 6.
- Hey. - Do you want to go down together?
Let's meet up then.
Great.
Is exit one far from here?
Most of them will choose among exits 5, 6, and 7.
(Instead of exit 8)
I think it'll be crazy around those exits.
Come if you'd like. Let's all go down together.
I'm possessed now.
Only ghosts can take down dumb heads, and that's me.
They won't come to this exit, will they?
Will there be two people at the exit? I hope not.
We only have 2... No, 1 minute left now.
- Did you decide? - Yes, I did.
I have no regrets.
(Haha arrives somewhere.)
It's driving me crazy.
(Haha is so nervous because he arrived at exit 8.)
I'll get off.
(He's nervous that there might be someone else here.)
I'll go and stand there.
(A cameraman is installing something.)
(So Min's here.)
It's Haha!
- Haha. - Don't get off.
- Goodness. - Is this real?
Are we seriously doing this?
Actually, I'm not interested in choosing exits 2 to 7.
I'll go for either exits 1 or 8.
The other members might choose the exits in the middle.
(Psychologically speaking, my choice would be...)
Can you do rock-paper-scissors with me?
If you win, I'll go for exit one. Rock-paper-scissors.
(If So Min wins, she'll go for exit 8.)
(So Min wins.)
I'll choose exit eight.
(The result in choosing exit 8)
It's not true, right?
It can't be.
Let's go. Where is it?
Is it over there?
So Min, did you choose here for certain?
I chose to go for exit eight.
(He overestimated her.)
Gosh, seriously...
What should I do?
We already need to divide by 2.
Gosh, it's tiring.
Tell me. Did you intend on coming here from the start?
- Tell me. - No, I wanted to go to exit one.
It was exit one in the beginning, and you all said you'd come to...
Someone's here.
We're in trouble.
(Is someone here again?)
Who is that?
Someone's here again.
What should we do?
- Is it Jae Seok? - It's Seok Jin.
Seok Jin! Why did you come here?
(Seok Jin has joined.)
- Hey, Speed. - Power, what happened?
(They aren't glad to see each other at all.)
I thought you were going to exit one.
I was going to,
but you all said you'd come to exit eight, so I figured you wouldn't.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- Hey. - I'm done for.
It's all right. It's still 33 dollars each.
They won't come, so don't worry.
I should've gone to exit one.
Gosh, this is crazy.
(While these doubtful members are gathered at exit 8...)
It seems like no one's here.
I don't think there's anyone there.
(Jae Seok goes somewhere secretly.)
Is this it?
Thank you.
Is anyone here?
(There seems to be no one.)
Hello.
(He finally slips away from the moths.)
My goodness.
It's you, Jae Seok.
Why did you come here?
Gosh, it's Seok Jin.
How annoying.
Jae Seok is here.
- No. - Did you come here?
He came to exit eight.
We'll only get 25 dollars each.
(He calculates.)
It's time to choose. Which exit will it be?
I choose exit eight.
After telling people on the phone that I choose exit eight,
I thought about changing my mind.
I think people will go to exits 5, 6, and 7.
Why did you come here?
- I didn't think you would. - I didn't think it'd be this many.
How did you come here? The maximum should be 2 or 3.
(Where are the others?)
I understand this game perfectly.
The mentality of the members...
and their habits that I've observed so far...
Instead of being a moth,
I'm clever like Jeong Yak Yong.
(He has a misunderstanding.)
Take a look.
I'm worried that someone else will come for 50 dollars.
I'll choose among exits 5, 6, and 7.
(Will she get greedy or stay safe?)
- Really? - These are three numbers.
I want to be arrogant and go to exit one.
I'll go to exit one like an arrogant person.
I want to get 40 dollars and live a normal life.
(Here's the arrogant man.)
I'm clever like Jeong Yak Yong.
(Like Jeong Yak Yong, Kwang Soo chooses exit one.)
This is also possible.
Many members could gather at 1 of the 70-dollar exits.
- I hope they're doomed. - That's possible.
- Look. - What?
Did someone else come?
- Don't come here. - Is that Se Chan?
(They didn't expect someone else would come.)
(Se Chan, the youngest moth, arrives.)
Se Chan.
- Is this a meeting place? - No.
- Why did you come here? - Hey, moths.
- Leave. - Leave.
- All the moths... - Leave.
- are here. - You should leave.
This is incredible.
I didn't expect the five of us.
Do we get 20 dollars each?
This is the worst.
This is exactly what I predicted.
It's because you came here.
- Why did you come? - Just wait and see.
I came here to catch you.
What about you? Why did you come here?
I didn't expect you and Se Chan to be here.
There's no one else.
Really? Okay.
(Jong Kook gets 50 dollars.)
Really? This is really amazing.
(Ji Hyo gets 70, Jong Kook gets 50, and Kwang Soo gets 40 dollars.)
(The rest gets 20 dollars each.)
It feels cool here.
It's very nice.
You can come here directly from the street.
I've never been here.
It used to be an overpass.
- It was Seoul Station. - Seoul Station?
- People used to... - It's nice here.
Walk over the road.
- Look at the trees. - It's in the middle of the city.
(Which mission awaits them at Seoul Overpass Park?)
Now that you're all here, here's the status of mission fees.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin,
Haha, Se Chan, and So Min.
All of you were at exit 8, so you get 20 dollars each.
How did all of you choose exit eight?
I thought everyone would think.
(What did he say?)
I thought you'd go to exits 5, 6, or 7.
Did you hear that?
It's because he won 50 dollars.
You were too greedy.
Who's more annoying than Jong Kook is Kwang Soo.
- Jae Seok. - How could you?
I wasn't being a coward.
I was only being clever. I wasn't being a coward.
What if people gathered at that exit?
I thought about exit one.
There's less than one percent chance of winning.
It's called Discordance Race.
(What is Discordance Race?)
- What is it? - Discordance Race?
If there's discordance among all the members during the mission,
- the race is over immediately. - Really?
- The race is over immediately. - Discordance?
Is it discordance among all of us?
- It's discordance among all. - If we went to different exits...
The shoot would be over if we went to different exits.
I just said that. Why are you repeating?
He wants to be heard.
You don't know which one the producer will use.
We don't know.
I already said it.
- He said it. - You've been talking a lot so far.
He might use mine.
You've been on the show for eight years.
- You know he won't use your part. - He sometimes does.
(It's sometimes.)
- Sometimes? - He can't...
let go of his hope.
Seok Jin continues.
Is the race over once everyone is in discordance?
(She interrupts.)
- Stop it. - Stay quiet.
Your part won't be aired.
Stay quiet. Your part won't be aired.
(Everyone wants to steal the show.)
This is what Seok Jin always says.
Okay, okay.
Is that it?
My line is, "Okay, let's go."
(He cried 8 years for that 1 line.)
That's my one line.
The part when he summarizes is always aired.
It's never aired when he scolds people.
The part when he scolds others.
The race will be over when everyone is in discordance.
- Okay. - Is that clear?
In other cases,
the members in accordance will receive Accordance Badges.
If there's any member who collects 10 Accordance Badges,
the race will be over.
If there's any member, the race will be over.
Everyone being in discordance will be hard.
Let's aim for collecting 10 Accordance Badges.
- Let's do that. - They should be 10.
- Let's go for 10 Accordance Badges. - Okay.
That's a good idea.
Accordance Badge.
This is great.
Collecting Accordance Badges is easy.
(They're excited for the race.)
Those who receive an Accordance Badge must pay a total of...
one dollar multiplied by the number of members in accordance.
- I see. - We have to pay.
Everything costs money.
When the race is over,
the member who has the most mission fee places first.
- That's important. - Will that person throw the dice?
Yes. The winner has...
the right to choose one member to be exempted from being penalized.
- One member? - Yes.
(The winner can free another member.)
(They must keep as much mission fee as possible until the end.)
(The winner throws the dice and attaches I Go Stickers to someone.)
(Who will win, and who will receive the Sticker?)
Here's your first mission.
It's called Where Is Your Hometown?
(The first mission is Where Is Your Hometown?)
You'll go and choose one of the staff members.
If their hometown is in discordance, the mission is cleared.
The hometown will be limited to 14 provinces.
The sound director isn't here.
(Let's find people from different hometowns.)
Director Kim seems like he's from Jeju Island.
Come here, Young Jin.
Haha.
Young Jin.
- The manager is from Busan. - He's from Incheon.
Someone else might be from Incheon.
There may not be many people...
who are from Seoul.
- Where are you from? - Seoul.
- Are you really? - Yes.
Kwon Ryeol.
(Jong Kook chooses Kwon Ryeol.)
Let's go, Kwon Ryeol.
- Where is your hometown? - Me?
I'm from Gangnam, Seoul.
- Stop joking. - Really.
You're lying. You aren't from Gangnam.
I know you're lying.
It's true.
Hyo Jung.
Hyo Jung, come here.
You look preppy today.
Has everyone chosen?
Seok Jin isn't ready.
- Is it only me who hasn't chosen? - Yes.
I can't decide.
Hurry up, Seok Jin.
Just choose someone.
Wait.
Where's your hometown?
(He approaches the sound director.)
- How about the sound director? - Please come.
It's because he looks interesting.
Come with us.
Bring the equipment.
- It's like a base station. - Let's go.
He carries a base station.
- Be careful. - You're right.
He makes it look interesting.
- But... - It's a base station.
The connection should be good.
Use wireless internet.
(Use data as much as you want.)
- Everyone. - We feel supported.
Each of you brought a staff member.
Let's check...
the result of Where Is Your Hometown?
Let's start with the left.
Here's the hometown of the staff whom Ji Hyo chose.
- She's our main writer. - Yes, she is.
It's Kim Mi Yeon.
(It's time to announce their hometowns.)
He still has to work.
(He stays focused on work.)
- You're getting close. - He has too much work to do.
He has a lot of work.
- He's amazing. - He has to work.
He's amazing.
- He's a real professional. - I'm sorry.
He's a professional.
He looks great.
(He won't miss a thing.)
Where's your hometown?
I'm from...
(My hometown is...)
I'm from Gochang, Jeollabuk-do.
- Jeollabuk-do? - I told you.
That's good.
- It's good. - Isn't Jeollabuk-do rare?
By the way, I worked with Mi Yeon...
when I did Plate Karaoke on "Happy Together".
- What are you doing? - She was the youngest writer.
- She was the youngest writer. - What are you doing?
- He's busy working. - Sir.
Let him rest for a while.
We'll record.
Isn't it the limbo game?
(Everything is good with one boom microphone.)
You can leave it.
I'll do it.
As I said, she was the youngest writer back then.
Now, she's the main writer.
- Really? - Yes.
(The staff member Ji Hyo chose is from Jeolla-do.)
- Next, Song Hwa. - Our youngest writer.
How long have you been working for Running Man?
- Five months. - Was it her?
- Five months. - How has it been?
Do you like the working environment?
Yes, of course.
Please be honest.
(I love it.)
- It's true. - Are you planning to transfer?
No.
Song Hwa works hard.
(Song Hwa, that was a nice answer.)
Where do you come from?
I come from...
(Where is the youngest writer from?)
I come from Daejeon.
- Good. - I come from Daejeon.
(The two answers so far are different.)
- Good. - Success.
- Nice. - This is not easy.
- The answers were different. - It might be possible.
- We might succeed. - They might be all different.
Who are you in charge of filming?
- After Gary left, - Se Chan.
- he shot only ants for two months. - Actually...
(After Gary left, he shot only ants for two months.)
(Since Gary left, )
(I've had no one to shoot.)
Hey.
Just shoot things like those.
(He had to shoot ants instead of Gary.)
(Se Chan, thank you for giving me something to do.)
- I see. - All right.
We've had Jeolla-do and Daejeon so far.
- Where are you from? - Gyeonggi-do?
(The last two answers have been different.)
(Where is the cameraman from?)
Pyeongchang, Gangwon-do.
(Pyeongchang, Gangwon-do)
- Perfect. - We never know.
- We might succeed. - We might.
- No one knows. - We might.
(It's as miraculous as that day.)
(Discordance Mission)
(We can do this.)
So Min, we can do this.
Unbelievably,
we just picked random people.
- Kwon Ryeol came late today. - Really?
I know. That's why he's shooting me.
- I see. - He came to the wrong address.
I'd love to know why you were late.
I woke up late.
According to someone on the social media,
you had a party last night.
He had a party?
He did?
When you have a shooting the next day, please don't...
- It applies to us too. - What party?
What kind of party was it?
It's my wife's birthday next week,
and I'll be away shooting that day.
- So you celebrated early? - Yes.
That's romantic.
(He always celebrates his wife's birthday with her.)
What did you do?
We had meat at a restaurant.
Isn't that what you like?
You eat out all the time.
Wasn't it for your sake?
I know where Kwon Ryeol comes from.
Where do you come from?
(It has to be a different answer for the 4th time.)
(Where is the romantic husband, Kwon Ryeol, from?)
- I'm from Seoul. - Nice.
(Seoul)
- Hwagok-dong. - Is he from Seoul?
- Really? - This is unbelievable.
Are you from Seoul?
You said we could go home.
- We have three people left. - This is going well.
This is unbelievable.
We have three people left.
This microphone belongs to this man.
The moving base station.
While you listen, some members can scream or something.
- Yes. - It must be...
It'd be great if you don't scream.
Whom are you talking about?
Kwang Soo.
He swears too often.
I swear?
- I swear? - Yes.
(Like this?)
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - See?
I apologize.
He's...
He hears it right away.
- I'm sorry. - He hears it right away.
I'm sorry. I was joking.
It's different from how we hear it.
He hears it directly.
All right. I'd like to ask you where you come from.
Please. Gyeongsang-do would be great.
That hasn't come out yet, right?
- No Gyeonggi-do either. - Where are you from?
I'm...
(Where is this base-station guy from?)
I'm from Seoul.
(Seoul again)
(Disappointing)
Is this it?
Wait. Think carefully.
Not where you live right now.
Not where you live.
Where were you born?
You might have been in Gyeonggi-do.
- Siheung, for example. - Where were you born?
Which island are you from?
I'm from Seoul...
(Hitting)
(I don't want to hear it.)
Where in Seoul?
Think carefully.
Did your phone number start with 02?
(Discordance Mission has failed.)
Wait.
- Hyo Jung... - Where are you from?
I'm from Yongsan-Gu, Seoul.
Haha's fashion mentor.
Where are you from?
I'm from Itaewon, Seoul.
- Jong Kook's... - Jong Kook's stylist.
Yes, she's his stylist.
Where are you from, Ji Sun?
I'm from Ganghwa Island.
Ganghwa Island.
When do you feel most rewarded while working for Jong Kook?
When was it the hardest?
Every day.
(It's challenging every day.)
Well...
(The interview ends abruptly.)
(This is the end of Where Is Your Hometown?)
All right.
You've failed the mission.
- Yes. - Yes.
Four of the answers were the same.
- Gosh. - Yes.
- Jong Kook, Seok Jin, - That's right.
Jae Seok, and Haha.
You have to pay a fine of four dollars.
- Again? - Please.
I have only 20 dollars. I can't give you 4 dollars.
- Excuse me. - You'll also get...
four Accordance Badges each.
- What? - Wait.
(They'll get 4 Accordance Badges each.)
- 4? - Isn't 10 the maximum?
- Yes. - Right?
Four each?
(When you have received 10 badges, the game will be over.)
Right?
- It's great. - Lend me four dollars.
You have to pay what you have to pay.
Just four dollars.
Please.
Give it to me.
Can I get one dollar off?
Come on.
I have only 20 dollars.
Take him away. He's asking for a discount.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? It's over.
- You look pathetic. - Pathetic?
- Yes. - Am I pathetic?
Yes, you are.
You guys...
You're unbelievable.
You should have chosen the right one.
(Ji Hyo: 70 dollars, Jong Kook: 46 dollars)
The next mission is...
Who Will You Eliminate?
- What? - What?
(Who Will You Eliminate?)
You'll move to a place...
and write down the name of the person you'll eliminate.
Think carefully on the way.
If two or more people write the same name...
Then you're out.
(They all have to write different names.)
- My goodness. - This is hard.
If no one else wrote the same name as you,
you don't have to remove the name tag.
(If no one else wrote the same name, you won't get a Badge.)
If someone wrote the same name, you have to remove the name tag.
You have to think.
- All right. - We have 20 dollars.
Let's move to the place.
- All right. - Let's go.
(Whose name would be the safest?)
Don't write our names.
- All right. - Don't write my name.
Let me in.
We can't.
Wait, whose name should I write?
I've made up my mind.
Seok Jin was considering Jong Kook.
(If you make the wrong choice, you'll lose money.)
You have to choose a person you think you can eliminate.
Or someone no one else would choose.
(Jong Kook? Kwang Soo? Haha? So Min? Seok Jin? Jae Seok?)
If all names are different, you don't have to remove any name tags.
- If they're all different? - Jong Kook would be number eight.
(Jong Kook would be number eight.)
(You want to write my name?)
No one can remove Jong Kook's name tag.
(If two or more people write his name, they have to.)
Exactly.
(Someone has to write Jong Kook's name.)
You don't want to give me Badges.
(Who has the courage to write his name?)
Who would write his name?
(Anxious)
You have to remove the name tag.
I will by all means.
Okay, I've made up my mind.
I don't think anyone else wrote this name.
(I won't show anyone what I wrote.)
All right, the result is out.
Okay.
Please.
I'll read out the names one by one.
You better get ready.
- The game starts right away. - All right.
All right.
You have just five minutes.
Don't do this.
Why are you approaching me?
(Your comrade can turn into an enemy soon.)
(Approaching)
You wrote my name, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
(You couldn't have approached me because you missed me.)
- I didn't write your name. - You did, didn't you?
- I didn't. - I can't trust you.
That's not true.
(Did So Min really write Ji Hyo's name?)
As I said before...
I promise you that...
if all names are different, we'll stop shooting right away.
Here we go.
Jae Seok chose...
(Jae Seok's choice)
Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok chose Kwang Soo.)
Kwang Soo chose...
Se Chan.
(The names are different so far.)
It might be possible.
- It might. - Se Chan chose...
(Se Chan's choice)
Jong Kook.
(Se Chan chose Jong Kook.)
(He took a risk.)
- We might succeed. - We might.
(Se Chan had announced that he'd choose Jong Kook.)
I don't think anyone else would choose Jong Kook.
(And he really did.)
Discordance!
(It's going well thanks to Se Chan's brave choice.)
Come here.
My goodness.
Jong Kook chose...
(Jong Kook's choice)
Haha.
(Jong Kook chose Haha.)
Wait. Hold on.
(Haha thought no one would write Jong Kook's name.)
(If his strategy is the same with Se Chan's, it means war.)
- Jong Kook wrote Haha's name. - Hey.
Hold on.
(Hold on. Did you write my name?)
(Moving back slowly)
(If Haha wrote Jong Kook's name, he will go to a war with Se Chan.)
The name Haha wrote is...
(Whose name did Haha write?)
(What is Haha's decision?)
Jae Seok's.
We still have a shot!
(Haha chose Jae Seok whom he thinks he can beat.)
Jae Seok's.
(Success is just around the corner!)
- Hey, this is... - We still have a shot!
We might be successful!
This is amazing.
(Only 3 members remain.)
Ji Hyo doesn't look so good though.
(Ji Hyo doesn't look so good though.)
(The names they wrote can't overlap with each other's.)
The name Ji Hyo wrote down is...
(Ji Hyo has a sombre look on her face.)
Hey, this might work out!
(Whose name did Ji Hyo wrote down?)
It's Seok Jin's.
- What happened? - This is amazing.
(Ji Hyo chose to write Seok Jin's name.)
(A miracle is happening!)
I can't believe this. Could we have really done it?
- So Min and Seok Jin are left. - Wait.
(If Seok Jin and So Min wrote the right names, a war won't occur.)
(A series of miraculous decisions continued.)
- What happened? - This is amazing.
Hey, wait.
(Now, only So Min and Seok Jin remain.)
(Whose names did they write?)
(It's a decisive moment for them!)
The name Seok Jin wrote...
is Ji Hyo and So Min wrote Ji Hyo's name too. Start!
(Seok Jin chose Ji Hyo and so did So Min.)
(The 3-way race starts!)
Goodness, she wrote Ji Hyo's name.
(Ji Hyo must hold out for 5 minutes.)
Why did you write my name?
(If she holds out for 5 minutes, it's a success for her.)
(Seok Jin and So Min must remove her name tag before one another.)
(It's a bloody battle in which her name tag is at stake.)
- Wait. What about us? - We are not doing that, are we?
- We don't have to remove the tags. - What about us?
- We don't have to play it. - We don't have to.
- It doesn't matter for us. - We aren't playing that.
(Why on earth are we running?)
- Oh, we don't have to play that. - Unbelievable.
- We don't have to. - That's right.
(Let's just watch them fight over a name tag.)
Look. Seok Jin isn't going easy on her at all.
(They are trying hard.)
Wait, Seok Jin. Stop.
- Seok Jin, stop it! - So Min.
(A battle between one who must keep the tag versus ones who must remove)
(The name tag is removed at last.)
(Seok Jin and So Min removed the tag almost at the same time.)
It's over!
(Which of them removed Ji Hyo's name tag?)
- Who removed the tag? - So Min removed it, right?
No, I did it.
(What are you talking about?)
(After replaying the video, )
(So Min removed the name tag first.)
Seok Jin, you just grabbed it, but it was her who removed it.
- It was you? - Hey, when we removed it,
- it was in my hand. - Hey, hold on.
- Hey, just let me hang this. - Don't you agree? It's the truth.
Gosh, it hurts!
(He accepts the Accordance Badge wholeheartedly.)
Hey!
(Can their decisions be all different next?)
(They set out for the next discordance.)
While we are moving,
you will get to play a bonus mission for discordance.
Okay. Great.
We won't get the Accordance Badge, right?
No, you won't.
- Why? - All right.
This is a bonus mission for discordance.
I am going to present you questions.
The mission is accomplished when every member...
- tells different, correct answers. - Really?
- I think this is manageable. - If a member can't...
answer the question or repeat someone else's answer,
the member will pay five dollars as a penalty.
- That's a lot of money. - We can't repeat the answers.
- That's too high of a fine. - You are too cruel.
- It's a big fine. - I only have 12 dollars.
- It's not a bonus mission. - It's a lot of money.
If all of you manage to say different answers,
only one member of your choice will receive five dollars.
Really?
- This is great. - We can play rock-paper-scissors.
- We can do that. - Here it is.
Ji Hyo will start.
Get ready.
Start.
Who is your closest, ideal type among celebrities?
- Time's up! - Pay five dollars.
(It is...)
- It was a hard question. - Why can't you answer that?
I can come up with 10 names.
- Why couldn't you answer that? - Pay five dollars.
Pay up.
- Ji Hyo has a lot of money. - Okay.
- This is hard. - She keeps losing money.
I'd like to ask Ji Hyo...
- why she couldn't answer. - Why couldn't you, Ji Hyo?
You could have just said Seok Jin's name.
Even though it's just a game, I don't think I can say his name.
(She bluntly rejects Seok Jin.)
(He's rejected.)
- Gosh, aren't you picky? - Even if it's a game...
- Se Chan will start now. - Okay.
- I won't fail. - Nice.
Get ready. Start.
Who is your closet, ideal type among celebrities?
(Unable to talk)
- Time's up. - Lee Ha Nee.
(The schemer waited...)
( for the right timing and robbed him of 5 dollars)
Hey, what was that?
- He covered my mouth. - What?
What do you think? Should he pay or not?
- He should pay. - He must.
But starting now, this isn't acceptable.
- I agree. - No one can do this from now on.
(Let's be fair.)
(This is how they're going to play?)
- Promise, everyone. - We can't cover someone's mouth?
- No. - I can do other things, right?
- I accept. - Okay.
- Se Chan, it was funny. - It was funny.
Because of you, we could make a rule.
- You can do it. - I can do it.
- Cheer up. - Let me start again.
If your answer doesn't make sense, it's considered incorrect.
- Of course. - Really? You can't do that.
- That's reasonable. - Let me ask you a question.
It's different from Jae Seok's Game.
It doesn't exist anymore, right?
- It doesn't. - It's gone.
- I'm pressured to change the name. - Change it to something else.
(We were pressured by SBS.)
Was the order from your supervisors?
I never knew that the game could disappear because of its name.
- It was because of the name. - I understand.
- The name can have a negative vibe. - Exactly.
Get ready. Start.
Whom do you want as a guest?
(Whom do you want as a guest on Running Man?)
Hwang Jung Min.
- Byul. - He answered it?
Ahn Jae Wook.
Noh Sa Yeon.
Time's up!
(That... Goodness.)
I was ready to say my answer.
Five dollars?
- It caught me off guard. - It's a bit hard.
I thought it was going to end with Seok Jin.
- You didn't know. - What was your answer?
- Here you go. - Okay.
We will start with Jong Kook.
Get ready. Start.
Whom do you think is the hottest singer now?
Yoon Eun Hye.
Jun Ji Hyun.
(What?)
- Gary. - Jong Kook.
- Wait. - Is Ji Hyun a singer?
- You were to name a singer. - Name a singer.
- She... - She didn't even release an album.
Released a song.
Where? Sing the song.
- Start. - Where did you hear it?
- Hold on. - Didn't she release an album?
Let me tell you.
She was in one of G.o.d's songs.
(She screamed "No!" in the song.)
("Lies" by G.o.d)
(No, no!)
- That's right. - That's not singing.
- She was in the song. - It's "Lies" by G.o.d.
It's not acceptable.
- Come on. - We can't accept this answer.
- Pay up. - Pay five dollars.
- Give him the money. - Goodness.
He doesn't have a lot of money. He has only 11 dollars.
- Jae Seok. - Yes.
- Get ready. - There are only a few left.
Start.
What is your favourite late night food?
Late night food? Tteokbokki!
- Jokbal. - Kimchi jjigae.
- Bossam. - Whelks.
- Sundae. - Doenjang jjigae.
Kimchi.
(It's late night food...)
(and kimchi is your favorite?)
- His favourite is kimchi. - No way.
What's wrong with that?
- Seriously? - It's a side dish.
- He keeps losing at this game. - Jong Kook.
Let's keep playing this game.
- He's not good at this. - He lost again.
- You should said something else. - He doesn't eat a lot.
We'll start with Ji Hyo.
- We'll play the last round. - Okay.
Start.
Who is your closet, ideal type among celebrities?
- Seok Jin. - Ha Nee.
(Seok Jin fails to answer.)
Time's up!
- Hey! - He did it for your sake!
- You can't name an ideal type. - Right.
- You can't name an ideal type. - You are married.
- You have a wife. - I can name my ideal type.
(You have a beautiful wife. How can you name someone else?)
- I bet she is thanking me now. - I agree.
- I'm sure she's thankful. - I can't believe I'm paying for it.
- I agree. - It's not about money.
You saw what happened though right?
Ji Hyo named Seok Jin even though she said she couldn't earlier.
(This is a shocking confession of Ji Hyo.)
- What's up with you? - She said she won't name him,
- but she said his name. - Ji Hyo.
- What's up with you? - Forget it!
- I'm sorry that I'm married. - Get off me.
I'm sorry that I'm married.
- I didn't know. I'm sorry. - "I'm sorry that I'm married."
- I didn't mean it. - I'm sorry.
- "Seok Jin". - Okay.
In five minutes, we will arrive at the restaurant.
All of us can have lunch, right?
You'll see.
- What if we can't have lunch? - Do we have to buy our own meal?
- No way. - Our choices have to be different?
- That makes sense. - Gosh, Seok Jin.
I at least want to have a meal.
I can eat everything at this time of day.
(With suspicions, they arrive. What is the mission at the restaurant?)
We are going to enter the restaurant now.
- Enter randomly one by one. - Pardon?
- I knew it. It's about the menu. - Who wants to go first?
- Se Chan, why don't you go first? - Hey.
Sure.
- Go. - Right now...
(A Chinese restaurant in Seoul)
This is the place.
Hand-pulled noodles.
(What did Se Chan see?)
I have to choose among them?
(A menu with 8 dishes?)
This mission is What Will You Eat?
(The mission is What Will You Eat?)
The mission is accomplished if everyone choose a different dish.
(They must choose different dishes.)
If two or more members' decisions overlap, it's a failed mission.
The members who choose the same dish can't eat.
(The members who choose the same dish can't eat.)
(They can only have the dish they order.)
- What? Those members can't eat? - No.
(Guessing the others' choices is the key.)
(It's what you want to eat versus what others won't choose.)
Jae Seok will choose jjajangmyeon.
Jong Kook will choose jjamppong.
- I want to eat what I want. - There's only one dish for me.
- There's only one. - Jjamppong?
Yes.
My goodness.
(He knows what Jong Kook likes.)
(There are many dishes to choose.)
It's between Tangsuyuk and fried mandu.
(Which dish will no one choose?)
I choose fried mandu.
Fried mandu.
I don't like my personality.
To be honest, I want to choose what I want like Jong Kook.
I choose fried mandu.
We'll order fried mandu. Please go upstairs.
(Se Chan chooses fried mandu.)
(It's Seok Jin's turn.)
- Do I choose? - Yes.
We discussed before I came.
I choose the most expensive dish.
(He chooses the most expensive one.)
I choose Tangsuyuk.
Tangsuyuk?
People won't choose Tangsuyuk.
I bet they want to eat soup.
I can't eat?
(It's Haha's turn.)
Seok Jin definitely chose Tangsuyuk.
(He's exactly right.)
When it's complicated,
it's fried rice.
When it's depressing, it's ulmyeon.
(Will others choose fried rice or ulmyeon?)
I feel depressed.
I choose ulmyeon.
(Haha chooses ulmyeon.)
- It's this way. - I actually want jjajangmyeon.
(Everyone is in discordance so far, and Jae Seok enters.)
I must choose a dish that no one else would choose...
while it's something I want to eat.
Someone might choose japchae rice.
I'll choose something uncertain.
(He thinks of choosing a dish that people may not pick.)
Tangsuyuk?
(It's a time of distress.)
I don't think it's Tangsuyuk.
How about fried mandu?
He's taking long.
(Why is he taking so long?)
Tangsuyuk.
(He chooses Tangsuyuk.)
What about japchae rice?
(Is japchae rice better?)
How about Tangsuyuk or fried mandu?
I don't know anymore.
(Which did Jae Seok choose?)
May I eat some pickled radish?
You should let us eat it.
- We can eat it, right? - Are we in a cage?
I should eat just in case.
(Eat something in case you can't later.)
We can eat it.
- He's here. - Jae Seok.
He's here.
Is it stir-fried or deep-fried?
Jae Seok definitely chose jjajangmyeon.
Right?
(Did he choose jjajangmyeon?)
Some dishes will coincide,
but others probably chose unexpected dishes.
Should I consider what I want to eat?
(Should I choose what I want?)
(Inside the bus while Ji Hyo chooses...)
(So Min starts to behave in a strange way.)
- Are you sleeping? - No.
Were you sleeping?
She tends to fall asleep easily.
I didn't fall asleep.
I got tired all of a sudden.
- What's wrong with me? - How is that possible?
(She thought about which to choose.)
Can you see me?
(We can see everything except her eyes.)
- You're really silly. - Why?
Why do you say that? I'm not.
Right, Jong Kook?
- That's why you look good together. - Next person is up.
Gosh, stop it.
Next person is up.
I'll go.
Enjoy your time together.
I always support you.
Then you take them away from me.
Come on.
It was also the case in Russia.
Kwang Soo.
Yes?
Good luck.
Is it high calorie or not?
It's high.
Ji Hyo definitely chose either jjamppong or jjajangmyeon.
- No, I didn't. - Is it deep-fried?
- I didn't choose them. - You like them, don't you?
Ulmyeon is...
something you can order.
I bet Jong Kook will order ulmyeon.
When it's depressing, it's ulmyeon.
(Don't order my ulmyeon.)
Ulmyeon?
(He's been indecisive for five minutes.)
I bet no one ordered ulmyeon.
(Will he order it?)
- What's there to think about? - Why is he thinking so long?
- There's no right answer. - What's there to think about?
Are you talking to me?
What's there to think about?
I meant everyone.
You seem too bold today.
Please sit. Did you think a lot?
You don't eat deep-fried food, right?
I don't.
(Did he choose ulmyeon?)
Let's see.
I can't give up because I might be able to win.
(He cannot give up winning.)
I wondered why everyone was taking so long.
I can't choose.
(Now he understands.)
(Which shall I choose?)
Can you say stop?
Stop.
(Is she playing that old game?)
I choose japchae rice. It's way too common.
I bet Seok Jin chose it.
Could you say stop?
Stop.
I don't want Tangsuyuk.
Why did you ask us to say stop?
This is the last time. Please say stop.
Stop.
(The last choice is fried rice.)
I don't like it.
What is it?
(She doesn't like fried rice.)
(The game was pointless.)
It was fried rice, but I choose...
(Which dish did So Min choose?)
(Se Chan, Seok Jin, and Haha's dishes are revealed.)
(All 8 members made their decisions.)
We have an interesting result.
- Is that so? - Many must coincide.
- My goodness. - Many of us probably...
- chose the same dish. - I don't think so.
(Probability of everyone in discordance is 1 out of 40,320.)
(Will everyone be in discordance?)
- I'll announce the result. - Please, please.
I'll start with Seok Jin.
He chose Tangsuyuk.
- I almost chose Tangsuyuk. - Thank goodness.
(He's relieved.)
(Which dish did Jae Seok choose?)
Tangsuyuk.
We'll order Tangsuyuk for you. Please go upstairs.
(Wait)
May I change it?
Change to what?
I choose japchae rice.
I almost chose Tangsuyuk.
Next is japchae rice.
(It'll be amazing if he's the only one.)
Jae Seok, Jong Kook and So Min.
(They all chose japchae rice.)
(3 members chose japchae rice.)
Gosh.
That's so many.
- Congratulations. - Many people chose that one.
- Congratulations. - Why did you choose japchae rice?
Don't you like jjajangmyeon?
I chose it because it was uncertain.
The three will receive three Accordance Badges each.
- Jae Seok. - How many badges do you have?
- You have 7. - You'll pay 3 dollars.
He has seven badges.
So Min has three badges.
My goodness.
Poor Jae Seok.
Next is ulmyeon.
It must coincide.
(Will Haha get to eat lunch?)
Haha and Ji Hyo chose ulmyeon.
When it's depressing, it's ulmyeon.
- It's jjajangmyeon when annoying - Pay two dollars each.
- Give it to me. - I'll enjoy my food alone.
Let's enjoy our food, Seok Jin.
This is great.
- This is good. - The rest of you.
Yes?
(Se Chan chose fried mandu.)
Seok Jin.
He chose Tangsuyuk.
(Seok Jin chose Tangsuyuk.)
(Their fate depends on Kwang Soo's choice.)
Se Chan and Kwang Soo chose fried mandu.
(They both chose fried mandu.)
(It's unfortunate.)
Are you serious?
I bet no one chose fried mandu.
I choose fried mandu.
(Kwang Soo was sure of himself.)
They chose fried mandu for a meal.
Fried mandu is too little, and it doesn't look cool.
How could you choose fried mandu?
Goodness.
I like fried mandu.
I love fried mandu much more than you.
Put on the badges.
Here's Tangsuyuk.
(Seok Jin gets to enjoy Tangsuyuk by himself.)
- It looks delicious. - May I smell it?
(He sniffs it.)
It smells good.
(He really wants some.)
(Why did you order fried mandu?)
- Goodness. - Give us one more chance.
- Just one more. - It's the last chance.
In that case,
I'll give you the last chance.
Choose a dish...
- individually. - How about rock-paper-scissors?
The winner should eat.
- Okay. - Eat something delicious.
(They're working hard.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors.)
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, and Kwang Soo win.)
Okay.
- It's not yet. - The three of us should play.
Gosh, this is annoying.
We haven't played together in a long time.
I'll eat.
Normally, I'm the winner among the three.
Right?
It's true.
Jong Kook is usually the winner.
- We must break the habit. - I will.
(He wants to defeat Jong Kook.)
(Jong Kook always avoids all penalties.)
(That's why the unlucky ones suffered.)
(They're determined to take revenge.)
- We must break the habit. - I will.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(They fail to defeat Jong Kook.)
(I was hoping in vain.)
- It's better to lose first. - Right.
You can never win.
If Jong Kook wins this time too,
it means Kwang Soo and Jae Seok...
can never beat Jong Kook.
- I can never beat him. - Never.
If Kwang Soo loses...
I've made up my mind.
- I'll definitely win. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jong Kook has taken everything away from me.)
(I'll get back at him today.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(It's a tie.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(Kwang Soo loses.)
(I see.)
(It was only a dream.)
You should have just lost early.
How embarrassing is this?
I'll have jjamppong.
Jjamppong? Okay. Jong Kook will have jjamppong.
It only did Jong Kook good.
- Great. - Jong Kook is unbelievable.
Kwang Soo can never win.
- It's unbelievable. - It is.
What are you doing?
(What are you doing?)
It seems like...
- you're getting tired of it. - What are you doing?
I am.
If he can't finish it, he has to pay five dollars.
- That's absurd. - You shouldn't waste food.
- You didn't say that. - You shouldn't throw away food.
- You have to pay five dollars. - Don't be absurd.
Who are you to decide?
(Don't be absurd. Who are you to decide?)
He has to pay five dollars if he doesn't finish it.
Seriously.
It's unacceptable.
You usually have to pay 10 dollars.
That's not okay.
(He donates his Tangsuyuk to the staff.)
You can't do that.
- He couldn't resist. - Why not?
(He couldn't resist.)
You should have resisted.
- Not many could resist that. - I know.
You should resist.
(He opens his mouth.)
(I want to eat it.)
- Wait. - What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
He was testing you.
- I'm sorry. - Did you see that?
I'll have to find a way.
(Careful)
Isn't it a little weird?
Ji Hyo.
Can you lend me five dollars?
Lend me five dollars.
- Can we switch places? - Ji Hyo.
- Jae Seok keeps... - Jae Seok.
I can lend you some money. Give me three pieces of Tangsuyuk.
- Sure. - Just three pieces.
Okay. I'll go get it.
Five pieces.
Just 3. You said 3.
If you have five pieces, you'll get tired of it.
- 3 pieces for 3 dollars. - You said 5 dollars.
- 5 dollars. - All right. 3 pieces for 5 dollars.
It's too expensive.
Seok Jin.
Can I get three pieces for a dollar?
(Can I get 3 pieces for a dollar?)
(Wait.)
(3 pieces for a dollar)
- Sure. - Okay.
(My goodness.)
All right.
Give me the money first.
So Min, give me the money.
Right now.
Give it to me.
You promised me.
- Are you a broker? - Give it.
No, I'm not. I just made a deal.
Really?
Give it to me.
You're taking a commission.
No, I'm not.
Are you taking 80 percent?
- She promised me. - Wait.
Is the fee 80 percent?
- I mean... - Give it to me.
You promised me.
What?
Give me three pieces. We made a deal.
You promised me.
This is why farmers have a hard time.
- Okay? - What?
So Min, give me your plate. I'll put the pieces on your plate.
- You... - Let me choose the pieces.
Let me choose the big ones.
I kept the promise.
He's taking so much money.
Kwang Soo.
(Do you want a piece for five dollars?)
What?
- What? - Hey.
Do you think I'm stupid?
(Do you think I'm stupid?)
I just saw everything.
Do you seriously think I'm stupid?
It'd be so funny if Kwang Soo buys it for 10 dollars.
What is it?
Two dollars.
- I'd buy it. - Hey.
I can buy 6 pieces for 2 dollars there.
(I can buy 6 pieces for 2 dollars there. )
There, I can get six.
Should I put them on sale?
You can get everything for a dollar.
I shouldn't use my money.
My situation is too good to use my money.
Kwang Soo is...
chasing Ji Hyo.
I had only 10 dollars, and I still ate it.
Just get it for a dollar.
I could do that.
Stop it. If you feel so hesitant, forget it.
Hey.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors and...
Okay.
(Whatever that is, I'm in.)
If I win, you have to pay two dollars.
If I lose, I'll give it to you for free.
(If Seok Jin loses, he'll give the food to Kwang Soo for free.)
- That sounds good. - If I win, you'll pay two dollars.
- It's worth a try. - If I lose, it's free.
- It's a nice deal. - It's for free.
(If Kwang Soo wins, all the food will be his.)
(But if he loses, he'll fall behind in the competition.)
- Okay. - It'll be for free.
(How will this match end?)
If I win, you have to pay two dollars.
(If Seok Jin loses, Kwang Soo can have the food for free.)
It'll be for free.
Okay.
(How will this rock-paper-scissors end?)
(Kwang Soo loses.)
Good. Give me two dollars.
(No words are needed.)
All right.
You should have said yes to a dollar.
You could have bought it for a dollar.
Why would you pay two dollars?
Seok Jin usually doesn't show paper.
I know.
- Why didn't you show scissors? - Kwang Soo showed rock.
I made some money with my Tangsuyuk.
2, 4, 6, 7...
I have 17 dollars.
I earned five dollars.
You could have bought nine pieces for a dollar.
You got 6 pieces for 2 dollars.
It tastes good.
It does.
(What is So Min doing?)
So Min.
(Laughing)
Why are you eating cucumbers?
Kwang Soo said I could.
(Kwang Soo is like that.)
Can I have the cucumbers?
Sure.
(He's so kind.)
(So Min will never starve.)
So Min is...
- She's strong. - She's so strong.
You're so strong.
She's eating smiling.
- She let you stay at her place. - She paid the driver too.
Give a couple of pieces to her.
I gave her the cucumbers.
(What more should I give?)
(They're friendly as always.)
How can you do that?
There's not much left.
- It tastes so good. - I was going to...
(Ji Hyo: 63 dollars, 2 Badges Kwang Soo: 32 dollars, 2 Badges)
We'll move to another mission spot.
I think it'll be our last mission.
This will determine the result.
I hope it'll be the last one.
- Let's do this. - We'll...
give you the last chance.
Okay.
If you succeed,
you can win as much as the amount you bet.
Again?
We'll play...
Jae Seok's Game.
(Bonus Mission 2: Jae Seok's Game)
- What? - What about Seok Jin's Game?
You have to say an irrelevant answer to 3 consecutive questions.
(You have to say an irrelevant answer to 3 consecutive questions.)
- Wait. - Has the name changed?
- I love it. - Wasn't that Seok Jin's Game?
That's Seok Jin's Game.
Did you change the name?
Is it the same game with a different name?
Is this called Jae Seok's Game?
They're relaunching the game.
- The changed their sign. - Did they change the sign?
They're opening the store again.
I love it.
Let's start from Se Chan.
How much will you bet?
I have only 10 dollars.
- Bet 10 dollars. - Bet just a dollar.
- I couldn't bet just a dollar. - Bet 10 dollars.
Hey, be a man.
5 dollars? I shouldn't bet 10 dollars.
I bet five dollars.
- Okay. - You're a man.
Here we go.
Let's go.
(What result will his manly betting bring?)
Ready, start.
- What's your girlfriend's weakness? - An air conditioner.
What makes you saddest?
Song Ji Hyo.
(What makes you saddest? Song Ji Hyo.)
- Do you have a crush on her? - Song Ji Hyo.
(I had to confess my feelings this way.)
What about her?
Did I...
- make you sad? - Did she make you sad?
Could it be because...
Ji Hyo's dream guy is Seok Jin?
- I see. - That's not true!
- Ji Hyo. - That's not true!
- I'm sorry I'm married. - Stop it.
I'm sorry I'm married.
I was thinking of Ji Hyo.
Too bad.
(Se Chan fails.)
- Next... - Two dollars.
- So Min, bet just 2 dollars. - 2 dollars.
- 2 dollars. - All right.
Ready.
Start.
What would you like to say to Kwang Soo's father?
Don't walk, run.
(Don't walk, run.)
- Hey. - What?
"Don't walk, run?"
How can she say that to my father?
Please run, sir.
He's old.
- "Don't walk, run?" - I mean...
I mean...
He just turned 60.
I'm sorry.
- You can walk. - Sir.
So Min wants you to run, not walk.
- I'm sorry. - How am I supposed to take it?
Here's two dollars.
Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, bet 30 dollars.
You should bet 30 dollars and place 1st.
Everything else is meaningless.
You need to place first. How much money do you have?
I have 55 dollars.
Ji Hyo has 55 dollars.
If you bet 30 dollars, you can place 1st with 60 dollars.
It won't be easy.
- I will bet 25 dollars. - 25 dollars is a good amount.
- Wait a minute. - Really?
- Okay! - Then Se Chan will place last.
- I will do it! - He will do it.
- This is a big game. - I'll take the challenge.
- All right. - I am betting 25 dollars.
That's a good choice.
(Kwang Soo overexerted himself to take Ji Hyo down.)
Let's begin.
Ready.
Set, go.
- What was your conception dream? - 3 times 7.
What do you want to have the most these days?
Cucumber kimchi.
(Cucumber kimchi)
What do you want to have the most these days?
Cucumber kimchi.
(Cucumber kimchi)
That's a small wish.
Did you want cucumber kimchi?
(Kwang Soo dreams of having kimchi.)
It can't be helped.
He will lose 25 dollars.
Why did you say that?
I will buy you kimchi.
(Kwang Soo fails to acquire money.)
The last chance is over.
We will move to the next location.
I fell asleep and leaned to this side.
Please hit me once.
- Where? - The head.
You are tired, right?
(Hitting)
- You shouldn't have hit so hard. - You need to wake up.
It hurts.
- What are you doing? - I asked him to hit me once.
Are you trying to simulate a relationship?
Don't force it. We are not interested.
It's not like that.
- It's not like that between us. - They are so annoying.
- Don't force it. - Stop it already.
It's not like that.
Gosh, So Min is ridiculous.
I hate it, too. I won't do it.
I don't want it.
Do you want it? I don't want it.
(She is upset.)
Why are you making a fuss?
What are you doing?
- I don't want to see them. - It's not like that.
Ji Hyo, I bet you want to simulate a relationship with me. I am sorry.
I am sorry. I won't be able to do it since I am married.
I won't be able to do it.
- That's not true. - I am sorry.
(Will this be his first on-screen relationship?)
We are at a coin karaoke.
- It's a coin karaoke. - A coin karaoke.
- It's nice. - It's a coin karaoke.
- This is fascinating. - There are numbers.
It looks like we have to choose a room.
- They set up the rooms. - Really?
(What kind of discordance will they have here?)
Your next mission is What Will You Sing?
(What Will You Sing?)
What Will You Sing?
Your next mission is What Will You Sing?
When we give you a singer, choose and sing...
a song of theirs.
The mission is a success if all members sing different songs.
- One singer will be given. - One singer will be given.
- Do we fail if the songs overlap? - Yes. The rules are the same.
In essence,
those who know a lot...
- of the songs have an advantage. - Right.
Those people should sing difficult songs.
- Okay. - Okay.
I'll go in room eight.
I am at a coin karaoke.
- Which song should I sing? - This is nice.
Before we start the game,
- we will play a warm-up game. - Okay.
When I tell you to start, begin playing the quick wit game.
(The quick wit game)
Does everyone know how to play?
- Yes. - Yes.
Open the door and shout your name when the game starts.
Get ready.
(They get ready.)
(They can neither go together or be the last one remaining.)
Set, go.
- Song Ji Hyo. - Lee Kwang Soo.
(Song Ji Hyo, Lee Kwang Soo, Jeon So Min)
(Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, and So Min fail from the start.)
(They are in sync in a situation like this.)
The three of them failed.
- I knew they would get caught. - That was amazing.
- Did they get caught? - Pay up three dollars each.
- Three dollars. - What?
So Min, Kwang Soo, and Ji Hyo must pay up three dollars.
- They make a great team. - They are hilarious.
- They make a great team. - That was hilarious.
What happened to me?
We will play the game one more time.
If you miss the timing and become the last one remaining,
- you will need to pay five dollars. - Five dollars?
(The last one remaining will need to pay 5 dollars.)
I will be the first one to go.
I will go first no matter what.
I told you, I am going to go first.
I will go first.
My door is already open. You can see it, right?
You know that I keep my words.
- I am a moth. - I will go first.
I have nothing to lose.
Seok Jin, did you understand the game?
(Seok Jin is quiet in his room.)
Seok Jin, did you understand the rules?
Are you sure you understood the rules?
- Should we tell him one more time? - Hey.
- Maybe he is sleeping. - Hold on.
- Is he alive? - Seok Jin!
(Wait a minute.)
I almost put a finger under his nose.
Watch him carefully.
I know what I am doing.
Promise us that you will move every five minutes.
(Do that just in case.)
This time,
we will include Accordance Badges too.
- What? - Accordance Badges are involved.
(It's an intense, warm-up game.)
This is bad.
(Relaxed)
Haven't you played this game before?
I have never gotten caught.
They can't hold out until the end.
(He speaks from experience.)
They're not patient enough.
(Let's come out in our room's order without telling Seok Jin.)
(The 7 members will end the game without telling Seok Jin.)
(Seok Jin will pay a fine of 5 dollars.)
Okay.
(They carry out their plan without Seok Jin.)
(I have never gotten caught.)
Get ready.
(They get ready.)
(Are you ready?)
Set, go.
- Yu Jae Seok. - Jeon So Min.
- Song Ji Hyo. - Haha.
- Kim Jong Kook. - Lee Kwang Soo.
Yang Se Chan.
Set, go.
Yu Jae Seok.
(Wait... What?)
What happened?
(Seok Jin gets the penalty.)
That was perfect.
You planned it, didn't you?
We did it.
He got the penalty.
- 5 dollars! - 5 dollars!
- You planned it, didn't you? - Five dollars!
(We have never had such a fun, warm-up game.)
Give me five dollars.
- You didn't come out. - It seems like you planned it.
You got the penalty because you didn't participate.
(Seok Jin is completely fooled.)
Now, let's get the mission started.
- Okay. - Okay.
The artist whose songs you must choose from...
is Kim Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
(They must pick a song by Turbo or Kim Jong Kook.)
(He debuted as a member of Turbo in 1995 and swept the nation.)
(As a solo artist, he won awards in all 3 broadcasting stations.)
(That's right. Jong Kook is a singer.)
I know a lot of his songs.
"One Man", "Reminiscence",
"At the Ski Resort", "Twist King",
and "Black Cat".
Let's see... Jong Kook's songs?
(They need to choose songs that won't overlap.)
I need to choose a song no one else would sing.
Please.
(The mission will be over if they all choose different songs.)
Should I sing, "Some Jazz Bar"?
(It used to be the top 1 song men sang at karaokes.)
That's the song, right?
Did someone choose this song?
I have many options.
I only need to choose a song people don't know.
(He is best-suited for this mission.)
"Men Are All Like That", "Because I Am a Man"...
What should I sing?
(Please don't let the choices overlap.)
Please write down the title of the song.
(Everyone has chosen a song.)
Now,
press the start button.
(Music, play)
("Black Cat" is a song from the 1st album...)
(with a cheerful beat and cute dance.)
(When you become sulky)
(He has no sense of rhythm.)
(Meanwhile, So Min)
It has been a while since I sang this song.
(She is getting ready to dance.)
(Her good cheer explodes.)
("Twist King" is a hit song from Turbo's 2nd album...)
(that made everyone in Korea do the twist.)
(Shake it.)
("Choice")
Turbo.
"Choice".
("Choice" is a song from Turbo's 1st album...)
(that has a stylish beat and sorrowful lyrics.)
(He lowered the pitch by 5 octaves.)
(He channels Kim Jong Kook.)
(A reggae mosquito from Jamaica appears.)
(He enters the realm of dolphins.)
(Meanwhile, Kim Jong Kook, the real singer, sings a song.)
("Don't Be Good to Me" is a song from Kim Jong Kook's 6th album...)
(about the sorrow of one-sided love...)
(that made men's hearts ache.)
(Absorbed)
(That's right. This muscular man...)
(was the king of singers...)
(before he became the king of removing name tags.)
(So far, the 4 members chose different songs.)
(Will there be discordance among them?)
Number one, Jae Seok, please open the door and sing.
(Jae Seok reveals his song.)
(Which song did Jae Seok choose?)
I won't be sad.
("Some Jazz Bar")
(5 people have been discordant so far.)
(So Min chose "Twist King" by Turbo.)
(What song did Ji Hyo choose?)
("This Is the Person" by Kim Jong Kook)
(They all chose different songs.)
(6 people have been discordant so far.)
(Haha chose "Choice" by Turbo.)
(He sings in a high octave.)
Nobody's the same.
This might work.
(They are all hopeful.)
(He's the biggest obstacle to their success.)
(What song did Seok Jin choose?)
("Men Are All Like That" by Kim Jong Kook)
(They all chose different songs.)
Next.
Next. Who's number six?
(7 people have succeeded so far. Who's left?)
(It's the unlucky Kwang Soo.)
(If Kwang Soo chose a new song...)
Nobody else chose "Some Jazz Bar" so far.
(If Kwang Soo chose a new song, they are all discordant.)
(Unfortunately, their fates...)
(are up to Kwang Soo.)
(What song did he choose?)
What?
("Some Jazz Bar")
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are concordant with each other.)
Did you choose "Some Jazz Bar"?
(They are the Unlucky Duo.)
Jae Seok.
Why would you choose this song?
Why did you choose "Some Jazz Bar"?
It's my favourite song.
("Some Jazz Bar"...)
(by the Unlucky Duo.)
(You betrayed me back then. How are you doing?)
Why did you choose "Some Jazz Bar"?
It's personally my...
- Jae Seok. - Gosh.
Since Kwang Soo and Jae Seok are concordant with each other,
Jae Seok now has 11 Accordance Badges.
- This is done. - So the mission ends now.
Kwang Soo paid two dollars as penalty,
so last place switched from Se Chan to Kwang Soo.
(After paying the penalty, Kwang Soo comes in last.)
(The tables are turned.)
- Really? - How much is it?
- How much is it? - Really?
- This is the person - This is the person.
- You're in last place - You're in last place.
- How much do you have? - You can't switch.
I have two dollars.
I have three dollars.
(It's a dollar's miracle.)
You fool.
This is the person, you're in last place.
- That was close. - So today's Discordance Race...
ends now.
The winner is Ji Hyo with 50 dollars.
- That's awesome. - The last place is Kwang Soo...
with two dollars.
(It's a new project on Running Man.)
(People's Recommendation Project:)
(A Place for 1 Percent)
(Once you receive 3 I Go Stickers, you must leave.)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(So far, Haha and So Min have 1 each.)
(And today, another I Go Sticker will be given out.)
Ji Hyo, please put the stickers on.
I'll do that.
Are you going in order?
That looks good. I have a chance.
- Can you give me 5, not 4? - That's for Se Chan.
- I'm 6. - Kwang Soo is 6 again.
(She assigns everybody a number.)
(There are Jae Seok and So Min left. What would Ji Hyo do?)
(She saves So Min.)
I left out So Min.
- Thank you. - She already has...
- an I Go Sticker. - Ji Hyo.
Why don't you try throwing the dice before you stick these on?
Let's just do it.
- Yes, let's just do it. - Just let it go.
- It won't be number 1. - I don't want to be number 5.
I don't want to be number four.
Are you one, Jae Seok?
(Haha has an I Go Sticker already.)
- Let's go. - Roll it.
- Start. - Roll it.
- Roll it, Ji Hyo. - Please.
- Start. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo rolls the dice.)
(She throws it up.)
(Who will get an I Go Sticker?)
(In a moment)
(These ladies catch the members' attention...)
(with their unbelievable skills.)
- Start. - Okay.
(An I Go Sticker will be given to the person with the number.)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
- Number four. - Yes.
- It's Seok Jin. - It's Seok Jin!
(Seok Jin is chosen.)
- Seok Jin is her ideal type of men. - He is.
(Ji Hyo gives an I Go Sticker to Seok Jin.)
- He's her ideal type. - I love you, Seok Jin.
- Good. - I love you.
(I'm sorry for giving you a Sticker. I love you.)
He's her ideal type.
- Seok Jin. - That was a twist.
(A week later)
- Hello. - Hello.
Here we are.
- How many years has it been? - We're back.
It feels like we're on a trip.
It feels like summer when we come here.
We have a staff member of this water park here.
Hello.
Here he goes again.
- Shouldn't he be... - Excuse me.
In a safari with these clothes on?
- Nice to meet you. - Why am I from here?
Aren't you a zoo keeper?
What do you mean?
- He works in the safari. - Gosh.
- Seriously? From the start? - He takes care of rhinoceroses.
Are you doing this as soon as we start?
It's going to be my turn soon.
Is this a bit too much?
(I have good fashion sense.)
How could they talk about fashion?
You were easy on Kwang Soo.
- Turn around, Kwang Soo. - Excuse me.
He's just a step before we reach you.
Is that right?
- I'm headed towards you. - You're the final destination.
- Is it my turn? - Are you at a sauna?
Excuse me for asking,
but you took care of your pet here, right?
- Me? - Don't say yes.
Don't say yes.
Isn't that it?
Hand.
- Good job. - It suits you.
- I'll give you a snack in a bit. - Nice.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Why aren't you pointing him out?
- Wait. - Do you think he'll get hurt?
- I'm sorry... - He tried to dress up.
He's just a tourist here.
He's a local.
No, you should ask the ladies when they get here.
I dressed...
the best here.
- Hey. - Are you serious?
This is the best swimmer's fashion.
(Confidence completes one's fashion.)
Don't you like this colour, Jae Seok?
It's pretty awesome.
I thought he was my shadow.
(He thought Jong Kook was his shadow.)
- Look at your backside. - What's wrong?
- This is normal of me. - You wear...
black too much.
- You look like a watermelon seed. - Really?
All right.
That's done.
We started with the zoo keeper.
We have a lot more to come,
so we can't waste more time on clothes.
People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent.
It's Number One Couple Race.
(Number 1 Couple Race)
- Really? - It's a couple race.
I had a feeling.
It's usually a couple race when So Min and Ji Hyo are not here.
It's been a while.
Before you meet the ladies,
I'll invite a special, male guest.
Hello.
(Who is it?)
(He's tall and handsome.)
It's Actor Lee Tae Hwan.
(He's making his mark on dramas and variety shows.)
(This audacious man is on Running Man.)
You have such wide shoulders.
I heard Tae Hwan is known for...
having broad, thug-like shoulders.
Whereas, Jong Kook is a real thug.
- He's just a gangster. - What are you saying?
- He's just... - I'm known for my shoulders too.
A normal gangster.
Tae Hwan is known for his shoulders.
- He has broad shoulders. - Let's welcome Tae Hwan.
(Lee Tae Hwan is here.)
It's a couple race,
so let's welcome the female guests who will be joining you today.
This feels so awkward.
(Are the ladies...)
(finally here?)
(Who will they be?)
First partner, please come on out.
(The first partner is revealed.)
(She doesn't hesitate.)
(She loads her finger gun.)
All right.
Good. Come on.
(I'll capture you with my finger.)
(The owner of tempting fingers, Song Ji Hyo)
(She only needs a finger...)
(to make Jae Seok dance.)
Good job. I like this.
- Good one. - That was good.
This must be "A Dog of Flanders".
(Is it a girl and Patrasche?)
Come here, puppy.
We are joined by Ji Hyo.
Let's welcome the next person following Ji Hyo.
Please come on out.
(The second partner is revealed following Ji Hyo.)
(Who will it be this time?)
(She looks shy.)
(Who will it be?)
It's Koyote.
- It's So Min. - It's her.
(It's So Min, the lively mascot of Running Man.)
Here she comes.
She's here.
Our crazy lady is here.
The crazy lady...
is here.
Hello.
I'm afraid.
So Min and...
Ji Hyo look different today.
(How do we look?)
During couple races, Ji Hyo...
puts a lot of makeup on her cheeks.
(Look at her.)
It looks good. It worked well.
- You're cute. - Your makeup looks good.
I heard Tae Hwan was joining us today.
- I even wore a hat. - Good job.
(Nice to meet you, Ji Hyo.)
- So Min was saying earlier... - Come on out.
(Is there somebody new?)
It starts from here, right?
(The third partner is revealed.)
- She has long legs. Who is it? - She has long legs.
Who are those two?
(These two ladies have long hair and skinny bodies.)
I like the color of their clothes.
(Who are these mysterious ladies?)
- What? - Come here.
Are they back?
(Who are these mysterious ladies?)
(It's Na Eun and Ha Young from Apink.)
(Here are the beautiful, idol stars.)
Yes.
(He's being so fussy.)
It's Apink.
(Their dance captures everybody's attention.)
(They'll steal the men's hearts.)
- Come here. - Come.
It's Apink's...
Ha Young and Na Eun.
This is insane. They're so pretty.
It's Apink's Ha Young...
and Na Eun. It's been a long time.
- Hello. - Hello.
Se Chan just whispered,
"She's mine."
(That's worth a laugh.)
- I'm not lying. - Hey.
Who is it? Who's yours, Se Chan?
- Say it. - Don't say that.
Don't do that.
I'm embarrassed.
- Who is it? - You look so happy.
They're so pretty.
All right, then.
Who's next?
(With her white shoes, she looks charismatic.)
- Look at her. - Look at her shoes.
Her shoes look very fierce.
They are.
(Who is the fifth lady...)
(who looks good in white shoes?)
Next person, please come on out.
Who is it?
(Who is she?)
That's me.
(Hey, boy)
(She causes a stir amongst the guys...)
(even before she appears.)
It's Lee Sun Bin.
(It's Lee Sun Bin.)
(She has hot looks and personality.)
Hello. Hello.
Increase the distance between your arms.
(She set Kwang Soo's heart on fire the last time she was on.)
(How have you been, Kwang Soo?)
She has such pretty eyes.
Her eyes.
These are the best guests, right?
I love those colours.
(Today's guests are some of the best.)
We're all a mess except for Tae Hwan.
Aren't we a mess?
We'll talk to...
- Sun Bin shortly. - Sure.
She said she liked Kwang Soo, but when she saw him...
and got tested on the lie detector, it was proven to be a lie.
It was a lie.
(Their first meeting)
(My ideal type of man is truly Lee Kwang Soo.)
(She answered yes without hesitation.)
(Is she telling the truth or a lie?)
(It's a lie.)
On interviews...
(No, you're mistaken.)
(I tried resisting. It hurts.)
(Their first encounter was a painful memory to Kwang Soo.)
Did you use Kwang Soo?
- I didn't. - You didn't?
- I'm a woman of principles. - Really?
Since that day...
And I'm not lying.
He couldn't sleep for two weeks because his heart was fluttering.
He told me on a serious note that he wanted to date somebody.
He said he wanted to be in love.
(Will they reunite today?)
Let's move on. There's another person.
There's another one? Why are there so many?
Why are there so many today?
Who is it?
(You can't help but be protective of her.)
(It's Son Yeo Eun who looks younger than her age.)
(She's a scene stealer on every drama she's in.)
(She's a great actress who can act as a protagonist and an antagonist.)
(Son Yeo Eun)
She's pretty.
She's Ha Eun's mom.
She kind of looks like So Min.
- She does. - She looks like So Min.
This is my first time meeting you.
- Same here. - Right?
- You two look alike. - When I went...
somewhere, this person...
called me by your name.
- Really? - That's when I realized.
- Really? - She's much prettier than I am.
- No way. - They look alike...
because...
they're both pale.
(They look alike because they're both pale.)
They both have light skin.
What if she talks a lot too?
I've met Yeo Eun before on a different show.
- She's not easy. - She's not?
Right.
(Who follows Yeo Eun?)
Next...
Jong Kook's woman is here.
Really? Oh, dear.
- They dressed the same! - Who is it?
- Jong Kook's woman is here today. - That's right.
He dressed like this for a reason.
I see.
Who's my woman?
You have one.
(Who's Jong Kook's woman with a similar fashion sense as him?)
("Ring Ring")
("Ring Ring"?)
(It's Hong Jin Young, the woman of trot music.)
It's Jin Young.
It's Hong Jin Young!
They're matching.
They're both wearing black.
That's too much.
My goodness.
Come here. Come to Jong Kook.
- It's okay. - Come to Jong Kook.
Hello.
It's been a long time.
- How have you been? - She's here.
Hello.
(It's Hong Jin Young, Jong Kook's woman.)
You've gained weight.
I had chicken feet last night before sleeping.
Is that right?
She looks like Ahn Moon Sook.
(Is she the friendly and easy-going Moon Sook?)
Who?
I agree.
No, Jin Young.
- He's wrong. - He's wrong.
- He means... - You should wear something else.
You look like a mature woman.
- That's what he means. - You look fine.
Jin Young is the last guest.
(The best guests are here today.)
It'll be fun.
Let's have a small talk with each of them.
As you may know,
- Na Eun is on Psy's "New Face". - "New Face".
She's the muse on it.
- That's right. - She's incredible.
("New Face" by Psy)
(Na Eun is the best of the best as an elegant lady.)
Can you show us "New Face"?
- Can you show it to us? - We need to see it.
- Look expressionless. - Let's see it.
Please come forward.
(She hesitates and takes a step forward.)
(She changes 180 degrees.)
Here it is.
(Yes, I want some new face)
- New face - New face.
One more.
My goodness.
(It's a powerful dance from such a small lady.)
Good job.
She's good.
- She's good. - She's good.
Good job.
She's so charming.
She's not done.
- Good one. - Good.
- New face - Good job.
- Na Eun. - Good job.
- You're the best. - That's it.
(Watch out for Na Eun's irresistible charms.)
(She's ready to dominate Running Man.)
- Move. - Move.
- Move. - You move.
They're my glasses!
Na Eun.
Hey.
Move over.
She cares about Psy's song more than she does her own.
What are you going to do?
I do dance to it more than our own songs these days.
You're dancing too hard.
- That was powerful. - Your producer will be upset.
What are you doing?
- What's wrong with him? - You are not on her level.
- Avoid him. - I just...
wore these sunglasses. What's wrong?
- I'm sorry, - Ha Young is next.
But do you sell weapons?
(He's dressed like someone who secretly sells weapons.)
You look like someone from Cuba.
That was good.
- That was great. - You guys are too funny.
(Talent show is always fun.)
(Next week)
(This is not the end.)
(The ladies show their charms.)
(They cry...)
(and laugh.)
(These love stories take many turns.)
(And)
Hey.
(Is this her charm or a horror movie?)
(It's a transformation beyond your imagination.)
(It's a bloody race...)
(to avoid I Go Stickers.)
(Who will become...)
(Running Man's best partner?)
(Suspicious Partners, next Sunday)