(Incheon International Airport on the day of departure for penalties)
People at the airport are in a frenzy.
They don't look so bad in the outfits.
(Oh, my goodness. Look at their outfits.)
- It looks like Kwang Soo owns it. - Poor Haha.
- It looks like Kwang Soo owns it. - It's as I expected.
Kwang Soo, it looks like you tried to dress up.
(What are the outfits that attract their attention?)
- Jong Kook and Haha... - It seems they have a unique theme.
(The Fashionable Trio: Airplane, Box, and Scales)
- Kwang Soo... - They don't look that bad.
- seems like he dressed up. - Exactly.
(Confident poses of men with a true sense of fashion)
Isn't it nice? It will be a popular look in Japan.
I think Kwang Soo owns the outfit.
(They didn't fathom that their last week's penalty would be so moving.)
If this is our airport fashion, shouldn't we bring our luggage?
- You guys look nice. - Shouldn't we have our luggage?
Do you remember how Haha insisted on taking the box outfit?
(Do you remember how Haha insisted on taking the box outfit?)
(This is the best out of the three.)
(You're still picky even now.)
- You know these outfits? - This is the best one.
It's better to wear something that completely stands out.
Otherwise, people think that's your real sense of fashion.
- Do you get it? - Yes.
(So when Haha chose the outfit first,)
(he was happy to get the box outfit.)
- But you... - Just to wear that outfit...
Did you work hard just to wear that outfit?
Now that I'm wearing this outfit, his outfit looks much cooler.
(I think the airplane outfit looks better.)
- You look so weird. - What about Kwang Soo's outfit?
- Jong Kook looks like an artist. - Me?
- Doesn't it look nice? - It does.
Whenever he walks, the airplanes fall.
(The planes drop just like his confidence does whenever he walks.)
- He had way more than that. - The amusement park...
- That one is much better. - It looks like you own the outfit.
Kwang Soo, you should just come to this side.
- Kwang Soo. - It looks like it's your outfit.
- What? - Isn't that his?
- Who would wear this? - Just come here.
Everyone can agree that this is made for him.
- Look at the length of the pants. - I agree.
(The pants length is customized for Kwang Soo, the model.)
How can it fit him perfectly?
It fits with his hairstyle.
Everyone, today is the day you'll depart for your penalties at last.
Do you remember the project, A Place for One Percent?
Haha and Se Chan were selected to ride Nevis Swing in New Zealand.
- We are going at last. - Among the viewers watching...
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo were picked to try Cage of Death...
In Australia for the project, Half and Half Tour.
- It was from Half and Half Tour. - That's not scary at all.
- We just got our visas to go now. - The penalties...
Four of you were exempted from participating in the penalties,
but So Min and Seok Jin will join them on their trip to Australia.
Ji Hyo and Jong Kook will join them on their trip to New Zealand.
We're tagging along just to tease them, right?
On these penalty trips,
- your decisions will cause results. - Really?
Today's special is called Swallowtail Butterfly Tour.
(Small decisions will cause big results.)
(Excuse me, Haha.)
- Stop hitting me with your box. - I'm sorry.
- Stop hitting him. - I just got too excited.
My goodness.
Is there a chance for us to redeem ourselves?
For this penalty trip, the place of your penalty was modified.
- For Haha and Se Chan... - That's right!
who might feel it's unfair,
- we prepared six special chances. - Awesome!
(The staff prepared a set of 6 special chances.)
Wait, Haha. It hurts.
- Are you serious? - All right.
However,
advantages and disadvantages are mixed in this set of chances.
(It's a mix of both?)
Team Australia and Team New Zealand will each choose...
- three Chance Cards randomly. - Chance Cards?
You can only read the Chance Cards when you accomplish...
the given missions presented to you in each country.
- You can also refuse to use them. - Okay!
We can refuse to use it?
- Seriously? - We've been wronged!
- We didn't choose this destination. - That's right, Haha.
(What are these random Chance Cards?)
"We won't receive it." "We will get it."
- What are these? - "We will go."
"We will do it." "We won't receive it." "We will get it." "We will go."
- Is it, "We won't receive money"? - All right.
(Team New Zealand chooses...)
"We'll be..."
- "exempted from the penalty." - That's right.
- "We won't get the penalty." - "We won't get the penalty."
- "We all won't do the penalty." - "We all won't do the penalty."
Look at this.
(They choose three cards accordingly.)
"We won't go to the penalty place."
"We'll have our meal."
- "We'll go home." - "We'll go home."
"We'll go home," is the best one.
(Team Australia also chooses their cards.)
- Hey. - This might be correct.
- "We won't go to a penalty place." - Choose a good one.
Kwang Soo, stand with Team Australia.
Why are you pretending to be in their team?
(I don't want to look out of place.)
- You're wearing your own outfit. - It's not that.
- It wasn't a penalty for you. - Stop acting like you're with them.
You're wearing your own outfit. Gosh, you stand out too much.
- It does look like your outfit. - Look at them.
Let me just stay with them.
(I miss standing with them.)
- Hey, line them up. - Please!
All right. So you have chosen your three Chance Cards.
Right now, the cards are covered. After you accomplish your missions,
you can choose one of the cards and read all of them.
That's the only way we can read them?
However, you can refuse to use the Chance Cards...
- even if you accomplish missions. - We have a choice.
Swallowtail Butterfly Tour will begin now.
We'll head to the boarding gate now as you are.
- Okay! - Okay.
- Look at Kwang Soo. - In this outfit?
It really looks like he owns the outfit.
How am I going to use the toilet in this outfit?
- You should remove the airplanes. - I have to take off everything.
- Remove some of the airplanes. - My goodness.
Do we have scissors? Make a hole in Haha's outfit for the toilet.
(Do we have scissors? Make a hole in Haha's outfit for the toilet.)
(Their journey to the gate is complicated and humiliating.)
This is humiliating.
- Which way is it? - Stay as a group.
I need to stand between them.
This is driving me crazy.
Don't you think it's ready by now?
I'm also carrying out a penalty too.
Kwang Soo, why did you dress up?
My outfit is a penalty too.
(They have a long way ahead.)
(They'll travel to Sydney together and then part ways.)
(They make a domestic transfer to Darwin.)
Why are you waving at the camera all of a sudden?
Do you think this is a travel TV show?
You're not on a trip to have fun.
Why did you do that?
Join me, Jae Seok.
We are here to carry out the penalty.
I want to at least feel like I'm traveling.
(I wish it was a trip, not a penalty.)
The in-flight mission will begin now.
(We filmed under cooperation of the crew and passengers.)
Let me see.
"When the seatbelt light is turned off, pick one representative...
and find Producer Jung Hae.
(1 presentative must find Producer Jung Hae. The assigned seat is 4B.)
What did you say?
- 4B. - 1 of us must go to 4B.
- Should I go? - Yes, So Min. You should go.
When they give you the mission, share it with us.
(He's nagging.)
Don't try to deceive us again.
(A close-up shot of a chatterbox)
- So Min. - Yes?
(She films a close-up shot of the chatterbox.)
(She studies Kwang Soo's facial features.)
Just go to 4B. Go to 4B.
- Go to 4B. - Go to 4B.
(Where is 4B?)
What if she can't find the seat?
(I'm right here.)
Hello.
(It's packed with staff members, and yet, you couldn't find me.)
(She closes up on him out of embarrassment.)
The first mission with the Chance Card on the line,
Relay Crocodile Quiz will begin.
(Relay Crocodile Quiz)
You succeed if 3 out of 4 members answers correctly.
Here comes the first question.
Crocodiles are reptiles within the subfamily of Crocodylinae...
with tough scales that cover their backs from head to tail.
Their leather...
is made into expensive handbags and belts...
when it has a great number of scales and beautiful patterns.
In that case,
(This is the first question with the Chance Card on the line.)
does this crocodile wallet contain...
10 dollars and above or not?
I still can't get used to these kinds of quizzes.
10 dollars and above?
Yes or no?
(Does the crocodile wallet contain 10 dollars and above or not?)
The production staff doesn't give us a lot of money.
Even if the wallet is expensive,
I think it contains less than 10 dollars.
(I think it contains less than 10 dollars.)
- It contains less than 10 dollars. - Yes.
Please check.
(It's time to check her answer.)
(10-dollar bill)
(1-dollar bill)
- How much money does it contain? - 11 dollars.
(She fails to get the 1st question right.)
You failed to get the 1st question right.
For goodness' sake.
Since you failed the mission,
please put your lip print...
on this acrylic board as big as you can.
(What? My lip print?)
- My lip print? - Yes.
What is So Min doing over there?
Look. She is doing something on her own.
- What is she doing? - She is looking at the mirror.
Is she looking at the mirror?
I just need to make it as big as possible, right?
(I just need to make it as big as possible, right?)
The thickness doesn't matter, right?
As big as possible.
(She draws big lips.)
(If you have small lips, draw big lips.)
That was unnecessary.
It needs to be a print.
Okay, I will give you my lip print.
(Why is she going this far?)
(Her lips are scary enough to make Joker run away.)
I need to print my lips before the lipstick dries.
(She kisses the acrylic board)
(She makes the print big and clear.)
(She laughs like a middle-aged man.)
(She leaves her lip print on the acrylic board.)
Here comes the next question.
Do I need to answer it?
No, when I give you the question,
bring someone you think would know the answer.
Do I get to keep this?
No, please give it back to me.
(I can't let you have it.)
He picked you, right?
I...
(What were you up to?)
What did you paint on your lips?
- What is that? - You look like a clown.
Jae Seok.
- You... - Jae Seok.
- What? - You should go.
Go.
It must be the mission.
Good luck, Jae Seok. Please succeed.
(So Min's face tells me...)
(that this mission won't be easy.)
Here comes the question.
- It's the second question. - What is this?
Please put a lip print...
that is bigger than So Min's.
(Put a lip print that is bigger than So Min's.)
(What?)
(Open your mouth like a crocodile and put a lip print.)
- Bigger than So Min's? - Yes.
(Revealing the 2nd question to So Min)
Please bring someone...
who will be able to put a lip print that is bigger than yours.
- You may not reveal the question. - Okay.
(She may not reveal the question.)
(She walks over to Jae Seok without worrying much.)
So Min...
didn't have to paint beyond her lips, did she?
(I don't understand why she painted beyond her lips.)
What is wrong with her?
Excuse me.
She doesn't mind her face.
"Excuse me."
(The clown calls over the flight attendant without shame.)
Aren't you embarrassed of your face?
I need to erase it quickly.
It's okay because Jae Seok will soon be in this state.
- Shall I go? - Yes.
(Can Jae Seok succeed when he only painted his lips?)
(Opening his mouth wide)
(He does the mission like an aggressive crocodile.)
I did it.
(So Min's lip print and Jae Seok's lip print.)
Did I succeed?
(The mission is a success.)
- So Min failed, and you succeeded. - Okay.
Here comes the third question. The third one is...
Crocodile Telepathy.
Go back to your seat,
choose a member who will be the best at telepathy,
and send him over here.
(Choose a member who will be the best at telepathy.)
There is no such member.
Telepathy?
You succeeded.
Yes. Kwang Soo.
- What is it? Did you succeed? - Yes. Go.
(He heads over to the producer without knowing about the mission.)
Here comes the third question.
Okay. It's a quiz.
The ancestor of crocodiles is...
Postosuchus of the Jurassic Period.
Postosuchus.
Here comes the question.
In that case,
yell either "Croco" or "Dile".
You fail if you yell the same word as me.
Crocodile.
(Between "Croco" and "Dile",)
(say the one that is different from the one the producer chooses.)
1, 2, 3.
- Croco. - Crod.
("Croco" and "Crod")
"Crod" isn't an option.
"Crod" isn't an option. "Codil" isn't either.
- Start. - All right.
1, 2, 3.
- Croco. - Croco.
Come on.
(Please give me one more chance.)
- I will give you one more chance. - Okay.
Here we go.
1, 2, 3.
- Dile. - Dile.
(With 2 out of 4 members out, the Relay In-flight Mission fails.)
Shall I leave?
1, 2, 3.
- Croco. - Croco.
(They are in sync like the members of a choir.)
(Kwang Soo is upset.)
How are you doing this?
Are you reading my mind? How are you doing this?
- You failed. - How are you doing this?
Please go back to your seat.
May we try one more time?
- One more time. - This is your last chance.
1, 2, 3.
- Dile. - Dile.
(For goodness' sake.)
(Their "cooperation" results in a failure.)
(Team Nevis Swing is heading to New Zealand.)
Half and Half Rock-Paper-Scissors?
(Half and Half Rock-Paper-Scissors)
(The producer and 2 members play rock-paper-scissors in turn.)
(The mission is a success if there are 2 wins and 2 losses.)
The two of you should go first.
Ji Hyo should go first.
We have it easy.
It doesn't matter if we win or lose.
Let's go.
Rock-paper-scissors
I lost.
(1 loss)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Scissors, paper)
- I lost. - You lost.
- Both of you need to win. - Win.
(Both of them need to win.)
(Both of them need to win for the Chance Cards.)
(Can Jong Kook start the miracle of the Chance Cards?)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Rock, paper)
(There is no miracle.)
(They fail to acquire the Chance Cards.)
Did we fail?
(I can't believe you failed us.)
(Watch me.)
Come on.
How are you so good at rock-paper-scissors?
He is good at rock-paper-scissors.
(Both teams fail to win the Chance Cards.)
(They fly for three more hours...)
(and arrive at Queenstown, New Zealand.)
(The nature of New Zealand is clean and clear.)
1, 2, 3.
(The production crew is waiting for the members to come out.)
(10 minutes pass.)
(Even after 30 minutes, the members don't come out.)
Why aren't they coming out?
Let me check.
We are stepping on land after hours.
This is incredible.
This is nice.
(The air is nice.)
(They get to see New Zealand...)
(two hours after landing.)
We are stepping on land after many complications.
New Zealand!
I have never seen...
people get caught for so long...
- at a tourist's destination. - A place full of pain, New Zealand
(No one is in their right minds.)
Let's go, Ha Pills.
- Ha Pills. - Ha Pills.
- Let's go, Ha Pills. - We have a lot to share.
We have a lot to share.
- Yang No Name. Song Kwan Tae. - Yang No Name.
For goodness' sake.
(The four of them come out with new nicknames.)
I am very curious...
about why we got out so late.
How did this happen?
Let's go over the first story.
Let's talk about Ha Pills.
I say this all the time,
but immigration check scares me.
I become anxious because I don't speak English.
- What did Haha say? - Haha gave me...
some words of courage.
- However... - "Se Chan."
"Se Chan, don't worry."
"No problem."
He continued to say those words.
(Se Chan, don't worry. No problem.)
At the immigration check to enter Australia,
I was trembling, and Haha went ahead of me.
He told the immigration officer,
"My crew."
"Oh, crew. Okay."
Then he stamped my passport.
I told Haha that he was my hero.
Haha continued to say,
"Don't worry, no problem."
He continued to say that.
I trusted him.
However, the immigration check was tougher at New Zealand.
Haha said,
"Se Chan."
"No problem. Don't worry." I said okay. A moment later,
- someone stopped Haha. - He was stopped.
"Why? What's wrong?"
(Surprised)
"Me?"
- I didn't say that. - You did.
Say just what actually happened.
- They took his baggage. - They took my baggage.
The sniffer dog started sniffing at my baggage...
and barked. They opened my baggage and found two anxiety pills.
(They found two anxiety pills.)
(It was for Nevis Swing.)
I was so surprised. I said, "Trust me."
- You said that too many times. - He said, "Follow me."
"These pills are popular in Korea."
"Very popular."
- My goodness. - My goodness.
- They took him somewhere. - They took me somewhere.
I was so annoyed. A woman patted me on the back.
- She was very nice. - They were nice.
She told me nicely, "You're not allowed to bring these."
I said, "But it's very famous in Korea."
She still said no. I just got my digestion pills back.
That's why my nickname is...
- Ha Pills. - Ha Pills.
Meanwhile...
Meanwhile, something hilarious happened.
While your baggage was being checked,
someone wanted to take a picture with me.
Se Chan was behind me. As he's a member too,
I told him to come.
She was being nice.
That person was getting ready to take a picture,
and I approached.
She looked at her phone screen and then at me.
(She looked at Se Chan.)
- "Who are you?" - "Who are you?"
She looked so serious. "Who are you?"
(Why are you ruining my picture with Ji Hyo?)
- Was she Korean? - Yes.
"Me?" So...
- Ji Hyo said I was a member too. - I said, "He's a member too."
"Really?"
In the end, she let me be in the picture.
And then she said,
- "What's your name?" - "What's your name?" I got hurt.
That's why your nickname is Yang No Name.
(It's a sad story.)
I'm Yang No Name.
- Work harder. - I will.
Ji Hyo's new nickname is...
- I'm sorry. - Song Kwan Tae.
Hi, Kwan Tae.
Why did you...
We stopped over in Australia on the way to New Zealand.
Ji Hyo wasn't showing up.
Then we heard an announcement.
It was in Korean.
Ms. Cheon Soo Yeon.
They were looking for Ms. Cheon Soo Yeon.
When she got there, it turned out...
- her baggage... - The thing is...
belonged to Mr. Kim Kwan Tae.
(5 hours ago at Sydney Airport)
Ji Hyo took someone else's baggage.
Really?
Her baggage is still on the carousel.
- Mr. Kim is looking for his. - Unbelievable.
- Mr. Kim, we're sorry. - We're sorry.
- Our member made a mistake. - She did.
Please forgive her. Have a nice trip.
We're sorry.
Kwan Tae.
My goodness.
Ji Hyo picked up that baggage so confidently.
- She did. - "That's mine."
- Right? - "That's mine."
"Is that yours?" "Yes."
Ji Hyo, he must have been as surprised as you were.
Mr. Kim, I'm sorry. I took your baggage by mistake.
I sincerely apologize.
I don't care about anything else. We just need Jong Kook.
You're right.
Look. It's beautiful.
I've seen this place on TV.
- That's permanent snow, right? - Yes. It never melts.
(Queenstown is a popular vacation spot for the locals too.)
- It's so beautiful. - It's so sunny.
You'll see a really beautiful lake soon.
It's so picturesque.
It was where "The Lord of the Rings" was shot.
- Really? - Oh, really?
- It's so beautiful, right? - It is.
It was such a long journey.
I'm so happy to finally see this.
This street is so beautiful. We should get out.
(They randomly decided to get out of the car.)
- It's so nice. - It's fantastic.
- The weather is perfect. - This is it.
It's crazy.
Are we really here for the penalty?
Se Chan, it's so nice here.
It's so beautiful here.
- Shouldn't we take a picture? - Let's do that.
Ji Hyo, come here.
Come close.
1, 2, 3.
(Kwan Tae, Jong Kook, Pills, and No Name)
Thank you, guys. I'm here thanks to you.
- It's beautiful. - It's crazy.
Gosh.
(The weather here is crazy too.)
It took so long.
How many hours was it?
We're finally here.
(Scruffy)
Did it take two days?
- I can't breathe. - It's very humid.
- It's humid. - It's the rainy season here.
The weather is...
- It's so humid. - It's very hot.
I'm the only one wearing a sweater.
- We're finally here. - I look like I'm in Korea.
(For the unlucky ones, even the weather is bad.)
- It's raining. - It's raining.
- It's the rainy season. - It's...
- It's the rainy season. - It is, and it's also off-season.
Shouldn't crocodiles take a rest?
Wouldn't they be sensitive now?
On the way here...
We've never been to Darwin before.
Everyone we met on the way said,
- "Why would you go there?" - "Darwin?"
"What can you do there around this time?"
"Everything must be closed now."
Even Koreans living here said, "Not many have been there."
It's near the equator.
It takes four and a half hours from Sydney.
By airplane.
It's raining. Excuse me.
It's...
- What about us? - heavy rain.
(Go on, you guys.)
- What? - It's like the Amazon.
- We were just starting to talk. - It started raining so hard.
I haven't seen this heavy rain in a long time.
Come here.
It's raining so hard.
(They hurriedly get in the car.)
You failed to complete the in-flight mission.
You're not allowed to open the mission bag.
How are we going to see the crocodiles?
Only Jae Seok and Kwang Soo will see them.
Oh, right.
Why are you two here?
- I don't know. - I don't know.
You two surprised Kwang Soo in the airplane.
- He even took a picture. - I was shocked.
- I was going to the bathroom. - You were mistaken.
They were...
sitting next to each other, holding hands.
I was so shocked.
(Were they holding hands?)
You were mistaken.
(They were both Seok Jin's hands.)
- You were mistaken. - I was so shocked.
It was so cowardly of me.
I just accepted it and went to the bathroom.
- That's ridiculous. - I just ignored it.
You're making me look weird.
I was mistaken.
- I was so flustered. - The picture looks so convincing.
- Wherever So Min goes, - Something goes wrong.
- Ridiculous things happen. - absurd things happen.
Wherever So Min goes, something weird happens.
And it's always something inappropriate.
It's always a bit dirty.
(It's always inappropriate for TV.)
- Right. - I don't understand.
I don't know what is wrong with my life.
That's very well said. It's always inappropriate.
It is.
We'll arrive at a park near our hotel soon.
- All right. - Let us take a shower.
- I want to take a shower. - I want to wash myself.
- I need to wash my hair. - I need a shower.
To be honest, and I know I'm no different,
but I was passing by So Min, and she smelled bad.
(The actress smells bad.)
So Min hasn't washed her hair in a while.
- It's itchy. - Does your hair smell?
No. Your hair smells too.
- Should we smell each other's hair? - No.
I want to see how bad it is.
- Stop it. - Let's do it.
- Hair? - Yes.
(Smell my hair.)
Take a big whiff.
(How does So Min's hair smell?)
(Laughing)
So Min, smell Kwang Soo's.
(Is it that bad?)
- Smell Kwang Soo's hair. - It smells so bad.
- I was so surprised. - See?
- It's bad, right? - I was so shocked.
I smelled it too.
It's like someone punched me in the nose.
- Smell Kwang Soo's hair. - I was so shocked.
- Let's not do it. - Come on.
- Don't do it. - Come here.
Gosh.
(It even looks dirty.)
- I think it'll smell bad. - It's going to smell terribly.
(How bad does Seok Jin's hair smell?)
Here.
Gosh!
(Jae Seok is furious.)
Gosh. Kwang Soo, it's real.
- Goodness. - I'm not acting.
(Is it that bad?)
How...
(Laughing)
- I can't believe it. - Hey.
It smells like tom yum goong.
Did you have tom yum goong?
(It smells like Asian food.)
So Min.
- It smells like tom yum goong. - Smell it.
- Exactly like tom yum goong. - So Min.
I've never smelled anything this bad.
Someone probably poured tom yum goong over his head.
Smell it.
Take a big whiff.
Gosh.
(Frowning)
It smells weird.
- It's tom yum goong, right? - It smells like toast.
- Toast? - Toast?
That sounds nice.
Toast smells good.
Gosh.
It smells almost like poop.
Let me smell yours.
He smells like an old man.
I don't smell that bad, do I?
It smells okay. It's annoying.
I'm sorry. After smelling Seok Jin's hair,
I lost the ability to smell.
I can't smell anything.
- Seok Jin smells the worst. - Seriously.
The viewers won't like it.
It's impossible to like the smell of your hair.
It's terrible.
When your hair smells that bad and you scratch your head,
- you get stuff under your nails. - Right.
It's awful.
Show me your nails.
- Why? - They might be dirty.
This is what I saw.
(Are they caught?)
- What? - That was the moment.
That was the moment.
(It seems familiar.)
- That was exactly it. - No way.
- Gosh. - Isn't it true?
Gosh, I'm tired of it.
Are you the new Monday Couple?
No, we aren't.
I'm okay with that, but what about So Min?
Don't ruin my future.
We're here.
(Where did Team Australia arrive?)
There's a view of the sea.
- The trees look amazing. - It's beautiful here.
It's the sea.
What are those?
- As soon as we arrive... - What are they?
They're cans.
What are they? Are those pickled cans?
It's a boomerang.
(There's even a boomerang.)
Here's your mission for the second Chance Card.
The mission for the second Chance Card...
is called Fly Like a Butterfly, Throw the Boomerang.
(Fly Like a Butterfly, Throw the Boomerang)
Throw the boomerang used for hunting in Australia...
to hit the cans with Australian specialty products written on them.
You must acquire all the products written on the cans that...
you've missed within the time limit.
Otherwise, you fail.
- Find them here? - What are they?
- Find them here? - If we hit...
all of them, we don't have to find anything?
- No. - If we hit all of them.
(It's important to hit many cans.)
Get out of the way, Seok Jin.
(Jae Seok makes a scene.)
So Min, get out of the way. You'll get hurt.
Don't throw it in our direction.
You're trying to act cool.
- Throw it like this. - I'm scared.
Be careful. That's not how to do it.
(Shall I try it?)
It won't fly, Kwang Soo.
Move out of the way.
Do you know a lot about boomerang?
(Do you know a lot about boomerang?)
Have you ever seen a boomerang?
My nickname was Yoomerang when I was a child.
No way.
What are you talking about?
- Hold it like this. - Isn't it the other way?
Like this.
Throw it low. Kwang Soo.
It's raining,
so consider everything before throwing.
Jae Seok, take off your leggings first.
(It's not time to brag.)
- Jae Seok. - What are you talking about?
(He's wearing tight leggings.)
- Aren't those pajamas? - Isn't it the boyfriend look?
- My goodness. - Seriously.
I didn't wear them for the shoot.
Do you wear them for yoga?
I wore these to be comfortable on the plane.
It feels great to run on the lawn.
(Seok Jin suddenly feels free as he runs across the green lawn.)
It's amazing.
- Seok Jin. - It's amazing.
It's great to run on the lawn.
(He's so excited.)
He's lying.
(However, he's lying.)
(No, I'm not.)
It feels great.
Is he trying to act young?
It feels really good.
Try running.
- Give it a try. It's great. - Seok Jin.
He's trying to act energetic.
Try running. It's great.
He said it was great to run, but he wasn't running.
(His running was slower than his walking.)
(It's because the flight was long.)
- I'll give it a try. - It's because of the game.
- I'll give it a try. - I didn't use much,
but it says that I used up all my data for the day.
- I'll give it a try. - It's because of the game.
- I'll give it a try. - You told me to download it.
I didn't use up mine.
- Challenge. - Why didn't you use wireless?
(She's determined.)
Let me try.
He told me to download a game, so I did.
- I used up all my data... - Why didn't you...
- for the day. - I'm going to play.
It says that I used up my data for the day.
You told me to download a game.
Challenge. Please show me some interest.
I didn't use the internet, but I don't have any data left.
- It can't be helped. - Seriously.
I'll turn mine on.
What is the function called?
Go ahead, So Min.
Wait, So Min. We were talking.
We need a conclusion.
(Wait, So Min.)
When can I go?
What is the sharing of internet called?
- You don't listen. - Jackspot?
(Is it called jackspot?)
"Jackspot"?
Do you even know?
It's called hotspot.
(Do you mean hotspot?)
Stay by my side.
You're my base station from now on.
(It doesn't matter how it's called.)
I downloaded a game because of you.
Now, I used up my data as soon as I arrived.
- Challenge. - It's time for you to play.
- It's real this time. - I'll throw this time.
So Min is up.
Here I go.
(There's no need to find the product written on the can that she hits.)
- You got it. - It hit the can.
(So Min fails.)
I told you not to do that.
You stepped on the line.
You can't step on the line.
- Don't step on the line. - Play fair.
So Min, we have to play fair.
- Right. I'm sorry. - Many people are watching us.
I'm sorry. I'll play fair.
(She exposes her head.)
The smell drifted away.
Are you polluting the air...
- in Australia? - No wonder I smelled something.
How could you?
You really need to wash your hair.
Get out of the way.
(Seok Jin goes next.)
(Swinging)
I didn't say, "challenge".
(He doesn't play fair by not saying the word.)
- I should say, "challenge". - Start again.
Challenge.
I think Seok Jin is talented...
- Be quiet. - in sports.
Be quiet. I need to concentrate.
(A talented athlete tries to concentrate.)
(It flies off.)
(That was so close.)
It wasn't close at all.
It didn't go far enough.
- It wasn't close at all. - It didn't go far.
- Not at all. - I thought a baby was throwing it.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
Move out.
- I'm upset right now. - Jae Seok.
(No one was successful. Yoomerang takes action.)
(Will Yoomerang hit the cans?)
- That's right. - Jae Seok.
(Yoomerang succeeds.)
Nice shot.
- You did it. - How many is it?
- Is it one? - I got it.
Didn't I hit three?
We'll count the knocked out ones.
- Three cans. - You don't have to buy them.
- What is it? "Manuka honey". - Do we have to go out?
It's a type of honey.
(It's a famous Australian honey that's good for digestion.)
Do we have to go out?
(He wants to taste it.)
(It explodes.)
Goodness.
(He's forced to dance with the fizz.)
Gosh, what is he doing?
Did you have to do that?
I wanted to drink it.
(He's disappointed.)
Why are you drinking it?
(I'm just going to drink it.)
Can we each play one last time?
Each of you get one more chance.
Okay.
- Let's be serious. - Let's go.
- So Min. - Come here, So Min.
It's okay even if we fail.
It's difficult.
(Jae Seok gains confidence.)
Make it curve.
(Will he succeed again?)
You got it.
(He hits another can.)
- He got it. - Did you hit it?
You didn't say, "challenge". Try it again.
(He didn't say challenge.)
- I did. - You didn't.
- No way. - You didn't say it.
- Didn't you hear me? - I heard you.
- What do you mean? - I said it.
- I heard him say it. - I said it.
- He succeeded. - Why did you whisper it?
- Why? - Did you say it or not?
He really whispered it.
- No way. - Can't he say it in silence?
It's because...
(He said it in his head.)
my Saturday show stopped shooting.
I lost confidence. Do I have to explain that?
- The broadcast network... - But that's...
Why if we don't want to say it?
All of us work in entertainment. I'm going through a tough time.
- Is it my fault that... - In that case...
I couldn't say the word?
(Is it my fault?)
(The word "challenge" has a special meaning for him.)
(We can empathize with Jae Seok's sad story.)
- He's so strict. - That's so mean.
I don't know about this.
I wonder what Haha would think about it.
He did say the word.
He whispered it.
Is it important whether he said it or not?
Don't you consider his feelings at all?
Forget it.
One day, I'll shout out the word as much as I want.
Jae Seok, I'm rooting for you.
Challenge!
(Jae Seok gets another chance.)
Let's say it together.
- Let's do it together. - That's better.
- Shout, "challenge" together. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Challenge. - Challenge. That's it.
- This is right. - I agree.
This is teamwork.
- It's more sincere. - This is teamwork.
(Will saying, "challenge" together be effective?)
(She hits a can.)
- It's because we said it together. - It worked.
They're spirulina...
- and vegemite. - Thank goodness.
Spirulina is a health product.
Vegemite is a type of jam in Australia.
- All right. - Let's say it together.
Let's do it together.
- In 1, 2, 3. Challenge. - Challenge.
(Jae Seok gets another chance.)
Okay.
(He hits 2 cans.)
- 2. - 2 cans.
That's right.
(He's truly Yoomerang after all.)
"Crocodile jerky".
"Didjeridu".
- What's that? - "Didjeridu".
(Didjeridu is the Aborigine's musical instrument.)
Didjeridu is Australia's traditional instrument.
- Didjeridu? - Didn't I say it right?
- Didjeridu? - Didjeridu.
Don't laugh at me. You already knew the name.
Isn't it didjeridu?
- Didjeridu? - Didjeridu.
You mispronounced it.
Carry the cans with you, and buy the products...
on your own.
- "Crocodile". - "Chain".
- Is it a key chain? - Take the cans with you.
- How about this one? - Look.
"Kangaroo skin" is kangaroo lotion.
(What's this?)
That's not it.
- It means leather. - It's the skin.
We need to find kangaroo leather?
How?
It isn't lotion.
Do you think kangaroos use lotion?
Do you think kangaroos...
carry lotion in their pouches...
- and use it? - How many do we have?
I thought they made it out of kangaroos.
- We have 5 items. - 5 items.
Let's go to the nearby mart.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(The items they need to get)
(Golden Wattle, Kangaroo meat, Kangaroo skin,)
(Crocodile paw key chain, Kangaroo paw key chain)
(Meanwhile, the happy Team New Zealand...)
My gosh.
It's so beautiful.
- This view is crazy. - It's gorgeous.
It's time for your second Chance Card mission.
What is this Chance Card for?
I think it's going to be something good.
New Zealand is where jet boats...
were first invented.
Really?
Since we're at the motherland of jet boats,
let's try a mission that's going to be full of thrill and excitement.
Here's the second mission.
It's The Memory Skills of the Tiger.
"The Memory Skills of the Tiger"?
(The Memory Skills of the Tiger)
Are you talking about me?
No. The tiger's.
There's a place in New Zealand...
that was listed in the Guinness World Records...
as the longest official place name in the world.
The longest name of a place?
If you succeed in memorizing the name of this place...
after a 10-minute, jet boat ride,
you'll be able to get a Chance Card.
That's way too easy.
- How long could it be? - How long is it?
I'm pretty sure the four of us will be able to memorize that.
- Hold this part. - Okay.
(What's the longest place name in the world?)
- My gosh. - No way.
Is this the correct name?
How can the four of us...
(How can there be a place with a name like this?)
(It has 45 letters.)
- This is practically a sentence. - Wait a minute.
What does it say? Try reading it.
"Taumatawhakatangihanga..."
"koauauo..."
- "tamateaturipukaka..." - My gosh, this is way too long.
"pikimaungahoronukupokaiwhe..."
"nuakitanatahu."
Bring me a New Zealander who can actually memorize this.
- This is so unexpected. - My gosh.
Bring me someone who actually memorizes this.
(Here's a New Zealander who can memorize the name.)
This place is located...
in southern Hawke's Bay, New Zealand.
It's a name of a hill that's located near Porangahau.
- They named it too long. - It's too long.
- There's a total of 85 letters. - 85 letters?
It was listed in the Guinness World Records, and this is what it means.
"The summit where Tamatea, a mountain climber with big knees,"
"played the flute for his loved one."
This is...
- This is way too much. - This is...
How are we supposed to memorize this?
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
- 1, 2, 3, 4... - Is that how you count?
(What in the world are you doing?)
That means there are 10... No, wait.
Can't you continue counting after 10?
Can't you continue on with 11 and 12?
I get confused.
- How does that confuse you? - There are 45 letters.
- That's more confusing. - It's confusing.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
7, 8, 9, 10.
- 11, 12. That's better. - 11, 12, 13, 14,
15, 16, 17, 18, 19...
(I can't argue. It's better to count this way.)
- 25, 26, 27, 28... - 25, 26, 27, 28...
(He's counting a lot better than he did before.)
I was right. It has 45 letters in Korean.
So tell me. Which way was easier to count?
My way was easier.
(He's being stubborn.)
- The first method? - There were four...
(The first method? Are you serious?)
Jong Kook, we're in New Zealand.
- We're in New Zealand. - Be reasonable. Which is easier?
(Se Chan, which way is easier?)
- Your method is way easier. - Right?
(He didn't even hesitate to answer.)
I have my own way of counting.
Your way of counting is absurd.
You obviously counted better the second time around.
Haha, your method doesn't matter...
when you're with Jong Kook. You should know that by now.
- But it's how I count. - No, that doesn't matter.
How are we going to memorize this? Let's give it a try.
We each need to memorize 11 letters.
You'll be riding the jet boat in five minutes. Please hurry up.
Then I'll memorize this part.
"Taumatawhakatangihangakoauauo".
Then I'll do the next part.
I'll continue on with...
- "tamateaturipukakapikimaunga". - Just memorize your part.
- This part is mine. - Yes, memorize that.
- Don't you think that's... - This part.
(How are they so confident? They're taking too many at once.)
(They start memorizing each of their parts.)
(Jong Kook tries to memorize it by using the most basic tactic.)
I'm done memorizing my part.
(Se Chan tries to memorize it by adding a rhythm to it.)
(Dancing)
Come on. Let's go.
(He tries using a dialogue from "Nameless Gangster".)
(Haha tries to memorize it by making it into a dialogue.)
(He memorizes it like a gangster.)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo, who is very bad at memorizing things,)
(has frozen on the spot.)
(I'm thoughtless...)
(because my brain is empty.)
- Let's give it a try. - I think we got it.
(They just need to combine what they've each memorized.)
Let's begin.
(Dancing)
(Acting like a gangster)
(Jong Kook's very stable.)
(Interestingly, they all succeeded in memorizing each of their parts.)
We got it. Okay.
We got the whole name right.
(Now, they just need to get it right again after they come back.)
- Everyone, get on the boat. - Let's go.
(Their Chance Card depends on this 10-minute, jet boat ride.)
(He continues to memorize his part out loud.)
Okay.
(They're trying harder than ever to memorize their parts.)
Jong Kook, remember this.
Haha and I will be able to avoid Nevis Swing.
- We need to win this Chance Card. - Yes, of course.
- I hope we get it right. - Let's get it.
(They keep memorizing it out loud.)
(Not only does Se Chan and Haha try their best,)
(but Jong Kook and Ji Hyo also try hard to memorize their parts too.)
- Let's go! - Let's go.
(They shout out each of their parts in order not to forget.)
- Let's go! - We can do it!
- Nice. - Let's go.
See you!
(Their mission to memorize the name begins now.)
Let's get it. Let's get it.
Let's go.
You're going to make it big in this episode.
Let's go!
(Warm sunlight and cool breeze)
Isn't the view beautiful? Just look at it.
It's so pretty.
- My gosh. - This is amazing.
- It's cool, but the sun is hot. - I know.
- It's really nice. - That's what makes it so nice.
The sun's shining, and there's a cool breeze.
But I can't stop memorizing my part as I look at this view.
- Okay! - My gosh.
(The jet boat starts to speed up.)
- Okay. My gosh. - My goodness.
My gosh, it's really fast.
What is this?
(The sightseeing's over. The jet boat starts going faster.)
Oh, my gosh!
- This is no joke. - My gosh!
- Let me look at the scenery! - Gosh, my sunglasses.
Let me enjoy the view!
(Screaming)
(They're screaming their lungs out...)
(with this beautiful scenery in front of them.)
Let us enjoy the view!
Let us enjoy the scenery!
(The driver allows them to enjoy the view by making turns.)
Let us enjoy the nice view!
(A deep sea creature has appeared in New Zealand.)
What is this?
This is not what I expected.
Give me my anxiety pills!
- My anxiety pills! - Anxiety pills!
(This is fun.)
Jong Kook's really enjoying this right now.
(They experience a thrilling ride in New Zealand.)
(Just then...)
- What? - He's going to spin?
- Jong Kook, hold on tight. - This is great.
He's going to make a spin.
(He's going to spin the boat in the middle of the lake?)
Hold onto your hats.
(The boat makes a 540-degree turn without slowing down.)
(This is what you call a real jet boat ride.)
- Oh, my gosh. - My gosh.
(This is only the beginning. The jet boat starts going faster.)
Slow down.
Slow down! The engine's going to burst!
This is going to overheat the engine!
Stop speeding! It's going to overheat the engine!
- There's a forest in front of us. - No!
(The jet boat heads straight to the bush.)
(No! We're going to crash!)
No!
(Stop the jet boat! Stop!)
(The boat passes right by the bush.)
(The driver is very skilled at driving the boat.)
- No, stop! - Stop this!
(They're already dumbfounded by what just happened.)
That's a rock over there! That's a rock!
- What? - No, wait. Stop.
- My gosh. - Where are we going?
(The pillars aren't very far apart, and there's a pile of rocks.)
(But the boat isn't slowing down.)
(Watch where you're going!)
(This is crazy.)
(Watch out!)
We're going to crash!
- This is practically a punishment. - My gosh.
(It was a shocking and horrific jet boat ride.)
This was unbelievable.
Please...
(But what were we supposed to memorize again?)
What was the name? I forgot everything.
I can't think properly.
- I can't remember. - You need to!
(It's as if they reset their brains.)
I forgot everything.
What was it?
(Thanks to the crazy jet boat ride, they forgot the name of the place.)
Jong Kook, do you remember?
- It was... - I can't remember anything.
- We can't forget. - My gosh.
- I can't remember anything! - My goodness.
(The last bit of memory that was left escapes from their minds.)
(When is this going to end?)
- Stop that! - No!
(She bursts into tears.)
You must remember it!
- I can't ride Nevis Swing tomorrow. - We must win the Chance Card.
We need that Chance Card! Please!
- Okay. We're here. - That was some good driving.
It was so scary.
(People do this for fun?)
Thank you.
(Their boat ride is over.)
Everyone, did you enjoy your boat ride?
- Sure. - Hold on. Hang on a second.
- Wait. - Give me a minute.
- Wait. - Hold on.
Wait.
(For some reason, everyone seems uneasy.)
- It starts with "Tau". - It does, right?
Okay. Let's do this. Let's give it a go!
(They pretend to be confident.)
That's a really good Chance Card, right?
- This is a great one. - Okay.
- This won't disappoint you. - Okay.
- Hey, are you ready? - Not yet.
- You can do it, right? Shall we? - Let's try it.
- Let's give it a try. - Can you do it? Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. - Let's get it.
Challenge!
(Their fate depends on this.)
Let's get it.
Taumatawhakatangi...
hangakoauauo.
- He got it right. - I speak with an accent.
Don't count my interjections.
- Hey. - Don't count it. This isn't it.
We won't count that.
Tamatea...
- You know? - "You know?"
- Turipukaka - You did it.
- You know? - You're doing fine.
- You know? - "You know?"
(Haha memorized his part with a method from his hometown.)
(As soon as he rode the boat, his mind went blank.)
- I can't remember mine. - Don't forget your part.
- Auauo. - I cannot remember my part!
(I trust you, my hero.)
(If they can't win the Chance Card here,)
(they will have to ride Nevis Swing tomorrow.)
(Was Haha's method good enough to beat the thrill of the boat ride?)
- Pikima. - Don't count, "you know."
- That was good. - Is it my turn?
Ungahoronuku...
Pokaiwhenu.
(Jong Kook remembers his as well.)
- Is it my turn? - This is great.
(Only six syllables remain.)
Aki...
(Please remember it, Ji Hyo!)
Akitanatahu.
That's correct!
(Team New Zealand successfully accomplishes their mission.)
- Yes! - We did it.
- I didn't think it was possible. - Oh, my. No way.
(It's time to choose a Chance Card.)
- You accomplished your mission. - Yes.
- There's a great Chance Card. - Okay.
- They are the ones we chose. - Look through the cards,
and choose 1 of the 3.
(They choose 1 of the 3 cards.)
(They will choose the card and decide to use it or not.)
"We won't do it."
Negative statements might give us positive outcomes.
- I agree. I thought so too. - Think about this one too.
Why are there 2 lines? What could these 2 lines mean?
Is it, "We won't do the penalty"?
But there are two lines.
This must be long.
- Hold on, Haha. - Why are there two lines?
- They actually might be good. - I don't know.
Why are there two lines here?
(This is driving us crazy.)
We don't know why there are two lines.
(He has 0 interest as to why there are 2 lines.)
- Haha, let's make this simple. - My goodness.
Gosh, didn't he sound so weird just now?
I asked why there were two lines.
He said, "I don't know."
(I don't care if there are lines or not. It's your penalty anyway.)
How could you say that?
- But I was telling you the truth. - Seriously.
- Hold on. - Right. The lines are covered.
I've never seen someone answer my question like that.
- Since I'm not doing the penalty, - "I don't know."
- I can't get into this. - He can't guess it.
What if they did this on purpose? You didn't, right?
(Anyway, they are very nervous about the two lines.)
Which one would you want? We can't make the decision for you.
Haha, let's go with "We won't do it."
- "We won't do it." - "We won't do it."
- This is the simplest out of all. - Okay. Go with that one.
(Haha and Se Chan choose the simplest one.)
If you are going to use the Chance Card,
peel off the tape. If you don't want to use it,
destroy it.
- You guys are so cruel. - But...
(Will they choose to use the Chance Card or not?)
Hey, whatever happens, we should go for it.
- Shouldn't we use... - A great card is 1 of the 3.
- Let's use this card. - We have a great card?
You do have to use the card. Think about it, guys.
We even played the game in order to win the card.
Destroying this doesn't make sense.
They just said a great card is among them.
- Let's peel it off. - Okay.
(Their final decision is to use the card.)
Peel it off. Do it.
(What is the Chance Card Team New Zealand chose?)
- What is it? - 1, 2, 3.
- "All..." - "All"?
"All of us won't do it"?
- It's "all of us". - "All of us won't do it"?
- It's "All of us won't do it." - All right.
"All of us..."
- "All of us..." "Nevis Swing..." - "Nevis Swing..."
- "Penalty"? What is this? - Wait, hey.
(All of them will do the penalty?)
- "Penalty". - "Penalty".
- "Complain..." - "Complain..."
(All of us won't complain about the penalty.)
My gosh, you guys are so annoying.
(They picked, "All of us won't complain about the penalty.")
- Does it mean all of us will do it? - Wait.
Hold on. How is this...
- How can this be a chance for us? - How is it a chance for us?
I told you it's a mixed set. A good one was among the cards.
- We won't complain about it? - What should we do?
- We can refute this. - It says, "all of us" here.
Does it imply that we are facing the penalty too?
All of you will face the penalty.
(The entire Team New Zealand will face the penalty.)
All of you will face the penalty, and you won't complain about it.
That means all of us are doing it together.
Yes.
We're going to join them too?
(Their penalty has become his penalty in an instant.)
I bet one of the cards will say, "The members..."
"won't face the penalty."
This feels...
nice. I don't like the penalty, but I feel good about it.
(He loves dragging people down.)
But I...
But I came here to support you.
(Jong Kook and Ji Hyo came to support but have become victims.)
(We're sorry, Ji Hyo.)
You're happy, right? You're okay with this, right?
I didn't plan on this.
- Let's get it! - Poor Ji Hyo.
(Chance Cards can be scary.)
All right. We figured that you might be hungry.
- We ordered some food for you. - Okay.
My gosh, look at the owner. He has the reggae look.
- Hello. - Hi.
- That looks really good. - I respect you.
(He has a presence.)
My gosh, that looks really good.
(It's a barbecue dish with mashed potatoes.)
(It's a roasted blue cod dish of New Zealand.)
(And there are more!)
- My goodness. - Gosh.
- Are we really eating this? - Thank you.
(It's a platter of fruits and vegetables with venison and ham.)
This is the best.
(Chicken salad with Manuka honey)
(Delicious)
(As soon as he has a bite,)
(he's mesmerized.)
- This is amazing. - Try this. Let me cut it for you.
Admire the scenery in the back while you eat.
Say that this costs 20 dollars,
but with the view, it's 40 dollars.
Is it crispy?
- How is it? - Or is it tender?
(They enjoy the meal with a picturesque view.)
The weather is great here,
but I wonder what Team Australia is...
- doing? - Doing?
(What is Team Australia up to?)
(Meanwhile, Team Australia...)
You accomplished your mission.
- Yes. - We did.
Let me check the items one more time.
Here's the crocodile paw key chain.
- Is this the key chain? - Yes, it is.
- It's the crocodile paw. - Yes.
Okay. It's the key chain, right?
- It's the kangaroo paw key chain. - It's the kangaroo key chain.
A key chain? A kangaroo paw key chain?
- This is interesting. What is it? - How much is it?
(Kangaroos are the symbol of Australia.)
All right. I have the kangaroo meat.
- Yes, yes. It's a kangaroo steak. - Is that kangaroo meat?
- Okay. This is it. - We got it.
This looks like liver.
Since the skin was too expensive, I took a picture.
I can't buy it. It's too expensive.
This is about 1,200 Australian dollars.
- A golden wattle. - I also have this in photos too.
Let me pick it up.
Well, I got them. They do smell like acacia.
You may choose...
- 1 of the 3 cards now. - Really?
(It's time to choose one of the cards.)
These are the cards you chose.
You have "We won't go," "We'll go," and "We will do it."
(The current status of Chance Cards Team Australia has)
I want to go to our hotel and home.
- Choose "We'll go." - I agree.
- What do you think? - I don't feel good about it.
"We'll go home."
- You chose your card now. - Yes.
If it's "We'll go home," we're going home right away, right?
It's up to you to either use the card or not.
(There's one more decision left. Will they use it or not?)
I already informed you. It's a mix of advantages and disadvantages.
- Okay. - Let's do it.
If you decide not to use it, you can just read the card.
If you decide to use the card, you'll comply with the card.
- Let's do this. - We ought to.
We earned this Chance Card.
- We fly into the face of danger. - Right.
- Let's jump into it. So Min. - We'll use it.
- You'll peel it off. - Okay.
- Let's go. - We will go home.
(They are certain they will be heading home.)
- We're going home. - Let's do this.
(This Chance Card has to do with the final penalty tomorrow.)
(Will this be their lucky chance to avoid these vicious crocodiles?)
(They are certain they will be heading home.)
- We're going home. - Let's do this.
(This Chance Card has to do with the final penalty tomorrow.)
(Will this be their lucky chance to avoid these vicious crocodiles?)
- "One more member..." - "One more..."
(One more member is going to be penalized.)
I told you.
- It doesn't affect us. - Gosh.
(They'll be penalized anyway.)
All right.
- Well... - We're...
It's bad for me, right?
One more member is going to be penalized.
Let's decide tomorrow...
who will be penalized.
There was no way it'd be "We're going home."
You said...
- It's a four-day trip. - What?
It won't do anything to you.
I knew it'd be a bad one.
It's no big deal.
They're two guys. A girl would be better.
(Now, you treat me like a girl?)
To be honest,
for Seok Jin, this might be the last chance.
(This might be your last chance.)
I don't mean anything bad.
So Min would have more chances...
- than you. - That's funny.
Let's decide tomorrow.
You're done for today.
- Really? - As you worked hard,
we prepared a special Australian meal.
Really?
- Let's go eat. - Let's go.
(They're going to try a special Australian meal.)
It's a steakhouse.
It smells good.
It smells like steak.
We thought you'd be hungry, so we ordered for you.
Thank you.
- Thank you. Let's share it. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - It looks tasty.
(They're happy to see food.)
The white one is crocodile steak.
(The white one is crocodile steak.)
What?
(Shocked)
(Crocodile steak?)
The white one is crocodile steak. The other one is kangaroo meat.
(Appetizing)
This is driving me crazy.
Why did you order this?
So Min, try the kangaroo.
It tastes good.
Let me try.
(I'll have a taste.)
This is crocodile.
- How does it taste? - Gosh.
- It tastes good. - It does.
It's a bit denser.
It tastes like kangaroos.
(It tastes like kangaroos.)
- What does that mean? - For example,
Jong Kook's flesh looks very hard, right?
I told you.
- Is it like liver? - No.
It's a bit denser.
You feel the kangaroo's muscles.
I've tried crocodile steak.
If you ignore the fact that it's crocodile,
- Does it taste good? - it tastes like fish.
Which part is it?
- It smells good. - Really?
Let me try.
Which part is it?
- I don't know. - How does it taste?
This is kangaroo meat?
It's a bit sour.
(Crocodile is a bit sour.)
It's sour?
Yes.
Is it close to fish or meat?
It's right in the middle.
If you forget that it's crocodile, it tastes good.
But I can't stop thinking about crocodiles.
(He can't stop thinking about crocodiles.)
I'm craving kimchijjigae.
Are you okay?
He's sweating.
- He's wearing winter clothes. - I'm just hot.
(It's not a cold sweat.)
So Min, I'm hot.
It's a thick sweater.
If you look up the Sydney weather on the internet,
it says the highs are around 23 to 24°C.
It's cold at night.
I'm an expert when it comes to this country.
- I've been here five times. - Really?
I shot my first commercial in Australia.
What commercial?
A beer commercial.
- You shot a beer commercial? - Yes.
You don't drink at all.
(You don't drink at all.)
A beer would knock you down.
- How did you shoot a commercial? - Be quiet.
I wasn't famous back then. It was shot abroad.
What?
We shot for three days.
Was it like the beer commercials we know?
No, it wasn't.
He was just swept away in the foam.
- Exactly. - He was swept away.
- So you were the foam. - Yes.
- You played the foam. - He did.
(Jae Seok in his early days)
(He threw himself...)
(into the beer.)
(He gave his all for his first commercial.)
Anyway, I shot my first commercial in Australia.
Australia is special to me.
You can go to the hotel now.
Do we get to decide tomorrow?
Sorry?
Do we get to decide which of the two will be penalized?
I'll think about it.
By the way, we managed to book only two times.
One of you will have to go alone.
(One of you will have to go alone.)
- Two will go together. - Alone?
(What?)
(I can't believe it.)
Isn't it already decided who will go alone?
Kwang Soo.
(Isn't it already decided who will go alone?)
I might prick you with this fork.
Anyway...
(They don't know who will go alone yet.)
All right. To Kwang Soo.
- Cheers. - No. Let's see.
(They comfort Kwang Soo.)
(The sun sets.)
Who will be going?
- Hello. - Hello.
- What are you doing? - Hi.
- What are you doing? - I just took a shower.
By the way, tomorrow,
you should be penalized for me.
I can't...
I'm sorry. I'm going to bed. Hello?
- Hey. - Hello?
Hey! What are you doing?
Unbelievable. She hung up on me.
(Age doesn't matter when it comes to penalties.)
(The penalty day is here.)
- Well... - Finally, it's today.
(The big day is here.)
Here we are once again.
We went to check the place this morning.
You won't be disappointed.
(You won't be disappointed.)
Were the crocodiles doing well?
- If they're tired... - Right.
- It's important. - Look.
It's off-season.
They'll be having visitors after a long time.
They'd be so excited.
They'd be so excited to finally have visitors.
They might even playfully bite you.
What?
Gosh.
You'll experience Cage of Death soon.
Before we meet the crocodiles,
let's get back to the Chance Card.
Between Seok Jin and So Min,
let's decide who will be penalized.
There are two cars outside.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo will choose between the two cars...
and get in the same one together.
Seok Jin and So Min will choose separate cars.
The one who chooses...
the car where Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are in...
- will be penalized. - So we should try to choose...
the car that's empty.
Whoever comes, I'll be so happy to see them.
My heart is pounding.
My day depends on this decision.
Please ask the drivers to set off as soon as they get in.
And one of us has to be penalized alone.
(One of us has to be penalized alone.)
What?
- Yes. - It's Kwang Soo.
Please decide who will go alone.
We have something prepared.
By the way,
there's this biggest, most ferocious crocodile.
(The biggest, most ferocious crocodile)
It's called Chopper.
It lost both of its front legs in the wild.
(It lost both of its front legs in the wild.)
(The crocodile lost its front legs in the wild.)
(The hidden card of Cage of Death)
(It's 5.5m long and weighs 790kg.)
Like in "Inside Men"?
Exactly.
"Inside Men"?
It must be a crocodile version...
of Lee Byung Hun.
(Do you know what life without arms is like?)
Should Kwang Soo and I choose a car?
- Yes, please. - Okay.
Seok Jin and So Min, please turn around.
Don't look.
We won't.
Our whole day depends on this.
Our day depends on this decision.
- Which one should we choose? - Are those our cars?
Yes. This is van number two.
- Honestly... - It's better...
It's better for...
Seok Jin to do it.
- So Min already... - He should just do it.
- went to Indonesia with you. - Yes.
- He might as well. - Seok Jin is so cunning...
- more than anything. - I agree.
We have to make him do it.
(Will their wish come true?)
Everyone.
They made their decision.
- Did they? - To be fair,
I'll write a number on the sketchbooks.
I'll put them down.
I want the squirrels.
- I'll take it. - I will.
(She chooses the squirrels.)
- I want the squirrels. - No.
- I have good feelings about them. - No.
I already decided...
to take the one you choose.
- I have good feelings about them. - No.
- I'll take it. - Please reconsider.
- No way. - This could be the one.
It's number one.
Okay, I'm number one.
- I'm number two. - This is good.
When you open the door,
if you find Jae Seok and Kwang Soo in the car,
you'll follow them to Cage of Death.
If not, you'll ride the car alone.
(One person will get exempted.)
(Who will join us?)
- Let's go. - Which one is 1 and 2?
- Let's crawl - Crocodile.
This is number two.
Do you see the camera inside?
Do you see it? They're filming the backseat.
(The cameraman is filming the backseat.)
I saw it.
After filming us, he turned around.
There must be people in the backseat.
- There's a camera in there too. - No.
Didn't you see him?
Look, he's filming the backseat.
Yes, I knew it.
My hunch is never wrong.
That's amazing. They're filming inside.
(Hello)
Wait a minute.
(Seok Jin will meet the crocodiles.)
- Wait a minute. - He got caught.
What's going on?
(She laughs triumphantly.)
(It's completely empty.)
(She can't stop laughing.)
Gosh, Seok Jin.
What's going on?
- Let's go. - No.
Put on your seatbelt.
- Goodness. - Wait.
Let's go now.
(Let's go before he runs away.)
Gosh, Seok Jin.
- We finally caught him. - We did.
Why was the cameraman filming the backseat?
He was fooled.
(She feels relieved.)
That was amazing.
I had no idea.
The weather is beautiful.
It's a perfect day to see the crocodiles.
(It's a perfect day to see the crocodiles.)
Because the weather was nice.
Because the weather was bad.
(The weather is beautiful today.)
(It's perfect to be with crocodiles.)
(She's excited to be exempted.)
(She's very excited.)
Look at So Min.
She's so cheeky.
- Gosh. - It's hard to decide who is worse.
I know.
So Min is really cheeky too.
Hello, everyone. I'm Jeon So Min.
We're in Darwin, Australia where crocodiles live.
Will...
those three members survive today?
Stay tuned.
(Stay tuned.)
(Let's go to Cage of Death together.)
- This must be it. - Where?
- "Crocodile"? - You're right.
Is it here?
(They finally arrive.)
One of you will go in alone.
(One of them faces the crocodile alone.)
You go in alone. Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
You don't have to worry...
because the cage that they had been using...
recently got cracked.
- How is that possible? - It got cracked?
They changed it to a new and sturdy one.
(The cage is new.)
(The old cage looks scary with scratches made by crocodiles.)
My goodness.
(With full of fear, they get out of the van.)
(Welcome to Australia.)
Be careful.
(Their fans congratulate them for meeting the crocodiles.)
(Prince of Asia came to see the crocodiles!)
(Lucky So Min enters as well.)
Wait for me.
We're here, So Min.
Be careful.
Hello.
(They enter the dark entrance together.)
Gosh.
- It's like a cave. - What's going on?
It's dark like a labyrinth.
You got lucky, So Min.
We were almost fooled by Kwang Soo's cameraman.
(What awaits the members?)
(They finally come into view.)
(They're giant crocodiles.)
- Gosh. - Do we go in there?
- Look at their tails. - Where?
Look over here.
(Are they real?)
It's a real crocodile tail.
- It's real. - Is it real?
- Is it real? - Look.
It's huge.
What if we get hit by the tail?
- What if it's fake? - I can't believe it.
Isn't it fake?
(They want to believe that it's fake.)
(However, the crocodiles above their heads are real.)
- It's the crocodile I mentioned. - Is that it?
It's Chopper.
(His front feet are missing.)
- Look at... - Is it alive?
the air bubbles rising.
- This is incredible. - It's alive.
It's like Lee Byung Hun of crocodiles.
(They see Chopper right in front of them.)
(They're speechless.)
Do we go inside there?
(They will stand next to that gruesome crocodile.)
(They move to where the cage is.)
- Look. - It's a baby crocodile.
It's a baby crocodile.
What if he jumps out of the cage?
No way.
- You can go inside there to look. - Right.
Go inside here?
- Gosh. - That startled me.
It startled me.
(They make eye contact with baby crocodiles.)
You can look at them in the eyes.
He's doing that again.
- He has his mouth open. - It's because...
You seem to be in a good mood, So Min.
She's all smiles.
- I'm so happy. - I try not to look at her.
- It's different from Indonesia. - Why?
It's great. There's so much to see.
There's a lot to watch.
What?
There were more to see in Indonesia.
Are we things to watch?
Goodness.
(You can do it, guys.)
(They're fun to watch.)
I'll give you time to look around.
- What? - Pardon me.
Do we go in here?
What's this?
(It makes them freeze.)
(The pool with crocodiles is deep.)
(Do we go in there?)
Look at the scratch mark.
- Do we go in the water? - Yes.
- Are they scratch marks? - Wait.
- Look at the scratch marks. - They're scratch marks.
(The new cage is covered with scratches.)
(These are teeth marks...)
(made by the crocodiles when they attacked the cage.)
- Claws? - Excuse me.
(This is insane.)
Are they paw scratches?
(They're teeth marks.)
They're teeth marks.
- Teeth? - Teeth.
(The crocodiles are more violent than expected.)
Look.
(And they're much bigger.)
They're huge.
It's like a dinosaur.
This crocodile is called Axel.
- It's the second biggest. - Axel?
(Axel is the second biggest crocodile here.)
(It's 5.1m long and weighs 900kg.)
Two of you will go in here.
On the right is Chopper that I mentioned earlier.
(One person goes in the cage near Chopper.)
This is insane. What should we do?
That's Chopper.
It's the one we saw earlier.
(Chopper is the biggest crocodile here.)
(He represents gruesomeness and violence.)
(Who will get lucky and face him alone?)
We'll decide which one of you will go alone.
The member without a partner will go in the cage alone.
It's the biggest crocodile here.
He lost his front foot in the wild.
It's 5.5m long.
It weighs 790kg.
A troublemaker crocodile awaits.
Goodness.
I didn't think it'd be this bad.
5.5m is longer than a van.
I can't believe it.
(He can't believe what's going on.)
- Now, - Why am I here?
your mission is called...
Cage of Clap. Here are the rules.
Did you see them?
Everyone was...
speechless.
Then suddenly they listen carefully.
- What's the mission? - Seriously.
Cage of Clap.
I don't want to live like them.
(Kwang Soo pays full attention after seeing the crocodile.)
Three of you will put on eye patches.
Clap or make sounds to notify where you are.
The two members to meet first will pair up.
Goodness.
- Are you joking? - Are you playing with us?
Rock-paper-scissors is simpler.
The one without a partner will be sad.
What is this?
My goodness.
(Clapping a lot is key.)
We have to clap a lot.
Wait.
Remember the 337 clap, okay?
(Follow this sound.)
Look at them.
(What do you think about this?)
My gosh, look at them.
I can't believe they're doing that.
What are you doing?
(Let's remember this sound.)
- Remember this sound. - Okay, I will.
Are you even human?
- You're unbelievable. - No, wait.
(You guys are so fun to watch.)
It's time for you to wear your eye patches.
(I need to do something too. Come follow this sound.)
What was that? What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
(He tries to seduce Kwang Soo by crying like a crow.)
- You can't make sounds. - Aren't we allowed?
- You can make sounds. - See?
(Really? Then let me make my signature sound as well.)
(They each cry like birds that are mating.)
Is this fun? Are you happy?
(This is so interesting to watch since I'm not involved.)
Hey, is it fun to see us so desperate?
- Hey. - Are you enjoying this?
I finally understand why Running Man is loved by so many people.
(This must be why our show is so popular.)
Please wear your eye patches.
Should I take off my bag?
Once they wear their eye patches, So Min can split them apart.
- You can separate them. - Okay.
My gosh, I really can't go alone. I'm being serious.
Let's just avoid going inside alone.
- I just need to avoid this. - Seriously.
So Min, please place them wherever you want them to stand.
- So Min. - Yes?
- Please be nice. - Okay.
- So Min, please be nice. - Yes.
- Stay here. - Where am I?
- Where's the center? - It's right ahead of you.
Come here, Kwang Soo.
- Where are you taking me? - Come here.
- Where are you taking me? - Come on.
(Wait a minute. Where is she taking him?)
- What? Where am I going? - No, don't worry.
Where am I?
- Follow me. - Why is my voice echoing?
How am I supposed to get out of here?
There's nothing in front of you. Take three steps forward.
1, 2, 3. Good job.
How do you expect me to get out of here?
Give it your best try.
- What? - Is everyone ready?
- Yes. - Yes.
What is this smell?
Ready, get set, go!
(Can you hear me? I'm over here!)
(Making sounds)
(Hey, guys! I'm over here!)
(The two birds are near each other.)
I can hear you.
(They both get a hold of where the other person is.)
Jae Seok!
(They're shocked.)
(Clapping)
Hey, I hear...
- I can hear a clap. - So Min.
(They're lost again because of So Min.)
Kwang Soo!
(Do you remember this sound, Kwang Soo?)
(I'm making that sound too. Where are you Seok Jin?)
(He makes sounds with his mouth as he makes clapping sounds.)
- Kwang Soo! - Seok Jin!
(Seok Jin slowly approaches where Kwang Soo is hidden.)
- I can't get out of here! - Who is this?
Where are you?
- Seok Jin! - Jae Seok!
- Where are you? - Where are you?
I'm over here!
- Jae Seok! - I'm over here.
(They both make sounds.)
- Jae Seok! - I'm here!
- Who is this? Oh, is that you? - What are you doing?
(I found someone! Oh, it's Kwon Ryeol.)
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm trying to find my partner.
I'm here!
(Where am I right now?)
Where are you, Seok Jin?
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin slowly start to approach each other.)
- Come over here! - Where are you?
- Here! - I'm here!
Where?
(They came into contact!)
Who are you? Who are you?
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin miraculously become partners.)
Jae Seok and Seok Jin have become partners.
- I can't believe this. - My gosh!
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin have become partners.)
(Wait a minute. They're partners?)
Wait.
How was I supposed to get out of there?
(I'm sorry, Kwang Soo.)
Wait.
(Kwang Soo has to enter Cage of Death by himself.)
You need to sign a safety agreement before you go in.
Do they need to agree with the fact that they're going to die?
What are you talking about?
- Hey. - Why would we die?
We're not going in there to become their food.
- I can't believe you said that. - We're not going to be their food.
You can't say stuff like that just because you're not going in.
- My goodness. - Unbelievable.
It's not even funny.
Oh, my gosh.
(They get ready to sign the safety agreement.)
What is this?
Do you know how to read this?
(It feels scarier because it's written in English.)
My gosh. Cage of Death.
(They complete signing the safety agreement in fear.)
- So Min. - Why are we even doing this?
(This is the cage that we saw on TV.)
You need to hurry up since there's not a lot of time.
Okay, okay.
Okay, we'll hurry up. We'll do as you wish.
Do we go inside right now?
They said we need to hurry up to meet the schedule.
I'm really angry right now.
I didn't know the crocodiles had a schedule.
- I didn't know that. - I'm so upset.
The crocodiles' schedule is more important than ours.
The crocodiles are busy scaring so many people every day.
- Do we need to wear this? - Why do we need to wear this?
So that we can get a good look of the crocodiles.
How am I supposed to put this on?
(I'm very aware of how angry you are right now.)
They want us to take a video of the crocodiles with this.
- So you're practically a camera. - That's right.
So Min, you should join us too.
(Seok Jin puts on his diving mask.)
Why are you wearing it like that?
I think she should join us.
Why do you have two noses?
How am I supposed to do this? How do I wear this?
- Like this. - Then I can't breathe.
- What are you doing? - That's how you wear it.
Then I won't be able to breathe.
- It'll leak that way. - How am I supposed to wear this?
(Seok Jin's big nose isn't helping at all.)
- I can't even wear this properly. - I'm so worried for him.
It's because Seok Jin's old.
- He's never worn this. - This is my first time.
Let's go inside.
We're not mentally ready yet.
This is driving me crazy.
I'm so nervous.
(They finally enter the infamous Cage of Death.)
(Both Jae Seok and Seok Jin can't stop sighing.)
My gosh, I still don't understand why I have to do this.
(The guy who needs to enter by himself feels more uneasy.)
We're ready.
- Are you ready? - We're ready.
- Are you sure? - We're champions.
Head on outside. When you go down the ladder, you need to face me.
(It's even more disturbing to watch.)
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
(They can't see the bottom of the ladder.)
(They're on their way to see the aggressive crocodiles.)
The crocodiles are angry. The crocodiles are hungry.
- They're angry and hungry. - Yes. They're angry and hungry.
(It's a lot more frightening from up above.)
My gosh, this is crazy. Why are we doing this?
You need to turn around and climb down.
My gosh.
I guess it's really narrow.
- Is it just the two of us? - This is so scary.
Don't we get a guardian?
No. They're going to remove the ladder.
- What? Really? - Yes.
My gosh.
We're going to remove the ladder. There are small holes like this.
- We need to keep our hands away. - Yes. Don't put your hands there.
The chain will extend once we move the cage.
- So be careful not to get caught. - Okay.
- We'll get rid of the ladder now. - Have there been any accidents?
Let's just hope nothing happens.
(It's bulletproof glass, but they can't help but feel nervous.)
(They finally remove the ladder.)
So Min, you can watch them from downstairs.
We'll see you downstairs, you guys.
Bye, guys.
My gosh, I have to go in there by myself.
Look at all these scratches from their teeth.
(These scratches are from the crocodiles' teeth and claws.)
This is crazy.
(The cage starts moving.)
(They begin going down.)
- Tell us first. - My gosh, that shocked me.
Please tell us before this moves.
(They're now fully disconnected.)
- I can't believe this. - My gosh.
- I'll close the cage now. - Okay.
I hope you come back alive.
Please don't say that.
- Be careful. - Okay.
My goodness.
- Oh, my gosh! - My goodness!
- Hey, keep your hands safe. - Okay.
Keep your hands inside.
Where are we going?
(The cage is heading towards Axel, the crocodile that's 5m long.)
- This is driving me crazy. - My goodness.
- This is really scary. - We're so high up.
- This cage is too tiny. - It's so scary.
This is already scary enough.
- This is the crocodile. - My gosh.
It just passed by.
I guess they're going to come here.
(A huge crocodile that's about 900kg is right above their heads.)
They're coming.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin haven't seen the crocodile yet.)
This is... My gosh.
(Where in the world is the crocodile?)
Where's the crocodile?
Where is it?
My gosh, are we going down?
(The cage finally descends.)
This is driving me crazy.
- Is there water coming in? - The water's coming in now.
(They start to feel scared as their feet start getting cold.)
They're coming in.
They're here.
I can't believe this.
(So Min and Kwang Soo are also shocked by what they see.)
They're really inside.
They're so nearby. That's a real crocodile.
(Is this seriously happening?)
- The crocodile's moving. - It's a real crocodile.
It's a real, living crocodile. This is crazy.
My gosh, how deep are we going to go?
(They're panicking.)
- What is this? - Are we really going to be okay?
- Where is it? - Where's the crocodile?
- My gosh. - How deep are we going to go?
This is much scarier.
- Where's the crocodile? - I don't know.
- My gosh. - Don't move the cage. Be careful.
- Stop shaking the cage. - Hey!
- What is this? - My gosh.
My goodness.
- It's right here. - It's over there.
My gosh, it's right over there.
- Where? - It's right here. Look over there.
(The infamous crocodile that weighs 900kg is right before their eyes.)
(It starts moving as soon as it sees humans.)
- My gosh. - That startled me.
What is this? Where did it go?
- My gosh, it's moving. - I know.
- It's moving. - Exactly.
My gosh. Look.
It came down.
(The ruthless crocodile, Axel, is right in front of the cage.)
It's right in front of us.
(I am the predator of this area.)
(Shouting)
(Munching)
It's so big.
Look at its teeth, Kwang Soo!
Look at its teeth!
It hurt its tooth.
(The broken tooth is a testament of its strong jaw movements.)
My goodness.
It's as big as a house. It's so big.
(Startled)
(It tries to swallow the pole that is used for feeding.)
- Stay still. - My goodness, it looked at me.
Look at this. Come here.
Come here.
It's cute.
It's not cute. Don't call it cute.
Stop it. Don't do that.
(She tries to communicate with the crocodile.)
Its foot is so big.
Look, it's peeing.
- It's peeing. - What is that?
My goodness.
(What is that?)
Don't say that.
What was that?
Are you asking because you really don't know?
What was that? Did you see that?
(They can't describe what they saw.)
(The world of crocodile is embarrassing and shocking.)
I told you to stay away.
You weren't respectful towards the crocodile.
(It's a male crocodile.)
It's a male crocodile.
- Hey. - Is it a male crocodile?
(At that moment)
(After peeing, the crocodile thrashes more violently.)
(Screaming)
(They back away as farthest as they can go.)
- It's going that way. - It's going.
(It's angry jaws threaten the middle-aged men.)
(Screaming)
(Fear makes them scream in the water.)
(They turn pale in a few minutes.)
It's angry.
It must be angry.
(We apologize if we made you angry.)
It's under us.
(It goes to rest in the water.)
(Maybe not.)
(It threatens them by slamming against the cage.)
(Its movements are more aggressive.)
(Can Jae Seok and Seok Jin finish the penalty successfully?)
(Next week)
(It's the real deal.)
(The king of crocodiles, Chopper appears.)
(It's more aggressive and ruthless.)
(Can the members come out in one piece?)
(This time, they meet the wild crocodiles.)
(They explore the wild swamp that is full of crocodiles.)
(The crocodile egg isn't that big.)
(Why are you at my home?)
(The crocodile is annoyed.)
(Is this trip safe?)
(Also)
(These two members are hanging from the steep cliff.)
(Countdown)
Hold on. Hold on.
- Hold on. - Please. Hold on.
- Hold on. - Please.
(Swallowtail Butterfly Tour Part 2)