(This is Running Man's global project of 2017.)
(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by the bloggers)
(Shark cage, USA)
(Cage of Death, Australia)
(Fly Toledo, Spain)
(Active volcano in Mount Bromo and Mount Ijen, Indonesia)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan)
(Nevis Swing, New Zealand)
(Insano water slide, Brazil)
(We are going to visit those places?)
(With this global project, the show has moved to another level.)
(Last week)
(In this dangerous moment, Se Chan and So Min joined the cast.)
Don't do it. Don't!
(Se Chan looks like he's fully adjusted to the show.)
They said I'm the ugliest here.
(With his perfect looks for variety shows, he happens to be unlucky.)
(With bad luck,)
(he and Haha receive 1 Tour Sticker each.)
(And today)
(What? You want us to leave right now?)
I didn't even buy the flight ticket.
(Are they really going overseas on the morning of the shoot?)
(They went indeed.)
(A specialized mission in Taiwan where the temperature is 34°C)
(A real survival mission in the unprecedented weather)
(A chase between So Min and these two middle-age old men in Osaka)
(Part 2 of the global project begins now!)
(Everyone is asleep at this quiet dawn.)
I slept briefly at home and woke up at 2am.
(Every member gathers at a hotel at 4am.)
- This is too early in the morning. - It's cold.
- Please don't be mistaken. - We need one more person.
- We're filming at dawn, not night. - You should explain.
When the sun rises, the viewers might be surprised to see the sun.
- Even the sun hasn't risen yet. - The viewers may be flustered.
- They might think the show ended. - Right.
We will tell you why we are filming early today.
- You ought to. - Okay.
Why did you tell us to bring our passport?
We have to get ready for the trip.
Someone will have to go three weeks later.
- I don't believe him. - Today isn't the day though.
- We have two more shoots left. - We are researching in advance.
- That's why... - Strangely, we're near the airport.
- This is weird. - What a coincidence, right?
(What a coincidence, right?)
(What is that crazy producer plotting?)
- Is someone leaving today? - What?
- No way. This can't be happening. - Will there be two stickers?
- Is today the last day? - It'll be two stickers and be over.
- Really? - Yes.
(We will get on a plane at Incheon International Airport...)
(and will be forced to head to this pit of fire today. Is that right?)
- This is crazy. You two are done. - That means...
- It will be Haha and Se Chan. - No way.
- We have to film one more time. - It will be one of you.
- Perhaps, both of them will go. - By the way, last week...
after the shoot, one of the members...
- sent a text late at night. - What did it say?
We showed you the possible destinations last week.
The member recommended another destination in the text.
(These destinations are scary enough.)
(Another destination?)
- Who sent the text? - That was completely useless.
- Who is it? - Didn't you send it?
Wait. If that person recommended it, he or she should go.
We will show you the recommended destination. Here it is.
That person ought to go since he or she recommended it.
- That person will know this. - What is this?
- Is this it? - Where is it? I can't see.
- In which country is this? - Is this in the States?
(The roller coaster climbs up briskly.)
- Goodness. - What is it?
Seriously?
- Isn't this too high? - It will drop from the top.
- Where is it? They are in the air. - This is in the States.
(It drops vertically perpetually.)
(What is this merciless ride?)
- It keeps going down. - Goodness.
(What is the identity of this roller coaster heading to the underworld?)
- I can't ride this. - No way. I can't ride it.
- Who sent you this? - This is impossible.
- Who recommended this ride? - Putting aside this ride...
- Who sent the text? - Is it you?
- You know I hate roller coasters. - Kwang Soo didn't send it.
- Did you send it, Seok Jin? - It has to be So Min.
- Is it you, So Min? - I haven't even been in the US.
- It's not me. - Is it you, Se Chan?
- It's not me. - It has to be one of you.
- It can't never be me. It's not me. - You sent it, Haha. Right?
- Isn't it you? - I swear I didn't recommend it.
- I swear I didn't recommend it. - Then it cannot be you.
Hey, then was it you?
Was it you? Did you recommend it?
It was you, Ji Hyo.
- Gosh. You've gone mad. - Why did you do that?
- Go there in your free time. - Just because you like it...
- How did you find this though? - Why did you do that?
The ride you just saw is in Ohio, USA.
- It's far. - It's called Top Thrill Dragster.
- This 130m tall ride drops... - What is this? Gosh.
at a right angle. This is known to be the most brutal roller coaster.
- This is crazy. - It's the most brutal.
Did you know this when you sent it?
- I recommend her... - I didn't know.
to collect insects in Africa.
(I recommend that Ji Hyo collects insects in Africa.)
- There are so many insects there. - I agree.
- There will be bugs all over her. - Let's see him getting bitten.
I recommend this ride for Kwang Soo.
I recommend that we make a situation where she has to eat the insects.
I recommend that he rides the roller coaster without the safety bars.
She wants me dead.
You wanted the same for me too.
Imagine you stay in the air when everyone else goes down.
(Why are you bullying me too?)
- It will be just like in a cartoon. - Right.
(He'll savor the sweet taste of the gravity without the safety bars.)
- He will stay in the air. - You will fall later.
Haha and Se Chan will most likely go.
- No. - No way.
- This is driving me crazy. - You are the closest.
- That can't happen. - Thank you.
(She feels bad.)
The race for these destinations will start today as well.
- That's horrible. - Today's mission will be...
carried out by 3 teams. 3 members will make 1 team.
(There are only 8 of us. How will we make 3 teams?)
Even when we have two new members, it's not even.
- Don't you need one more person? - What is it?
- We invited a special guest. - Is someone coming?
We invited a beautiful lady to join us.
(A beautiful lady will fill in the last spot?)
- I was about to say that... - A beautiful guest.
new members haven't adjusted yet and we shouldn't call a new guest.
- I don't want to say that anymore. - There will be a beautiful guest.
- I changed my mind. - Who is the beautiful guest?
- We will move to meet the princess. - The princess?
(Who is the princess that will join them on the dangerous trip?)
- Let's go. - I'm curious to find out.
(Current time is 4:46am.)
(They are walking towards the princess with fluttering hearts.)
(At the end of the path, who will be waiting for the members?)
- We are doing this again. - Again?
(Is it the belt from last week?)
- What is it? - Please sit comfortably.
(The advanced belt that delivered them to the dangerous next door)
- There are 2 belts. - There are 2 ways.
All right. The princess you have been waiting for is...
- in the room you see in front. - In that room?
- She's in that room. - There she is.
- It's nice to meet you. - What?
(It's nice to meet you.)
- I like her laugh. - She sounds cute.
- I really like her laugh. - She sounds really cute.
I think I heard her laugh a lot from somewhere.
Can you laugh one more time?
I will laugh when I want to.
(I will laugh when I want to.)
- She sounds a bit weird. - Isn't she Hong Yun Hwa?
She must have appeared on a lot of variety shows.
- I don't think she's an actress. - You think so?
- Her laugh sounds so familiar. - It does for me too.
(Who is this mysterious princess that lets out a cute laugh?)
All right. I will reveal today's mission.
- What is it? - Part two of the global project.
The mission is Dangerous Princess.
In order for you to meet the princess,
you have to accomplish the mission.
Here are the rules. Each one of you will write one questionnaire...
about a topic in which you think you will be ranked first.
The princess will choose the topic randomly...
and personally rank the members.
The member ranked first will receive a Golden Badge.
The member ranked last and the members on the same belt...
will be dragged to the dangerous next door and face the penalty.
- Good. Kwang Soo is on that belt. - Jae Seok.
Everyone on the same belt will face the penalty?
(They must predict their ranking and choose their seat.)
She might answer the questions differently though.
I have played this game before.
I can write a question I know for certain I will be ranked first.
There are so many questions.
- Questions I will be ranked first? - I have to...
It's not easy to write one.
I don't have any special traits.
- So Min, that's not true. - Questions I will be ranked first?
(Everyone finishes writing the questions.)
(Kwang Soo, The person you want to kiss the most)
(So Min, The member who has the lowest income)
(Jong Kook, The one you want to go to a jungle with)
(Ji Hyo, The one you think has a short temper)
(Seok Jin, The one you think looks good in glasses)
- She's reading them, right? - Who is this princess though?
- Princess. - Yes?
Please tell us what you chose for the first topic.
The first topic that I've chosen...
- is... - She sounds familiar.
- I think I recognize her voice. - Me too.
Is it Bo Mi?
It's the person I want to kiss the most.
- Who wrote this? - That's the topic.
- Okay. - We can't say it out loud, right?
- You guys can rank yourselves. - We rank ourselves?
- Move over. - Hey, move.
- Move. - Be honest.
- Everyone thinks I have great lips. - Get out of my place.
I'll be honest. I've had a lot of women kiss me first.
What are you talking about?
I got married thanks to my lips.
I'm being serious. Jae Seok, come on.
- My lips... - That's such a lie.
- My bottom lip is so plump. - Stop talking nonsense.
- So Min, why are you sitting there? - Move.
- Seok Jin, let's be serious. - Move over.
- My gosh, these two are so brazen. - Get out of my seat.
- They must be crazy. - Move over.
- Get out of my seat. - My lips are like latex.
- Get out of my seat. - You should avoid...
sitting in the same line as the person who comes last.
- You sit here. I'll be the second. - Okay.
- You can sit next to me. - What are you doing?
- Move! - You honestly...
- It's my seat! - You honestly deserve it.
- Fine, I'll be the third. - Okay.
How are you the third?
Fine, I'll be the fourth then.
Okay, I'll be the fourth.
I forgot to put on lip balm today.
I should've put on lip balm today.
Who put it on? Let me use it too.
Did you finish writing down their names?
Yes, I finished ranking them.
- You guys must be nervous. - Yes.
- I'll announce the ranking. - Okay.
The person who came in first is...
(You've seen how charming our lips are, right?)
- Congratulations, Ji Hyo. - I told you.
(She has the most charming lips.)
- Thank you. - No.
- Thank you. - It's hard for her to choose a guy.
- It's hard for her to choose a guy. - May I continue?
- Yes. - Yes.
- The person who came in second... - It's probably So Min.
- is So Min. - See? I told you.
- That's so unfair. - She's being unfair.
- She's being unfair. - I'm so nervous.
- Please calm down, everyone. - You should be more honest.
- She's trying to seem naive. - I can't believe this.
I'm sure the next person was supposed to be number one.
I'll announce the next person.
- The person who came in third is... - This is the real deal.
(Who will come in first among the male members?)
- It's Haha! - I knew it.
This princess really knows what she's talking about.
- I'm being serious. - What are you talking about?
- She's trying to save her face. - She's not being honest.
- She's just trying to be nice. - No, she's being honest.
I used to say that my ideal kind of woman is Ms. Kim Hye Ja.
- She's just trying to play safe. - I know.
She's the type that wants to play safe.
- Who came in fourth? - This is so funny.
The person who came in fourth is Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok ranks 4th on the list.)
You see that? She's only trying to save her face.
- She's being serious, right? - Okay, fine.
- She's being absolutely serious. - I think I'm going to come in last.
(Only 30 seconds ago, he was busy criticizing her.)
(But he quickly changes his attitude.)
She's not joking at all.
I didn't know she'd be so cunning.
Please announce who ranked last. Everyone on that line will lose.
I'm sorry, but the last person on the list is...
(It's either Kwang Soo or Se Chan.)
(Which line will end up getting a group penalty?)
It's Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo ranks last on the list.)
(Everyone sitting on the same line as Kwang Soo will get penalized.)
- I'm sorry. - I came in last?
(The 4 men who fought over the seats enter the dangerous room.)
- This doesn't make any sense. - I should've sat there.
- She should be more honest. - I can't believe this.
- What is this? - Bye
(I hope you return safely.)
- It's not because I'm scared. - My goodness.
My gosh, Kwang Soo.
What is this?
(What did they encounter?)
- I think she's going to be pretty. - Yes, I agree.
She might even be an actress.
- Please send them back out. - Do you think so?
This is unbelievable.
Tell her that she should be more honest.
(Shocking)
- My goodness, look at them. - They look so pretty.
Tell her that she should be honest.
You guys look pretty.
- He looks so cheap. - My goodness.
She really should be more honest.
- You guys look pretty. - This is ridiculous.
May I tell you why Seok Jin had a low rank?
- Yes, please tell us. - Yes.
I think Seok Jin's lips...
will feel a bit soggy.
(She shocks them with the word "soggy".)
- "Soggy"? - My goodness.
She's one weird lady.
I'm sorry.
- It's because... - Your lips do look soggy.
They're not soggy. They're moist.
- They look very damp. - Exactly.
- She's an eloquent speaker. - Wait.
Is she Do Yeon?
- Do Yeon? - She sounds like her.
She talks like Do Yeon.
- He's right. - Right?
Hey, Do Yeon.
(You're all curious, aren't you?)
She sounds like Do Yeon.
- She does talk like her. - I agree.
- Do Yeon tends to... - Right.
- She uses words like "soggy". - Yes, she does.
- Go ahead. - The next topic I chose is...
the person who seems to earn the least amount of money.
- The person who earns the least? - Isn't it you, So Min?
- Who wrote this? - It's So Min.
I wrote it!
You might not come in first.
- She probably has her own standard. - Everyone.
I'm not aware of how much money you guys all earn.
Therefore, I'll be writing the list based on your outer appearances.
Our appearances? That means it's not based on actual facts.
Then we need to change seats.
What's wrong with my appearance?
Do I look poor?
- This is confusing. - So Min should come down.
We really can't predict anything.
- Your eyes are fine, right? - Yes, they're fine.
The person who I think earns the least amount of money is...
(Who does she think is the poorest member?)
It's Seok Jin.
Congratulations.
- Why? - Hey.
Right now,
he befits that image because of how he looks.
(Seok Jin is penniless and has soggy lips.)
- Excuse me, do you think... - Yes?
Does it seem like I'll earn less money than Se Chan?
Well, Se Chan is still young...
and has a longer life ahead of him.
(She's very logical.)
- She's right. - I'm sorry.
- I'm still young. - Right.
- She's realistic. - That makes sense.
- She's very logical. - I'm sorry.
- I'll announce who came in last. - Listen up.
- It's probably Jae Seok. - The last person on the list is...
(Who does she think earns the most amount of money?)
It's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok ranks last on the list.)
You just came in last.
- You shouldn't be happy. - It's a bad thing.
- Bye. - See you.
(Ji Hyo, Haha, Jae Seok, and Jong Kook will get penalized.)
I'm happy with being the seventh.
I came in first, but I it doesn't feel so great.
(Screaming)
- It must be something painful. - I think they're getting a massage.
Maybe they're getting pinched.
My goodness.
(Who could it be?)
(Who is this familiar person?)
(He's responsible for taking care of the members' health.)
(He's Masseur Kim Hyung Joon, the master of sports massage.)
- Please don't hurt us. - My goodness.
I'll try to endure it.
(Screaming)
(Along with his students, he gives them a massage.)
My gosh, stop.
(Electrifying)
It must be painful.
It must hurt a lot.
- Be careful. - They're coming.
- What was the penalty? - We got a sports massage.
- I see. - Sports massage?
I shouldn't have cried for joy.
- Why were you happy? - He thought it was a compliment.
I thought it was a compliment.
(He was excited for a split moment.)
(Next topic is the one looks like they'll have a short temper.)
(They each try their best to show her their temper.)
(Jong Kook comes in last, so Ji Hyo, Haha, and Kwang Soo get penalized.)
- The princess... - She makes bad decisions.
- Why didn't Jae Seok come in last? - I ranked first on the list.
How old are you?
I'm old enough.
Hey, Do Yeon.
I think she's Do Yeon.
- It's not her. - She sounds like Do Yeon.
- It must be her. - How tall are you?
Your foot size is 280mm, right?
- 280mm? - Yes.
You're funny.
(She thinks he's funny.)
(That has to be Do Yeon.)
- She's definitely Do Yeon. - It's Do Yeon.
- She's Do Yeon. - Her foot size is 280mm.
The way she just laughed. Her laugh sounded familiar.
I agree with everyone else, but not with Jong Kook.
(They return with shocking appearances.)
(It's both shocking and scary.)
- I can't agree with Jong Kook. - Do Yeon, this is too much.
- Look at Ji Hyo! - This is ridiculous.
- Do Yeon. - Do Yeon, this is too much.
Look at Ji Hyo!
- My gosh, Do Yeon. - How can you do this me, Do Yeon?
- I treat you nicely. - Good job.
(This is fun.)
- Hey! - Ji Hyo.
I'll deal with you once you come out.
- Seriously. - I'm not going to let this pass.
She's not a princess. She's just a giant.
It's been a while since I've seen Kwang Soo like this.
- He looked like this before. - We wore green sweatsuits.
(He looks very familiar now.)
(In 2013, he came out looking like the stupidest person on Earth.)
(He was bald and wore green sweatsuits.)
Yes, that's right. I remember.
(He's back.)
- This is nice. - You used to look like this.
But I noticed that Do Yeon...
(They've already decided that she's Do Yeon.)
- We know her now. - It's her.
I don't understand why you think I'm Jang Do Yeon.
I can smell your feet from here.
- Does her feet smell? - Really?
- Her feet stink. - I see.
It's Do Yeon whose foot size is 280mm and has stinky feet.
- Her foot size is similar to mine. - She has bigger feet than I do.
- Is she really Do Yeon? - She must be.
(Is the princess really Jang Do Yeon?)
Come on out.
(The princess finally reveals herself.)
Bigfoot.
Why do they keep saying I'm Jang Do Yeon?
If not, I'm very sorry.
It's definitely Do Yeon.
(Who's the one with stinky feet?)
- I knew it. - Hello.
It's definitely Do Yeon.
(Dangerous Princess is Jang Do Yeon.)
- I knew it. - Hello.
She has big feet.
The princess is Jang Do Yeon with big feet.
It was Jang Do Yeon after all.
(Dangerous Princess is Jang Do Yeon.)
Each woman will be a team leader.
You'll be divided into three groups. Let's go.
- Okay. - Three women?
(What's the dangerous mission that awaits them?)
The sun is finally rising.
With Ji Hyo, Do Yeon, and So Min as team leaders,
you'll compete with three members on each team.
- Really? - Yes.
The mission to determine the teams...
is called You're My Cinderella.
- What is it? - Cinderella?
It must be related to shoes. Are your feet okay, Do Yeon?
- No way. - It relates to shoes.
- Stop it. - You have a disadvantage.
Her feet are big and stinky.
That's Do Yeon.
This is terrible.
Any part of the skin can smell.
On the 11th floor of this hotel,
three pairs of glass slippers...
for the princesses are hidden.
Male members are given 10 minutes to find the slippers...
that belong to the princess they want to choose.
Come back here once you find them.
While the male members look for the slippers,
the team leaders will compete...
by shelling pumpkin seeds.
The one who shells the most pumpkin seeds...
will get a Chance Card.
The princesses may sit here and shell pumpkin seeds.
The male members will look for glass slippers for 10 minutes.
Will Seok Jin draw us in the meantime?
Stop it.
- Like that painter? - Remember him?
I remember that painter.
- That painter? - Yes.
- Today, - Let's draw.
maybe he has an exhibition.
(He dances like a fool.)
I'm sorry, Seok Jin.
Don't you know who the painter is?
- I don't. - He's a fool.
Maybe he's a fool.
- Maybe he's a fool. - Don't you know him?
(Whom are they talking about?)
I was wondering why he was acting this way.
He thought we called him a fool.
- Come on, Seok Jin. - He thought we said a fool.
- What was he doing? - He was acting like a fool.
That's enough. Let's go.
(He goes to look for the slippers.)
That's outdated.
- Let's go. - Did you mean that painter?
You have 10 minutes.
Do Yeon's slippers will be stinky.
- They'll definitely stink. - They'll be 180mm.
No, they're 280mm.
Is this a room?
(The slippers are hidden somewhere.)
This is amazing.
(It's great in here.)
Are they glass slippers?
We haven't searched for things in a long time.
(He looks around thoroughly.)
I'm careless when I search.
Right.
(He finds things even when he searches carelessly.)
(He peeks inside.)
What?
(He finds a box in the fridge.)
It's here.
(He finds So Min's slipper.)
(Kwang Soo searches in the bathroom.)
What?
(He finds a box under the bathroom sink.)
(To whom does the slipper belong?)
Get ready, set, go.
(The princesses start the competition.)
How do I shell them?
(Snap)
I'll just shell them.
Does it still count if the seed breaks in half?
I'll eat those that break.
How do I shell them?
Shelling pumpkin seeds can be boring.
Who do you want to join your team?
I hope it won't be Seok Jin.
Why not?
Seok Jin is very needy.
During the beginning of the show,
he looked exhausted already.
(He's too old for clearing missions.)
No one wants Seok Jin to join her team.
- Right. - Is that what we all think?
That's right.
He needs to be taken care of all the time.
- That's true. - What about you, So Min?
I was always on the same team with Kwang Soo.
I want to work with someone else this time.
He always makes me nervous.
I know what you mean.
You never know when he'll betray you.
He makes people nervous.
We could say he's Cheap Lover.
- Cheap Lover? - It sounds offensive.
- Cheap Lover? - He falls in love easily.
(They concentrate.)
Can we go home even if we don't shell everything?
(Can we move on to the next mission?)
Are you really doing it?
Are you shelling pumpkin seeds?
They're shelling pumpkin seeds.
Was that the real mission?
So Min, you hardly shelled anything.
So Min ate some.
So Min does so many strange things.
(Time is up for You're My Cinderella.)
It's time to announce to whom the glass slippers...
- belong. - Okay.
Mine belongs to Do Yeon.
(He's on Do Yeon's team.)
She's my soul mate.
It's Ji Hyo.
(Haha is on Ji Hyo's team.)
Did you know they were in a love triangle at first?
- She made my heart flutter. - We were in a love triangle.
(We look forward to their teamwork.)
(Team leaders)
(The members on each team)
Here's the result for shelling pumpkin seeds.
Ji Hyo shelled the most.
That wasn't the real mission.
What is it then?
(What was the real mission?)
(Their shelling effort was in vain.)
In the meantime, I asked them a few questions.
They shelled pumpkin seeds while answering.
I see.
They also badmouthed other members.
Is that what they did?
- This isn't a mission. - So Min is the best at it.
Let's start with Do Yeon.
She made comments twice.
- Twice? - Is that all?
She agreed with the others once.
- I agreed? - She agreed?
- She agreed with them. - I see.
Ji Hyo agrees with others a lot.
- You say, "That's right." - I agree with people a lot.
- Is it a reaction? - Next is So Min.
- It's revealing. - I'm sure she talked a lot.
She made comments seven times.
- Comments? - Seven times.
- You're scary. - Did she talk about others?
- It's possible in 10 minutes. - What about pumpkin seeds?
She said Jae Seok and Seok Jin...
are needy when they're on her team.
- How could you say that? - She considers them old.
- Gosh. - This is surprising.
She said she's least comfortable with Haha.
- Really? - Why?
- So Min? - Why?
- Didn't he buy you a meal? - She's like that.
- What's wrong? - She's like that.
- I don't understand Haha. - Why not?
I'm the least close to him.
(It was hard to approach Haha.)
- She's like that. - She thought he wasn't friendly.
She thought he wasn't friendly.
- So Min. - He isn't friendly.
I didn't want her to get a wrong idea.
- Gosh. - I didn't want to make her uneasy.
She wouldn't feel uneasy.
- Don't misunderstand. - Okay.
I'll show you how friendly I am.
(He'll be friendly.)
So Min has the most points.
Ji Hyo made six comments about others.
- My goodness. - That's a lot.
She agreed with others five times.
- I knew it. - With a total of 11, Ji Hyo wins.
(Ji Hyo's team wins.)
She's the best.
She talks a lot about others.
No, I don't.
- Do Yeon is nice. - It's because she's nice.
I didn't know this was the mission.
- She could have done well. - I can make nasty comments.
You're divided into teams now.
We'll start the real competition.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(What's the next dangerous mission?)
This is amazing.
What's this?
It's Running Marble.
You put a lot of effort in the dresses.
It's that board game.
(What is this about?)
I like the color of your t-shirt.
- Really? - It's pink.
My team's outfit looks depressing.
- I asked for one in my size. - The outfit looks bad.
Goodness. Why didn't we get something in pink?
Are you being biased towards us because we're old?
(Is it because of our age?)
- My goodness. - We're old?
- What are you talking about? - It has nothing to do with it.
You don't look good in clothes as an actress.
(He counterattacks.)
- Seriously. - Listen.
Let's just focus on work.
Okay.
I'll make you do all the difficult tasks.
The first team mission is called...
Running Marble.
- Do you know how to play it? - Yes.
There's money in the back.
Each team gets 2,000 dollars.
It's money.
- That's a lot. - Each gets 2,000 dollars?
It's like the board game.
The rules are simple.
The winning team of Running Marble...
will get a reward.
You may buy land after you finish one round.
Only the female members can throw the dice.
- Let's start with Do Yeon. - Okay.
Please throw the dice.
It's nice to get Golden Key from the start.
Here I go.
It's quite heavy.
(She throws the dice.)
- It's really heavy. - Four.
(It's 4.)
- Let's see. - It's Jeju Island.
- Okay. - Who's next?
- There's no pressure. - Do you need help?
(Ji Hyo throws the dice.)
(Where will Ji Hyo's team land?)
- It's 1. - It's 1.
(They go to Taipei.)
- It's Taipei. - That's not bad, Ji Hyo.
- It's not very heavy. - It isn't?
- Isn't it okay? - Throw it high.
Throw it high.
(Where will So Min's team land?)
It's three.
(They head to Osaka, Japan.)
Everyone, you went around once.
- You didn't build any hotels yet. - Right.
- What's this? - It's interesting.
This is Part Two of Global Project.
The real mission is called...
Dangerous Trips.
- Pardon me? - Go to the city...
where you landed.
- What? - You may go now.
- What? - Do we have to go there?
- You may go now. - What?
Do we have to go there?
- It's a joke. - Really?
No way.
- No way. - What are you talking about?
- Do we go to Jeju Island? - Do we go to Taipei?
How can you say that with a straight face?
I have a live recording tomorrow.
- How can we go to Osaka now? - Do you mean that?
The three teams will go to their city...
on a backpacking trip for one day.
Go and enjoy your trip.
I can't believe it.
- What about the other pieces? - I don't believe it.
- How can we go to Osaka now? - We have to go to Osaka.
One day in Osaka?
That's why you asked us to bring passports.
Was it for this mission?
- Is it a one-day trip? - My manager said...
I'll be starting a new show on MBC.
I was happy to get more work, but it was about this.
- Gosh. - Unbelievable.
There are backpacks behind you.
Each backpack has...
a member's name in it.
You have to get a souvenir...
for the member whose name is in your backpack.
A souvenir?
(A one-day trip...)
(and souvenirs?)
This is unbelievable.
Please pick a backpack.
- Okay. - Well...
We won't have time to eat anything.
Your backpacks are important.
- So Min, please go ahead. - Pick a blue one.
(She touches the props.)
I'll go with the members, right?
(She destroys everything around her.)
Look at this.
I told you, right?
I'm so worried about you.
- I thought you were bowling. - There's so much space.
Exactly. How did she even touch them?
- Did you see? - She's so clumsy.
I'm so worried.
(Everyone has picked a backpack.)
Now, please leave for the country you chose.
We don't even have flight tickets.
- When are we buying tickets? - As soon as the choices were made,
we started booking flight tickets.
- You're unbelievable. - That's amazing.
Give us our passports back.
- This is unbelievable. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- See you. - See you.
(What will be waiting for them on this unexpected trip?)
(With everyone getting ready for departure, it's a chaos.)
(All they have is a backpack.)
- Please give me a pair of socks. - Okay.
I have to come back.
I have a shooting tomorrow.
Are we really leaving now?
Like this?
Let's hurry.
The flight is five hours long.
(They get in the cars to head to the airport.)
- We really are going to Osaka. - We are leaving.
This is really happening.
We're going abroad from this early morning.
My goodness.
I didn't know we'd go abroad.
- I never imagined this. - This is so unexpected.
- It's unbelievable. - It is.
- Seaweed soup with roe is amazing. - It's amazing.
- I love roe. - It's fantastic.
Grilled cutlassfish is good too.
Jeju Island has great cutlassfish. We made a great choice.
- We made the best choice. - We did.
Jeju Island is the best place in Korea.
(Let's go to Jeju Island.)
This is unbelievable.
Are we really going?
We really are at Incheon International Airport.
(They arrive at Incheon International Airport.)
- This is impossible. - Are we really going?
(Everyone keeps asking, "Are we really going?")
Are we really going to Osaka? Maybe we are.
- We really are going. - Is it this way?
- See you later. - See you.
- Are you really going? - See you, Ji Hyo.
- Maybe we really are going. - So Min, good luck.
- Okay, see you. - You guys are not going, are you?
Are you sure you're not going somewhere else?
Are we really going to Osaka?
- This might be a prank. - We might not go.
I have a live show tomorrow.
- Even I... - We're coming back tonight.
We must come back tonight.
(I'm sorry, but you guys really are going.)
Guys, we don't know yet.
We don't know until we're on the plane.
Hey, it's over.
- Se Chan, it's over. - I don't believe that.
- Hello. - Hello.
Are we really going to Japan?
Yes, you're going to Osaka.
(There really are boarding passes for them.)
Are they business-class seats?
Yes, all three of them.
- Why? - There were no economy-class seats.
Oh, my.
- We're lucky. - This is my first time.
They had to book the tickets this morning.
- It was last minute. - Economy-class seats were sold out.
Were there only business-class seats? We're lucky.
- This is my first time. - Really?
- Really? - I've never sat in business class.
This is fun. What's different? Is the food different?
Yes, the food is different.
(Then...)
Can I have some beer?
- We're shooting. - What are you talking about?
I'm getting excited no matter what this is.
This is your itinerary.
- We have 9 hours. - You're coming back tonight.
Our return flight is at 5:50pm.
Is this really possible?
- You visited Osaka last year. - Yes.
Let's make an acrostic poem with Osaka.
- "O". - On our trip,
- "Sa". - I'll disappear.
(What?)
Where's So Min?
(So Min goes missing in Osaka.)
(They shout So Min's name in the middle of Osaka.)
(Criss-crossing Osaka)
(Bouncing around)
(You'll find out what happens in Osaka soon.)
- "Ka". - It's the last one.
(What about the last one?)
- "Ka". - "Ka".
(What is this?)
(What is with her?)
Well...
(He changes the subject quickly.)
What's wrong with that?
Let's go.
(How will their trip go?)
Once we go in there, it's over.
- We can't come back here. - We already have boarding passes.
They might cancel them later.
- We'll just go in. - We'll be back.
- We can do this. - I'll be kicked out.
(I'll be kicked out of "Comedy Big League" if I don't return.)
He might be kicked out of his show if he doesn't come back in time.
I'll be kicked out.
Is this really happening?
- Okay, this is it. - Are we going in?
Let's go.
- We don't have much time. - We don't.
- We really are going. - We are.
Are we really going?
This is incredible. We're such a global show.
- We're global. - We really are.
(The flight for Osaka departs.)
I feel good.
(It's always fun to go on a trip.)
- I'm feeling good. - Me too.
(Crying)
(It reminds her of something.)
I used to cry a lot when I was a baby.
My mom said...
(Why are you suddenly talking about it?)
I cried even at a honking car.
(Talking)
(It never ends.)
So Min sure...
loves to talk.
You never stop.
You have too many stories to tell.
(They fly over the sea with fluttering hearts.)
(The talkative girl has fallen asleep.)
(Sleep is better than beer.)
(Shaking)
(They arrive at Kansai International Airport at 11:20am.)
Ladies and gentlemen...
- We're here. - We're in Japan.
We really are in Japan.
- We're in Japan. - It's quite chilly.
It's chilly.
It's a lot colder here than in Korea.
It's colder here.
You should protect your bones from the cold wind.
We're not that old.
- So Min. - It's quite chilly.
(Their trip in Japan starts.)
Where are we going now?
Where are we going?
- We're in Taiwan. - We are.
- Is this Taiwan? - We're not in Incheon.
(It feels like they're just in another city in Korea.)
- It's hot. - It's so hot.
Do you think Taiwan is Daejeon?
Welcome to Taiwan.
- Why did you make us come here? - Gosh.
- We're in Jeju Island. - Welcome to Jeju Island.
It feels so exotic.
Only one option was in Korea, and Do Yeon chose it.
- Right? - I'm a patriot.
- You really are. - She's a daughter of Korea.
Of course. This is the best place in Korea.
I'm so happy.
- You're in Osaka now. - Yes.
As I said, you'll look around the city...
and get souvenirs for the members whose names are in your bags.
- Souvenirs. - Okay.
It would be nice if that was all you have to do.
- Go on. - I'm sure there's something more.
- There's a mission for you. - What is it?
You have to complete a mission here in Taiwan.
You have to complete a mission here in Jeju Island.
- What is it? - A mission?
If you fail to complete the mission or go back to Korea today,
you'll get a Tour Sticker.
Tour Sticker is on the line again.
(They'll be given a Tour Sticker if they fail.)
(The one who accumulates 3 Tour Stickers...)
(will be sent to a dangerous tourist attraction.)
We're at a disadvantage.
Let's just avoid getting Tour Stickers.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Why are you telling us now?)
Let's go.
Here is today's mission.
What is it?
- "Costume play"? - What?
I saw "costume play" written on it.
- "Hair salon"? - What are those?
(What's that?)
- What's that? - "Getting a hairstyle..."
(Getting a hairstyle that is trendy here)
My goodness.
What do you think you're doing?
- Are we to pick one? - "Bathhouse"?
- Are we picking one? - Wait. "Visiting a bathhouse..."
"run by an owner whose last name is Suzuki"?
- What is this... - There are three options.
Visiting a bathhouse, taking a picture with costume players,
or getting a hairstyle that is trendy here.
My goodness.
So Min will throw her shoe.
- Me? - So Min has to do it.
- So Min, do a good job. - Do a good job.
Which one do you want?
Taking a picture with costume players seems best.
I'll aim for it then.
- Don't pick the hairstyle one. - Don't pick that one.
- That's the worst. - I didn't bring my hair powder.
- Hey. - Hey.
(She threw her shoe all of a sudden.)
Be more careful.
(She started without any notice.)
Visiting a bathhouse is not that nice either.
(Screaming)
- Don't aim for anything. - What did you do?
I aimed for the costume play one.
Costume play.
- Don't aim for anything. - My gosh.
(Will you please listen to us?)
- I said not to aim for anything. - Goodness.
- Tell us before you start. - Okay.
Let's start. Start!
(They can't even start their mission.)
- You can't even succeed in this? - So Min.
Just land it on the paper.
It doesn't matter which mission we do.
- She's a terrible new member. - Gosh.
Hey.
You are driving me crazy.
You can't land it there?
- So Min. - Can't you just kick it there?
- Try to do better. - Try it.
(There's no more time to waste.)
(She must gently place the shoe on it while her foot merely helps.)
(Will they be able to start their mission?)
"Take a bath at the bathhouse run by a Suzuki."
A bath?
All right.
The most common last name in Japan is "Sato".
The second most common last name is "Suzuki".
So you didn't book one already?
- You didn't? - We didn't.
We have to find a bathhouse owned by a Suzuki?
(On a one-day trip, we will go to a Suzuki's bathhouse?)
So we have to find it.
The bathhouse must be owned by a Suzuki.
- The owner must have... - The last name must be Suzuki.
I got it.
We will get going to start your mission.
- Yes! - Immediately?
- Yes? We have to find the place. - Let's go.
My goodness.
Are there a lot of bathhouses?
- You will know when you get there. - I don't think so.
- What? - We will know once we are there.
- You will know once we are there? - Yes.
They didn't reserve a place in advance.
(They are busy.)
- They should have... - Hey, help us remove them.
You ought to help us get rid of them.
- It's only us here. - Someone will remove them.
I guess it's hard to remove them.
Why is it so hard to detach this?
- Remove this. - Is it that hard?
Yes.
- Let me try. - I already finished.
By the way, this mission sounds really challenging.
First of all...
- We have to find Mr. or Ms. Suzuki. - We can't even speak Japanese.
- How can we find a bathhouse? - Let's use a translating program.
- What? - A translating program?
- Suzuki. - A translating program.
What are the other teams doing?
What do we do?
The mission is about food. This is amazing.
This is the best.
The rule is very simple.
Three of you will kick your shoes.
You finish the mission when you eat all the food your shoe chose.
- Look. We have to eat beef noodles. - We must eat beef noodles.
- Look at that. It's tasty too. - Danzai noodles?
Are those noodles?
- It is. - Those noodles are tasty.
- Hot pot. - We must have the hot pot!
- Hot pot! - Hot pot!
We should buy pineapple cakes. There's xiaolongbao. Look.
- Stinky tofu dish? - Will it...
- I can't eat stinky tofu dish. - We can't eat that.
I can't eat that.
Let's avoid that.
If your shoe falls on more than one dish, you must eat all the dishes.
Eating is not a problem, but can we finish on time?
- What time is our flight? - We have to eat them in time.
We might get the stinky tofu dish if we try to get the hot pot.
- Okay. I'll aim for beef noodles. - Aim for beef noodles.
- Kick gently. Gently. - She's right.
- Gently. - Please.
(Will his shoe make their wish come true?)
(Please don't let it be the stinky tofu dish.)
Haha, it fell short. Don't! Goodness.
(It's a betrayal of his shoe.)
- Don't! Goodness, Haha. - Hold on.
(They'll taste the stinky tofu dish which they've been wishing for.)
Your shoe chose the stinky tofu dish and mango shaved ice.
Haha, you kicked in that direction on purpose, right?
Next member, please get ready.
- Ji Hyo. Let me try. - Okay.
Haha, we ought to eat beef noodles.
(Let's eat beef noodles.)
We really should at least eat beef noodles.
Move a bit more. Just a little bit more.
(On which dish will his shoe fall?)
- Hey, that's great. - This is great.
- It's on the line. - No.
- It's on the line for beef noodles? - Is it on the line?
Look. The beef noodles...
(Pushing)
(I really want to taste beef noodles.)
(Did they forget about Tour Stickers?)
Beef noodles...
We will let you have the beef noodles.
(They add the beef noodles on the list!)
Ji Hyo. You are the last one.
- Let's have the hot pot. - Hot pot!
- Shall we? - Or the pineapple cakes.
Xiaolongbao isn't a bad choice too.
- Gosh! - Pineapple cakes!
(Pineapple cakes and danzai noodles are selected!)
- We have 5 dishes to eat. - 5 dishes.
- I should have gotten the hot pot. - You got those two dishes.
- We have to eat quickly and go. - Right. Let's go.
We really should hurry.
- Let's go. - Let's go!
To taste the stinky tofu dish, come to Taiwan!
We should eat the stinky tofu dish and mango shaved ice, right?
Right. We have to eat something sweet after that.
Shall we start with danzai noodles?
- Let's start with danzai noodles. - Great.
- This kind of trip isn't easy. - You're right.
- We have to make time for trips. - Right.
- We have to make time for trips. - We are here to have lunch.
You know what? Other teams...
Should we do this? It's been a while.
- What are other teams doing? - What are other teams doing?
(Jeju Island, foreign land in Korea)
- What are we going to do? - Let's go with ramyeon.
Don't pick women divers.
(On a lucky day, what will the shoe choose?)
(Will it choose oranges from Jeju?)
(Will it choose sightseeing a view that UNESCO acknowledged?)
(Please let today be a happy day.)
(Sea?)
(Will they have to dive into the water?)
(They all freeze.)
Your shoe chose the sea.
Wasn't UNESCO a good choice too?
I will explain the mission for the sea.
The mission for the sea is that...
you have to wear a diving suit and dive into the sea with women divers.
You must catch an octopus with your own hands and make ramyeon with it.
(Sea? Women divers?)
(Catch an octopus with women divers in the blue sea of Jeju Island.)
We have to catch an octopus?
We have to dive into the water and get an octopus, right?
- Right. - What was the mission for UNESCO?
Women divers are registered as Intangible Cultural Heritage...
of Humanity. You will wear the diving suit with them and...
(Welcome)
He's a con artist!
When did Running Man degenerate?
I thought this was a just program.
(The truth of their mission board is revealed.)
The mission about the activity is...
It's the most famous activity in Jeju Island.
Through the activity of women divers, you will catch an octopus.
(Welcome. You won't be able to escape from this trap.)
What a jerk!
(They must cook octopus ramyeon.)
(They set out to experience women divers' job.)
(Which team will receive a Tour Sticker?)
(Their mission is to visit a bathhouse run by Mr. or Ms. Suzuki.)
Since Suzuki is the second most common last name,
it's like Lee if I were to compare it to a Korean last name.
Hey, I'm not just saying this. This is really absurd.
- What are we doing here? - Why do we have to find it?
We have to find a bathhouse run by Mr. or Ms. Suzuki. Goodness.
- We can't call... - By the way, our flight is at 6pm.
It's around 5pm.
- We have to be back by 4pm. - We have two hours.
- We don't have much time left. - I told you. We do not.
- We have to buy presents too. - This is...
We are in trouble.
What is bathhouse in Japanese?
- I will let you know. - What is it?
- First of all, we should... - "Sento".
- "Sento". - "Sento"?
("Sento" means a bathhouse.)
- We should know it before we go. - "Sento".
Suzuki's "sento".
What happens if we can't find one?
(Their destination is Suzuki's bathhouse.)
- "Sento". - "Sento".
"Suzuki's bathhouse".
Was it "sento"?
- Yes. - Yes.
"Suzuki's..."
"Suzuki's bathhouse".
- You need to sound cheeky. - "Sento".
- "Suzuki's bathhouse". - What do you mean, cheeky?
(You are cheeky for saying that.)
Doesn't it sound a bit manly?
"Suzuki's bathhouse". You have to sound nice.
- You sounded like a girl. - No, I was being kind.
(He sounds like an angry father.)
What was that?
Shouldn't we say, "Are you Suzuki?"
"Are you Suzuki?"
Isn't it asking if something is a bathhouse?
No, it isn't.
Now that I speak decent English, I can't speak Japanese.
What do you mean you can speak English?
- Goodness. You're frustrating me. - There you go again.
- Fine. - Lower your knees.
- To where? Here? - Hey. Look.
- You're blocking the shot. - Where would I put my feet?
I have to split my legs like this then.
- Look at the frame. - Aren't you being too mean?
- That camera is filming you two. - Seriously.
- The camera is filming only her. - You don't have to...
Only this camera is filming me.
Your knees are blocking the shot.
- Hey, lower them. - Let go of them.
Other cameras are filming you guys, but not me.
- This one is filming you. - Hey.
- Let go of my leg. - Move your legs.
- It's the only camera filming me. - Let go of me.
(Surprised)
What happened?
The camera is so up close.
(It's as if she found a hidden camera.)
That was sudden. You've been sitting like this.
Just because you act surprised...
What are you doing, So Min?
- Just stay still. - Stay as you are.
- She's such an odd girl. - She is.
Nothing changes because you act surprised.
- Will that change anything? - Will it?
- She's so weird. - She's strange.
What are you looking at?
- What are you doing? - What's wrong?
- You shouldn't avoid your camera. - Sit back.
I feel suddenly...
(Can I borrow your shoulder for a moment?)
What are you doing?
- So Min is so weird. - She's so weird.
She's really weird.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
(She covers the camera with her hand.)
What are you doing?
Give me that camera.
Stop it.
My goodness.
Will we be able to find a bathhouse run by Suzuki?
We'll go to Dotonbori...
and have lunch.
And then we'll take a bath at a bathhouse run by Suzuki.
- Okay. - That's our plan.
Good.
(Osaka, Japan's second largest city, is famous for...)
(its historical sites and food.)
- It'll be so tasty. - I'm hungry.
I didn't eat anything on the plane.
Are we there yet?
- What are you doing? - I spoke Korean unconsciously.
I think we're here.
Should we get out?
(Are we really in Osaka?)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
We're in Japan.
(We really are in Osaka.)
Gosh, we're in Japan.
(Colorful signs welcome them.)
That sign is so pretty.
It's so cute.
(Delicious Japanese food)
This is nice.
This is really nice.
We came here unexpectedly,
- and it's nice. - This is nice.
It's nice to be here so unexpectedly.
(It's even nicer because it's unexpected.)
I feel so good.
- Where are we now? - The sign...
We're in Dotonbori. Look at that.
- Oh, that. - You know that, right?
- Are we in Dotonbori? - Yes.
This is nice.
Now I understand...
- what you meant by Cheonggyecheon. - It's right here.
I smell food.
Okonomiyaki...
- Let's go. - We're going to play a game.
The loser will treat the whole staff.
(Ouch)
(The pole was there the whole time.)
(He bumped into it.)
"The loser will treat the whole staff."
(Seok Jin was too excited.)
- Seok Jin. - Gosh.
- What did you do? - I'm okay.
You can get on a boat here too.
We should try.
We should try, but we don't have time.
We have to... Gosh.
We have to leave here around 3pm at the latest.
Hey, we're not shooting a travel show.
What is she doing?
I wish we could get on a boat.
My goodness.
- What is she doing? - What are you doing?
Like I said,
I'm going to write a report on her within two weeks.
She's...
on the verge now.
So far, she's been just a little odd.
- She's been a little odd. - She's really odd.
She's odd.
(So Min is going to turn Osaka upside down today.)
There are so many people.
Goodness. What should we do?
(Meanwhile...)
(Next to the weird girl...)
(is an overly excited middle-aged man.)
This is nice.
(He has gotten his youth back.)
I love this.
I love sudden trips.
I'm feeling so good.
(I'm feeling great.)
I love it.
Hi.
Hi!
(He encounters a group of Western tourists.)
We are the world
We are the children
We should take a picture.
(They take a picture.)
One, two, three.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Why do you speak English?
Thank you.
Why do you speak English? She's Korean.
Why do you speak English? Thank you.
Didn't she speak Korean?
Seok Jin is...
- I love this place. - So Min, this place is fantastic.
- Right? - Yes.
- So Min. - Yes?
Let's have lunch.
- Okay. - Let's have lunch.
Oh, it's takoyaki.
It's takoyaki.
It looks good.
- Is that takoyaki? - Yes.
Takoyaki?
- It must be a famous place. - It is.
- It is? - Should we try some?
Should we play rock-paper-scissors to decide who will pay?
Should we do that?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok wins.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin loses.)
Thank you.
Thank you, Seok Jin.
(Welcome)
- They look so tasty. - They look amazing.
- They're huge. - They look so tasty.
My goodness.
We're having takoyaki...
for lunch in Osaka.
This morning, I had no idea.
This is unbelievable.
They look so tasty.
(Jae Seok's camera angle is a bit strange.)
(Surprised)
They look great.
Thank you.
(This is the birthplace of takoyaki.)
Try it. This is great.
(He takes a bite.)
We should...
find the restaurant and have lunch.
(They have to find the restaurant.)
Let's move.
- Let's cool it down. - Let's do that.
I'm so excited.
Isn't it nice?
Let's try it.
It's still hot. Be careful.
(There are not many.)
They taste great.
(He takes the tray in his hands.)
It's too hot.
You just have to eat it...
- There's so much octopus in it. - even if it's hot.
It tastes great.
(They eat,)
(eat,)
(and eat.)
Well...
Is this your lunch?
(He finished 5 pieces in a flash.)
You had five pieces.
So Min.
Seok Jin has already had lunch.
(We're still going to have lunch.)
He had five pieces of takoyaki.
(This takoyaki tastes great.)
Where's So Min?
(So Min has disappeared?)
Where did she go?
(She talks to someone.)
(30 minutes ago)
- Wait. - Wait.
- What did you say? - What does it mean?
Is it a line from a drama?
(Is she good at Japanese?)
Suzuki's bathhouse...
Where is the bathhouse?
(Where is the bathhouse?)
Bathhouse...
In Dotonbori?
- Yes. - That way.
(Dotonbori is that way.)
Is it in Dotonbori?
What should I do? They're Japanese.
(They manage to find each other.)
(She keeps exploring the place on her own.)
Where's So Min?
She has disappeared again.
Where did she go?
(She carries out a mission on her own.)
Where is So Min?
- Hey! - The thing we've said the most...
- in Japan is, "Where is So Min?" - So Min!
(She's shopping bath products.)
- We need some lotion... - Should we get something?
- if we're going to have a bath. - You're right.
Excuse me.
You were here.
(They've finally found each other.)
- This place is nice. - I love it.
- Seok Jin, come here. - Seok Jin.
- We have to get tickets. - What are you doing?
- Are we going to eat here? - Yes.
- Let's eat here. - What do they have?
- Ramen. - Ramen.
Ramen?
It looks tasty.
(Rich broth and chewy noodles)
This is interesting.
- This is... - What is this?
Noodles in soup with extra...
(They have to use a machine to order.)
This one has pork too.
- Let's take that one. - Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok loses.)
Okay.
- Was this your plan? - Thank you.
- No. - No.
We don't do such a thing.
Insert it here.
(They have to order.)
That's where tickets come out.
(How...)
(does this machine work?)
This is hard.
It doesn't light up.
You have to press this.
I think it's this one.
Hold on.
(If it's hard to order three bowls at the same time...)
- There's only one solution. - Order them separately.
Exactly.
(They'll order one bowl at a time.)
- That's a good idea. - Order three times.
- And... - Hold on.
Wait.
- Wait. - You have to insert the money.
- That was why. - You have to insert the money.
(They should have inserted the money first.)
- There you go. - It worked.
Two dollars.
(They're done ordering the food.)
We can finally eat now.
We're having ramen.
(How will the ramen taste?)
I wonder how it'll taste.
You can smell...
- the pork broth. - Yes.
(Tourists are taking pictures.)
I'm sorry to make it inconvenient for you two.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm the one who should apologize.
- So Min. - Yes?
It must be very new to you.
- Yes. - Right?
I'm sorry.
They just care a lot about me, that's all.
Please understand.
The staff should understand too.
- It's not because of you. - I'm sorry.
It's so hard to even get some lunch.
I'm sorry.
(While they're being narcissistic,)
(the ramen is prepared.)
It's here.
(Steaming)
This...
So Min, I'm so curious how it'll taste.
Thank you for the meal.
(Minced garlic is added.)
Where's Seok Jin?
We can just leave him behind.
(Chives are added too.)
(Let's start.)
What do you think?
It tastes good.
It's tasty.
(Wait.)
(What is this perfect combination of flavors?)
It tastes great.
(Jae Seok starts eating.)
(He takes big bites.)
This is nice.
It tastes good.
(So Min slurps continuously.)
It's tasty.
(Slurping)
(She doesn't cut the noodles.)
I don't know how this ramen compares to other dishes.
(She slurps without taking a break.)
Perhaps it tastes better because I am hungry.
(Meanwhile, Seok Jin...)
(slurps a little.)
(He cuts the noodles right away.)
(He groans like a middle-aged man.)
It's savory.
It's bit spicy.
It's really good.
The more I eat it, the better it tastes.
(The more you eat,)
(the bigger bites you want.)
This is nice.
- I am serious. It's really tasty. - It's really tasty.
It's a bit...
small.
Thank you, So Min. It's delicious.
I don't usually add rice to ramen soup.
(They groan like middle-aged men.)
- It's really tasty. - It's really tasty.
(So Min inhales the dish.)
I am not lying when I say it's tasty.
(I am glad I came to Osaka.)
(Taipei, Jeju Island, Osaka)
(Team Taipei begins the tour.)
(It's a trip with great taste and atmosphere.)
(Welcome to Taipei, Taiwan.)
Let's go.
Let's begin the tour. Gosh, it's hot.
- My goodness. - My goodness. Hello.
This place makes me realize I am in a foreign country.
- This is Taiwan. - This is Taiwan.
I like the atmosphere.
(The center of food and shopping...)
(has a great atmosphere.)
The atmosphere is really nice.
(We are here.)
(Look at how cool they are.)
(Haha)
(Song Ji Hyo)
(Yang Se Chan)
(We are...)
(currently absorbed in the atmosphere of Taiwan.)
- Danzai noodles. - Danzai noodles.
The dish looks similar to ulmyeon.
- It looks like kalguksu. - That's right.
Kalguksu or ulmyeon.
This place feels like Hongdae.
- You are right. - It feels like Hongdae.
This is incredible. This place is really pretty.
Haha, that alley looks like Yeonhui-dong.
You are right. This is very cute. You should take a picture of it.
Taiwan has a nice atmosphere.
- It's very cute. - It's Running Man.
Taipei and Running Man go incredibly well together.
I don't know what to do.
- There is mango shaved ice. - My goodness.
- This place is the best. - You are right.
Let's come back here later. That restaurant is the best.
- It's peking duck. - Peking duck.
(Peking duck looks impressive.)
- It looks really tasty. - My goodness.
- It's chicken. - I don't know what to do.
It looks incredible.
There are so many clean venues that serve delicious dishes.
(I want to eat everything.)
- Tripe. - My goodness.
- What's that? - It's tripe.
- Right? - Tripe?
What is that?
This is danzai... Danzai...
Danzai noodles.
This is the dish.
- Is this the right dish? - Danzai noodles. This is the dish.
Thank you. Danzai noodles?
- Danzai noodles. - They have the dish. Let's go.
The menu is in Korean, too.
(The considerate menu makes the mission easier.)
(Danzai noodles is a dish which originated from Tainan.)
(It is made with mung bean sprouts, cilantro, shrimp, and minced meat.)
(Its rich meat broth satisfies the five senses.)
(They only need to order now.)
- The menu is in Korean, too. - Best of the best.
The best product. Wait, I said, "product" in Korean.
Danzai noodles.
Three, please.
Also... Wait, wait.
You continue to mix English and Korean.
(Choose a language.)
(Embarrassed)
Is this roll tasty? Let's eat fried shrimp.
- She said it's tasty. - Are you in Korea?
- You are in a foreign country. - People understand.
- People understand. - We are the world.
- I can communicate using Korean. - We have the best teamwork.
- We are doing great. - I feel bad for other teams.
Should we give them a call?
Let's do that.
Should we call the team in Osaka?
- Osaka? - Should we call Team Osaka?
I am answering a video call from Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo. Did you answer the call?
- Ji Hyo. - Where are you?
- Where are you? - Seok Jin.
- Where are you? - We are in Taiwan.
- Taiwan? - We are in Osaka, Japan.
- We are in Osaka. - What is your mission?
"Mission".
(She pronounced it as if it's a Korean word.)
How else should I pronounce it?
- This is green plum liquor. - We are on a food trip.
- What? - Your mission is nice.
- Green plum? - Green plum?
You look exhausted because of So Min.
We are exhausted. She keeps saying she will take care of us.
I apologize for her behavior.
You will know when you watch the episode. She runs wild.
She runs wild.
Everything looks peaceful over there.
- I will leave on my own. - We are so confused.
Look at her. She is leaving on her own.
What is your mission?
We need to find Suzuki's bathhouse and take a bath.
Suzuki's bathhouse?
- Stop lying. - You are lying.
I am serious. We are looking for Suzuki's bathhouse.
We need to go. We will see you later.
- Okay. - See you later.
(They end the call after checking up on each other.)
- Our mission is the best. - It seems that way.
- The dishes are here. - It's very small.
- Danzai noodles? - Danzai noodles. Yes.
The dish is very small.
We ordered other dishes as well.
- It smells of meat. - It is topped...
- with minced meat. - There are mung bean sprouts.
It looks like miniature pho.
It smells great.
Ji Hyo will try it first.
My goodness.
Se Chan, good job. It tastes amazing.
- Is it good? - Yes.
(Slurping)
Joon Hyun will finish it in one bite.
(It's self-explanatory.)
- Try it. - I feel bad for other members.
Haha.
(He stuffs his mouth with noodles.)
- It's good, right? - It's good, right?
(He drinks the broth immediately.)
(My goodness.)
I was...
in a program called "Gourmet Road".
I will describe the taste.
(Haha will give an assessment of the dish.)
This taste is...
crazy.
(He uses cliche expressions.)
I am serious.
It contains a bit of cilantro.
- It has the taste of Taiwan. - Yes, it has the taste of Taiwan.
In conclusion,
- it's crazy. - It's crazy.
- Do you understand me? - Yes.
(She doesn't care if the others are talking or not.)
It has a clean taste.
(Ji Hyo unleashes her appetite.)
(She spots another target.)
- Bulgogi. - It tastes like bulgogi.
(She forgets about the shoot and focuses on the food.)
It's not too rich.
I am happy to be in Taiwan with the two of you.
This is great.
It's so tasty.
(We cleared the dishes.)
I wonder how the other teams are doing.
- What are they up to? - What are they up to?
(Jeju Island is raining.)
I can't believe I am going into the sea.
Me neither.
- It doesn't feel real. - I know.
(Jeju Island is known for its good weather.)
We will be able to come back, right?
(However, this is the reality today.)
What? Okay.
My goodness.
How is this happening?
- So it's really happening. - How is the weather so bad?
- We are really going into the sea. - This is ridiculous.
How will we find octopus?
My goodness, it's so cold.
(Even the camera sways.)
What is going on?
(How can Jeju Island have this kind of weather?)
We can't enter the sea in this weather.
(She was hailed as the princess.)
(She was happy to wear a dress.)
(She thought she would get to eat...)
(grilled hairtail, sea urchin, and seaweed soup.)
(She wanted to make good memories under the sunlight of the island.)
(How is this happening?)
(They need to catch an octopus in this weather.)
The wind makes it hard to stand on land.
How will we find octopus...
in the open sea?
Isn't this what you see in the news when there's an incoming storm?
The waves are very big. Is it safe to enter the water?
(They must catch an octopus to return to Seoul.)
We welcome you to women divers mission.
You welcome us?
- They must be serious. - Is this really happening?
- We are really doing this. - They are not hired by the program.
(Women divers enter proudly.)
(They are on the list of Intangible Cultural Heritage.)
(They gather seafood in all types of weather.)
(Even the giant octopus...)
(is an easy prey for them.)
(They specialize in catching octopus.)
They are real women divers.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(It's nice to meet you.)
Ma'am, do you go into the sea in this kind of weather?
- No, we don't. - What?
(What did you say?)
You can't go in right now. The waves are too strong.
- You can't go in? - No, you can't.
- Then why are we going in? - The weather is too bad.
Then why are we going in?
You can't go in.
- You are a real diver, right? - Yes, I am.
We came here to gather seafood, but had to cancel.
(They canceled their plans.)
- What should we do? - That means we can't go in.
Today...
(He stifles his laughter.)
- We won't be able to go in. - We can't catch an octopus.
I was so ready.
I really wanted to catch an octopus.
On our way here, we heard the news that you can't enter the water.
That's sad.
- What now? - What now?
Please.
- I'll hold it for you. It's heavy. - We're so disappointed.
- It's okay. - We're so disappointed.
We'll be back next time to help.
- Thank you. - Look at the forecast next time.
- That's right. - We're sorry.
- It was supposed to rain today. - Yes.
So we...
wanted to experience this indirectly...
(He's flustered.)
How do I put this?
Are you making this up?
- You can't think of it? - No,
I'm not making anything up.
One of you will put on the diving suit...
and eat the octopus ramyeon to complete the mission.
It must be sold nearby.
It'll be funny if Kwang Soo puts it on.
Yes, he'll look like a model.
(We'll see who gets to wear it.)
Please come over here, ma'am.
(The women divers will decide who gets the punishment.)
Please pick somebody who'll look good in it.
Because...
(They're thinking seriously.)
- Look at this broad back. - Madam.
I don't think I'll fit into diving suits.
- I'm over 2m tall. - He looks like a model.
- I'm over 2m tall. - It'll be funny for a tall person.
- I don't agree. - Let's do it for fun.
Please go ahead...
and stand behind the person who'll look the best in the suit.
(One person will have the honor of wearing the diving suit.)
(The chosen one will have the chance to look great in it.)
(They'll be picked by the women divers.)
Which star will look the best in the diving suit?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Who will it be?)
(It's Model Lee Kwang Soo.)
Thank you. You're the best.
- He's a model. - Thank you.
- He's a model. - Madam.
- He'll look great. - Thank you.
- Thanks so much. - Thank you.
- I feel happy. - Oh, dear.
- You're skinny... - And tall.
- You also have a nice body. - That's right.
You're handsome too.
- That's right. - I agree.
He's so happy.
- This is great. - You didn't have to.
- Don't say that. - He's happy.
Don't say that in front of others.
It worked out.
(Let's see his fashion.)
- You can come out. - Come out.
Come out.
(He looks pretty good.)
You look good.
- He looks good. - Wait a minute.
(He's satisfied himself.)
Doesn't he have to put this on?
- There's a hood. - The hood?
- There's a hood? - You have to put it on.
This looks too good.
You look so fashionable.
- What hood? - It's the seal-looking one.
- I forgot. - You did forget.
You have to wear it. That's right.
She's putting it on for him.
- Put it on. - That's the right way to put it on.
Is it always this hard to put it on?
Ma'am.
- You look like a monkey. - It's good.
- Is this how you put it on? - Yes.
- Is this right? - Oh, dear.
(The divers have fallen for his beauty.)
- Is this right? - Yes.
What about the goggles? Right.
- That's good. - Okay.
(His style has improved.)
They're so happy.
It's perfect.
I can't hear you. Can you speak up?
You look good.
- Do I look okay? - You look handsome.
- Does it look okay? - Yes.
Your face is so small right now. It's one-twelfth of your height.
- Really? - Your face is so small.
I'm so jealous.
Is this how I look?
- Why am I frowning so much? - No, you look happy.
That's it. This is great.
(Meanwhile, in Osaka...)
- I think we should ask. - Let's ask.
- Let's ask a Japanese. - Come here, Seok Jin.
- Let's ask a Japanese person. - Ask about Suzuki.
- Ask them, So Min. - Those police officers.
Ask the policemen.
- Say excuse me. - Excuse me.
(She asks carefully.)
(They pass by.)
- Hey... - Thank you.
I knew it.
"Excuse me and thank you"?
Hey.
(She thanks them as soon as she excuses herself.)
- Who wants to ask? - Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Where's Suzuki in the bathhouse?
What was that?
(What was that?)
(What did you say?)
(They don't know how to reply.)
- Bathhouse. - Bathhouse.
- Bathhouse? - Bathhouse.
Are you talking about bathing? Where you wash yourself?
(It's the place where you do this.)
- Mr. Suzuki. - Mr. Suzuki.
(Let me see.)
Is Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse...
a liquor bottle?
(What are they saying?)
If you go straight from the lights, there's a bathhouse.
But I don't know if it's Mr. Suzuki's.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- So... - So...
after listening to her...
(They just laugh.)
You're trying to guess.
- You found out when she did this. - Don't try to guess.
I heard it exactly.
It's like she was saying, "I'm not too sure."
- No, what she said was... - "That might not be it."
"There's a bathhouse if you go this way,"
"but I'm not sure if it's Mr. Suzuki's."
(There's a bathhouse if you go this way,)
(but I'm not sure if it's Mr. Suzuki's.)
(They translated by looking at her.)
Excuse me.
(They ask another person just to make sure.)
Mr. Suzuki...
- Mr. Suzuki? - Yes, Mr. Suzuki.
Where's Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse?
- Bathhouse. - Bathhouse.
(They all pretend like they're taking a bath.)
- It's a bathhouse called Suzuki? - Yes.
There's a bathhouse across the street.
But I'm not sure if it's called Suzuki.
- There's a bathhouse across. - Did you understand?
Of course, I did.
That's what she said.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you so much.
What did she say?
- This is what she did. - Did you understand her?
- You understood her, right? - She said, "It's quite tricky."
- No, she said this. - What did she say?
"There's a bathhouse nearby,"
"but I'm not sure if it's Mr. Suzuki's."
You're guessing.
You're supposed to understand language by gestures.
But how are we supposed to find Mr. Suzuki?
Where's his bathhouse?
(I have to step up.)
Mr. Suzuki's...
bathhouse...
(He pretends to bathe himself.)
Where?
(Jae Seok asks on his own.)
Excuse me.
(He repeats the question again.)
(He's been asking about the bathhouse for two hours.)
(Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse?)
(Please tell me you know.)
I know where the bathhouse is. Should I try looking for it?
You're looking it up.
Yes, please.
- He's looking it up. - He is too.
There's a Sumoto Hot Spring nearby.
Where?
(He can't tell.)
Here? Mr. Suzuki?
I'm not sure if it's Mr. Suzuki's.
Can you unlock the pattern?
(Everybody in the world does down and right.)
Everybody's similar. It's simple.
Here.
I found it.
(Excuse me. He found it.)
(Go ahead.)
- Thank you. Bye. - Mr. Suzuki's here?
- Take a picture of this. - Try it.
- Go ahead. - Hold on. How do I do this?
Can we ask him to send it to us?
(That's a good idea.)
- Then we'll become friends. - We need his number.
We have to be friends?
- Don't do that. - I mean...
- I'm sorry. - Where's the address?
Address?
(They're friends already.)
- "Three people". - It's every Saturday.
If it's more than three people, it's free.
- It's free if it's more than three? - No?
- How can you... - Isn't that what it says?
- Here it is. - Where?
- This. - Okay.
(They find something that looks like an address.)
- That's it. - Thank you.
- Let's hurry. Thank you. - Thank you.
We found it.
How do we get there?
- Let's take a cab. - What were you saying earlier?
If it's free for 3, is it free for a group of 50?
- Come on. - How does that make sense?
- That's not nice. - Maybe it's 1 free for every 3.
- You shouldn't forget this. - It should be 1 free for every 3.
The highlight of today was this.
"Excuse me."
"Thank you."
(She was so timid.)
I saw too.
(She apologizes and thanks people.)
- Show him, Seok Jin. - Right, the picture.
Excuse me.
- Here. - Okay.
- Okay? - Okay.
- Navigation. Okay. - That's right. Thank you.
I wonder if it's Mr. Suzuki's. We need to ask once we get there.
I know. I hope...
it's Mr. Suzuki's.
We came this far. It has to be right.
Wait a minute. You kind of look like No Ju Hyeon.
"You punk."
That's Joo Hyun.
- Wasn't that No Ju Hyeon? - No.
We didn't ask for an impression of him.
That came out of nowhere.
I've never had someone respond like that.
- You didn't expect it. - I'm flustered.
(Actresses usually don't volunteer to do it.)
(She keeps trying it.)
Seok Jin is really good at impressions. He used to be so good.
- It's too old. - It's just too old.
(I used to be funny.)
Were you a comedian, Seok Jin?
You didn't know?
I debuted four times.
- Isn't he steadily funny? - Yes, I agree.
It's like he's a quiet river.
A small fish jumps up once in a while.
That's about it.
Jae Seok...
is like a valley.
- A valley? I'm deep, right? - What's that?
No, it's not deep.
It keeps on trickling with water.
The stream bumps against rocks.
- You're like the current. - I'm like the current.
- He's the current. - That sounds good.
I'm like the current.
- He keeps on chatting away, right? - Yes.
So Min,
is it difficult for you to act as a tragic character?
No, I can do it.
- Don't you want to do it? - Can you do it?
- A tragic... - I can do it.
Can you act as if...
you're going home after a breakup?
You can look out the window.
(She starts acting right away.)
(I sometimes...)
(tear up.)
(I like how...)
(I cry my heart out and not think about it.)
Are there any lines?
I teared up.
(She teared up.)
- That's awesome. - I acted with my eyes.
- I saw her tears. - She's good.
- So Min, - That was fast.
you didn't have to do that.
- Why are you crying? - You didn't have to cry.
- Were you serious? - I'll work hard.
Drama producers...
SBS drama producers,
I'll work hard.
Whom are you talking to?
Focus on Running Man.
(Let's find the bathhouse first.)
- I think we're here. - We're here.
(They have arrived at their destination.)
(They came,)
(but would Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse be here?)
- So Min. - So Min.
(So Min)
Let's...
not give her time.
Why do you keep... We keep calling you.
We are always looking for you.
When we started out,
you said you'd look after us.
Do you know how many times we looked for you?
We've been repeating...
Mr. Suzuki and your name.
It's just been you two.
We keep looking for Mr. Suzuki and you, So Min.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Where is it? - Let's go.
Let's go. Where is it?
- Where is it? - Here.
- Where... - We can't go if we don't know.
- Where's the bathhouse? - Hold on.
We need to find a similar sign.
We don't know...
Where are we?
That's the sign we saw.
- It's right. - What is it?
It's here.
(Is that the bathhouse?)
(It says something hot spring.)
- I think it's here. - Please.
(These are the same words they saw before.)
(They match what they found earlier.)
When I saw it,
it said they open around 3:30pm.
- Okay. - If three people come together...
Here.
They open at 3:30pm.
It's 2:45pm right now.
Should we check if it's run by Mr. Suzuki?
- Right. - That's what we have to check.
If 3 people come together, it's 1 free admission.
It's so nice here. It smells nice.
This is Japanese...
Excuse me.
(Is he...)
(Mr. Suzuki?)
Suzuki...
Mr. Suzuki?
Yes, you're right.
(They found Mr. Suzuki in Osaka.)
- Bathhouse? - Yes, I run the bathhouse.
- Yes. - Hold on. We have to be sure.
(They don't know what he's saying.)
- Wait. - You learned something earlier.
- Hold on. - Try it.
I should look it up.
"Is this Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse?"
Is this Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse?
Is this Suzuki... Suzuki's... Bathhouse?
(Is this Mr. Suzuki's...)
(He practiced,)
(and practiced, and practiced.)
Mr. Suzuki... Bathhouse...
(Even So Min practiced in her sleep.)
(They came this far to ask one question.)
(Is this Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse?)
Yes, it's fun.
(Is he saying yes?)
- It's right? Mr. Suzuki? - Yes.
- You're the CEO? - Yes.
This is Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse.
(They've been asking for 20 minutes.)
(It's the name of the bathhouse.)
- Your brother? - Yes.
(You're Mr. Suzuki's brother?)
Are you Suzuki's brother?
(Well...)
You're the boss.
(He's the boss.)
- Your full name. - My business card.
Business card?
- It smells... - It smells nice.
- like soap here. - It smells like a bathhouse.
Let's see.
- Can you read it? - "Mr. Suzuki".
(He's very precise.)
(Is that a Korean business card?)
- I'm right. - You don't know.
Owned by... Bath...
(Look at this.)
- Suzuki? What's your full name? - He's the owner.
- Junji. - Junji Suzuki?
(His last name is Suzuki and first name is Junji?)
(They have confirmed his identity.)
- I'm Jee. - Mr. Jee.
- Jeon... - Ms. Jeon.
Ms. Jeon?
What is your name again?
- It's So Min. - Yes, So Min.
- "What is your name?" - Jeon.
(He's losing his memory.)
Jeon and Yu.
- Is it the name for women? - So Min.
- So Min. - She's cute.
Thank you.
- She's cute? - Yes.
(Japanese people think she's cute too.)
- You must love it. - That looked so strange.
(Shaking)
What was that?
We have to keep watching her. She has multiple personalities.
Can we take a bath now?
This is for men.
Wait. Let me ask.
It said 1 admission for 3 people.
"Is it 1 free admission for 3 people?"
- Hold on. - Free pass?
- Three person? - Stop it.
"I heard it's 1 free admission for 3 people."
It'll be awesome if it's true.
I heard it's 1 free admission for 3 people.
(What is he saying?)
No?
(Is there 1 free admission?)
(That's not possible.)
Can we take a bath now?
Yes, okay.
It's boiling.
- Boiling? - Yes?
Did he say, "Shy"?
- Shy? - Shy, shy, I'm shy
(We're embarrassed by these two.)
We have a staff member who speaks Japanese so he'll speak.
Can you ask if we can film...
before 3:30pm?
(Can we film before you open at 3:30pm?)
(It's okay as long as you stop before 3:30pm.)
- We can film? - Yes.
Can we go?
Yes, this way is for men.
That way's for men.
This is for women.
- So Min. - She's cute.
We don't meet inside, right?
How much is it for three people?
4 times 3 is 12. It's 12 dollars.
- Three people. - Yes.
(They pay for 3 adults.)
(Who knew they'd take a bath in Japan?)
He didn't have to say, "Three people".
See you.
This is Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse.
We're here.
All are welcome here.
(They finally enter Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse.)
It's nice.
(They enter the bathhouse.)
Look.
(It's nice here.)
- It's nice. - It's like those old bathhouses.
- Are you filming? - Yes.
- This is a community bathhouse. - It's nice.
- These are... - It feels like a bathhouse.
(You can see how detailed Mr. Suzuki is.)
(The bathhouse is simple and neat.)
It's been such a long time.
It's been a long time.
- We can take a locker. - Let's hurry.
- We have to hurry. - We have no time.
(How's So Min in the women's side?)
It's a real bathhouse.
The scale.
It's an old scale.
It's fascinating. Should I weigh myself?
(Flapping)
(She's 52kg.)
I usually don't weigh this much.
This scale...
The needle...
(She's exactly 52kg.)
(She's flustered.)
I ate too much in Japan.
(She reveals her weight just like that.)
It's open here.
- You can talk to each other. - Really?
- What? - It's open on top.
- So Min. - Yes?
Seok Jin, it's...
Do we have to buy towels?
That's right. It's 90 cents.
- Right? - We have to buy towels.
Hold on.
It's open, So Min.
Right.
(Would Team Osaka be able to complete their mission?)
Ta-da. This is the bathhouse.
Can you see this?
It smells like an old bathhouse.
These things are so tiny.
They're so cute.
(The boiling bathhouse has cute decorations.)
(Groaning)
(Shall we go in?)
(Here comes the first old man.)
It's nice here. It's so nice.
- It's nice. - This place...
(And here's the second old man.)
(Groaning)
(Exclaiming)
- You left your glasses on? - Pardon?
It's nice here.
(They're being so loud.)
It's nice.
It's so cute.
(They finish bathing at Mr. Suzuki's bathhouse.)
It was so nice.
We have no time. We have to leave.
It's like we're at somebody else's house.
I need to dry my hair.
You have to pay. It's 20 cents.
This is quite...
private.
(It's cozy.)
- It's... - It looks like a library.
- It's private. - I'm going to do it too.
There isn't one here.
As you can see, this is a powder room.
It's for personal use.
I'm going to get a massage.
I'm drying my hair right now.
- Would 20 cents... - Would it dry?
(Would he be able to dry his hair with 20 cents?)
I wasn't sure, but it's enough.
It lasts a long time.
It's enough for two.
(He's become one with the massage chair.)
I'm done drying my hair. Let me dry Seok Jin's too.
(Can two people dry their hair with just 20 cents?)
- Does it still work? - Yes.
Is it still working?
- It's still working. - Let's switch. Come here.
Use the massage chair.
(They're using their 20 cents to the fullest.)
This lasts a really long time.
It really does.
What time is it?
It's 3:20pm.
- We need to hurry up. - We need to go.
(Taipei, Jeju Island, Osaka)
(Meanwhile, in Taipei...)
- We succeeded with our first meal. - It was a great success.
- We did it. - The first meal was a success.
Let's have beef noodles as our last meal.
- We should leave that for last. - I'm not lying.
- I'll just follow your orders. - Look for the stinky tofu dish.
Okay, I'll do that.
- Where is the stinky tofu? - Okay.
Excuse me.
Where is the restaurant that sells stinky tofu?
(What?)
Tofu. Stinky tofu.
(Stinky tofu?)
(Tofu?)
We're talking about tofu.
Stinky... The square-shaped food.
- Stinky tofu. Stinky tofu. - Haha.
- This place just sells socks. - Stinky tofu.
- Why are you asking here? - This place sells socks.
- We should go to a restaurant. - Why are you asking for tofu here?
(Embarrassed)
People who sell socks tend to be nice.
You're right. Haha, look here.
(If you have trouble abroad, just go to a place that sells socks.)
- Stinky tofu. - What's this?
Stinky tofu.
(They continuously...)
(look for stinky tofu.)
We're looking for stinky tofu.
- They don't sell it here. - This place sells ribs.
I think they only sell side dishes.
- Do you sell stinky tofu? - Stinky tofu?
- No, no. - You don't have it?
(They eagerly look for stinky tofu.)
No?
A lot of celebrities must've came here.
(Does this restaurant sell stinky tofu?)
Isn't that stinky tofu?
Stinky tofu.
(Did they finally find it?)
- Do they have it? - Is it this?
(Is this the stinky tofu they've been searching for?)
- It's a skewer. - No, that doesn't count.
(That doesn't qualify.)
Thank you.
It's really hard to find stinky tofu.
- Finding stinky tofu isn't easy. - Right.
I feel like this place will sell stinky tofu.
Excuse me.
(Please be here.)
- You have the best pronunciation. - Okay.
Excuse me.
(Do you guys sell stinky tofu?)
(Yes, we sell it.)
- Do they have it? - Stinky tofu?
(Do they really have it?)
Okay, thank you.
- Where should we sit? - This place is nice.
It looks yummy.
If we even succeed with stinky tofu,
- that'll be beautiful. - This is...
Because your team leader, Ji Hyo, peeled off...
the most pumpkin seeds earlier,
- you guys won a Chance Card. - That's right.
We will give you guys the Chance Card right now.
- Right now? - My goodness.
Can we open it?
(What could it be?)
- What is this? - You can use this card...
against the other teams.
(What is it?)
We can use this against them?
This is incredible.
- We're so lucky. - I can't believe our luck.
You guys can choose one team...
and use this card against that team.
Which team will you attack?
- We don't even need time to think. - Let's just choose.
Please tell us the team you've chosen. In 1, 2, 3.
- Osaka. - Osaka.
You've used your card against Team Osaka.
- Did we just use it? - Did we use the card?
- I wonder how they'll react. - I wonder.
I wonder.
- Thank you. - I feel great.
(They've finished taking a bath without knowing what's going on.)
I was in a rush, so I didn't even put lotion on.
- So Min. - I didn't get to put lotion on.
(Is that you, So Min?)
You look so clean. Do you want to borrow our lotion?
- I have one. My face is bare. - Do you have one?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Wait. Where's So Min?
Where's So Min? Where are your eyebrows?
(She doesn't look familiar.)
I'm going to put makeup on now.
- Really? - You don't need to put makeup on.
- Let me see your face. - It's better to see her like this.
- You don't need to put makeup on. - Everyone.
You've succeeded in finding...
- Suzuki's bathhouse. - Yes, we did.
- You've completed your mission. - Yes!
- It was really nice. - I loved it.
- I wanted to stay here longer. - Me too.
- I really liked this place. - Me too. It was so cute.
- It was also very clean. - It really was.
However,
Ji Hyo received a Chance Card earlier. Do you remember that?
Yes.
(Team Taipei has attacked Team Osaka.)
That card...
(What kind of effect will it have on Team Osaka?)
- Will have an effect on your team. - What?
(Team Osaka has cleared their mission,)
(but they will now be facing hardships.)
- On our team? - Ji Hyo's team...
used that card against your team.
- They're unbelievable. - What is...
- wrong with them? - Why are they doing this?
So that's why we were given such a nice meal.
I guess so.
(Next week, they will face a more challenging mission.)
(The three teams are not done with their missions yet.)
(What will be the result?)
(Also,)
(Running Marble has become more global.)
(One single dice...)
(will decide on their future destiny.)
(Where will they end up going?)
(Running Man's Global Project: Dangerous Tourist Attractions)
(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by the bloggers)
(Tour Stickers)
(3 Stickers and you're chosen.)
(Who will end up going?)
(Running Man's Global Project: Dangerous Tourist Attractions)