(A wedding hall in Ilsan is on the threshold of winter.)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Good morning. - Hello.
Doesn't Jong Kook look great in his outfit today?
- Jong Kook. - In our last shoot, people...
looked down on me when I dressed down.
- You just wore a new coat. - So I dressed up today.
- That's right. - Seok Jin.
When I take off the coat, it's the same outfit.
- You only wore a new coat. - Why is he being so stubborn?
- You just have a new coat. - No one can change his mind.
(His outfit hasn't changed.)
Today, you'll be joined by actors who receive more love...
whenever they do evil things.
It is a race with actors who are most know for portraying villains.
- My goodness. - Actors will join us today?
- These days... - Villains are very popular.
- They are indeed. - That's true.
(He walks with confidence.)
(His silhouette exudes the presence of a villain.)
- My goodness. - Gosh.
- It's him. - He's a great actor.
- He's dressed up. - He's like a brother to me.
He's like a brother to us. We are close friends.
(Choi Gwi Hwa, the most sought-after villain actor)
(He's the devil-like cop in a plain outfit in "A Taxi Driver".)
(He acts in various roles and is a popular actor in film industry.)
It's like he dressed up for an awards ceremony.
I thought you were the owner of a restaurant.
(Sir, is everything to your liking?)
- I'm ready to order now. - My brother.
- I'd like a hamburger steak. - Hello.
- Sure. - A hamburger steak, please.
Why did you get so dressed up?
Why did you bring this book? Is it called "Tongue Fu"?
There isn't a reason behind it.
I just wanted to rely on something.
- That was part of your act? - Gwi Hwa...
Did you bring it from home?
- No, I got it from here. - Gwi Hwa...
He is...
- As you all know... - Don't do that. He looks older.
- Seok Jin. - He's younger than me.
I didn't know, but I found out he's my college alumnus.
- Really? - He's a junior alumnus.
- Seriously? - That's right.
- I went to school before him. - Is that so?
He's younger than you, Haha?
No, he's not younger than me.
- I entered college before him. - You went to school before him.
- Gwi Hwa is a year older than Haha. - He is?
- Just 1 year? - 1 year?
(He's only a year older?)
- He must've gone to school late. - He's a year older than me.
- I went to school a year later. - Have you heard about Haha?
I actually saw him a lot.
- How was he then? Be honest. - Exactly.
I heard he went to Itaewon often.
He used to tout on the street.
- He was like an arch in Itaewon. - What?
(Haha was an arch in college.)
Arch? He was like an arch?
- Arch? - He was always there like an arch.
- I see. - I get it.
- I have a funny story about him. - What is it?
- Was it Haha and my classmates? - Senior alumni?
One time, they went over to Haha's house.
- Really? - They went to his house late drunk.
- People do go to his house often. - His mother...
(They went to his house drunk late at night, and his mother...)
She threw salt at them and said, "You demons!"
(Demons, get lost!)
You demons!
- It was when she was religious. - "You demons!"
- She was very religious then. - I see. She was into that.
When I went home drunk...
How drunk were you?
"You demons".
"You lewd beings!"
That's hilarious.
- Let's bring out the next guest. - Okay.
- Please come on out. - I'm so curious.
Who is it?
(A man in a red suit...)
(is here to take over Running Man.)
- My goodness! - Oh, my!
- "Do you know who I am?" - Here he comes.
- His outfit looks great. - He was in a gang in a film.
- My goodness. - He only plays scary roles.
(Heo Sung Tae, a late bloomer)
(He debuted in "The Age of Shadows" after working at a big company.)
(Do you know who I am?)
(He's a hair-raising actor that the whole nation knows.)
Please come here.
Come this way, please.
- He's shy as expected. - This is great.
- He looks shy. - He's shy.
Sung Tae.
- He looks so young among them. - What is this?
- It's a corduroy suit. - It's coffee.
- Why are you drinking like that? - What is that?
- Why are they putting up an act? - Why is he coming up with an act?
- I'm sorry. - This is so obvious.
Why did you put coffee in a water bottle?
- What are you doing? - It's tasty.
Did you make your own coffee at home?
- Yes. - Sung Tae.
- Yes? - Did you buy new shoes?
(Shiny)
- They are... - They are new shoes.
- The head of my agency bought them. - Oh, really?
They were for Running Man.
The head of your agency bought them for you?
The head of my agency runs a tailor shop.
(He's feeling shy.)
- I'm serious. - Seriously?
- He really runs it? - He runs a tailor shop?
- The suit is a bit... - The corduroy suit...
The corduroy suit looks great on you.
- The head of his agency runs it. - I see.
- This is interesting. - It's unique.
Right now, he seems quite innocent.
- He's like a naive country guy. - Right.
Seok Jin, he dressed up for today. Don't say he's from the country.
I just meant emphasize that he looks very innocent.
I think you're recycling a few of your own lines.
- I came up with 5 lines today. - 5 lines?
I keep on switching with those five lines.
- I only use those five. - They are all the same.
- When the guests come out... - I don't have many.
(He shouts first.)
"Who is that?"
- He doesn't know their names. - He doesn't.
"A naive country guy."
He only has about five lines.
- All right. The next guest. - We have another guest?
- Who is that? - Here it is.
(Hang on. That actor is...)
(Who is the third villain actor who defies their expectations?)
- Hey! - You're seriously frightening!
He's the lawyer.
- He's such a great actor. - He plays the lawyer.
That's right.
It's Lee Sang Yeob.
(Lee Sang Yeob, a good-looking actor with unexpected charisma)
(He played an evil lawyer in "While You Were Sleeping".)
(His charisma concealed in his gentleness wins women's hearts.)
I was texting So Min last night.
She must have known who the guests would be.
She complained to me that Lee Sang Yeob will be...
the only guest who is young.
- So Min said that. - My goodness.
- I can't believe her. - Please don't mind her.
They are young.
- They aren't very old. - Seriously.
For goodness' sake.
Please step back.
My goodness. I am sorry, Haha.
What has gotten into you?
I stepped on your foot.
She took on a strange concept.
(She acts strangely in front of Sang Yeob.)
Is there someone you like?
It must be Sang Yeob.
She must like Sang Yeob.
She said, "He is handsome."
- He is the young guest. - She was shy.
You know,
just how many people are you interested in?
Seriously.
She is interested in Sang Yeob today.
(Let's see if So Min's love comes true.)
It's time to introduce the last guest of the day.
- Please come on in. - Don't get too excited.
- My goodness. - It's a woman.
- My goodness. - Kwang Soo knows her.
(The female guest in a black dress piques everyone's interest.)
My goodness.
(She is beautiful.)
- Kwang Soo knows her. - That's right.
- She played your wife in a drama. - That's right.
- Go Bo Gyeol. - Go Bo Gyeol.
(Go Bo Gyeol has an innocent charm that grabs people's attention.)
(When she plays the villain, her innocence looks give a twist.)
That's right.
- I recognize her. - Hello.
Bo Gyeol, it's nice to meet you. Please come here.
It has been a while.
Bo Gyeol,
is this your first time to appear in a variety show?
The first variety show I was in happens to be "One Night Two Days".
- Were you in "One Night Two Days"? - Yes.
- Really? - How did that happen?
It happened by chance.
I ran into the members in a bus on New Year's Day.
(She ran into Jong Min and Jun Ho on a bus.)
- We will meet again. - That's right.
(She appeared for 3 seconds.)
You will be a great actress.
Don't give up on your dream.
With whom were you on the program?
- She wasn't invited as a guest. - "One Night Two Days".
I doesn't count as a TV appearance.
It only counts if you receive the official payment.
(It only counts if you receive the official payment.)
"The official payment"!
(The technical term sounds a bit cheap.)
It only counts when you get money sent to your bank account.
- You didn't receive an invitation. - No.
Then this is your first appearance.
It only counts when there is an order from the CEO.
This is your first appearance on a variety show.
I see.
She was my wife in a drama.
- Really? - Yes.
- Really? - She is his ex-wife.
- Why did you break up in the drama? - She didn't play my ex-wife.
Have you received a personal text from Kwang Soo?
- No, I haven't. - You haven't.
I think Kwang Soo is under the wrong impression.
He said you liked him a little bit.
For goodness' sake.
What are you talking about?
You didn't, did you?
- It's a groundless rumor. - It's a groundless rumor, right?
- A groundless rumor! - I thought so.
No, no.
I never said that. He is lying.
Please don't misunderstand.
Please don't feel awkward. I never said that.
Se Chan's comment will make you uncomfortable...
throughout the shoot today.
Why did you say that during the opening?
You made me uncomfortable.
It's something you always do.
- Is it really a lie? - Yes, it is.
For today's race,
we have talented actors who play villains.
Enduring pain will give you...
- a higher chance of winning... - Endure pain?
- in The Age of Scream. - What is that?
The prize money for each round will be 1,000 dollars.
The winner will receive the money right away.
- Will we receive cash? - You will receive it right away.
- Right away? - Will we receive cash?
Let's move on with the first mission that has 1,000 dollars on the line.
- Please stand in a single line. - Why?
We can stand wherever we want as long as it's in a line?
- The order is random. - I want to change positions.
- Which end is the front? - It's a hit-or-miss situation.
Which end is the front?
The left is the front.
We can stand in a horizontal line.
Gwi Hwa, do you want to move to the front?
Sure thing.
(Clearing his throat)
I am sorry, but...
- My goodness. - Are you okay?
- I forgot. - He has phlegm.
Gwi Hwa is the phlegm fairy. He spits out phlegm very often.
- I didn't get a lot of sleep. - I see.
You didn't get a lot of sleep.
The sound wasn't grating.
- It was pleasant. - It was cute.
- Are you saying my phlegm is cute? - It was a clear sound.
He doesn't try to hide it.
How should we decide on the order?
Let's go with our instinct.
- I like it here. - Where do you want to stand?
First?
- I will stand next to Ji Hyo. - Okay. Stand here.
In that case...
- Don't do that! - What are you doing?
Then I will stand between them.
Then I will stand over here.
(This isn't what I wanted.)
That's possible.
Bo Gyeol, do you want to stand here?
- Come here. - Then I will stand over here.
Come here.
Gosh, Kwang Soo is at it again.
(He suddenly changes his attitude.)
You called her over here.
- You are at it again. - What are you talking about?
- You can move to the other side. - What are you talking about?
Hold on. In that case,
- I will stand between them. - Don't be ridiculous!
For goodness' sake.
(They nip Kwang Soo's advance in the bud.)
The position is set.
(The position is set.)
The first mission is...
Scream-inducing Confession.
You will play rock-paper-scissors with the person next to you.
The winner gets to hit the loser's forehead...
or pull their sideburns.
(Hit the loser's forehead or pull their sideburns.)
- I should have stood over here. - Oh, my goodness.
- Which way are we moving? - From right to left.
These sideburns are perfect for the game.
(He has sideburns that are perfect for the game.)
You get eliminated if you make a sound or grimace.
The last one standing receives the prize money of 1,000 dollars.
If you lose in rock-paper-scissors,
you receive the penalty...
and the direction of the attack changes.
If it's a tie,
the other member gets eliminated right away.
The other member gets eliminated if it's a tie.
Ji Hyo will begin.
How will I hit her?
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- I would rather not get hit. - Rock-paper-scissors
(The winner hits the loser. Sang Yeob is out if it's a tie.)
(Who is the winner of the first match?)
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
She won.
(Ji Hyo wins.)
Ji Hyo won.
You get to hit his forehead or pull his sideburns.
- You won't slap me on the cheek. - I will hit your forehead.
Give me your forehead.
You only need to get hit on the forehead, right?
- That's right. - You only need to get hit once.
You just need to get hit.
Sang Yeob, I will hit you hard.
- I know. - Don't change your expression.
(Ji Hyo doesn't go easy on anyone.)
- Hurry up, and hit me. - One.
Hurry up, and hit me.
Hurry up, and hit...
(I am begging you.)
(He's afraid of Ji Hyo.)
Okay. Okay.
In 1, 2.
- He made a sound. - He made a sound.
- He made a sound. - Sang Yeob is out.
- Sang Yeob is out. - Sang Yeob is out.
Not even a sigh is allowed.
- Look at So Min. - She hit him softly too.
Look at So Min.
She wanted to play the game with Sang Yeob.
However, he got eliminated right away.
(Sang Yeob, why are you there?)
She wanted to play the game with Sang Yeob.
It's So Min versus Ji Hyo.
- Sang Yeob is out. - I am sorry.
How did this...
Play rock-paper-scissors.
It can't be helped.
Please eliminate me.
Rock-paper-scissors
It's a tie.
(So Min is out.)
You are out. Go, and talk to Sang Yeob.
(Good for you.)
- Go, and talk to him. - Hello.
Talk to him.
- It worked out. - Talk to him.
- It's Seok Jin's turn. - Rock-paper-scissors
(Seok Jin loses.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(My goodness.)
- What will it be? - She is good.
- What? - What will it be?
- Forehead. - Ji Hyo is the best.
- Let's go. - She's good at rock-paper-scissors.
It's okay. I can endure the pain.
- Ji Hyo, eliminate him. - Okay.
Ji Hyo might end the game by eliminating everyone.
Don't hit my eyes.
My goodness.
Gosh, why is your hand so plump?
- Her hand is so plump. - Don't agitate her.
That's right. Receive the blow quietly.
- Okay. - He agitated her.
I should catch him from behind.
Your expression can't change either.
(It's a match between Ji Hyo's hand and Seok Jin's forehead.)
Smile.
(The sound is loud and clear.)
(My goodness.)
(He is moved by her slap.)
She did it.
She hit Seok Jin harder than Sang Yeob.
Are you insane?
- Don't discriminate. - I think...
- I forgot to stay quiet. - I think...
Gwi Hwa...
will be slapped like a member despite being a guest.
(He'll be slapped like a member.)
Just watch and see.
- Let's do this. - I'm serious.
Gwi Hwa will...
(He kneels automatically.)
Wait, we haven't played the game.
No, you haven't.
- Let's go. - You can do this.
- Gwi Hwa. - Let's go.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(It's the forehead fairy versus the phlegm fairy.)
(Ji Hyo wins again.)
- Gosh. - What is going on?
- Is this Ji Hyo's game? - What is going on?
- She is the winner. - Seriously.
This will be my facial expression.
You look like Joker.
(Joker with bad bronchial tubes)
I am sorry.
My goodness.
(Groaning)
(The phlegm fairy is knocked down.)
How many casualties must we have before this game ends?
I couldn't help but make a sound.
I am already scared.
- Seriously. - You need to beat her.
You need to beat her in rock-paper-scissors.
Ji Hyo eliminated so many people.
If you win, the direction changes.
- If you win, the direction changes. - That's right.
It's Jong Kook.
Ji Hyo is impressive.
- Let's go, Ji Hyo. - Rock-paper-scissors
(It's a rock-paper-scissors match between the two ace members.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo wins again.)
What is going on?
- I don't understand. - I planned to play scissors.
Why did I play rock?
(How impressive can Ji Hyo get?)
Is it the effect of the witch's coat?
- She is a mind reader. - She looks like a witch.
- She is getting ready. - This is a disaster.
Jong Kook won't make a sound.
If Jong Kook endures in silence,
Jong Kook will challenge Se Chan.
- He will endure in silence. - That's right.
I think he'll definitely endure it.
- Jong Kook... - I'm so curious.
(Jong Kook is good at enduring pain.)
- Gosh. - Her hand is at its best now.
- It's hard not to scream. - The sound is so scary.
Right. You can't help screaming.
(Will Ji Hyo win for the 5th time in a row?)
(Will Jong Kook succeed to the throne?)
(What will be the result?)
(Groaning)
(Jong Kook has fallen.)
(The audience is exhilarated.)
Good job. That was nice.
(I'm sorry.)
- Nice. - That was a nice one.
- It was nice. - It really hurts.
Jong Kook lost!
Jong Kook wasn't in pain. He was annoyed.
Jong Kook is angry?
He endured the pain, but not his anger.
- He's angry. - The sound was so clear.
- It was incredible. - The sound...
Ji Hyo is killing us all.
What is this?
She's killing us all.
Hold on.
It sounded like the air was compressed.
- It sounded so clear. - Exactly.
Ji Hyo is so good.
Look at all these people. You have to win rock-paper-scissors.
If Se Chan wins, the direction will change.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo's hand has warmed up. You have to win.)
(What will happen to Se Chan?)
Okay!
(Ji Hyo finally loses.)
(Ji Hyo loses after winning 6 times.)
Se Chan is very strong.
- Me? - Play rock-paper-scissors.
- I think Ji Hyo will endure it. - Se Chan is strong.
- Se Chan... - Ji Hyo, endure it.
(If Ji Hyo endures it, her next opponent is Haha.)
- Ji Hyo, endure it. - Se Chan.
- Endure it. - You can do this.
Ji Hyo, kill them all.
Here we go.
(Se Chan is not afraid of anything.)
(Will Se Chan be able to beat Ji Hyo?)
Ji Hyo!
(Slapping)
Are you okay?
(Why you little...)
- He hit her hard! - She just swore!
She swore.
(Se Chan's slap made her swear.)
- It's true. - She endured it, didn't she?
It's Ji Hyo's turn to attack Haha.
- She endured it. - She endured it.
Ji Hyo is so strong.
- She endured it. - She's amazing.
Ji Hyo, take it out on Haha.
- Yes. - But she has to win first.
(It's finally my turn.)
(Haha has been waiting for his turn quietly.)
(I'll stop Ji Hyo!)
He looks so weak.
- Let's do this. - He looks so weak.
(Ji Hyo is angry, and Haha has been waiting for this moment.)
(Who will win?)
Rock-paper-scissors
- It's a tie. - Haha lost.
Move.
(What?)
(Haha gets eliminated right away.)
- Move. - It's so disappointing.
- Move. - Get out.
- I waited so long. - It's over.
Move.
Let me get hit at least.
- No. - It's over.
- Move. - Haha.
He has pickled radish on his eyes.
Ji Hyo is really good at this.
It's Sung Tae's turn.
- It's hilarious. - She's amazing.
- Ji Hyo is amazing. - I'm looking forward to this round.
Will Ji Hyo kill us all?
- She's unbelievable. - Gosh.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(Sung Tae has been quietly watching.)
(Who will win?)
(Sung Tae wins.)
- You can hit her. - But...
- you can pull her sideburns too. - You can.
- You can do that too. - Should I just pull her sideburns?
You can pull her sideburns.
How long do you have to endure the pain?
For 5 seconds.
- For 5 seconds. - For 5 seconds?
I think she'll endure it.
Downwards?
(Ji Hyo, it's going to hurt a bit.)
- We haven't started yet. - He has to say "start" first.
(What are you doing?)
(Oh, my. I'm sorry.)
- You're mean. - What did you do?
- You should pull it upwards. - I'm sorry.
- Pull it upwards. - I'm sorry.
Wait until it starts.
Sung Tae is having fun.
- Pull it upwards. - Pull it upwards.
He looks like a villain right now.
(He's mean when playing games, too.)
Say, "start". Then we'll count.
1, 2, start.
1, 2, 3,
- Four... - Is she enduring it?
(Amazed)
(If Ji Hyo endures it, her next opponent will be Se Chan again.)
He'll pull out her hair.
(Ji Hyo endured the pain.)
- How can she do this? - She's incredible.
Ji Hyo, take it easy.
(This situation is...)
(a nightmare to someone.)
(I'm doomed.)
- You can say it hurts. - Is it Bo Gyeol's turn?
No. It's Se Chan's turn. The direction has changed.
(I knew this was coming,)
(but I didn't expect it so soon.)
(Se Chan, I've been waiting.)
- Rock-paper-scissors. - I'm doomed if I lose.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Did you get stung by a bee?
You're doomed if you lose.
Ji Hyo is furious.
- The best scenario is... - Hey.
- that it becomes a tie. - You might die if you lose.
You might die if she hits you now.
Everyone.
Look Bo Gyeol's face.
- Her eyes are wandering. - She doesn't know where to look.
(The intensity is overwhelming.)
(Culture shock)
It's her turn soon.
She must be so nervous.
(It's her first game on her first variety show.)
I'll win 1,000 dollars.
- Do it, Ji Hyo. - She's determined.
Survive, Se Chan.
- I want a tie. - Don't see it.
- Rock-paper-scissors - Rock-paper-scissors
(It has to be a tie.)
(Will Ji Hyo get her revenge, or will Se Chan escape it?)
(What will happen?)
It's a tie.
(Se Chan is eliminated.)
(Thank goodness I'm eliminated.)
Ji Hyo...
(Annoyed)
(He couldn't be happier.)
I'm so happy. Jong Kook...
He's so happy he's eliminated.
My legs are failing me.
- My legs are failing me. - Good job.
Ji Hyo is so annoyed.
You got revenge on her for me.
What will Bo Gyeol do?
It's Bo Gyeol's turn.
- Now... - It's Bo Gyeol's turn now.
Ji Hyo will take it all out...
- on her. - Exactly.
- She's going to explode. - Bo Gyeol, you just wait.
(You just wait.)
- Bo Gyeol. - My goodness.
- She should've gone first. - She looks so worried.
This is her first variety show.
- Bo Gyeol might win. - From the beginning...
She's going through hazing.
Rock-paper-scissors
(Will Bo Gyeol overcome this situation?)
(Ji Hyo wins.)
(What did I do?)
- It's so harsh. - Hit her forehead.
- Hit her forehead. - Should I hit her forehead?
- Hit her forehead. - Yes.
Just don't scream.
She shouldn't frown or scream.
Please let me watch this.
(Haha comes to the front.)
You've never done this, have you?
No.
- You've only seen it on TV, right? - Yes.
Don't cry.
Don't tell your mom.
- Don't call your manager. - Don't call your manager.
Just endure it.
Ready.
You'll probably never do a scene like this in a drama.
- Imagine you're getting a shot. - Go.
- I'll support her. - Here we go.
- Don't cry. - Don't.
- Go. - She's already crying.
She hit her.
She just hit her.
- I'm sorry. - Are you okay?
I didn't want to hurt her.
She's crying.
I'm okay.
- I heard something crack. - It was a mistake.
It's really okay.
- Bo Gyeol, you lost. - Okay.
Did she make a sound?
- Yes. - She made a sound?
I couldn't help it.
I'm sorry.
(It was a mistake.)
Unfortunately, Bo Gyeol lost.
I might beat her in rock-paper-scissors.
- Then the direction will change. - By the way,
will Ji Hyo kill us all today?
She's amazing.
You know, right?
- Of course. - It's going to hurt.
Jae Seok is good at it.
- He's strong. - He is.
Gosh.
(I've been waiting for this moment.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Ji Hyo is ready to kill them all. Jae Seok has been waiting for this.)
(Jae Seok wins.)
(It's finally time.)
It's the goblin versus the witch.
- Should you pull her sideburns? - Should you pull her sideburns?
- Should I? - Just slap her forehead.
That's your specialty.
Ji Hyo should understand.
- Sure. - Considering...
- my situation... - We could...
- On the count of three? - just stop here.
- When are you going to hit me? - We could stop here.
- On the count of 3. - On the count of 3?
- Okay. - He might hit you on two.
(He's ready.)
(Jae Seok has been feeling jealous of Ji Hyo's winning streak.)
(After a long wait,)
(this is his chance to show off his skills.)
He'll hit her on the count of one.
What?
(Screaming)
I screamed.
- She's eliminated. - I screamed.
She's eliminated.
I screamed.
- It's over now. - It must be frustrating.
It must be...
You win.
- It's over. She screamed. - What is she doing?
- She screamed. - I didn't even hit you.
She screamed.
Ji Hyo, gosh.
- She screamed. - I didn't hit her.
- She screamed. - It must be so frustrating.
(Annoyed)
She's a genius.
- I can't believe this. - She's a genius.
Are you okay?
Hold on.
- Jae Seok might become the winner. - If I win...
If it's a tie, or if Jae Seok makes him scream, he'll win.
If it's a tie, Jae Seok will be the winner.
These two...
- If he wins... - It's going to be fierce.
All right.
Rock...
Rock-paper-scissors
(This will determine the winner.)
(Who will win the chance to hit the other?)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Jae Seok wins.)
- Just endure it. - My forehead?
- Okay. - Your forehead.
Hit his forehead.
- Kwang Soo. - This is the final. I must endure.
You have to endure it.
- It's the final round. - You can win 1,000 dollars.
- It's worth it. - Of course.
If I endure this one time, I'll win 1,000 dollars.
- If he endures it... - Like this.
Okay.
Jump before you hit him.
(Culture shock)
All right.
- Let's go. - I'll make your hand hurt more.
Do it. The forehead is stronger.
Kwang Soo, you can endure it.
- Just do it once. - I'll endure it no matter what.
My goodness.
(He falls back.)
- Wait, didn't he get hit? - No.
(Isn't it considered a hit?)
Were you hit by the wind?
Kwang Soo feels pressured.
(Sighing)
Fear defeated him.
- Kwang Soo. - You can do it, Kwang Soo.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo face each other in the final round.)
(If Kwang Soo endures once, he gets a chance to attack.)
(Will he endure Jae Seok's attack?)
His expression changed.
(Surprised)
(He attacks his sideburns instead.)
(What happened?)
Is that what you did?
(While everyone was focusing on his forehead, I saw his sideburns.)
That was great.
- Good job. - I win 1,000 dollars.
- He made a surprise attack. - What?
It was a surprise attack.
His forehead was prepared, but he pulled his sideburns.
(Jae Seok wins the first mission.)
The result of the first mission is...
- Jae Seok places first. - I admit that it was good.
Congratulations.
He should thank Ji Hyo.
- It was thanks to Ji Hyo. - That's right.
He won mostly because of Ji Hyo.
She handed the victory to you.
Jae Seok will receive a prize of 1,000 dollars.
Immediately?
- Immediately? - Right now?
(Hyeong Sun hands him the prize.)
- Will he receive immediately? - I see.
- What? - What's going on?
(She collapses to the ground.)
(The assistant director...)
Hey.
(The assistant director collapses.)
- What's wrong? - Hey.
- Hey. - She's pretending.
- This is wrong. - How could you?
- What's going on? - Stay away.
- She's pretending. - What's going on?
- What? - What's happening?
- What is she doing? - What's going on?
What are you doing, Hyeong Sun?
- She's smiling. - Hyeong Sun.
- She's smiling. - What's wrong with you?
- What happened? - Hyeong Sun collapsed.
Here is today's real race.
It's called Bad Guys...
- War Against the Villain. - The villain?
There are 2 villains among you who stole 3,000 dollars...
and eliminated the assistant director.
There are two detectives who are after the villains.
There's one person who can has evidence that identifies...
- the villains. - Among us?
Can she leave first?
- Leave her alone. - Hyeong Sun.
Are you okay?
Is this why you did your hair today?
This is the crime scene.
This is it.
The member who wins the mission...
will be given hints.
If all of the villains are eliminated in the final race,
the detectives and the citizens will win.
The villains and detectives were informed about the situation.
(The villains and detectives were already informed?)
They're among us.
(They were informed.)
There are villains and detectives.
If one of the villains survives,
the villain team will win.
The winning team wins a prize of 3,000 dollars.
Wait, so does this mean this game was meaningless?
- That's right. - Give me my prize.
- I got hit. - Does he get a hint?
Jae Seok, who won the mission,
will receive two hints instead of the prize.
- That's a lot. - Please step forward.
Give me 1,000 dollars instead.
(He wants the money instead.)
It's stolen.
I already got hit.
Only you get to look at it.
(He gets a hint about the villains and the witness.)
(The hint is important for today's win.)
Come on.
(The witness is an actor.)
(Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo, So Min, Bo Gyeol, Gwi Hwa, Sung Tae, Sang Yeob)
- Gosh. - Is it a hint about the detectives?
It doesn't make any sense.
- How could you? - He got hit so much.
(The villains have appeared in movies.)
(Se Chan isn't a villain.)
(The witness is one of the actors.)
(Will they catch the villains?)
We have a lot of people today. Let me think.
- How many are we? - There are 12 of us.
That's so many.
- This is incredible. - We're like Super Junior.
By the way,
why are Gwi Hwa and Sung Tae sitting next to each other?
Pardon?
Are you conspiring in the back?
- I knew it. - They're trying to conspire.
- Don't do that. - Are you the villains?
Which role do you play today?
I'm just the audience.
(He simply watches what's going on.)
- I'm the audience. - Here's what's important.
- Kwang Soo is one of the villains. - No.
(Kwang Soo is one of the villains.)
(He's always a suspect.)
Why did you do that yesterday?
Do you remember last night?
- You mean what he said? - I don't know if it was filmed.
Last night, I asked if we started at 9am today,
and he started to say it started at 7am.
- He said his call time was 7am. - Then he stopped himself.
It's because I thought...
our call time was at 7am.
Forget it.
I think we identified one of the villains.
- What do you mean? - What about the witness?
Next mission is a group mission.
If you succeed,
everyone will receive a hint about the villains.
Here's the next mission.
It's called Subtract, Not Multiply.
(Subtract, Not Multiply)
(Subtract the 2nd number from the 1st.)
- That's easy. - For example, 3 by 6 is...
- Negative 3. - We have to subtract.
In these games, the villains will try to get it wrong.
Whoever gets it wrong is a villain.
We'll start from Ji Hyo,
So Min, Seok Jin, Jong Kook,
- Bo Gyeol and end with Sung Tae. - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is terrible at this game.
Let's start.
(Subtract, Not Multiply starts.)
- Subtract, Not Multiply - Subtract, Not Multiply
- 6 minus 5. - 5.
Wrong.
(Isn't it one?)
- That's wrong. - It's one.
I told you.
- Ji Hyo is terrible with numbers. - How could you get it wrong?
- This was too easy. - I know.
Don't I multiply and subtract the first number?
- No. - Do I simply subtract?
- Yes. - I got it.
- Ji Hyo. - I'm sorry.
I misunderstood.
(She gets another chance.)
Let's start over.
(They restart the game after understanding the rule.)
- 6 by 5. - 5.
It's one.
(She definitely said that she understood the rule.)
- Listen. - Just give up.
- What did she say? - Wait.
Let's hear why her answer was five.
- How did you calculate? - Why is it five?
I only heard the last number. I'm sorry.
She's quite stubborn.
(Instead of stubborn Ji Hyo...)
- Let's start with So Min. - So Min should start.
Come on.
- Let's go. Subtract, Not Multiply - Subtract, Not Multiply
- Subtract, Not Multiply - 3 minus 3.
- 0. - 6 minus 5.
- 1. - 2 minus 4.
- Negative 2. - 3 minus 5.
(Next is Ji Hyo, who is terrible with numbers.)
Three.
- What? - Why?
(How did she get 3?)
Why?
Why is it 3?
- Ji Hyo, you're the main guest. - She only heard three.
You're the main guest.
Are you a villain?
I hope you're a villain.
I hope so.
Please, I hope she's a villain.
Why can't I do it?
- All right. - What can we do it?
Let's start with Sung Tae and end with Ji Hyo.
- Okay. - I got it.
- This is incredible. - I got it.
Let's start with Sung Tae.
(Subtract, Not Multiply starts.)
- 7 minus 5. - 2.
- 3 minus 5. - Negative 3.
Negative three.
(How did he calculate that?)
This is impossible.
- I'm similar to Ji Hyo. - Do you understand the rule?
- Let's start over. - I'm bad with numbers.
(He gets another chance.)
Let's start with Sung Tae.
Subtract, Not Multiply
6 minus 5.
- 1. - 7 minus 5.
Negative two.
- The answer is two. - Goodness.
- Isn't it 7 minus 5? - He's a villain.
- It's 2. - It's positive 2.
Ji Hyo, you got lucky.
- Ji Hyo, you're laughing a lot. - You got lucky.
She's not the only one thanks to Gwi Hwa.
This game is usually fun, but it's really boring.
We can't continue.
- Then... - When will we get to play?
- Let's start with Bo Gyeol. - Start with Bo Gyeol.
Is this the real game?
- Yes. - It's for real.
- Let's start. - What's going on here?
There are about 8 spies.
We stop after three members.
Let's go. Subtract, Not Multiply
- Subtract, Not Multiply - Subtract, Not Multiply
- 7 minus 5. - 2.
- 2 minus 4. - Negative 2.
3 minus 5.
(Will Gwi Hwa answer correctly this time?)
Negative three.
Wait, let's hear his explanation.
Why is it three?
- Is it positive three? - Come on.
We can't play at all.
Let us play.
I haven't played either.
At this rate,
- we can't even multiply. - This is terrible.
Let's try multiplication.
- Gosh. - Seriously.
- Let's try multiplication. - Okay.
Let's do multiplication.
At this rate, we can't succeed.
- How do we play? - This is multiplication.
You multiply the numbers.
I see.
Let's multiply
(Let's multiply starts.)
- 2 by 5. - 10.
- 6 by 6. - 36.
(He stutters the answer.)
- 7 by 5. - 35.
- 2 by 4. - 8.
- 6 by 5. - 6 by 5 is 35.
(What did you say?)
I meant 30.
Jong Kook is suspicious.
- He's hiding something. - Right.
- I'm sure of it. - I meant 30.
- 6 by 5 is 30. - He can't play games on the bus.
- I'm terrible. - He's bad at games on the bus.
- I get too nervous on the bus. - He was nervous.
But 6 by 5 is 35 is too much.
- Seriously. - Let's call out our names instead.
What do you mean by call out our names?
If I say Jee, you say Seok Jin.
Yu Jae Seok.
We'll get it wrong if we play fast.
How about this game?
If you say "Choi",
- I should say "Gwi Hwa". - Okay.
Answer to "Yang" is "Se Chan". You must answer immediately.
- Answer to "Go" is "Bo Gyeol". - The next person answers.
We play all kinds of games.
Let's say each other's name.
- Let's memorize names - Let's memorize names
- Yu. - Jae Seok.
Kim.
Sung... Sung Tae.
- Kim Sung Tae? - Who is that?
- Hey! - I can't believe this.
- Hey, this is hard. - He's the villain.
- You got my name wrong. - My goodness.
We can't play a single game right.
How can't we get past the first three members?
- It's odd you'd get my name wrong. - Choi...
He's disappointed.
- Jong Kook is upset now. - Hey.
- Something is definitely wrong. - You guys own a restaurant.
His mistake is worse than my multiplication mistake.
(His mistake is worse than my multiplication mistake.)
- Here he goes again. - He got my name...
- Jong Kook said wrong answers too. - I can't do this.
Jong Kook, didn't you get all of the questions wrong today?
You'd better shut it.
I was just pointing that out.
(He backs down.)
We should start from the other side.
All right. We'll start from Ji Hyo this time.
- Let's memorize names - Let's memorize names
- Yang. - Se Chan.
- Heo. - Sung Tae.
- Yu. - Jae Seok.
Choi.
Whose family name is Choi?
(What?)
- Goodness. - Choi Gwi Hwa.
(Gwi Hwa is sitting behind him.)
- You're acting weird too. - Hold on a second.
- Hold on. - No, it's not that.
- He knows names of the whole staff. - No, it was an honest mistake.
- Okay. - Unbelievable.
- I want to play the game too. - I understand...
- why you'd suspect me. - Hang on a second.
He is definitely a villain, a detective, or a witness.
He's a villain. It's a game to get a hint about the villain.
I see. He could be a villain.
Besides, Gwi Hwa got really upset.
- Gwi Hwa. - When Jae Seok couldn't answer,
he went, "Come on!"
- Seriously. - "Come on!"
I mean he made it so obvious that he's the villain.
- I forgot for a second. - It was too obvious.
- I'm sorry, Gwi Hwa. - That's all right.
- Which game can we finish? - Gosh, Sung Tae.
- Which game can we actually play? - Let's play this one more time.
- Hey, we should just... - Why do we always...
Let's avoid using our brain. Let's just remove name tags.
Why would we try to be smart and earn hints?
Forget about the hint.
- Just turn off all the cameras. - Let's just go to our destination.
Hey, let's close this down.
- 1, 2, 3. - I won't play it anymore.
- So then... - We're done for the day.
- we won't provide the hint then. - Okay.
(The hint evaporates into the air.)
Oh, yes! We're having braised cutlassfish.
- What? - Look at the cutlassfish.
Gosh, It's braised cutlassfish.
- Look at the cutlassfish. - It looks so delicious.
I've never seen something like this.
It's Kwang Soo!
Why is that me? How?
This is just like Kwang Soo. It's so long.
(With braised cutlassfish as long as a giraffe's neck...)
- They put an entire cutlassfish? - My goodness.
The meals are divided into high, middle, low.
(What is the mission?)
I just need to avoid getting put into the low group.
(Cutlassfish, abalone seafood stew, and rice with dried laver)
The middle set is good too.
With this mission, you will get to win your meals.
The mission is National Acting Contest.
(The mission for their meal is National Acting Contest.)
You will each choose the script of a famous scene...
and a regional accent randomly.
The members who chose the same script will become partners...
and act out the scene together.
The special panel's evaluation will determine the set you will receive.
The pair with the highest mark will win the mission.
(The special panel will determine their meals.)
I hope you like my acting.
(A cameraman, an AD, and restaurant owner)
- Ji Hyo, you should go first. - Is it our turn?
(The first pair is Ji Hyo and Gwi Hwa.)
Ji Hyo and Gwi Hwa.
They didn't know what we were doing today.
(He warms up his voice.)
Hey, do something with your phlegm.
You should spit it out over there.
My gosh, the phlegm fairy is back.
The phlegm fairy.
(That sound is so not pleasant.)
He clears his throat. It's like a performance to him.
- We'll do "The Wailing"... - It's better to do it alone.
- with the standard accent of Seoul. - Really?
("The Wailing" with the standard accent)
I'm a cop. I know when people lie.
(This is the original version of the film.)
You've met him, right?
Is that what matters now? Is it?
Is it?
(This is the original version of the film.)
The concept we're going to go for is this.
- We moved to Seoul from a suburb. - That sounds great.
- We'll try to use standard Korean. - That's great.
- That sounds fun. - This is a hard thing to do.
It's a good concept.
This is quite difficult.
I'm the father, and he's the daughter.
(However, Ji Hyo is the father, and Gwi Hwa is the daughter.)
- He's the daughter? - Yes.
He's the daughter?
I guess the daughter is a heavy smoker.
Don't you think this is absurd?
Shouldn't he get treatment first?
He's planning to get treated soon.
- We'll begin now. - Okay.
("The Wailing" with standard accent of Seoul)
Hyo Jin, I'm a cop.
I know when people lie.
She is trying to speak standard Korean.
She sounds too nice.
I know when people lie.
You've met him, right? Tell me.
Hurry.
(He clears his throat.)
(The phlegm fairy returns.)
My goodness, your throat...
- He's using it as a special skill. - What is he doing?
The phlegm...
(The phlegm fairy focuses on his role.)
Is that...
(He speaks with a weird accent.)
(From which province is that accent from?)
His enunciation is amazing.
Tell me everything.
Tell me where you met him, and what you did.
Why must I tell you that?
Is he a foreigner?
- Doesn't he sound like one? - He might be.
They sound like idiots.
(I recently moved to Seoul.)
Because it's very important.
Is that what matters now?
Why are you being so stubborn?
Is that truly what matters now?
Is it? Is it?
(His throat is full of phlegm.)
Is that what matters now?
(Thanks to his phlegm, they end with a bang.)
I bet that's part of the act.
- This is unbelievable. - Gosh, he's a phlegm fairy.
Let's check their score. 1, 2, 3.
(Ji Hyo and Gwi Hwa wins abalone seafood stew.)
- My gosh. - You won the middle set.
- They won the abalones. - That's a good one.
- The abalone seafood stew... - Chan Hee...
Chan Hee isn't a generous judge.
I was next to him. It was just disgusting.
(Gwi Hwa's phlegm grosses Chan Hee out.)
He found it to be disgusting.
- We won a good one though. - Okay.
- We will act out... - Okay.
- the film, "Friend" with... - That's going to be a fun one.
- Chungcheong Province's accent. - Chungcheong Province's accent.
That's great.
- This is a good one. - Se Chan is good...
- at skits. - That's right.
He's the master of skits.
- It's like "Comedy Big League". - He's the funniest.
- What does your father do? - He's a gangster.
(This is the original version of the film.)
(The teacher takes off his watch and curses at him.)
Se Chan is the most confident when he does a skit.
- What is that? You have a hat? - Sorry?
Later on, I have to hit you with a watch.
(Later on, I have to hit you with a watch.)
You have to hit me with a watch?
I was going to improvise later.
He prepared that without giving me a heads-up.
We're going to start now. Give us the signals.
(He puts on his props for improvisation.)
Ready, action.
What just happened?
"You run into an enemy at the worst time and place."
What did you do, Dong Soo?
What does your father do?
- He... - Your father is...
Your father is busy trying to buy you shoes and pants...
and to provide for you.
How could you be ungrateful?
Hey.
What does your father do?
- He is... - Wait.
(He pinches both cheeks tightly.)
Hang on.
(He adds an additional part.)
What does your father do?
- He is a... - Right, your father...
Doesn't Kwang Soo have lines?
What does your father do?
- He is... - Listen. Your father...
is busying trying to support you.
You shouldn't be like this, Dong Soo.
It seems Kwang Soo has no lines.
Dong Soo, tell me.
- My father... He is... - You.
Your father is trying to...
(He slaps Kwang Soo with love.)
Dong Soo, go back to your seat!
(He yells at him.)
Jun Seok, you're next.
(Dong Soo exits without a word.)
Jun Seok is next? You'll be Jun Seok now?
You rascals. You know that I'm very busy.
Jun Seok.
(I'm going to say my lines this time.)
"You run into an enemy at the worst time and place."
Fancy meeting you here.
(His lines are identical.)
- He's so good. - What does your father do?
What does your father do?
- He is... - You know what? Your father...
is busy trying to provide for you.
You shouldn't go around hitting on girls.
(That's right! He does hit on girls a lot.)
What does your father do?
- He is... - What does he do? What's his job?
How could you do this to him?
Go back to your seat!
Hey, tell Kwang Soo to come up.
They don't know how scary I can be.
(He summons a student that isn't in the script.)
(Jun Seok is out, and here comes Kwang Soo.)
(Is this deja vu?)
"You run into an enemy at the worst time and place."
(I memorized the line.)
Isn't this Kwang Soo?
I haven't seen you today.
Kwang Soo, first of all,
I can't let you off the hook.
(The teacher takes off his watch.)
You need to get a good beating first.
(It's part of the script.)
What does your father do?
He runs a furniture shop.
He's the principal.
Is that so? Go back to your seat.
(He's kind to Kwang Soo all of a sudden.)
I'm sorry.
This is it.
(Se Chan and Kwang Soo put on a great scene.)
- That was hilarious. - They were good.
They were amazing.
- They were fantastic. - Let's check their score.
1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan wins a meal with braised cutlassfish.)
We got the high set.
We got the best one.
They'll get to eat the cutlassfish.
(High, Middle)
We'll go next.
- We'll do Gangwon Province accent. - Gangwon Province accent?
- I'm not familiar with the accent. - Gosh, this is...
I speak fluently with Gangwon Province accent.
- Sit down. - It seems you're younger than me.
("Nameless Gangster")
Don't drop the honorifics.
- What are you acting up for? Sit. - Don't you dare...
touch me! Where's your boss?
- Ready. - Okay.
Action.
("Nameless Gangster" with Gangwon Province accent)
Sit down.
Hang on a second.
- Hold on. - Isn't it your Won Bin impression?
- That was your impression of him. - Wait.
(Isn't that your impression of Won Bin?)
(It matches with his impression of Won Bin a month ago.)
- Hey! - That's "Autumn in My Heart".
What are you talking about?
Isn't that the Gyeongsang Province accent?
That is right.
- "Sit here." - Focus.
"Sit here." That's the accent.
- Focus. - It's the Gangwon Province accent.
- Gangwon Province. - Let's try again.
Sit here.
I'm older than you. Show some respect.
That's the Gyeongsang Province accent.
(It sounds the same as the original version.)
You should speak the Gangwon Province accent.
- Practice first. - Speak the Gangwon Province accent.
- "Show some respect." - "Stop it."
I'm older than you. Show some respect.
- Nice. - That's the Gangwon Province one.
Hey!
He hit her for real.
(Hey!)
(He hit her.)
He hit her for real.
It says, "hitting her head".
Why are you so proud?
Sit down.
Are you out of your mind?
How dare you hit me? Where's the chief?
Bring Chief Kang. Do you know who I am?
I'm...
- That accent is wrong. - Every sentence sounds the same.
In old comedy sketches,
they put "ski" at the end of every word to sound Russian.
How do you know our chief?
(Jae Seok speaks like So Min now.)
Does your chief live...
in Namcheon-dong?
(Only the last part sounds like a Gangwon Province accent.)
Say, "Yes."
- Yes. Why? - "That's right."
You know,
your chief and I...
The day before yesterday...
That's Gyeongsang Province.
We even ate together.
We went to a sauna together, too.
You know?
Hit me. Okay?
(She coughs up the red hat.)
My hat...
What are you doing?
I'm coughing up blood.
- It's blood. - Is that blood?
If we show blood, our show will be X-rated.
Does it end like this?
(Jae Seok and So Min finish up hurriedly.)
- I'm not familiar with the accent. - The accent is too difficult.
Please show us your score.
1, 2, 3.
(Jae Seok and So Min...)
(will only eat dried laver and rice.)
- So Hyun is so stingy. - What?
- You laughed. - You're so stingy.
No?
Gosh.
(After passionate acting, they're starving.)
Your meal will be ready soon.
- Wow, this is a feast. - It looks amazing.
(High, Medium, Low)
Let's eat.
I'm happy with Medium.
- Look at this. - Bo Gyeol, you're an angel.
It looks so tasty.
Look at this cutlassfish.
(Kwang Soo and Se Chan get to eat cutlassfish.)
- We can't give you any. - Fine.
All right.
The soup tastes amazing.
(Jong Kook and Bo Gyeol won High too.)
- Bo Gyeol. - Gosh.
Let us taste the cutlassfish.
Let us try.
Can I try the cutlassfish soup?
Put some effort.
Here.
So Min can do an impression of...
Joo Hyun.
- Really? - Yes .
Try.
"Gosh, you brat, give me some shrimp."
That brat.
(Kwang Soo gets mad.)
Gosh.
Hey, Kwang Soo, you punk.
So Min.
Please wait.
(So Min approaches the shrimp.)
Good job.
Gosh, you brat.
Let me taste the shrimp.
Give me some soy sauce.
- You brat. - Who is that supposed to be?
- Give me some soy sauce. - Give me soy sauce.
- Let's give them a piece. - Please.
- A piece? - Hey, give it back.
So Min.
We can give you a piece.
- Stay out of this, you brat. - What?
What?
- Stay out of this. - What?
I'm laughing...
because it's silly, not because she's good.
Sang Yeob, can you do impressions?
Please do an impression of Jang Hyuk.
Jang Hyuk?
- I can tell if he's good. - How about Jung Woo Sung?
I'll do an impression of Jang Hyuk first.
(He's aiming for a piece of cutlassfish.)
Hello, I'm Jang Hyuk.
(He sounds pretty similar.)
Eon Nyun!
(Eon Nyun!)
(It's hilarious, but it's actually pretty similar.)
It's how Hyuk calls Da Hae in "The Slave Hunters".
I'm sorry, but I didn't watch "The Slave Hunters".
- It was perfect. - Really?
- It was perfect. - Jong Kook.
- Should we talk on the phone? - Sure.
(Sang Yeob calls Jong Kook in Jang Hyuk's voice.)
- Hyuk. - Yes.
Where are you?
- It's similar. - What are you doing?
I'm shooting Running Man. What about you?
Give me some cutlassfish.
Give me a lot.
- He sounds just like him. - He does.
I admit it.
You'll get cutlassfish.
If you do one more,
- we'll give you shrimp too. - It's Jung Woo Sung.
Jung Woo Sung.
(Can Sang Yeob copy...)
(Jung Woo Sung's soft voice?)
Did you eat?
Give me some cutlassfish.
It's perfect.
He sounded just like him. It gave me goosebumps.
Oh, my.
I haven't done it in five years, but it worked.
- We'll give you some cutlassfish. - You try.
We'll give you some cutlassfish.
- Shrimp and cutlassfish. - "Look at these bullets."
(Sang Yeob wins shrimp and cutlassfish.)
Look at these bullets.
Two shots in Vladivostok...
- Is that Joo Hyun? - Two bullets...
- So Min. - What's that?
It's Lee Jung Jae.
Try. You're doing great.
There are two bullets.
"Two calves"? What are you saying?
What?
"There are two bullets."
(It's supposed to be...)
(It's Lee Jung Jae's line in "Assassination",)
("There are two holes.")
- So Min. - "There are two bullets."
"Two calves"?
"Two bullets".
Gwi Hwa, can you do something?
I can.
- He's been waiting. - This is Bae Chul Soo.
(He clears his throat.)
Hello. I'm Bae Chul Soo.
Michael Jackson...
and Mariah Carey's song that has been attracting...
Gwi Hwa, just drink your soup.
(Gwi Hwa, just drink your soup.)
(Okay. I will.)
Gwi Hwa.
Just drink your soup.
(This soup tastes great.)
Can I try again for Gwi Hwa?
Sure.
I'll do two. I'll start with Lee Sun Gyun.
That sounds great.
Sun Gyun calls me,
and I pick up. "Hello."
"Where are you, you brat?"
(He's a human, copying machine.)
That sounds real.
"Where are you?" "Give Ji Hyo some food."
"Give her some soy sauce."
Two spaghetti alle vongole.
Stop it.
Be quiet. Just eat your shrimp.
- Two spaghetti alle vongole. - Eat your shrimp.
Bo Gyeol, can you do something?
I can copy Shimarisu-kun.
- What? - What?
- "Bonobono". - "Bonobono".
Oh, "Bonobono".
- I'm sure many people know it. - I know it.
"Shimarisu-kun..."
Amazing. Take this.
(Amazing. Take this.)
It was perfect. It's insane.
I can't help it.
Take everything.
It was insane.
- "Hello." - It was perfect.
"Hello."
(Hello)
"I'm Bae Chul Soo."
"Bae Chul Soo's Music Camp".
(Let me try.)
- Hey. - Go back.
- That's not Bae Chul Soo. - Come back here.
- "Bae Chul Soo's Music Camp". - Be quiet.
- Stay still. - You ruined it.
- Don't do anything. - Give me some cutlassfish.
Stop it. Gosh.
"Yong Nyeo."
Stop it. Just eat.
(Stop it.)
- Can I try? - Try what?
There's this app that's very popular.
- You can lip sync to movies. - I know that app.
- Right. - Let me try.
- Let me try. - It's so cute.
Kwang Soo and I will try.
Even IU and Suzy tried it.
- It's so popular. - Right.
(They want to show off their acting skills.)
This one.
Don't start yet.
- Start. - We should look at the screen.
Hey, do you want to have ramyeon at my place?
What? Ramyeon?
(Their acting is being recorded.)
- Sure. - He's good.
What are you thinking about?
(Shy)
(Se Chan slaps Kwang Soo.)
What was that?
- Good. - Good.
What?
Isn't Kwang Soo older? He's been slapped so many times.
(Thanks, Kwang Soo,)
(for getting slapped so many times.)
(Slap)
Should I be the girl?
Okay. You'll be the girl.
- You'll be the girl. - Okay.
All right.
Do you want to have ramyeon at my place?
Jae Seok is good.
What? Ramyeon?
Sure.
She's an actress.
Which ramyeon do you like?
- What? - What are you thinking about?
You can only see half of So Min's face.
(You can only see Jae Seok's face.)
I mean... You can only see...
- He has to be in the center. - You can only see me.
(How does their video look?)
(Jae Seok is in the center, and you can only see So Min's eyes.)
All you see is my eye.
Let me explain the rules of Sing with Your Body.
What's the title?
- "Pain". - "Thorn".
"Thorn" by Buzz.
(They have to describe the lyrics with their bodies.)
You're a criminal, aren't you?
You'll get only one hint about the villains.
(Everyone is given a hint about the villains.)
The villains are both men.
(The villains are both men.)
Both of them are male?
(Is it Jae Seok and Gwi Hwa?)
Are these two the villains?
You keep suspecting me.
You suspect that I'm a villain.
(The final race at Tanhyeon Center)
Here's the final mission to identify the villains.
It's called I Saw the Villains.
(I Saw the Villains)
"I Saw the Villains"?
(I Saw the Villains?)
In this building,
there are hints related to the villains, detectives, and witness.
There are hints.
Based on the hints that you find,
point out the member whom you suspect to be a villain...
at 2 trials that take place once every 30 minutes.
That is how you eliminate them.
(Arrest the villains at the trial.)
If you eliminate both villains,
the detectives and the civilians win.
If one of the villains survives,
the villains win.
The winning team receives a prize of 3,000 dollars.
(The prize is 3,000 dollars.)
The detectives may eliminate the villains,
and the villains may eliminate the witness by tearing off the name tag.
If a detective eliminates the witness by mistake,
the civilians lose immediately.
(The civilians lose immediately.)
(Detectives must protect the witness.)
- It's dangerous. - Be careful, Detective.
Be careful.
If the villains eliminate civilians instead,
a hint related to him will be revealed.
If a villain eliminates a detective,
the villain's name will be revealed.
Then we can catch him.
The witness must obtain a hint about the villains...
and attend the trial.
The witness will show evidence.
(The witness must find evidence.)
If the witness is eliminated, the evidence won't be available.
(Then the villains win.)
Please go to your starting point.
- Let's get it. - Okay.
(Which team will win?)
Where are you going?
Why, Mr. Villain?
Why is everyone suspecting me as a villain?
- Who do you think it is? - What?
I made up my mind.
(Se Chan has a conclusion.)
- The villain is... - One of them is Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook has been suspicious.)
- Pardon? - Jong Kook.
- He's definitely it. - There's Gwi Hwa.
(He's startled.)
Why are you eavesdropping?
Gwi Hwa, you're a villain.
I'm a detective.
Me too.
What are you talking about?
Detectives received the mission this morning.
- Which mission? - Mission for detectives.
I got it too.
What do you mean? I received it.
Where did you get it?
- It was in Ilsan. - Where in Ilsan?
- In the parking lot. - You're lying.
You might hit me.
(He's about to lose his temper.)
- You might hit me. - Where did you get it?
- Pardon? - Where did you get the mission?
(He takes off his jacket.)
- Put it back on. - Why are you lying?
I'm really a detective.
(Is it true or false?)
- Are you... - I can't believe it.
Where did you get the mission?
Let's say it at the same time.
- I'll be honest. - Me too.
- Let's say it. - In 1, 2, 3.
- At a coffee shop. - Shop.
(Which shop?)
(Is he really a detective?)
I'm really a detective.
I'll keep my eye on you.
- It must be true. - Yes.
(Is Gwi Hwa a detective?)
- At a coffee shop? - Let's verify.
Once we find a hint...
Okay, I hope you find it.
- Okay. - He must be a detective.
Sung Tae is a detective.
(They must identify who is who.)
And...
Jae Seok is a villain.
I'm not sure about what Sang Yeob is.
Gwi Hwa...
(He guesses the villains.)
Kwang Soo?
They keep saying that they're detectives.
It seems suspicious.
They might be creating a confusion.
(Nervous)
The countdown starts.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Race starts.
Let's find the hints.
(The race starts.)
Where are the hints?
Hints.
Could it be here?
(The female members aren't the villains.)
I found a hint in a place like this.
(Where are the hints?)
(So Min finds a hint.)
(Hint about Detective A)
"Detective A is over 180cm tall."
(Sung Tae, Gwi Hwa, Sang Yeob, or Kwang Soo)
Detective A?
Here it is.
(Sung Tae finds a hint.)
"Detective A is a guest"?
("Detective A is a guest"?)
(Sung Tae, Gwi Hwa, Sang Yeob, or Bo Gyeol)
"Detective A is a guest."
(When two hints are combined,)
(Detective A is either Gwi Hwa, Sung Tae, or Sang Yeob.)
(The hints narrow down the choices.)
- The prize is 3,000 dollars. - Yes.
If the villains win, they split the prize.
(Kwang Soo finds a hint.)
Let's see it together.
No, you could be a villain.
- What? - Let me look first.
Come on, stop playing.
"Stop playing"?
- Let's read it together. - Stay away.
Fine, but how can you suspect me?
Let's read it together.
(The hint that Kwang Soo finds...)
(is related to the villains.)
(Villain B's name has a J.)
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, or So Min)
- "Villain B..." - You aren't one of them.
"Has a J."
(Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo or So Min)
- These two aren't it. - No.
It can't be Seok Jin. It's either Jae Seok or Jong Kook.
(Suspects are Jae Seok, Seok Jin, or Jong Kook.)
- What is it? - What?
What?
- I'm scared of you. - Me? Why all of a sudden?
Who do you think it is?
(They stay away from Jong Kook.)
It could be Jae Seok or Gwi Hwa.
(They keep a distance.)
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
Can you only eliminate the witness?
- What? - Can you eliminate the witness?
Why would I?
(They suspect him.)
- Why would I? - Or protect the witness?
- Why would I? - It's nothing.
Did you find a hint about me?
- We found a hint. - We did.
What did it say?
- It's unfair. - In the villain's name,
there's a J.
There are so many names with that letter.
- There are only three. - But...
- It's not certain. - Hello, Detective.
(A detective-like person arrives.)
- Detective. - Yes?
- Is he a detective? - You can eliminate him.
Eliminate him.
(If a detective eliminates the witness, the civilians lose.)
Why do you suspect me to be a villain?
(If a detective eliminates the witness, civilians lose.)
Be careful, Jong Kook.
Will you tear off his name tag?
What? You're a detective.
You must be certain...
- to eliminate someone. - Right.
What happens if he's a civilian?
- Why do you suspect me? - Don't we lose?
(It's hard to make a move.)
Let's split for now.
- Okay. - Let's go.
Whom do you suspect, Kwang Soo?
(Is Gwi Hwa a detective and Jong Kook a villain?)
Which floor are you going, Gwi Hwa?
- Which floor? - Let's go upstairs.
- Shall we? - Okay.
Are you going upstairs?
(Are they staying together?)
Can a villain eliminate a detective?
- What? - That's not possible, right?
- That's not possible. - No.
- Then you may go. - Gwi Hwa.
(Kwang Soo feels relieved.)
- No. - Wait for me.
What's wrong with you?
- I'm trying to find out. - What's wrong with you?
There are many with Js in their names.
- He's calling for trouble. - Gwi Hwa.
I'll tell you the hint that I found.
You should be careful of him for now.
- Okay. - Goodness.
Salute, Detective.
(He expresses his loyalty.)
(Trust me.)
See you.
(He walks away without realizing what he's done.)
The villains are male, right?
- They're men. - Right.
- The villains are men. - Okay.
(He decides to share the hint with them.)
I'm being very generous.
- We have one too. - Us too.
- We'll help you. - Do you trust me?
- Of course. - We do.
I'll identify myself to you.
Are you a witness?
- Do you have a badge? - Please trust me.
(Is he revealing his identity?)
(Haha's identity is...)
(A private investigator)
(My goodness)
- Come on. - I'm a private investigator.
Show us the hint now.
- Show us the hint. - Okay.
- Show me yours at the same time. - Okay.
Detective A is over 180cm tall.
Detective A's name doesn't end with consonants.
(Detective A's name doesn't end with consonants.)
(When these three hints are combined,)
(it's narrowed down to one person.)
Hey, the detective has to be Gwi Hwa.
For sure. He's Detective A.
(Gwi Hwa is Detective A.)
(Gwi Hwa is a homicide detective.)
I'm a detective.
(Earlier today)
Today's special is Bad Guys: War against the Villains.
The two of you are detectives who can arrest the villains.
I'm a detective?
(Me?)
(That's how he became a Running Man detective overnight.)
(He returns to his office for a moment.)
Excuse me.
Please stay.
You need to cover me.
(He's undercover right now.)
(I got you.)
(No, don't cover the camera.)
No.
I'll pretend like I'm asking you a question.
(He gives up going undercover.)
(Good luck, Detective.)
(He looks around.)
They usually hide something here.
(There must be a hint here.)
(There's no hint,)
(but Jong Kook is here.)
What are you doing?
(Peekaboo)
- Sit down. - I'm sorry.
No, have a seat.
- Sit down. I know. - Jong Kook.
Sit.
(Is Jong Kook a villain?)
- I'm not the witness. - You are.
(He's certain.)
(Is Jong Kook a villain who's looking for a witness?)
Here it is. Nobody's been here yet.
(Seok Jin finds a hint.)
"Villain B is not married."
(This is an additional hint about Villain B.)
(Both of these hints...)
(point to Jong Kook.)
(Kim Jong Kook)
I have to...
(They're annoying.)
I have to eliminate the witness.
(He needs to get rid of them.)
I think Kwang Soo is the witness.
I have a feeling.
I'm not the witness.
You are.
(I have to eliminate you.)
(What's wrong with him?)
This is like a scene from a film.
(It's a thriller.)
- Will I die? - What?
(I can't even do anything.)
All right.
(If he is the witness, the villains win, and the race is over.)
I'm really not...
(This is not fair.)
(Before he gets eliminated...)
Gwi Hwa!
(Detective Choi is here.)
- Gwi Hwa! - Hey.
Who's this?
(Save me, Detective!)
(Hold onto him.)
- Hold onto him. - Rip it!
(Kwang Soo has Jong Kook's hands tied.)
(He tries to oppress the brutal villain.)
- Rip it! - Hold onto him.
(Ripping)
(They eliminate Jong Kook.)
- Rip it! - Hold onto him.
- I got him. - You got him.
- You got him. - Kwang Soo.
I almost got eliminated.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Detective Choi. - Detective?
- Detective Choi. - Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
- All right. - He grabbed my name tag.
We got him. He's arrested.
How did you know he was a villain?
I have instincts.
I was following him around.
(Jong Kook kept tailing Kwang Soo.)
He kept on following Kwang Soo.
(Upset)
- Gosh. - You got caught here.
- That was so close. - What a timing.
You're like an anaconda.
I didn't know it was you.
(Villains versus detectives)
Villain Kim Jong Kook is out.
(How will this race end?)
Jong Kook is out?
My gosh.
(They're not shocked that he was a villain,)
(but that he's out.)
(They have to find Villain A now.)
We have to find Villain A.
My head is about to explode.
(He's about to cry.)
(He's anxious.)
Why does nobody...
have any hints about the witness?
We have to know the witness.
Sang Yeob.
It's too obvious though...
if it's him.
(Is Sang Yeob looking for the witness?)
It can't be anybody else.
Is it Se Chan?
(She bumps into somebody while thinking about the villains.)
- I'm here to find hints. Why? - Come.
(What?)
(She was gone with a cry.)
Civilian Jeon So Min is out.
What?
- What did he say? - What did he say?
Here's a hint...
- about Villain A. - Civilian Jeon So Min is out?
(An innocent civilian is out, so here's a hint about Villain A.)
Villain A got an award as a rookie.
(Villain A got an award as a rookie.)
A trial is starting soon.
- Please head to court. - Let's go.
I don't know who it is.
(Round 1 finishes as So Min gets eliminated.)
(1st trial begins.)
We'll start with the first trial.
The person with the majority of votes will be on trial.
If that person is a villain,
the race is over.
If not, we'll move ahead to the next round.
If you don't catch the villain in the second trial as well,
even if all of you are alive,
the civilians lose.
(If they can't catch the villain by the 2nd trial,)
(the civilians lose.)
As a detective, let me say something.
(He talks out of nowhere.)
- How are you the detective? - All right.
We don't know if you're the detective yet.
I know Gwi Hwa is,
but I don't know about you.
When they were eliminating Jong Kook,
Gwi Hwa took the lead.
But Jae Seok got scared, so he stayed behind.
- Why would a detective do that? - You're wrong.
You're mistaken.
He's not a villain,
because we both got the mission this morning.
(This is what the detective says.)
So is he...
- They're both detectives. - Is he a detective?
Is he?
Right on.
Right on. Hey.
You should have told them earlier.
(They both got the mission, so he is a detective.)
The two of you are detectives who can arrest the villains.
I'm a detective?
(Like Gwi Hwa said, Jae Seok is also a detective.)
At the final race, if a villain survives,
- the villains win. - My gosh.
- You know what he means, right? - I'm not sure.
(I'm actually not sure.)
(These two are a team.)
(Cowardly Detective Yu makes a comment.)
The hint I have says that...
they are film actors...
and that they won a Rookie of the Year award.
We know these hints.
- It comes down to two people. - Who?
Sang Yeob and Kwang Soo.
(The suspects are Sang Yeob and Kwang Soo.)
He got an award?
- He... - Hold on.
Rookie of the Year award?
- He did. - Really?
- You got one? - Yes.
(Both of them got the Rookie of the Year award.)
It didn't even occur to me.
Have you made up your minds?
- Can I have one person... - Hold on.
Can we hear the closing arguments?
I want to hear from Kwang Soo...
and Sang Yeob who got the award.
It's the closing arguments.
- I... - One at a time. Go, Kwang Soo.
I think this is a coincidence.
I'll just say one thing.
The scene.
Detective Choi and Detective Yu.
You both saw it. They are my witnesses.
When I was about to get eliminated,
- the detectives saved me. - That's right.
- Is that true? - Yes.
- You scared me. What's wrong? - Hold on.
(Did he just think of something?)
What's wrong?
Hold on.
- What? - I was after Jong Kook.
And?
And then I lost him because he went into a room.
Then I met those two. What I saw was...
Jong Kook was making Kwang Soo sit...
and was about to rip his name tag.
(Detective Choi saw Jong Kook about to eliminate Kwang Soo.)
They could have been acting.
- That's what I'm saying. - You think they were acting?
Detective Choi, they could have waited for you.
- That's right. - Because...
Jong Kook was trying to protect Kwang Soo.
He wanted to save Kwang Soo.
Jong Kook knew he couldn't win.
- That's it. - That's it.
He got himself out.
- That's right. - This is no joke.
- That's not... - Gwi Hwa guessed right.
- That's possible. - He was laughing...
- for some reason. - That's also possible.
You said it yesterday. Who was on standby at 7am?
- Right. - That was...
(Is Kwang Soo really Villain A?)
Let's hear Sang Yeob's closing argument.
(This is his closing argument.)
I don't have much to say,
but I cooperated with Haha.
And during that time, it was just the two of us.
If I was the villain, I would have ripped his name tag.
But I didn't.
He's sitting right before us.
- If Haha is the detective... - No.
If Haha is the witness,
Sang Yeob could have eliminated him as the villain.
He has no reason to eliminate civilians or detectives.
So that's how this will go.
It's time to decide.
You have no more time.
Let's have one of them go on trial.
(It's time to pick one person.)
Who do you think it is, Sung Tae?
Sang Yeob.
- That's right. - Sang Yeob?
What about you, Detective Choi?
I'm certain it's Kwang Soo.
- You saw me. - What about...
I think he was acting.
- What about you, Se Chan? - Is it Kwang Soo?
Are you certain, Detective Choi?
- Yes. - Really?
Come to think of it, what I saw looked too artificial.
Jong Kook grabbed my name tag...
and twisted my arm when Gwi Hwa came in. He didn't know what to do.
- It's acting. - Yes.
- So it's acting. - "Yes"?
- Did you just say, "Yes"? - No, I mean...
(Did you just say, "Yes"?)
(That's what you just said.)
- No, this is not acting. - It is.
He was acting, not me.
Jong Kook was acting by himself.
- Se Chan. - I choose Kwang Soo.
- Listen to me. - Your remark wasn't convincing.
- You got it right. - Your closing argument.
- What about Ji Hyo? - You said you were acting.
I thought it was Sang Yeob,
but after hearing from Kwang Soo, I think it's him.
I've been arguing it's Kwang Soo all this time.
This doesn't make sense. Bo Gyeol,
think about me today.
- It's Sang Yeob. - Right.
What about you, Haha?
- Sang Yeob. - What?
Okay, I pick Sang Yeob.
Hold on. It's 4 to 3. Jae Seok has the final say.
It's up to Jae Seok.
Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok gets to decide who goes on trial.)
- Detective Yu, may I say something? - Yes.
The scene I witnessed was awkward.
- I'm thinking about that too. - I have an instinct.
I didn't see it myself,
so I have to rely on Detective Choi's words.
I heard what he said.
I'm an expert.
He grabbed my name tag.
Okay, I'll follow Detective Choi's...
Hold on. Se Chan.
- Then... - You were with me all day.
It's Kwang Soo.
It's 5 to 3. Kwang Soo, please stand on the platform.
- It was a decisive moment. - It's okay, Kwang Soo.
It's Kwang Soo.
(It's the 1st judgment.)
I trusted you, detectives.
(How could you do this?)
I tried my best today.
(I was loyal.)
- Are you certain? - He was acting.
In 1, 2...
(The majority chose Kwang Soo.)
(What is his identity?)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo is...)
(a civilian.)
He's a civilian?
(He's disappointed.)
Why were you acting like that?
- Kwang Soo. - I got goosebumps.
I'm so sorry.
- Come on. - He's just a civilian.
I'm so sad you picked me.
(If Kwang Soo is not the villain...)
It's you then.
(Is it Sang Yeob?)
(1st trial comes to an end with a mystery.)
You can go now. In 30 minutes, we'll hold the last trial.
If you can't catch the villain, it's over.
(The last trial is in 30 minutes. The race resumes.)
- Detective Choi? - Yes.
I'll grab Sang Yeob. You can eliminate him.
(Everybody is after Sang Yeob.)
- Let's eliminate him and end this. - Okay.
(If Sang Yeob is the remaining villain, the race will be over.)
It's Sang Yeob.
From the hints we have,
it was Kwang Soo or Sang Yeob.
I told you to eliminate him if he's acting weird.
I never saw him.
Let's eliminate him.
- We have to eliminate him first. - Haven't you seen Sang Yeob?
No, I haven't.
(The detectives are searching now.)
(Somebody is in a hurry.)
Where are you going?
The ladies are not villains.
- No. - Right?
- I'm not a villain. - Right. The ladies are not.
Where are you going?
I'm a witness.
(He looks around.)
- Stop lying. - I'm serious.
So I have to find it.
If you see Bo Gyeol or Gwi Hwa,
- tell them. - All right.
(Sung Tae says he's a witness.)
(These detectives are after Sang Yeob.)
- Go there. I'll go this way. - Okay.
(Where are you, Sang Yeob?)
(What?)
(He finds Sang Yeob.)
What are you doing?
This...
Sang Yeob.
- Yes, Gwi Hwa. - Where is he?
Where is Sung Tae?
- Sung Tae? - Yes.
I thought you came to catch me.
- No, it's not me. - Grab him.
(Get Sang Yeob.)
It's really not me.
(Sang Yeob finally gets caught.)
(If he's the villain, this race will be over.)
It's really not me.
I'm a civilian.
(Sang Yeob is a civilian?)
What?
- Sang Yeob. - Yes.
- He's a civilian? - Kwang Soo...
- It's either you or him. - Jae Seok.
Somebody is lying.
Sung Tae.
- What's this? - What is this?
What?
- What's this? - We got it.
It's Sang Yeob.
(Villain A has three syllables in their name.)
Where were you?
I was searching.
What if you get caught by Sang Yeob?
It's okay. I'm confident.
(He says something odd.)
(Sung Tae is so relaxed.)
- Hold on. - It could be him.
Sung Tae.
It's Sung Tae.
Why didn't we think about that?
The villain could have lied.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, Sang Yeob. - I am...
- going home. - I'm sorry.
- I'm really sorry. - It's okay.
I'm so sorry, Sang Yeob.
- It's Sung Tae. - Right.
It's Sung Tae. Wait.
Wait. It's Sung Tae.
- Oh, gosh. - Hey.
(The puzzle come together.)
- We have to catch Sung Tae. - It's Sung Tae.
- It's him. - He said he was the witness, right?
He's the culprit.
- Sung Tae. - Yes?
- Where are you going? - First floor.
You have to be careful, Sung Tae.
- You can't go around by yourself. - Okay?
- Don't go around by yourself. - Don't do that.
- We have to protect the witness. - Let's go.
We're his bodyguards.
He looks so naive.
You can't survive in this world like that, Sung Tae.
Sung Tae tricked us all.
The witness won't say it's him.
- Exactly. - Right?
- I... - But...
But Se Chan got tricked.
Hey, Sung Tae.
- Yes? - Did you find it?
No, not yet.
- Not yet? - Yes.
(You can't because you're not the witness.)
Have you seen Sang Yeob?
(I have a bad feeling.)
(Sung Tae feels threatened and runs away. Jae Seok chases him.)
Catch him!
- What's going on? - What?
(Somebody is attacking our witness.)
- Help me! - What? Who is it?
Help me!
- What is it? - Catch him.
- He's the villain. - I'm not!
- He is. He's the villain. - Wait.
He got it wrong.
- Is he the villain? - He is.
Sung Tae...
Then...
Then we'll see during trial.
- Come here. - No, he's the witness.
- He's the witness. - I'm not it!
- He's the witness. - He's not!
- He is. - He's the villain!
- He was lying. - Let go.
(If the witness gets eliminated, the villains win.)
- He's the villain. - He's not.
He is.
We'll see you during trial.
- This is driving me nuts. - Go.
- He's the witness. - This is driving me nuts.
We're going to protect our witness.
(Is Sung Tae the witness or the villain? Who's right?)
Five minutes before the race ends.
I think it is Sung Tae.
Have you met Sung Tae?
It was chaotic.
Who and who?
Sung Tae is here.
(Catch Sung Tae!)
Sung Tae.
Goodness.
Come here.
Come here first.
- Jae Seok... - Go in.
I have to find the box.
(I have to find the evidence.)
(Only the witness can open the evidence box.)
Sung Tae, I think it was in the dressing room.
- What was? - The box.
(How do you know, Haha?)
I have to do something as the private investigator.
(Haha was anxiously searching for hints.)
(He found the evidence box...)
It's here.
(in the dressing room.)
- It's the decisive evidence. - Let's go up.
Come out. Let's check together.
- Together. - It's this.
(Sung Tae and Detective Choi collect the evidence box.)
We don't have much time. We have two minutes.
(They have only 2 minutes until the final trial.)
The witness should open this.
(If you're the witness, please open this box.)
(Is Sung Tae really the witness?)
Are you the witness? You are.
You're the only witness who can find the decisive evidence...
about the villains and reveal it.
(Sung Tae was the witness.)
This key...
can open the evidence box.
(It proves that he's the witness.)
(This key will reveal the truth.)
(He opens the box.)
I have a feeling.
- Really? - Yes.
(The box finally opens.)
"One of the..."
(What is the decisive hint...)
(inside the box?)
The trial is starting soon.
Please gather in court.
I think...
- In the end... - Did you find it, Sung Tae?
I did.
(He truly was the witness.)
- I'm sorry, Sung Tae. - Did you find it?
I'm sorry. I was mistaken.
- He's the witness. - He really is?
I was mistaken, Sung Tae.
I'm sorry.
I was mistaken. It wasn't Sang Yeob.
The final trial will begin.
(The final trial begins.)
Witness, did you find the hint?
Yes.
(He will reveal what's inside the box.)
Good job.
(What's the truth inside this box?)
I think...
we had our stereotypes.
(I think we had our stereotypes.)
"One of the villains..."
(One of the villains...)
"is a detective."
(One of the villains is a detective.)
"One of the villains is a detective."
(Either Gwi Hwa or Jae Seok is a villain.)
This person is like Lee Jung Jae in "New World".
(Everyone has a mental breakdown.)
Lee Jung Jae in "New World".
- May I speak? - I...
- May I speak? - Please go ahead.
Which detective tried to kill the witness?
Yu Jae Seok.
(Yu Jae Seok.)
(5 minutes before)
(Detective Yu tried to eliminate Sung Tae, the witness.)
(Only the villain aims to silence the witness.)
(Is Detective Yu the villain?)
Everyone.
The villain is an actor. I am not an actor.
Excuse me. There is something I want to ask.
- Who saw that hint? - I did.
We only heard from Jae Seok that the villain is an actor.
- Has anyone else read the hint? - No one has read it.
- No one has read it. - We believed his words.
- That's why we doubted the actors. - Who framed...
Kwang Soo and Sang Yeob in the beginning?
- You need to keep that in mind. - Isn't it strange that...
every piece of the puzzle is working...
- in Gwi Hwa's favor? - Then explain yourself.
I have been set up.
- I have been set up - No.
Everyone.
I almost made a big mistake today.
There is another thing.
- Gwi Hwa eliminated Jong Kook. - Yes.
I asked Gwi Hwa...
how he knew that Jong Kook was a villain.
He said that he trailed him on a hunch.
(While everyone else was focused on finding the hints,)
(Detective Choi arrested a villain right away.)
You arrested him.
(How did you know that Jong Kook was a villain?)
(I had a hunch.)
I trailed Jong Kook.
(Did he catch Jong Kook on his hunch alone?)
What do you think it means?
It was in the scenario that was written...
- by the two villains. - That's right.
"If I eliminate you, people will believe me."
"When everything ends,"
"let's split the money." Isn't that what happened?
Although I am a detective like him,
I felt chills down my spine toward the end.
I believed him.
When he began to chase after someone...
We didn't know it was Jong Kook. When we heard that...
the villain's name had a J...
(Clearing his throat)
(The phlegm fairy appears.)
My goodness.
He is the phlegm fairy.
Go to the restroom.
- Go to the restroom. - I am sorry.
If you are done, I would like to plead.
(Detective Choi counterattacks.)
Firstly, let's go over what happened the most recently.
The decisive hint.
(The box that contains the decisive hint)
If I were a villain...
The three of us opened the box and read the hint together.
(He read the hint with Sung Tae and Haha.)
I could have eliminated them before opening the box.
That's right.
Then I would have won the race.
I could have eliminated all the members...
by meeting them one by one.
- As the villain? - Right.
There is something I want to add.
(Additionally)
Who chased after you to eliminate you?
(He stresses that Jae Seok tried to eliminate the witness.)
Have I ever chased after you to eliminate you?
- So... - I haven't.
(The two detectives' defenses end.)
We won't have an open vote. If you write a name and turn it in,
we will give the chosen one the final judgment.
(The detective with more votes receives the final judgment.)
(No one knows how this game of truth will end.)
(The 8 members finish voting.)
(Who has more votes?)
There is a total of eight votes.
The result is 5 to 3.
(The result is 5 to 3.)
It's 5 to 3.
The person who received five votes...
(Who is the chosen one for the final judgment?)
(Is it Detective Yu who aimed for the witness?)
(Is it Detective Choi who caught Jong Kook on a hunch?)
(Which detective is the chosen one...)
(for the final judgment...)
(with five votes?)
Yu Jae Seok, please come to the stand.
- All right! - You fools!
(Yu Jae Seok, please come to the stand.)
- You fools! - Please come to the stand.
- Justice wins. - You are fools.
- Seriously. - It's Gwi Hwa!
I should have eliminated him.
(I am so upset.)
(It's the final judgment.)
If Yu Jae Seok is the villain, the civilians and witness...
will win.
If he isn't the villain,
the villains win.
His identity will be revealed.
One.
(The witness checks his identity.)
Two.
(What is...)
Three.
(Detective Yu's...)
(identity?)
(Ripping)
I told you!
(Yu Jae Seok was a detective.)
(The civilians, witness, and detectives lose.)
I told you!
(The villains win.)
For goodness' sake.
I told you.
- You fools! - I told you.
I knew something was off.
You are a villain who stole the prize money of 3,000 dollars.
However, there is another villain who will help you.
(Here is your partner.)
My goodness.
- Hello. - Hello.
Choi Gwi Hwa...
is also one of the detectives.
What do you mean? I am a villain and a detective?
- That's right. - You know,
he looks like both a villain and a detective.
(That's how the two villains joined forces.)
Salute!
(As soon as the final race started...)
(and they were left alone...)
Listen to me. There is something you must keep in mind.
A lot of the hints point to me.
If I am in danger of getting eliminated,
you must rip off my name tag.
You must rip off my name tag.
(They agree to make Gwi Hwa gain trust.)
(Later on)
All right.
I am not a witness.
(He pretended to hunt Kwang Soo.)
What is going on?
Gwi Hwa! Gwi Hwa!
Hold onto him.
- Rip it! - Hold onto him.
- I got him. - He almost got me!
He almost got me!
My goodness.
- Come here for a second. - Are you alone?
- Have you met Jae Seok? - What?
- Have you met Jae Seok? - No.
- Why do you ask? - It's nothing.
(Then Gwi Hwa could hunt without anyone suspecting him.)
No way...
I am sorry.
(A wonderful collaboration between the phlegm fairy and ace member)
Thus, the prize money of 3,000 dollars...
go to the villains.
(The villains receive the prize money of 3,000 dollars.)
(It's the age of the villains.)
I struggled a lot.
I worried a lot.
(Sad)
Gwi Hwa, take this.
(Gwi Hwa receives the donation card of 3,000 dollars.)
Donate the money.
The money goes to donation under your name.
(They donate under the villains' names.)
This is the twist.
- His face turned dark. - The money goes to donation.
Congratulations, Gwi Hwa.
The four guests,
Sang Yeob, Sung Tae, Gwi Hwa,
and Bo Gyeol deserve a round of applause.
Thank you.