(This is Running Man's global project of 2017.)
(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by bloggers)
(Shark cage, USA)
(Cage of Death, Australia)
(Fly Toledo, Spain)
(Active volcano in Mount Bromo and Mount Ijen, Indonesia)
(Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear, Japan)
(Nevis Swing, New Zealand)
(Insano water slide, Brazil)
(Haha and Se Chan are on the threshold of these dangerous trips.)
(And)
(Last week, they played Running Marble for their dangerous trip.)
(Before they knew it, their one-day trip around the world began.)
(They had no plans or preparations and went to the airport with a bag.)
(They arrived at the airport at 7:30am. Is it really happening?)
(3 hours later)
(So Min's team arrived in Osaka.)
(Ji Hyo's team arrived in Taipei.)
(Do Yeon's team arrived in Jeju Island.)
(However)
(They can't see further than their nose. Can they finish the mission?)
(Team Taipei has to complete eating five dishes.)
(Team Osaka has to find a bathhouse run by someone named Suzuki.)
(In the center of Osaka, they are looking for Suzuki.)
Where did So Min go? Where is So Min?
(In the center of Osaka, they are screaming So Min's name.)
Jae Seok is like a valley.
It's not deep.
It keeps on trickling with water.
(Team Osaka is in chaos as they are trapped in So Min's conversations.)
(She is shy to be in front of the cameras. She's a new crazy member.)
(She doesn't care about the mission and is filming a movie alone.)
(Team Osaka's hidden mission is to analyse So Min's personality.)
- We found it. - That bathhouse is it.
(After many obstacles, they found a bathhouse run by Suzuki.)
(They accomplished their mission. Can they return safely to Korea?)
(Team Osaka, stop right there!)
(Team Taipei is pursuing Team Osaka with a voracious appetite.)
Stinky tofu dish?
(They are on the move to find a stinky tofu dish.)
(Will Team Taipei be able to find a stinky tofu dish?)
Since the team leader, Ji Hyo peeled off the most pumpkin seeds earlier,
- you guys won a Chance Card. - That's right.
We will give you guys the Chance Card right now.
- Right now? - My goodness.
(Team Taipei has the Chance Card in their hands at last.)
(It's a hidden weapon that will change the game completely.)
- What is this? - You can use this card...
against the other teams to...
We can use this against them?
(The secret of this Chance Card will be revealed right now.)
(Team Taipei doesn't hesitate...)
(to use this on Team Osaka.)
(Meanwhile, Team Osaka enjoyed their bath.)
- Gosh, this is refreshing. - Nice.
(They had a wash and brush up.)
I was in a rush, so I didn't even put lotion on.
- So Min. - I didn't get to put lotion on.
(You washed thoroughly.)
You look so clean. Do you want to borrow our lotion?
- I have one. My face is bare. - Do you have one?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Thank you, Mr. Suzuki.)
Wait. Where's So Min?
(When will So Min be out?)
Where are your eyebrows?
I'm going to put makeup on now.
- Really? - You don't have to put makeup on.
Let me see your face.
- It's better to see you like this. - You don't have to put makeup on.
Everyone. You've succeeded in finding Suzuki's bathhouse even...
- though the mission was difficult. - Yes, we did.
- You've completed your mission. - Yes!
(Team Osaka accomplished their mission.)
- It was really nice. - I loved it.
- I wanted to stay longer. - Me too.
- I really liked this kind of place. - Me too. It was so cute.
- It was also very clean. - It really was.
However...
(They get a bad feeling right away.)
Ji Hyo received a Chance Card earlier. Do you remember that?
(They had forgotten about the card.)
The Chance Card was Doubling Card.
- Okay. - What is that?
The team which the card was used on has to do another mission.
(Why are you telling us that?)
Ji Hyo used that card against Team Osaka.
- They are unbelievable. - What is...
- wrong with them? - Why are they doing this?
That's why they took time enjoying their meal.
I guess so.
Look at us. We are completely ready to go home.
- I don't look presentable for TV. - We had a nice meal.
- We even had snacks. - He washed his hair...
with cleansing foam.
My hair is so dry right now.
Don't I look like I came from hiking?
- Gosh. - You...
- You don't have time. Let's hurry. - What is the mission?
The mission is to get a trendy Japanese hairstyle.
(Japanese hairstyle?)
(Welcome to the world of style.)
- We don't have much time. - Do we have time for that?
We need to leave soon. Where is a hair salon?
We could have gone to a barbershop, but it's closed.
It's closed.
Let's go to a shopping mall...
- and see if there is a hair salon. - We won't find anything here.
- This is harsh. - What do you mean?
I thought we were done with the mission.
- You pronounced it wrong again. - I know.
How else am I supposed to pronounce it?
- "Mission". - "Mission".
Mission.
(It's So Min's mission to learn how to pronounce it.)
- Wait a minute. - Let's have something to drink.
- Shall we get beverages? - Yes.
- Who wants something to drink? - Let's get green tea.
- Green tea. - Okay.
This tour is very homely and nice.
- I feel like I am playing house. - Get green tea.
- It's cheaper than it is in Korea. - Let's get one more bottle.
Wait a minute. In that case, give me green tea as well.
Why won't it come out?
Did you insert the coins wrong?
- The machine ate the coins. - I inserted them.
- I inserted them. - The machine ate the coins.
I inserted them.
This is...
- It came out. - Vending machines are the same.
- Vending machines are the same. - It came out.
(Vending machines are the same everywhere around the world.)
Okay.
This is a tour in Japan.
(He is excited.)
- Put some lotion on your face. - Suddenly...
- Your face... - I'm feeling good all of a sudden.
- Seok Jin's face is too dry. - Let's drink...
cool green tea.
Seok Jin's face is like a dry rice paddy.
- A dry rice paddy. - This is a tour in Japan.
- Did you apply lotion? - Yes, I did. Why do you ask?
- Do I look weird? - What are you doing?
- I am putting makeup on. - Do it thoroughly.
How does my face look?
- Is it flushed? - It looks like a dry rice paddy.
(She applies makeup in front of the camera.)
Please show me how I look on the camera.
(Staring)
- I cleansed my face. - You look fine.
Let's get in the car.
(They go to the center of the city in search of a hair salon.)
It would have been nice if the barbershop was open.
Then we could have left after getting our hair done.
We still have 30km left to go.
Will we be able to complete the mission?
(What will be the fate of Team Osaka?)
(Meanwhile, in Taiwan...)
(Team Taipei entered the stinky tofu restaurant.)
Thank you. Thank you.
- The atmosphere is nice. - I bet the dishes are delicious.
We won't have any problems if we succeed in eating stinky tofu.
- Here is the menu. - It looks nice.
It says it's spicy. "Duck".
"Spicy duck"...
- This is seonji. Seonji. - Blood?
"Tofu". It says "stinky tofu".
(That sounds intense.)
(Nervous)
(Stinky tofu is made with tofu that is salted and fermented.)
(It's hard to enjoy the dish because of its strong smell.)
(The stinky tofu dish is served.)
(What is this smell?)
It looks like it would be difficult to eat.
(They are lost for words.)
(What should we eat first?)
Tell yourself that it smells like hot pot.
- It smells like hot pot. - It does.
- Let's try the dish. - Shall we try the soup first?
Stay positive.
(How does the soup of duck blood and stinky tofu taste?)
- It's tasty. - It's delicious!
This is duck blood.
(She tries duck blood this time.)
- It tastes like seonji. - Seonji?
Ji Hyo is incredible.
She is Big Mama of variety shows.
She is like Lee Hye Jung.
- This is stinky tofu, right? - This is stinky tofu.
I am serious.
It smells a bit.
- Wait a minute. It smells a bit. - Ji Hyo, what is up with you?
(Chewing)
(She puts down the chopsticks.)
- The smell isn't too strong, is it? - It isn't too strong.
(Even Ji Hyo gave up on eating this dish.)
Try it. It tastes like tofu that tastes slightly strange.
Stay positive.
(Chewing)
It's okay.
(Staying positive makes him strong.)
(Your face tells me otherwise.)
You aren't breathing.
- The power of positivity! - "It's okay."
Let's eat a dumpling each.
- That's a good idea. - Let's eat a dumpling each.
Let's soothe our stomach first.
The dumpling wrapper...
is thicker than it is in Korea.
(Putting something on the top)
(Here is stinky tofu for you.)
(Don't be picky with your food, Haha.)
Eat it with stinky tofu on the top.
Ji Hyo is working hard today.
Okay.
(Haha tries stinky tofu thanks to Ji Hyo.)
It's okay, right?
Does the juice of dumpling conceal the smell of stinky tofu?
Do you taste the dishes separately?
I taste the dishes separately.
(It doesn't conceal anything.)
Then there is no point in eating them together.
- It's delicious. - Is it okay to eat it that way?
- Foreigners hate cheonggukjang. - This is the same thing.
The more you eat cheonggukjang, the more charming its taste becomes.
I know. You fall in love with its savoury taste.
I want to fall into the charms of stinky tofu.
- Try another bite. - You should go first.
You should fall into its charms first.
- Since there is a piece... - Let's have one person eat it.
Let's get rid of it that way.
After you eat it,
you can't drink soda. Swallow and stick out your tongue.
- After that, you can eat dumplings. - Okay.
Here comes the roulette.
(The roulette appears.)
I have an idea.
- 1st place gets 3 slots. - 1st place gets 3 slots.
- 2nd place gets 5 slots. - Then there will be a slot left.
Last place gets eight slots.
Even if we do that, we won't know...
- who will get chosen. - That's right.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors. - Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
(Haha gets 8 slots.)
Haha is unlucky today.
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
(Se Chan won.)
- Nice! I am lucky today. - He is lucky.
I am lucky today.
You are the ones who came up with the rules.
You have to chew the tofu without soda...
or dumplings before you finish it and stick out your tongue.
Who will spin it? Will the producer do it?
- Let's have the producer spin it. - Okay.
Otherwise, we might resent each other.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Stinky tofu dish has rich history and nutrients.)
(Who will get to enjoy the precious taste?)
(Stinky tofu dish is ready to show its charms.)
(What will be the result?)
(Congratulations, Se Chan.)
(This is incredible.)
(Is this for real?)
(He defied the probability.)
His luck is like super poop.
He is the unluckiest.
(What have I done wrong?)
(I won the game of rock-paper-scissors.)
(Haha was supposed to be the one.)
I have 3 slots. Don't you have 8 slots?
(Start eating.)
(He starts eating the sticky tofu.)
Stay positive.
Stay positive. It will be tasty.
Please make this match come true.
- Yang Se Chan versus Lee Kwang Soo. - Kwang Soo.
It will be a match of the century. It's like Batman versus Superman.
He is right.
Who do you think will win?
- The recent events say Se Chan. - Right?
- He is terribly unlucky. - Go, Se Chan.
I can drink soda after I stick out my tongue, right?
Yes.
(He puts stinky tofu in his mouth.)
(Chewing)
(Did the charm of stinky tofu touch you?)
(Grabbing)
Think of your mom.
(My mom and my brother were so happy when I joined Running Man.)
Think about the hard times.
Hang in there.
(Se Chan, stay positive.)
He is incredible.
I stuck out my tongue.
(Se Chan succeeded in eating stinky tofu in one bite.)
I respect you.
I totally respect you.
It felt like I was eating Do Yeon's foot.
(The woman with charms of stinky tofu is in Jeju Island.)
- Thank you. Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(They leave for a mission of eating octopus ramyeon.)
- Let's go. - He won't be able to hear us well.
(Come closer, Kwang Soo.)
- Hold our hands. - I mean...
Hold our hands.
- Slide in. - Well...
Do it like you are slipping on sea water.
(Depressed)
(This isn't Jeju Island we dreamed of.)
My hands and feet are numb.
Who is that?
(Who is calling me?)
Ji Hyo video called me earlier.
I didn't answer.
Why did my sister call me?
My sister called...
to show her child, but I can't answer the call.
(My sister called to show her child, but I can't answer the call.)
- It's heartbreaking, right? - Take off the head part.
(She feels bad.)
(I am sorry. Uncle is working hard.)
The fabric must be very tough. I can't see the outline of his ears.
- I have big ears too. - His ears are missing.
- Do you have big ears? - His ears are missing.
- That's hilarious. - Why are his ears missing?
Jong Kook.
Didn't you force me to wear the cap and goggles?
(Give him the cap and goggles.)
(Is there a cap?)
That'd complete the outfit.
(He is very kind in moments like this one.)
(Laughing)
I was perfectly fine before you interfered.
- This is how women divers look. - You're right.
You looked too good before putting on the cap.
Exactly.
Every time I look at him... Gosh, look at him.
(Ridiculous)
(Where...)
(did it all go wrong?)
Before it gets colder...
We haven't eaten anything since 1pm.
I'm so hungry.
- We even went into the water. - Let's eat something.
Jeju Island is famous for...
- omegi rice cakes. - Omegi rice cakes?
There's a rice cake shop. Should we buy some?
- Should we do that? - Should we try?
(They're finally getting something to eat.)
What's going on? Are they out of business?
(Is no one here?)
- Are we breaking in? - Excuse... Is this a private home?
Isn't this omegi rice cakes?
Excuse me.
- Look at this. - Excuse me.
(What is this creepy-looking rice cakes?)
- Excuse me. - Hello.
We'd like to buy some rice cakes.
- Is this a prank? - It reminds me of "The Chaser".
It looks so old.
(The rice cakes look mysterious.)
It's green.
Excuse me.
Should we report?
(But they could find no one in there.)
Why is it so hard... Why are we so unlucky today?
My goodness.
Why is it so hard to have a little rice cakes?
(Team Jeju Island's misfortune continues.)
(They had to buy donuts at a bakery instead.)
- Did you buy something? - Yes.
(I've been so hungry.)
(Something is wrong again.)
I don't believe you.
Usually, fresh donuts taste good.
(Laughing)
Seriously? What's going on today?
You can't expect everything to taste good.
- What do you think? - Be honest.
It makes me thirsty.
- I know. - My throat hurts.
It's so dry.
It absorbed all the moisture...
- in my body. - Exactly.
I've never been this thirsty since my military training.
Seriously.
(So far, they've been able to laugh it off.)
Here.
- We got another bad news. - What is it?
We booked flight tickets this morning, right?
The teams were decided this morning.
We're trying to book our return tickets right now.
- But it's not going so well. - No way.
No way.
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook's flight...
departs at 5pm.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook's flight departs at 5pm.)
Kwang Soo and Jong Kook's flight departs at 5pm.
(So soon?)
- We should hurry. - Really?
Do Yeon's flight...
departs at 8pm.
What am I supposed to do here alone for three hours?
There are no available tickets for the rest of the staff.
Really?
(Jeju Island has been harsh on them.)
(They head for the airport without having octopus ramyeon.)
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook have to get on the flight.)
Put on the goggles.
(They have to get on the plane within 10 minutes.)
(All they did in Jeju Island was struggle.)
(Will Do Yeon be all right?)
Gosh, it's cold.
(What will happen to us?)
(Meanwhile, what is Team Taipei doing?)
It feels like we're backpackers.
You're right.
We're backpackers.
- We are. - Our backpacks are pretty too.
- You're right. - They have nice colours.
They're red, yellow, and green.
(They look like traffic lights.)
Wait. There's a beef place.
- Where? - There's a cow.
That's right.
That's the place.
Let's go.
- What's this place? - It opened in 1958.
(They found a place with a long history.)
- Jackie Chan was here. - That's right.
- Jackie Chan was here. - Let me see.
Look. It's Jackie Chan.
He appeared on Running Man before too.
(Jackie, is this place good?)
- Let's go in. - Let's go.
(Beef noodles, a representative noodle dish of Greater China)
(The broth is made only with beef and has a clear taste.)
I'm excited.
- I think it'll taste good. - I think so too.
(The combination of rich beef broth and chewy noodles)
Today...
- To our memorable trip. - Yes.
We must be ahead of the others.
We gave them another mission.
Team Osaka has to complete another mission.
They might be late.
Ji Hyo, you did a great job badmouthing other members.
You did a great job.
I'm good at badmouthing people.
- We found her talent. - She's good at agreeing too.
If we continue this way,
- we'll win. - But we can't relax.
There's something Jae Seok said on "X-Man".
- What is it? - We have...
safety bread.
What does that mean?
It means we're safe.
(We're safe.)
(We know we won't lose for certain.)
We're very safe.
(Beef noodles are served.)
It looks so tasty.
(It looks and smells tasty.)
(Let me try the soup.)
Please describe the taste well.
Try it.
(Slurping)
(Impressed)
(How can it taste so good?)
This is insane.
(Emotional)
(He thinks of his mother back home.)
Don't cry.
(The beef broth makes you cry.)
Haha, stop crying. It's okay.
(My mother likes beef noodles.)
(Holding back his tears, Haha tries the soup again.)
My gosh.
I think this is the tastiest broth I've ever tasted in my life.
This is the best meat broth I've tasted.
If you eat the noodles with the beef,
it tastes like galbijjim.
Really?
It tastes like galbijjim.
(Every bite surprises them.)
(Tasting)
It's interesting.
(Beef noodles tastes interesting.)
The texture is very interesting.
The taste is very interesting.
(Is this your first time trying beef noodles?)
It's very interesting.
(The taste is unbelievable.)
It tastes so refreshing at the end.
I'm so full.
(They've emptied their bowls.)
When you're full,
- you should have dessert. - You're right.
(They have to try mango shaved ice and pineapple cake.)
I wish I could do this every day.
- Look. - It's right here.
- Look at that. - It's crazy.
(They found a shaved ice place.)
Let's share it.
(Mango shaved ice has a sweet and fresh taste.)
(They're about to enjoy it now.)
- Ji Hyo. - Oh, my.
- It's here. - I can't believe this.
(It's the perfect time for mango shaved ice.)
- It looks so tasty. - Is that kimchi? What's that?
It looks so luxurious. I don't want to touch it.
- I don't want to crush it. - Let's try.
(All three of them are amazed.)
- It tastes so good. - Taiwan.
It feels like when you go into a bank...
to avoid heat on a hot summer day.
It's so cool in the bank.
It feels exactly like that.
It feels like I stepped into a bank.
- Good job. - I'm relieved.
It's the best way to describe it.
(I love Taiwan.)
(An arm comes in.)
Our staff members couldn't resist, and they are starting to try it.
It's beautiful.
- It's too hot. - Come here.
Try it. It feels like you're in a bank.
- Right? - It's delicious.
- It tastes so good. - It's tasty.
(The bank is crowded.)
We have to get on the plane soon.
- We don't have much time. - It was so tasty.
- Let's get souvenirs. - Okay.
- Okay? - I'll...
(Souvenirs?)
You have to get souvenirs for a member...
whose name is in your backpack.
What should I get?
(They separate to buy souvenirs.)
What should I buy?
I've been thinking,
and I have an idea.
(What kind of souvenirs will they get?)
Once you see it, you'll know whom I'm getting it for.
(Sa Chan finds a pineapple cake store.)
(It's a cake made with pineapple jam.)
- I'll open it for you. - Thank you.
I tried one earlier.
- You did? - Yes.
(It's their fifth food.)
We picked the right dishes.
(It was like a course meal.)
This jam tastes so good.
Our parents would love it.
(It's a popular souvenir too.)
Your mission has been completed.
(They have completed their mission by trying 5 Taiwanese dishes.)
Haha looks so happy.
He's so happy.
I feel sorry for Team Osaka.
I wonder...
- what they're doing right now. - What they're doing right now.
We've been in a hurry all day.
We've been so busy.
If there's a shopping mall around the airport,
let's look around.
How long does it take to the airport?
- More than 30 minutes. - We'll be there around 4:30pm.
(We spent too much time in the bathhouse.)
This tour has been so hectic.
It has.
We've done so much.
(The six hours went so fast.)
So Min is so funny.
She said...
- she'd take care of us. - She said she'd take care of us.
I made things easier for you.
"Eat."
"Add chives. Add garlics."
We like freedom.
- We don't want to be controlled. - We hate it.
You're so oblivious.
As I'm on the same team with Seok Jin this time,
So I think I'll be able to enjoy being on the same team...
with anybody else and...
Wait. That's not what I mean.
So you're saying that I'm the worst teammate you could ever have.
Right? After being on the same team with me,
you can handle everybody else.
Am I really the worst teammate you could ever have?
- I can't believe she said that. - My goodness.
We're here.
We don't have enough time to do the mission, right?
Right now, it's time for us to go back.
- Exactly. We have to go back. - My gosh.
Is this the last plane?
Yes. I'm sorry to say that you've failed the mission.
So one of you are going to get the Tour Sticker.
- Do you remember the game? - Yes.
The one whose shoe lands on a different mission will get it.
- That's a great idea. - Yes, let's do that.
(There are 9 boxes with 3 different types of missions written on them.)
So Min can go first.
You need to follow me, okay?
If you fail to throw your shoe inside the box,
- you're out. - That person will get the sticker.
- That's not fair. - Go on.
(The reason she's so nervous is because...)
(when they arrived at Osaka 7 hours ago,)
(she failed to throw her shoe inside the box.)
- Hey! - Put some effort into the game.
- Costume play! - Don't aim for a certain box.
(She failed to get her shoe inside any of the boxes.)
(She wasted 30 minutes in selecting a mission.)
(So Min doesn't know how to aim and throw.)
- Do I go first? - Yes.
- You need to follow me, okay? - Okay, don't worry.
(Please aim for the mission I get.)
(Previously, out of 14 throws, she only succeeded once.)
(Will she fail again?)
You got it in.
(She got it inside the box.)
- You're good. - It's my turn.
- It's your turn. - Aim for the costume play box.
- I'll go for the costume play. - Okay.
I'm really bad at aiming.
I'm not so confident.
(If he fails, he'll be the one to get the Tour Sticker.)
(He must get it inside one of the boxes.)
(What will happen to Jae Seok?)
You failed!
- Wait a minute. - You failed. Let go of me.
- Let go! - Wait, Seok Jin.
- Please give me another chance. - No way. It doesn't work like that.
You failed.
- If you fail, we get to go again. - Of course.
(If Seok Jin fails too, they'll have a rematch.)
(If he succeeds, Jae Seok will be the one to get the Tour Sticker.)
(The fate of the Tour Sticker is in Seok Jin's shoe.)
(Will he fail?)
(Or will he succeed?)
(What will be their destiny?)
(Seok Jin succeeds.)
(Jae Seok gets one Tour Sticker.)
- Jae Seok failed on purpose. - Yes, I think he did.
I can't believe how hard this is.
(Feeling unfair.)
(All three teams have now completed their one-day trip.)
(Everyone comes back at around 10pm.)
- I'm so tired. - We're back.
Is it 3am again?
I'm sorry Do Yeon. Do Yeon!
Do Yeon, are you okay?
- I'm back alive. - Do Yeon.
Good job, Do Yeon.
I thought I was going to be treated like a queen.
You're just a tall woman.
I guess I'm just a tall woman.
I'll announce the results of the team missions.
Team Taipei, you completed your mission.
(Team Taipei succeeded in their mission.)
- All you had to do was eat. - Exactly.
We had to eat stinky tofu,
- I'm so hungry. - and Se Chan...
- Stop it. - Should I?
- Why? - Tell us.
He said it tasted like Do Yeon's foot.
- Stop. - Stop it already.
(Was Do Yeon's foot in Taipei?)
(Stop making fun of me.)
- Can I just say one swear word? - Don't.
(You little stinky tofu.)
What? What did you say?
- What was that? - It was nothing.
- Good job. - It's really a bad habit.
- He uses my weakness. - I understand.
I always say good things about you. My gosh, forget it.
(Forget it.)
(There's no point in talking to you.)
- Let's carry on with the show. - You lost.
- Don't take it too seriously. - He's right.
- I lost. - It's just a joke.
- Team Jeju Island. - Yes.
Thanks to your team leader, Do Yeon, you guys completed the mission.
(Thanks to Do Yeon, they successfully completed the mission.)
- We did it. - Thank you.
(Do Yeon was left alone in Jeju Island.)
Hello. I'd like to have one bowl of ramyeon, please.
My gosh, it looks incredible.
Look at this meal. It looks great.
(Its spicy soup is perfect for chilly weather.)
Look at the octopus and abalone. They're so big.
It's so soft.
Kwang Soo, we suffered so much because of this octopus.
(If only Kwang Soo knows what this tastes like...)
(Here, have a bite, my friend.)
(The imaginary Kwang Soo takes a big bite.)
You eat well, Kwang Soo.
(I'm so lonely.)
I'm so lonely.
(She completed the mission on her own.)
Team Osaka. You succeeded in meeting Mr. Suzuki,
but because of the Chance Card attack, you failed your mission.
This is so unfair.
It was so hard to find Mr. Suzuki. Jae Seok gets one sticker.
- Jae Seok got one. - He might go on the trip.
It's not over yet. You were told to buy a gift for...
- your designated member. - That's right.
- I remember. - Yes, that's right.
Now, it's time for you to give it to its owner.
- Okay. - Let's start from Kwang Soo.
Okay.
(Kwang Soo chose...)
He chose Jae Seok.
- It's my present for you. - It's very heavy.
- It's nothing much. - Thank you, Kwang Soo.
The person who received a present should go next.
- It looks light. - What?
Give it to Jong Kook.
- Is it for me? - I got it from Japan.
- Really? - I'll go next.
- You will be so moved. - Why?
- It's for Seok Jin. - Really?
- Take a look. You'll like it. - It looks heavy.
- It's really warm. - It must be poop.
(It must be poop.)
(You little...)
- My gosh. - It's not poop.
- I can't believe you said that. - It could be his own.
- My gosh. - If it's warm, it could be that.
(Everyone finishes exchanging gifts.)
- This was great. - It's getting warmer,
- so a lot of people were on trips. - There were so many.
- The ambiance was lovely. - I had a great time.
- It was really lovely. - You guys must think it's over now.
- Aren't we done? - We exchanged gifts.
Do we have to play another game now?
- You guys exchanged gifts. - That's right.
- I knew this would happen. - There's one last mission for you.
- What is it? - It's Scale of Justice.
- Please hold this. - We need to weigh something?
The weight of your gift will decide whether you win or lose.
The person who has the heavier present will be the winner.
- My gosh. - The heavier one?
(It's advantageous to have a heavier present?)
Do we get a Tour Sticker if we lose?
- Yes. - Are you serious?
(The loser will get a Tour Sticker.)
(It'll bring them one step closer to the dangerous tourist attraction.)
(Who will be the unlucky one to get the Tour Sticker?)
- Mine's really light too. - The first person to...
- weigh their bag is Jong Kook. - It's Jong Kook's turn.
- The heavier one will win. - But Jong Kook's bag looks light.
- Exactly. - I didn't know about this game.
- I got him something light. - This is as light as his mouth.
- I'm serious. - My goodness.
- Is it that light? - I'm sure you'll like the present.
- I'm doomed. - I guess he got him something nice.
Who's going to go against me?
- It's going to be Jae Seok. - My gosh, this is unbelievable.
- I can't believe this. - You can just leave it there.
I already have a Tour Sticker.
- You can get one more. - Let's go.
In 1, 2, 3.
(The first round of Scale of Justice)
(Whose bag will be lighter?)
(Jong Kook's bag is light while Jae Seok's bag is very heavy.)
(What?)
- You lost. - My goodness.
- My gosh, Jong Kook. - I feel so bad.
- You're so stupid. - What were you thinking?
- Hey, Kwang Soo! - He thought he won.
- No problem, Jae Seok. - Thank you.
The person who loses against Jong Kook...
- He got me tangerines. - Really?
(These tangerines saved my life.)
- That's right! - Kwang Soo!
- Kwang Soo. - When did you get them?
- I got them just for you. - When did you buy them?
I got it when I had time.
I would've gotten a Tour Sticker if it hadn't been for you.
I could've gone on the trip next week.
That's enough. Stop it.
- Stop it. - I'm so happy.
- It's Seok Jin's turn now. - Come on.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Seok Jin wins easily.)
(What a gift!)
- Thank you. - Seok Jin's really happy right now.
- Did you see him disappointed? - My goodness.
(So Min wins easily too.)
- What is it? - It's bread.
They're leftovers of what we had.
(Jong Kook wanted to give her the leftovers.)
- We ate that. - Look.
It wasn't delicious at all.
(He's lost for 4 consecutive times now.)
How light is Jong Kook's bag?
I got it for you so you can drink at home.
- Who got that? - Seok Jin.
(Jong Kook loses again.)
- My gosh. - How can this be?
- This is a great present. - I know.
- Really? - You can give that to your son.
- Thank you so much. - It's a coin bank.
- Where's the rock? I brought it. - The rock?
Here it is.
- What? - What is that?
(It's really just a rock.)
- She's really weird. - Right?
I told you, didn't I? She becomes really weird.
- What is that? - What's that for?
- I got it for you as a souvenir. - Are you serious?
He might throw it away.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Jong Kook loses six times in a row.)
- Jong Kook. - Jong Kook, you're doomed.
- What is in that bag? - I'm so curious.
There's a meaning behind my present.
(What's inside Kwang Soo's bag?)
(3 hours ago at a convenience store in Jeju Island)
(She grabs something.)
I'm going to get octopus' friends.
(She gets a squid snack.)
(She gets Kwang Soo some squid snacks.)
He won't throw these away, will he?
(No way.)
(Throwing)
(He immediately throws them away.)
- Why did you do that? - Are you serious?
- Hey! - What did she get you?
(The memories of Jeju Island are quite painful.)
- Se Chan. - Now, it's...
- Se Chan's turn. - Se Chan needs to be careful.
- Se Chan. - If you lose,
- you'd be done for. - Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - Just go to the airport right away.
- What did you put in the backpack? - Se Chan, snacks are in there.
- We don't know what will happen. - Se Chan can head straight there.
- His backpack is really light. - One...
(Se Chan's backpack looks light at a glance.)
Two...
(What is the result of the seventh weighing?)
Let go.
- What's happening? - What is going on?
- How can this happen? - What is this?
(How can this be so close?)
- Does this make sense? - Is it tied?
In case this happened,
we have prepared a scale that will tell us the weight.
We will weigh the backpacks to figure out their weights.
If I lose here, I'm done.
This is Jong Kook's backpack.
(We will weigh it precisely.)
(The weight of Jong Kook's is...)
It's 945g.
- It weighs 945g. - The weight is 945g.
Next.
I don't know who's going to win.
(If Se Chan loses, he will move one step closer to the dangerous trip.)
Se Chan.
(Will Jong Kook lose? Or will Se Chan, the new unlucky guy, lose?)
Let go of the backpack.
- Yes! - It weighs 822g.
(Se Chan's backpack weighs 822g.)
- I won, right? - Jong Kook wins.
- Poor Se Chan. - I'm saved.
- Poor Se Chan. - Show us what's in the backpack.
- Se Chan will go on the trip. - I didn't know.
- Se Chan now has two stickers. - I really didn't know about this.
- I got this for Jong Kook. - Is that underwear?
- What is this? - They are underpants.
- You like the US. - Aren't they for a girl?
(It was underwear.)
I like it.
- It's a thoughtful gift. - Aren't they nice?
- I'll wear them in the US. - You should.
You'll feel like you're in the US with just socks and underpants.
- I thought about you. - Thank you.
- Jae Seok thought about him. - That is a sincere gift.
- Of course. - They look great on you.
Do Yeon, you are the last one and will place your backpack soon.
Do Yeon is a guest and Tour Stickers don't apply to her.
That's why we installed something special in her name tag...
- just in case she lost. - Really?
(If she is ranked last, the member on her left gets the Tour Sticker.)
- Please. - All right.
- We will weigh Do Yeon's backpack. - Let's weigh mine.
- Se Chan's weighs 822g. - We don't know yet.
- You have to place it on the scale. - Wait.
(Will it weigh more than 822g or not?)
(The last weighing will determine the member who will be ranked last.)
(The result will bring him closer to the dangerous tourist attraction.)
(Which 1 of these 2 will be ranked last?)
- It's 835g. - Her backpack weighs 835g.
(On the grounds that he has the lightest backpack,)
(Se Chan will receive a Tour Sticker.)
Good for you!
- It's Se Chan. - He got it.
(Why is my life so hard?)
- The difference was 13g. - Is this really happening?
- I didn't know this would happen. - Okay, Haha.
- We were family. - Let's open her backpack.
Let's see what Ji Hyo gave her.
- Sure. - It's Se Chan.
- He's so unlucky. - He is indeed.
- What is it? - It's aroma oil.
- I like it. - I bought it for her because...
Se Chan kept teasing her about her feet.
Is this show about health? We talked about my feet for hours.
(This isn't a health program. Let's stop talking about my feet.)
- No. - Do Yeon, you will need it.
- You will need it later. - What is this?
- My feet are healthy. - It will be useful in the future.
It's for your future.
- When you have your foot bath, - She washed her feet.
- I really like this though. - you can relax.
- I really like this oil. - It's good oil too.
- What does this mean? - It holds a meaning.
Since you became a part of our Running Man family,
you'll be running a lot. I didn't want you to get athlete's foot.
- That's why I gave them to you. - That's cool.
- These are meaningful. - Yes, they are.
You can go and get that meaningful punishment.
You can wear them on the trip.
Anyway, Se Chan is ranked last for the race, Dangerous Trips.
(Se Chan finishes last in the race.)
- He's the new unlucky guy. - It was so close though.
- He's in the lead. - I can't believe it.
Running Man's new project is a global race with new members.
(Global race with new members)
(A member will go on a trip with 3 Tour Stickers.)
(Which member will go on a trip to the dangerous tourist attraction?)
(Running Man's Global Project: Dangerous Tourist Attractions)
- Hello. Hi. - Hi.
(In April, Deungchon SBS)
(Haha is the last one to stand in his spot for the opening segment.)
(What? What is that?)
(He's wearing a colorful outfit for spring.)
(The whole staff laugh.)
Haha looks like a kid.
Look at the color of your pants.
Now, even the staff members are laughing at me.
After the identity of his mentor for the outfits was revealed,
his outfits have changed a lot and that part even aired on TV.
(His outfits changed after everyone found out he was copying outfits.)
- Look! It's Haha's fashion mentor. - Stop it.
(I'm sorry, Haha, but stop copying my outfits.)
Stay in the car!
I said hello to Young Jin because I thought he was Haha.
He used to copy his outfits.
Fortunately,
a lot of viewers are happy that Se Chan and So Min have joined.
- 9012... - Forever!
Forever!
Although Gary did get married...
Although Gary changed his number...
- Although we didn't know... - Although we didn't know...
- 9012! - 9012!
- We won't abandon him. - He didn't even contact us.
- Right. He did change his number. - He didn't tell us he got married.
Gary, where are you?
- We won't try to visit you. - Are you even in Korea?
You're forever in our hearts. 9012!
The funny thing about him is that he keeps sending me hats.
- He does? - I just can't reach him.
- He sent them anonymously. - That's right.
- I'm so grateful. - He keeps sending the hats.
He turned into an anonymous philanthropist.
He became an anonymous philanthropist for Haha.
- Goodness. - I don't know his number.
Se Chan and So Min. What do your acquaintances say about the show?
Before I joined, fans abroad already told me how they felt about me.
- I don't speak English though. - Me neither.
- Do you understand only a bit? - I know "Don't" and "Hate you".
Those comments sort of bothered me.
I know what "Hate you" means.
They don't want me to join.
A fan put a heart between Se Chan and me...
- so that we become a couple. - That's right.
- The fan wants you to be a couple. - Nowadays,
- fans want a love interest. - That's true.
- They wrote nice comments. - The fan meant that I can't be...
a couple with other members. I should only be with Se Chan.
- Only you and I. - So it means...
the fans want them to be only with each other.
- She can't be with other members? - Fans are protecting other members.
- They don't want us to be involved. - How about with Kwang Soo?
They said I can never be with him.
I am only allowed to be with Se Chan.
But a lot of people liked them after the show aired.
- I agree. - They did.
Anyway, Se Chan has two Tour Stickers for the race.
- I do. - Look at Se Chan.
If he gets another one this week, he will have to go on the trip.
This is driving me crazy.
Today is the part 3 of Running Man's global project.
Before we reveal today's mission,
only So Min and Ji Hyo...
will go inside.
- Why? - To where?
(Will So Min and Ji Hyo receive a hidden mission or something?)
What is this?
(There's a huge world map and mysterious houses.)
Are we going in?
(There are only 2 female members, but why are there 3 houses?)
The first mission will divide you into 3 teams of 3 members.
It's Guess with Your Senses.
So Min, Ji Hyo, and a special, female guest...
are in the houses you see on the side.
- Okay! - Who is it?
I will be on the special guest's team.
(I will definitely choose the special guest by all means.)
You will have to guess the house the guest is in using your senses.
Members who are on the guest's team will receive a Chance Card.
- I have to be on the guest's team. - Why?
I have to get that benefit. I am in the most vulnerable position.
You're right.
Can we hear them say hello?
The red house is the first house and so on.
The first lady in the red house, say hello.
Hello.
- That's the guest. - It's Ji Hyo.
- It has to be the guest. - It sounds like Ji Hyo.
Let's move onto the second house.
(How will the 2nd lady sound like?)
Hello.
- It's Ji Hyo! - It's her.
- No, I am not certain that she is. - It's Ji Hyo.
- That's her. - I know her voice.
- No, it's not her. - That's definitely her.
- The second one is Ji Hyo. - I agree.
- It's Ji Hyo. - It's her.
Let's hear the third lady's voice.
Hello.
- It's So Min! - That's right.
- Is it really her? - "Hello." She tried to sound cute.
- I think she sounded a bit old. - It's not So Min?
- "Hello." - Who is that?
I think I am positive that Ji Hyo is in the second house.
Really?
(You think Ji Hyo is in the 2nd house?)
I won't choose the second house.
- Don't say that out loud. - Hey, that's mean.
- Keep your opinion to yourself. - I'm sorry.
I almost said, "Me too."
(Jong Kook and Haha, let's have a talk later.)
All right. The first hint of the senses is...
sight.
- Sight? - Sight.
Their feet will be exposed through the door in the bottom.
You can guess the house the guest is in by looking at their feet.
- I've never seen their feet though. - That's true.
For the last seven years, I've never seen Ji Hyo's feet.
- You've never seen them? - Maybe I just don't remember.
- Her feet never left an impression. - It could be because...
Ji Hyo kicked you a long time ago.
- That's true. - That's why you don't remember.
Now, Seok Jin goes along with your teasing.
He doesn't fight you.
- Ji Hyo kicked him in the face. - She kicked my face.
He passed out. That's why he doesn't remember her feet.
(This is the class of a talker with 25 years of experience.)
We will begin now.
We will start with the lady in the first house. Please show your foot.
(Sticking out)
- Wait! - I can recognize Ji Hyo's feet.
- Hold on a second. - We can look at it up close?
- Her pants... - Hey,
- I think it's Ji Hyo's foot. - It's So Min's foot.
(Her foot is white and long.)
Wait. I think she doesn't wear heels a lot by the look of it.
- No, she does. - Since So Min is...
- tall, she doesn't wear heels. - I see calluses.
- So Min's feet are white. - She has long toes.
I don't think this is Ji Hyo though.
Aren't her feet as big as 280mm?
- It's Do Yeon. - Do Yeon!
- This is Do Yeon. - It's Do Yeon.
- Is it her? It's a big foot. - Look at this.
Look, her foot is as big as Haha's.
- Stop it. - Come on.
Kwang Soo, that's not a polite thing to do to a lady.
- How can a lady's foot be so big? - I'm sorry to do this,
but my shoe size is about 270mm.
(Her foot is quite big.)
- Your foot is big. - It is indeed.
It's bigger than 250mm.
- I think so. - If her feet are big,
- it's not Ji Hyo. - Which celebrities have big feet?
Can it be Park Chan Sook?
(Chan Sook is a basketball player.)
How about Kim Yeon Koung?
- She can be an athlete. - She could be a player.
- That's possible. - It's because...
- her foot is as big as 270mm. - It's Yeon Koung.
- Yeon Koung? - Yeon Koung?
(Her identity is becoming more of a mystery.)
Isn't that So Min's?
I think it is.
Let's look at the second lady's foot.
(Pushing out)
- It's Ji Hyo. - It's Ji Hyo.
- It's Ji Hyo. - It's definitely Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo likes to paint her toenails dark.
- It doesn't look cute at all. - It's definitely Ji Hyo.
- It doesn't look cute at all. - It's very dry.
- It's very still. - Let's find out her personality.
See?
(Don't touch me.)
(It's definitely Ji Hyo.)
See? It's Ji Hyo.
- Definitely. - It's definitely Ji Hyo.
(Is it really Ji Hyo's foot?)
You can guess the person's personality from her foot.
This foot looks a bit aggressive.
- It's sharp. - It looks angry.
- It's aggressive. - It's angry.
Ji Hyo doesn't wear high heels often.
(They check again.)
(The foot is angry.)
- I'm sure. - It's certain.
Shouldn't you hang a sign that says, "Don't touch"?
(They're getting curious who is in the 2nd house.)
- Let's move to the third house. - Let's go.
We're looking forward.
- Excuse me. - It must be a guest.
Please show us your foot.
- Show us your foot. - Your foot.
(Show us your foot.)
(The 3rd person shows her foot.)
(It's tanned.)
It's tanned.
It's very dark.
The foot is tanned.
Is it Beyonce?
- Beyonce? - The foot is small.
She's wearing very fancy nail polish.
- It must be a singer. - Stick out your foot farther.
As Jong Kook said, she must be a singer.
- Hyo Lyn. - I don't think so.
She's tanned.
One of the people who have a tan is...
Jo Hye Ryun.
- She has a tan. - Right.
- You're right. - You're right.
- Is it Hye Ryun? - It's her.
This foot is...
quite chubby.
- It's... - It looks heavy.
I think the person is a bit older.
It's a very small foot.
(Has Jae Seok found the answer?)
- Is it Sa Yeon? - Is it Sa Yeon?
No way.
(I'm here, boys.)
She's trying to deceive us.
Judging from her foot,
- she must be a bit older. - Exactly.
She must be at least 41 to 42 years old.
(Seok Jin takes a guess.)
(Shaking)
The foot is shaking. She's laughing.
Seok Jin said she would be 41, and she's laughing.
Aren't you 41 years old?
Let me summarize what we've been saying.
- She's a bit older. - She's older.
- She takes care of her health. - She likes to work out.
She's healthy.
Who do you think it is?
- Jo Hye Ryun. - Jo Hye Ryun.
All right. 1, 2, 3.
(The third person is Jo Hye Ryun.)
(She's laughing.)
Number 1 is So Min, number 2 is Ji Hyo,
- and number 3 is Hye Ryun. - And number 3 is Hye Ryun.
You're so good.
After hearing Hye Ryun's name, I can't think of anyone else.
- Right. - Here's the second hint.
We already have the answer.
- It's Hye Ryun. - Just to be sure.
- This time, it's sound. - Sound?
We'll let you hear their laughter.
Guess which one is the guest's.
(Number 1)
(Laughing)
- It's So Min. - I'm not sure.
- I'm not sure. - It's So Min.
Don't pretend you know.
Let's listen to number two.
Number two.
(Laughing)
- It's Ji Hyo. - It's Ji Hyo.
(I can tell from the laughter.)
- It's Ji Hyo. - Excuse me.
Don't pretend you can tell from the laughter.
We all know.
He's acting like he's close with her.
- It's Ji Hyo. - How do you know?
Let me hear number one again.
Number one.
It's So Min.
(It's So Min.)
- It's So Min. - We already knew.
- We all knew. - It's So Min.
- What is this? - Let's hear number three.
- Let's hear number three. - Guess this one right.
Let me try.
(Laughing)
It's Hyo Lyn.
- It's Hyo Lyn. - It's Hyo Lyn.
It's either Jessi or Hyo Lyn.
- It's not Jessi. - It's definitely...
- It's Hyo Lyn. - Hyo Lyn.
(Is Hyo Lyn here?)
Jong Kook talked about her dream girl two weeks ago.
What?
- Unconsciously... - What?
He likes tanned girls with thick thighs.
- That's Hyo Lyn. - No.
- Hyo Lyn! - Hyo Lyn!
(Jong Kook's dream girl was revealed.)
He likes healthy-looking women.
- Of course. I like Hyo Lyn. - We've talked about her.
Hyo Lyn is amazing.
(Hyo Lyn, are you there?)
It's time to make a final choice.
Male members,
please stand in front of the house you think the guest is in.
If more than two members choose the same house,
the female member in the house will choose the team members.
If you're not chosen,
you'll have to stand in front of another house...
to get into a team.
Should we get started?
- Okay. - Let's start.
We have no choice.
We have to go to the third house.
- We have to. - We have no choice.
Then it'll be too competitive.
The guest will choose her members.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
(I want to go to the 3rd house too.)
(Why are you hesitating?)
(The lady in the 2nd house lures Jae Seok.)
Jae Seok is being lured.
Ji Hyo and So Min are attractive,
but they're not my type.
I can seduce Jae Seok with one finger.
(I can seduce Jae Seok with one finger.)
Hey, don't be absurd.
Be careful.
(Jae Seok was confident he wouldn't fall for her.)
- Jae Seok is being lured. - Look at him.
With one finger.
- With one finger... - He's being lured.
My pride is hurt.
What are you doing?
Do you mean you can seduce me with one finger?
(Of course.)
- My goodness. - Stay here.
- Stay here. - I can't believe this.
He's been seduced.
With one finger...
Ji Hyo, you've seduced him.
I can't believe this.
(Ji Hyo seduces Jae Seok with one finger.)
- Ji Hyo. - I can't believe this.
(I'm free today.)
Jae Seok is blushing.
Okay!
(Jae Seok gives in.)
Okay, Ji Hyo.
(Jae Seok is too easy.)
Okay!
(A foot sticks out.)
What is this?
What is that?
Are you trying to...
What are you doing, So Min?
Do you want me to hold it?
Guys, come here.
So Min can do this.
Her toes are long.
- They're long. - Gosh.
Jae Seok is so easy.
You can seduce him even with your feet.
A finger...
and toes...
That foot is attractive.
(Hold it.)
(I won't hesitate.)
I'm here.
It's over now.
It's over.
Is it over?
- I was just trying to be funny. - It's over.
It's over.
- It's over. - It looks weird.
I don't even touch my wife's.
It's over.
Don't make me look weird.
- I was just trying to be funny. - It's over.
- I was just working hard. - It's over.
You held it.
You two stay there.
You have...
Se Chan, Jong Kook,
and Seok Jin here.
Is there someone you want to keep?
- Yes. - Yes?
Who is it?
Jong Kook.
(The mysterious lady chooses Jong Kook.)
- You'll fall in love today. - You'll fall in love.
You'll fall in love today.
Jong Kook.
Excuse me.
Yes?
(Do you want to say something?)
Lucky you, Jong Kook.
What?
Be quiet.
- Ma'am. - Ji Hyo, stay quiet.
(It was silly of me.)
Stay quiet.
Don't say anything. Stay quiet.
(Jae Seok sticks his head in.)
Don't say anything when it's not about you.
It's Ji Hyo. I checked.
You're not supposed to do that.
(It's definitely Ji Hyo.)
What? It's Ji Hyo.
It is Ji Hyo.
(As everyone expected, it's Ji Hyo.)
You can choose who should stay.
For example, you can say, "Seok Jin, leave."
"Se Chan, leave."
It's really okay. Tell one person to leave.
One, two, three.
(Who will be sent away?)
Bye, Se Chan.
(She bids farewell to Se Chan.)
(Happy, sad)
- I'll see you in a while. - Is she sending Se Chan away?
Is she older than me?
- Come here. - Who is it?
Se Chan, come here.
- What's with you? - Se Chan, come here.
(Ji Hyo seduces him with her finger again.)
It won't work.
She sent Se Chan away.
- All right. - Is it really Hyo Lyn?
Three teams have been formed.
- Number one... She's already out. - She's already out.
So Min.
(So Min, Kwang Soo, and Haha are a team.)
So Min, your feet are so big.
My feet are very long.
- Now... - Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo, Jae Seok, and Se Chan are a team.)
She's the finger girl.
She can seduce guys with one finger.
- She's the finger girl. - With just one finger.
Now, the third house.
- Who is it? - Is it Hyo Lyn?
I think it's Hyo Lyn.
- It'd be so funny if it's Hye Ryun. - No, it's not Hye Ryun.
- Please come out. - Please come out.
(You with tanned feet,)
(could you please come out?)
(Jong Kook's dream girl, Hyo Lyn, is here.)
Jong Kook.
(Happy)
It was Hyo Lyn.
Hyo Lyn is so nice.
- You two look great together. - They do.
- They have similar skin tones. - By the way,
Hyo Lyn once...
- danced with Gary. - You're right.
They danced together.
They were like a South American couple.
- It was an incredible dance. - Exactly.
(This dance by Hyo Lyn caused some stir.)
What's that?
(What's that?)
(They all panicked.)
(This sexy dance made many men fall in love with her.)
Since then, Jong Kook started taking interest in her.
- Is that right? - Yes. He pretends otherwise.
(He's been watching her from afar.)
Now that I have a look...
(If these two are an item...)
- You're going around with them. - What does that make me?
He's their aide.
- I get why you picked me. - He's the youngest.
He's like Sebastian.
You can order me around. I'll do everything for you.
- He's Alfred. - You can order me around.
(Is he a butler that serves this couple?)
You don't have to do anything. I'll do everything today.
- Can you get a costume for him? - He's like...
- Alfred from "Batman". - Can you get something?
When you go on a vacation, you take various items...
but you usually forget things like wet wipes.
(He's like wet wipes.)
- Don't say that to him. - Hey.
(That was mean.)
What's wrong with that? There's nothing wrong with that.
They're very important to have.
- When you go on trips... - You need them but you forget.
You guys are meaner for laughing along.
Wipes are so important.
(It's break time after selecting teams.)
It looks pretty.
- This is pretty cool. - What's so cool about it?
- It has a nice color. - It's insane.
- Okay. - It worked.
(It saved your silly face.)
(They set up an iris scanner.)
(Running Man's Global Project: Dangerous Tourist Attractions)
(The world's deadliest tourist destinations rated by bloggers)
(Global Race with new members)
(A member will go on a tour once he or she gets three Tour Stickers.)
(Which member will end up going on this dangerous tour?)
(Running Man's Global Project: Dangerous Tourist Attractions)
(They change into their team uniforms.)
(Something falls.)
- Oh, dear. It fell. - Let's get started.
(Here you go, Hyo Lyn.)
(He's taking care of her. What's going on between them?)
(Excuse me.)
Her microphone fell off.
He's so nice to her.
It fell off.
(Something's going on between these two.)
(Seok Jin is nice to her too.)
- Okay. - It fell.
(She turns down his kindness.)
- Seok Jin wanted to do it for her. - She refused him.
- Don't you usually say yes? - She pushed him away.
Don't do that to him, Hyo Lyn.
- I understand. - Women are...
He's like the wet wipes of this team.
- I'll wipe everything. - He's a tissue.
If you get something on you, please call me.
I wonder how much more he'll take this.
- He's going to blow up once. - He looks...
He looks a bit upset. Look at his face.
- Just a bit. - No, I'm okay.
- By the way, Seok Jin did get... - You're important.
- mad at me once years ago. - Because you made fun of him?
Yes, he got mad and left.
The next day, he was like, "Hi, Jae Seok."
- He forgot. - I forget easily.
I forget too easily. I forget about my enemies.
That's good. He's going to live long.
- I don't worry too much. - Exactly.
Let's get started. The first team mission is...
Running Marble Part Two.
(This is their first mission.)
(They're playing Running Marble from last week again?)
- What's that? - They brought it back.
We won't be going anywhere, right? This makes me anxious.
They took my passport.
What's this? Are we going to Thailand?
- Are we leaving again? - No way.
(Last week, they went abroad for a day.)
(Are they going to a farther destination today?)
- You know the rules, right? - Yes.
Roll the die, buy land,
and the team that goes bankrupt loses. It's simple.
The order you go is obviously important.
We'll play a simple game to decide who goes first.
It's better to go first.
In order to choose who goes first, we'll play our favorite game...
called Be Irrelevant. It's also known as Jee Seok Jin game.
Why is it called so?
- Just leave it. - His words are usually irrelevant.
He got mad last time when I told him he's irrelevant.
- He said he never was. - He wanted to play again.
You said it's Jee Seok Jin game, and he agreed.
Our staff members are great.
You know another funny thing about Seok Jin?
When I used to talk about his nose, he would call me...
- and tell me not to mention it. - Really?
He was worried that people would only talk about his nose.
Did you listen to him on his radio show?
"Hello, this is DJ Big Nose."
(This is DJ Big Nose.)
Whenever he does this,
- He's so delicate. - I get so disappointed.
- That makes me disappointed. - Exactly.
Jee Seok Jin game, it is.
Hyo Lyn may not know the rules so let me explain.
Each team has to give an irrelevant answer to my question...
three times in a row. We'll decide who goes first...
depending on which team gets the most questions.
- You can't make any sense. - Let me try it on Seok Jin.
- What do you want to eat right now? - Frogs.
- This is wrong. - You shouldn't do that.
(Why is he doing well suddenly?)
- This is wrong. - It has to make no sense.
Let me try it on Haha.
Do you have to answer as soon as you hear the question?
It has to make sense.
Did you get good grades in school?
- You don't look good in red cap. - That's it.
I don't think I'll know what to say.
It's a xylophone battle.
Shouldn't Seok Jin take it if it's his game?
- But I'm good at this. - You're good at it.
- But it's my game. - Still, you can't do anything.
- Hey. I'm a host too. - It's the truth.
- Listen to Jong Kook. - You're the old host.
- He's good at striking it. - I'm good with it.
- Go ahead. - I don't think I can do this.
Ready.
You can do it.
(Let's go, Hyo Lyn.)
Please speak up.
Ready, set, go.
- What do you want to eat right now? - Shoes.
- What is your guiding principle? - Hats.
- Can't you eat shoes? - What?
- You can't eat shoes. - You can't eat shoes.
- You can't eat shoes. - How do you eat shoes?
(He strikes the xylophone.)
- You can't eat shoes. - I had it for breakfast.
- I had it for breakfast. - It's pretty good.
- It's good. - It's great for snacking.
There are scenes in cartoons where they roast shoes.
(Goodness)
(They actually do eat shoes.)
(She cracks up.)
It's in "Mickey Mouse". There's a scene where they roast shoes.
I don't eat them often but I do sometimes.
(Fine. Forget it.)
- Let's go again. - That was good.
- We're being lenient. - Ready.
- What should I do? - You get taller from eating shoes.
What do you want to do during your free time?
- Phone. - What do you do...
- Phone? - It's wrong.
- Why? - You play with your phone.
- You want to use your phone. - You're thinking too much.
- You do play with your phone. - Exactly.
(It's great to go on your phone while you're lying in bed.)
This is so difficult.
- It makes sense. - We can't do anything.
None of it works.
What do you want to do during your free time? Red. That works.
- It works. - That does work.
- Do we get another chance? - No, stop it.
(I was just asking.)
- How many chances do you want? - I would have given it.
- You went five times. - I should have taken that.
- You'll be playing all day. - Stop it.
- That's old style. - I went too many times.
The xylophone should be given to the most generous.
That was enough.
Are you tearing up, Seok Jin?
(Are you crying?)
No, I poked myself in the eye.
- No. - Your eyes were glistening.
- Your tears were reflected. - I poked myself. I'm not crying.
- I'm strong. - Next.
- It's Jong Kook's turn. - Ready,
set, go. What do you usually lie about?
I go to an uninhabited island...
(What do you do in an uninhabited island?)
(He's flustered.)
(Hold on.)
- What do you do on an island? - Don't think.
- It makes you think. - What are you planning to do?
- Sorry? - You're so lustful.
You're cunning.
He met his ideal type.
It says island on the board.
- I just read it. - These questions are much harder.
- It's harder. - It's been upgraded.
This will be fun to play on vacation or during company dinners.
- It'll be fun. - It's difficult not to lose.
- It'll be worse when you get drunk. - You know my role model is poop?
Really?
Because of this game, my role model is poop now.
(When he was asked who his role model was, he said poop.)
(His role model has a strong scent.)
(He smells.)
You have all failed.
Seok Jin's team loses Jee Seok Jin game.
It's your turn now.
(Give me the xylophone.)
I can take care of this.
- Hey. Fine, take it all. - We shouldn't have gone first.
- We should have started with you. - Let's go.
Ready, set, go.
- What do you do on a rainy day? - I want to go to Hawaii.
- Why? - That's wrong.
(You want to go to Hawaii on a rainy day?)
- On a rainy day? Come on. - Why?
- Hey! - What was that for?
- How does that make sense? - It does.
I'd eat pancakes at home. Who would go to Hawaii?
Who eats shoes?
You can go to Hawaii on a rainy day.
I've been to Hawaii on a rainy day.
- We admit it. He's out. - I admit it.
These questions are so difficult.
- They're so difficult. - They're scary.
How do you answer that question? It has to make no sense.
- Frogs. - Red.
- Frogs. - Frogs come out on rainy days.
They're asking what you want to do.
- You can do frogs. - How?
- You can hop like a frog. - It doesn't make sense.
How does that make sense?
- Hey. - Use your hands.
Don't use both.
- How does that make sense? - Don't use all your limbs.
It doesn't make any sense.
- It does make sense. - I want to do frogs.
- It makes sense. - It does.
Frogs. It makes sense.
Whose side are you on?
- Me? - We're wearing the same color.
(We're Team Yellow.)
Look at his cap. We're wearing the same color.
(Didn't you know? Jong Kook is on Team Red too.)
- We're a team. We're one. - He's on our team.
We're one.
I see.
Ji Hyo is next.
- I have to find something. - Pay attention.
- What? - Just daydream like you always do.
Set, go.
What do you want to say to Seok Jin?
The red light came on.
What is your nickname?
You.
(Me?)
(That makes sense so that's wrong.)
- It's her nickname. - You.
(Her nickname is the Dangerous Producer.)
What was that?
- What was that, Ji Hyo? - Chang Min.
First question was fine. What was that?
Isn't the first one wrong?
- How? - Why?
- She can say that to me. - What she wants to say to you?
(It's wrong then.)
- Let's go again. - Can't you do it properly?
(Can't you do it properly?)
I did do it properly.
- What was that for? - Strike it.
- What was that? - Strike it.
- You better do good or else. - Fine.
- My gosh. - Good job.
- Should I not do anything? - You're so scary.
You should win. Somebody should win.
I can make a person ring with sounds.
(Just watch.)
- Where would it ring from? - Have you heard it before?
Once you punch someone, your ears ring.
I've heard it before.
You have to think about it. You can't think about nothing.
- Can you take over, Haha? - Sure.
(Fine, I don't want it.)
- Don't even bother. - What?
- What's wrong? - Haha's good with it.
(Look at how Haha grabs it.)
- I'm good too. - Seok Jin.
I'm good too. This is my game.
(This is Jee Seok Jin game.)
(The xylophone is mine.)
Good job.
- I think he'll get it right. - It's okay.
Let's just accept it.
- I'll pay attention. - Let's go.
This will be fine.
- Set... - I already thought of an answer.
- I analysed this. - Ready.
Set, go.
- What's in your fridge? - Paulownia tree.
Paulownia tree.
(You have a paulownia tree at home?)
- You have a paulownia tree. - It's wrong.
He has a paulownia tree.
He has a paulownia tree in his fridge.
- You have it in your fridge? - Do you?
Yesterday...
- Who has a tree in their fridge? - I have a pine tree at home.
And... Hold on.
- Answer after he finishes asking. - Give me another chance.
Fine. I got nervous.
I got nervous.
Give me another chance.
- We'll give you one more chance. - Don't be nervous.
- I was too nervous. - Ready.
(He's determined.)
Set, go.
What do you call your wife?
Oh Jung Tae.
Oh Jung Tae. It's the comedian.
(Wait. Are you talking about him?)
- This question... - Look up "Oh Jung Tae".
Oh Jung Tae.
Are you okay, Mrs. Yu?
- I... - Are you okay, Mrs. Yu?
Why did you say Oh Jung Tae?
I was going to do nouns. I had paulownia tree and Oh Jung Tae.
- Paulownia tree. - Paulownia tree and Oh Jung Tae.
I don't know how to respond.
I didn't know he'll ask me that.
- Don't worry. - This is too funny.
You call your wife Oh Jung Tae?
It's her nickname.
Six people failed so far.
- Okay. - You can do it.
Set, go.
What do you often say to your girlfriend?
Sister-in-law.
(Your girlfriend is your sister-in-law?)
Hold on.
His girlfriend is also his sister-in-law?
His girlfriend is also his sister-in-law.
Who's this sister-in-law?
- Hey. - It's not true.
- Who is it? - It's not true.
- You ungrateful... - Is it my wife?
Our wives were saying how weird you are.
- They love me so much. - Say who it is.
What are you talking about?
- It's true. - I can believe him.
You're making me look like trash.
That was your fault.
This is hard. This is so difficult.
- Ready. - Look at her eyes.
(Staring)
Go ahead.
You're playing this game.
(It's your turn.)
- She's not going to focus. - All right. Ready.
Set, go.
- How do you relieve stress? - Waterproof device.
What is your nickname?
Strict actions will be taken against smoking inside the studio.
- What is your biggest lie? - Fire hydrant.
That works.
(That was perfect.)
That worked.
- Wait. Fire hydrants? - That worked.
What is your biggest lie? Fire hydrant.
What's wrong? That works.
- Don't be so stubborn. - No way.
It doesn't make any sense.
- He keeps insisting. - Look.
Jae Seok's wife's nickname is Oh Jung Tae.
(That makes sense.)
- Hey. - Right?
It doesn't make sense that her lie is a fire hydrant.
- What was that for? - This one's right.
- What? - She got it.
So Min passes.
She's so good.
Her team came in first,
so we have to decide who goes first.
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors. - All right.
That's too ordinary.
Do you want to play this game against each other? One person each?
Okay. Hyo Lyn and Ji Hyo can play each other.
- Do I ask? - Yes.
You ask then she'll do it too.
Let's go. Hyo Lyn goes first.
Set, go.
What do you want to eat now?
I'll build you a house.
How do you feel now that Gary is married?
You.
(She says it again.)
- She doesn't know what to say. - Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo.
She said that earlier too.
(She might be cursing.)
How dare you change your number?
(Ji Hyo is flustered by Gary.)
- "You." - "You." That's all she said.
I heard the question.
Why couldn't you answer it?
- Ji Hyo. - My gosh.
You, Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo fails.)
Doesn't this remind you of the Of Course Game?
Why couldn't you answer, by the way?
- Ji Hyo, send him a video message. - You.
(Is she going to send a video message to Gary?)
Hey.
(To Gary.)
(It's been a while since she called him.)
Be happy.
(Be happy.)
(Congratulations on getting married, our dearest Gary.)
The orders have been decided.
You can start Running Marble now.
- What is she doing? - So Min.
Predict what number you're going to land on.
- I pick 5. - 5?
(Move the number of spaces on the die and buy the place you land on.)
(What country will Team So Min land on?)
You got four.
- One, two, three... - It's Thailand.
- Buy it. - 20 dollars? We'll get it.
It's Hyo Lyn's turn.
I'm really bad at this.
- You'll be fine. - Throw it.
Gold key sounds good.
- Four. - Yes. Okay.
You can move.
It's your turn, Ji Hyo.
(What will this lucky woman land on?)
- Two. - Japan.
- Let's buy it. - Buy it.
- You have thrown the die once each. - Yes.
There must be something to this.
- They're moving fast. - Are we leaving?
- Are we leaving? - No way.
Am I going to Japan again? I was there last week.
You were told to bring your passports.
(Are we going on a one-day trip again?)
I'm going to Thailand?
- It takes 5.5 hours. - It takes 6.5 hours.
These lands are not yours yet.
In order to buy these countries, you must spin a roulette...
and win the mission first.
So Hyo Lyn's team might buy it if we can't.
If each team buys two countries with the same color,
or if a team goes bankrupt, this game is over.
Two countries of the same color.
Once a team earns two countries with the same color,
the remaining team with the least number of countries loses.
If a team goes bankrupt, they lose.
One of these teams will get a Tour Sticker.
(Haha and Se Chan are in danger of going on a dangerous tour.)
(Will they leave? Or will we get new candidates today?)
Go, Haha.
- Spin the roulette. - You can do it.
- Me? - Which one do you want?
Let's go for "Cultural Experience" and get a massage.
(If they get a difficult mission, it'll be hard to buy a country.)
- Don't touch it. - I think it's moving.
- It was like this. - It's "Cultural Experience".
Hyo Lyn's next.
Food is the best.
It's food. I think we'll get it.
(Will they be able to eat?)
(They get to eat Thai food.)
- I was shocked. - It's okay.
Let's go, Ji Hyo. Food.
(What is Team Ji Hyo's mission regarding Japan?)
- "Buy an item." - Made in Japan.
There are so many things made in Japan.
You can get going and complete your missions.
(They have to complete each of their missions.)
(10 minutes before the start of mission)
You'll get going now.
Before you go, we'll play a game called...
Obtain Extra Money.
(Obtain Extra Money)
It's called Obtain Extra Money.
Are we going to play a game?
Each member gets five dollars.
You will get this amount only if all of you write this down.
- That's easy. - If you write...
the lowest amount among the three of you,
that person will receive 10 times the written amount.
What?
That member will get 10 times the written amount.
The other two...
will get the minimum amount of money.
Remaining two will get the minimum amount of money.
Let's not do this.
(Gain 5 dollars for loyalty or 10 times the money for betrayal.)
(How will the 9 members decide?)
To make it anonymous,
we will give you cell phones.
Send your name and the amount to the staff's number.
- Let's think about this. - Let's write the same amount.
We should be loyal to each other.
(They need to message their amount.)
- Write 5 dollars. - 5 dollars.
- Jae Seok. Se Chan. - Yes?
Look me in the eye.
I am not going to worry about the consequences.
- That's my decision. - Will you write the minimum amount?
There is no need to discuss the matter.
We already have the answer. All of us should write five dollars.
Let's take a selfie as a team.
The screen is very wide.
- It has high resolution. - That's right.
One, two, three.
(Let's play as a team.)
Okay.
- How nice! - It's a nice picture.
Wait a minute.
What should I write?
- Okay. - We are a team.
Don't write 50 cents.
Let's write the same amount.
- Let's write the same amount. - That's right.
Other teams will fail to unite.
- At first... - Haha.
- Pretend to listen to me at least. - All right.
- All right. - I can see...
- his head spinning. - I want to do that,
but I don't trust you two.
I will really write five dollars.
- Se Chan. - Yes?
Don't be that way.
What do you mean?
Write five dollars.
I erased what I had written down.
(The members begin to analyse each other.)
Why are you licking your lips?
- Don't be suspicious. - Why did you do that?
It wasn't anything like that. There is nothing to think about.
So why did you lick your lips?
Let's write five dollars.
- Se Chan, what was that? - Why did you lick your lips?
I did not. This cell phone has nice functions.
(The air of distrust is heavy.)
(They use the state of the art security system.)
It opened right away when I put my face in front of it.
- I will write the text. - Where do we write it?
(They send texts secretly.)
- Jong Kook... - Did he send one?
- submitted his answer. - I didn't write mine yet.
- Okay. - We are a team.
Okay, that's a good amount. I sent a text.
What should I do?
(Did they choose betrayal or loyalty?)
Look at this. It works right away.
- I unlocked it. - I can do that too.
It won't work if you use my phone.
(They check out the security system of the phone.)
- It doesn't work, right? - It's fascinating.
- Does it scan my iris? - Yes, it does.
- How many times was it? - 10 times.
Why do you need to ask that?
You are making me nervous, Haha.
I sent mine.
- I sent mine. - I think you sent it to me.
- You sent it to me. - I sent it wrong.
- Let me check your answer first. - Go ahead.
- Let me see what you wrote. - I typed in the wrong number.
- I stayed loyal. - Let me check.
"Lee Kwang Soo, five dollars".
That's my answer.
- "Lee Kwang Soo, five dollars". - That's my answer.
- Did you fake the mistake? - It was an honest mistake.
- He is cool. - You still doubt me.
No, I believe you.
(Everyone sent their answers for the secret emergency fund.)
(The result for Ji Hyo's team is revealed.)
This team is loyal.
Ji Hyo wrote...
five dollars.
- Of course, I did. - You did.
Se Chan wrote...
one dollar.
(Se Chan wrote 1 dollar.)
I can't believe you.
I had no choice. I am in no position to take chances.
- This is too much. - I had no choice.
How can you deviate when we promised to write five dollars?
I have two Tour Stickers.
Jae Seok wrote...
65 cents.
(Jae Seok wrote 65 cents.)
For goodness' sake.
I can't believe you.
- I was desperate. - I knew...
he would do that when he licked his lips.
- I will get 65 cents. - At least...
I had a semblance of conscience.
All three members...
submitted different amounts.
All of us would've gotten five dollars...
- had we remained loyal. - I knew this would happen.
The person who wrote the minimum amount is...
- Hyo Lyn. - What was the amount you wrote?
What was the amount you wrote?
What happened? Did I write the minimum amount?
Does that mean I get 10 times the amount?
You will get 10 times the amount.
(She is joyful.)
She betrayed us.
- It's not like that. - Hyo Lyn...
wrote three dollars.
- Three dollars? - I can't believe you.
Hyo Lyn will get 30 dollars,
and you two will get three dollars each.
Haha wrote...
- 3 dollars and 90 cents. - For goodness' sake.
(I knew you would do that.)
Where did 90 cents come from?
- That's too much. - Where did 90 cents come from?
- That's too much. - Let's wait and see.
You could have written a smaller amount.
Secondly, So Min wrote...
50 cents.
Do you call yourself human?
- 50 cents. - Do you call yourself human?
You wanted to get five dollars.
I don't understand.
Why did you write 50 cents?
What's 10 times the amount?
- You wanted to get 5 dollars. - You will get 5 dollars.
You could have written down five dollars.
I don't trust you.
She doesn't want to give us that money.
You shouldn't have said anything.
Why are you laughing?
This is a ridiculous situation.
The last one is Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo wrote...
- 50 cents. - Forget it.
(Forget it. We are all the same.)
I wrote the same amount.
The two of them are the same.
I had my reasons.
In conclusion, Haha will get 50 cents...
while So Min and Kwang Soo will get five dollars each.
(The teams receive their results.)
It couldn't be helped. Everyone is on his or her own.
(Ji Hyo's team, Hyo Lyn's team, and So Min's team)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Running Marble starts.)
We are leaving.
It will be tasty.
- What should we eat? - Where should we go?
- Let's go to Itaewon. - Itaewon.
- Itaewon would be the best. - Is there a restaurant you know?
We can go to Suk Chun's restaurant.
- Shall we go there? - That would be for the best.
Which Japanese product shall we buy?
- Let's look it up. - That's a good idea.
When you press this, it shows nearby shops.
There it is. You see the button for shopping, right?
- There it is. - I see it.
- You see it, right? - This is incredible.
How about we go to a stationery store?
- That's a good idea. - A stationery store is good.
- Let's go. - My goodness.
(They leave for a stationery store nearby.)
Let's go to a stationery store...
and get a Japanese product first.
Let's do that.
(While Hyo Lyn's team and Ji Hyo's team are advancing...)
- Let's divide it evenly. - Play rock, paper, scissors.
- Okay. - Let's divide it evenly.
- Let's divide it evenly. - Let's do that for now.
- If we lose, - Let's take a look.
give me 5 dollars and give him 10 dollars, okay?
(1st place gets 70 dollars. 2nd and 3rd places get 40 dollars.)
I can't believe you.
Okay. I can't believe you wrote down 50 cents.
They can't pull off a big scam.
Right?
We won five dollars.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors. The winner gets more slots.
Okay. Winner gets eight slots.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
(So Min comes last.)
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Okay.
(Kwang Soo comes first place.)
My goodness.
(I don't know why this is so annoying.)
- This is so annoying. - He is annoying.
I don't want Kwang Soo to win.
- Please. - Let's do this.
Can you give me one slot?
(Please give me a slot.)
- What? - Can you give me a slot?
I will be good to you.
Please give me a slot.
Sorry, I wrote everything down.
(He doesn't give So Min a chance.)
I have five slots.
I need to do well.
All right.
(So Min only has 3 slots.)
The winner will get 70 dollars.
(The winner will get 70 dollars.)
This is for first place.
(Who will the roulette decide?)
The probability...
(Kwang Soo wins.)
(It's an unexpected win for an unlucky man.)
I will win today.
I am first place in my team.
Then I will get five dollars more.
- It's in the packet. - Really?
Is my 50 cents in the packet?
(Haha was the victim of the 50-cent duo.)
You are quite thorough.
(It's the betrayers versus the trickster.)
(What will become of this team?)
I haven't been to Itaewon often.
Hyo Lyn, your feet are very small.
I know.
- What's your shoe size? - Well...
Is it 225mm?
- I wear 225mm or 230mm. - I knew it.
Your feet are very small.
Your feet are very small for your height.
It's the right size for my height.
I am pretty short.
- Your height? - You look tall.
Men don't like tall women.
- Don't be ridiculous. - Men don't like tall women.
- You are wrong. - It's true. They really don't.
Jong Kook is the same.
He is right. I don't like tall women.
Women who are tall don't seem like women to me.
(He likes petite women...)
(like me.)
What is your ideal type?
- Me? - Yes.
(Listening)
I like men...
who are dependable.
That's the type of men I like.
(He makes the most dependable facial expression.)
There are people who get along.
That's right.
Do you go to a tanning salon every day?
- No. - Do you go once a week?
I go to a warm country.
I love warm countries. This is what I do when I go there.
As soon as I wake up,
I soak up the sun...
and lounge at the swimming pool.
- I do that no matter what. - I am the same.
- I don't come out of the water. - That's right.
I am like a seal.
When I get tired, I take a nap under the sun.
You like water.
I like water.
I like water, too.
(Whatever Hyo Lyn likes,)
(Jong Kook likes.)
(There is a scent of spring between them.)
Listen.
Let's move as one...
- for this mission. - That's right.
There is no reason to distrust each other now.
This is clean.
I figured out how your minds work.
I was very surprised by 50 cents.
However, I feel better...
because you aren't fit for a big scam.
It consoles me.
- I am serious. - Don't look down on us.
It's cute.
I didn't think anyone would write 50 cents.
Me neither.
I just wanted to receive my share.
Me too. I wanted to receive five dollars.
I understand you perfectly.
- I know that you're a good person. - Right?
You are innocent.
- I had no bad intentions at all. - I could feel that...
- What a load of nonsense. - you didn't want to harm anyone...
- Whatever. - after hearing what you wrote.
You guys seem to get along very well.
Keep living like this and you'll become very successful.
- We'll be really successful. - Right.
- I can't disagree with that. - Me neither.
Your apartment will be at least 126m.
- I agree. - Me too.
We'll be able to save up a lot of money.
But I also feel like we could end up in prison.
- It's okay. You guys play safe. - Do you think so?
You can go to prison on behalf of me.
I'll make sure our money's safe and sound.
(So Min plans their future quite meticulously.)
What? I know what kind of a person you are.
You'll be gone by the time I get out.
Right? I know you very well.
You need to trust me.
She is unbelievable.
She wants you to go to prison on behalf of her.
(This is only the beginning of their betrayal.)
This is a fight between ourselves.
(Who are they betraying each other for?)
(It will be the biggest...)
(war of betrayal in the history of Running Man.)
(They also start carrying out their missions.)
(Running Man has become more global.)
(Running Marble has become more diverse.)
(A global world will unfold...)
(at the places we know best.)
(They'll find a connection to many places of the world in the city.)
(The only thing they can trust is the die.)
(It's an unexpected global mission in the city.)
(Who will be the chosen one to go to the Dangerous Tourist Attraction?)