(Hongye Park, Chungcheong Province)
- Hello. - Hello.
(It's a beautiful spring day.)
Look at the sun. The weather is fantastic.
It's a sunny day in Chungcheong Province.
(Welcome to South Chungcheong Province.)
- We're at Chungcheong Province. - I love Chungcheong Province!
- It's been a while since we came. - It feels great to be here.
- This is great. - I'm so excited.
Today, Ji Hyo isn't here with us.
- You're right. - I feel like we're going to be...
- doing a couple game today. - I think so too.
- My heart is fluttering. - We might pair up with actors.
- I can see some vans over there. - It's been a while.
We haven't done this in a while, so we should give it a go.
- I wonder who's here. - It's the popular Choi Tae Joon.
- Oh, it's Tae Joon! - Tae Joon is here!
(It's prince charming, Choi Tae Joon.)
(We invited the hottest actor to balance out the gender ratio.)
- It's nice to see you. - Hi.
- How have you been? - It's good to see you.
- Hey. - Tae Joon came on the show...
a couple years ago as a guest. How long ago was it?
- It was around two years ago. - That's right.
- It was cold back then too. - There were other male guests.
- He got eliminated really quickly. - Yes, I did.
(The sad memory comes back.)
(He appeared on the show as a passionate rookie guest.)
(But sadly, he got eliminated as soon as the game started.)
I heard that we're going to be doing a couple game today.
I really want to pair up with Ji Hyo.
- I see. - That's really great.
- Thanks. - I wish you all the best.
- Thank you. - If he pairs up with Ji Hyo...
It's okay. Ji Hyo's a pretty good player.
Let me tell you guys a little bit about Tae Joon.
- He's great at imitating people. - Really?
- Try imitating Lee Sun Gyun. - People refrain from imitating...
Sun Gyun outside because the wind makes it hard for us to hear them.
It's hard, but let's give it a go.
"Hey, Joon Hyuk. You're not the only doctor here. I'm a doctor too."
- He's good. - He sounds similar, right?
- That was great. - He sounds exactly like him.
(Glancing)
Excuse me, but can you stop looking over there when we're all...
- trying to focus on Tae Joon? - I just can't wait.
- What's wrong with you? - I'm curious of who's left to come.
- My goodness. - Ji Hyo will be Tae Joon's partner.
Let me introduce our other guests who will be joining us today.
- Come on out. - Who are you?
(She's the princess of Running Man, Song Ji Hyo.)
Hey, get rid of that frown.
(Dancing while frowning)
- Did the cold make you go mad? - It's seriously so cold today.
- I thought she was Um Hong Gil. - It's really cold, isn't it?
- Are you... - I thought you were Um Hong Gil.
Ji Hyo, you look like a top celebrity today.
(Why is Um Hong Gil here instead of our princess, Ji Hyo?)
- She looks... - Stop it, you guys.
- Stop it. - I'm really serious.
- Ji Hyo. - I'm not joking right now.
- No, I'm just... - Tae Joon, she's not your partner.
- Hello. - Come over here.
- She's not your partner yet. - No, come over here.
- He's not your partner yet. - Why?
- I told you he's not your partner. - Let me work with someone new too.
- Move aside, Jae Seok. - Ji Hyo. Come here.
- Ji Hyo. - She's forceful as always.
Why don't we bring in the next guest? Please come on out.
Come on out.
(Who is the real princess they've been waiting for?)
It's Jeon So Min.
(Jeon So Min, Princess Aurora)
- Nice to see you, So Min. - Hello.
- I haven't seen you for ages. - Have you been well?
- She was Kwang Soo's partner. - Beer, beer!
- She was paired up with him. - She became so pretty.
(She was Kwang Soo's partner.)
(So Min desperately asked for beer in the morning 3 years ago.)
(They performed well as the crazy couple with her unique charms.)
- Did you two work well together? - We did.
- Was she your love interest? - No.
It was the first time I didn't have a love interest in a couple race.
It hurts my feelings. Perhaps, you don't like me.
No, we are just colleagues.
So Min. What are you up to these days?
I'm not doing anything.
Is that so?
- So Min... - Are you just drinking beer?
- She's straightforward and blunt. - It's nice.
Which brings me to say this. To all the directors in Korea,
I'd like to say I am worth your money.
(I am Jeon So Min, the cost-effective actor.)
(It's a culture shock.)
- Stop it, So Min. - Please cast me.
- Please stop it. - I will work hard.
- Work hard on our program. - What's wrong with you?
So Min.
- You're the talk of the town. - Why?
What she did was...
she made a choreography and named it herself.
What is the choreography?
It's called Old Lady Dance.
She uploaded a video of this dance.
You garnered a lot of attention from many viewers, right?
- I wouldn't say a lot though. - I don't know what it is.
(It's all very new to them.)
- I've never heard of it. - I keep up with the news.
- We can watch her dance. - Go home if you will be mean.
- Go home if you plan to misbehave. - Have you seen it?
No. I haven't!
I'm going to see it now!
(So shut it!)
This is the Old Lady Dance which will be the talk of the town soon.
- Can you show us the dance? - Isn't it so sudden? Now?
- Yes, please show us now. - In 1, 2.
- In 1, 2, 3, 4. - In 1, 2, 3, 4.
(She reveals the dance without any music.)
(Cute)
So Min.
(She dances hard.)
I don't think viewers will like this.
- She became crazier. - So Min.
How can you say she's crazier? Please watch your tongue.
I mean she became more unique.
All right. We will bring in the third guest now.
- It's very cold today. - Come on out.
(Isn't this "Ah-Choo" by Lovelyz?)
It's Lee Se Young!
She's Lee Se Young.
(Welcome. It's Se Young of Ah-Choo Couple!)
She's Lee Se Young of Ah-Choo Couple.
(She played a role of Princess Cheongseon in a historical drama.)
- She turned into a lady. - It's been ages.
She got popular while being a cute couple with Hyun Woo in a drama.
- "Ah-Choo" was their theme song. - There was a song about the couple.
- I'm happy to have you join us. - She starred on the drama.
- Who is feeling cold the most? - Who is it?
- Someone's in a short sleeve shirt. - It's Kang Han Na.
(She's wearing a short sleeve shirt in this cold weather?)
(Stop talking and get on with the show.)
Then I should call her in right away. Hold on.
- Come on out. - Let's see who she is.
- How can she wear that? - It's so cold to wear that.
(While everyone was chatting,)
(she was freezing. Who is this princess?)
- She's not in a short sleeve shirt. - That's not a short sleeve shirt.
- She's wearing it inside. - I see.
It's Kang Han Na.
(She played the role of a mean princess on a drama last year.)
(She's wearing a summer outfit.)
Goodness, she's pretty.
She is beautiful in person.
(She is the prettiest in the world.)
It is a see-through jacket.
- There's nothing underneath. - Aren't you too cold?
When my stylist gave me this, she said it was a spring jacket.
You might not know, but she used to do ballet.
- Really? - That explains.
- Isn't that true? - It is.
I learned it for about 9 or 10 years.
- You learned it for 9 years? - Goodness.
In 1, 2...
She can't start dancing like this. You're not cultured enough.
- You don't know anything. - He's really unsophisticated.
- You know nothing about culture. - "Culture"?
(He's too uneducated.)
- I'll make this short. - Sure.
It's nothing to brag about.
You did it for 9 years.
(Her feet position looks professional.)
- Amazing. - How did she do that?
- Are your feet okay? - Yes, they are fine.
I should hurry. Hold on.
You seem to talk to yourself a lot.
- It's hard to do it without music. - It could've been over by now.
- I'll hurry. - Okay.
(She starts in a rush.)
(She moves like an elegant and graceful bird.)
- Her posture is great. - It looks like she's experienced.
But she's a bit stiff.
(He criticizes her.)
(She goes back to her spot in a hurry.)
- Why did you say that? - I'm sorry.
I thought you two were a couple.
- Are you two vets? - What's going on?
- Do you work at the animal shelter? - You two look like vets.
- You know nothing about culture. - It's a culture shock indeed.
- He knows nothing about the arts. - It's a culture shock for me.
- Let's bring in the next guest. - She's the last guest, right?
(It's time to meet the fifth princess.)
(The foul-mouthed princess from a film "Sunny" has come.)
- It's Park Jin Joo. - Hey, Jin Joo.
Swear at us. Please!
Jin Joo is joining us today.
(She's an expert in acting.)
- It's nice to meet you. - This is nice.
- Her outfit is suitable for today. - Yes. I feel happy about it.
- You are? - Yes.
She starred on a film "Sunny". You all watched it, right?
- She was amazing. - Her character was foul-mouthed.
- Her role left an impression on us. - She was great.
First of all, please swear at us.
(He requests her to swear at him although they just met.)
- Swear at Jae Seok. - Yes, please.
- Are you okay with this? - Yes.
- We just met. - That's all right.
- I'll try then. - Okay.
Hey, you. Which bakery...
are you from, you loaf of bread.
(Bread turns into a swearing word instantly.)
I got it.
(He's about to lose his mind.)
She said, "You loaf of bread."
(Thank you for your witty swearing.)
She's amazing. I also heard she sings well.
Can you sing us a song?
- I will sing "Onara". - She'll sing "Onara".
It's a great weather for the song.
This song is suitable for a day like this.
Please sing us the song.
Come here
Are you coming?
- She's really amazing. - Are you going for good?
(She sings the best she can.)
- Han Na. Do the ballet now. - I'll stop here.
(Stopping)
She was about to do it.
- Han Na. - I wasn't going to.
- You went like this. - It can be a song for ballet.
They could have had a joint performance.
Wait. Can you dance like that too?
- You can also do popping dance. - I thought you did ballet.
You can do this.
- How disappointing. - I wanted to see it.
This was Jin Joo.
(Welcome, Jin Joo.)
The last guest remains.
- She must have waited for long. - There's another guest?
Please come on out.
It's Um Ji.
(Um Ji of Gfriend, the hottest idol group, visits.)
- She's dancing. - She's in Gfriend.
(I will steal Running Man members' hearts.)
She doesn't look startled at all.
(This cute choreography will melt the cold wave.)
(Um Ji of Gfriend)
- Um Ji of Gfriend is joining us. - Hey, Um Ji.
(Um Ji has returned with a new song.)
Everyone is a princess. Um Ji is a princess by her name.
- She's Thumbelina. - She is.
We have six guests joining us today.
(We'd like to welcome 6 princesses and 1 prince.)
We need to choose our partner.
How will we choose our partner?
The mission that will determine your partner is called "My Lovely Face".
The female members will draw...
your own self-portrait for 10 seconds.
The male members will look...
- at the portraits. - We'll choose a portrait?
- You can pick a portrait you like. - We have to pick.
- I see. - This is nice.
- You have 10 seconds. - I'm sorry,
but couldn't you include your outfit in the portrait?
- Draw a hat if you're wearing one. - Draw your hat.
You can draw however you want.
(They are ready.)
I'm nervous. Why am I nervous for this?
Get ready.
(Today's partner depends on this self-portrait.)
10 seconds are way too short.
Can we draw it in 10 seconds?
Set.
(The mission starts.)
(They are serious.)
- Draw your hat! - Seven.
(Princess Ji Hyo, please draw your hat for Tae Joon.)
(Can someone shut him up?)
(I will put my soul into this portrait.)
- Two. - Your hat!
(They draw until the last second.)
Time is up.
(How will their portraits look?)
- Where's the hat? - How will we know with these?
Do we have someone that looks like this portrait?
(Did someone who looks like this join us today?)
Who drew this flower?
Isn't this Hong Gil?
- This is... - I want Ji Hyo as my partner.
- This is Ji Hyo's. - Really?
- This has to be hers. - No, that is not Ji Hyo's portrait.
- I think this is Jin Joo's. - I see. It looks like Jin Joo's.
- This has to be Ji Hyo's. - She can't draw like this.
- No one looks like this. - I'm certain this is Ji Hyo's.
(Tae Joon chooses the drawing of flower.)
- I will choose this flower. - That has to be Ji Hyo's portrait.
- Who drew this? - This is...
Wait. You grabbed one.
- Once you grab it, it's done. - You chose that.
Hold on to it.
- I'll choose this one. - Are you certain?
- I have a good feeling about this. - Hurry.
(They are done choosing the portraits.)
Do you want to switch? This is your last chance.
(They are excited.)
I won't switch.
(Current status of the selection of the portraits)
Haha, step forward.
- Reveal it when I count to three. - It's a really nice drawing.
- In 1, 2, 3. - It looks like Jin Joo.
(It's a round, cute face. Is it Jin Joo's portrait like Seok Jin said?)
Everyone can guess this is Jin Joo's portrait.
(It's Jin Joo.)
It really is Jin Joo.
- I wanted her. - We'll survive.
Next up is Kwang Soo.
I can't wait to find out.
- Who is it? - I think I know.
- I'm curious. - This is so fun.
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
Who is it?
(Whose drawing is it?)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Who is Kwang Soo's princess?)
Is it So Min again?
(It's her again.)
(She cries in sorrow.)
- What's wrong? - That's so mean.
What's wrong, So Min?
You don't know how charming I am.
Listen, So Min.
Aren't you happy you're partners again?
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
With whom do you want to be partners?
I wanted Han Na too.
(He wanted someone else.)
(The worst couple is forced to get back together.)
That's hilarious.
We have no choice.
It's good.
I look forward to this couple today.
- You look good together. - They don't like each other.
All women tense up as Seok Jin steps forward.
(Everyone is tense.)
This isn't the final round.
(Each one has a 25-percent chance.)
Just wait.
It's 1 of the 4. Just wait.
Who will it be?
In 1, 2, 3.
Let's see.
- It's this. - Whose is it?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Their eyes quiver.)
(They hesitate and get flustered.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 2, 3.
(She walks forward slowly.)
- You startled me. - It's Han Na.
Their outfits match.
Our outfits?
(They have matching jackets.)
She looks so unhappy.
She denied that it was her drawing at first.
She hesitated at first.
Han Na looked at me right now.
Wasn't she asking Ji Hyo to step forward instead?
(She asks Ji Hyo for help.)
By the way...
- They look uncomfortable. - It sparkles.
Next is Jong Kook.
(Who will be Jong Kook's partner?)
I'm in trouble.
(His heart starts to beat fast.)
- No way. - In 2, 3.
Is it her in the middle?
That's right.
(Who drew a face with a big smile?)
Three.
(Jong Kook and Se Young become a couple.)
They're like an uncle and his niece.
I was so startled.
- This is great. - Right now,
many of you aren't happy with your partners.
It's very obvious who drew this.
- Why do you say that out loud? - Isn't it Um Ji?
Isn't it Um Ji?
Isn't it obvious?
Tae Joon recognized Ji Hyo's.
- He was right. - That's good.
- I hope I'm right. - Let's see.
(A man waits for her while holding a flower.)
Ji Hyo?
(Is this your flower, Ji Hyo?)
- I hope I'm right. - Let's see.
(Ji Hyo's flower blooms.)
Um Ji.
You're prettier than this flower.
Thank you. You're the best.
I heard it's Couple Race today.
I came here because I wanted to be your partner.
(He meets his princess.)
(The members are divided into couples.)
You're divided into couples.
Today's mission is Cheapskate Couple Race.
(Cheapskate Couple Race)
- This is great. - Cheapskate Couple Race?
The couple with the most money left...
will be the final winner.
Each female member will pick an envelope.
There's an amount from 10 to 60 dollars...
in each envelope.
- 60 dollars? - Really?
There's an amount from 10 to 40 dollars...
in the male members' bags.
- Also, - How much?
the envelope's amount times two.
(It's twice as much as what the woman has.)
It could divide the amount by two.
(It's half of what the woman has.)
- Divide what the woman has by two? - Right.
If you divide 10 dollars in half, it's 5 dollars.
- I'm very frugal. - Really?
Did you hear what Um Ji said?
"I'm very frugal."
(Don't worry, Jae Seok.)
It means she's confident.
Jin Joo.
You're popular these days.
- Hurry and pick one. - Trust your instinct.
- Jin Joo? - She picked that one.
(Each woman picks an envelope.)
Okay.
- Which one do you want? - This one.
(So Min picks 60 dollars.)
- Let's eat delicious food. - Don't make it obvious.
Don't make it obvious.
(Han Na picks 50 dollars.)
Is there anything else?
(Se Young picks 40 dollars.)
(Jin Joo picks 30 dollars.)
That's good.
- This is enough, Ji Hyo. - It's okay.
(Um Ji picks the least amount.)
Let's not tell them.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Let's go. - This is more important.
(Men's choice will determine their fate.)
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's go. - I pick this.
I pick this one.
(They choose randomly.)
Why would we play rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's pick again. - Come here.
I pick this one.
- You can't do that. - I didn't look inside.
Is this good?
We should play rock-paper-scissors.
Why should we?
- Why? - We should.
- Why? - Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
(Such reaction only means one thing.)
(He picked dividing by two.)
- Did you pick division? - Why don't we play it?
You picked division.
(He becomes poor in an instant.)
Let's start our first round.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Which couple will make the most out of it?)
Let's go.
Here we go.
(These are current amounts each couple has.)
- Let's eat delicious food. - Seriously.
Let's eat something delicious.
What's going on here?
It looks like a karaoke machine.
Jin Joo would be the best.
- Jin Joo? - This is the first round.
It's "Couple Karaoke".
("Couple Karaoke")
The winner will be determined by your singing scores.
There are bonus scores.
Choose 1 of 6 money sacks.
While you sing,
count the amount of money in the sack.
- While singing? - Yes.
If you count the amount accurately,
you get 50 additional points to your singing score.
- 50? - That's a lot.
Do we get the money?
No, you have to return it.
Don't you have enough money?
- Us? - Do you need more?
No, we have enough.
(He doesn't admit it.)
We have enough.
- I feel rich as I'm with Jong Kook. - Of course.
Even if we live in a small studio,
- we can be happy. - That's nonsense.
Stop joking around.
Be careful.
- I'm happy. - Stop joking.
Let's start "Couple Karaoke" right away.
(The mission starts.)
May I drink water?
- There are shrimp chips. - Yes, you may.
Can we eat shrimp chips?
We need a high score.
- Han Na. - Yes?
Which song do you sing?
(They plan to make it exciting.)
Let's determine the order.
Are we playing rock-paper-scissors again?
No, we're tired of that.
- Han Na suggested flipping hands. - No, I didn't.
Han Na suggested we play flipping hands.
- I think she used to play a lot. - Flipping hands?
She mentioned flipping hands.
Do you know what flipping hands is?
Isn't it face up or down?
Face up or down?
We call it flipping hands in my neighborhood.
What about you, Jin Joo?
- It's called sseulmano. - What?
- Sseulmano. - What's that?
Sseulmano, whatever you want, put your hand out
- What? - Did you make that up?
- What was that? - Did you make it up?
Did you live in Japan?
Usually it goes, "Face up or down".
- Flipping hands - Flipping hands
Are all of you from Seoul?
Can you say it again, Jin Joo?
Sseulmano, whatever you want, put your hand out
"Put your hand out"?
It sounds Russian.
- This is how I played it. - How about you, Tae Joon?
- Flipping hands - How about you, Ji Hyo?
Me too.
What about you, Jong Kook?
- It was up to me. - Flipping hands
- What do you mean? - I divided the teams.
You did?
"You're on this team, you're on that team."
(She's impressed.)
I bet that was so much fun.
(He was the boss.)
- That's cruel. - He's the best.
How about you, Kwang Soo?
Flipping hands and hands
(Hands and hands?)
(The extra word is the key.)
- No way. - I'm being serious.
- Stop it. - Kwang Soo.
- Stop lying. - Go away.
- Go away, Kwang Soo. - Ask my friends.
- "Flipping hands and hands"? - That sounds strange.
I'm not lying.
(Running Man respects every culture.)
Anyone can make it up.
Face up's and down's
(How about this one?)
(Do you like the dance with it?)
- What are you doing? - You can make it.
You can make it easily.
Face up's and down's
(He can come up with 100.)
(They determine the order by drawing lots.)
(Tae Joon and Ji Hyo go first.)
We'll sing "Hawaiian Couple".
- That's a good song. - Does the song go like this?
- It's a cute song. - It's "Hawaiian Couple".
- I love this song. - It's a great song.
I like it.
Was the title "Hawaiian Couple"?
- It's a good song. - Aloha.
- Aloha. - Aloha.
- Mahalo. - Mahalo.
(He starts dancing.)
(You're cute)
You're cute when you smile
(You're so cute, my lover)
(You're handsome)
(The song is very sweet.)
(Se Young gets into a trance.)
(Every joint in her body dances.)
Show us your powerful dance.
(Show us your dance.)
(The idol singer's dance is different.)
Come on, Han Na.
(Han Na starts to dance.)
(She swings her legs.)
(She moves her feet.)
Good job.
(She dances like a pretty man.)
Look at her.
(She dances like a robot.)
(So Min shows how to do popping.)
(She shows off her talent and can't control her excitement.)
Next is Jin Joo.
(She dances like a b-boy.)
(She keeps it cool until the end.)
Come on, Um Ji. You can do it too.
(Is this a dance competition?)
(She swings her arms like a windmill.)
You can do it, Han Na.
That's right.
- Go. - Let's go.
- Here comes Jin Joo. - Go.
(I'm the best dancer here.)
- Jin Joo! - Go!
(It's a mess.)
Get out of my way!
(Get out of my way!)
(Ji Hyo and Tae Joon finally get the money sack.)
Hey!
That was great.
- Great job! - Do it again later.
Just dance, everyone.
(They have to count the money accurately.)
(My performance is not over yet.)
- That's amazing. - Um Ji, dance with her.
Do the wave.
(The princesses wave together.)
(Roll it...)
(and toss it.)
(Bouncing)
(The old man is here again.)
Great job, Um Ji.
(While the team is counting the money...)
(and singing,)
(the dance competition goes on.)
- You're doing great! - What's that?
(She sacrifices her bottom.)
(Her joints are not cooperating.)
- What's that? - Nice!
(Stiff)
(It looks more like gymnastics.)
You're so cute and sexy.
(The dance battle comes to an end.)
Distract them!
(They're losing concentration.)
- It's almost over. - Six, eight...
- They should follow the rules. - 10, 12...
- You dropped some. - 12...
(What is this?)
Good job.
It's over now.
I thought it was "Gayo Stage".
- It was like a night club. - Ji Hyo, Tae Joon.
- Thank you. - We had so much fun.
We had a lot of fun.
I didn't expect this song to excite us so much.
- I didn't expect it either. - I didn't know.
(Their score is 83.)
- Tell us. - 53 dollars and 34 cents.
- Wrong. - All right.
- How much was it? - It was 58 dollars and 74 cents.
You were right about the four cents.
We didn't distract you so much.
- We didn't? - We didn't.
I'm looking forward to Haha's team's performance.
- It's not that. - Let's go.
- It's "I Cheated". - They look great together.
- They're both great singers. - They look good together.
- Pick up your microphone. - Jin Joo is an amazing singer.
- Jin Joo is a great singer. - She is.
(Many are looking forward to their performance.)
(Can you really handle our performance?)
(Are you ready to have fun?)
(Here we go.)
(Let's go.)
(Here comes rapper Haha.)
(He's owning the stage.)
(I'm on fire)
(Burning with passion)
(The atmosphere heats up)
(We're on fire right now)
(Look at us.)
(This is teamwork.)
(We're the real scene stealers.)
- We didn't plan this. - Did you practice?
(They show off their teamwork.)
- I'm sorry, Mom - Mom
(The money sack is handed over.)
(Will they be good at multitasking?)
(We're a bit busy)
(We're not sure if we have time to count the money.)
(Laughing)
We can't stop laughing
- We have to do this. - I'm on fire
(They're making an X-sign with their bodies.)
- They don't miss anything. - That was so random.
I'm on fire
(It might go viral.)
How can you have such great teamwork?
(Here comes the climax.)
- Here we go. - Go.
(It's Saturday night)
(Let's have some fun)
(She has an amazing voice.)
- She's an amazing singer. - She's amazing.
(Jin Joo owns the stage.)
(They have a party in the middle of counting money.)
(It doesn't get better than this.)
(They show off their incredible stage presence.)
Let's fly
(We're the best duo.)
(It was amazing.)
- Let's find out the result. - We didn't distract them.
That was amazing.
- They got 81 points. - They got 81 points.
How much is the money?
It's about 39 dollars.
- Just take a guess. - Take a guess.
- One, two... - Say it's 39 dollars and 72 cents.
About 4 dollars and 70 cents?
- Say it's 42 dollars. - It's 43 dollars and 70 cents.
- Your answer is wrong. - Thank you.
(They leave the stage after giving an amazing performance.)
- They sang so well. - There was 5 more cents here.
We're going to sing, "All for You".
(It's Jong Kook and Se Young's turn.)
- Go, Jong Kook. - Go, Jong Kook.
(The girls are getting excited.)
- It's so romantic. - I've never listened to...
the original version.
(Se Young is worried because she doesn't know it well.)
(Jong Kook is by her side.)
Start from the right side.
(Will they have good teamwork?)
- Start from the right side. - What are we doing?
One, two...
- Two, three, four... - It's already been days
(Se Young starts to sing carefully.)
- Is this Cool's song? - Yes.
(Rubbing)
- Stop pushing me. - I'm just dancing.
(They start the distraction.)
We're dancing over here.
(Careful)
I can see that Han Na used to be a ballerina.
(Her dance moves are extraordinary.)
- Han Na. - I can see it.
(We'll mimic her.)
Look at Ji Hyo and Tae Joon.
(The love song is bringing the couples together.)
(It's time to count the money.)
(The song is slow. We can do this.)
(They're counting the money to the beat of the song.)
Seriously.
- It's 59 dollars and... - It's 59 dollars...
- You said it's 60 dollars at first. - It's not.
- Stop. - 50 cents...
- 50 cents... - You have to stop now.
You got 82 points. How much is the money?
It's 59 dollars and 57 cents.
(Their performance got a pretty high score.)
(Did they count accurately?)
Correct.
It's correct.
- We did a good job. - In addition, they got 82 points.
(They get 50 extra points.)
(They're so good.)
The distraction will get worse and worse.
- It was too much. - You have to get used to it.
We have no choice.
- We'll sing, "Say Hello". - Kwang Soo likes these songs.
I'm not sure this song will help.
("Say Hello" by Byul)
I'll do an arm bar on you.
(Please don't.)
Be prepared.
(Focused)
(Stop it.)
So Min must like this song.
(We've broken up before)
- She's a good singer. - This is nice.
(This is nice.)
She's a good singer.
(So Min has an attractive voice.)
It sounds like an soundtrack.
She's too close to the microphone.
(Next to her is...)
(We now know)
This is not too bad.
(The man kneels down in front of his microphone.)
(The microphone pops up.)
(This is too much.)
(The song nears its climax.)
- What about the next team? - Now
(Even if we love each other)
(We should stop)
This is nice.
(The microphone drops.)
(It doesn't work.)
I'm allowed to do this much, right?
(The team doesn't give in.)
(They show off their dissonance.)
Why does he try to sing in harmony when it never works?
(It's not only the microphone's fault.)
(Kwang Soo has to follow his microphone.)
(His microphone never stays in the same position.)
(There's no chance we'll get a high score.)
(In the midst of chaos, the money sack is handed over.)
(She shakes the sack...)
(and drops it.)
Look at that.
- It's 50 cents. - If you lose it, it's over.
- A coin fell through the gap. - It did?
- It fell through the gap. - It was a 50-cent coin.
- It was 50 cents. - A coin fell through the gap.
(They have a hard time keeping up with the song.)
- It was a coin. - It was 50 cents.
(They're in chaos.)
(Count pieces of paper instead.)
(Focus on singing.)
(We'll count the money for you.)
Count it.
(Wait.)
(This is such a clever way.)
(They distract the team in so many ways.)
(So Min never gives up.)
(Let's smile and say hello)
This is so much!
I want to kill everyone!
(The beauty has turned into a beast.)
- This is too much. - She wants to kill us all.
- What? - What did you say?
- Who are you? - Count it.
This is 5 dollars. I have 6 more dollars in my pocket.
It's 5 dollars and 12 cents.
- It's... - You can't count it now.
Stop it.
(Give me a chance to count it.)
- What are you doing? - You can't do that.
(Their score is 78.)
- It's 29 dollars and... - It's 29 dollars and 62 cents.
- 29 dollars and 62 cents? - It must be wrong.
(Despite all the difficulties,)
(will they manage to win extra points?)
Wrong.
- What's the difference? - The difference was just 50 cents.
- It fell through the gap. - Exactly.
- Was it true? - I told you so.
- Was it true? - I was telling the truth.
- We told you. - I didn't believe him.
- It did fall. - Was it true?
- Was it true? - I thought you were lying.
- I'm not like that. - I thought he was lying.
My parents didn't raise me that way.
We were just trying to distract them.
- My father told me never to lie. - So that's why.
What an obedient son.
We'll sing "In the Bus" by Zaza.
Okay.
Zaza!
("In the Bus" by Zaza)
(They start dancing to the beat.)
(Cheerful)
(They recharge themselves with joy once again.)
Han Na is intelligent, Han Na is attractive
(This song is for you.)
(As soon as Seok Jin finishes rapping the intro,)
(they quickly hand over the money sack due to lack of time.)
Hurry up!
(How well will they do?)
Every day on the bus to school
(Clinging)
(As expected, Jae Seok starts to distract Seok Jin.)
(I need to concentrate. Let's not get distracted.)
- I'm not confident - Hey, give me a dollar.
(He gets on Seok Jin's back.)
(He squeezes him tightly.)
(Although her partner is suffering from pain,)
(she continues to sing with her nasal voice.)
(Their ways of distraction become more intense.)
(When did they move the microphone?)
(It's so hard to sing a song.)
(I don't think I can make it, Han Na.)
(She continues to sing in the midst of all the chaos.)
She's doing great.
(The song is almost coming to an end.)
- We're almost done. - Look!
It's a mummy!
- It's a goblin with a huge nose! - It's a mummy!
- It's Gong Yoo. - Their score is 79.
In 1, 2, 3.
- It's 72 dollars and 32 cents. - It's 72 dollars and...
(What will be the result of Han Na's persistent effort?)
(Did he get it right even when we distracted him like that?)
- You're wrong. - Oh, no.
- What's the answer? - It's 78 dollars and 33 cents.
(It was close.)
We almost got it right.
- Han Na is good at singing. - I agree.
- Your voice is fantastic. - I know.
What do you want to sing?
- Do something cheerful. - Sing a song with a fast beat.
Then we'll...
- Should we get revenge? - Yes!
(It's finally the time for revenge.)
- Go smash them into pieces. - Let's start.
(The last song will be "Me Gustas Tu" by Gfriend.)
- Let's start cheerfully. - I love this song.
Gfriend!
(She has an innocent appearance but dances powerfully.)
I used to know the dance, but I forgot.
- Yes! - Um Ji!
My heart flutters toward you
Starting from today, us
(Here's a professional cameraman.)
(The guys are all excited.)
(Haha, the cameraman, is taking a close up shot.)
(It's a melody that never fails to cheer people up.)
(Me gustas tu, gustas tu, I like you)
(Seok Jin slowly gets ready to distract him.)
(It's time for punishment.)
(As soon as the song ends, Seok Jin starts disturbing him.)
(You are responsible for your own sin.)
(The camera sticks to his face.)
- Gosh, this is too... - This is so funny.
You look hilarious.
(Jae Seok is known for his looks.)
Keep singing. Hey, Um Ji. You have to go on.
(Um Ji calmly continues to sing.)
(What is it now?)
(Squirting)
(The water attack has his soul torn into pieces.)
I'll be brave and confess to you
(Jong Kook lifts him up.)
(This time, it's time to fly.)
(We prepared a variety of events for you.)
(While Jae Seok is busy paying for his sins,)
(she's busy finishing the song.)
I will not forget this!
I will never forget this!
My goodness. Um Ji!
(I'll finish our mission, Jae Seok.)
(I trust you, Um Ji.)
(Don't worry. I'm good at counting money.)
(You don't need to worry about me. I'm really fine.)
(She concentrates on counting the money.)
(They're still busy tormenting Jae Seok.)
(I need to take a photo of this.)
(We're all good friends.)
(His microphone is in his nose, and his socks are on his hands.)
(It's a very strange look.)
Um Ji, you need to continue singing.
(She continues to focus on the mission.)
- He's a mess. - Look at her.
(She doesn't move.)
The show must go on.
- It's 54 dollars. - Um Ji...
(What a unique character.)
- Unbelievable. - She doesn't care.
(Leave all the missions to Um Ji.)
You knew this was coming, right?
(Jae Seok and Um Ji's performance has finally come to an end.)
I messed up.
(Their score is 98.)
- They got 98! - My goodness!
- Isn't that the highest score? - We got 98 points!
How dare you touch her with your foot!
I'm sorry, Um Ji.
If they get the number right, they'll come in first place.
I think it's 56 dollars...
56 dollars...
Wait, just use one microphone.
- Which one will you use? - Do I need to choose?
- Don't be greedy. - He's greedy.
- I'll use this one. - He's one greedy guy.
(He chooses the one in his nose.)
- You said it's... - It's 56 dollars and 85 cents.
(Her answer is 56 dollars and 85 cents.)
(If they get the right number, they'll be the only team to win.)
(Will they be able to get the right answer?)
- You're wrong. - Yes!
What a pity. You were wrong only by two cents.
(She was only 2 cents away from the answer.)
- What a pity. - I was really surprised at Um Ji.
She was so calm during all the chaos.
- She didn't care. - She kept singing.
Did you know I was being tormented?
- I didn't know. - You didn't know?
What a liar!
- She missed two cents. - She was so close.
- What a pity. - It really is.
The team that came in first place is the one team that succeeded in...
completing the mission. It's Jong Kook and Se Young's team.
(Jong Kook and Se Young come in first place.)
- I can't say no to that. - They're really incredible.
- I can't believe they got it right. - Exactly.
He's really impressive. I couldn't even do anything.
I already told you the name of today's race.
It's called Cheapskate Couple Race.
Along with the 15 dollars you need to pay for the karaoke fee...
(Karaoke fee?)
What? You want us to pay?
You also need to pay three dollars for water and snacks.
- My goodness, I didn't know. - What is this?
- You want us to pay 18 dollars? - You need to pay 18 dollars.
However, the team that came in first doesn't need to pay.
- Come on. - No way.
- My goodness. - They don't have much money anyway.
- The remaining five teams will... - Equally divide the money?
- pay after rolling the roulette. - Make one team pay for everything.
However, if the roulette points to "Free of charge",
no one will have to pay. The staff will pay for everything.
- Let's go. - Only one team will have to pay.
- We'll write down the teams. - Go ahead.
- We only get one section. - Wait.
- We get two sections. - It was fun.
- Seok Jin always gets unlucky. - Done.
It's all done.
- Se Young has a pretty handwriting. - I can write like her too.
I can't write that well.
(Kwang Soo's team has their name written down the most.)
- We need to pray. - Get ready.
Let's end it in one go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(The fate of the five couples are in Se Young's hands.)
(Please let our team avoid having to pay for everything.)
(18 dollars isn't a small amount of money.)
(Which team will end up having to pay for everything?)
(Kwang Soo and So Min)
I don't have to pay!
(The survivors cry for joy.)
- I'm so happy. - You're really one unlucky guy.
(It's not a surprise for Kwang Soo.)
Please pay 18 dollars.
- I had a lot of fun. - Thanks a lot.
(Kwang Soo and So Min pay 18 dollars.)
The two poorest couples are sitting together.
These two couples have the least amount of money.
When can I stop hanging around with those beggars?
I don't think you guys are that well-off either.
No, we have a lot of money.
Um Ji, we really need to show them.
These two couples are the poorest ones here.
- I'd love to throw money at you. - No, don't show them our sack.
Let's show him that we know how to spend money.
Um Ji is usually very frugal, but we'll show you.
(They're on their way to eat.)
(It's time for lunch.)
Two servings of octopus set dish for our table, please.
- You must be really rich. - Let's have rice with toppings.
(Eating)
It tastes nice.
- This is good. - Hey, Jong Kook.
- Yes? - Do you want some?
It would be nice to have some.
Then stand up and write your name with your bottom.
(If that's all I have to do, I'll do it right now.)
(Moving)
Here you go.
(How cute.)
(The prize goes into Se Young's mouth.)
(Se Young, you look the prettiest when you eat.)
The kalguksu originally costs five dollars,
but if you make your own dish, you can get a 50-percent discount.
- We'll make our own dish. - You'll make it yourselves?
(Ji Hyo puts in a lot of effort.)
Wow, how can you cut it so evenly? Have you done this before?
You must be a really good cook.
(This team has a table full of food.)
Hey, don't we look like newlyweds?
You guys look like a sad married couple.
(They successfully make the kalguksu with their own hands.)
Right now...
(They're enjoying their dish to the fullest.)
- Let's get dumplings... - Let's get dumplings and naengmyun.
Thank you for the meal.
(If 2 people successfully finish 4 servings, they won't have to pay.)
(They eat passionately.)
(All six couples enjoy their meals in their own ways.)
- Let's go. That was a great meal. - Thank you for the meal.
(Kwang Soo's team: 64 dollars, Ji Hyo's team: 19 dollars)
- I'm so full. - That tasted great.
- Did you all enjoy your meal? - Yes.
- It was great. - I'm so satisfied.
We're at Gongju where the Tomb of King Muryeong...
and Gongsanseong Fortress exist.
I've been to the Tomb of King Muryeong when I was little.
If you win the next mission, you'll be able to win a great deal.
You'll be able to...
(A great deal?)
- get an Exchange Card. - Exchange Card?
- No way. - Is there Exchange Card?
We haven't spent all our money.
- We should have spent all. - Exchange Card...
allows you to exchange wallets with another couple...
- or exchange your partner. - Partners?
(Exchange the wallet or the partner.)
So Min wants to switch her partner.
You can switch your partner?
- Wait a minute. - That's a good idea.
- I disagree. - Wait a minute.
- Do you have money in the wallet? - Yes.
For some couples, only women have the money.
- I gave all to my partner. - Me too.
- The person who has the money... - I didn't give it to her.
- will keep it. - I paid for the food.
This is good.
Can you give me 10 dollars?
That's if you switch partners.
Do you want to switch partners?
- Seriously. - I won't.
All of my money...
I guarantee you that So Min will abandon you.
No, I won't ever abandon you.
- I won't make it easy. - I promise.
When Kwang Soo breaks up,
it gets messy.
Give me everything I gave you.
Everything I've given you.
Gosh, he's terrible.
You'll be divided into two groups for this mission.
The first part is a free tour.
It's called "Romantic Fortress Tour".
(The only advantage is that it's free.)
(Although it's free, you must climb many stairs.)
(It's a date that requires labor.)
You have to pay an entrance fee for the second part.
It's called "Luxurious Tomb Tour".
- How much is it? - We'll pay.
- How much is it? - How much?
(With reasonable cost, you get to enjoy the best tour.)
(It's indoors and offers snacks.)
(Everyone wants to know the price.)
- The entrance fee is five dollars. - Okay.
The total will be 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars? - Please choose now.
- We'll take the luxurious tour. - We'll pay.
We have one team that will pay.
- We'll pay too. - "Romantic Fortress Tour".
- We'll also pay. - We won't pay.
Really, Jae Seok?
Let's go in the order of who has most money.
- We'll pay 11 dollars. - They'll pay 11 dollars.
- We'll also pay 11 dollars. - We'll pay 12 dollars.
Let's stop. It'll be our loss.
How about 15 dollars?
Don't go if you can't afford it.
Seok Jin made an offer of 20 dollars.
- 20 dollars? - That's a lot.
- I won't go. - I'll take the free tour.
- Me too. - I won't go for 20 dollars.
Seok Jin's couple will pay 20 dollars.
Other couples can pay 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars? - What?
- Me too. - Here's 10 dollars.
What's wrong with you?
I raised my hand for 10 dollars.
You can choose two couples.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
(They play rock-paper-scissors.)
Yes.
- Isn't Kwang Soo's couple out? - What?
- All right. - What did you say?
The ones for "Romantic Fortress Tour"...
are Seok Jin's, Jae Seok's,
and Haha's couple.
(Three couples go to "Luxurious Tomb Tour".)
Am I going with Jong Kook and Ji Hyo?
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo are going to "Romantic Fortress Tour".
(Couples to go to different tours)
This is where the history of Baekje took place.
- It's beautiful here. - Is it Tomb of King Muryeong?
- You're right. - It's Tomb of King Muryeong.
Gosh, it's peaceful.
This is great.
- I've never been here. - It's beautiful.
- This is great. - Amazing.
- Hello. - There are desserts.
There's more food.
- We just had lunch. - I'm still full.
You chose "Luxurious Tomb Tour" for Tomb of King Muryeong.
As you tour the historic site,
come up with two questions...
for the other couples.
- Do we come up with them? - Yes.
- Let's go. - Let's keep the manners.
Let's keep it common sense.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Please start the tour and come up with questions.
- We got tricked. - Please start.
- Let's go. - It's over here.
Is this where the tour is?
I think so.
- Do we have to study? - Yes.
(Exchange Card depends on their questions.)
Let's not make silly questions.
"Woongjin Period". Write down everything.
- When was Woongjin Period? - This is hard.
No one will know the answer.
If I make a question from this, no one will know.
- The 2ㅜ2nd. - King Munju.
- King Munju. - No one will ask this.
(It's like they're members of history club.)
(The three couples take notes furiously.)
- There's a lot of information. - We can't know the answer.
(How are the other three couples?)
Is this it?
- There's more than I thought. - It looks great.
- Here are the rules. - What?
The first part of the course is "Piggyback Race".
You will run with your partner on your back.
Depending on the order of arrival, you'll be asked a question...
about the next course's history with different difficulty levels.
(Their question depends on the race.)
(Exchange Card is on the line. Which couple will be taking the lead?)
(Which couple will win Exchange Card?)
("Piggyback Race" starts.)
(They run quickly.)
(They race competitively to turn the table with Exchange Card.)
Don't push yourself too hard.
Shall I hold in my breath?
(They start running uphill.)
The difficult part starts here.
(Jong Kook passes easily.)
You have 10 more steps left.
(Kwang Soo is the runner-up.)
A little more.
(Jong Kook and Se Young are in the lead.)
Come on, Tae Joon.
They're following us.
Hurry up.
(The gap widens.)
(Tae Joon and Ji Hyo are the last.)
We're in trouble.
(Jong Kook and Se Young win the easiest question.)
I'll get off.
The uphill is hard.
(The others struggle.)
We're here.
(Kwang Soo and So Min win the intermediate level.)
(The last gets the most difficult question.)
(They move on for their next course.)
Gosh, I can't run anymore.
(Why is it still uphill?)
I'm sorry.
Just leave without me.
Meet a better man.
I can't do it.
(Saving money is this hard.)
Running uphill is so hard.
(He can't go on.)
I feel like vomiting.
I really feel like vomiting.
The second course is "Up and Down Race".
Male members will listen to the question at the start line...
and run up to the partner. If she answers correctly, you succeed.
If you fail, go back to the start line...
- Jong Kook. - for another question.
Here's your question.
On the day when Baekje was destroyed,
what's the name of the rock where all the court ladies sacrificed...
their lives for the royal king?
That's so easy.
Number one, Seokguram.
Number two, Nakhaam.
Number three, Nakwaam.
Number four, Baekwaam. Please go.
What an easy question.
On the day Baekje was destroyed,
where did the court ladies...
(He must remember the question.)
Sacrifice themselves...
(He must climb 108 steps to deliver the question.)
(Will Jong Kook remember the question accurately?)
(Otherwise, he has to climb up again.)
Here it is.
On the day...
On the day Baekje was destroyed,
what's the name of the rock where...
court ladies jumped off?
Number one, Seokguram.
Number two, Nakhaam.
Number three, Nakwaam.
Number four, Seokhwaam.
(What is the name of the rock where all the court ladies sacrificed?)
- What's the answer? - Number three, Nakwaam.
(He's doubtful.)
No, that's not it.
(She screams after seeing the look on his face.)
Number two.
Nakhaam.
(Is it number two?)
(Is the answer Nakhaam?)
Number two, Nakhaam.
That's incorrect.
(The answer is number three.)
Why did you give me that look?
Did I give the correct choices?
Three of them were correct.
Was I wrong about number four?
- You did a good job. - Will it be another question?
(Kwang Soo is in pain after running.)
Kwang Soo, here's your intermediate-level question.
I'll make it no matter what.
King Injo of Joseon escaped to Gongsan Fortress.
Wait a minute.
Someone offered rice cakes to him.
As he was impressed by the taste, he named them.
What's the name of these rice cakes?
Number one, rainbow rice cakes. Number two, gaetteok.
Number three, honey rice cakes. Number four, injeolmi.
Please, please.
Rainbow, gaetteok, honey, and injeolmi.
King Injo. Gaetteok. Rainbow, gaetteok, honey, injeolmi.
(It was a long question, but he only remembers the rice cakes.)
(My goodness)
(Would Kwang Soo be able to repeat the question correctly?)
Please. King Injo...
(King Injo was fleeing to Gongsan Fortress.)
- got rice cakes as a gift. - What?
(He loved the taste and name it himself.)
What is the name of this rice cake? Number one, rainbow rice cake.
Number two, gaetteok.
Number three...
(He's not sure.)
Honey rice cake.
Number four...
(The choices are rainbow rice cake, gaetteok,)
(honey rice cake and injeolmi.)
Injeolmi.
Number four, injeolmi.
- What is your answer? - Number four, injeolmi.
(She picked it randomly. Is it correct?)
You're correct.
(Injeolmi is the answer.)
They got it right?
- Really? Where do we go? - Let's go.
- Really? - Let's go.
(Who knew So Min was so good in history?)
How did you know? Did you know this question?
I just picked one.
- I picked my favorite rice cake. - Good job.
You like injeolmi? I'll get it for you.
- Let's go. - I have 80 cents.
- It's a stretch. - They got it right.
Here's level-three question.
Which treasure was not found in Gongju?
Number 1, 7-story pagoda in Cheongnyang Temple Site.
Number 2, 5-story stone pagoda in Magok Temple.
Number three, Jungakttan in Mount Gyeryong.
Number four, Jikji.
Go and come back, Tae Joon. Hurry.
Go and come back.
(If he remembers this question, he must be a robot.)
What's the matter with me?
This is going to make me throw up.
Every time I come on the show, I always get difficult missions.
I always have to go far too.
Ji Hyo, I didn't memorize all the answer options.
It was too long.
But even if you get it wrong, I'll go again.
From the following, which is not found in Gongju?
- Okay. - There's...
seven-story stone pagoda in Magok Temple.
There's also Mount Gyeryong or something.
Number four is Jikji.
- What's that again? - Jikji.
- Number four, Jikji. - Jikji.
- What's your answer? - Number four, Jikji.
(Is this the right answer?)
- You're correct. - See?
(Jikji is the answer.)
We did it.
(We are in last place.)
- Tae Joon. - Wasn't that good?
That was level three.
(What a miracle!)
Oh, dear. How did you know?
(Ji Hyo and Tae Joon move on to the next course.)
You're the best.
- They got it right. - They did?
Let's hurry. They got it.
(Ji Hyo and Tae Joon are right after them.)
- Tae Joon. - That was smart of me.
We should never be up against Ji Hyo and Jong Kook.
Are they the strongest?
We should only go against Seok Jin and Jae Seok.
(Where are Seok Jin and Jae Seok?)
We're in trouble. There are so many.
What are we supposed to do?
Should we ask about something that's hidden?
We should. Something that's hard to find, right?
(She learns quickly.)
- There are too many things. - How do we learn all this?
- I should ask something irrelevant. - Don't you think they'll know?
I'm going to do this one.
Listen.
"Building graves" and "polishing graves".
(Do you see these working figures on display?)
I'll ask them to count how many figures there are.
(That's an unexpected question.)
I have a clever partner.
This is the best thing that's happened to me this year.
How many figures are there?
(How many figures are building the graves?)
(You can guess if you want.)
"Number of ancient tombs". Nobody will get this right.
(What is their strategy?)
(Her radar is on.)
(She looks at the other team's paper.)
(She scans what he's written down.)
(Thanks for the information.)
- What are you looking at? - I didn't look.
(What are you looking at?)
- What are you doing, Han Na? - I was looking at this.
- What are you looking at? - I didn't look.
- That was too obvious. - No, she's not like that.
- I didn't think you would do that. - I was reading about that...
- across from you. - Come on.
- I didn't think of you like that. - I'm not like that.
What are you talking about?
- I was reading that. - My gosh.
Hey, Han Na.
Look at you.
(She's so sneaky.)
My gosh.
(I see how it is.)
(He tries to block her view.)
Okay. I got it.
(He quickly scans through the information.)
I'm speechless.
(He's faking it.)
(You must ask a question other teams haven't thought of.)
- We went around once, right? - We did.
- I don't think we tried here. - Should we go?
Let's go. We have to look every corner.
(Haha was here already.)
(I'm getting ideas now.)
1, 2...
(He counts with his head just in case others see him.)
(I did that 5 minutes ago.)
I'll change my question.
I can't believe you found this.
- What's going on? - What are you looking at?
- What was I looking at? - I saw you do this.
(Nodding)
People might ask about this.
I can change my question, right?
- He's counting. - I saw him.
Let's change it.
They might ask the number of figures, Um Ji.
I agree.
"Mount Maebong".
(2 minutes before questions are up.)
(You must get the most difficult question you can find.)
(She finds information is found only in the computer.)
(Nobody will guess this right.)
I got it.
(Seok Jin is also making a question about figures.)
"How many figures are there?" Building graves.
(This must be a hot place to visit.)
(What did Han Na think of?)
(She makes a question about Chinese characters.)
(Write Baekje in Chinese characters.)
- Um Ji. - Yes?
How's this? "Describe the current status of investigation..."
"on the ancient tombs of Baekje."
"Write it in Chinese."
(That's a great idea.)
- "Write it in English." - Are you sure?
What about me?
You have to think carefully.
(What is Jae Seok's tricky question?)
This is it.
"Draw the mural inside Songsan-ri Ancient Tomb."
(He makes a drawing question.)
They have to draw it exactly the same.
(Running Man is a place where people use petty tricks.)
This is perfect.
(All questions have been submitted.)
- Did you submit your question? - I did.
I didn't know you were like that, Han Na.
- You're so sneaky. - What do you mean?
She stood behind me and...
(Peeking)
I would turn back and she would be there.
(Cheating)
(And again.)
(It doesn't look like it's her first time.)
(She is Running Man's official sneaky princess.)
- She's sneaky? - She is.
Each team submitted two questions.
You can ask one question each...
to whichever team you would like.
- This question is for Haha. - All right.
They'll never know.
What?
(This is going too far.)
You can use this. Can we have our question?
Can we have our question?
(He doesn't know what to do with this English question.)
What should we do?
"Describe the current status of investigation in English."
Isn't this unfair?
How's this unfair?
I asked you because it was there.
- Can we have our question? - Give us a question.
- This is difficult. - Here it is.
- This is too long. - What does it say?
- What's wrong with it? - "How many figures are there?"
(Wait. The figures must be...)
- Let me see. - What was that again?
- This is too hard. - Exactly.
- Why? - I counted earlier.
Really? No way.
- Building graves... - I know this. I asked that too.
- You did? - Polishing graves.
I was going to ask that question, but I saw somebody counting.
- I was counting. - Whatever.
- I know this too. - But you know what?
You have to be accurate.
- There are ones you can't see. - All right.
- I counted them too. - You have to get them too.
- You won't get it. - Once I get back inside,
that figure will come alive and wave at me.
(I'm done.)
"What is the phone number written on the website?"
- That's too easy. - This is too easy.
You would think so. Try your best.
- You're making me mad. - Go find your answers.
Sure. Take your paper.
- Which one? - "Width of Mount Maebong".
Write it on my name tag. You can rip it.
(Jae Seok heads straight to the figures.)
(Thank you, Seok Jin.)
(He's been here before, so it's easy for him.)
12.
(He's an expert in solving tricky questions.)
"Investigation on the ancient tombs of Baekje".
(Describe the investigation on the ancient tombs of Baekje.)
(Where's the answer?)
Isn't this talking about ancient tombs?
- This is it. - Where does it talk about Baekje?
- Baekje. - I can't write all this.
(Han Na heads straight to the tombs for the drawing question.)
How am I supposed to draw all this?
(She looks around carefully.)
(She's taking out her artistic side thanks to Jae Seok and Um Ji.)
(She's focused on drawing.)
(He's studying English.)
What am I doing here?
The viewers won't find this funny.
(My blood pressure is rising.)
When will I finish writing this?
Where's the exhibit about Mount Maebong?
(It was her idea.)
I see exhibits about mountains.
(She hits the jackpot.)
Here it is.
(She finds a hidden question from the machine.)
(Jae Seok and Um Ji get the answer first.)
- I got it. - Let's go.
I have to do this a bit more.
We can do it when we get there.
(Seok Jin and Han Na get the answer at the same time.)
Let's go.
Read the question and tell us the answer.
Our question was,
"What is the total height of Mount Maebong?"
The answer is 8.4km.
It's correct.
We had to count the number of human dolls that were...
involved in building the grave, bricks, and tomb furnishings.
- How many were there? - There were 76 human dolls.
Jae Seok. Um Ji.
(What will Exchange Card's fate be that'll change the race's dynamics?)
Jae Seok. Um Ji. It is correct.
(Their answer is correct.)
(What? Is this it?)
(Thanks to Seok Jin's question, it ends in an instant.)
- The game is over. - The game is over.
What? What happened?
I didn't even write half of it.
The game is over.
(I only studied English.)
- It's over? - Yes.
- Did you draw it? - Yes, I did.
- You. - Let me see.
(She's a victim of Jae Seok's question.)
(She's an artist.)
- It really looked like this. - You are right.
- She drew this. - She drew it correctly.
She drew it thoroughly.
- It should've been harder. - Did you write it down?
I wrote up to "tunnel".
Goodness. This is amazing.
(Let's just use our bodies.)
Jae Seok and Um Ji earned the Exchange Card since they won.
Take a look at it in private.
What is it?
I'm so jealous.
(Switch Card)
- Let's hurry. - There it is. That must be it.
(Which team will take the last Exchange Card?)
(Kwang Soo and So Min are in the lead.)
The last course is simple.
It's "Archery Course".
The mission is accomplished when you shoot...
3 balloons on the target using only 5 arrows.
I wasn't going to brag, but I'm good.
(Kwang Soo tries.)
(Shooting)
(The aim was perfect.)
- Okay. - You are good.
Kwang Soo. You are awesome.
(I will win that Exchange Card.)
- I'll challenge now. - Kwang Soo, you are so cool.
I will pick the middle target.
- Let's go! - Go for it, Kwang Soo!
(I will gather all the energy in the universe to the tips of my fingers.)
(I will hit the target and acquire the Exchange Card.)
(He gets ready to shoot.)
(It ends up on the ground.)
- I'll really try now. - You did well before.
- Hold on. - Are you going to buy more arrows?
- I will. - Now I know why my friends...
- dated older women. - For additional arrows,
it's 50 cents for 5 arrows and 80 cents for 10.
- Buy 10 arrows. - Please give me 10.
Give me 80 cents back.
They are coming. We are in trouble.
(The members join the last course, seeking for the Exchange Card.)
Let's hurry.
- Kwang Soo. - Shoot it that way.
- Shoot as many as you want. - I'll consider you to be my senior.
(They hoard up the arrows.)
Shoot as many as you want.
- We're almost there. - Okay!
You are so awesome, Kwang Soo!
(He hits the target at last!)
- You are so awesome. - Wait.
You are like Hwarang. You're Lee Hwarang.
- Lee Hwarang. - You're exaggerating.
- So Min. - You look so cool.
(Where will his next arrow land?)
(He misses.)
Go and get me more arrows. We are running out of time.
Please give me 8 arrows.
(Kwang Soo's target is full of arrows.)
How many have you shot? It might turn into a hedgehog.
How many will you shoot?
- So Min. Buy some more. - Again?
(Popping)
- He's catching up. - I got this.
(It's a disaster. I've invested a lot in this mission.)
(Kwang Soo gets ready to shoot.)
Kwang Soo. Go for it.
(Popping)
You are amazing.
- Compliment me a bit more. - You're incredible.
Kwang Soo. You are so handsome.
(Only one balloon remains.)
(If he gets this, he will win the Exchange Card.)
Go, Kwang So! You can do it!
This is my last arrow.
You have long legs.
(He releases the arrow as So Min compliments him.)
(Will his investment be fruitful?)
(His last arrow shoots the target.)
(I'm proud of you, Kwang Soo!)
This is outstanding. You are awesome.
I'm proud of you.
But the thing is, we bought like 50 arrows.
The winning team of "Romantic Fortress Tour"...
is Kwang Soo and So Min's team.
(Kwang Soo and So Min acquire the Exchange Card.)
- Good job. - Thank you.
So Min. What are you planning to do?
- I just want to see it. - Are you going to betray me?
We will go and discuss this in private.
(Jae Seok's team and Kwang Soo's team acquire the Exchange Cards.)
Let's go inside.
According to the results of the mission,
Jae Seok's team and Kwang Soo's team won the cards.
It was a close match.
You can either switch the wallet...
or your partner.
(It's a chance to change their partners.)
When you go pass that door,
there will be a piece of paper on the table.
Each of you will write what you want to do.
(They will write either "wallet" or "partner".)
If one person writes wallet and the other person writes partner,
the one who chose wallet will change the wallet..
and the one who chose the partner, will change the partner.
- We will change our own wallet? - Yes.
I can't be completely certain if she won't write "partner".
- She doesn't let her feelings show. - I don't think she'll switch you.
I don't think she will try to switch you out.
- I knew it. - Let's be loyal to each other.
- You won't betray me, right? - I told you not to doubt me.
(He says not to doubt him and yet, he seems restless.)
(Starting with Um Ji, they start to fill out their exchange form.)
Should I write it big on the paper?
(She looks around.)
(She writes it down after giving much thought.)
I can't believe you people.
(It's a crucial chance to get closer to winning the race.)
(What will their decisions be?)
- Decide which team will go first. - It's important.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Um Ji will play. - So Min. You should do it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(So Min wins.)
- We will go after them. - We will let them go first.
I will announce the result first.
- Jae Seok. - Yes.
- You wrote wallet. - Of course.
- You wrote wallet. - I did. What else would I write?
- Um Ji. - She probably wrote wallet as well.
- No way. - Did Um Ji write partner?
If she did write partner, I'd be surprised, but it'd be funny.
- I mean it. - No way.
(He pretends to be indifferent.)
(No one knows how she feels. What is her decision?)
- She wrote wallet. - All right.
(She chose to switch wallets.)
Well done, Um Ji.
- I'm curious about their decisions. - So...
you can switch your wallet with the wallet of your choice.
I don't know whom to pick.
It looked like Jong Kook's wallet was pretty heavy.
No, I don't think so. He doesn't have any money.
The couples who went to "Luxurious Tomb Tour" won't have money.
- She's smart. - We didn't think about that.
- That's true. - We don't have any money.
- Jong Kook isn't reacting. - He really doesn't have any.
- He must have a lot of money. - Tae Joon must be rich.
- He opened his eyes widely. - Hey.
- You know about them, right? - Hey, don't touch me.
Look at this. Money is sticking out.
- This is confusing. - Jae Seok.
- Kwang Soo has at least 30 dollars. - Seok Jin is the rich one.
He still has 30 dollars?
I know this because...
he pulled out a 50-dollar bill when he was buying food.
Really?
(Two hours ago, during snack time)
(She carefully handed over a 50-dollar bill.)
Can you give me the change in secret?
- That's a 50-dollar bill. - You're so rich.
(That couple gave a 50-dollar bill for sweet and sour chicken.)
(Did you notice that?)
- They gave a 50-dollar bill. - Really?
(The suspicion about the 50-dollar bill arises.)
- It was a five-dollar bill. - Give me your wallet!
- Our wallet? - Yes. Bring it.
Kwang Soo took 10 dollars as change.
The 50-dollar bill was crucial.
Seriously? You didn't see that?
- How can he have that bill? - We spent it. We spent the money.
Even if you did...
- Even if he did spend it... - Give me the wallet.
We can check too, right?
(Before exchanging, they check their wallets.)
- We want to see it too. - I'm so curious.
(They hit the jackpot. There are many bills.)
- Um Ji is surprised. - Is there a lot of money?
(Smiling)
- There's a lot of money? - How did it go?
- Did you check our wallet? - We did.
- Which one of them is mad? - I can't tell.
You were dirt poor.
He's the poorest person I've ever seen.
I spent my money freely today.
I spent as much as I could.
(They were the most wasteful couple.)
- I spent money like water. - You are a true man.
- Good job. - Now...
(Clinking)
(However, the war of money isn't over yet.)
Now, I will announce the result for Kwang Soo's team.
I will announce what Kwang Soo wrote down.
I can't wait to hear this.
(No way. I can trust you, right?)
Unexpectedly, he wrote down wallet.
(What a twist. He chose the wallet.)
(Blushing)
- He picked the wallet? - He's a real man.
(He pretends to be manly.)
You are a real man.
This is amazing. This is not like him.
So Min...
(If she picked wallet, they can retrieve their wallet.)
She wrote down partner.
Way to go, So Min!
(She decided to replace Kwang Soo with a smiling face.)
(So Min announces shocking news of their breakup.)
- She had faith in her. - You didn't do it.
- I knew it! - Why did you do that?
(He's pitiful.)
- That's insane. - She's the best.
- So Min. - Good one.
- Why did you do that? - "Why did you do that?"
- Why did you do that? I have money. - I'm sorry.
- You're the best, So Min. - You had money?
I thought you were going to betray me and take all the money.
Oh, dear.
(50 minutes ago upon arrival at Hanok village)
(They do rock, paper, scissors to decide who takes the money.)
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
(He won.)
(Kwang Soo is in charge of the money.)
(Can I trust him?)
(This is where the mistrust brew.)
- Good job. - He started acting cold.
- He's like that. - I did that?
I didn't act cold. Were you born in 1986?
- Yes. - I was born a year earlier.
(They were never meant to be together.)
Kwang Soo, you can take the wallet you want.
- What now? - Aren't you getting greedy?
(Give me my wallet, Jae Seok.)
(You can't take it back.)
You can't beat this. Nobody will have more than this.
- Is it that much? - If you become my partner,
I'll give you all my money.
- That's cool. - How much do you have?
- That one was really good. - Can we switch?
Does Tae Joon have no money?
Haha can multiply the numbers, so you can go to him.
You have no money, so you'll still end up with nothing.
It's zero dollars even after you multiply it.
(Multiply all you want.)
I looked earlier.
We didn't have anything.
(He's the worst ex-boyfriend out there.)
- Do you really have nothing? - I don't.
Men don't usually carry money.
- I choose Jong Kook. - She's so innocent.
(So Min, please.)
- Why? - No?
- He has no money. - You don't?
- Have you made up your mind? - No, think again.
- He might have money. - He does.
Se Young.
- Please switch. - Please switch.
Something's going on.
(The others are getting swayed now.)
- He might have money. - That's what I was thinking.
- You don't have money? - He was pretending.
- He was being so frugal. - So Min.
She picked Jong Kook?
There was something going on between him and Se Young.
Jong Kook might have been pretending.
- I don't think so. - Do you have zero dollars?
No, right? Do you have nothing?
- What's 0 divided by 2? - I mean...
- "0 divided by 2?" - My goodness.
I haven't met a more clueless woman.
You're so unlucky, So Min.
- Do you feel empty? - You have money, right?
I'm sorry but all I can give you is love.
(I'll give you love and divide your money in two.)
- But I have some. - You do?
- You have money? - How much?
Sorry, I hid some money.
You...
What's going on here?
- This is a drama. - My goodness.
- She does have money. - She does.
- We each stole 10 dollars. - Didn't you steal some?
- Didn't you? - I hid 10 dollars too.
(He took 10 dollars just in case.)
- Hey. - I hid it in my phone case.
You are incredible.
(This is a fun drama to watch.)
- You can't do that. - You're so dirty.
When did you take it, Kwang Soo?
I was pretending to go to the bathroom and I took it.
You're so dirty.
If we put all the money together, we would have won.
Forget about it.
- Se Young. - Oh, dear.
Try to forget all about it.
I feel so bad for you.
- Is this the end? - It is.
- What now? - However,
there's a chance to turn the tables around.
- What? - It's a simple mission.
- What's wrong? - Does that mean we can win too?
- How much do you have? - Hold on.
I guess he gave it to Um Ji.
- He did. - When?
(Is that true?)
(What happened?)
- That's insane. - Is this allowed?
- I don't think so. - We can do whatever we want...
- without money. - It wouldn't matter.
- That's insane. - I'm getting goosebumps.
(What's going on?)
That wouldn't matter.
(Kwang Soo decided to switch the wallets.)
- He's not like that. - Would we get it taken away?
- We might. - They might take Jae Seok's.
(Kwang Soo would do that.)
(She secretly withdrew the money.)
(Nobody was paying attention.)
Did you take it out?
(Um Ji predicted all this and took a chance.)
- You don't have 30 dollars, right? - Jae Seok.
- They knew they would lose it. - You're the most sneaky.
- Um Ji has it then. - It was Um Ji.
- She has it? - She did it.
- She's the best. - She's the sneakiest person.
This is unbelievable.
Here's the last mission.
The guys will go into the house...
and hide the money. You can decide the amount.
The ladies will look for the money...
and whoever finds it, keeps it.
Whoever finds the money keeps it?
- Really? - However,
if nobody finds your wallet,
you get three times the current amount.
(If nobody finds it, you get three times what you have now.)
- If nobody finds it? - Three times?
- This is a gamble. - Three times?
- Let's bet everything. - There's a chance.
This is the last chance.
- Let's give it a try. - Let's do this.
- Whoever comes in last place... - Is there a penalty?
has a private meeting with us.
We have a mission for you.
(It'll be happening in Gongju Station while everybody is gone.)
(Which couple will have the honor?)
("Protect Your Money" starts now.)
- Hurry up. - Let's do this.
(I have to hide it so nobody can find it?)
Let me go inside.
(The married ones are experienced.)
(The six guys are thorough.)
If you can find this, you are unbelievable.
(There's chance to get three times the money.)
Be careful.
(Is Jae Seok looking in the bathroom?)
(It's the sewer.)
(He's unbelievable.)
(They are done hiding the money.)
(They hid different amounts.)
It's the ladies' turn.
Please take the red ropes on the table.
It's random. Don't pull it yet.
Two of you will tie each end around your waist.
(Who will be partners?)
In 1, 2, 3.
(So Min and Jin Joo are a team.)
(Um Ji and Ji Hyo are a team.)
I was hoping Han Na didn't end up with Se Young.
- Se Young is strong. - She's strong too.
(This is so that they don't talk.)
- You have only five minutes. - Let's go slowly.
Ready.
Set...
(The ladies start.)
Be nice to each other.
- Se Young. - Can we do this?
Take your socks off, Han Na.
You don't have to take them off, Se Young. You'll still win.
(They must find the other guys' money.)
Is it not there?
(They look determined.)
Hold on.
(Jin Joo runs away.)
(The rope tightens around her waist.)
Jin Joo, look everywhere.
(She keeps going straight.)
(Tripping)
Hold on, Jin Joo.
I think there's something here.
Let me look. I think I can find it.
(I can smell money around here.)
It's harder than I thought.
(Is she looking here?)
(Tae Joon hid his money here.)
(I think it's here.)
Is it Jin Joo?
- It is. - Did you look here?
She's great.
(She just has to reach out.)
Did anyone find one?
No, we haven't.
How much time do they get?
There should be something in the living room.
What are you doing with the cane, Han Na?
(She uses a tool to search the top.)
Where are you going, Han Na?
(Don't look there.)
Kwang Soo is quiet. Look near the ceiling!
Kwang Soo must have hidden it near the ceiling.
(Punching)
(Why would you do this to me?)
(Near the ceiling?)
The air conditioner.
- Sorry. - You have one minute left.
Han Na.
- Yes? - Is there something?
(Um Ji walks towards...)
(Jong Kook's hiding spot.)
(Will she find Jong Kook's money inside the camera?)
(Please don't look there.)
(She finds five dollars.)
(She stole Kwang Soo's wallet and has found Jong Kook's money.)
- She found it. - Who did?
(Um Ji is the best.)
- She found it. - You found it, right?
(Did you do it again?)
- It's Jong Kook's. - She found it.
(This is her victory dance.)
- Where? How much? - Um Ji.
(The others start to get anxious now.)
- 8, 7, - I have no idea.
(Please don't find mine.)
(We have no chance.)
- They are not here. - 2, 1.
(Five couples get to keep their money.)
(Jong Kook and So Min lose theirs.)
- They didn't find mine. - Jong Kook comes in last place.
He's the loser. We get three times this amount.
So Min is so unlucky.
Where did you hide it?
(She comes in last place.)
(Here are the results.)
Let me announce the first place.
It was a close match between Kwang Soo's team and Jae Seok's.
(It was a close match.)
Thanks to Um Ji.
(One of these couples is the winner.)
(Is it the rich guy Kwang Soo...)
(and his new woman Se Young?)
All you have to do is turn on the water.
(Or is it Jae Seok and Um Ji who stole the other couples' money?)
Um Ji, did you find it?
(Cheapskate Couple Race was full of twists.)
The winners are...
(Which couple won the race?)
Kwang Soo and Se Young.
(Kwang Soo and Se Young win.)
(Delighted)
Good job, Um Ji.
Um Ji played a big role today.
(So Min, are you watching?)
Um Ji, you did a great job.
If we had gone all in, we would have won.
(We should have gone all in.)
The winners will receive matching bracelets.
(Matching gold bracelets)
Jong Kook and So Min...
will be given a penalty.
We're at Gongju Station.
It's beautiful here.
- It's beautiful. - It is.
It takes only an hour and a half to Seoul.
- Are we taking the train? - Should we?
- Are we? - It won't take long.
It takes only one hour.
It'll take even less to Seongnam where I live.
We might arrive even earlier than the others.
- That's possible. - We might.
Two train tickets are hidden somewhere around the station.
The train leaves soon. Find the tickets before that.
- Are they around here? - Yes.
They might be around this sculpture.
(They have 30 minutes.)
(Let's hurry.)
- I want to go home. - They might be here.
- I want to go home. - Be careful.
(I want to go home.)
They must be hidden.
(The station is too big.)
- They're around the station. - How cute.
Let's look for the tickets.
(They met a savior.)
It's a dog.
- It's so cute. - Come with us.
Let's go to Seoul together.
Help us find the tickets.
(They're joined by an unexpected friend.)
We have to find the tickets to go home.
(The dog guides them into the station.)
Where could they be?
(Wait.)
(Did the dog guide them to the right place?)
(They're not here.)
Where are they?
(We have to get on the train soon.)
Hello.
(Jong Kook is going to look for witnesses.)
Well...
They're here.
Where?
Look at this.
(Are they really tickets?)
They're here. They were around the ticket office.
(This is the power of experience.)
Thank you.
We can go home now.
We found our tickets at Gongju Station.
- I live in Anyang. - I live in Ilsan.
- Ilsan? - Yes.
- Bye. - We're going home.
(We thank the citizens of Chungcheongnam-do.)
(Running Man's Food Guide)
- Food Guide? - It looks delicious.
(We fight to win food.)
What is she doing?
I'm here to eat.
(We run to win food.)
- Where is it? - We can eat good food.
I'm so tired.
(We make people laugh to win food.)
- I'm talking. - All right.
(We'll bring back your appetite.)
(Running Man introduces amazing restaurants to you.)
This is perfect for spring. We can have good food.
(Running Man's Food Guide)