(The grand finale, Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear)
(The extreme fear they have never experienced)
(The experience came to an end after many tears.)
(We are finally done with the penalty.)
(However, Global Project Part 2 began right away.)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(The one with 3 I Go Stickers must go with a chosen companion.)
(The travel attraction is chosen by 1 percent of the viewers.)
(Running Man will go to a place for 1 percent.)
(From the ossuaries to the cliffs, the decision is up to the viewers.)
(Running Man will leave once again to a recommended travel attraction.)
(It will be exciting to have the members experience it for me.)
(Not a minute passed since the scary trip.)
(Why are you doing this to us?)
(Among numerous destinations given by the viewers around the world, )
(they will go to the place that was recommended by 1 percent.)
(If you don't want to go, avoid the I Go Sticker.)
(Part 1 will start now and decide the 8 members' fates.)
People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent, Part 1.
The 1st race is a search for the best 1 percent,
The 1st Place Tour.
(The 1st Place Tour?)
(They must find the best in The 1st Place Tour in Tokyo.)
You will be divided into 3 teams for The 1st Place Tour.
Before the end of the mission,
a team must find the first place in various areas...
and receive the most number of stamps to win.
(The winners will be exempt from the I Go Sticker.)
(An exemption from the I Go Sticker is not the only benefit.)
The winners will decide...
who receives the I Go Sticker by rolling a die.
(It would be the best to win.)
That means we won't be free tomorrow.
What are you talking about? Did you think we would go home?
I thought we would leave after enjoying some free time.
You thought we would go sightseeing?
Since we struggled a lot, I thought they would buy us a meal.
- It's time to decide on the teams. - Yes.
The members who went to Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear...
- brought back name tags, right? - Yes.
If you take a look at it again, you will see colors.
There it is.
- You are right. - Mine is red.
(On the name tags are glow sticks in three colors.)
Please stand with a member who has the same color.
(Team Green, Team Blue, Team Red)
Now,
Jong Kook, Haha, and Ji Hyo of Team Happy Trip...
will each join a team.
It looks like which team you join is important.
That's right. It will be your team for the new project.
(Haha chooses first since he used the least amount of money.)
This is a very important decision.
In that case,
I will have to choose people who are very cunning.
That's So Min.
(She is the queen of slyness.)
I will join Jae Seok's team.
My goodness.
Look, we must join forces...
for this mission.
My goodness.
Next.
I am next. I had made up my mind...
- from the start. - Really?
- Really? - Which team will you join?
I choose Se Chan.
Okay!
(I choose Se Chan.)
She chose Se Chan, not Seok Jin.
- Seriously. - Se Chan.
- Se Chan. - It's okay. We are still a team.
I chose Se Chan, not you.
- Why not? - That means...
Jong Kook...
(Jong Kook is scarier than Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
You shouldn't use this as a weapon.
- Come on. - I didn't do anything wrong.
- Hey. - What?
Are we in the same team again?
Aren't you happy?
I am happy.
There are only two of us.
- That team has 2 members. - There are only 2 of us.
One team is short of a member.
That's why we invited a special guest.
- Is there a guest? - Really?
Is someone here?
We invited the queen for one percent.
(The queen?)
- Did a guest come at this hour? - Right now?
- Really? - Right now?
Who came at this late hour?
I present the queen for one percent. Please come on out.
(Who traveled the long distance to join them?)
- My goodness. - My goodness.
- My goodness. - Hello.
- It's Hye Sung. - Hello.
What brought you here?
(The master of cute acts, Actress Jung Hye Sung)
(She is the rising star of 2017 everyone is focusing on.)
(The 1st place guest with charms and acting skills, Jung Hye Sung)
Hello, I am Jung Hye Sung.
(Fresh)
My goodness.
(Did you see the way she smiled at me?)
Is Kwang Soo possessed?
(Scared)
I think he is possessed. Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo, get a hold of yourself.
Will Hye Sung join our team?
- Yes. - Really?
It's a blessing.
I sweated a lot.
Hye Sung.
You must have waited for a long time.
(They say that sweaty men are sexy.)
What is wrong with your hair?
- It's okay. - Did you take a shower?
Why are you acting cool?
He acts like he just came out of the shower.
That's sweat.
He sweated a lot since he was scared.
(Only walk on the flowery path, Hye Sung.)
You look like a loser.
(Kwang Soo, you are doing it wrong.)
How do I look?
(The way he shows his charms is a bit off.)
Why? How do I look?
- Kwang Soo. - You look cool.
You look like a musician.
Hello.
Go and get a haircut right away.
For goodness' sake.
The three teams will now move to their accommodations.
There are tree types of accommodations.
The first one is a luxury hotel in the city center.
(It's a luxury hotel.)
The second one is a traditional ryokan.
(The high-end ryokan)
The third one are tents at Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.
What?
(The tents are set up at the gate of Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
You should let us sleep in peace.
Tents at Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear?
That means some of us will end up sleeping here.
The teams will now move to their accommodations.
- We don't know where to go. - You already chose where to sleep.
When did we do that?
How did we do that?
(Did we choose the accommodation?)
There were three colors per name tag.
You chose a name tag of a certain color.
Taking off the name tag will reveal...
where you will sleep tonight.
No way.
(In order to start the tour full of energy, )
(they must avoid staying at the Labyrinth for the night.)
(Who will spend the night in the tent in front of the Labyrinth?)
- We got ryokan! - It's ryokan.
- I'm relieved. - We got ryokan.
What about us? What did we get?
(It's Team Hye Sung's turn, but Kwang Soo is in her team.)
(Ever since arriving in Japan, his misfortune has heightened.)
(The start of his misfortune was small as he got 10 slots.)
(However, he ended up having 20 slots at the end.)
(With this momentum, he advanced to the Labyrinth by himself.)
(Luck seems to run away from him. Where will his lodging be?)
What did we get?
- We got luxury hotel! - Luxury hotel!
(Has his curse been lifted?)
- What? - I wasn't expecting this.
(That means Team Ji Hyo has...)
Darn it!
(For them, the experience at the Labyrinth isn't over.)
I wasn't expecting this.
This isn't bad at all.
(Yes! We are saved!)
Are we going to sleep here?
You will pitch a tent and sleep in front of the Labyrinth.
- Really? - That's harsh.
(It's nice. I'll get to see the ghosts again.)
Gosh, how will you manage?
They will be cold during the night.
- Go and sleep in your lodgings now. - We can go now?
- We'll go now. - See you tomorrow, Se Chan.
- Good work, everyone. - I'm sorry.
- We are going now. - Goodnight.
- Take care. - We'll see you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow. - See you.
- Hye Sung, see you tomorrow. - All right.
- Good job today. - I'm about to lose it.
(Which team will experience the most 1st places?)
Let's go, Jong Kook.
(Team Hye Sung heads to a hotel in the city.)
- What is this? - Let's go. I got this for you.
- I bought this for you. - Of course he did.
- Really? - Yes.
- I saw you buying this. - This is quite expensive.
(He manages to be in her good graces with the wallet.)
- This is Totoro. - Right.
Goodness.
- Please stand in the center. - Yes, stand in the middle.
- Thank you. - Gosh.
(I have a good feeling about this. This might turn into something.)
When I go into a haunted house like this one,
I can't control myself but curse right away.
Oh, you curse.
- You do curse. - She's not so different from us.
I can understand though.
What are we doing tomorrow?
- I heard we have a mission. - Jong Kook.
We don't know anything about that.
(Why do you have a bug on you?)
- Was that a bug? - Yes.
(Startled)
- Why were you surprised? - He startled me.
- Why were you startled? - He scared me.
(The cameraman startled Kwang Soo.)
- Hye Sung, go before me. - Kwang Soo.
No, I am fine. Please go without me.
- Please go. - Kwang Soo.
- That was really uncool of you. - Hold on.
You were so lame.
- Gosh, Hye Sung. Please go. - Kwang Soo.
- Let me just stay here for a while. - Kwang Soo.
Please go without me. I said go!
Go now!
- Why are you sitting down? - Go! Wait for me in the car.
- Why did you sit down? - You're sitting alone.
- Why are you sitting down? - What?
To give this to Hye Sung.
(I wanted to give this to Hye Sung.)
I knelt down to give this to you.
(I fooled you, didn't I? I like surprises.)
This was all for her, right?
- What am I doing? - I was startled too.
Hye Sung, I'm sorry about him.
(She accepts Kwang Soo's gift.)
(I am such a cool guy.)
- By the way, - We'll get going now.
I am relieved we aren't spending the night at the Labyrinth.
- I am really relieved too. - That's right.
Had we gotten the Labyrinth, I would have cried.
Seok Jin...
He was really angry.
He really was.
I can't understand this.
- I'm sorry. - I know.
When I saw it... Goodness.
I was so sorry when I saw the tent.
- Seok Jin and Se Chan, tomorrow, - Yes?
- let's show them what we've got. - I agree. Let's do that.
- I'm ready to do anything. - Let's do this.
- Let's head to our cozy tents. - Let's go.
I guess they're all set up.
This is driving me crazy.
- I'm about to lose it. - I see the weeds.
Come on. What is this?
(Their home is located in front of the Labyrinth.)
How are we supposed to sleep here?
The left tent is Ji Hyo's.
The tent on the right is for Seok Jin and Se Chan.
This is insane.
(Even the ghosts wouldn't want to spend the night in the cold tents.)
How can we sleep here?
Give us the heating packs, and put the lights on the tents.
Is this how you treat your stars?
(Yes, this is how the stars are treated on Running Man.)
(Going in)
(What's worse is that it's uncomfortable and cramped.)
There's a sleeping bag for us.
We can sleep in the sleeping bags.
- Goodnight. - Goodnight, Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin, let's win tomorrow. - Let's win.
I think I really saw a ghost in there.
(Can Team Ji Hyo take the 1st place tomorrow?)
- Hello. - Hi.
(Kwang Soo manages to sit next to Hye Sung.)
- Do you want some chocolates? - What should we do?
Gosh, you are an angel.
- Thank you. Goodness. - Thank you.
Taste the chocolate awarded by the angel.
(Hye Sung laughs at something.)
Kwang Soo, you look so cute in this photo.
(What is the photo she saw?)
(Is he cute? The crew of Running Man respects your preferences.)
Kwang Soo, you look so cute in this photo.
(His heart pounds.)
- Look, he looks cute. - You really are an angel.
What an angel.
Hye Sung, I'll talk casually to you now.
Please do.
- You don't have a boyfriend, right? - No.
- "We Got Married" ended recently. - That's right.
We happen to be single too.
(Is that so?)
- You are really single? - I don't mean anything by this.
Kwang Soo is...
- You are single too? - Yes.
- We don't have any. - We really don't.
- Why? - How are you single?
What? Why?
- I am really single. - I don't get it. How is that?
Why didn't you ask me that?
(Is it natural that I'm single?)
- I said I was single like he is. - I know that you are popular.
- That's right. He's popular. - I was...
Do you like Jong Kook?
- What's up with you? Stop it. - It's just that...
- Let's be honest. - That's not what I meant.
- It's not that. - In Russia...
(He chokes up.)
Something similar happened.
(His romance with Dasha began as everyone rooted for their love.)
(A long-distance relationship won't be that bad.)
(But as time passed by, )
(Jong Kook overcame the language barrier all by himself.)
(What was the name of the English academy Jae Seok promotes?)
(While Jong Kook and Dasha were getting along well, )
(Kwang Soo was completely forgotten.)
What do I do?
No one is paying attention to me!
(He was traumatized when Jong Kook stole his thunder.)
In Russia, I had a bad experience.
Guys like you are my type.
(It's going to happen today!)
Don't be insecure.
It's true.
I like tall, slim men.
(This is Hye Sung's ideal type.)
(Kwang is very slim and tall.)
I feel like I have to protect you.
I can be the one leading.
Don't fall for me too hard though.
(Don't fall for me too hard though.)
Let's take things slowly.
Kwang Soo always falls in love.
I just fall in love, but I don't have a girlfriend.
It's one-sided love.
Even at this very moment, I am in love.
I can't tell you who it is.
(Hye Sung plays along.)
On the way to the hotel, we should get to know you more...
and what kind of a person you are.
I am very shy.
- You are? - I'm being shy now too.
- Oh, really? - When I feel comfortable...
When I start to feel comfortable,
I have mood swings.
- Really? - Mood swings?
When I am excited, I get really hyper.
When I am tired,
I get like this.
(Flustered)
What's wrong, Kwang Soo?
(I thought we could be soulmates.)
- Why? - This is unexpected.
I didn't know Hye Sung had mood swings.
(Will Hye Sung and Kwang Soo be able to get close?)
- Take this too. - Thank you.
Great work.
- Thank you for your service. - Thank you.
Gosh, this ryokan is...
- This ryokan looks really nice. - It looks great.
This isn't what I had in mind.
(Ryokan is a type of traditional Japanese inn from the Edo period.)
(It consists of a Japanese garden and tatami, Japanese mat.)
I didn't expect we'd stay at a nice ryokan like this.
I was so surprised when I arrived here.
("Walk to the Ryokan with Reporter Jeon So Min")
That's right. Ryokans...
don't have beds. Look.
(It is furnished with tatamis and blankets instead of beds.)
Where is the room for Jae Seok and Haha?
(Jeon So Min, actress from Neunggok)
This is their room.
Can I come in?
Gosh, look. There's the hot tub.
Is that the hot tub?
(This is a tub filled with hot spring water.)
(Mesmerized)
That must be so warm.
(Hot spring water is pouring out.)
Should I dip my feet?
(I'm sorry to say this, but this is Jae Seok and Haha's room.)
- So Min. - Yes?
Jae Seok is taking a shower right next to that tub.
(She's flustered.)
He's in a bind now.
I should get going now.
Jae Seok is taking a shower.
I should go and take a bath too.
(Members at the ryokan end their night on a good note.)
(A team is in desperate need of a hot bath.)
Ji Hyo, you picked us, but I am sorry this happened.
No, don't be. Let's win tomorrow.
- We'll definitely win. Don't worry. - Let's do that.
- I mean this. - Okay.
We will see you tomorrow morning.
Goodnight.
(Goodnight as you dream of turning the tables.)
(The morning of the 1st Place Tour in Tokyo has come.)
(Strategies are important. What is Team So Min's strategy?)
- Good morning. - Morning.
After your breakfast,
you can start your mission.
As I have told you last night, today's project is...
part 1 of People's Recommendation Project, A Place for 1 Percent.
You must find places that boast to be the best.
Right now, what on earth...
What was yesterday's project?
I can't keep up with the projects at all.
We're done with Tour Stickers, and now, we have I Go Stickers.
- We will get those stickers now. - It's like a new season.
- We are done with Tour Stickers? - Yes.
You have new stickers called I Go Stickers.
Goodness.
This is really challenging.
Because you are...
wearing that outfit, you look like a frog even more.
(She looks exactly like a frog.)
Your eyes...
- Aren't they swollen? - Yes.
I had the cup noodles Haha gave me last night.
- You ate that last night? - Yes.
I saw you eat gimbap by yourself last night too.
We were all tired and knocked out,
but she was eating gimbap at a convenience store.
I ate it with a soft-boiled egg.
It was fine until I finished them.
I came back, washed up, and was putting lotion on.
- That's when I felt something. - That happens sometimes.
Everything seemed so scary all of a sudden.
The wardrobe, the blanket chest, and behind the curtain...
Even in my room... You don't have it in your room.
You know the Japanese dressing table with a folding mirror...
It's in my room.
I suddenly felt they were watching me. I was alone in the room too.
- I really... - I was just sound asleep.
Missed Ji Hyo last night.
- What? - I missed her very much.
Even that video call...
Even...
- that video call... - I'm sorry, but I've had enough.
(When will you stop talking? I'm losing my patience.)
So Min, stop talking now.
We didn't even say a word and listened to what you had to say.
This room is much brighter. My room is way...
- The mood is... - It's because of the lights.
Is that so?
(Dazzling)
So Min...
You need to come to your senses. You see the lights are on.
- From the morning... - We kept silent...
not because we didn't know how to talk.
- Them too. - Why then?
I can't stand seeing them either.
Those cameramen.
They're so annoying.
They made it scarier by screaming so hard.
(Kwon Ryeol screamed to death which made Jae Seok more scared.)
(He wanted to avoid ghosts, )
(but he kept on filming. He's indeed a professional cameraman.)
How could he film like this?
(He's now an expert in filming horror stuff too.)
Goodness.
He was so annoying back in Mongolia too.
You, Kwon Ryeol.
We were at our lodging, and he was installing a camera in my room.
I asked whether it captured this side as well.
He said it didn't since he adjusted its angle.
I later watched the show and it captured the entire room.
(It's the angle Jae Seok expected to be captured.)
(It's how Kwon Ryeol adjusted its angle.)
(Jae Seok's privacy was then captured in the camera.)
Seok Jin and I walked around the room without any clothes on.
- It got aired? - Me too.
It happened to me too.
I thought it didn't capture my entire room,
- but apparently, it did. - Right?
It didn't. It's not the case for you. I'm serious.
- Really? - Don't make up stories to talk.
(Don't make up stories and butt in the conversation.)
You come over here.
(Is it your mission to talk a lot today?)
My face is swollen, isn't it?
Why would you change the subject again?
This is making me tired already.
(Japanese breakfast is served for the three who're tired of talking.)
- Thank you. - Good morning.
Hello.
We're grilling meat?
Are we having meat from the morning?
(Kaiseki is a Japanese course meal where various dishes are served...)
(in small amounts in order.)
(It contains the traditional Japanese taste and cooking skills.)
- This must be sushi. - Goodness.
(It looks delicious.)
It's butter.
(She puts butter on the plate.)
(They grill beef on the hot stone plate.)
- Gosh, the sound. - The grilling sound.
It's still in the morning. I need to buy this for home.
I love it.
It melts in my mouth.
(They enjoy the luxury thanks to their choice.)
Gosh, I've never...
had this kind of breakfast before.
- It's like we're playing house. - Really.
It's a bowl of rice.
(Careful)
(He should've asked a question, but messed the sentence up.)
- What did you just say? - It's frustrating.
(He better speak in Korean if he's going to be terrible at it.)
(Here)
- Thank you. - I'm Korean, So Min.
(Thanking in Japanese)
(Jae Seok's flustered.)
- That was funny. - Why would she...
"Thank you... What?"
Goodness, So Min.
Why would you thank me in Japanese?
Come to think of it, my top is wasabi colored.
(She's wearing a wasabi-colored top.)
Gosh, it's delicious.
(He pretends as if he didn't hear it.)
- Why do you ignore her? - What?
(Can't hear anything.)
She just said she's wearing a wasabi-colored top.
I was talking to myself.
- It's delicious. I'm serious. - It's great.
I'm not just saying. It's really good.
I searched online last night.
- There's something. - Tell me about it.
In Tokyo, there's a restaurant...
which first came up with pork cutlet.
- What? - Really?
There's a place pork cutlets first originated from?
(Even Koreans love pork cutlet.)
(This pork cutlet restaurant opened its business in 1895.)
(They maintained its original taste for over 100 years.)
(It's popular among both Japanese and tourists even until now.)
I searched online in the morning as well.
This person runs 100m on 4 legs.
I've seen him on TV before.
- On four legs? - Does he live near here?
On four legs. Yes. He's set a Guinness record.
It says he can run 100m in 15 seconds on 4 legs.
(Ito Kenichi is the living legend of running on four legs.)
(He set a world's fastest record of running 100m in 15.71 seconds.)
He's really running on four legs.
Then does he wear shoes on his hands too?
- Gloves. - He wears gloves.
Well, he runs on four legs, so I was curious.
(Why does today's morning seem so long?)
We have a translator with us, so we can try contacting him if you want.
Really?
If you could do that for us...
(While the staff is trying to contact Ito Kenichi, )
(the three come to experience a hot spring in ryokan.)
Is it awesome?
So Min.
It's so warm and nice.
Gosh, it's hot!
(It's hot!)
- It's hot? - Yes, it is.
- It looks like a waterpark though. - Wow, here...
This must be why people love going to hot springs.
(Haha enjoys with a broom on his head.)
It's nice.
Jae Seok, how many stamps do we need to get?
You can get as many until you arrive at the airport at 4pm.
(They have time until 4pm.)
Then after we have pork cutlet,
I'll move around for stamps alone.
Well...
I have...
(He's the king of online searching.)
I have some places in mind already.
(She becomes curious all of a sudden.)
Haha, let me join you.
Go away.
Even her coming towards me is so scary.
(I want to join you and get a stamp too.)
Stop it.
See how I'm not saying anything. I don't even ask where she's going.
She's not being scary. Let me clear things out.
She's being very annoying.
(She annoys people.)
I'm serious. She annoys people.
I'll go with Haha.
He walks around on four legs like this.
That's very different.
Stop moving around like that.
She's stressing me out.
(The two are exhausted by her chirping.)
(How will their fate turn out?)
I'm still tired even though I had some sleep.
It's ill-fated around this place.
We're still in front of the Labyrinth. Let's leave this place.
Anyway, we have to go look for whatever is in the 1st place, right?
Other than the amusement park ride, is there anything else?
- You need to search yourself. - Search yourself.
- Really? - Yes.
Then... What do you do for the program exactly?
(He wonders what the staff does for the show.)
What are you waiting for? Use your cellphones already.
You'll have nothing to do then.
- Search online now. - Hurry.
- You shouldn't be sitting around. - What do you take us for?
- You made us sleep here already. - Why did you bring us here then?
Goodness, seriously.
Around here, there's an amusement park ride that's ranked on...
- Guinness World Records. - Gosh.
- Is this it? - What?
- Oh, no. - Are you talking about this?
(Are you sure it's this?)
(The roller coaster climbs straight up above the ground.)
(At the end of the climbing, )
(you arrive at a dropping point which is 43m high above the ground.)
(And...)
(they slowly encounter...)
(the extreme fear of the inverse slope that's 121°.)
(They'll have another extreme experience following the Labyrinth.)
Let's ride this first since it's nearby.
Let's move onto the legendary pond after.
(He's found another one.)
(Legendary pond?)
- "Legendary pond"? - It's a pond?
It's at Oshino Hakkai Springs in Yamanashi Prefecture.
Why do they sound so scary?
This seems amazing.
It feels frightening.
"It's part of Mount Fuji."
It's also been designated as a UNESCO World Heritage site.
(By the way)
How should I get on that ride? Are you good at riding those?
Well...
- What? - What's the sound?
(They suddenly hear a mysterious chime bell sound.)
It's in the morning...
Thank goodness, it's bright now.
- It's still scary in the morning. - At least it's bright.
I would've wondered what it was if the sound had been creepier.
- Thank goodness, it's bright now. - Gosh, here...
(Startled)
(They become stiff.)
- The amusement park must be open. - Gosh, it's scary.
What is going on?
- I guess. - Let's get going.
Let's not waste time and hurry.
(Bell ringing)
(Darn it.)
Gosh, let's go.
- I almost swore just now. - You did.
- Let's go. - All right.
- It's open. - The music is exciting.
(They head to find the 1st place items.)
Roller coasters here are unbelievable.
They all look so scary.
Look.
It's dropping straight down.
Straight down.
(I guess everything's at right angle in here.)
That's ridiculous.
I hear people scream all around here.
(Where's the ride in 1st place?)
Where is the ride we're looking for?
That must be it.
- Where? - Over there.
(Did they find the roller coaster?)
(Bingo)
(Guinness World Records admitted to its steep slope.)
(It's called Takabisha.)
(It's also known as Four Great Scream Machine.)
(It's frightening just by looking at it.)
Does it descend vertically?
(Is that the roller coaster we must ride?)
There's no way.
Gosh, what do we do?
(Their jaws drop down.)
It curves inward, so the angle is more than 90º.
(The slope is 121º.)
(Takabisha makes your whole body tremble.)
Gosh, that looks intense.
Let me explain the rules.
The 1st Place Tour is a team competition,
but you collect the stamps individually.
(Stamps are collected individually.)
Based on your decision to stay with the team or not,
the result will vary.
(They must choose every time.)
You may choose...
to be together or separate.
If you choose to be together,
the result of the roulette will apply to all of you.
(The result applies to all if they choose to be together.)
If you choose to be separate,
the result of the ladder will apply to you individually.
(The result of the ladder applies individually.)
(A stamp makes you exempt from the activity.)
Do we get to choose?
This is if we're together.
- That's if we're separate. - Right.
We should go separately then.
(We should go separately then.)
(He chooses to go separately without hesitating.)
What about what you said yesterday?
You said we should win as a team.
- Suddenly... - We should go separately.
Will you play individually?
That's not why.
Isn't it better for the team if we increase the probability?
Right? Let's try it.
- Okay. - Say your decision out loud.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Which will they choose?)
- Separate. - Individual.
(Individual, Separate, Separate)
She said "individual".
(Individual)
- Do you mean individualism? - Individual?
Why did you say that?
- It's done deal. - We all chose to go separately.
- Let's play separately. - Let's do that.
- Let's play separately. - It can be a war.
- I don't know. - I don't know.
I don't know.
- I choose number 2. - Number 2?
(Lucky Ji Hyo chooses number 2.)
(Will she be exempt from riding Takabisha?)
That's right.
I'm number two.
- Okay. - That's Ji Hyo.
- I choose number 1. - Number 1?
Se Chan.
(Each person gets a slot.)
- Seok Jin gets this automatically. - This one.
Seok Jin.
Will we get a stamp without riding it?
(They can get a stamp without riding it.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(What's the result of the separate ladder?)
(It seems unlucky.)
- What's going on? - It seems unlucky.
- It seems unlucky. - Why is it like this?
Take it off slowly.
(Is it an omen?)
What's the result?
O?
- Stamp? - I get a stamp.
I get a stamp.
- Will he be exempt too? - I get a stamp.
I hope he'll have to ride it.
He should ride it.
(If he's exempt from getting on the ride, he's very lucky.)
(It's a circle.)
(They see a circle.)
(One person gets on the ride.)
Se Chan.
(He's in despair.)
(They're happy as long as it's not them.)
(Seok Jin will ride Takabisha.)
(The second slot is revealed.)
- Do it from the back. - I'm in trouble.
Let's see.
(Will Se Chan be exempted?)
- I'll take it off slowly. - Slowly.
- Am I exempt? - You shouldn't be.
You have to. Please.
If so, I'm automatically exempt.
He has to ride it.
(He has to go on the ride.)
(Takabisha is full.)
(However)
(There is no stamp.)
(Se Chan gets no stamp.)
(He remains unlucky in Japan.)
- Gosh. - Se Chan...
is very unlucky.
You should take my misfortune.
You're so lucky, Ji Hyo.
(She gets a stamp and is exempted.)
You'll go on the ride. Put on the camera on your wrist.
Your cameraman will also go on the ride...
in the seat next to you.
(They're the cowardly cameramen from Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear.)
It's not friendly between the two.
I haven't made eye contact with him since this morning.
(At Super Scary Labyrinth of Fear the night before)
(He finds his name tag before other members.)
(He leaves the labyrinth faster than anyone.)
(How could he leave without me?)
You can't get off in the middle of the ride.
- That's true. - We're in this together.
You ran away yesterday, but you have to stay this time.
- Here you go. - What?
Do I have to ride it?
- You have to ride it. - I really don't want to.
He doesn't want to.
You must ride it.
Do you think I want to ride it?
(Their friendship is at risk.)
Why am I walking toward the ride?
What happens if I refuse to do it?
Can't I refuse?
- Then... - It's a democratic country.
You should just go home.
(You should just go home, Seok Jin.)
- Why are you here? - Why?
Get him a flight so he can go home.
You should go home.
(You're so merciless.)
My goodness.
This is insane.
- See you, Se Chan. - I'll come back alive.
I already get the chills.
Ji Hyo, I'll stay alive.
Bye, Se Chan.
Let's take a photo together.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They smile and say goodbye. Poor cameraman)
- See you. - Goodbye.
How does this work?
(The four start their thrilling journey.)
What's this?
Hello.
- No way. - What's going on?
It's so dark here. Why am I on this ride?
(It's the vertical accelerating part.)
(Yelling)
(Screaming)
(Everyone screams on top of the lungs.)
(They start when they come out of the tunnel.)
(Consecutive 360º turns)
(Screaming)
(He films with his eyes closed.)
Yoo Seok couldn't film Seok Jin at all.
I saw him.
He had his eyes closed.
That happened so suddenly.
Is this the end?
No, it's just starting.
- I'm nauseous. - Is it starting only now?
(It already felt like a long ride.)
This can't be the start.
(How can it be the start?)
(They lose their minds.)
I can't do it.
Is it 90º?
- It's over. - I'm really sorry.
What's going on?
(The sight makes your hair stand.)
(It's a vertical ascend of 90º.)
What's this? I see the sky.
(The fall is at 43m from the ground.)
Please.
What's going on?
I can't breathe.
What should we do?
Endure it, Seok Jin.
I can't.
Why am I here?
- Stop the ride. - Don't look down.
My goodness.
(The fear is extreme.)
(The ride stops right before it descends.)
- No way. - I'm scared.
- I can't open my eyes. - I can't see the ground.
- Gosh. - What's going on?
What's going on?
(It's time...)
(It's time to fall.)
(How does it feel?)
(Is it your first time riding the world's best roller coaster?)
(The face experiences the thrill.)
(It's the best facial muscle show.)
I'm sorry.
(It's a moving scene.)
(Se Chan's face...)
(and Takabisha make the best combination.)
This is unbelievable.
- I'm nauseous. - I saw the ground.
Over there.
The ride is over.
Yoo Seok.
(Did they arrive safely?)
I couldn't take photos of them.
Gosh, it was hilarious.
(He heaves a sigh.)
(He's about to pass out.)
You look dizzy.
It's impossible to ride it.
You shouldn't...
ride this roller coaster.
Are you okay?
(He's thankful for still being alive.)
(Ji Hyo and Seok Jin get a stamp.)
(Team Hye Sung in Tokyo)
Is he still sleeping?
(One person is missing.)
Didn't he set his alarm?
Let's go.
(They look for Kwang Soo.)
Is he really sleeping?
It's the 10th floor.
I sent him a message, but he didn't respond.
It was a while back.
This is the room.
(Is he too tired to get up?)
(They ring the bell.)
(It's quiet.)
Is this the room?
It is.
(What's going on?)
(Why isn't he answering?)
(Ringing)
(What are you doing, Kwang Soo?)
(Last night, she confessed that she had mood swings.)
(You never know when her mood will change.)
(I'm here, Kwang Soo.)
(The door opens.)
(Kwang Soo's door finally opens.)
This is not okay.
- Kwang Soo, this is not okay. - Kwang Soo.
What's going on?
It's 10am.
What happened to your nose?
Gosh.
- What about my nose? - What happened?
- He's not wearing pants. - Kwang Soo.
- He's not wearing pants. - Hey.
Kwang Soo is not wearing pants.
I shouldn't look.
Kwang Soo, put on your pants.
Hey.
We're late because of you.
- Get ready. - Kwang Soo.
Are you sure you just woke up?
You look quite okay.
(Wait, what did you just say, Hye Sung?)
You look like you're in the middle of a photo shoot.
(Do I look good right now?)
This is fun.
(Hye Sung and Kwang Soo show off their chemistry.)
Thanks to Kwang Soo, we're starting our day laughing.
(Something is going on between Hye Sung and Kwang Soo.)
How much time do you need?
10 minutes, I promise.
- What about five? - I'm sorry.
Okay, five minutes.
- Five minutes. - Okay.
I'll keep track of the time.
Hye Sung will keep track of the time.
(You have exactly 5 minutes.)
(Will Kwang Soo get ready within 5 minutes?)
Keep track of the time.
(Brushing teeth)
(Changing)
You're lucky that our guest today is Hye Sung.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
You know what might have happened otherwise.
(Time is our advantage.)
- Are we doomed? - Yes, we are.
No. I'll make it up to you.
This is so fun.
- Even if we fail, it'll be fun. - Of course.
- I'm sorry, Hye Sung. - It's okay.
- It's okay to fail. - It'll be good memories.
You're right.
- It'll be good memories. - When will we get to do this again?
With a guy who looks like your sister.
(I'm sorry.)
(This has never happened in the past 7 years.)
This is nice.
(I kept everyone waiting.)
- I'm sorry, Hye Sung. - It's okay.
I'll make it up to you.
I'll do my best today.
(I'll make it up to you.)
It's okay, Kwang Soo.
(Team Hye Sung starts their tour a bit late.)
We have to travel as little as possible.
Are we going...
- to the tallest... - Tower.
- Exactly. - The broadcasting tower.
(They checked this 1st place spot last night.)
(They're on their way to Tokyo Skytree.)
You don't want this picture?
- I gave it to you. - You look so cute.
(You look so cute.)
(Do I look cute?)
Right?
Kwang Soo is so cute.
- He's cute. - He's cute.
- He's really cute. - He's really cute.
Amazing.
He's so cute.
(Hye Sung fell for my charm.)
Your nickname should be Cute.
In Korea, your nickname is Love.
- Here, it's Cute. - Cute.
(Team Hye Sung is full of love.)
(They'll arrive at the world's tallest broadcasting tower soon.)
Gosh, it's so tall.
- Look at that. - Oh, my.
(The world's tallest tower)
It's so tall.
(Guinness World Records states it as the world's tallest tower.)
(It's the 2nd-tallest man-made structure in the world.)
(The world's tallest broadcasting tower, Tokyo Skytree)
As you will see soon,
you will do something fun.
(Sorry?)
(The producer is putting us to the test again.)
What?
What are we going to do?
(Worried)
Are we bungee-jumping?
There is...
a very popular activity here.
Is it something like sky-walking?
(What is waiting for us at the top of the tower?)
(There is an activity at the top of the tower?)
Together or separate?
(They have to choose between together and separate.)
(Together or separate?)
- Hye Sung, I'm sorry. - It's okay.
(Kwang Soo promised he'd commit to the team.)
(He makes up his mind after thinking for a moment.)
- Separate. - Okay.
(Separate?)
(I knew it.)
My goodness.
Hye Sung, which number?
- You can choose first. - You choose first.
You decided.
(The 1st Place Tour)
Number three.
Let's see.
(What will Kwang Soo get?)
Here.
One.
Two.
1, 2, 3.
(He has to participate without getting a stamp.)
(We knew it when he confidently chose "separate".)
(It serves you right.)
(Kwang Soo is participating in the activity.)
(Hye Sung makes a choice.)
- Number 1. - Number 1?
She chooses number one.
(What will Hye Sung get?)
1, 2, 3.
(Hye Sung is participating in the activity.)
(It means...)
(it's the two of us.)
Nice. You two go.
(It means it's the two of us.)
What's with me?
(What's with me?)
What?
- It's a good thing. - See you.
You two go together.
(Anything is fine as long as we can do it together.)
- See you. - See you. Be careful.
We'll see you in a while.
- See you. Good luck. - We'll be quick.
(Jong Kook will be waiting.)
What will we be doing?
I hope it's bungee-jumping.
(They have to go to Observatory 1, which is 350m high.)
It's 350m high.
Are we going up right now?
- My ears. - I feel pressure in my ears.
(They're going up at the speed of 600m per minute.)
We're going up at the speed of 600m per minute.
(In 50 seconds, they're 350m high.)
Are we already 350m high?
Are we 350m high?
Unbelievable.
(Kwang Soo's jaw drops.)
(How does the world's tallest broadcasting tower look?)
(It's so high.)
It's so high.
(Tokyo is at your feet.)
(The tower provides amazing views over the city.)
(What will Kwang Soo and Hye Sung be doing here?)
(Kwang Soo is scared.)
Amazing.
(Hye Sung is excited.)
Don't worry about me. I can see from here.
(Don't do it.)
- You don't like it? - No.
(The skyscrapers look like toys.)
This is beautiful.
(Holding onto the handrail tightly)
(I didn't want to look like this in front of Hye Sung.)
It is very high.
(From the outside, they look like a cute couple.)
(What activity will they participate in?)
It's your turn soon. Get in line.
What are we doing?
You have to stand on this.
(Enjoy the horror of the height.)
It makes me dizzy.
What are you talking about?
Kwang Soo, it makes you dizzy.
(I can imagine.)
- Goodness. - Kwang Soo.
What is this?
Look here.
(Come here.)
You don't have to look down.
- This is scary. - You don't have to look.
(Come on, Kwang Soo.)
Look somewhere else.
(You can rely on me.)
(It's okay. Don't be scared.)
Don't look.
It'll make you dizzy.
(Obedient)
(I can't back off in front of Hye Sung.)
(Under Hye Sung's guidance, Kwang Soo steps forward.)
Look down for three seconds.
(Hye Sung said she was attracted...)
(to a guy she could protect.)
Don't fall for me too much.
(They were just joking around last night.)
- Three seconds. - Okay.
- 1, 2, 3. - I feel a tickle on my toes.
Done.
(They accomplished the Skytree mission.)
(Hye Sung has won 1 stamp.)
- It was fun, right? - Yes.
(Yes, it was very fun.)
I like it.
(I like it.)
Sorry?
I like activities like this.
(Out of embarrassment, Kwang Soo tries to joke.)
I like it too.
(How can she be so unafraid?)
(Dizzy)
(Gulping)
(Her daring attitude makes him gulp.)
It feels like we're on a date.
You think so?
Yes.
You're so much taller than me.
- He really didn't like it. - Who?
- Kwang Soo? - He was afraid of the height.
He was probably embarrassed.
- Is that so? - That's right.
(There is no need to be embarrassed.)
She held my hand.
(Kwang Soo is knocked out.)
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do in this kind of situation.
I will have to study hard...
because I have a long way to go.
Did you see Kwang Soo fall apart?
When you held his hand, he pushed his shoulder down...
to make sure his hand meets yours. Did you see it?
He pushed his shoulder down a little.
I am swinging only my left hand just in case.
His right hand is remaining still.
- Look at that. - You are cute.
- He is really cute. - He is cute.
I heard that there was an incident in Russia.
It was hilarious.
- I can explain. - He fell for a Russian woman.
I told you a little bit of it yesterday.
I was interacting...
with the captain's daughter.
Then he seduced her.
Jong Kook did that.
(Then he seduced her. Jong Kook did that.)
- I didn't seduce her. - He didn't help me out.
- I didn't do that. - He seduced her.
(That was mean of you, Jong Kook.)
My goodness.
That's why I am worried right now.
(I feel bad for Kwang Soo.)
(I will protect you.)
My goodness.
(I can't remain standing up.)
He collapsed.
Don't do that to him.
(He comes 1st place when it comes to heart rate.)
He is very cute.
(Will Kwang Soo and Hye Sung continue to flirt?)
(10:30am, Team So Min's ryokan)
I feel so refreshed.
We need to go meet Ito Kenichi.
- The meeting time is approaching. - Really?
Then we should go right away.
Let's go. It will take some time to reach Tokyo.
(Let's go to Tokyo.)
Are we finally going to Tokyo?
I thought I wouldn't get to see Tokyo.
Other teams got a stamp.
What can we do?
We don't have much time.
It will be 1pm when we arrive.
The first place.
(Thinking hard)
Can it be someone who is the first place in ugliness?
(The 1st place is sitting right next to me.)
- If you do it properly... - Really?
We can stop a passer-by and compare him to Jae Seok.
(Offended)
Haha, you are in no position to talk.
(You are in no position to talk.)
You look very ugly right now.
When you were soaking in the hot spring,
your face was as big as a mountain.
(I saw a sunfish at the hot spring.)
This park is very pretty.
There is a track.
There are a lot of runners.
That man has a sense of presence.
I have seen him on TV.
He is very fast.
I know what he looks like.
I will be able to recognize him if I look closely.
Ito Kenichi.
That's not him.
- No? - That's not him.
- Mr. Kenichi. - That's not him.
(I know because I saw him on TV.)
That's not him. I saw him on TV.
Mr. Ito Kenichi.
I am telling you that's not him.
- I am sorry. - I am sorry.
Don't talk to people. For goodness' sake.
That must be him.
Mr. Ito Kenichi.
He isn't Ito Kenichi.
- That's not him. I told you. - He is really cool.
Can't you tell?
It's obvious that he isn't waiting to meet someone.
- What is it? - Is he over there?
Do you recognize him?
That's him.
(Jae Seok found someone.)
Are you Mr. Ito Kenichi?
- Mr. Ito Kenichi. - Mr. Ito Kenichi.
(Are you Mr. Ito Kenichi?)
(Will they finally meet the 1st place holder?)
(The man who ran 100m in 15.71 seconds, Ito Kenichi)
(The man they only saw on TV...)
(is finally before them.)
Mr. Ito Kenichi.
You are not allowed to film here. Please stop.
(Are they not allowed to film here?)
We can't film here.
You can't film here without submitting a request.
Okay. We will stop.
We can't film here.
(They have no permission to film due to the sudden shoot.)
(Will they be able to see the 1st place holder run on all fours?)
(30 minutes later)
(They resume the shoot at a nearby park.)
Everyone,
you finally found Ito Kenichi,
the champion of running on all fours in The 1st Place Tour.
He is the person I saw on TV.
I imagined him...
- to be a tall man. - That's right.
I thought he would be muscular.
He has muscles like those of Bruce Lee.
He has compact muscles.
However,
while The 1st Place Tour is a match between the teams,
stamps will be given to individuals.
Decide whether or not to share the fate with the team members.
Your decision will change the result.
(Will they share the fate or not?)
Her eyes grew bigger.
I want to stay with my teammates.
(I want to stay with my teammates.)
Let's stay together.
Let's do this the clean way.
Sure.
- Let's decide by majority. - Let's do that.
Who wants to do this separately?
(Me)
(It's every man for himself.)
Then we will do this separately.
- It was bound to happen. - That's right.
I am sure other teams did the same thing.
- It's the ladder. - Is this what we will use?
There are three options.
Watch Mr. Ito Kenichi...
run on all fours and receive a stamp.
Watch Mr. Ito Kenichi run on all fours,
but fail to receive a stamp.
(You don't receive a stamp.)
Have a cameraman watch instead and fail to receive a stamp.
The person who chooses that option won't even get to see him run.
That person will have to leave.
We came all the way here to see him run.
- One of you will have to leave. - If we hadn't set up...
a meeting with Mr. Ito Kenichi,
we could have visited two places.
Let me ask again.
Will you do this together or separately?
Let's raise our hands. Who wants to do this together?
In 1, 2, 3.
(Me)
We will do this separately.
I really want to watch this.
- This is the rule. - Okay.
Now, let's choose the numbers.
Mr. Ito Kenichi.
(The 1st place holder will choose the numbers.)
Okay.
(Jae Seok, the oldest member, )
(gets number one.)
Number one.
He must have recognized Jae Seok as number one.
Thank you.
(Haha with a unique haircut...)
Three.
(gets number 3.)
That hurts my feelings.
You are number three in this group.
- Thank you. - Number two.
So Min is number two.
(So Min gets number 2.)
- Thank you. - Okay.
I will begin with number one.
I am excited.
(Jae Seok goes down the ladder of fate.)
- Open. - Open.
Please.
- Maybe I will have to leave. - No way. It's number one.
(Will Jae Seok get to see Mr. Kenichi run?)
(Watch and earn a stamp)
(I am off to a good start.)
This is a disaster.
He will earn a stamp.
- Thank you. - This is a disaster.
- Haha. - Okay.
This is a disaster.
(It's Haha's turn.)
(Will his 3 hours of effort bear fruit?)
(Watch, but fail to earn a stamp)
(A slight difference in numbers changed their fate.)
- Thank goodness. - Haha failed to earn a stamp.
So Min, please leave.
What? I want to watch him run.
The cameraman will watch in her place.
- I want to watch him run. - Please leave.
- I was curious. - Please leave.
- Please give me an opportunity. - No, So Min.
- I can watch from afar. - Bye.
(She has to leave by herself.)
We don't have much time.
Am I really not allowed to watch?
- Am I really not allowed to watch? - Please wait at the car.
Does that mean Si Yeon will watch?
So Min, we are running behind.
- We need to move things along. - So Min,
- bye. - Bye.
Bye.
- Really? - Thank you.
I can't believe it.
Am I really not allowed to watch?
My goodness.
Hold the camera.
- I have to go and watch him run. - My goodness.
(Please hold the camera so I can get a good look.)
Go and watch him run.
- Go and watch him run. - I will be back.
He is really leaving.
Si Yeon,
tell me about it later.
(Please enjoy it and give me a review.)
Now, Mr. Ito Kenichi will run.
Mr. Ito Kenichi usually runs 100m.
It's too bad that this park...
is a bit small.
It must be about 20 to 30m long.
(Running Man Sports)
It's too bad...
that we are doing this...
at a playground in the residential area.
First, Haha will give it a try.
(Haha versus Ito Kenichi)
(Ito Kenichi)
(He set the world record by running 100m in 15.71 seconds.)
(The human cheetah, Ito Kenichi)
(I am confident when it comes to running on all fours.)
(7 years of variety shows gave Haha a lot of practice.)
(Who will be the 1st in the world?)
All right. Get ready.
Get ready.
(Ito Kenichi versus Haha)
Start.
(It's a competition between Ito Kenichi and Haha.)
He runs 100m on all fours.
(He calls the start of the race.)
(He's a wild cheetah on the hunt.)
(He's the fastest in the world.)
(He's mesmerized by the cheetah.)
Start.
(He falls over.)
(He couldn't resist the gravity.)
(Embarrassed)
He's very fast.
(The race seems pointless.)
It's not easy to move on all fours.
Right.
(He moves awkwardly.)
You're going sideways.
- It's hard. - I thought you were a crab.
(I thought you were a crab.)
You looked like a crab.
- Crabs are in season soon. - Right.
Thank you again, Ito.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Now that I'm carrying the camera,
I understand the pressure Si Yeon must feel.
It must've been hard to carry it at the Labyrinth yesterday.
I bet it looked like this.
(I bet it looked like this.)
(She's playful even when she's alone.)
Shall I take a peek?
Shall I take a peek? I think I can see him from here.
I see him.
(She decides to zoom in with the camera.)
I see the camera director.
He's running.
You can see him by zooming in.
I couldn't see him. When he leans forward...
to run on all fours, I can't see him.
I only saw a part of his buttocks.
(She's disappointed.)
You're working hard.
This place looks pretty.
(Si Yeon comes back.)
You're back, Si Yeon. Did you see him?
- Tell me. - I only saw him run.
Did you see him?
Tell me what you think. How did he run?
He ran very quickly on all fours like a monkey.
Was he very fast?
Do his hands and feet move separately?
- Or do the hands move together? - Hands move together.
Is it really surprising?
Yes, it's surprising.
I see.
Give me the camera.
Thank you.
(Her film shoot ends.)
- The camera is quite heavy. - Yes.
It's very heavy.
In the end, I couldn't see him.
(She gives it a try.)
Was this how he did it?
(We hope she won't be exempt next time.)
By the way, we're running very late.
Will we be able to get another stamp?
Let's go to the pork cutlet restaurant now.
Pork cutlet will make me feel better.
The way it's served...
- looks very delicious. - Really?
It looks classic.
(It's simple and made without artificial flavoring.)
(The restaurant made classic pork cutlet for 122 years.)
We must be together no matter what.
Why aren't you responding?
(Why are you silent?)
I was wondering if that would be necessary.
I prefer to play separately.
(She wants to play individually.)
It's possible to have that opinion.
You may not be aware, but I'm very lucky today.
I have a good feeling.
You may want to play separately, but...
Let's wait and see if that feeling is unlucky.
Unlucky?
How could you say that?
- Let's see what happens. - Okay.
- So Min. - Yes?
If we agree on playing together, we'll stay together.
If we agree on playing separately, we'll be separate.
- I see. - Okay.
Okay.
Try to convince me.
(In that case, try to convince me.)
- What are you talking about? - No way.
- We're still a team. - What's wrong with you?
Convince you? What are you talking about?
"Is it together or separate?"
- "Convince me." - I can't believe this.
That makes a good title.
It has a ring to it. What is it?
"Is it together or separate? Convince me."
(It's a segment within a segment.)
"Convince me."
- So Min. - Yes?
Don't be sly again.
- Share your ideas. - Do some research.
I found the oldest cafe...
in Tokyo that still exists.
- I found it. - We should go there.
- You know this cafe? - Let's go there.
- We should go there. - That sounds great.
- Let's go there. - This cafe became famous...
after John Lennon and Yoko Ono's visit.
- Really? - That's great.
So Min who lives in Neunggok...
would love it.
She's the first in Korea.
She's an actress from Neunggok.
She's a silly woman from Neunggok.
(How dare you?)
("Silly Woman" by Haha)
You should stop singing old songs.
You always sing old songs.
(He became an old man.)
(He sings a recent song.)
- What? - Stay quiet if you don't know.
Just stay quiet.
Is this it? Let's go.
Let's get out.
- We're getting out. - Take it.
Thank you.
- Where is it? - Is it here?
Where is it?
(It's the world's best pork cutlet restaurant that opened in 1895.)
(With 122 years of history, the restaurant's pork cutlet is light.)
- Before you go in... - We don't have time.
All right.
Will you be together?
- Separate. - Separate.
(What did you say?)
- Will you be separate? - Yes.
- That's cruel. - We have to keep researching.
Fine, we'll be separate.
One is eating pork cutlet and getting a stamp.
One is eating pork cutlet without a stamp.
- I want to place second. - One is not eating.
One is not eating without a stamp.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
We could have been together.
I don't want to.
- Number 2. - Number 2.
Just go home.
(Haha gets to eat without a stamp.)
You get to eat but will not get a stamp.
1 of the 2 is the worst.
What if I don't get to eat?
I choose number one.
- Number one? - Yes.
Goodbye, So Min.
(Will So Min get lucky or not?)
(Who will get lucky on the ladder?)
(She neither gets to eat nor gets a stamp.)
(Is it because Kwang Soo isn't here?)
- That's incredible. - It's because Kwang Soo isn't here.
(So Min gets very unlucky.)
(She misses him. Are you well, Kwang Soo?)
I'm leaving.
- Where are you going? - Haha...
and Jae Seok will go eat.
I think...
I'm very lucky today.
It's a sad reality.
(What's wrong with me today?)
My goodness.
(They enter the best pork cutlet restaurant.)
The way you punch in the numbers in the calculator...
- Is it like a typewriter? - Yes.
(He decides to ask the owner.)
Is this the first restaurant?
That's right.
(Started as a French restaurant, it made the world's first pork cutlet.)
French cuisine?
(It became famous as a pork cutlet restaurant.)
It's an honor to be here. I love pork cutlet.
(How will it taste?)
Thank you very much.
It looks very simple.
(Pork cutlet is served only with cabbage and without any sauce.)
This is...
(It's the most classic pork cutlet.)
Look at how juicy the meat is.
Look.
- It's the first pork cutlet. - I need some mustard.
(So Min watches them eat.)
The meat is different.
(It's thick.)
It's very meaty.
It's soy sauce.
(He takes a big bite.)
(The best, nutty flavor spreads inside his mouth.)
I couldn't watch Ito Kenichi run.
I can't eat either.
It's so delicious, So Min.
It's good without any sauce.
(She stares at the food.)
Give me one bite.
- I want to. - Give me one bite.
I really want to.
It's so delicious.
How about...
(How about we tease So Min whose mouth is watering?)
(She reaches for it.)
(She falls for Jae Seok's trick.)
- What are you doing? - Weren't you giving it to me?
I thought you were.
I was about to eat it.
Why did you try to eat it?
I didn't know.
I thought you were giving it to me.
(She reaches for it again.)
What are you doing?
I thought you were feeding me.
It's really delicious.
(Give me one bite.)
What are you doing?
(I'll eat 100 pork cutlet in Korea.)
- Hurry and eat. - I finished.
We should hurry. Where's the cafe?
I think it's nearby.
- Really? - Let's run.
- Let's go now. - Okay.
Where's the cafe?
It's called Paulista.
Other than the cafe, we have one more place to go.
We're running late.
(Some are lost near Mount Fuji.)
Okay, let's go.
- Let's go, Seok Jin. - Ji Hyo.
There's a place called Wakuike.
A lot of water runs here.
There are many bodies of water,
- but it has the most water. - Let's go there.
We should tell them because it's the first place.
It's the top.
(Wakuike is a lake in Oshino located at the bottom of Mount Fuji.)
(With the most amount of water, it's registered as a natural monument.)
(Drinking water from this legendary lake brings you luck.)
(The lake springs the most amount of water due to permanent snow.)
Will you be together or separate?
The same rule applies.
- This time, - Let's be together.
- we're here... - Together?
Already.
Let's drink water together.
Be together?
In 1, 2, 3.
- Together. - Together.
We'll spin the roulette.
- "Doing it for one stamp". - "Doing it for one stamp".
- No activity and no stamp. - No stamp.
- There are two options. - It's 50-50.
Now that we're here, we should drink the water from the mountain.
If you end up not doing the activity,
only the cameramen will wash their hands.
(Only the cameramen will wash their hands.)
We will wash our hands too.
We will do it.
Please.
(With a 50-percent chance, they will get to wash their hands.)
(With a 50-percent chance, only the others will benefit.)
(What result will they get together?)
(They will do the activity and get a stamp.)
- Yes! - Yes!
(What is going on?)
We should of course try the water.
- Of course. And wash our hands. - We'll wash our hands too.
The water is from Mount Fuji.
- When will we get to try it again? - Exactly.
Then drink the water and wash your hands.
- You'll also get a stamp. - Okay.
The staff members should wash their hands too.
I'm getting excited.
We have to hold out for 30 seconds.
- Hold? - One...
Can you keep track of time?
(Having your hands in the water for 30 seconds brings good luck.)
1, 2, 3.
(The cold hits.)
(Their hands are freezing.)
It's so cold.
It's ice cold.
It's unbelievable.
It's 27°C to 28°C outside.
Let's win the game today.
(Let's win the game.)
Like this?
(They drink the water too.)
It's so cold.
(This is why people love to drink permanent snow.)
Will I have a second child?
Will this water give me a second child?
(The permanent snow makes you plan for a second child.)
- Seok Jin, good luck. - Seok Jin.
- I'll have a second child. - Good luck.
I'll have a second child.
- We rode the rollercoaster. - We did.
We washed our hands with the glacier water.
Now...
- Let's go for some sushi. - Sushi?
Okay. Find a famous place.
Find the number-one place.
Since our theme is to find first places,
we have to visit the best sushi place in Japan.
I saw a place with Michelin stars.
- A sushi place? - Yes.
They won 2 Michelin stars for 4 years in a row.
I'd love to try that place. Will we be able to go there?
- This place looks amazing. - We might have to wait.
(It's a sushi restaurant owned by a sushi master, Ono Jiro.)
(He is the oldest chef with 3 Michelin stars.)
(Seok Jin is searching too.)
- We should... - Hey.
Amazing. Hold on.
There is the world's first red bean bread place.
- The world's first. - I saw that place yesterday.
It opened in 1875.
We'll go to the sushi place first.
- If we fail... - If we fail, we'll go to...
- the bakery. - We'll go to the bakery.
- We don't have much time left. - We don't.
(They have about 4 hours left.)
Sir, please...
go to Tokyo.
- We are going there. - We are going there.
Please go to Tokyo.
(We're already on our way there.)
Tokyo.
You've seen the signs.
Why do you say that?
I love Tokyo.
(We've been heading to Tokyo since morning.)
We finally get to see buildings.
(After 2 hours, they finally arrive.)
I think we can have the red bean bread.
But the sushi place closes at 2pm.
- At 2pm? - Yes. What time is it now?
It's 1:50pm.
- Gosh. - That's a problem.
We might not make it.
- Can we pull up here? - You have to run.
Okay. Let's run.
(They arrive at the sushi place 5 minutes before the closing time.)
We don't have much time.
Let's run.
- Turn right. - Turn right.
Turn right.
It's there.
(Seok Jin: 2 stamps, Ji Hyo: 2 stamps, Se Chan: 1 stamp)
Time is running out.
What time is it now?
(They have to get there within 2 minutes.)
- It's 1:57pm. - It's 1:57pm.
Where is the place?
It's here.
(Will they get to try the sushi and win stamps?)
Is this the place? Excuse me.
Is it closed?
- No sushi? - No sushi.
- I'm hungry. - No.
I want this sushi. I like this sushi.
We're already closed for today.
(We're closed.)
- Come back another time for dinner. - Dinner?
What time do you open?
From 5:30pm.
- Oh, my gosh. - 5:30pm?
Is that so?
You have to make a reservation.
- A reservation? - What about...
- What about takeout? - No takeout.
- No takeout? - No takeout.
No takeout.
- We're going back to Seoul today. - To Seoul?
- Please. - Bye-bye.
(Bye-bye)
- Let's have red bean bread. - Let's run.
We have to get there before the other team does.
Let's try the world's first red bean bread place.
- Are we going to the bakery? - Finally...
- That looks tasty. - That looks tasty.
Can't we get one?
We don't have much time.
- Let's try one. - We don't have time.
Lead the way. Where is the place?
(They're on their way to the world's first red bean bread place.)
- It's here. - Where?
(The place sure looks old.)
- It's here. - It's here.
(This red bean bread place opened in 1869.)
(They invented red bean bread in 1874.)
(What will they choose this time?)
- Sorry? - Right.
- We have to make a choice. - What choice?
Together or separate?
- Here? - We have to choose "separate".
We choose "separate".
1, 2, 3.
- Separate. - Separate.
(Team Ji Hyo chooses "separate".)
- I choose number 3. - Number 3.
I choose number one.
Here we go.
I'm getting nervous.
(Will Ji Hyo stay in 1st place?)
Let's see. It's an X.
- It's an X. - You get no stamp.
(No stamp and no bread)
- Yes! - Yes!
- You can wait here. - You can wait here.
(Enjoy your bread.)
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
It's my turn.
- I get the bread. - You get the bread.
- And a stamp. - And a stamp. Yes!
Then we'll be tied.
(Seok Jin and Se Chan will get to try the bread.)
(I want to swear at them.)
- Let's try the red bean bread - Hurry.
- I wish Seok Jin didn't get one. - Wait here.
It's okay, Ji Hyo.
- Wait here. - Finally.
Let's go in.
That was close.
(They enter the bakery after dancing.)
(It's crowded.)
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
(They look tasty.)
Two of those.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
(They order in Korean.)
This too...
Look at Ji Hyo.
(Do you guys know how I feel?)
(I'm watching you eat the world's first red bean bread.)
You want some, right?
(I'm watching you eat the world's first read bean bread.)
I wish Seok Jin didn't get any bread.
(His bread should have been mine.)
Let's try them.
(They try the bread right away.)
It smells so good.
(Teasing)
(Let me taste the red bean paste.)
It has a history of 148 years.
You don't get any.
Let's hurry.
- This tastes amazing. - What is this?
(Let me at least touch it.)
It has sticky rice in it. Look at this.
(Ji Hyo puts it in her mouth.)
- Hey. - Ji Hyo.
It's not red bean bread!
(Ji Hyo eats the bread!)
- Hey. - Here.
(Spit it out right now.)
You can have one.
My goodness.
- It's not red bean bread. - It's not.
(Ji Hyo swallowed the sticky rice bread right away.)
What is this street called again?
- Harajuku. - Harajuku.
- I haven't been here in forever. - Same.
(30 minutes ago)
- It's not so crowded. - Right?
There's a crepe street in Harajuku.
Why don't we find the oldest place?
The oldest crepe place.
Let's do this.
Yes!
I haven't been here in forever.
(They look for the oldest crepe place.)
(It's a street of youth.)
After the crepe place...
- I think we can find a lot here. - Right?
(The street is full of pretty accessories and good food.)
Is that something else?
It is.
It's hard to find the oldest place.
It's harder than I expected.
"Is this the oldest place?"
(We should ask them.)
(They enter the crepe street, trying to memorize the sentence.)
Is this the place?
- Is this the place? - It's either one of them.
If it turns out to be the oldest place, I'll give you the rules.
- What was it? - "Is this the oldest place?"
(Let me ask.)
Is this the oldest crepe place?
(Is this the oldest crepe place?)
(The place look similar to the other new stores.)
Yes, it is.
- Is this the place? - Is this the oldest place?
(They find the oldest place.)
- It is the oldest place. - It is.
(It's the oldest crepe place in Japan.)
(It's been in business in Harajuku for 41 years.)
Hye Sung, you choose first.
- Number 2. - Hye Sung chooses number 2.
(What will Hye Sung get?)
Here we go.
(No food and no stamp)
I get nothing. What did I say?
I said I was unlucky.
Hye Sung, do you want to wait in the car?
Jong Kook chose number three.
(Jong Kook's result is revealed.)
One, two...
(Who will get the stamp?)
(Jong Kook: crepe and no stamp, Kwang Soo: crepe and a stamp)
No way.
Kwang Soo.
(It's the Harajuku miracle.)
(He's been unlucky for 7 years. Is the curse broken now?)
This is so not fair.
He woke up late, and he got everything.
- He gets the food and the stamp! - He's trash.
- Wait. - I was the first one to get up.
Why am I trash? I didn't choose to do this.
He comes to Japan often and met many Japanese women.
He's used to Japan.
- I see. - What are you talking about?
- I'm not trying to make an excuse. - You have the power from Japan.
- He has the power from Japan. - What is she talking about?
- I was the first one to get up. - That won't do.
Let's order first.
Please go ahead.
(He denies any rumors and orders crepe.)
She's making it.
- She's making it on the spot. - She must be a master.
(She adds whipped cream on top of baked dough.)
- That's incredible. - Is it kind of like...
- sweet pancakes in Korea? - I think so.
She's so good.
Originals are different.
(This is the original crepe.)
She didn't even take 10 seconds.
Can you ask how long she's been doing this for?
Thank you very much.
It's been 10 years.
10 years?
Really?
Does that mean you started when you were in elementary school?
I started when I was in 18.
She started when she was in 18.
- Really? - I see.
- Thank you. - She looks to be 20.
- I'm serious. - Thank you.
Me? Pardon?
She said you look to be 20.
Can you tell her I'm 42?
(I'm 42 years old.)
(What? Really?)
Excuse me, but what are you guys doing?
- Are you trying to ask her out? - No.
- Thank you. - Let's leave.
- You're acting strange in Japan. - No way.
Thank you.
- Thank you very much. - Thank you.
(Does this crepe contain a dose of love?)
It's the original. It's like the original granny's restaurant.
(How does the crepe taste?)
(Why is Hye Sung holding the crepe?)
Hye Sung.
(You see...)
- I gave it to her. - I'm taking a bite.
(I gave it to her.)
She wanted some.
(This strange man gave his hard-earned crepe to Hye Sung.)
(What did you say? Oh, my goodness.)
(I feel bad for eating it alone. Would you like some?)
It's okay. Can I have a bite?
(It's okay, Hye Sung. Can I just have a bite?)
I know what this is.
(He pretends like he doesn't see it.)
I bet women like it.
(What's between Jong Kook and Hye Sung?)
Did you stay in New York for a long time?
No, I was in LA.
(Jong Kook and Hye Sung can't stop talking in the car.)
Don't you like going to the amusement park?
I love amusement parks. I went by myself once...
because my friend didn't want to go.
(You know I'm here too, right?)
(Hye Sung, do you remember the chemistry you had with me earlier?)
I love going to the sea and surfing.
A lot of people do that.
(Forget it. What's the whole point?)
I love water too.
There's sea everywhere.
It's the same with every ethnicity.
If I don't react too much here, use the portion from Russia.
(What are you talking about, Kwang Soo?)
(Don't you remember, Jong Kook?)
(Don't you remember the love triangle 3 weeks ago?)
(Is this some sort of a deja vu?)
I wanted to try that.
- You drive... - Road trip.
- That's right. - It's the best.
- I wanted to try it. - It's the best.
(Get off. I want to be alone.)
- That sounds awesome. - You know what? The views...
- are incredible. - I think I would love it.
You'd get speechless.
(Actually, I can quit this team.)
(What's going on, Kwang Soo?)
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - What?
- What's wrong? - I'm hot.
Let go.
- Let go. - What's wrong?
It's hot.
Why are you hot?
I'm just sharing my experience.
It'd be good for her to try.
It's a great experience.
You shouldn't have said you'd set us up.
(Don't ever say that again, Jong Kook.)
I'm sharing my travel stories.
No, it's okay.
- I'm okay. - We were talking about traveling.
I'm okay.
- We're here. - You should...
- try it. - It's fine.
(They're near their next destination.)
(Giggling)
When did this take the wrong turn?
Did I wake up too late?
Is it the king crab? When was it?
Can you go a bit back, Kwang Soo?
I'll go all the way back.
I'll start walking from here.
Go, you two. It looks better that way. It looks great.
- Why? - Keep going.
- What's wrong? - He wants me to go to the back.
He wants me to go to the back. I was covering you.
I was covering you two, so he wanted me to go away.
I shouldn't be standing here like a third wheel.
He wants me to go away.
- What do you mean? - I'm right.
I was going to leave you be anyways.
(Where did it all go wrong?)
It's here.
Paulista.
Let's do this together.
- Let's do this together. - Sure. I'm in.
- Together? - Let's try it.
Okay.
Okay? Let's try together.
- Sure. - Sure. Let's do it together.
If I get another stamp and win,
- you two... - No.
This depends on luck.
- You'll arrange us in good places? - Yes.
(If Jae Seok wins, he'll give them good positions on the dice.)
Can you promise us?
- Stamp, autograph, copy, - Sure.
- and laminate. - You too.
(They finish their contract ritual.)
Okay.
- Let me win. - Okay.
- Make sure you help him win. - Help me, okay?
- We'll do this together. - We might get a stamp.
- That's right. - Of course.
- We'll start. - Start. Go ahead, So Min.
Go, So Min.
Please.
(They are betting their hopes on Jae Seok.)
Show me my luck.
(Will they be able to get some stamps?)
(They win stamps and food.)
(Their strategy worked.)
(Nice, So Min.)
You're awesome. I won a stamp.
That was awesome.
I have three stamps.
- It's possible. - It is.
Would you like three traditional coffee?
- Yes. - Yes.
Here it is.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Is this the oldest coffee? - Yes.
That's interesting.
The scent...
What do you think, Jae Seok?
It's old style.
It's old style coffee.
It's plain, old style coffee.
It does taste like old style coffee.
I'm getting nervous.
I think you can do it.
You won't betray us, right?
- Everybody. - Right?
If I become the winner,
I won't forget about you.
- Please become the king. - I'll never forget.
- I'll give you my vote. - Please become the king.
- I plead you. - Please become the king.
(I plead both of you.)
- Please help me, So Min. - I will.
I hope you don't forget our loyalty.
I won't.
Please make me the king.
- I know you can do it. - I'll work hard...
for you.
Rise, King Grasshopper.
I'll send Jong Kook...
- abroad. - Please send him.
Ji Hyo has never been penalized.
- Please send her. - I'll send those two away.
Please keep your promises.
I will.
Please become the king.
(Please become the king...)
(and grant our wish.)
Rise, King Grasshopper.
(What will become the fate of King Grasshopper?)
Seok Jin, what about the oldest building?
Oldest building?
- Oldest building? - What about the oldest car?
Oldest building or oldest car.
Or should we go to that bestselling lottery place?
Right.
- They're bestselling lottery place. - That's a good idea.
- We don't have time. - You only have...
(There's only 13 minutes left.)
You only have 13 minutes left.
- We have to get back too. - Right.
- It won't work then. - It won't.
It's too bad,
- but with limited time... - No, I'll get down on my knees.
Please.
(Let us do the mission.)
Isn't this the first ever?
- This is the first ever. - This is where...
Ji Hyo went down on her knees in Japan.
- That works. - You're right.
- Please give us a chance. - She's being sincere.
- You should accept this. - I'll beg.
Give us one chance.
(I'm sorry, but time is ticking. We must leave now.)
(Meanwhile)
- Are we passing by it again? - In 1, 2, 3.
(Kwang Soo wins 2 more stamps.)
Let's think about something else.
- What about a toy store? - Toy store?
Or McDonald's? The burger restaurant?
Book... Bestselling book.
- Bestseller. - That works.
Let's go for the bestselling book.
We can do albums too.
That's right.
How pretty.
Excuse me, sir. Are there any...
- first ever places in Japan? - Are there any?
There's this really old supply store nearby.
- Let's go. - How old is it?
(Well...)
It's really old. Maybe over 100 years?
- Let's go there. - Let's go. Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Itoya?
Do you have the comic book "One Piece"?
- "One Piece". - "One Piece".
- Okay. Thank you. - They have it.
It's here.
"One Piece" is on Guinness World Records.
- It's been published the most. - Really?
It's "One Piece" volume 44.
Good.
Where is it?
Cross the street.
This is Itoya.
That.
It's huge.
- It's the oldest store. - This is it?
- It's so clean. - It's huge.
It's a stationery shop? It's so pretty.
(It's the first ever stationery shop that was built in Japan in 1904.)
(It has everything you could ask for from stationeries to necessities.)
Please.
Please become the king.
Just once.
- All right. - Please become the king.
Would you like to be together or separate?
- We've always been together. - We'll try together.
From beginning to end...
- We've always been together. - Since the start of this tour,
we've always been together.
Go, King Grasshopper.
- Go, King Grasshopper. - May I...
- try? - Do it.
(Lucky girl So Min turns the wheel.)
(Please...)
- I have a bad feeling. - It's okay.
Would you like to go together or separate?
- Let's do it separately. - Separate.
Choose a number, Kwang Soo.
I choose 2. No, 3.
- Is it three? - Okay.
(Kwang Soo chooses number 3 at the end.)
- It's simple. - Is this it?
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are both in 1st place right now.)
That wasn't what you expected.
I have to get it this time.
You have to get it to win.
(This stamp will decide who the winner is.)
(Who's the ultimate winner?)
(5pm at Narita Airport)
Hello.
Everybody.
People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent.
I'll reveal the winner...
of the First Place Tour in Tokyo.
My gosh.
(Who gathered the most number of stamps?)
The winner of the First Place Tour...
collected...
(Is it Kwang Soo who went for 4 stamps at the end...)
(or Jae Seok?)
It's Jae Seok who won four stamps.
(Jae Seok is the winner of the 1st Place Tour.)
It's Jae Seok?
Tell us. How did he win four stamps?
I almost had four.
I could have been the king.
(At the first ever stationery shop in Japan, )
(So Min spun the wheel.)
(She was the king maker...)
(who helped Jae Seok win.)
My gosh.
(Meanwhile, this was Kwang Soo's fourth try.)
(He hoped for something else, )
(but there was no miracle.)
(He didn't win any stamps.)
- I almost had it. - Goodness.
That turned around.
- You've become the king. - Thanks so much.
(Jae Seok is the winner, so he doesn't get any I Go Stickers.)
(The person with the assigned number on the die gets an I Go Sticker.)
(If you get 3 I Go Stickers, you get to visit the recommended place.)
(That place for 1 percent...)
(might be scary or thrilling.)
(Which member will be on their way to that place for 1 percent?)
(Jae Seok's team members made him the king.)
(They were faithful king makers.)
(Jong Kook is the target because he always gets the best of them.)
(Ji Hyo is always exempt from penalties.)
Keep your promises.
(Please become the king and punish these two.)
The winner will get to decide your fates.
(Their fates depend on Jae Seok's hands.)
(It's party time for So Min and Haha.)
Why are they happy?
- Wasn't this an individual game? - They were on the same team.
- Things happened. - We were fighting intensely...
- and something happened. - Something worked out.
Please be understanding.
Can I toss the die?
You can practice.
I figured this out from yesterday.
It's all chances.
It's one-sixth of a chance.
I want to save my team members...
and give them the lower percentages.
What do you mean? It's all the same.
It's all the same.
I have a good feeling.
Me too. Let's think about chances.
(He gets 2.)
What's that?
Research at home.
We have no time.
Why would you try it here?
I don't have this at home.
(He ignores Jong Kook.)
- Why do you keep trying? - I got two.
- I keep getting two. - Stop it.
Please give me six.
- I'll give you six. - Thank you.
- I'll give you six. - Stop it.
- King Grasshopper. - King Grasshopper.
I'll assign my team members...
to six.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- You are both six. - You can lay them out.
Jong Kook and Ji Hyo have to go. They have to go.
I'll put Jong Kook...
in three.
- Ji Hyo can take one. - Okay.
- Kwang Soo can be two. - Is there no dud?
Kwang Soo.
- All right. - Let's go.
Okay. Start.
(This is Jae Seok's lofty and calculated plan.)
(Will Jong Kook be chosen?)
(Or would it be Ji Hyo who's never been penalized?)
- Jae Seok. - I'm number five.
(Ji Hyo is number 1.)
(Will either of them be chosen?)
I figured this out yesterday. It's all about probability.
(From simulation, he got number 2 the most.)
(Unlucky Kwang Soo has that number.)
(Jae Seok put his team members in number 6 because he never got it.)
(King Grasshopper, please toss a small number.)
(What will happen to So Min and Haha?)
Please toss number six.
- Move. Move over. - Toss number six.
I hope it's not me.
(The die...)
(is cast.)
(Who will...)
(be the lucky ones?)
(Is it somebody unexpected or one of Jae Seok's targets?)
(Haha and So Min get a Sticker each.)
Jae Seok.
(Goodness)
(It's time to celebrate.)
(Is he serious?)
Toss it high.
He never got six in practice.
He never got six.
What was that?
- What are you? - I made this dramatic.
What are you?
- Viewers, I did it. - You punk.
- What are you? - Hey.
(Haha and So Min get an I Go Sticker each.)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(Mismatch Race)
I'm at exit eight.
(It's a possibility under 1 percent.)
(All members have to choose something different.)
(That's the only way for the race to end.)
(This is over, right?)
(These ladies make you look.)
(Yes, it's you.)
(You next to her...)
(and you.)
(They'll make your heart flutter.)
(They're strange women...)
(and the more strange couples.)
(Yes, I want some new face.)
(They are strange women...)
(and strange faces.)
(Yes, I want some new race.)
(Next week on Running Man, Strange Partners)