The weather is amazing today.
I'm sweating immediately.
It's either rain or hot weather.
- Because it's summer. - It's so hot.
- Today... - Luckily, it's not humid.
- Look at the sky. - It's so hot.
Today's race is the Summer Vacation Special,
and it's called Partner Race at Running High School.
- Running High School? - Partner?
- We took a gap year. - It's like Benjamin Button.
- Traveling back in time. - We took a gap year.
Since it's Partner Race, you need to partner up with someone.
- Sure. - Please come in.
Right away?
Where are they coming from?
(The music sounds familiar.)
What?
(Could their partners be...)
(They are hotter than this hot summer.)
(They're joining today's race as the members' partners.)
- It's Girls' Generation. - Girls' Generation!
- My goodness! - Girls' Generation!
(They're happy to see them.)
Girls' Generation!
- Welcome! - Goodness!
How long has it been?
My goodness.
(They're back on Running Man after 2 years.)
- Right, this was it. - They still remember the dance.
They haven't forgotten about it.
("Into the New World" by Girls' Generation)
Goodness.
I remember those dance moves.
(It's their debut song that portrays their youthful charms 10 years ago.)
Great.
It was like an oasis during my military life!
Let's go!
Is it "Gee" this time?
(The entire country knows this song.)
- No, no, no, no, no - No, no, no, no, no
(They're releasing all their stress.)
- My body shakes, gee - My body shakes, gee
(Shouting with all his might)
- Oh, yes - Oh, yes
(You can't help but fall straight into their charms.)
(I love it!)
(Girls' Generation has returned to Running Man after 2 years.)
- They're still pretty. - Goodness.
Girls' Generation!
(He's going crazy to see them.)
It's awesome.
- It's so exciting. - Hi, guys.
- So exciting. - I know.
- I love it. - All your songs...
- became incredibly famous. - We were crazy about their songs.
They're all just so good.
They didn't show us "Gee" though.
(Come to think of it...)
(He wonders why they didn't perform "Gee".)
They just showed us that song.
- It was the second song. - Did they?
- They performed "Gee". - We did it.
- It was the second song. - What's wrong with you?
They did it.
(Embarrassed)
- I can't believe you said that. - Sorry.
This is wonderful news. It's finally...
their 10th year anniversary since their debut.
(Congratulations!)
You should all be aware of...
how great this means.
They debuted when they were high school students.
They were so young when they first made their debut.
Now, they're showing their amazing talents in many kinds of fields.
- I know. - Right.
Yu Ri is still panting.
(Her body is different from 10 years ago.)
- Come on. - Why don't you go wash your face?
- I mean... - You're being too mean...
when I'm here after a long time.
- Are you tired? - Yu Ri is the only one...
- who seems very exhausted. - Goodness.
Whenever I see Yu Ri, I'm reminded of Trick Yu Ri,
- the segment we did long ago. - Right.
- Oh, right. - The questions.
Right, I remember too. The quiz.
- Right. - The quiz.
She made Kwang Soo's heart flutter then.
- She was the first one to do so. - There was something between us.
It was Yu Ri.
(During Trick Yu Ri 7 years ago)
(He's shy.)
(His face turned red.)
I've never seen him this way.
Do you love her? Is your heart beating quickly?
(I'm glad that I joined this program.)
(What is happening? Are we in a romantic relationship now?)
(I'm envious.)
(Yu Ri became the first woman to make his heart flutter in the show.)
She definitely made his heart flutter back then.
We were a thing.
I remember now. You're doing this program for quite a long time.
(She treats him like an outdated celebrity.)
- What do you mean? - I mean...
Yes, I'm still alive.
What are you talking about?
- Kwang Soo is alive. - Goodness.
- It's so funny. - Seriously.
- He falls in love quickly. - Right.
He never dies.
Please introduce yourselves to the viewers one by one.
Hello, viewers of Running Man.
I'm Tiffany who's shinier than jewelry.
- Tiffany. - Good.
(She introduces herself like a rookie.)
(She's become much cuter than before.)
- Good. - You became so cute.
- She's still motivated. - Good.
- Next up is Hyo Yeon. - Like when you were a rookie.
- All of a sudden? - Hyo Yeon.
Hello, I'm the dancing queen, Hyo Yeon.
- Should I do this? - Do it all the way through.
- Goodness. - Dancing queen.
I'm sorry, but I guess you don't remember how you did it.
- Pardon? - How you did it.
- Do you not remember? - Was that your nickname?
I'm not sure.
(Silly)
- The dance... - What are you doing?
- What was it? - Wasn't it a dancing machine?
- Dancing machine? - That's right.
- Dancing machine... - Didn't you do like this?
They say I was a dancing machine.
I see, dancing machine.
- Right. - Please do it again then.
I'm the dancing machine, Hyo Yeon.
- Goodness. - Like a machine. I see.
Next up is Soo Young.
Hello, I'm the bright princess of Girls' Generation, Soo Young!
- Right, she was the princess. - Princess Myeongnyang?
(He heard it wrong.)
- Was it your nickname? - Yes.
We were all princesses with particular talents.
- Really? - Why was I the machine then?
I don't know why her nickname was the machine.
- She was the only one? - Yes.
All right. Yu Ri, please go ahead.
Hello, I'm the black pearl of Girls' Generation, Yu Ri.
- Black pearl. - Right.
- Because of your skin. - Following Lee Bon.
Hello, I'm the tiny leader, Tae Yeon.
- So cute! - Tae Yeon.
Hello, I'm the charming girl of Girls' Generation, Yoon A.
The charming girl.
- Charming girl. - Charming girl.
It's not easy to call oneself charming.
Seo Hyun couldn't make it because of her drama schedule.
- But Yoon A also... - Don't you have to film your drama?
We already finished filming the drama before its broadcast.
I see.
When will it start?
- It's being broadcast now. - It already started.
(It's being broadcast, so please stay quiet.)
Whisper to me before acting so stupidly.
- Okay. - Goodness.
- I understand your intention. - Come on.
Please don't upset our guests.
- Please don't. - I'm so embarrassed.
(Seok Jin's still the same as before.)
Following Yoon A,
- next is Sunny's turn. - Sunny!
(It's Soon Gyu's turn.)
(Hesitant)
Hello, I'm the energizer of Girls' Generation, Sunny.
Her gestures are still there.
- I'm sorry. - "Sunny."
I think she's the best in appealing her charms.
She always makes a huge impression even if her part is very small.
She gives a huge impact.
- Right. - She's impressive.
Actually, rather than appealing myself in my part,
I mostly do it behind others when they're doing their parts.
(They totally agree with it.)
That's selfish.
- Show us. - Show us an example.
Have you been surprised to watch one of your music videos?
Behind us, she goes...
Right, I know what she's talking about.
She does something like this.
- Right, she winks a lot. - Show us a little bit of it.
Please show us a bit.
- Let's say it's Yoon A's part. - The part we saw earlier.
Don't laugh because I am embarrassed
Don't tease because I am serious
(She catches everyone's attention.)
(It looks like Sunny's part.)
I thought it was Sunny's part.
I only had eyes for Sunny.
- Didn't you look at me? - No, I didn't.
(Yoon A is disappointed.)
I didn't see Yoon A once.
How did she do that in such a short period of time?
She is fresh.
She is like a vacuum cleaner of attention.
- She is ready for the camera. - I know. She is amazing.
- She works hard. - That's right.
Today, you will have Partner Race with Girls' Generation.
My Girls' Generation, My Bad Girls' Generation.
(Girls' Generation...)
(and Bad Girls' Generation?)
What is that?
Since there are six male members,
there will be six teams that are comprised of a man and a woman.
Three women without partners...
will make up Team Singles.
(6 men make 6 teams, and 3 women make Team Singles.)
That means we will be partnered with a woman no matter what.
I can't believe we got this opportunity.
We will be partnered with a woman no matter what.
Among the female members...
are three bad girls who break up couples.
(Among the 9 female members are 3 bad girls.)
(The men need to beware of the 3 bad girls during the race.)
I want to be in a team with the female members.
The team that wins in a mission...
will be given a hint about the bad girls and an exchange card.
After the final race,
Team Partners wins if they find two or more bad girls.
Team Bad Girls win if they don't.
The losing team will receive an ice shower.
- Ice shower? - In short,
- we need to find the bad girls. - That's right.
Three bad girls are hiding among you.
- This is like "X-Man". - Already?
(3 bad girls with a mission are hiding among the female members.)
- They are already among us. - We have three bad girls.
They received a mission.
- They received a mission. - Sunny seems to be a bad girl.
We must watch carefully when we play games.
Even if the men succeed in apprehending the bad girls,
they will receive the penalty if their partners are bad girls.
Please be careful in choosing and exchanging partners.
(Partner up with a trustworthy girl and avoid the bad ones.)
We might have to exchange partners.
Since heatwave alert has been issued,
we will start the race inside the school.
- Let's go. - Go, go.
(Partner Race starts inside the school building.)
We are inside the school to avoid the heatwave.
- All right. - Yes.
(They are glad to enter the air-conditioned classroom.)
- Thank you. - This is nice.
Beware of heatwave.
(He is the honorary ambassador of health.)
We will now have a mission to decide on the partners.
The title of the mission is...
Tell Me Your Wish.
(Tell Me Your Wish)
- Tell me your wish - Tell me your wish
Six male members will give a keyword for the partner of their wish.
Then the female members will compete against each other.
(The female members must compete against each other.)
The winner will get to be the partner.
There will be a fierce competition.
They must compete for us.
It will be ruthless.
(I want to be a member of Team Singles.)
- You must be thinking... - We just need to choose.
We just need to choose.
"Why do I need to do that..."
"when I am back after a two-year break?"
- However, it can't be helped. - Someone will be my partner.
Someone will be my partner.
- Okay. - Get excited.
- Be prepared. - They need to be prepared.
(They have chills down their spines.)
Seok Jin, please present a keyword for your partner.
- Should I go first? - Yes.
(Haughty)
- Look at them. - Whoever...
Look at them.
- I can feel the atmosphere. - Hey.
I thought I was at the North Pole.
- Why did it become so cold? - They turned ice cold.
- What is up with the atmosphere? - Don't ignore me.
They turned cold.
Let me give you a tip.
I will consider partnering up with the one who meets my eyes.
Hey.
You...
(Why are you looking away?)
For goodness' sake.
This is incredible.
He is like Medusa.
They don't want to meet Medusa's eyes.
Seok Jin is Medusa.
Okay.
Accept the reality. There are fewer men than women.
- Think of it as an honor. - Seok Jin.
You don't have to pretend to be okay.
Your face turned red.
To be honest, my heart is wounded.
W.H.
Do you know what W.H. is?
- A wounded heart. - That's right.
They are the new generation.
Don't look this way.
- "They are the new generation." - The new generation?
- They are the new generation. - W.H. is old.
You know that W.H. stands for a wounded heart.
- Don't be ridiculous. - My goodness.
(The girls of the new generation are shocked.)
I like rock, paper, scissors.
I will choose the one who comes first...
in a game of rock, paper, scissors.
(The one who comes first in a game of rock, paper, scissors)
What?
- What? - The winner will be my partner.
The winner will be my partner.
You have to participate in a game of rock, paper, scissors.
Does that mean I have to lose?
- You have to lose. - Right.
- You have to lose. - You have to lose.
- You are good at it. - No.
Yu Ri is good at it.
I think...
Sunny will be my partner. I think Sunny will win.
(He thinks Sunny will be his partner.)
- Sunny, Sunny! - Sunny, Sunny!
- Sunny, Sunny! - Sunny.
(He is flustered.)
You don't have to pretend to be okay.
(Stop it.)
- Seok Jin. - My heart is wounded.
(The shoot almost gets stopped.)
- He might collapse. - I am smiling...
for the shoot.
Look at their facial expressions.
I remember the dance.
The first round is between Yu Ri and Hyo Yeon.
(Hyo Yeon versus Yu Ri)
This is the tournament of death.
- The tournament of death. - Please step forward.
The unlucky one will win.
- This is a death match. - The unlucky one will win.
This is a death match.
You only get one chance.
- In 1, 2, 3. - I hope I don't win.
- Rock, paper, scissors. - Rock, paper, scissors.
(The winner takes one step towards Seok Jin.)
(Yu Ri wins.)
(Happy versus sad)
That surprised me.
She hates the fact that she won.
I haven't seen anyone become that sad after a victory.
I don't know what to do.
How unfortunate!
The next round is between Soo Young and Yoon A.
Why am I so nervous?
(It's a fierce match between the tall rivals.)
(Seok Jin is even more nervous.)
Let's play rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Yoon A wins.)
(Screaming)
(Their screams have different meanings.)
Yes!
She is so upset.
I feel bad for Seok Jin.
Seok Jin's heart is wounded.
- My heart is wounded. - He got a heart attack.
You can't help but scream, right?
(She can relate.)
I couldn't help it either.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Tae Yeon wins.)
(I have to go because I lost.)
(Screaming)
(Seok Jin tries to give her a high five.)
(She hates it.)
- You acted like... - What was that?
(What am I? An insect?)
- What was that? - You acted like he was a cockroach.
What was that?
You acted like he was a cockroach.
- Seok Jin became a cockroach. - Seriously.
I just wanted to give her a high five.
Don't treat Seok Jin that way.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(In Round 4, Tiffany wins.)
(I can't believe I won.)
My goodness.
(All 4 remaining contestants are members of Girls' Generation.)
- What is going on? - What is going on?
- What is going on? - This is incredible.
Yu Ri, Yoon A, Tae Yeon, and Tiffany.
This is incredible.
- Their reactions are... - They are genuine.
genuine. It is very obvious.
This is happening for real.
Now, we will have...
a match between Yu Ri and Yoon A.
(Yoon A versus Yu Ri)
This is fierce.
You will only get one chance.
Who do you want to win?
I hope Yu Ri wins.
- What about you, Yu Ri? - Yoon A.
This is like the final round of a beauty pageant.
- Miss Korea. - Seriously.
- They care about each other. - That's right.
(The 10-year-old girl group has a deep friendship.)
(Each of them wants the other to win.)
All right.
This is the semifinal. Rock, paper, scissors.
(Yu Ri wins.)
For goodness' sake.
I won.
Seok Jin, I am sorry.
(She hides her happiness.)
My goodness.
You are sad, right?
- All right. - This is a disaster.
You are one step closer to becoming Seok Jin's partner.
This is a disaster.
(The ones who were eliminated are relaxed.)
Good job.
This is the semifinal of rock, paper, scissors.
Who will meet Yu Ri at the final round?
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Tiffany wins.)
Congratulations, Tiffany.
You are almost there.
Endure the wounds for a little bit longer.
Hang in there.
Tae Yeon, you look very happy.
Either Tiffany or Yu Ri will be my partner.
This is the final round, right?
- Yes. - Okay.
This is the end.
Let's go.
(Only one of them gets the honor of becoming Seok Jin's partner.)
This is the final round.
Rock, paper, scissors.
(Who is lucky enough to be Seok Jin's partner upon comeback?)
(Yu Ri and Seok Jin become partners.)
My goodness.
(Screaming)
(What a bitter victory.)
(Strangely, the selection of Seok Jin's partner made him sad.)
- Everyone. - I screamed without realizing it.
(The loser accepts the defeat well.)
So with this,
Yu Ri and Seok Jin will be each other's partners.
(It's settled that Seok Jin and Yu Ri will be a pair.)
- Accept it. It's fate. - No.
(Sighing)
Why are you so good at rock, scissors, paper?
I don't know.
(I don't know.)
You did well. What's wrong?
- You did a great job. - You won.
Accept it.
(Seok Jin, stop pretending you're okay.)
Next up is Kwang Soo.
(It's Kwang Soo's turn to choose a partner.)
- Kwang Soo has a good start. - He already loves them.
- Everyone is looking at you. - Hold on.
To become my partner,
you must be chosen by Mr. Barrel.
(To become my partner, you must be chosen by Mr. Barrel.)
(Kwang Soo is the guy Mr. Barrel has chosen.)
(Probability-wise,)
(it can't be explained how he is the favorite of Mr. Barrel.)
Whoever gets Mr. Barrel to pop out will become my partner.
- That sounds good. - All right.
- He's the popular guy among us. - That's right.
- He's handsome. - He's the best one here.
He's pretty good-looking.
- He's the most good-looking here. - Look. Jae Seok is laughing.
- Among us... - Are you looking down on him?
(Hello, I'm Kwang Soo from Running High School.)
He's very popular here.
Unexpectedly, you look quite nice.
(Kwang Soo is everyone's pick.)
- He's gone mad. - I...
I talk Kwang Soo up to my acquaintances a lot.
- Everyone. - Yes?
- We have to improve ourselves. - We have to improve our looks?
Yes, we must.
- Goodness. - He's the good-looking one here.
- That's right. - I agree with him.
- Kwang Soo, do your best. - He's the good-looking one.
Yu Ri, but I'm ranked second though.
- But... - Yes?
can I challenge to enter the race?
- Do you... - Can I?
- Stay out of this. - I mean...
- Stay out of this. - You can't do that...
because it was a cutthroat battle to select you as his partner.
- This is why. - I told you to accept the reality.
- Kwang Soo, this is good for you. - You'll be my partner for today.
All right. Everyone.
You should play the game one by one.
- Should we stab the barrel? - That's good.
- Let's do this. - Stab the barrel.
- Let's go. - Hurry.
- Hurry. - Goodness.
- It'd be funny if it pops up early. - This is quite exciting.
One of you should stab it.
Okay. Go back to your spot.
- Next is Hyo Yeon. - In 1, 2, 3.
(Hyo Yeon and Soo Young pass their turns safely.)
- You passed. - Sunny, you are next.
- Sunny. - We'll know soon.
I think Sunny is a bit nervous.
(Sunny, are you desperate to be my partner?)
(Unlike other girls, Sunny seems nervous.)
That's right. She has to get Mr. Barrel to pop out.
(Does Sunny really want Kwang Soo as her partner?)
She's being very careful.
We have to see how this will go first.
(Choosing carefully)
It didn't pop out.
(As soon as she stabs it, she seems happy.)
- You don't want me, do you? - She doesn't want him.
(He has a realization that Sunny doesn't want him as her partner.)
She's reacting in a similar way when it was Seok Jin's turn.
- Fine. I got it. - Okay.
- A similar thing happened to me. - I didn't want her either.
- Okay. - I wasn't thinking of her either.
- Tae Yeon, you are next. - Did that hurt you?
She's thinking hard about this.
- Stab it. - Here we go.
(She breathes a sigh of relief.)
Hold on.
- What? - Can it be slow?
Are you sad?
- Yoon A, you're next. - She's playing it.
(Yoon A also passes her turn safely.)
She's happy about it.
What? You don't want me as your partner?
- No. - You don't?
- What is this? - She looks happy.
- She doesn't want you. - Tiffany.
So Min.
You should take him.
The spirit of variety shows.
- We are starting once again. - No way, So Min.
- No way. - I'm relieved.
- Ji Hyo, you should take him. - Ji Hyo.
- All right. - Let's start with her again.
First of all, it went around once.
(Everyone passed their first turn.)
This is a very exciting game.
- Jae Seok, let's start with Ji Hyo. - Kwang Soo.
Did you feel that among them,
there was someone who wanted to be your partner?
- Tell us. - So...
it's someone who wants to be your partner, not vice versa.
- From the feeling I got? - Yes.
- I have about two in mind. - Isn't it Tae Yeon?
- I bet Tae Yeon is one of them. - Really?
- Who are they? - Who are they? Can you tell us?
(This is embarrassing. Let me whisper their names to you.)
- They are Tae Yeon and Yoon A. - Hold on.
- How can you tell their names? - Well...
- They might not be my partner. - Why did you tell me then?
You told me to do so.
I told you to tell us, not whisper them to me.
Goodness. Tae Yeon?
- He picked Tae Yeon and Yoon A. - They will try to fail on purpose.
All right. This time, Ji Hyo, you will start.
Go for it. You can do it.
- It's right next to another one. - Let it pop out.
(The girls are avoiding the dud slot as they choose very carefully.)
(Gosh, I survived.)
Goodness, this guy doesn't want to pop out at all.
(Goodness, this guy doesn't want to pop out at all.)
What is this? What's going on?
This is weird. We have a lot of turns left.
We never made it this far before.
(Time has passed.)
- Tae Yeon. - Now,
two guests you wanted still remain.
- Tae Yeon and Yoon A have to go. - Kwang Soo.
(Everyone can see that Mr. Barrel is about to pop out.)
(This is a fierce battle.)
- Tae Yeon and Yoon A have to go. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - If you want it desperate, wait.
- There are five left. - All right.
- No way. - I bet he's going to pop out.
If she stabs the right slot...
- Yoon A, you're up. - Is there something wrong with it?
(She's disappointed Mr. Barrel didn't pop out.)
There are four left.
- This is so interesting. - If she doesn't get it...
(Kwang Soo and Yoon A become partners.)
(The partner Mr. Barrel has chosen is Yoon A.)
(Mr. Barrel has made my wish come true.)
Here you go.
(He's overwhelmed.)
- I was so startled. - That was cute.
- What is this? - Excuse me.
- I'm sorry to interrupt, - He seems so happy.
but you two are not going to be a couple or anything.
- I'm aware of it. - It seemed you wanted Yoon A.
This is so funny.
- He's really different. - Mr. Barrel approved this.
Next up is Haha.
(Haha is the third to choose his partner.)
- How are you going to choose yours? - Well,
I'm going to choose the most flexible one.
- I'm really flexible. - Most flexible one?
- I'll choose the most flexible one. - I'm really flexible.
Yu Ri is the most flexible.
- Is that so? - I'm really flexible.
(Why are we playing this game now?)
- Hey, you. - Yu Ri.
No, it's just that I'm sad I didn't get to play.
- I don't want you either. - No.
(He tries to keep the last trace of his dignity.)
(I don't want you either.)
(She's at a loss for words.)
(Seok Jin is upset.)
I was sad about the game.
- All right. The first one... - Should I go first?
Would you like to go first, Ji Hyo?
Ji Hyo seems enthusiastic about the game. All right, Ji Hyo.
- By nature, my body is stiff. - Mine too.
I can't do the split.
She and I live in the same district. We are close friends.
- Don't talk. - All right.
- It hurts already. - You have to start from here.
You have to start from here.
Come on, Haha.
- You need to start here. - Wait.
You're already hinting that you don't want her?
- Go easy on her. - You're being too obvious.
- It's not that, Ji Hyo. - He doesn't want you.
- You little... - I'm serious.
- Did you just curse at me? - Ji Hyo.
- Calm down. - Don't curse in your uniform.
Ji Hyo, please calm down.
You have to do Muay Thai too.
This morning, Ji Hyo put on the uniform...
and crossed the center of the school yard with the crew.
As soon as Se Chan saw her walking, he asked,
"Didn't she have colorful school days?"
I could sense that right away.
- That's right. - I felt that.
- Didn't you sense that? - I did.
- She gave off that vibe. - She made me feel modest.
- We're starting. - Let's start.
You have to start at the line.
- Put your foot on the line. - It has to be fair.
- Goodness. - This is good.
- Let's stop. - Stop.
- Okay. - Ji Hyo's record...
- is 182cm. - Was she this flexible?
(Flustered)
- That's not a bad record. - You got flexible.
(Ji Hyo's record is 182cm.)
- You got flexible. - She's flexible.
- Tae Yeon is next. - That was amazing.
(Tae Yeon is the second challenger.)
- Tae Yeon. - Can I do the split like this?
- Of course. - That doesn't matter.
- Everyone seems willing to play. - They are.
- We were partners a lot before. - Hold on.
- Goodness. - To be honest... Oh, my.
(Stretching)
Hey, try to point your toes.
- Move back a bit. - She's doing it.
It's okay if you get cramps.
- Hold on. - More.
(Haha wants Tae Yeon as his partner. What will be the result?)
- All right. - Your foot...
(Stretching)
Your sock...
(Laughing)
(What are they doing right now?)
Tae Yeon's record is 200cm.
(Tae Yeon defeats Ji Hyo with the record of 200cm.)
All right. It's 200cm.
Tae Yeon's record is 200cm.
Is her shoe size 300mm?
This...
depends on Haha since he came up with the game.
(All right. This was good defense.)
Hyo Yeon is next.
Hyo Yeon.
- I really like you. - Wasn't she on a Christmas special?
- I mean it. You know that, right? - Yes.
I haven't stretched in ages.
Stretch before you start.
- Hyo Yeon. - Hyo Yeon.
Do you really want me as your partner?
Yes. Where...
(Kicking)
(She's forced to take off her shoe.)
This is great.
I like how active you are.
You're eager. I like that.
Oh, my. I got a cramp in my leg.
(I got a cramp in my leg.)
(For the first time on a show, a singer complains of a leg cramp.)
- It's dangerous. - Hey, stop.
(I will help you get rid of your cramp.)
Where is your cramp?
- No. - Where is your cramp?
- Right here. - Where?
- Where is it? Are you okay? - It's right here.
(Excessive enthusiasm may cause cramps.)
(Because of her leg cramp, the set is thrown into a chaos.)
(This is too embarrassing that I can't look.)
All right. Hyo Yeon is out of the game.
(Hyo Yeon is out of the game.)
All right. We'll exclude you.
(This is for her own welfare.)
- That was close. - Goodness, the look on her face.
- Are you okay? - I really like you though.
- Goodness, Hyo Yeon. - Sadly, she'll be excluded.
- Hyo Yeon is disqualified. - Oh, no. She's the best.
It's finally Soo Young's turn.
- She has long legs. - Take off your shoes.
- She has long legs. - Her feet are big.
That's great.
Goodness.
(What will be Soo Young's record?)
However...
- She's better than So Min. - Soo Young.
(What are you doing, Soo Young?)
(Is it as far as she can go?)
- Wait a minute. - Her legs are long.
She's not flexible at all.
Are you being serious?
Soo Young.
(She's being serious indeed.)
- Her legs are long. - Wait a minute.
- She's not flexible at all. - Go back.
- Soo Young. - What's wrong with her?
- Let's see. - Come on, you can do it.
- Stretch farther. - You can do it.
(Will she break the record?)
- Soo Young wins. - It's 210cm.
(Her record is 210cm.)
- Her legs are cramping. - Your legs are so long.
(Soo Young wins.)
- She went over the line. - By the way,
there must be bad girls among them.
(There must be bad girls among them.)
Is that true?
That's why they're working hard.
Do bad girls work hard?
Everyone, I just got goosebumps.
- I thought they simply liked me. - Bad girls must find partners.
Three bad girls are given a mission.
They must find a partner.
Otherwise, they get an ice shower.
I see.
(Bad girls must do their best to find partners.)
(Who are the bad girls among them?)
Are you a bad girl?
- What? - You can't tell us, right?
She's definitely not it.
My goodness.
- I tried my best. - She worked very hard.
I played rock, paper, scissors and won.
- She's not it. - I won the game.
Haha's partner is Soo Young.
(Haha and Soo Young get paired up.)
You only have three chances...
- to find a partner. - It's competitive.
Those who don't get a partner...
have to be on a different team.
I'd like to see how much fun you can have.
- "Fun"? - Yes.
Express the amount of fun you have.
You don't have to dance.
Let's play some music.
Let's take a look since one of them likes to dance.
Shouldn't they express themselves without music?
- We'll play music for them. - Right.
Se Chan dances well.
This is an example.
(He demonstrates dancing without music.)
(Singing)
(He enjoys himself.)
(He's full of fun.)
Do something like this, and show me your fun
(Jae Seok's partner must be a lot of fun.)
That's great.
(Will she get another chance?)
It's more than possible. You can do it.
(What is she doing?)
It's possible.
That's good.
(So Min tucks in her skirt to dance.)
(She dances without any music.)
(She grabs him.)
(Jae Seok, let me be your partner.)
(She experiences a culture shock.)
Look at her skirt.
She did it.
(What have you done with your skirt?)
(She has tight pants on.)
What kind of pants are they?
She's so annoying.
What are you doing?
- Goodness. - She lost her mind.
Gosh.
All of you seem lost in thoughts.
My mind went blank.
- It's because... - I don't know what to do.
they didn't expect anything like this.
Why did you tuck in your skirt?
I can't believe it.
All right, please play the music.
(It's time to find Jae Seok's partner.)
This song is for dancing.
Isn't it a great song?
(Only 3 out of 6 will find a partner.)
- This is exciting. - It's great.
(Ji Hyo approaches.)
That's great.
You're doing well, Ji Hyo.
(She dances for Jae Seok.)
She can't control her excitement.
(Jae Seok is impressed.)
She can't control it.
- Let's go. - That's right.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Jae Seok, make me your partner.)
(Ji Hyo knows how to have fun.)
(Running Man members are intense.)
(Having a partner is an advantage.)
She can't control her excitement.
That's great.
(Having a partner is an advantage.)
You can stop.
Go back to your place, Ji Hyo.
Go back.
- Next up is So Min. - So Min is up.
(So Min starts.)
Here's So Min.
(Dancing left to right)
(She dances and bounces like a gangster.)
What's wrong with her?
Goodness.
(What do you think of me, Jae Seok?)
So Min is great.
(They look like a pair of gorillas.)
She's great.
That's good.
(Her dance gets more desperate.)
What kind of move is this?
(She gives up competing against her.)
My goodness.
She's impressive.
- Keep going! - I can't watch her anymore.
(I'm Jae Seok's partner today.)
- Here she comes. - You should go.
It's Hyo Yeon.
(She's full of confidence.)
(She grooves with confidence with 10 years of experience.)
She dances well.
(She gets into the music.)
(He likes Hyo Yeon's dance.)
She dances well.
(Do you want to dance with me, Yu Ri?)
Yu Ri.
(I already have a partner.)
(She joins her.)
(What are you doing?)
(She dances her heart out.)
(She dances passionately, hoping to change her partner.)
(She makes weird noises.)
(She expresses her regret of having Seok Jin as her partner.)
Goodness.
(He's disappointed.)
Next up is Soo Young.
Show us your hip hop dance.
- Hip hop. - Hip hop.
- Hip hop. - Dance hip hop.
(Are you talking about this?)
What are you doing?
(It looks creepy.)
- That's not hip hop. - Where's hip hop?
What kind of hip hop is that?
Wait a minute.
(It's similar to a comedian's dance.)
That's unbelievable.
(Please don't do that, Soo Young.)
How about you, Yoon A?
(My partner is the best.)
Next up is Tae Yeon.
(She bounces lightly.)
(She gets very cute with her bounces.)
(Do you want to be my partner, Jae Seok?)
(Of course, I do.)
Goodness.
(She attracts others who have partners already.)
(He gets on the floor.)
(Bouncing)
(Inspired by Tae Yeon, Haha creates his R-rated bouncing.)
(Sunny is up next.)
Next up is Sunny.
- It's your turn, Sunny. - That was funny.
She's so good at dancing.
There she goes.
(She's cute and sexy.)
(They go weak at the knees for Sunny.)
(She does a body wave.)
She dances so well.
(She does a body wave with confidence.)
(She's so good.)
Next is So Min.
(So Min dances again.)
- Go. - Go, So Min.
(Shall I try again?)
(What is she doing?)
(She's not as good as Sunny, but she slides on the floor.)
(Moving about)
- Stop it. - So Min.
- Please stop dancing. - Stop it.
Hey!
(The music stops.)
So Min, do your own dance.
Why did you ruin the fun?
- I wanted to try it. - She wanted to try it.
- You'll hurt your knees. - Do your own dance.
She wanted to imitate her.
Yu Ri was hilarious. She wanted to survive.
(She danced out of desperation.)
She wanted to get another chance.
- Come on. - You danced well.
(She danced passionately, hoping to change her partner.)
(Seok Jin is sad.)
Please save me.
"Help me!"
"Someone is drowning!"
Should I laugh?
- Yes. - I should laugh, right?
You should laugh.
You'll seem laid-back if you laugh.
It's very difficult to select a partner.
Let's imagine that we're at a dance club.
The person to pick the number one spoon will be my partner.
(The person to pick number one becomes his partner.)
(Running Man's dance club opens.)
(I heard this club is full of hot boys.)
Here he comes.
(Who is this man?)
He's hot.
He's hot. It's Jae Seok.
It's Jae Seok.
Gosh, it's him.
(He steals everyone's attention.)
It's Jae Seok.
(He's Jae Seok who knows how to have fun.)
(All the women are excited to see Jae Seok.)
(They want to be partners with him.)
(It's tiring to be so popular.)
It's Jae Seok.
(Splash)
(I'm sorry. You looked so cool.)
(The hot guy is understanding.)
- He's so cool. - He's amazing.
- He's sexy. - He's so cool.
(Sunny picks a spoon.)
(Sunny is eliminated.)
(Spitting)
(Fine, I'll get going.)
(I'm sorry.)
(Hyo Yeon is eliminated.)
(Tae Yeon is eliminated.)
There are not many left.
It serves you right.
(Only Tiffany, Ji Hyo, and So Min are left.)
(Tiffany is eliminated.)
(The remaining ones are...)
(Family is the best.)
(Come here, Jae Seok.)
(The final candidates are Ji Hyo and So Min.)
(Hi, Running High School's hottest boy.)
(Jae Seok and Ji Hyo become partners.)
Now, it's Se Chan's turn.
(Se Chan and Jong Kook are the only male members left.)
We've been having so much fun. It's time to calm down.
Let's calm down a little.
(We have to be chosen this time.)
Let's do an acrostic poem with my name.
- With "Yang Se Chan". - That's not easy.
Make it funny, clever,
or romantic.
- They can choose. - If I hear it...
- and like it, - It's for your own satisfaction.
- I'll choose that person. - Selfish interests.
I'm not sure if the bad girls are...
among these three.
If they are, they have to be chosen.
- That's right. - That's right.
(The bad girls have to be chosen by either Se Chan or Jong Kook.)
The bad girls have to be chosen.
Let's start from Sunny.
I want to hear hers last.
- You do? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
- What are you doing? - What's with you?
- I want to hear hers last. - I see.
Just choose Sunny.
(If that's how you're going to be...)
Sorry?
She's losing her patience.
It's too hot here.
All right.
Let's start from So Min.
(So Min goes first.)
- All right. - Let's do this.
An acrostic poem with "Yang Se Chan".
Come here.
Are we supposed to look at each other?
(It's too much for her.)
- Yes. - Yes.
Later,
we'll hold hands too.
Why would you hold hands?
- Are you going to hold hands? - Yes, for the sake of variety.
But not now.
(We're not holding hands now.)
Just stand straight.
No. Stand straight.
We'll start standing straight.
Stand straight.
I'm sorry.
- Not now. - Give me your hands.
Why don't you make her turn around?
- Turn around? - Yes.
That sounds good. Turn around.
Look at the mountain over there.
Look at the mountain far away.
Imagine I'm over there.
Look away.
Yang.
- Yang? - Yang.
Yang, you punk.
What did you say?
(Yang, you punk.)
- What did you say? - "Yang, you punk?"
Can't you make it nicer?
- Yang... - Yang.
Yang. Look away.
Yang.
(She is forced to look away.)
Se.
Gosh, you brat.
(Gosh, you brat.)
What are you doing?
Just insult me in my ear.
- It's an acrostic poem. - It is?
Why do you put weird words in the beginning?
- She said, "you punk". - Yang Se.
She said, "you punk".
Chan.
Is that it?
Get lost.
Disappear into the mountain.
(Chan)
That's enough.
Is she drunk?
So Min, it wasn't bad. I get your intention.
All right. Tae Yeon.
They should hold hands.
- Both hands? - Yes.
Both hands.
What are you doing?
It's to develop a new kind of acrostic poem.
What is this?
It'd be boring if we just stand straight.
- Give me the first word. - Yang.
What are you? A punk?
(Are you a punk?)
That was great.
- I love her voice. - Good job.
- Her voice is amazing. - What are you? A punk?
It was amazing.
- What are you? A punk? - I love that.
- Se. - My goodness.
- Chan. - Cut it out.
(Cut it out.)
(It was a simple and clever poem.)
That was great.
You're amazing.
I love her voice.
- What are you? A punk? - I love that.
- Good job. - Hyo Yeon.
(It's Hyo Yeon's turn.)
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Yang.
Quality over quantity.
(Quality over quantity)
Se.
- I'm a tenant. - A tenant?
(I'm a tenant.)
I can relate.
- I'm a tenant. - You're a tenant.
Quality over quantity, and I'm a tenant.
It makes sense. Okay.
Chan.
I have no cold water.
(I have no cold water.)
(It was a clever, realistic poem that Se Chan could relate to.)
(It deals with the depressing situation many tenants are in.)
"I'm a tenant, and I have no cold water."
It was clever.
Well... Tae Yeon...
(Sunny is standing before Se Chan.)
I think he'll choose Sunny regardless.
- It's neck and neck. - You can change the format too.
Sunny, do a cute one.
Cute one?
I'll let go of your hands.
(If you're going to do a cute one, I'll let go of your hands.)
Do whatever you want.
- "Do whatever you want?" - Surprise me.
I won't look away.
(What is she going to do?)
- Sunny. - Let's go.
Here we go.
Yang.
I'm a sheep.
(I'm a sheep.)
(A sheep? From the beginning?)
My goodness.
(The impact is massive.)
Unbelievable.
(I have a partner. I shouldn't be like this.)
Se.
Let's not look at her.
I wash my face.
(I wash my face.)
(You can do whatever you want.)
(I can't breathe.)
Chan.
It's a beautiful morning.
(It's a beautiful morning.)
(Cute)
I've made up my mind.
- My goodness. - Amazing.
- I love it. - Good job.
(What is that sheep?)
It was so clever.
I'm a sheep.
- I'm a sheep. - So Min.
Stop it.
- Try. - Try.
Give it a try.
Go.
- I'm a sheep. - You are?
- I wash my face. - I see.
It's a beautiful morning.
Okay, next.
(It doesn't work for So Min.)
(I want only Sunny.)
- Se Chan. - All right.
Sunny is here.
No.
(He hesitates.)
Just tell me, and I'll...
- This will be easier. - Yes.
- Please say it loud. - Sure.
So.
What?
That's what I heard.
There has been a misunderstanding.
My pronunciation was bad, right?
- That's what I heard. - Diction is important.
Diction. Pronunciation.
- Pronunciation. - All right.
(Enunciating)
Sun...
(Angry)
Sunny.
(Se Chan chooses Sunny.)
(Se Chan and Sunny become partners.)
They look cute together.
Seok Jin and Yu Ri,
Haha and Soo Young, Kwang Soo and Yoon A, Jae Seok and Ji Hyo,
Se Chan and Sunny, and Jong Kook and Tiffany are partners.
You belong to Team Partners.
So Min, Hyo Yeon, and Tae Yeon belong to Team Singles.
(These three don't have partners.)
- They have strong members. - They're strong.
I want to join that team.
They're strong. You never know.
However,
this is not the end.
As I said earlier,
the winners of each game will get hints about the bad girls...
and the chance to change partners.
(They get the chance to change partners.)
Soo Young has been quiet.
Yoon A has been quiet too.
I'll get hurt if Yoon A is a bad girl.
- I'm not. - A bad girl is quiet?
Soo Young is usually a good talker.
Are bad girls supposed to be quiet?
- Aren't they supposed to try hard? - No, I mean...
I'm sorry.
See?
Haha, you seem to be scolded a lot.
Don't be.
Don't say something meaningless.
- Don't try to blame an innocent. - Okay.
She's unbelievable.
She's so attractive.
Soo Young...
I love the words she says.
Her attitude tells us she's the bad girl.
I love it.
Aren't you a little hungry?
- Yes. - Yes.
We've reserved two restaurants nearby.
(Braised spicy seafood and short rib patties.)
There are four cars parked outside,
and two couples will ride in each car.
But Team Singles will not share a car with the other teams.
You'll compete against a team that goes the same direction as you go.
You'll have to choose which team to share your car with carefully.
Okay.
Let's move now.
- Seok Jin! - What?
Let's go together.
- No, he's coming with us. - Come on.
- Hold on. - Goodness.
- No. - He's going with us.
Were you that easy to deal with?
It seems like everyone thinks you're easy.
- He's just popular. - Right, I am.
Go with me.
- Ji Hyo! - Okay?
Should we choose braised spicy seafood?
Let's go.
(Which teams will head to the same location?)
We must have meat.
I thought I would be a couple.
Me too.
Whom did you want to partner up with?
When we started our shooting,
I found Se Chan so funny.
The way he danced and everything.
- He's unexpectedly popular. - Really?
Did you have anyone you wanted to partner up with?
I...
(The member I wanted to partner up with was...)
I think it's so much better to do it alone.
(They're all the same anyway.)
- Team Singles. - I'm happy to be Team Singles.
You must not be a bad girl for certain then.
(That, I don't know.)
- Aren't you a bad girl? - No, I'm not.
(Perhaps, one of Running Man members is a bad girl.)
They never give me a crucial role.
I see.
They're worried I mess it up.
I made a huge mistake last time.
(Is So Min the bad girl?)
- Hyo Yeon is suspicious. - Hyo Yeon.
- Sunny. - I think...
What do you think?
- I think it's Sunny. - Right?
- Sunny? - She tried really hard just before.
Sunny acted unusually cute.
She did act unusually cute.
(She has a point.)
She does seem suspicious.
Sunny...
(Is Sunny a bad girl?)
From what I saw today,
I think Tae Yeon, Hyo Yeon, and Sunny...
acted very unusual.
- Really? - They're suspicious.
All of them are going to where we're going.
No, Sunny is going the other direction.
It's Tae Yeon, Hyo Yeon, and Soo Young.
No, it's Sunny.
Tiffany, Haha has decided...
that I'm the bad girl since yesterday.
To him, Soo Young is the bad girl for certain.
- It's been decided. - She's the bad girl.
It's been decided.
Her role is to cause confusion in her team.
Bad girls, you have to be thankful to me.
- I'm not sure who you are, - She's taken the role.
- but be thankful. - Right.
- Goodness. - He's sure about it.
Did you have anyone in mind whom you wanted to partner up with?
- Right. - That's important.
You had someone in mind?
I really wanted to partner up with Kwang Soo.
- Really? - Really.
(I really wanted to partner up with Kwang Soo.)
(Are you sure?)
- Really? - Really.
Tell me the reason.
You look great...
with that long hair.
- It's not easy to look great in it. - My long hair...
(Happy)
So you like men with long hair.
- Ryoo Seung Bum has long hair. - Yoon A,
I can grow my hair to my bottom.
I can do that as long as you like it.
(Thank goodness I grew my hair.)
Give us an example.
Who do you think looks good with long hair?
Won Bin with long hair, for example.
Won Bin and Kwang Soo are way too different.
(It's like they're two different species.)
(So you just like handsome guys instead of long hair.)
- You're a bad girl, aren't you? - She must be.
(As soon as she mentions Won Bin, she is cornered as a bad girl.)
- I just thought of him. - Well...
- She's a total bad girl. - Goodness.
He's a fool to be deceived like this.
How can he fall in love this quickly?
What are you talking about? She meant it.
I wouldn't have partnered up with you...
- if I hadn't liked you. - Right, right.
You chose to have braised spicy seafood.
- Yes. - Yes.
Now, you'll play a game to acquire...
a hint, a chance to switch partners, and the food.
- What is it? - It's called 5 Seconds.
You'll play this game.
You have to give 3 answers to a question in 5 seconds.
For example, the question is "What do you do before you go to bed?"
- You answer three things you do. - I see.
- You have to give three answers. - Got it.
A female member from each team will play.
The winning team will receive a hint and a chance to switch partners.
They'll also be given the main menu, braised spicy seafood.
The rest two teams will be given...
rice and dried laver.
- Okay. - It sounds hard.
Is it just one question?
Only the female members will play it, right?
- Right. - I see.
(Which team will win 5 Seconds?)
Ready.
(Yoon A will ask a question first.)
Go.
What do you do when you go to the toilet?
(What will be Ji Hyo's answers?)
I poop, wash up, and brush my teeth.
(I poop, wash up, and brush my teeth.)
(She's so straightforward.)
- Gosh, this... - You got this.
- Goodness. - They all do what you do.
- Don't you agree? - Ji Hyo.
- Everyone poops. - Of course.
(Team Ji Hyo succeeds.)
Well...
When do you hate to see Kwang Soo's face?
When he eats, sleeps, and washes up.
(When do you hate to see Kwang Soo's face?)
When he sleeps?
How do you know that?
(Did you just say when he sleeps?)
(Shy)
When he sleeps?
Have you seen him sleep and wash up?
- When he washes up? - Goodness.
- Goodness. - When he sleeps and washes up.
- She said it so suddenly. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - When did you see me wash?
(He's so shy.)
Even my mom didn't get to see it yet.
- By the way... - When he washes up.
(Yoon A and Kwang Soo succeed as well.)
Let's go with something silly.
Give me three reasons why you hate the producer of Running Man.
(Three reasons why she hates the producer of Running Man)
He's ugly, talkative, and annoying.
(The producer is ugly, talkative, and annoying.)
(She was in a hurry, and said her real opinions about him.)
I'm sure this is what she really thinks.
- Poor Chul Min. - Goodness.
(I just said whatever came to my mind.)
Good job, Ji Hyo. Good job.
He placed 128th among all the staff members for his looks.
- He placed 128th? - Yes.
- Isn't that the last? - 128th.
- He isn't within the 101 members. - No, he isn't.
He can't be 1 of the 101 members.
(We can't show you his front side due to his appearance rank.)
What do you think...
Kwang Soo was in his past life?
Goblin, beggar,
and... Wait.
Yes!
(Goblin, beggar,)
(and something unknown)
She said beggar.
A beggar with long hair. Gosh, you beggar.
A beggar with this kind of hair.
Beggar.
- Beggar... - Beggar...
Didn't you say you liked my hair?
(Didn't you say you liked my hair?)
Now, you'll play a game to acquire...
a hint, a chance to switch partners, and the food.
- You'll play Yu Jae Seok's Game. - Okay.
- Tiffany. - What is that?
You have to give random answers.
A female member of each team will play the game.
The winning team will receive...
a hint and a chance to switch partners.
They'll also be given the main menu, grilled short rib patties.
- You can do it! - Okay.
(Tae Yeon versus Soo Young)
- Let's go. - Start.
Whom do you respect the most?
I'm so hot.
What do you want to have for your birthday gift?
You have a very big nose.
How do you release your stress?
Poop color.
(Why did she have to mention someone else's nose?)
All right, next.
What's wrong with you?
It's only a game, so why are you sulky?
She only said your nose was big. Why are you sulky?
- Is it because of me? - Yes.
I'm sorry.
(His mind isn't as broad as his nose.)
You're handsome.
Awesome.
It's Tae Yeon's turn now.
(Soo Young succeeds.)
Let's go.
What's your nickname?
It's too hot.
What does Kwang Soo mean to you?
Handmade acorn jelly.
(Handmade acorn jelly)
(Kwang Soo is handmade acorn jelly.)
(They didn't know there was a menu like Kwang Soo until now.)
They won.
This completely makes sense.
- We won. - Perfect.
They won.
- Why? - Kwang Soo is handmade acorn jelly.
Gosh, the rice is yellow.
Because it's turmeric rice.
(Only the winning team gets to taste the main dishes.)
This tastes interesting.
(They enjoy the dishes.)
It's good.
(They try not to get envious.)
What are they eating?
(The grilled short rib patties are delicious,)
(but the braised spicy seafood is delicious too.)
(Team Ji Hyo is the winning team.)
Gosh, this abalone.
- It looks so tasty. - Right? It looks so good.
(Whispering)
Is that octopus?
- Yes. - Yes, it's octopus.
Look.
Yu Ri prepared something.
- What is it? - Take a look.
Could you please share some of it with us?
(It's Fools' Generation.)
That's not good enough.
What?
(It's not acceptable if it doesn't meet his standard.)
(Seok Jin said it'd work.)
- She's a Girls' Generation member. - What happened?
(Laughing)
What are you doing, Yoon A?
(Yoon A prepares something.)
She'll be the female version of Se Chan.
Female version?
(Will she turn into Se Chan?)
Give me some braised spicy seafood right now.
(Yoon A shows her unexpected charm.)
(Even Se Chan enjoys her imitation of himself.)
(It's 22-year-old Se Chan.)
(He acted as a father on "People Looking for Laughter".)
Give me some braised spicy seafood.
Give me some now.
(He's very content.)
- "Give it to me now." - "Give it to me."
"Give it to me now."
(Their fun lunchtime is over.)
Jae Seok and Ji Hyo came first place.
- Here's a hint for you. - Thank you.
(They get a hint about the bad girls.)
That's very important.
(They take a look at the hint.)
Take a look at the hint.
Jae Seok will decide whether to exchange partners or not.
Will you exchange your partner?
Does it say who they are?
Is the hint too general?
- No, it's pretty specific. - Really?
I had no idea before reading this hint.
I have to exchange partners.
(He decides to exchange partners.)
You read it too, Ji Hyo.
- Really? - Come on.
May I say the answer?
With whom will you exchange?
I will...
If he's partnered with a bad girl, he'll be punished.
(Whom will Jae Seok choose?)
I choose Sunny.
Why? Isn't she a bad girl?
(Is Sunny not a bad girl?)
- Why not? - What?
Isn't Sunny a bad girl?
We thought Sunny was a bad girl.
- We thought so. - I'm innocent.
I had no idea.
(Bad girls were born in Korea. Sunny and Tiffany were born in the US.)
Haha,
will you exchange partners?
Yes.
(Haha changes his partner since Soo Young was born in Korea.)
I choose Tiffany.
Me?
I'm sorry.
(She's very happy.)
It's bad to be partnered up with Soo Young.
What's wrong with me?
- Here's some information. - Don't share any information.
(What information is he about to share?)
Don't say anything.
- It says... - No.
"Soo Young is a bad girl."
(Soo Young is a bad girl no matter what.)
- Bad girls are alive. - Is she that bad?
I told you not to blame an innocent, didn't I?
I told you not to say anything meaningless.
Therefore...
(Tiffany looks at So Min.)
You seem like a bad girl.
That's also possible.
I heard what she said in the car.
What did she say?
(What did she notice about So Min?)
(It could be a determining factor.)
She really wants to be a bad girl.
(She wants to be in the center of attention.)
- That's right. - That's what I felt.
Are you serious?
She always wants to be the cause of a conflict.
(Let me be in the center of attention.)
She's such a genius.
She's wise.
- She's a narrator. - She's amazing.
(SBS Ilsan Production Center)
You changed your partner to Tiffany after reading the hint.
Sunny and Tiffany aren't bad girls...
- based on the hint. - Shall we sit here?
Okay.
- 2, 3. - Let's sit here.
- Have a seat. - I want to fight.
- Sit down. - Come here.
Please take a seat.
- Okay. - Where should we sit?
(They take a seat.)
One sitting mat is missing. Take a seat anywhere.
- What did he say? - It's Tae Yeon.
It has to be in the right form.
Tae Yeon doesn't have a sitting mat.
You're the tagger.
(She's the tagger?)
(What on earth?)
She's the tagger.
- Stand in the center. - This is fun.
I'm flustered.
Is it a talent show?
(What kind of a game is it?)
This mission is called Run Devil Run.
(Run Devil Run?)
(She has to steal a seat.)
All the members except the tagger stay seated on the mats.
Of the numbered mats, there are three red mats.
Those sitting on the red mat when the game ends...
will receive a hint and an Exchange Card.
(If you're on the red mat, you get a hint and Exchange Card.)
You can exchange partners?
It's the red mat.
(Only three members get a hint and an Exchange Card.)
The tagger will be asked, "Which partner do you like?"
If the tagger says, "I like partners with glasses",
- those wearing glasses... - I must stand up.
must run and grab a toy.
- Grab a toy. - Then return to your seat.
Tae Yeon, as soon as you answer the question,
take an empty seat.
Every time you're a tagger,
you'll get a mark on your face.
The tagger before you will mark the face.
I'll do it for Tae Yeon since she's the first tagger.
Make a mark on her nose.
Put it next to her lips.
- Put a mark. - That's it.
- It's so hot. - It's hot.
(I'll destroy whomever I catch next.)
(I don't want to be a tagger.)
Let's start Round One.
Get ready.
Start.
- Which partner do you like? - Which partner do you like?
I like...
partners wearing black microphones.
(A black microphone?)
(That's me.)
"Partners wearing black microphones"?
My goodness. It's all of us.
(Tae Yeon runs to a sitting mat.)
You're the tagger.
What happened?
(Seok Jin is the tagger.)
Tae Yeon, mark him properly.
- Okay. - It's a nice mark.
That's too nice.
- Tae Yeon is too kind. - He looks like Rudolph.
- Look. - This isn't nice.
(He's angry.)
(Seok Jin turns into Rudolph.)
- Which partner do you like, So Min? - Which partner do you like, So Min?
Look at the front.
I like partners with green ties.
(Her eyebrows are connected across her forehead.)
- What are you doing? - Look at Sunny's face.
(She drew on her face.)
My goodness.
She looks good.
You look good, So Min.
(People go far in their revenge.)
(I like partners with green ties.)
- What did she say? - What?
Get out of the way.
(He catches So Min,)
(and nails her to the ground.)
- How could you? - Goodness.
Hey.
(He still ends up being the tagger.)
It's Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo needs a pair of sunglasses for the summer.
Kwang Soo has many moles on his face.
Connect all of them.
(Simple as that.)
Connect all of his moles.
- You'll find a constellation. - Are you serious?
Connect them.
She's connecting his moles.
(It's a game of connecting dots.)
It looks amazing.
It's amazing.
Kwang Soo, you look like Johnny Depp dressed as a pirate.
(He doesn't look like him at all.)
(He's humiliated.)
"Johnny Depp"?
- "Johnny Depp"? - This is the final round.
(It's their last chance.)
This is the final round.
It's the final.
(It's their last chance.)
- Which partner do you like? - Which partner do you like?
I like partners who weigh over 40kg.
Goodness.
(Kwang Soo runs toward the mats.)
(He takes a blue sitting mat.)
Where?
(Se Chan takes a red mat.)
- Sit here. - I won't sit here.
I have no idea.
(Instead of Yoon A, Hyo Yeon takes a red mat.)
(Haha also takes a red mat.)
I have no idea.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
(Run Devil Run is over.)
- I dropped it. - Raise your hand...
if you're on a red mat.
Yes!
Please stand up.
- Okay. - How did they take it?
I want to read the hint.
Let's see.
She seems very anxious.
(Hyo Yeon seems worried as she reads the hint.)
Hyo Yeon, whom will you choose...
to be your partner?
She should be partners with a bad girl since...
bad girls should be on Team Singles.
- Right. - I choose...
(Whom will Hyo Yeon choose?)
Yoon A.
- Is she a bad girl? - Who's her partner?
- Is she a bad girl? - What's going on?
Shall we ask if she thinks Yoon A is a bad girl...
or if she simply likes Yoon A's partner?
(He's suddenly interested in Hyo Yeon's choice.)
- Which one is it? - Kwang Soo.
I want to know the reason.
Is that important?
(He said he'd grow his hair down to his bottom.)
(He said he'd gobble up the hint that could make Yoon A suspicious.)
(Yoon A is betrayed.)
Why did she exchange with Yoon A?
(Hyo Yeon and Kwang Soo are a team.)
Why was it with Yoon A?
- It's my turn. - Look at the hint.
(It's Se Chan's turn to look at the hint.)
(Why was Yoon A sent to Team Singles?)
(Bad girls do not have a stage name.)
(So Min, Tae Yeon, Yoon A, Soo Young, Yu Ri, Hyo Yeon)
(There are six members who do not have stage names.)
(Ji Hyo is eliminated.)
I'd like Ji Hyo...
(However)
I'd like Ji Hyo to switch places with Sunny.
(He chooses Sunny again.)
Is Sunny a safe one?
- Sunny must be a safe one. - Exactly.
- She's a safe one. - She must not be a bad girl.
- I'm scared. - Yoon A.
I'd like Tiffany...
You're a bad girl.
(Haha's partner, Tiffany, is not a bad girl.)
I'd like Tiffany to switch places with Sunny.
- What? - That's funny.
(Se Chan became partners with Sunny 30 seconds ago.)
What?
(I will kill you.)
It's been just 30 seconds.
(Partners)
It makes no difference.
(The final race)
- They're Team Singles. - Team Singles.
Yoon A is on Team Singles.
I wasn't expecting this.
The members have changed.
Let me announce the final mission.
It's called I Got a Boy Race.
(I Got a Boy Race)
(I got a boy?)
It's a race.
- I got a handsome boy - It's a nice name.
I got a nice boy
The race will start soon.
Find the hidden hints within 30 minutes,
and arrest the three bad girls.
If two or more bad girls get arrested,
Team Partners will win.
If not, Team Bad Girls will win.
The losing team will get an ice shower.
(The losing team will get an ice shower.)
Bad girls can be arrested through a vote.
Through a vote?
After the race,
Team Partners will get two voting rights per team.
Team Singles won't be given the right to vote.
We don't?
We don't.
Once the race starts,
Team Partners have to wear couple bracelets.
Team Singles can take someone's place...
by cutting her bracelet.
(Team Singles can take someone's place by cutting a bracelet.)
The three of them?
Team Singles will, of course, try to attack Team Partners.
Team Partners can stop their attack...
by eliminating their name tags,
which will force them to dance at the spot for a minute.
(They have to dance at the spot for a minute.)
(Dance?)
That's too harsh.
- I got a boy - That's too harsh.
(Like this)
If any of the guys become partners with a bad girl...
more than twice, he'll lose the right to vote.
(They'll lose the right to vote.)
If you become partners with a bad girl more than twice?
But if you become partners with the boss...
of Team Bad Girls even once, you'll lose your right to vote.
(Becoming partners with the boss will take away the right to vote.)
I'll announce who has lost the right to vote...
one minute before the race ends.
Let's say my partner already is a bad girl, and I become partners...
with another bad girl. Will that take away my right to vote?
Yes, it will.
But I'm not a bad girl. Don't worry.
You said you'd be a bad girl today.
I did,
- but I'm not. - You're not?
If I end up with a bad girl, will I be penalized?
Correct.
(Glancing)
(Smiling)
Am I already partners with a bad girl?
(Tell me.)
(Laughing)
Am I?
I'm confused.
(What is this girl?)
All right.
Please put on the bracelets.
Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Where are we going?
(Who will end up with the bad girls?)
It's definitely Tae Yeon, So Min, and Hyo Yeon.
(Tiffany makes her guesses.)
You're very good at games.
- I watch a lot of television. - Really?
I watch a lot of American dramas.
How is that related to this?
- It's... - How is that related to this?
Today, it's pretty much "Game of Thrones"
(You just don't know, Se Chan.)
- "Game of Thrones"? - Yes.
We move from place to place,
fight, and suspect each other...
- It's a big-scale game, right? - Yes.
I know you're not a bad girl.
- How did you find out? - I just know.
- Thank you. - I really know.
That's why I chose you.
- I'm so touched. - Really.
Hyo Yeon. I'm 100 percent sure she is a bad girl.
(Me?)
Is there a reason why you sent Yoon A...
to the other team?
She looked like a bad girl.
(She looked like a bad girl.)
Were there any hints or...
Either you or Yoon A is a bad girl, right?
Correct.
Is it you?
I'm sorry.
If you are a bad girl, why did you choose me?
I'm definitely not a bad girl.
You'll see when this is aired.
The red mat just happened to be in front of me.
(Confused)
Who do you think is a bad girl?
We didn't have lunch together.
(You)
Let me explain.
- What should I do? - Let me explain.
We'll just have to break up the couples.
We have to take someone's place.
- Yes. - We have to do that.
(Bad girls on Team Singles have to become someone's partner.)
I'll just chase everyone.
I'll do my best.
I haven't had any partners yet.
(The good girls on Team Singles have to rescue...)
(the boys from the bad girls.)
(How will the three play?)
- The race will start soon. - Let's go.
- Five, - Let's go.
four, three...
- Two, one. - Two, one.
The race starts now.
Let's go.
(They have to find as many hints as possible.)
- Let's look for evidence. - Let's go.
We have to find hints.
(Partners)
We have to find as many hints as possible.
(Once a bracelet is cut, partners will be changed.)
If Team Singles tries to cut our bracelet, remove their name tags.
- Okay. - They'll stop for a minute.
Wait.
This camera...
- only follows special people. - Why is it here?
(A camera for special people?)
Why is it here?
It means either you or I am special.
(I don't think I'm special.)
I mean...
- Why do you suspect me? - I'll stop.
(Doubtful)
You're suspecting me.
- Not here? - It's filming you.
(It's filming you.)
I'm not a bad girl.
(Gosh, you bad girl.)
(Wink)
(Team Partners are looking for hints.)
(Team Singles are waiting.)
Last time, I was an angel.
This time...
Let's do this.
(Here we go.)
(Team Singles are on the move.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Do you want to go first?
(Looking around)
(Who is that?)
It's Tae Yeon.
Let's run.
(They instinctively run.)
(It's a dead end.)
- We can't go here. - Come.
Come here.
(Come here, cameraman.)
(Is she gone?)
What are you doing there?
(Here you are.)
(Smiling)
You're not a bad girl, are you?
You shouldn't ask that so explicitly.
(Locked)
What are you doing?
(They have to eliminate Tae Yeon's name tag.)
She is a bad girl. I told you.
- Is the door locked? - I know you.
Is it locked?
She is a bad girl.
Hold on.
Didn't you see how she came down the stairs?
If we tear her name tag,
we can just enjoy her dance.
(You want to rip my name tag?)
What?
Has the situation reversed?
Come here.
Let's see her dance.
- Hurry up. - No.
No. I'm not a bad girl.
I'm not, guys.
Dance now.
(Name tag eliminated)
(Tae Yeon is penalized.)
- Dance for a minute. - Go.
She looks scary.
(Dancing)
- Let's go. - She's scary.
(She is definitely a bad girl.)
(A bad girl's groove)
(Is Tae Yeon really a bad girl?)
(Dressing room)
(There may be hints hidden around here.)
Where?
(A hint is found.)
Let's go.
We have to hide.
(Bad girls have won a Rookie of the Year award.)
"Bad girls have won a Rookie of the Year award."
- Girls' Generation... - You've won it, right?
- We've won it. - Then everyone has.
What about So Min?
We should ask.
(If So Min has won the award, she is a candidate too.)
She has.
(So Min has won a Rookie of the Year award.)
So Min should be included too then.
Okay.
- Okay. - We can't exclude her.
This is incredible, isn't it?
So that's how it is.
(Where is everyone?)
Over there is...
a bad girl.
- She looks like a ghost. - Over there is So Min.
Let's run.
This isn't the right way.
No.
Run.
(The partners run away.)
Stop running.
No, we need to run.
- Stop running. - She is coming this way.
Run.
(So Min targets the weakest couple.)
Stop following us.
- No, Seok Jin. - No.
No, no, no.
Let go of me.
(So Min tries to take Seok Jin while Yu Ri tries to stop her.)
No, So Min. No, no, no.
- No. - I cut it.
- I cut her bracelet. - So Min cut the bracelet.
(Seok Jin and So Min are the new partners.)
If Yoon A is a bad girl, I don't have the right to vote.
You are right.
- "You are right"? - Wait, that's not true.
- You said, "You are right." - No.
That's not true.
(Are you a bad girl too?)
I don't think it's here.
(Partnering up with a bad girl twice makes you lose your right to vote.)
Gosh, look.
That's incredible.
(The boss of Team Bad Girls is over 165cm tall.)
The boss of Team Bad Girls is over 165cm tall.
Kwang Soo, I am 161.4cm tall.
Yoon A is 168cm tall and Yu Ri is 167cm tall.
Soo Young is 170cm tall.
One of the bad girls is over 165cm tall.
That's right.
Other bad girls could be shorter.
Do you think I am one of them? Wait and see.
- Let's find one more hint. - You will see that I was right.
We just need to find one more hint.
- Who are the candidates? - Yoon A, Yu Ri, and Soo Young.
- What about So Min? - Right, there is So Min.
Is she over 165cm tall?
I am not sure.
I think she is taller than that.
Who do you think it is?
(Staring)
I am sorry.
I didn't stare because I thought it's you.
I was thinking.
It really isn't me.
Let's put our hands inside the blood pressure monitor.
(Jong Kook and Soo Young are looking for hints.)
(Putting his hand inside)
This is unbelievable.
(He finds a hint out of pure luck.)
This is unbelievable, Soo Young.
All right.
The bad girls' blood types are O or AB.
(The bad girls' blood types are O or AB.)
You must know their blood types.
- I am type O. - You are type O.
- Tae Yeon is type O. - Okay.
Yu Ri is type AB and Hyo Yeon is type AB.
(Soo Young, Tae Yeon, Yu Ri, and Hyo Yeon)
Is Yu Ri type AB?
- Hyo Yeon. - Tiffany is type O.
What? Really?
(The combined hints reveal the 4 bad girl candidates.)
Every hint must be like this.
You are right. It doesn't tell us anything definite.
Did you say you are type O?
- A lot of us are. - So...
Most members are type O or AB.
- They are types O and AB too. - You are right.
That's right. They are types O and AB.
Look at her. She has a strong will.
Tae Yeon does. Right?
- Tae Yeon has a strong will. - She looks scary.
- Look. She has a strong will. - She looks scary.
Let's go down.
We need to go. She is suspicious.
(Not even Jong Kook can fight the bad girl.)
Don't run. I am not going to run.
She told us not to run.
- "Don't run"? - That's scarier.
For goodness' sake.
Why are they coming down?
Do you know So Min's blood type?
So Min's blood type? It's AB.
So Min said that her blood type is AB.
(Does that mean So Min is a bad girl?)
- You aren't a bad girl, are you? - No, I am not.
I want to be a bad girl.
(Both So Min and Yoon A are in Team Partners now.)
This is crazy.
I am so scared.
- Who is next to Kwang Soo? - Yoon A.
- Yoon A. - Hyo Yeon is gritting her teeth.
- I heard you gave your arm. - You gave your arm.
Are you sure you aren't a bad girl?
- If you aren't a bad girl... - Listen to me.
- Are you sure that you aren't? - I am not.
- Wait a minute. - Listen to me.
- Let go of his arm. - You can decide.
(You can decide.)
(What is Kwang Soo's decision?)
(He exchanges his partner.)
I knew he wasn't a cool man.
- What are you talking about? - Hyo Yeon.
Having Terius' hairstyle doesn't make him cool.
I need to look for hints.
People all think you are a bad girl.
Forget it.
I didn't give my arm.
Let's get some air on our palms.
(Let's see.)
I think she is...
My goodness.
What was that?
(Laughing)
Are you a bad girl?
- You lost your voting right. - Why?
- Why? - You changed partners twice.
(What is So Min's identity?)
(The preliminary shoot before the opening)
- Hello. - Hello.
(So Min is a bad girl.)
Today, it'll be Partner Race with Girls' Generation.
The mission is called My Girls' Generation,
My Bad Girls' Generation.
(The bad girls are So Min and 2 members of Girls' Generation.)
The three of you are the bad girls...
- who break apart the partners. - We are the bad girls.
So Min is the boss of Team Bad Girls.
(Am I the boss of Team Bad Girls?)
(So Min is the boss of Team Bad Girls.)
- Look at his face. - Kwang Soo,
- Jong Kook said she is a bad girl. - I am not a bad girl.
- I am not. - Jae Seok said the same thing.
- I am not a bad girl. - Get a new partner quickly.
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo don't have voting rights.)
Who is that?
Yu Ri is okay.
- Who is that? - Who is that?
(Tae Yeon is behind Yu Ri.)
Who are the bad girls?
What is it? Are you a bad girl?
Are you a bad girl?
- Stick to the wall. - Tae Yeon is just standing there.
(Cutting)
- My goodness. - You have a new partner.
It's an exchange.
(Who is Yu Ri?)
- It's an exchange. - Are you a bad girl?
I am not a bad girl.
It's just that I don't have a partner.
(Team Singles continues to thrive.)
You cut the couple bracelet to make me lose my voting right.
- That's not true. - She must be a bad girl.
(Peeking)
(This is the moment.)
Seok Jin.
(Tae Yeon attacks.)
(Tae Yeon Alert is issued.)
My goodness. What are you doing?
The couple bracelet got ripped.
It got ripped when you fell down.
Are you okay?
For goodness' sake.
Did you cut it?
(She loses her position as Seok Jin's partner.)
With so many partners, I must have lost my voting right.
- Seriously. - This is hilarious.
My partner got switched so often.
(The current couples)
(Yoon A, Hyo Yeon, and Tiffany are the singles.)
(Meanwhile)
Why are we running? Do we need to run away?
- It's not like that. - Let's go.
(Let's take away his voting right.)
You have a partner.
- What is going on? - She has to be a bad girl.
- That's not true. - She has to be a bad girl.
What is wrong with you?
It hasn't been 30 seconds since we became a couple.
She rips every couple bracelet in sight.
It's So Min.
What was that?
Don't you want to be my partner? What is wrong with you?
What is wrong with you?
Are you a crazy girl or a bad girl?
Do you have something against couple bracelets?
Wait a minute.
You are a bad girl, right?
I am not.
- I am not. - Come here.
- Come here. - It's not like that.
- You have to be a bad girl. - I am not a bad girl.
Save me.
Here is a bad girl. Here is a bad girl.
I will help him.
I am not a bad girl.
(Thanks to So Min, Kwang Soo doesn't have the voting right.)
You have one minute before the end of the race.
Currently, Seok Jin doesn't have the voting right.
What?
(Seok Jin doesn't have the voting right.)
Currently, Kwang Soo doesn't have the voting right.
(Kwang Soo doesn't have the voting right.)
Seok Jin, you don't have the voting right.
Why?
He partnered up with a bad girl more than twice.
- Are you a bad girl? - No, I am not.
I told you before.
You may not talk about bad girls and partners.
Who are the bad girls?
- This is incredible. - It's not Hyo Yeon, is it?
- I am not a bad girl. - It's you, right?
It's not me.
- So Min was Kwang Soo's partner. - Hyo Yeon.
So was Hyo Yeon. He had a lot partners.
- Yoon A. - So Min is a bad girl.
- Hyo Yeon has a brother too. - I think Tae Yeon is too.
I think Hyo Yeon is a bad girl too.
- Hyo Yeon has a brother. - She does, right?
Everyone,
the race is over.
Each person can vote for two bad girls.
The three girls with the most number of votes will be judged.
(The 3 girls with the most number of votes are the final candidates.)
Soo Young's couple bracelet hasn't been cut once.
She could be a bad girl.
I... Sure, I am a bad girl.
So Min had different partners.
So Min is a bad girl.
- So Min is a bad girl. - So Min.
The other two bad girls are...
The ones without voting rights are...
(Seok Jin and Kwang Soo don't have voting rights.)
Yoon A, Tae Yeon, and So Min.
Now, Jong Kook will vote first.
We need to catch two bad girls. I am going in.
(The 3 girls with the most number of votes are the final candidates.)
My goodness.
I have no idea.
(The vote of fate begins.)
I am not sure about the last one.
(The suspicious ones,)
(Tae Yeon)
Tae Yeon.
(Tae Yeon and So Min are picked the most.)
I'm certain.
Here you go.
(So Min)
(Tae Yeon)
(The polls close.)
(If 2 out of 3 chosen ones are bad girls, Team Partners wins.)
- We have the result. - Okay.
(The result is revealed.)
The one with the most votes...
(The one with the most votes...)
received nine votes.
Everyone voted for her.
- It's So Min. - Why am I always suspected?
- Really? - Haha,
- why do you always suspect me? - No, I didn't.
We have apprehended a bad girl.
- We have caught a bad girl. - Right.
And the second-most voted one...
(The 2nd-most voted one...)
- received six votes. - Is it Tae Yeon?
It's Tae Yeon.
- Were you confused? - Goodness.
- You're not a bad girl. - She is...
It'd be crazy if she turns out innocent.
If she weren't, why did she play like that?
Exactly.
(What is the identity of Tae Yeon?)
Let's look for hints.
(Actually, she was...)
Please give me a hint.
(Actually, she was an innocent girl, desperate for a hint.)
(She just looked for hints the best she could.)
Can you give me a hint?
(She just wanted to become a couple.)
(Unfortunately, she took the 2nd place in the voting of bad girls.)
(So Min, the 1st place, is a bad girl while Tae Yeon isn't.)
Who took the third place?
I will announce the one with the third-most votes.
The final result will be revealed at the set...
for the ice shower.
The one with the third-most votes...
received three votes.
It's Yu Ri.
(Yu Ri received 3 votes.)
(It's Yu Ri? What a twist.)
Hyo Yeon took the 4th place by 1 vote.
(So Min is a bad girl, and Tae Yeon is innocent. What about Yu Ri?)
(The final judgment)
This is the final judgment.
On the count of three, if you are not a bad girl,
you can take a step back. We'll start.
Were you able to apprehend...
the bad girls?
(So far, there is 1 bad girl and 1 innocent girl.)
(What is the identity of the third nominee, Yu Ri?)
- Someone who can lie well. - Someone brazen.
(Yu Ri has been constantly suspected as a bad girl.)
I think Yu Ri is a bad girl.
(Their suspicion continued until the final race.)
(As she daringly attacked others,)
(she managed to stay as a couple until the end.)
(Is Yu Ri a bad girl or just an innocent girl?)
(Or is Hyo Yeon a bad girl who had the 4th most votes by 1 vote?)
- That's right. - The reason why you chose Yoon A...
(She seemed suspicious during every game.)
(She, who's known to be strong, lost an arm wrestling match to Tae Yeon.)
(All day long, Hyo Yeon has been enjoying the twists.)
(Is Hyo Yeon a bad girl?)
(The final judgment)
Were you able to...
(If they are not bad girls, they will retreat on the count of three.)
One.
(If Hyo Yeon is a bad girl, Team Bad Girls wins.)
Two.
Three.
(If Yu Ri is a bad girl, Team Partners wins.)
(What is the result?)
(Yu Ri and So Min are the bad girls.)
(These two bad girls get the ice shower.)
- Tae Yeon wasn't a bad girl? - What?
Hey, Yu Ri!
I didn't know she was one.
Tae Yeon wasn't a bad girl?
- Jong Kook, I'm really sorry. - What?
(Jong Kook, I'm really sorry.)
(I'm a bad girl.)
She said she's sorry. She apologized to me.
(Soo Young and Jong Kook get the ice shower as well.)
She was a bad girl?
(What a shocking twist!)
- This is unbelievable. - You were a bad girl?
- I told you it was Soo Young! - It was Soo Young?
- She was the last bad girl? - Goodness.
- Tae Yeon wasn't the bad girl? - Unbelievable.
I told you that I wasn't the bad girl!
Gosh, I didn't see that coming.
- Goodness, Soo Young. - Gosh.
- I was so surprised. - I got goose bumps.
(Today's bad girls were Soo Young, Yu Ri, and So Min.)
(Running High School)
Hello.
(This morning, 30 minutes before the shoot)
(The bad girls' preliminary meeting)
- Hello. - Hi.
You are bad girls who will interfere with other partners.
(The birth of bad girls)
You know us well.
I'm at a disadvantage.
No one will try to be my partner.
Girls' Generation is joining us today.
Should I rip my uniform, so I can seduce them?
What should I do?
(So Min, no. That's what a crazy girl does.)
- It's Bad Girls' Generation now. - It's Bad Girls' Generation now.
- It will be Bad Girls' Generation. - It will be Bad Girls' Generation.
- Bad Girls' Generation forever. - Bad Girls' Generation forever.
(Thus began the highlights of the bad girls.)
We have to separate the bad girls.
(During the race, they deceived everyone...)
(and did their celebratory gestures alone.)
(The bad girl of this area...)
(is me!)
(Before she got caught, she put on a serious look.)
(The best bad girl has to be Soo Young, hands down.)
Hey, bad girls.
(Sometimes, she acted tough.)
(Sometimes, she was gentle.)
(She was even able to make Jong Kook let his guard down.)
(She's the ultimate femme fatale.)
All right. So today's bad girls were...
Soo Young, Yu Ri, and So Min.
This is a twist after a twist.
- I didn't know Yu Ri was one. - I didn't know Soo Young was.
- I didn't even suspect her. - Soo Young.
It's their 10-year anniversary. They joined us after 2 years.
Thank you for joining us on a hot day like today.
It was fun, and we enjoyed it very much.
Thanks to you, we were so happy.
Let's give it up for Girls' Generation.
Great work!
(Their lovely day with the girls has gone by.)
(All of a sudden, someone has paid them a visit.)
This is giving me the chills.
(It's a series of mysterious events...)
(that can't be identified.)
(There's more than meets the eye.)
(This is 2017 Running Man's Horror Special.)
(Find the Ghost)