(2017 Running Man's 3rd Global Project)
(Half and Half Tour)
(Salar de Uyuni is nature's biggest and clearest mirror.)
(Bora Bora is Venus' island located in the South Pacific Ocean.)
(Rome is the eternal city that has the history of the Roman Empire.)
(Antelope Canyon is a sandstone formation created by rain and wind.)
(Alaska is the home of extreme sports and aurora.)
(Lake Hillier is a romantic lake that is made pink by plankton.)
(Bow River lets the visitors enjoy fly fishing in the Rocky Mountains.)
(Krabi is a fantastic vacation spot where the sky and sea connect.)
(Did you think there'd be only paradise ahead of you?)
(There are also hideous vacation places which the staff recommended.)
(8 recommendations from the members and 8 recommendations from the crew)
(Each week, the members have a match to put their names on the roulette.)
(First destination turned out to be the Nevis Swing in New Zealand.)
(Jae Seok, the icon of penalties, got Nevis Swing in New Zealand.)
(Second destination was...)
(Bora Bora, the fantastic vacation spot, which Haha recommended.)
(So Min, the icon of luck, got Bora Bora.)
(And)
(Last week)
(Lee Elijah)
(Sun Mi)
(Hwang Seung Un)
(Baek Z Young)
(Kei)
(Sol Bi)
(Sung Hoon)
(Cho Sae Ho)
(The 8 guests with 8 different charms are here in Running Man.)
(It became the talk of the town last week.)
(This is an accident.)
(Mimicking)
(Dancing)
(Cute charm)
(Unacceptable, cute charm)
(Sexy charm)
(Unacceptable, sexy charm)
(Those charming guests have fully adapted to Running Man.)
(Have they really adapted to it?)
(They end showing off their charms and begin their race.)
Each couple...
(There are 14 remaining vacation spots.)
(The staff has added two more balls about mission money in the box.)
(Each couple draws 2 balls from the box among the total of 16 balls.)
(What the winning couple has picked will be put on the roulette.)
(And they begin the lunch mission suddenly.)
(Their destinations are decided by the order of arrival.)
(Everyone wants to have Korean table d'hote.)
(Jae Seok is forced out to have samgyetang.)
- Hey. - What?
(Let's switch destinations.)
(They plan to change destinations and have Korean table d'hote.)
(They secretly and quietly snatch the Korean table d'hote.)
- Jae Seok. - Yes?
(Be prepared to be my Korean table d'hote menu.)
(He acts like he doesn't know.)
All right.
(Jong Kook is upset. How will the members' fate turn out to be?)
(The bus is almost there at the Korean table d'hote place.)
I'm not worried about anything...
except for Jong Kook.
(They're anxious.)
- Thankfully... - We have not much shooting left.
Right.
And he beat me up so hard,
so he can do this much.
- That's only natural. - It wasn't a penalty.
He literally beat me up.
- I agree. - Don't you agree?
Let me see your arm.
- Seriously. - Goodness.
(The story behind his swollen arm)
(It'll be revealed now.)
(1 hour before they board the buses)
Let's go.
This mission is called Add the Numbers.
(Add the Numbers)
You'll either be penalized to get hit on your forehead...
or obtain more mission money through this mission.
A couple will throw two dice.
They'll follow what it says regarding the added-up number.
If the 2 numbers add up to 7,
they have to get hit on their foreheads once.
Then they can raise the number of forehead hits as they want...
and throw the dice again.
If the 2 numbers add up to 8, they have to choose...
whether to get the total hits or to avoid it by paying 3 dollars.
- Three dollars... - You need to get hit instead.
If the 2 numbers add up to 9, they will get the total hits...
and throw the dice once again.
If the 2 numbers add up to 6, the playing order will go backwards.
If the numbers are double 1 or double 6,
they will have an exciting dance time and take the accumulated fine.
- That sounds great. - They'll also...
decide on who will get the accumulated forehead hits.
(The added number of their dice will play a critical role.)
Sae Ho, you can do it, right?
Sure, I can do this.
It's going this way.
You'll throw the dice in this order.
Ji Hyo and Sae Ho will start first.
Let's go!
Shall I throw it first?
It's all bad except for the double numbers.
It's good to have 6 or 1.
I'll go first.
- I'll go. - You better throw it well.
You've done nothing well so far.
- I didn't do well? - No.
Okay. 1, 2, 3.
(He powerfully throws his die.)
- It's four. - It's not good.
- It'll be 7, 8, or 9 for certain. - 7, 8, or 9.
It'll be either 7, 8, or 9 for certain.
Make it six.
- It'll be 10 then. - I'll go.
(Will the lucky Ji Hyo avoid paying the fine and getting the penalty?)
Ji Hyo can avoid it.
It's nine.
- What is that? - They get the penalty for certain.
- What is nine? - You get hit on your forehead.
Gosh, you get the penalty.
Haha, do it.
They get hit by whom? Us?
- Yes. - Oh, my.
(Which one between the 2 will get the penalty for the 1st time?)
Sae Ho will get hit.
(Of course, it's Sae Ho.)
- Is it going to be 1 of the 2? - Yes.
Sae Ho will get slapped.
- Me? - Of course.
- Are you good at this? - Not really.
(It's his first time getting Haha's finger flick.)
(Slap)
(Thud)
You're good at it.
- It was too weak. - Are you okay?
- Goodness. - It's not that bad.
It's bearable.
- Okay. - It's bearable.
Okay, let's move on.
(After getting the forehead slap)
Please throw the dice again.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Go first.
(They throw the dice again.)
- 8. - It's 8.
(They have to either get the penalty or pay the fine and try again.)
- What is it? - Get the penalty or pay the fine.
(Penalty or fine)
Sae Ho, take it slowly.
Your forehead is so red now.
Are you going to get a forehead slap or pay three dollars?
We don't have money. We can't pay three dollars.
- I'll get the slap. - We have no money.
(They have no choice.)
(Thud)
(Getting slapped again)
- Goodness. - That must hurt a lot.
My goodness.
Please throw the dice.
Excuse me. Until when will you throw the dice?
- We need to move things along. - Listen.
Let's enjoy the game together.
I am terribly sorry,
but I want to stop throwing the dice too.
I am only following the rules.
- I apologize. Here we go again. - We need to move on with the shoot.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(It's their 3rd attempt.)
It will be 8 or 7.
- 8. - 8.
(It's 8 again.)
- Eight. - Take another slap.
- Take the penalty. - Take a slap on the forehead.
- 8. - 8.
(Is he playing the game by himself?)
- People are waiting... - This is...
for their turns.
- Don't do this in front of us. - I am not doing this on purpose.
- This is too much. - Bring us chairs.
- We need to move on with the shoot. - Let us have a turn.
- I can't do this. This is hard. - Sae Ho, come on.
- Go on. - How many slaps am I taking?
In 1, 2.
- My goodness. - You are good at this.
(Please stop.)
You will have to throw the dice again.
- My goodness. - What are you planning to do?
Do we have to see blood?
I will slap your forehead so hard this time.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
We did it.
(What is the result of their 4th attempt?)
11. We won't get a penalty. Okay.
(They finally escape the never-ending cycle of dice.)
We did it.
- Shall we throw the dice? - Let's throw them together.
In 1, 2, 3.
(After a long wait, it's Kwang Soo and Seung Un's turn.)
- 6. - 6.
(If it's 6...)
Okay.
(The dice come to them again.)
- It goes in the opposite direction. - It goes in the opposite direction.
- It's Sae Ho's turn again. - It goes in the opposite direction.
(He receives a round of applause from the unlucky members.)
It's Sae Ho and Ji Hyo's turn again.
(Where is the end of this road?)
Sae Ho, let us play.
We need to move on with the shoot.
Look.
We need to move on with the shoot since they are busy people.
This is too much.
- I apologize, - We need to move on with the shoot.
but this is beyond my power.
- Sae Ho is like a swamp. - I am sorry.
(You can't escape from Sae Ho's swamp.)
All right.
(Ji Hyo and Sae Ho change the direction with 6.)
- Throw the dice at the same time. - Let's throw them together.
- Let's throw them together. - They will throw the dice together.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(What is the result of their first attempt?)
(Receive a penalty, or pay a fine and go again.)
Receive a penalty, or pay a fine.
- It's a single slap, right? - You might not get another chance.
Take a forehead slap this time.
Kwang Soo, would you be okay later?
- I will take the forehead slap. - Really?
Should I slap you?
(He sacrifices his body to save the mission money.)
Where should I slap you?
Should I slap you here?
- It doesn't matter where you slap. - How about the forehead?
- Slap wherever you want. - Really?
Jong Kook, smile. How is he supposed to slap you?
(Don't be scared. Slap my forehead.)
- Why are you grabbing me? - It's nothing.
- It's not a title match. - I know.
Slap me.
(The betraying giraffe, Kwang Soo, versus Anyang tiger, Jong Kook)
Kwang Soo wasn't earning points from Jong Kook from the start.
(Jong Koo, long time no see.)
(You hit me even when I was eating...)
(or when I was with other people.)
(You made me suffer in front of the guests.)
(Jong Kook, let me give you a forehead slap.)
(He punches Jong Kook's forehead.)
Wait a minute. It's not like that. Listen to me.
You told me to slap however I wanted.
- My goodness. - It's not like that.
I am serious. He gave me permission.
Jong Kook, you told me to slap however I wanted.
(He can't contain the anger from getting his forehead punched.)
Kwang Soo is over.
Jong Kook, you told me to slap however I wanted.
Let me slap him once.
He shouldn't have used his hand.
I also think that he didn't follow the rule.
- He didn't follow the rule. - He deserves a slap.
- That's right. You deserve a slap. - A slap?
- That's right. - Take a slap.
- Shall I slap your wrist instead? - What?
- Shall I slap your wrist? - I will take a slap on the wrist.
Shall I slap your wrist?
That will hurt as well.
That's going to hurt.
(Kwang Soo, I promise to go easy on you.)
I'm sorry for what I did.
- Shall I slap your wrist? - Yes.
(Why do I feel a chill down my spine?)
(He collapses.)
For goodness' sake.
(Are you in pain? I am in pain too.)
(Joyous, satisfied, and refreshed)
Did you see that?
His hand went like this.
In slow motion, you will see his arm bend.
(We hope Jong Kook and Kwang Soo will become close.)
Let's move on.
(Jae Seok is scared from watching the event.)
You might end up getting a slap from Jong Kook.
My ears are ringing from a slap on my wrist.
I might have one more person to slap.
(Getting 8 or 9 earns me a slap from Jong Kook.)
Sun Mi, let's pray that we complete the round safely.
(Let's complete the round safely.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Sun Mi goes first.)
Three. I need to get three.
Jae Seok. Jae Seok.
Jae Seok.
- What are you doing? - I want to watch.
Am I not allowed to stand here?
No, you aren't.
(Really?)
My goodness.
Why do you keep doing this to me?
He quietly beckoned me over earlier and said,
"You should stay back since you are in a bad condition."
"Stay back?"
He said that my stories are too weak.
You are in a terrible condition today.
He told me to stay back after I apologize to Ji Hyo.
He said that I am doing a terrible job.
- You are doing a terrible job. - Really?
- Your stories are too weak. - Really?
(I must avoid 5 and 6 since Sun Mi got 3.)
- Eight. - This is the worst.
(Receive a penalty, or pay a fine and go again.)
(He is the original unlucky member.)
Will you receive a penalty or pay a fine?
(Choose between paying a fine and getting a slap from Jong Kook.)
- Pay a fine. - Sun Mi, let's pay a fine.
Sun Mi, it's only one slap.
- Is it 1 slap? - It's only 1 slap.
- If it's only one slap... - No way.
- Sun Mi has something to say. - I already received the change.
(Seok Jin and Sol Bi go next.)
Eight.
(Upon receiving 8, he pays a fine without a thought.)
Let's pay up.
Why would you do that?
- Look at his face. - Take a slap.
- Look at his face. - You can't pay a fine.
You should take a slap.
Why would you tell me what to do with my forehead?
(My forehead is precious.)
- What's wrong with you? - You can do this.
- You can take the slap. - Then you should do it.
I am paying three dollars.
They are paying a fine one after another.
We can take it back.
- How will we take it back? - Listen.
An incredible amount will come to us next time.
Sung Hoon and So Min.
So Min and Sung Hoon.
Seeing as how So Min is quiet, her heart must be fluttering.
(So Min is usually chatty.)
- That's not true. - She is in love.
So Min is uncharacteristically quiet...
- in front of Sung Hoon. - Seriously.
- That's not true. - Are you out of your mind?
Aren't you going to work?
(Magnet, aren't you going to work?)
What do you think you are doing?
(A variety show is like a war. We have no time for romance.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(Please let us have 1 and 1 or 6 and 6.)
Come back to your senses. Focus.
11.
(They get 11.)
Getting 6 and 6 would have been amazing.
- We passed the round safely. - That was close.
(His heart is pounding.)
This is nothing, but my heart is pounding.
(This is nothing, but my heart is pounding.)
(She gets to touch his chest.)
(She feels his excitement and regret with her palm.)
Wait a minute. What are you doing?
- Why did you hold So Min's hand? - I was nervous.
- I wanted her to feel my heartbeat. - Suddenly...
Suddenly, he took my hand like this.
(Sung Hoon's behavior makes people feel excited and jealous.)
(It's the signal of the heart.)
This is an opportunity.
- Did the order change? - Yes, it did.
We are going in the opposite direction.
- Throw high. - This is your chance.
Let's complete this round and slap someone.
My goodness.
(Six)
- That's good. - You can do it.
You will take all the money if you get six.
- We will earn money. - Six?
- You will take all if you get 6. - 6.
6. 6.
Six.
Excuse me.
(The die doesn't roll.)
(I am a trickster.)
I am sorry. I am sorry.
I didn't realize this before, but she is deceitful.
Stop complimenting her on everything she does.
- I am sorry. - What was that?
I will teach her well.
- We will remedy the situation. - You need to host the game well.
They need to have some manners.
Be quiet.
(Let's end it here.)
(Sae Ho, your talk is weak.)
- Please be quiet. - Okay.
Elijah.
(He leaves after cutting Sae Ho off.)
You can't do that.
(Should I go home early?)
If you agree to this rule,
we will end the game when a team gets a same set of numbers.
- Okay. - We need a same set of numbers.
That's right.
You can go first.
- It's their turn. - Okay.
(It's So Min and Sung Hoon's turn.)
- Two. - Sung Hoon, get two.
- Two. - Two.
(Sung Hoon needs to get 2.)
He did it.
(They get 2 and 2.)
Sung Hoon!
(So Min and Sung Hoon take the accumulated fine.)
It's unfortunate that it ended before us.
- You should dance. - Should we dance?
Should we dance?
(Dancing)
(So Min and Sung Hoon win Add the Numbers with an odd dance.)
Whose dance are you imitating?
All right.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
This mission includes...
meal cards and mission money.
- Meal cards. - It would be great to eat.
Guess the Movie.
- Guess the Movie? - What is that?
Guess the Movie?
Oh, it's about listening to a movie scene.
You have to guess the title of a given video clip.
If you choose the section of the video which you'd like to listen,
we will play the video from that part for 10 seconds.
You have to guess its title right only by listening to the scene.
It may be a scene from a drama or a movie.
(The questions are not only from movies this time.)
The winning couple will be given a meal card and 10 dollars.
Nice.
And the couple in the second place will be given a meal card.
The rest will be given dried laver and rice.
(The rest will be given dried laver and rice.)
There's nothing we can do with dried laver.
Make it just for the couple who places last.
- There's nothing we can do with it. - I'm hungry.
You need to press a strange buzzer in order to get a chance to speak.
A strange buzzer?
(It's another upgraded rule.)
(They must clear a simple mission...)
(to get a chance to speak for each question.)
After listening to a 10-second audio,
the couple who first presses the buzzer will get to speak.
You'll get to choose another section to listen to before you guess.
(They will get to pick another section to listen to.)
(It means they can listen to it once more if they ring the buzzer.)
If you guess wrongly, the couple on your right will be given a chance.
(The couple on their right will guess.)
(The mission money and meal cards are on the line.)
(Only two teams will be able to have a delicious meal.)
(Which couple will succeed in acquiring the meal cards?)
The female members will have to ring the buzzer for this question.
- All right. - I need to press it.
- The female members. - That's right.
Do I go out and guess?
- What? - I don't understand.
Only the female members can ring the buzzer this time.
- So I go and ring the buzzer. - Right.
You need to tear plastic wrap...
to press this first buzzer.
(The first buzzer is about plastic wrap.)
(They understand.)
- All right. - What?
What does he mean? How do I tear it?
- With your face. - Goodness.
Here's why I feel bad about her.
She's been teasing Seok Jin...
for not understanding rules throughout the day.
(She's been teasing Seok Jin throughout the day.)
- She's worse. - What are you doing?
Seok Jin understands the rules better than you.
- We have to use only our faces? - You...
- I feel confident because of you. - Seok Jin.
Just wait. I'm not going to ask you from now on.
Z Young.
- It's from a drama this time. - Okay.
All right.
I'll play the video for 10 seconds now.
- Here we go. - Let's go.
(They have to guess the drama title.)
(Which couple will get the first question right?)
Who told you to do such work?
Your business will get better once the weather gets warm.
Why would you choose to suffer? Think of your age too.
We're still in our youth.
Don't worry about us, and take care of yourself.
- Hold on. - Go ring it.
Go ring the buzzer.
- Do you know what it is? - Do you know?
Yes. Do it.
(Do you want me to tear the wrap with my face?)
You better get it right.
(They have no idea.)
Do you know?
I think it's a series drama. The actor...
(They must tear the plastic wrap first to speak.)
Goodness.
- Goodness. - You can do it.
1, 2, 3.
- That's not enough. - You need to do it harder.
(That's not enough.)
It's that thick?
- Gosh, your face. - Your face has been stamped on it.
(You can tell it's Z Young.)
- Gosh, your face... - How do I do it?
- Awesome. - Goodness.
It's worth keeping.
- Take it home. - Take it to your house.
- Your face... - Your face's been stamped on it.
Even your double eyelids are there.
(Her challenge left a huge mark.)
How could...
You can try it at the same time.
You just to need to tear it first.
I need to tear it before the others do?
You can try it at the same time.
(Is that right?)
- You just to need to tear it first. - Really?
Yes, you need to tear it before the others do.
(She doesn't hesitate.)
So Min...
(That's not how you use your pretty face.)
- Goodness. - So Min.
(So Min succeeds.)
- How did you... - So Min succeeds.
- How did she do it? - All right.
- You get a chance to guess. - That was amazing.
(She's in shock.)
I know the answer.
Hold on. She might get it wrong.
- All right. - Let's wait and see.
Is it a daily drama?
Please play the video from 31 minutes.
All right. Wait.
This is the construction report on the lands in Gangnam.
Please review it.
Is that so? Did you organize them already?
I'm sure it's Kim Yong Gun's voice.
Hurry up, and get it wrong.
- What is this? - I have no idea.
Just guess anything.
What is your answer?
The answer is...
(There's Kim Yong Gun's voice in the ordinary conversation.)
- Stop. - The answer is...
"Woman of Dignity".
(It's wrong.)
- I just don't know. - Gosh, this...
I think I know.
- His voice is so familiar. - Exactly.
- The way he talks... - When I heard the second audio...
I'll go.
Please play the video from 13 minutes and 20 seconds.
- Honey, hurry out. - Okay.
"Honey"?
I'm sure it's Kim Yong Gun's voice.
(The sound of his leaving)
The drama...
(The sound of closing doors)
- What? - You picked the wrong part.
- We only heard door sounds. - They're closing doors.
Goodness.
I can only hear door sounds.
(His choice isn't of help at all.)
They're closing doors.
- Seok Jin. - Is it "Love on a Jujube Tree"?
(Whispering)
(Did Haha figure out something?)
But he said, "Honey."
"We Got Married" is too...
Do you think I'm a fool?
(Kim Yong Gun was on "We Got Married"?)
He told me it's "We Got Married" because he said, "Honey."
(Whatever)
- "We Got Married". - Goodness.
Can it be something about an earthen pot?
What is your guess?
"Seoul Earthen Pot".
That's so old.
I didn't know you'd remember "Seoul Earthen Pot".
She told me if it was "Chief Inspector".
"Chief Inspector".
- 15 minutes. - Last one ended with water sound.
- Something might come out after. - After that part?
- We choose 15 minutes. - Okay.
- Okay, 15 minutes. - All right.
(Will there be any important clues?)
He wore the same ring as mine.
- Is that a commercial? - And he...
kissed me too.
So what does it mean?
You wear matching rings and have kissed too.
- It means... - Goodness.
Can it be "My Husband Got a Family"?
- I don't know. - Goodness.
Can it be?
This drama...
It's driving me crazy.
- What is your answer? - "My Husband Got a Family".
- I think it's right. - No.
(Acting smart)
Did it make a hit?
- What can it be? - It was very popular.
Goodness. It's driving me crazy.
- 3 minutes and 20 seconds. - Okay.
(What's the result of his strategy to choose the beginning part?)
- Don't you think so? - Right.
It's right.
(They hear the familiar music.)
(Our guess was right.)
(They figure out what it is as well.)
- Goodness. - We were right.
- I'll go. - Go ahead.
"Temptation of Wife".
(The answer is "Temptation of Wife".)
(This legendary drama received 40 percent of viewer ratings.)
(Its theme song became just as popular as the drama.)
"Temptation of Wife".
(Sung Hoon's choice allowed them to listen to the theme song.)
It was worth tearing the plastic wrap.
I recognized the song right away.
Here comes the second question.
The first question...
- is from a movie. - All right.
Let's go.
I'll play it for 10 seconds.
Here we go.
You'll part ways with your family, so why don't you take a picture?
- Really? - Goodness.
- Let go. - Hey.
It sounded like people...
"Hometown Report"?
Are you sure you didn't film nearby here?
Is it us?
- It goes this way? - Team Ji Hyo, tell us...
- which part you want to listen. - Okay.
You'll get a feeling if you listen to the beginning part.
(What?)
Sae Ho...
56 minutes.
- What? - You don't make sense.
(You said differently 5 seconds ago.)
What are you talking about?
He said he'd listen to the beginning part.
- Ji Hyo didn't like the idea. - What was that?
Shouldn't we listen to the beginning part?
No, it'll be hard to know.
Then how about 30 minutes?
We'll go with 60 minutes and 40 seconds.
- Pardon? - 60 minutes and 40 seconds.
60 minutes and 40 seconds.
We'll play the movie now.
I got a call from Jacque at dawn today.
He's a corporal of the French army.
He's working with his twin brother, Paul.
- It's difficult. - How are we supposed to...
Is it illegally downloaded?
- I heard some cracking sounds. - I know what this is.
Five...
I know the answer. This is...
I know what this is.
(Sae Ho, do you really know the answer?)
It's "Tunnel".
- It's "Tunnel". - Be specific.
- I don't need to spell this out. - No, but be specific.
- "Tunnel". - "Tunnel".
(It's wrong.)
"Tunnel".
(He made all the fuss, but it's wrong.)
Nothing's going right with you today.
Why did she hit you?
I don't know. She got upset and hit me.
(They're in a love-hate relationship.)
- It's Kwang Soo's turn now, right? - Yes.
I'm going to get it right for certain.
An hour...
No, I think it's better to listen to the beginning part.
I figured it out when I heard the part which they first played for us.
- Is that right? - You need to focus on dialogues.
- Do you know what it is? - Come on.
I'll get it right for certain when my turn comes.
- 10 minutes. - 10 minutes?
I'll play it until 10 minutes 10 seconds.
We'll play the movie now.
I saw a photo of him holding heads in both of his hands.
Goodness.
Everyone has done that in Vietnam.
Have you seen me?
- "Vietnam"? - Was it the character's name?
Which one is it?
(It's "Ode to My Father".)
(I'm a genius.)
Go, Se Chan.
I was accurate.
I got it.
I have no idea.
- You don't know the answer. - What is he holding?
- 4, 3. - "Silmido".
(Wrong answer)
(This is the answer.)
I select 1 hour 20 minutes 30 seconds.
1 hour 20 minutes 30 seconds.
We'll play the movie now.
Commander, are you okay?
Commander!
(Various people screaming)
- It's confusing. - Why is there a commander?
- Why is there a commander? - It's confusing.
It's what the director wanted.
(The answer is obvious.)
Why do you ask that?
- He looks confused. - Three.
- Two. - "Ode to My Father".
(Se Chan's answer is the same as Sae Ho's.)
(Will their answer be correct?)
"Ode to My Father"?
- It's wrong. - I knew it.
(It's not correct.)
Gosh, Sae Ho is wrong all the time.
(She's speechless.)
Come on, Sae Ho.
(I'm wrong again.)
Gosh.
He's driving me crazy.
I must answer correctly.
(Whispering)
(Oh, that's right.)
Isn't it right?
(She's desperate to answer.)
I select 49 minutes 20 seconds.
49 minutes 20 seconds.
We'll play the movie now.
They're trying to buy time.
Have you contacted the headquarters?
- No. - I'm 100 percent sure.
It's not up yet.
I know the answer.
(Everyone recognizes his voice.)
(It's Jae Seok and Sun Mi's turn to answer.)
Wait.
- You may answer. - It's...
(It was an important clue.)
(Did Jae Seok recognize which movie it is?)
It's "R-Point".
(Sigh)
(More sighing)
("R-Point" is correct.)
- I knew it. - Goodness.
(It was released in 2004.)
(It's a horror movie that everyone still talks about.)
(The director needed a commander.)
(It starred Son Byeong Ho and Kam Woo Sung.)
It was "R-Point".
(Jae Seok and Sun Mi guess correctly.)
(We did it.)
(Things aren't going well for us.)
Kwang Soo is in 1st place for answering 4 questions.
Didn't they finish playing?
- They're in first place. - We'll win.
Next mission is...
push-ups.
The female member must do 5 push-ups in 10 seconds...
to clear the mission.
The female member?
Many of them work out.
Here's the next movie.
We'll play the movie now.
(A random part plays.)
What brings you here? Wait.
Hey, what's that sound?
What sound?
Someone talking in his sleep?
I heard a girl's voice. What was it?
A girl's voice? Really?
Really?
(I know the answer.)
Buzzer.
Let's go, Seung Un.
No, we should listen more.
You have 10 seconds to do 5 push-ups.
- You know the answer? - Do it.
- Get ready. - Just do it.
- Set. - I can't do five.
Start.
(What should I do?)
1, 2, 3.
Four.
She can do it.
(Ji Hyo is amazing.)
1, 2.
(Her posture is perfect.)
- She did five. - Success.
Great.
(She did 5 perfect push-ups in 10 seconds.)
(You must give the right answer.)
It sounds somewhat familiar.
22 minutes 10 seconds.
We'll play the movie now.
Hey, you.
Don't come in.
You punks.
- I'll throw you against the wall. - Goodness.
Darn it.
(Seung Un found out the answer again.)
"Throw you against"?
What is it?
Sae Ho was serious when he told me that...
he'll pay me 1,000 dollars for the right answer.
- It's true. - Come on, Sae Ho.
He was being serious.
- Are you trying to brag? - That's what he said.
I was trying to help him.
He's not lying. This is what Kwang Soo whispered to Sae Ho.
- He said it's "Mulberry". - He said it's "Mulberry".
- Kwang Soo. - Five minutes.
- 1 hour 5 minutes 20 seconds. - I'll give you 1,000 dollars.
1,000 dollars.
(He tries to make a deal.)
(Kwang Soo gave him the wrong answer.)
He tried to take 1,000 dollars for "Mulberry".
- He said "Mulberry". - What's the answer?
- Wait a minute. - Wait.
You have three seconds.
- What's the question? - Three.
- Do we guess the movie title? - Sae Ho.
(What are we doing right now?)
We've been playing for so long.
- He says he doesn't know. - One.
Time is up.
- Is it... - I know.
- Think carefully. - Here's my answer.
I'll say the answer in a stylish way.
The answer is...
(Sae Ho has been mostly incorrect. Is he confident this time?)
It has three syllables.
(Under pressure,)
(Sae Ho comes up with an answer.)
(What is his three-syllable answer?)
It's "The Attorney".
Oh Dal Su starred in it.
We know the answer.
Oh Dal Su starred in many movies.
He's in many movies.
He really is.
I told you to think carefully.
I had to say something.
Why are you scolding me?
- Ji Hyo. - Goodness.
1 hour 10 seconds.
That's a good time.
Play movie.
- Leave it alone. - It's Lee Yae Seung.
He says Yae Seung when he sees boxes.
I know the answer.
(An inarticulate voice)
(Yae Seung)
- I know the answer. - It's obvious.
(It's Oh Dal Su's voice.)
It's "Miracle in Cell No. 7".
They got lucky.
Yae Seung made it obvious.
He suddenly said Yae Seung.
- That made it obvious. - It gave the answer.
- I got goosebumps. - 1 hour 10 seconds...
was a good time.
("Miracle in Cell No. 7" is a popular family movie.)
(Thanks to Yae Seung, Kwang Soo gets the right answer.)
Kwang Soo and Seung Un get a Korean table d'hote meal...
and mission money of 10 dollars.
The couple that placed second...
gets a Korean table d'hote meal.
That's good enough.
Sung Hoon and So Min placed first.
- Jong Kook and Kei placed second. - Okay.
Thank you.
(They win mission money.)
Goodness.
Are they stone pots?
Gosh, this is too much.
Is this galbi?
(It's a very fancy meal.)
- It looks delicious. - It seems healthy.
- Eat up. - It's impressive.
Just eating the rice would be good enough.
(They enjoy a fancy meal.)
- Just rice would be good enough. - Let's give some to Ji Hyo.
(They can't hear him.)
- Isn't that galbi? - It's such a fancy meal.
(Even at a samgyetang restaurant,)
(they only get to eat dried laver.)
They serve delicious dried laver.
It's so delicious.
It's delicious.
It tastes great.
This is better than samgyetang.
It's true.
I'm not jealous.
Samgyetang is...
The broth is rich.
(Which couple will be the final winner?)
(Currently, Haha and Z Young have the highest score.)
The final mission is...
Roulette Name Tag Elimination.
(Roulette Name Tag Elimination)
(Name Tag Elimination?)
Is it Name Tag Elimination?
(Roulette Name Tag Elimination?)
It's Name Tag Elimination.
It's Target Name Tag Elimination with a time limit of 30 minutes.
(Target Name Tag Elimination)
- Gosh. - Do you see the roulette?
(The members' names are written on the roulette.)
I knew it.
Spin the two roulettes that have your names on them...
to determine two target members.
Those whose name tags get eliminated will be reset on the roulette.
New target members will be announced through the speakers.
This is scary.
The reward will be 30 dollars.
Turning the tables is possible.
(I won't miss this chance.)
Gosh.
The couple to eliminate the target's name tags gets rewarded.
You may choose to exchange...
the ball that the target members have.
(Exchanging the ball with target members is possible.)
However, you may not check what's inside the ball.
If the target member and his partner press buttons...
before their name tags get eliminated,
the roulettes will spin and change the target members.
(If they find the reset button, the target member changes.)
Okay.
The winning couple's choice of destination will be on the roulette.
They may purchase name tags with the money they win.
It's not easy.
Please go to your assigned places.
- It's not easy. - We can do it.
(Who will have the honor of winning the race?)
First off, as long as they don't target us,
we should take off the name tags.
Let's remove the name tags everyone is targeting and earn 30 dollars.
- Let's get the reward. - Yes, we should.
Hopefully, we won't be selected, and we'll only remove the name tags.
That's the best scenario.
If one of us is the target, the other one should run.
That's a good way to go about this.
I wouldn't say we'd be running away from them.
We have to find the button.
- Right. We should find the button. - We have to search the area for it.
We should be running while we keep an eye for it.
Sae Ho, I'm counting on your luck today.
Ji Hyo, after the shoot,
I'll make sure you tell me...
that you will treat me to a meal.
I'll make you want to buy me a meal.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
If not,
as soon as the shoot ends,
(If not, as soon as the shot ends,)
you'll be dead meat.
I'm serious. Just wait.
You'll be dead meat.
(Sae Ho might have to put his life on the line for this race.)
Depending on how you play today,
I might end up here if things go south.
(Ji Hyo chose hammocking in Indonesia.)
That must be so fun.
(You're going to be in a hammock?)
Ji Hyo, where else would you have the chance to experience it?
(Gosh, Sae Ho. You haven't come to your senses yet.)
Don't you think so?
(Whispering)
I think my ear is bleeding.
(Figuring out others' destinations is the key.)
- Should we each have a ball? - Shall we?
- It's not really necessary though. - We'll just do it.
- We earned a lot of money. - We don't have any good ones.
(They have balls of 2 destinations the crew picked.)
- I have a blue ball. - Okay.
I chose Copper Canyon.
(1 destination of the members and 1 destination of the crew)
I knew it. You're a princess from Rome.
Ta-da.
(They chose 2 destinations of the members.)
(Rome, Italy, and Salar de Uyuni, Bolivia)
I chose Alaska and a chance to see the aurora.
I chose Australia.
(Se Chan and Elijah, who are ranked 3rd, chose two blue balls.)
- I'm going to be hiding. - In where?
You should just find the button and press it for me.
If I'm selected, I'll be hiding.
If you're picked, you should hide.
That's a great idea. Let's do that.
(Let's stay 1st in the race.)
Sun Mi, how could you pick that one?
You chose Indonesia...
- The volcano tour. - and the volcano tour.
(They're 6th in the race, and Sun Mi chose the volcano tour.)
Why do bad things always happen to us?
(I had faith in you.)
Look at this. I chose...
the division card.
(They're the unluckiest. They will divide the mission money by 2?)
This is how unlucky I am.
I'm tired of being the unlucky one.
- We can give that to someone else. - That's true.
- I can just give mine to anyone. - Exactly.
(I must get rid of this first.)
I didn't know...
- Right. - there's only one of this.
I think this is the best one of all.
I really thought that there were more multiplication cards.
(He might've used up all his luck he has left this year.)
- You should hold on to this. - No, no.
They'll take this away from me.
- I'll protect you. - Okay.
Hold on. You're not going to switch our partners, right?
No, we won't.
- I doubt it. - I mean...
- That wouldn't happen. - I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(They chose a destination of the crew and multiplication card.)
(Current ranking on each couple's mission fee)
(Haha and Z Young chose Bow River and Cage of Death.)
Let the race begin.
The targets will be selected.
Two roulettes for male and female members will be spun.
Two members will be chosen as the targets.
(It's time to select the first target.)
(Which 2 members will be selected by the roulettes?)
(The male member the roulette has picked is...)
(Se Chan.)
(The female member the roulette has picked is...)
(Sol Bi.)
(The targets have been selected.)
The male target is Yang Se Chan.
(The first male target is Se Chan.)
- I should be on the run then. - Let the race begin.
The female target is Sol Bi.
- Let the race begin. - What do I do?
The male target is Yang Se Chan. The female target is Sol Bi.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(The race to remove the targets' name tags has started.)
Let's hurry.
We should just catch one. I saw one of them over there.
(I'll just catch one of the two targets.)
- Let the race begin. - Why does it have to be you?
Let's find the button.
(Their goal is to reset the targets.)
Come on. Go! Run.
What do we do?
(The couples with targeted member must find the reset button quickly.)
- There are stairs, right? - Yes.
- They're coming. - Oh, no.
Find it.
We must get that button.
Where would the button be?
Don't you think it would be downstairs? Hey!
Run!
(Hunters are spotted ahead.)
(Run, Sol Bi. Run!)
You shouldn't run slowly.
- Hurry! - What do we do?
- Hey, Sol Bi. Run! - They're so fast.
(If they remove Sol Bi's name tag, they'll receive 30 dollars.)
Go to the right. You're too slow. We have no choice.
Why are you so slow?
(This wanted member takes shelter in the elevator.)
(Kwang Soo finds the target, Sol Bi.)
- Go down, Sol Bi. - No, no!
- No, get away from me. - Sol Bi!
- Sol Bi! - No, don't do it.
- Come. Take the stairs. - No, I can't.
- Sol Bi, come out of there. - I can't.
- I'm sorry. - This won't work.
- Run away from us. - Help me. Hurry.
It's just that we don't have money.
- No. - Wait.
(The door just closed?)
- I'm sorry. - The cameraman didn't get in.
The cameraman didn't get in the elevator.
(The cameraman is feeling lost.)
I don't have nothing to film.
They stopped at the eighth floor.
(The cameraman rushes down to the 8th floor.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Seok and Sun Mi are looking for Se Chan.)
Where is he?
Hey.
(They find Sol Bi who was fighting her battle without a camera.)
No, Sol Bi!
- Go find Se Chan. - Go after Se Chan, not me.
- Get the name tag! - Why are all of you after me?
(Se Chan is looking for the reset button.)
Let's find the button.
(Se Chan is a target like Sol Bi, but isn't sharing the same trouble.)
(I can't believe he's a target.)
I guess there's no button on the seventh floor.
"How Is This Possible"?
(Oh, my. Se Chan is the target. How is this possible?)
(She looks excited with everything going on.)
(How on earth can this happen?)
- Let go of her! - Gosh, she's so strong!
- Z Young got it. - She got the name tag!
(In the end, Z Young removes her name tag.)
(Z Young is truly the best fighter.)
You're awesome.
Who got the name tag?
(Sol Bi is eliminated, and Haha and Z Young stay in the lead.)
I have to go find Se Chan now.
Sun Mi, we don't have time to rest. We have to find Se Chan.
(They earn a chance to switch the ball as well.)
- You're unbelievable. - Seriously.
Is there a ball you want to switch with?
The ball you have...
(Haha and Z Young have red balls. Seok Jin and Sol Bi have blue ones.)
- The ball you have... Let's switch. - Switch the ball.
Let's switch.
- Come on. Give some thought to it. - No, ours isn't that bad either.
- Ours isn't that good. - Okay, fine.
- Are we changing them now? - Our isn't much either.
The roulette will be spun to select a new target.
(The roulette for female members is spinning again.)
We have to find the button first. I'm serious.
We should run first, Jong Kook.
(Who will be the next female target?)
(The new target is Elijah.)
The new target is Elijah.
It's you?
(So both of us are the targets?)
- Hold on. - We are both the targets.
Why are you doing this to us?
(Everyone is targeting Se Chan and Elijah.)
- If we catch both, it'll be great. - Exactly.
Let's look for them as we make our way down.
(Hey, 60 dollars. Where are you hiding?)
- They must be scared. - They'd better.
- We should catch them together. - Okay. I'm in.
Sol Bi and I can take down Elijah easily.
- She's an easy target. - She's done.
(It's a chance to earn a lot of money. Everyone starts hunting.)
(Cautious)
- On which floor were we? - We were on the third floor.
- Really? - We moved up two floors now.
- Let's go to the sixth floor. - Gosh, this is so tiring.
- Sixth floor. - The stairs...
(The door flings open.)
I found them!
They're right here!
(The wanted couple is spotted.)
(Screaming)
- We got her. - No!
- Stop! - Seok Jin, get her name tag.
(I'm sorry. I must save myself.)
You're hurting me.
(Taking off)
I'm sorry.
(They removed Elijah's name tag!)
(She's a mess.)
I'm such a coward.
I must reset this.
(Elijah is eliminated, and Seok Jin and Sol Bi gain 30 dollars.)
- My ball? - Yes.
We have to change my ball.
(The winner's dilemma is whether to change the ball or not.)
If that's the case, we won't switch.
(My ball is a good one.)
(They are 2nd in the race now.)
The roulette will be spun to select a new target.
(Who will be the next female target?)
The new target is Z Young.
(Z Young is the new target.)
- What? - It's me.
- Let the race begin. - Z Young, let's go there.
Hide right there.
- I'll be on the eighth floor. - Okay.
- I'll find the button. Stay here. - Okay.
- Can you find the button? - Yes, I can.
(Z Young, wait for me. I'll find you the reset button.)
(Haha, come back quickly.)
Hello, have you seen a button here?
- Sorry? - Have you seen a button?
(The male target, Se Chan, is looking for the reset button.)
Excuse me.
- I am sorry. - Elijah.
- I am sorry. - It's okay. Survival is the key.
I am sorry. I am so sorry.
- I couldn't stay behind. - I understand.
You did a good job.
I stayed behind on purpose...
- to give you time. - Thank you so much.
- This place is too big. - I know.
(Where are the targets?)
It's Se Chan.
- I will give you an entrance card. - Come this way.
Come this way. Hurry up.
(I refuse to lose him.)
You should go first.
(She is a bodyguard.)
(And I...)
(will always...)
(save you.)
No.
(How dare a grasshopper chase after Se Chan?)
(This is the power of love.)
No.
(She is pushed aside.)
(I must save Se Chan.)
(Pushed aside)
No.
(They move on as if she doesn't exist.)
No. No.
(The power of love lasted 0.01 seconds.)
(He doesn't know that Elijah couldn't help him.)
(He hides one floor above.)
(Can Jae Seok find Se Chan, the male target?)
- Jae Seok. - Come here.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
(Ripping)
(Se Chan is out.)
He is here. My goodness, what is going on?
It's over.
- Se Chan. - I should have come here sooner.
(Sae Ho is one step behind.)
Where were you?
- Where were you? - Did you get his name tag?
Sae Ho. Hurry up, and come.
My goodness.
Did you get your name tag ripped off?
(Jae Seok and Sun Mi rank 3rd.)
My goodness.
I should exchange my ball with Se Chan's.
Why do bad things always happen to us?
(They need to divide the mission money by 2.)
It is decided that you won't exchange the balls.
It is decided.
You lost your chance to exchange it.
(You must exchange the ball at the spot.)
(The other target, Z Young, is hiding at the stairs.)
It will be a disaster if you leave this place.
They will want to rip the name tag off of the remaining target.
(Don't worry, I can find the reset button.)
You are the remaining target. You are in danger.
The new target is Haha.
(They're both wanted now.)
Currently, the male target is Haha,
and the female target is Baek Z Young.
(Are both of us the targets?)
- This is unbelievable. - What should we do?
We must find the reset button.
(The reset button is the key to their survival.)
I heard the sound of an emergency exit earlier.
Shall we go and see?
I hope we run into them here.
- Right? - Come on out.
(Jong Kook and Kei start the hunt in earnest.)
(We must not make a sound.)
Didn't you hear a sound?
(Sung Hoon is above,)
(and Jong Kook is below.)
(We must find the reset button.)
Wait a minute.
(They find the reset button.)
(It's the button that changes the targets.)
(From now on, it's a matter of time.)
(What comes first? Catching the targets...)
(or pressing the button?)
- Should I press it? - Press it.
(She presses the button.)
(Clicking)
Team Haha pressed the reset button...
- and spun the roulette. - We are lucky.
We are lucky.
(Are the targets reset?)
We should go up again if the targets are upstairs.
(It seems like we missed them.)
This won't do.
(It's 15 minutes before the end of the race.)
The roulettes are spinning.
The new targets will be selected.
(The new targets are being selected thanks to Haha and Z Young.)
Who are the new targets?
(Who will be the chosen ones?)
Who are they?
(New female target)
The new female target...
is Kei.
(The new female target is Kei.)
(What should we do, Jong Kook?)
- My goodness. - I see people over there.
- Where? - Am I wrong?
Come here. People won't come this way.
It will be hard to remove Kei's name tag...
- because of Jong Kook. - She has Jong Kook by her side.
It will be impossible to remove it.
Seung Un, it will be hard to win today.
Let's give up.
The new male target...
is...
Yu Jae Seok.
(The new male target is Yu Jae Seok.)
(This is insane.)
For goodness' sake.
This is insane.
I need to go to the ninth floor.
(Why does he want to go to the 9th floor?)
(10 minutes ago, the rooftop garden on the 9th floor)
This is incredible.
(They found the reset button.)
If we become the targets, we need to come press this.
- Okay. I'll stay here. - Good.
(They called dibs on the button.)
Please, please, please. Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
This is a good place.
- Shall I hide? - Sit here.
- Can I turn on the light? - Wait here.
- Okay? - By myself?
- Remain hidden. - Okay.
I will go and find the reset button. Wait here, okay?
Can I close the door?
I will close the door.
(She gets separated from her big brother.)
I am scared. I hope no one comes here.
It looks like there would be a reset button here.
(While Jong Kook is looking for a reset button,)
(Jae Seok enters the 9th floor.)
(Is Jong Kook coming?)
(Peeking)
I don't see them.
(She gets caught.)
What should I do?
What should I do? I should lock the door.
(Peeking)
(Kei, are you there?)
(Holding her breath)
No one is here.
(Look inside.)
(She is found.)
(Kei fails to remain hidden.)
Good job. Good job.
Save me.
(Save me, Jong Kook.)
Where could it be?
(Jong Kook is looking for a reset button.)
(Jae Seok is the only one who can save Kei.)
Kei, Kei.
This is great.
All right.
I am sorry. I am sorry.
This is great.
- I am sorry. - Sung Hoon.
You are cool.
- Kei, thank you. - How did you find her?
(Help me, reset button.)
Jae Seok pressed...
the reset button...
and spun the roulettes.
Where was the reset button?
The new targets could be among us.
Grab them.
(Grab the name tag.)
- You can't do that. - Kwang Soo.
Grab her name tag.
Stand up.
(Seung Un, don't lie down on the floor.)
Watch where you touch.
- What? - Wait a second.
- Wait a minute. - You went too far.
- All right. - You went too far.
- Seung Un, are you okay? - Excuse me.
- Seung Un. - My goodness.
(I am serious. I only grabbed her name tag.)
You went too far.
- What do you think you are doing? - Don't touch her during a game.
- I was joking. - What do you think you are doing?
Seung Un, watch where you touch.
It will be funny if one of us becomes the new target.
If one of us is the new target, let's give up the name tag.
Shall we rip each other's name tag?
The roulettes are spinning to select the new targets.
(It's time to select the targets.)
(Who are...)
(the new targets?)
(The new female target is Hwang Seung Un.)
The new female target is Hwang Seung Un.
Let's go to a different floor. Let's go down.
Let's go down. I shouldn't be here.
(Seung Un plans to hide.)
(It's okay to leave her by herself, right?)
- There she is. - Where?
There is Seung Un.
(Is Seung Un spotted...)
(already?)
- Seung Un. - That's So Min.
(He is imagining things.)
- That's So Min. - That's So Min.
What's wrong with me today?
How can you confuse Seung Un with So Min?
Hurry up.
- Let's take the elevator. - Is it okay to move as a crowd?
This elevator is too crowded.
Please take the other one.
- I am sorry. - He can take my spot.
Excuse me, keep your hands off of me.
The new male target may be announced while we are here. Be careful.
We shouldn't go up. Should we go down?
(Se Chan and Elijah take the next elevator.)
(At that moment)
The new male target is Yang Se Chan.
(The new male target is Yang Se Chan.)
(Is Se Chan the new target?)
(Se Chan is right before their eyes.)
You little...
They are going down.
- Which floor are we on? - We are on the sixth floor.
(The door closes.)
It must be us. It must be us.
- Oh, my goodness! - We're going down!
(Oh, no! What are we going to do?)
(Everyone, we're leaving before you!)
It was us!
The new target is Se Chan.
- It's Se Chan? - What?
- Se Chan is the target. - It's Se Chan!
(Everyone is panicking.)
- Hurry. - What floor?
He's on the sixth floor.
- Hey, hurry. - Come on. Get in quickly.
- Hurry. - Move faster.
- Just get in. - Get in.
We should've let him take the elevator.
He was here a few seconds ago.
We should've let him.
(Se Chan and Elijah search for the reset button, beating the crisis.)
Why is it already me?
Se Chan, let me go before you.
(Elijah acts as his bodyguard.)
- Hey, this... - We might get locked up here.
Hey, you haven't seen Se Chan?
- No, I haven't. - He went downstairs where you were.
Haha, I'm right here.
Z Young.
(A long journey in search of Se Chan)
What is it?
(Hey!)
(Did she find Se Chan?)
- You're not the target? - No, he's not.
You're not the target?
(So Min cheerfully attacks Haha.)
- It's Se Chan. - Right. This is so confusing.
Goodness.
(She always has new ways of making us laugh.)
- Hey, what about this? - Okay.
Don't open the door yet.
Go to the end of the hall.
Elijah, go to the end of the hall.
- No one is here. - Go to the end of the hall first.
Go first.
If someone's there, pretend you're looking for me.
Hurry.
(Women versus Wild, Guard Se Chan)
(So Min searches for Se Chan with Sung Hoon.)
I saw someone. Come on. Hurry.
(She spots someone.)
(She's getting nervous. Someone is coming here?)
(Save me.)
- They're coming? - Yes.
(Let's change our strategy. Come. Let's hide!)
Where are they?
I saw someone there.
(So Min and Sung Hoon are getting close.)
(They reach the hallway where Elijah was.)
(I definitely saw someone...)
(somewhere around here.)
Sung Hoon.
Someone's here.
(This voice...)
(is So Min's.)
(It's going to be me who catches Se Chan.)
(Only a door is standing...)
(between the destinies of these two.)
(Now...)
Let's find the button.
(Se Chan,)
(are you hiding here?)
(Se Chan is rushing to find the reset button.)
(Did he find something?)
(He finds the reset button...)
(at last!)
(Se Chan, are you here?)
Let's not go there. He's not there. What should we do?
(She ran and ran, but she fails to find Se Chan.)
(Se Chan, we did it!)
(Oh, the days when we were chased and hunted...)
(With one push to this reset button, those days are over.)
(Pushing)
(The reset has been completed after a long chase.)
The new male target is Yu Jae Seok.
The new female target is Hwang Seung Un.
(The roulette selects Jae Seok as the male target.)
(The roulette selects Seung Un as the female target.)
Kwang Soo, I'll be on the 10th floor.
- Hide on the 10th floor. - Okay.
No, no. Are you going to come with me?
She went down a while ago. She went down.
- To where? - To the first floor.
Where? Where is she?
(She locates the target with her good vision.)
She's either on 1st or 2nd floor.
A floor below us? Which one is it?
I think she's a floor below us.
She went down.
(Through the window, Seung Un's back is spotted.)
(I'm going to catch you. It's their chance to turn the table around.)
- Everyone knows we're here. - Goodness, I...
- was going to stay here. - They're coming. Hurry. Get in!
Close the elevator! They're coming. Hurry. Get in!
(Where are you running off to, guys?)
(She lowers her body right away.)
(She presses the button to close the door desperately.)
(Kwang Soo, please stop them.)
(Kwang Soo is blocking the way the best he can.)
(You want to outdo me in strength?)
(The doors are closing. Did she succeed?)
(You thought you could get away from me?)
Close the elevator.
(After dashing at full speed like a tiger,)
(he sticks his foot in to prevent the doors from closing.)
Close it!
(Where are you going?)
- I got her! - Seung Un!
- I'm sorry. - No, don't.
I'm so sorry.
(The race was almost over.)
- Are you okay? - I'm okay.
Kei, I got the name tag.
- Goodness. - I'm glad at least we got one.
I stopped the elevator with my foot.
We scored one at the end of the race.
Please decide if you're going to switch your ball or not.
(All they have left to do is to decide whether to change or not.)
(Kwang Soo and Seung Un tried desperately to keep the ball.)
(It's the chance to double their mission money.)
(Kwang Soo wanted Seung Un to keep it as he was worried.)
(Just like Kwang Soo's request,)
(does she have the ball with the multiplication card?)
(The time has come.)
Hold on. Let me see my balls. I can switch them.
(Shall I switch my ball?)
(Kwang Soo must keep the ball to win the race.)
- I can switch them. - Switch the ball with ours.
(Is this a smoke screen tactic?)
(As she's willing to switch, it's getting more suspicious.)
(Seung Un is asking him to switch the ball in a nonchalant manner.)
(What is at the end of the road for these two teams?)
The race is over.
Everyone, please assemble in the lobby.
This is Half and Half Project Part 2.
I'll announce the winners of Public Enemy Race.
It's either Jong Kook or Haha.
(Jong Kook and Kei have 50 dollars after removing Seung Un's name tag.)
Haha and Z Young...
(What is the current score of Haha and Z Young?)
- I guess he won. - Did we...
You've won the 1st place with 93 dollars.
(Currently, they are ranked 1st.)
(What?)
Haha won again?
Haha won three weeks in a row.
I haven't applied the multiplication card yet.
(Current standing of the mission money)
- Are you serious? - You haven't?
- This is amazing. - We did so well.
- If Haha wins... - We won because we are good.
If Haha wins again, that means he won three weeks in a row.
But if another team has the doubling card, they can change the outcome.
(The game...)
(isn't over yet.)
They can change the outcome.
(The winners of the race will be determined...)
(depending on who has the multiplication card.)
Currently, Haha and Z Young, who are in the lead,
have one last chance to change their ball.
You can change either one or both balls of your pick.
(They can change their balls with a couple of their choice.)
(This is the perfect chance for us.)
- Seriously? - This is unbelievable.
This is incredible.
- Z Young, this is no joke. - He's definitely going to win now.
This is driving me crazy.
If you have the multiplication card, you'll win.
But if we get the division card, that'll ruin us though.
This is driving me crazy.
If you get to double your money, you'll win for sure.
You don't have to change your balls.
But I don't want to do that.
(To win, he must acquire the multiplication card.)
(Which couple is holding the multiplication card?)
(He's caught at a crossroad.)
(An incident flashes by in his head.)
(From the start, Kwang Soo had drawn and kept it.)
(I won't be safe.)
(You should hold onto it. They'll remove my name tag.)
(He gave it to her as he predicted that his name tag would be removed.)
What should I do?
(They were careful in order to keep the card.)
(Let's win. Protecting this card is the only thing left for us.)
Let's go downstairs for now.
(And a man has been...)
(eavesdropping their conversation the whole time.)
(I already know...)
(what your plan is.)
(Is he going to switch the ball with Seung Un who had it all along?)
All right.
(I have made my decision.)
(With whom will he switch the ball?)
I'll choose Jong Kook's.
(I'll choose Jong Kook's.)
(Did he just choose Jong Kook's?)
(What a twist. He didn't choose Seung Un's.)
(He chose Jong Kook's ball?)
Is it possible he didn't check?
(Haha makes an unexpected trade. He switches it with Jong Kook's.)
I guess he really didn't check.
Then the information that leaked during the race...
might have been false.
- That's possible. - It's not over...
- until it's over. - Really?
They were saying how they had multiply by 2" and got it stolen.
- Don't let your guard down. - Can I check?
Then Z Young, please reveal what your ball is.
(Z Young reveals her ball.)
It's a full-course tour in Rome, Italy.
(She has Rome, Italy.)
I want to go there.
This is amazing.
- You should win. - You should.
(If Team Haha wins, they get to go to the beautiful Rome.)
Next, we'll reveal Haha's ball.
(Haha chose an unexpected one. Does he have multiply by 2"?)
(If Haha doesn't have "times by 2" and Team Kwang Soo does,)
(everyone except Kwang Soo has to go on the Insano Water Slide.)
(Multiply by 2" ball will be the deciding factor.)
(What is the future that awaits the Running Man members?)
It was true.
(This is what he was hoping for.)
(Haha found multiply by 2".)
It was true.
(He actually found it.)
(That means Jong Kook had Seung Un's ball.)
(How did Haha find out?)
(5 minutes before the end of race)
(He was watching something before the mission was over.)
(Jong Kook was ripping Seung Un's name tag in the elevator.)
(He was watching everything live.)
(Jong Kook had to switch his ball with Seung Un now.)
(Shall we switch?)
(No, don't take hers.)
(Kwang Soo could only win if he kept the multiply by 2" ball.)
Let's switch our balls.
All of a sudden?
(She had to switch with Jong Kook's ball.)
(Jong Kook's Fly Toledo in Spain...)
(got switched with her multiply by 2" ball.)
Isn't she back yet? Kwang Soo, come here for a second.
(Is this over for us now?)
(Haha saw everything and put the puzzle together.)
So Haha and Z Young win with 186 dollars.
(They win with 186 dollars.)
(It was a dramatic win thanks to Haha's move.)
Haha's been winning for three weeks.
- He's been winning for three weeks. - The married ones win.
- That doesn't make sense. - That's awesome.
- The destination is Rome, Italy. - It's a full tour.
It's worth going.
You can buy a name tag for 30 dollars.
3 times by 6 is 18. They can buy 6.
- You can buy 6 in total. - They can buy 6.
Before that...
(What is it now?)
Since we have guests here today, I said they'll get a huge reward.
- That's right. - I said it's a good one.
- Please bring it in. - It's amazing.
(These are all great items.)
They can buy them.
Z Young gets to choose.
You have 186 dollars,
so you can purchase name tags with the remaining amount.
Can I get two boxes of Korean beef?
Then you can't buy any name tags.
What are the name tags for?
(She doesn't understand.)
Sorry, but can you please wash your face and focus?
Why do we need to buy name tags?
- Just get these two. - Right.
She'll get pregnant with her second child soon.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- You're getting no name tags? - Congratulations.
Congratulations, Z Young.
(Honey, I'm bringing home meat.)
Z Young made her comeback, so please spin the roulette.
- Spin it. - Z Young.
- Thank you. - You can do it.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Today's destination...)
- Seok Jin wanted to go there. - That's right.
(It's a city everybody wants to visit.)
I wanted to go there.
(It's the city of everybody's dreams.)
(It's an opportunity to experience the cultural heritage.)
(Who will get to go to Rome, the historical and romantic city?)
It's stopping.
(Please come to me, Rome.)
- Yang Se... - Jee Seok Jin.
(At this rate, it's either Seok Jin or Jae Seok.)
(It passes Seok Jin.)
Yu Jae... Who is it?
(It goes back.)
Me?
(Will he get picked again?)
It's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok gets picked again.)
(He gets picked every time the roulette gets spun.)
He's so lucky.
Take them all.
You can take everything, you greedy person.
- It looks good. - Se Chan.
Is this Jae Seok's "Let's Go on a Trip"?
- Is this a new show? - Jae Seok is all over the world.
(He's already on two of them.)
(In a moment)
(The roulette war is not over yet.)
(It's the final race of Half and Half Project.)
(There are suspicious rooms and doors to decide the final location.)
(What are these rooms for?)
It's a nice, cool day.
(A few days after the Couple Race)
Why am I here by myself?
What's this?
- Is this today's mission? - Here we go again.
These punks.
"There are doors numbered 1 to 4 at the place you'll be gathering."
"Each door contains a different amount of mission money."
"Number 1 is 30 dollars, number 2 is 50 dollars..."
"Number 3 is 70 dollars, and number 4 is 100 dollars."
"Please choose one exit, and meet by 12pm."
"You'll divide the mission money depending on the number of people."
(The mission money gets divided up by the number of people there.)
It gets divided up.
Please tell us the exit number five minutes before you arrive.
Again, the key point of today's race is the mission money.
Is this the last one?
Is this the last race of Half and Half Project?
If I don't get chosen today, it's all over.
This is the race of death.
Oh, gosh.
Everybody is going for 100 dollars.
(What would the members choose?)
I'm going for 100 dollars. There's no point in discussing.
I won't go for 30 dollars or something.
If you are last place again...
(Please be careful, Jae Seok.)
- Sorry? - You already have enough.
Oh, gosh. Why would you say that?
- Why? - You've been really unlucky.
I'm so unlucky these days. I'm so unlucky.
There are only four options.
(Let's be cautious today.)
Exit 4 won't work.
(It's the exit with 100 dollars.)
It's going to be messy.
Oh, dear. This is a dilemma.
You only live once.
Should I go for it?
- Where are you going? - I'm going towards Exit 2.
Why would you do that?
There were five people last time.
(In June, 5 people gathered at the exit with 100 dollars.)
(So Min only got 20 dollars last time.)
I want to be a new person now.
I'm going to give up on Exit 4.
You never keep your word.
(He doesn't trust her.)
How can I trust her? I just can't.
I'm going to Exit 3 regardless.
(Is Ji Hyo going to Exit 3?)
Don't do that. I'm giving you an advice.
I would say Exit 4 is empty.
No, I'm going to Exit 3.
Let's both go to Exit 4 and take 50 dollars each.
- 50 dollars each. - No, I'm going to Exit 3.
Oh, my. Exit 3, it is.
(He copies Ji Hyo.)
Should I go to Exit 4?
I'm so confused.
(She's having so much fun.)
I'm going to collapse.
He wanted to go to Exit 3.
(Was she playing a psychological game?)
Kwang Soo's going for Exit 1.
Yes, Kwang Soo. Where are you?
I guess you're going for Exit 4.
(You little moth.)
No, petty thief. I guess you're going for Exit 1.
Who's a petty thief?
I don't think there will be any money for you.
(There's no money for you, petty thief.)
How much will I get?
- You'll get around two dollars. - Oh, gosh.
I'm going to change my tactics.
I'll go for Exit 4. I'll go for 100 dollars.
People have a very wrong idea of me.
I'll show them. I'm serious.
I have to be different today.
(He's also trying to transform.)
I won three times in Half and Half Project.
This is incredible.
This is a record. This is me so far.
I want to pretend like I'm a genius today.
My gut and impression...
are very keen, logical, and accurate.
I want people to see that.
The three times winner chooses...
(The keen winner chooses...)
(He's nonchalant.)
Can you put hearts or chicks around my mouth?
(Sorry, we forgot.)
(Haha, the 3 times winner arrives first.)
This is so stressful.
Please watch and see where my predictions take me.
(What are we supposed to watch?)
(He steps into the suspicious mission ground.)
(Wait, what's this?)
(Today's different. It's a strange place.)
(The exits are on all sides of a square.)
(One step will change your destiny. What is this place about?)
(Haha already made up his mind 5 minutes before arriving.)
I'll enter.
(Which exit did he choose after winning 3 times?)
Am I first?
(Haha chooses...)
(Exit 3 with 70 dollars.)
Let's win four times in a row.
(He has a good feeling.)
(He steps into the exit.)
(Why is there a room?)
(This is not the end. The room is closed on all four corners.)
Do I need to escape or something?
(He's flustered.)
(Peeking)
(The door opens.)
This is it.
(Somebody must be here.)
(The next member to arrive...)
(is Se Chan.)
Let's get it.
(It's Se Chan.)
(If he chooses Exit 3,)
(they have to split the 70 dollars.)
(Haha chose a room with a high amount.)
(Se Chan is a rookie and always jumps into the fire pit.)
(Are they going to share a room?)
Is nobody here?
(He enters Exit 1.)
(Let's get 30 dollars.)
(So Min enters next.)
Hello.
I have to look cool when I open this.
(It's the female warrior, So Min.)
Ta-da.
(She wants to avoid the high amounts this time.)
(There were too many Running Man members last time.)
Exit 2.
(Hold on.)
(Hesitating)
Can I change?
(Where does she want to go?)
(Is she going to switch?)
Do I go in?
(She suppresses her instincts...)
(and chooses Exit 2 with 50 dollars.)
There's nobody here.
No one's here.
Not everyone's here, right?
(Please don't come.)
Please don't come.
(Haha, So Min, and Se Chan are in separate rooms.)
(Jae Seok is next, and Exit 4 is still empty.)
(He passes by Exit 3 where Haha is.)
(I've protected my 70 dollars.)
(The only exits remaining...)
(are Se Chan's with 30 dollars and So Min's with 50 dollars.)
(Would he have to split with them?)
(Or would he choose Exit 4 and enjoy the wealth on his own?)
Oh, gosh.
(Jae Seok,)
(welcome.)
(Jae Seok decides to play safe and has to share with So Min.)
Please...
Why are you here?
Oh, gosh.
So Min.
You told me not to come here.
Why are you here?
You should have gone to Exit 4.
(I didn't know you'd be such a coward.)
There's Exit 3 too.
I felt like many people would go there, so I came here.
Why did you do this?
I told everybody I would go...
to Exit 2 today. I'm serious.
I should have gone for 100 dollars then.
(Someone did go for it.)
(Ji Hyo enters Exit 4 by herself.)
Please don't come.
(What a relief.)
(The rooms are full now.)
Gosh.
(Any exit now will be occupied.)
Exit 4.
(Seok Jin is next.)
(He had a dilemma between 3 and 4. What did he choose?)
(He chooses number 4, and there's somebody inside.)
Why are you here?
(She's mad, but it's funny.)
- You said you wouldn't come here. - You said you'd go to Exit 3.
(He was attracted by the higher amount.)
- This is a success. - How?
You said you'd go to Exit 3.
You said you'd come, so I didn't go. I changed my mind.
I changed at the end too.
- It's the same. - Me too.
(They both enter the same room due to their mistrust.)
This is pretty good.
(It's good if we each get 50 dollars.)
(Hold on.)
(We have another roommate.)
(Jong Kook enters the rather peaceful 100-dollars room.)
What is it?
I was certain. You weren't like this before.
- What's wrong with you? - This is the last one.
What? I was certain.
They'll all come here.
- Will they all come here? - I think so.
(At this rate, they'll each get 33 dollars.)
(This is the current status.)
I was shocked she came here.
This is the last one.
(If Haha and Se Chan's rooms don't get any more people...)
I'm here by myself.
(They get to keep the money.)
(Kwang Soo enters last.)
(He was called a petty thief all morning.)
(Kwang Soo got called all kinds of names.)
(He was determined not to be petty and be bold.)
(Walking)
(Did he end up choosing the room with 100 dollars?)
(Please don't come to my room.)
(Which roommate will he get?)
I'm the only one.
(He chooses the room with 30 dollars.)
(You coward)
What's wrong with you?
- Why are you here? - What about you?
Why do you keep getting in my way?
You are getting in mine.
You said you wouldn't come here.
I told you I'd come here.
What is wrong with you?
- Come on. - You're unbelievable.
It's just 2, so isn't that okay? It's 2 out of 8 people.
This is the 30-dollar room.
We get 15 dollars each.
I got unlucky.
I'm the one that became unlucky.
(We're both unlucky.)
Everybody has entered.
In Exit 4 with 100 dollars are Seok Jin,
Jong Kook, and Ji Hyo.
You each get 33 dollars.
This is not bad.
(In Exit 4, they each get 33 dollars.)
I think many people went to Exit 3.
In Exit 3,
there's only Haha.
He gets 70 dollars.
(In Exit 3, Haha takes 70 dollars.)
People who chose 50 dollars...
are Jae Seok and So Min, so you get 25 dollars each.
People who chose Exit 1...
are Kwang Soo and Se Chan. You take 15 dollars each.
(Giggling)
- I'm so embarrassed. - Really? Kwang Soo.
- Se Chan. - Is she there?
I'm so embarrassed.
I knew it.
Kwang Soo.
(They are cowards.)
- I'm so envious of Haha. - Right?
What's going on with me?
Half and Half Project is perfect for me.
Here's the second mission where you can win...
more mission money.
(What? There are more missions?)
It's a game called...
Open Sesame. Let's get started.
(It's the second mission.)
(Open Sesame)
Underneath the table, there's a card with images and words on it.
If you get the password right, the door will open.
In the middle of the table, there's a suitcase with 50 dollars.
The 50 dollars goes to the person...
who escapes the room first and takes the suitcase.
(They must escape and take the suitcase to win 50 dollars.)
In the middle of the room?
- It's in the middle? - Let's escape.
(Let's escape and take the suitcase.)
Race starts now.
(Open Sesame starts.)
- What table? - Underneath the table?
Where? Is something there?
- No. - A card with words?
(Ji Hyo finds the card.)
- That's right. I've seen it. - This is it.
Haha has to solve it by himself.
- Let's see. - It's here.
(Haha overcomes the loneliness and finds the card.)
"Decipher the following password, and type it on the laptop."
"2 syllables plus 2 syllables. The password is 4 syllables."
Is this a word?
What's this? Russia, rules,
- pizza, and Kwang Soo? - It's Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo? - Giraffe.
What does "2 syllables" mean? The password is 4 syllables.
(Kwang Soo is in the question.)
- Are there hints in this room? - Which country's flag is this?
- What country is this? - Croatia?
No, it's France.
(They saw Russian flags everywhere a few months ago.)
It says...
(They have no idea.)
This is what it says.
I know. Where's a pen? Don't you carry a pen?
- Why would I? - You're frustrating.
(He's being unfair.)
What could it be?
Look, there's a pattern.
What is it?
What's the opposite word for paradise?
(When rearranged,)
(it reads "What's the opposite word for paradise?")
That's correct.
- Jong Kook. - It's "underworld".
(The answer is underworld.)
It's "underworld".
That's right.
Underworld is the opposite word for paradise.
- If it's underworld... - What kind of underworld?
What's the opposite word for paradise? Which underworld?
What are the syllables?
"What's the opposite word..."
"For."
Wait.
Don't break it.
Let me do it.
(He tears the card.)
What's wrong?
(He starts to tear the card for some reason.)
(Let's look for hints.)
(While Se Chan is occupied,)
(Kwang Soo throws it away.)
Did you find something? What did you do with the rest?
(He feels something flying by.)
Where's the rest?
- Let's solve this. - What?
(He throws away the other part.)
Did you throw it again?
It's too late. Let's solve this.
That's not important.
(Forget about it.)
I'll throw it away too.
- Then it's over for us. - That's right.
Tell me what it is.
You found out the answer.
(Tell me the answer.)
What's the opposite word for ramyeon?
(What's the opposite word for ramyeon?)
What are you talking about? That's not the right spelling.
Tell me what it was.
What's the opposite word for genius?
What's the opposite word for innate?
Stop lying. It can't be "innate".
You must have seen all the syllabuses...
for you to say that.
Tell me what it said.
Tell me clearly.
- It said "the above". - What?
"The above".
What's the opposite word for the above?
- Are you sure? - Yes.
It said "the world".
(He keeps giving wrong words.)
(He's desperate for hints.)
(Everyone else except Haha answered correctly.)
(He must solve the picture to complete the password.)
Is it underworld of ants?
(Is it underworld of ants?)
What does it mean by "rules"?
(Is it underworld of rules?)
- "Talking underworld"? - "Talking underworld"?
What else is there?
(So Min's nickname is...)
Didn't I call you that?
Type in "talking underworld".
- I did. - It's wrong.
It's not talking underworld.
(It's a wrong answer.)
There are four rules.
- It's roulette. - There are four rules.
It makes a roulette.
Roulette, rules, and Russia.
What can it be?
(What does it mean by four rules?)
Kwang Soo is unluckiest with roulettes.
(Are four rules related to Kwang Soo?)
Goodness.
What does Russia have to do with rules?
It's Russian roulette.
(It must be the answer.)
(The one word that everything indicates is roulette.)
Type in "roulette".
(Russian roulette, four rules, roulette-shaped pizza, Kwang Soo)
(All of them are related to roulette. Is it the right answer?)
It's correct.
("Roulette underworld" is the correct answer.)
(Now So Min and Jae Seok must run for the money bag.)
We got it.
- So Min. - Wait.
(The first to grab the bag wins 50 dollars.)
- Wait. - Hey.
- What's going on? - Open the door.
(Did they get the correct answer?)
Someone unlocked the door.
How did they do it?
(He has no idea.)
(Russian flag, Russian roulette)
(Four rules, roulette)
(Pizza is roulette-shaped.)
(Kwang Soo is unlucky with roulettes.)
(Roulette)
(Roulette underworld)
- Hey, stop. - Wait.
(They struggle for the bag.)
Stop it.
(She misses it.)
(Jae Seok touches the bag.)
- Wait a minute. - Jae Seok wins the money bag.
- How could you? - Who?
- Is it me? - Goodness.
Door number two is open.
So Min.
(I'm sorry, So Min.)
(Jae Seok wins 50 dollars of mission money.)
Was it roulette underworld?
- Roulette underworld. - That was the answer.
It seemed like soccer with World Cup in Russia.
(Other members enter the mysterious room.)
We guessed underworld of flies instead.
- I guessed... - I didn't think of roulette.
it was talking underworld.
(The door closes.)
(Doors start to close.)
(They're being firmly locked.)
(What is going on here?)
Now,
we'll start the final race.
You're currently imprisoned in Roulette Underworld.
(You're currently imprisoned in Roulette Underworld.)
(This room is Roulette Underworld.)
There's a roulette on every wall.
(Roulettes are on all four walls.)
The roulettes will determine all of your decisions.
- I see. - Okay.
You're currently imprisoned in Roulette Underworld.
You can't escape before clearing the mission.
- So Min. - What's going on?
What's going on?
- Why are the lights out? - This is scary.
(What kind of place is it?)
(Roulette Prison)
(Welcome to Roulette Underworld.)
(Someone is hidden in the darkness.)
(Pursue the one who created Roulette Underworld.)
(Unless you escape, you'll be punished.)
(And)
(Will it be paradise or torture?)
(Determine the destination and members)
(Who will go where?)
(People's Recommendation Project: A Place for 1 Percent)
(Wooden cable car in Indonesia)
(So Min and Kwang Soo are selected to be penalized.)
(They go to Indonesia, the land of promise.)
(They stand in front of a frightening cable car.)
(It's extremely dangerous.)
(It's impossible to predict.)
(They go on a dangerous cable car ride.)
(What will happen to them?)
(Dreadful Final Race)