It's Running Man's new year project.
It's Member's Week.
The second member to participate in the project is Kim Jong Kook.
(Kim Jong Kook)
(Did you decide what your episode will be about?)
(I will leave it in the hands of the crew.)
(Everyone wants only one thing from Jong Kook.)
(This year will be the right time for him.)
(He even talks about finding his love.)
(Why don't you get married through Running Man?)
(Marriage?)
- You look so red. - Let's help him out today.
(This is why we have prepared this episode.)
(This week's special is Marrying Jong Kook Off.)
If you wait there, I will be there shortly.
(At least for today, he's not the Jong Kook we know.)
(Jong Kook, who only cares about love, is at the best age to marry.)
(Will our Jong Kook be able to meet his bride?)
(Although it is freezing, hearts feel warm.)
It is 2017's Running Man's new year project.
The second member of the Member's Week...
is Kim Jong Kook.
Jong Kook left the theme of this week's episode...
in our hands.
That's why we have prepared the second episode of the Member's Week.
(What is it?)
We came up with this as we wished he would meet his love this year.
It's a project for his first blind date.
It's Marrying Jong Kook Off.
- That's right. It's about time. - But this is...
- He really has to get married now. - I seriously agree.
- He wants to date this year. - Right.
- Of course. - I hope...
the blind date goes well and he won't be as angry as he is now.
It's caused by hysterics of being an old bachelor.
- It's true. - I say this because he isn't here.
We talk about this a lot.
We must do something about his temper.
- It'll be good for everyone. - Seriously.
He must find a good woman.
- Everyone will be happy. - That's right.
How possible will it be?
Look at him dressed up.
He's very dressed up.
(What is he wearing for his blind date?)
(Good morning, everyone.)
(Jong Kook looks very fancy today.)
- He dyed his hair. - You're wearing a coat.
Why did you put red lipstick on?
- No, I didn't. - He's blushing.
(Jong Kook likes to dress up.)
- You look great. - You're so determined today.
Why didn't you dress up like this for my wedding?
He wore gym clothes all the time.
(He didn't look as fancy at the award ceremonies.)
Dressing up is the least he can do.
- That's what I'd do. - I think he looks great.
- It's perfect. It isn't too much. - Do I look okay?
- It's just right. - I'm not overdressed, right?
- You should be on a date already. - This is hilarious.
He's going on a blind date with this on his back.
(He wears a name tag on his blind date.)
Why did you put it on?
- You're going on a blind date. - Why does he have a name tag?
We're wearing the same color.
- You're not overdressed. - The tear on his pants makes him...
look like a bad boy.
(The tear gives him a bad boy look.)
Your coat is covered with dust.
I'm okay.
- You need it. - I'm fine.
- Do it on this side, too. - You need to get rid of dust...
on your coat.
(Kwang Soo is worried about his knees.)
- What are you doing? Stop it. - Cover up your knees.
- I can cover them up. - Why would you?
(Your knees will get cold.)
It's too cold.
Jong Kook's blind date will be aired for the first time.
For his date to be successful,
we need help from all the members.
We prepared two types of dates of opposite qualities.
(There are two types of date.)
Depending on whether the members clear the mission,
what Jong Kook does on his date will change.
We must clear the mission for Jong Kook's date...
to enjoy a great time.
Do well today as if your life depends on it.
Jong Kook is very serious today.
- Please do your best today. - Okay.
Don't worry. I'm good at matchmaking.
- Don't do it. - Please don't.
- Don't do it. - We'll definitely succeed today.
I know everything about dating.
He tricked me several times.
(Jae Seok is speaking nonsense.)
(Everyone, please stop.)
- Don't worry about a thing. - I can be your wedding planner.
Jae Seok and Haha, please focus on clearing the missions.
Don't be so tactless.
- He's lucky to meet us today. - You're being so tactless.
- You don't have to do a thing. - Don't do anything!
Okay.
The blind date is coming up soon.
- Here's your first mission. - What is it?
It'll determine the mode of transportation to pick up...
- his date. - This is important.
Since it's the first mission, it'll depend on Jong Kook's performance.
(It depends on Jong Kook's performance.)
Within 60 seconds, pull the van with 5 members in it...
up to the flag in front of the vehicle of your choice.
- I have to pull the van? - He needs to pull the van?
(Must he pull the van?)
- He's not an ox. - He has a blind date coming up.
For today,
I'm going to stay calm.
- I won't get angry. - You aren't getting angry.
I decided to stay calm today.
I was surprised that you didn't get angry.
(He slaps him.)
You should always stay calm like this.
(He tries to tolerate everything.)
This is what you need.
The first mode of transportation at 5m is...
a scooter.
(It's a scooter.)
- It's too cold to ride a scooter. - It's too cold.
There's a van at 10m.
To make the first meeting less awkward,
you'll ride the van with five other members.
- This is it. - What did you say?
- You'll succeed with this. - This is it.
- This is the answer. - You could even get married today.
- Of course. - I have to ride with them?
If you move the van 15m, you can use a car.
While having a conversation in private,
you can move to the next destination.
(He wants the car.)
(The first impression of Jong Kook depends on the result.)
(Five members get in the van.)
It won't be easy to pull this van.
It won't be easy at all.
(He's been attending weddings for 20 years.)
(He wants his own wedding this time.)
The time limit is one minute.
- Let's go. - You can do it, Jong Kook.
You can do it, Jong Kook.
- You can do it. - You can do it.
Get ready.
- Start. - You can do it.
Let's get married, Jong Kook.
Imagine that there's a cliff behind you.
(Which mode of transportation will he get?)
(The mission starts.)
(He pulls with all his might.)
(Everyone is desperate.)
Let's get married, Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is good at everything except love.)
(What's going on?)
- This is difficult. - It isn't easy.
It's not easy.
(10 seconds passed.)
(The van hasn't even budged.)
(He must move the van.)
It's not working.
It's impossible to pull this alone.
(The van moves slightly.)
- You're doing well. - We're moving.
(Wait for me, my future love.)
(Jong Kook will get married.)
- We're moving. - He's amazing.
(He starts to pick up speed.)
It's working.
He's amazing.
I can't believe we played Name Tag Elimination with him.
I've tried it before, but it isn't easy.
When he's close to the van, step on the brakes.
Jong Kook needs us.
(The van moves easily.)
Let's ride with him.
(Will he win the car?)
- We need to stop him. - This is amazing.
- We need to stop him. - Why?
(He struggles.)
Why?
Why isn't it moving suddenly?
(The van was definitely moving.)
(You need us, Jong Kook.)
- Let's ride with him. - Can I step on the brakes?
Don't step on the brakes.
(Kwang Soo removes his foot a little late.)
(Only 13 seconds remain.)
Let's ride with him.
- Keep going, Jong Kook. - 10, 9.
Hey.
(He only has 10 seconds.)
(Two married men meddled in Jong Kook's business.)
(He laughed in disbelief.)
(Kwang Soo falls in love too easily.)
(It's the worst combination possible.)
(Riding the van with them will ruin his date.)
(He can't give up now.)
- 10, 9. - Hey.
(His love depends on the last 8 seconds.)
In 7, 6.
(It's a ride with five members...)
(versus a car only with his date.)
- This is incredible. - Three.
(He doesn't want to ruin his date.)
One.
Three.
(What's the result of the first mission?)
Hey.
(We'll help you with your date.)
Two.
One.
Jong Kook's mode of transportation...
is...
the van with five other members.
(They're excited to meet his date.)
How did he pull this van?
(He's disappointed.)
Don't feel pressured. Pretend like we aren't here.
- We're invisible. - We'll stay quiet.
It turned out well. We'll help him out.
- Okay. - It gives us something to do.
Here's the name and the number of your blind date.
(He gets happy again.)
I'm about to lose my mind with excitement.
My heart is fluttering.
(Where is his love?)
(At that time in Dosan Park)
(She's waiting for Jong Kook with full excitement.)
(Will they become a couple?)
(Jong Kook goes to pick her up.)
I feel excited about Jong Kook's blind date.
How long has it been since your last blind date?
- On TV? - Isn't it your first time on TV?
I've never been on a date on TV.
Some meet on TV shows and get married.
- Right. - Today might be that day.
This is just a blind date.
Did you meet your wife on a blind date?
- Me? - Did you approach her?
- No, he seduced her. - What happened?
Come on, that can't be.
(Jae Seok is good at picking up women.)
(He invited her wife to eat a bowl of soup.)
- You're right, Jong Kook. - Right?
No, you didn't.
- It sounds funny. - It may seem strange for Jae Seok.
However, it's true.
- Jong Kook, if I like your date, - Tell me.
I'll drink some water as soon as she gets in the van.
- You will? - Who cares what you think?
I think you're misunderstanding something.
This isn't your blind date.
Why would you do that?
(Seok Jin keeps thinking he's the main member today.)
As your big brother, if I like your date...
- You aren't my real brother. - We're still close.
Listen, Jong Kook.
If Seok Jin tries to do something bad,
I'll splash water on him.
- I'm being serious. - I won't do anything bad.
I have my best intentions for Jong Kook.
I'll be on your date's side.
Your future wife might feel excluded.
- I was about to slap you. - Why?
You'll make her feel pressured if you call her that.
- She has to like Jong Kook, too. - Of course.
- How shall I call her? - She has to like me, too.
I just hope Kwang Soo doesn't fall in love with her.
Come on, what are you talking about?
- He'd better not fall in love. - No way.
Don't fall in love with her.
You'd better not fall in love easily.
Even my mom says that about me.
She likes that nickname.
- She knows the truth. - "Come and eat, Kwang Soo."
"Wake up, Kwang Soo, who easily falls in love."
(She must be proud of her son.)
We're here.
Shouldn't you call her?
- Should I? - Tell her that you're on your way.
It's better to call before.
- Send her a short message. - We're almost there.
- Should I call her? - Tell her you're on your way.
(He presses her number first.)
- You must call her. - You should call her first.
Just call her once.
- I want to hear her voice. - Call her first.
Be quiet.
(Everyone, be quiet!)
You have to wait in front.
Are you calling her?
What song is that?
- Jong Kook. - It's Han Dong Geun.
- Hello? - She has a lovely voice.
- It's Han Dong Geun. - She has a lovely voice.
Hello, I'm Kim Jong Kook. Is this So Young?
Yes, hello.
She sounds young.
Isn't it cold? Are you outdoors?
Yes.
- We're almost there. - I'll be there soon.
- I wonder what she looks like. - We're here already.
I'm so curious.
- This is so... - You need to smile.
- Careful. - Watch out.
- Where is she? - In the park somewhere.
Her voice is so pretty.
She sounded so young.
- Jong Kook. - She's too young.
We're here. Go and get her.
- Where is she? - The park's that way.
- She sounds so young. - I'll be right back.
See you.
- Shall I go with you? - I'll leave this here.
Why would you come along?
That really hurt.
- Why? - Good luck.
Good luck.
- Get going. - Jae Seok.
Bring her over.
(He's very nervous.)
My goodness.
Why am I dressed like this?
(It's their first date and everything's bothering him.)
(He looks around while taking nervous strides.)
- He's on the move. - He's walking splay-footed.
- That's his gait. - A mobster walk.
Where is she?
(Intense nerves)
I should call and ask where she is.
(He's sorry to make her wait.)
(The lady he's searching for is very nearby.)
(Hey.)
(Grinning)
Hang on.
Is it the lady in the burgundy coat?
(A lady is wearing the same colored coat he is. Could it be her?)
It's her.
(She answers her phone.)
- Hello? - Hi.
Hi.
I'm... I'll be right there.
- Okay, see you. - I'll see you soon.
(He's 10 seconds away and on his way to meet her.)
What should I do? Our coats are the same color.
(Are they meant to be?)
(The unintended fact is making his heart pound.)
How... Is this possible?
(This is the blind date everyone wished for.)
(Let's meet the special guest who made all this possible.)
(This is who today's show is all about.)
(Jeong So Young, 29, accountant)
This is crazy.
(He feels so nervous.)
(As he walks up to her, she turns and they make eye contact.)
(Smiling)
Hello.
(Such awkwardness)
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- Our coats are the same color. - I know, I was so surprised.
- Hello. - I'm pleased to meet you.
(I'm Kim Jong Kook.)
- Same colors? - They dressed like a couple.
- She's in burgundy, too. - She is.
- Do you feel cold? - A bit.
- I'm so sorry. - The weather's nice, though.
(The main couple of today's episode finally meet.)
Did you get here early?
- No, not that early. - Not that early.
(We've never seen Jong Kook this shy before.)
- Sorry to have made you wait. - It's fine.
The previous shoot got delayed.
(Jong Kook talks to help her relax in front of the camera.)
The others are waiting in the car.
- Are they really? - Yes.
- They must tag along. - Really?
(She's never met a guy who brought five friends.)
They're coming.
Reverse a bit.
Should I open the door?
He'll open it for her.
Don't do anything.
- Shall I help? - Sit still.
Let Jong Kook take care of it.
Let him deal with it.
- I'm embarrassed to death. - Me, too.
The color of our coats...
Mine even has a name tag.
It might be a bit too much for you.
(Get married, Jong Kook!)
Is this too much?
Shall I take it off?
Let's take this off. It's too much.
It's...
Just a moment.
(Now it gets worse.)
- Hello. - Welcome!
- So Young. - Hello, So Young.
Have a seat.
- Sit here. - Welcome.
- I should go inside. - Right.
- Welcome. - Hello.
Was the step this high up?
Welcome on board.
Welcome, So Young.
Nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you. - Hello.
I'm so pleased you agreed to meet Jong Kook.
- Thanks so much. - Hello.
It's fate.
The possibility of this happening...
I hope to see you more often.
- Now... - Have you eaten?
You need to eat.
I only had breakfast so far.
You must be so hungry.
We'll set off, then.
(The team head over to the restaurant.)
I think So Young would look great in a hanbok.
- Do you want her to change? - No.
Watch what you say.
- Seok Jin. - You're so silly.
She's a typical Asian beauty.
Did you leave early this morning? Do you live far away?
I live near Sindorim.
- Sindorim? - Sindorim?
It's right next to Yeouido.
You don't have to say things like that.
- I work in Yeouido. - Do you?
Are you in securities or stocks?
I'm an accountant.
- An accountant? - An accountant...
The CPA?
Oh, my gosh.
It's not your blind date.
Why are you so shocked?
Sorry, but I studied Business Management...
and I know how hard that exam is.
It's the economics equivalent of the bar exam.
- I'm impressed. - CPA?
Do you have any siblings?
- Be quiet. - Let Jong Kook ask that later.
You're so rude.
You asked something Jong Kook should during lunch.
- I have an older brother. - I have a younger sister.
- A younger sister? - So do I.
(We have something in common!)
Who cares? Jae Seok, I whacked him on the head.
Well done. I have two younger sisters.
They look like him.
Hey!
It's true. Family members look alike.
I want to know her blood type.
I want to ask her age.
Sorry.
- I apologize. - She has to be within range.
We're against this if you're too young.
- Why are you against it? - What right do you have?
Why are you against it?
We're in no position to be against anything.
- I was born in early 1989. - Early 1989?
- We're 12 years apart. - We are.
We have the same Chinese zodiac.
(It's a perfect match.)
- This is great. - I don't believe this.
How old is your sister?
- She just turned 27. - Did she?
My brother's two years older.
- He's a plastic surgeon near here. - I see.
He's really sweet.
(He had no idea then...)
(that his sweet brother would visit the restaurant.)
(There's no need to say that on a blind date.)
(Facts become vicious weapons.)
(Do you hate him sometimes?)
(Of course, I do.)
(The battle of the brothers is coming right up.)
I have so many questions.
There's so much we want to ask but we're holding back.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
No, right? You saw these people on telly.
"Telly"?
(He came all dressed up and used such an old-fashioned word.)
He said, "telly".
(The old-school singer just showed the limit of his vocabulary.)
"Telly"?
Unbelievable.
- "Telly." - He said, "telly".
(They finally reach the restaurant.)
We're here.
- You can get out. - Move it, Jong Kook.
Get the door for her.
No, wait!
Don't get out.
It's dangerous.
(Jong Kook's so chivalrous.)
Well done.
- Congratulations. - Get out.
Enjoy yourselves.
- Enjoy your meal. - Go on upstairs.
(We reserved a romantic restaurant where they can enjoy a meal.)
(The man and woman head to the room reserved just for them.)
- Welcome. - Hello.
- The room's on your right. - This way?
(Jong Kook opens the door for the lady.)
(They get some privacy at last.)
It's awkward, isn't it?
It's not too bad.
I felt the urge to protect her.
I wanted to look after her and protect her.
He seemed very masculine.
I like that he was so caring.
(The man and woman sit down for a private chat.)
What now?
(His brain formatted.)
- This situation's... - Yes?
- How did you end up doing this? - Pardon?
I've never been on what you'd call an average date.
I became a celebrity at a pretty young age.
- I hope you can understand. - Sure.
Should I open this?
It's a gift for you.
What were they thinking?
Hang on. This is...
It's your name tag. Why...
- On my coat? - Yes.
Let me.
(Let me put your name tag on for you.)
(So chivalrous)
I can't believe I'm doing this.
(We've never seen this side of him before.)
I wish he were just half as kind to us.
Less than half would do.
I wish he was 10 percent as nice to us.
Jong Kook's never put on my name tag for me. He's only ripped it.
And I never knew his voice was that soft.
- He's so kind. - He's whispering.
(He usually explodes.)
(He roared like a lion...)
(and preyed on the members for the past 7 years.)
(The tiger now turned as gentle as a lamb.)
His voice is so low.
He normally doesn't sound like that.
Today, we have a guest joining...
- for the blind date. - Who is it?
- Wasn't it just us? - Somebody's joining us?
- Why are you here? - Hey.
- Hello. - Hello.
- His brother is here. - Why is he here?
- Welcome. - Hello.
- Hello. - Aren't you working today?
- I cancelled an operation. - Really?
- Have a seat. - Thank you.
Jong Kook was just talking about you.
(As an insider, he knows Jong Kook more than anybody.)
(His brother is watching him.)
You must have some expectations for today.
I was actually close by. I got a call...
saying that he's on a blind date.
I came without telling him.
- I didn't even tell him. - That's her.
She's beautiful.
He will definitely like her.
- Exactly. - He's smiling.
I think he likes her.
(But in reality, )
(there's an awkward silence in between them.)
(What am I supposed to say?)
- It's a nice day today. - Right.
(Within one second, it's silent again.)
- Isn't this awkward? I think it is. - A little bit.
Have you been on many blind dates?
I wouldn't say many,
- but more than you did. I suspect. - Is that right?
(He starts the conversation but it stops again.)
How do we order?
(Please, we need food at least.)
Excuse me. Is there anybody here?
(He sounds so inexperienced.)
We'd like to order. Is there anybody here?
(Please save this poor lamb, waiter.)
He's so serious.
He's supposed to act witty.
I think it's important to make her feel comfortable...
- rather than make her laugh. - He doesn't want to joke too much.
- He's taking this very seriously. - For real.
- He's very serious. - I think he's too serious.
- Appetizer is ready. - Thank you.
(The waiter saved him.)
(The appetizer will hopefully make things less awkward.)
Thank you.
- Please eat. - Okay.
- Aren't you feeling uncomfortable? - No, it's okay.
- Jong Kook... - I think he likes her.
- really likes women who eat a lot. - That's right.
That's important.
What kind of food do you like to eat?
I don't think we eat similar kinds of food.
(What is she saying?)
Sorry? Why not?
I like to eat, but I like food that's not good for your health.
I don't smoke, drink or drink coffee,
but I like greasy food such as meat.
(This is his 1st crisis. They have opposite tastes in food.)
This isn't good. She likes food that's not good for you.
She likes greasy food.
I like greasy food.
I like meat.
- Really? - Yes. I like meat.
- Well... - I don't eat a lot of vegetables.
Really? You don't like vegetables?
(He fails to keep a straight face after hearing that.)
- You must eat a lot of meat. - Yes, I eat mostly meat.
I see. You need to eat a lot of vegetables.
- I try to eat a lot. - That's great.
I didn't eat a lot of vegetables when I was younger.
After I started eating vegetables,
my...
(He's a true health expert.)
My bowels are more regular.
It feels cleaner.
The key word of the blind date so far...
- is "health". - That's right.
Jong Kook is a health expert around here.
I don't know what...
- So Young will say about that. - Jong Myung,
- do you think he likes her? - I think he does.
- Right? - He doesn't usually say things...
about himself from when he was younger.
- He brought it up. - He kept on talking about it.
I think he likes her, too.
- What kind of food do you like? - Me?
(Let's see. What food do I like?)
(She's curious.)
(Let's look back on the type of food he ate in the past.)
You can only look at it.
(He doesn't even eat fried chicken.)
- I can't eat fried food. - Why not?
Do you know how much oil there is in jjajangmyeon?
(Stop nagging and just eat.)
(He hates oil but loves protein. What would he say?)
I am actually not...
that picky about food.
- He's lying. - That's a lie.
- That's a lie, right? - I don't think he's right.
He's so picky about food.
He doesn't eat anything that's delicious.
He even washes kimchi before he eats it. What is he saying?
(Jong Kook can only eat washed kimchi.)
He says Jong Kook is totally picky.
He's gotten better than before.
It's most important to find a common area of interest.
Is that right?
Do you usually work out during your time off?
I usually work out or my only hobby...
- is talking to my friends. - I see.
Do you like to travel?
- Sorry? - Travelling?
- I like to travel. - Do you?
- I love to travel. - Is that right?
Yes, I...
travel...
(He starts talking about travelling.)
whenever I have free time.
My destinations are limited though.
I usually go to LA in the States.
- I see. - Because...
You can't eat a lot...
- on the first date, right? - That's right.
That's what this is, right?
Women are like that.
You can't hear the other person when you eat at the same time.
That's why.
I have a lot of friends in LA. The streets are also similar.
For me, I usually travel to take breaks.
I don't...
go around a lot.
I go there, work out, rest,
and eat good food.
That's what I like to do.
- She's eating a lot. - She must be starving.
So Young must be really hungry.
- Exactly. - She's stuffing down a big piece...
- of lettuce. - She doesn't even care anymore.
It's the size of a hand.
I thought she was eating a huge burger.
Jong Kook is talking too much about himself.
- He's not listening to her. - She has to talk, too.
- She does. - He's talking too much.
He loves to talk.
Ask her to speak.
(His audience yells at him for being carried away.)
- What did you just do? - I couldn't hold it.
- They heard you. - That was inside my head.
They heard you. They're chuckling.
Please listen to So Young.
Listen to So Young.
- I think they can hear us. - Really?
The main dish has to come.
- That's right. - Right, Ji Hyo?
- Yes. - They had too much salad.
They'll be eating now.
Jong Kook's menu...
will be decided by you.
- I hope he eats something good. - It's important.
I have a game for you to play.
You can go down...
- and play. - Okay.
(Let's give them steak.)
(What game do they have to play to get steak?)
I think this will open up.
- What is this? - What's this?
(Why is this in the middle of the restaurant?)
What's this?
- What is this? - What's this?
(Why are there paper cups in the restaurant?)
- I hope he eats something good. - It's important.
What's this?
The mission is called, "Escape the Paper Mines".
(The mission is called "Escape the Paper Mines".)
This is the most important part of the meal.
What's this?
Three members will be blindfolded...
and walk across the paper mines in a row.
You can only move on to the next person within five steps.
The goal is to reach the finish line without touching the paper mines.
It's so difficult.
If you succeed,
- you'll get this premium steak. - It looks good.
If you don't,
you'll get this Pikachu tonkatsu, which is every child's favorite.
- Pikachu? - I hope he gets to eat steak.
We have to get steak.
Let's...
help him eat steak.
Kwang Soo, Jae Seok, and Ji Hyo can go.
- That's right. - Open the window.
Open the window, Jong Kook.
- Open the window. - Open the window, Jong Kook.
- Am I supposed to open this? - Jong Kook.
Okay. Hold on.
(He's forced to open the curtains.)
We're going to play a game.
How do you open this?
- This is how it opens. - Really?
- You need to pull. - You have to push.
- I have to push? - Yes.
- There's a string here. - Open it, then.
He usually gets mad but he's not today.
- Jong Kook. - Why are you not getting mad?
- What's wrong with you today? - Why aren't you getting mad?
- Sorry? - Are you in a good mood?
- Why are you not getting mad? - Why would I get mad?
- Why would I get mad? - What's this?
- Jong Kook. - Yes?
Can you be 10 percent as nice as you are today?
- Please. - Really.
- Okay. - This is touching.
- Why? - You're too nice.
- And then... - Seok Jin,
thank you for doing this in the cold weather.
- What? - Did he just thank him?
- What was that? - You can do it.
I'll make sure you have steak with So Young.
- This looks hard. - You can go first, Ji Hyo.
- Should I go first? - You have to pay attention.
- Start on your left foot. - We have to look.
- Let's get going. - So Young is watching.
Okay.
Watch us, So Young.
We're doing this so that you can have steak.
Ready.
Set...
(Don't worry, Jong Kook. I'll let you eat steak.)
Take a big step.
- Take a big step. - Bigger.
- Here? - Bring it down.
- Slow down. - No.
- Don't touch it. - No, that's not.
- That's good. - You're good.
- Put your foot down. - Slide your foot forward.
(He's nervous.)
- Slide your left foot. - Slide a bit more. That's good.
- Excellent. - You're good.
(Thanks to the kind audio guide, she manages to pass through.)
- To your left. - It's on your left.
- It's on your left. - Is it here?
- No, stretch your leg more. - Move it.
- Not there! - No!
- Move it back a little. Lower it. - Move it back.
- To the back. - That's good. Lower it.
- Speak clearly. - Move it back.
(He fails to speak clearly.)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
(They are all making a fuss.)
- You can put it down completely. - There you go.
- Slide your foot. - It's right here.
- Put your foot down. - It's on your right.
(The next spot doesn't have any cups.)
(He hits her leg.)
(She loses balance.)
(She was doing well, but she lost her balance.)
No. Don't do that.
(With one shake, he will end up with tonkatsu.)
Don't!
(She manages to get her balance back. She's an expert.)
(She only has 3 steps left.)
It's right in front of you.
- That's good. - Lower your foot.
- Lower it. - Slide it forward.
- Put your heel down. - Slide it forward.
- Slide it farther. - Push it forward more.
(There's a huge gap between her legs.)
You only have three steps left.
(Now she has to escape the paper mines within 2 steps.)
- It's on your left. - Just stretch your leg forward.
- Stretch it more. - Slide it more.
(The next target spot is closer than the last spot.)
- Lower your foot. - Hold on. Wait.
(She lands her foot by inches.)
- This is it. - She has to jump now.
(She longs for Ji Hyo's success.)
- Jump from where you are now. - Hold on.
- Is it this way? - Yes.
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(If she succeeds, they will get a step closer to having a steak.)
(Jumping)
- In 1, 2, 3. - In 1, 2, 3.
(She manages to escape without touching any cups.)
(If two more members succeed, they can have the delicious steak.)
- You did it. - I really couldn't see anything.
- Thank you. - Jong Kook, I succeeded.
- Nice. - I couldn't see anything.
- I will do it like this. - You can do it in three steps.
(He scans for possible routes.)
Try it. Practice.
- You can jump three times. - One, two,
- three, four. - There you go.
(It's nothing.)
You can do this.
(He smiles brightly.)
- Remember your steps. - Okay.
- I will succeed by any means. - Start with your left foot.
(I can succeed if I follow the route.)
I'm getting nervous.
(I still have 5 paper cups left.)
(So Young likes steaks.)
(Don't you worry. I will get you the steak.)
Start. Don't forget the steps.
(He steps on it.)
Remember the steps.
(There's a feast at the paper mines.)
One, two, three.
(Hey, Kwang Soo.)
- Three. - Remember the steps.
(He keeps stepping on the cups.)
- It's still a success. - I did it?
- It still counts as a success. - He stepped on four cups.
(He's the king of destruction.)
You are indeed the unluckiest member.
(I have a feeling we will eat tonkatsu.)
- Memorize the route, Jae Seok. - Okay. Hold on.
(If he steps on even a single cup, they will have tonkatsu.)
- Start from here. - He'll lose the sense of direction.
- Three members have to succeed? - Let me try it out first. Hold on.
- That's good. - One, two, three, four.
- He did it. - Just do what you just did.
Jae Seok, you can do it, right?
I can do it. Don't worry.
I will make sure you two eat the steak.
(If he steps on a cup, they will have to say goodbye to the steak.)
Here I go.
(Jae Seok tries it.)
- Start. - Start.
(Hold on. Wait. No way!)
(He strides.)
One.
(I will let you have the steak.)
Three, four.
(Jae Seok succeeds at once at an incredible speed.)
(The mission is accomplished.)
This is unbelievable.
(Thank you, everyone.)
I can't believe this.
(He's like a mine detector. What a surprise.)
- This is incredible. - He did it.
(A wish to marry off Jong Kook has made a miracle.)
- How did he do this? - Jong Kook.
Isn't this wonderful?
(I told you I'd get you the steak.)
My goodness.
(I'm so touched, Jae Seok.)
You'll have the steak.
(Enjoy your steak.)
- I'm so glad it worked out. - Jae Seok, you were awesome.
- It was amazing. - Yes, it was.
(I respect you. You are a walking mine detector.)
How did he manage this?
(Jong Kook and So Young earn the steak.)
She likes eating meat.
- Thank you for the food. - Please enjoy.
(She takes a bite.)
(This is delicious.)
- This is good. - Is it?
Your cheek is bulging out.
(It's cute.)
You had a big bite.
His voice is so low that it might go underground.
Why doesn't he talk to us in that voice?
- I think he likes her. - I agree.
- Don't you think so? - I think so.
His face says so.
If he gets married, I should be the host for his wedding, right?
Haha should sing at the wedding.
- I can sing. - Seok Jin can, too.
- Count me in, Jae Seok. - I used to be a singer.
I also hosted Haha's sister's wedding.
- You did my sister's wedding, too. - Right, I did.
I hosted the wedding for Seok Jin's sister.
He said my father's name for the groom's name.
(He's a breaking up the family tree.)
He said, "The groom, Ji Chang Gyun." It's my father's name.
- I was... - We were so taken aback.
It was only my second wedding that I hosted.
I was a bit nervous.
At that time, I still got the butterflies in my stomach.
I said, "The groom, Ji Chang Gyun."
And his father said, "No. That's my name."
I apologized and I did it again.
I said the wrong name again and his father said it was wrong again.
(Even after his apology, he called out the wrong name.)
So you've been to South America.
How about the States? Have you been to the North America?
- I've been to San Francisco. - I see.
I was on a business trip to Mountain View near Silicon Valley.
(His eyes are gleaming.)
So I've been to San Francisco once.
(Should I have a bite now?)
How about Europe? Which countries have you been to in Europe?
(Please give me some time to chew.)
I'm sorry.
I asked when you just had your bite.
Please take your time.
On a blind date, it's only two of you. So you don't have time to eat.
You are supposed to eat and talk at the same time.
I think your mother would like Europe, too.
- I think she would. - Right.
Why don't you take her there?
I want to, but I don't think it's a place I should go with my mom.
You're right. She can go with your father.
The problem is...
my father doesn't like going on trips.
Your family is similar to mine.
That's why she's always alone...
and I can't bear to see her like that.
A lot of ladies may not like this,
but I go on a lot of trips with my mother.
(I should shut his mouth.)
That's true. He travels a lot with his mom.
- They go on too many trips. - He's the best son.
- But... - He shouldn't say that on a date.
My friend, Tae Hyun, always...
tells me not to say this to a woman.
He always says if I do, I won't be able to get married.
But there is a reason...
behind this.
My mother used to be sick.
She suffered from breast cancer.
When I was young and in high school,
I caused much trouble for her.
I always thought I should be a better son.
I worked as a singer for 1 or 2 years.
I thought I should succeed and make a lot of money...
so that I could do things for my mom and be a good son.
Then out of the blue, I heard the news.
I found out she was diagnosed with breast cancer.
I thought to myself that things don't go as I plan.
I thought time won't wait for me to get ready to take care of her.
I decided that I should take her on a trip starting that day.
So that's when it all started.
That was when I was 23 or 24 years old.
That's when we first started traveling together.
After going on that first trip,
we always go on trips together.
His love for his parents is incredible.
- Especially his love for his mom... - You're right.
They go everywhere together.
However, his girlfriend won't...
- be pleased... - She might not like it.
- if he goes on too many trips. - I can't stop him.
That worries me a bit.
He shouldn't say such a thing on a blind date.
Right.
My father used to work in the army.
(He moves on talking about his father.)
- I see. - That's why he is so righteous.
(He talks flawlessly.)
I used to hate it about him.
(She's been listening to him for 30 minutes.)
I hated it about him, and I acted the same.
(Stop talking and ask her some questions.)
Stop talking about yourself and ask her questions.
They should get to know each other. He's been talking about himself.
She can look it up online. Why is he telling her that?
I had a big breakfast.
(He's not done talking.)
(He may end up publishing his autobiography.)
- Is that so? - I had meat for breakfast.
Stop talking about breakfast.
She doesn't want to know about it.
He should ask her about her ideal type and her preferences.
- He should be asking these things. - Why don't we...
text him and tell him this?
- Why would I text him? - Ask her about her ideal type.
Ask her about her ideal type and her last dating experience.
(Resonating)
(I won't get angry. So Young is sitting in front of me.)
I will go and get Jong Kook.
If he keeps this up, she might fall asleep.
- You're right. - She might have her dinner as well.
(The temperature between them is negative 10°C.)
(Running Man Dating Agency)
(Their target is Kim Jong Kook.)
That's why I eat...
(Jong Kook, look here.)
(We need to talk.)
(However, the target seems uninterested.)
(Coughing)
(He only focuses on the steak.)
- I'm not good at languages. - Really?
(He's frustrated.)
(He tries to communicate with him through a sketchbook.)
(Jong Kook, come to...)
(I hope my heart can reach you.)
(Jong Kook, come to the 2nd floor...)
(Jong Kook, tell her that you are going to the restroom...)
(and come to the 2nd floor.)
(Jong Kook is clearly bad at blind dates.)
(Kwang Soo summons him to the headquarters.)
I wasn't talented in that field.
- It was difficult. - He saw my message.
My brother and I are very different.
(He ignores what he saw.)
I think he's ignoring it.
(Kwang Soo writes again angrily.)
(Why are you ignoring me?)
(He turns the page.)
(If you don't want to ruin your blind date, )
(come to the second floor.)
(He forces Jong Kook to come.)
He saw it.
(It's Kwang Soo's strange sketchbook.)
I'm sorry, but I'll be right back. They're calling me.
Okay.
(Why are they interrupting me?)
- What's wrong? - Let's go upstairs.
What?
What's wrong?
Why did you call me? I'm doing well.
(You're not doing well.)
- Jong Myung. - You keep talking about yourself.
- What brings you here? - Your brother came to help you.
- What's going on? - Come here.
- She's left alone for too long. - I know.
- Tell her he went to the restroom. - Ji Hyo, will you join her?
Shall I go downstairs?
- Go downstairs. - Shall I go?
Don't go, Kwang Soo.
(He should stay here.)
I'll go downstairs.
You're doing well, but even your brother said this.
You're talking too much about health.
(He talks too much about health.)
(He brings up vegetarianism out of the blue.)
(He's talking too much about health.)
This is what shocked Jong Myung the most.
He said it's the last thing you should say.
You told her about traveling with your mom.
I told you not to say...
- that you travel with Mom. - I explained to her why.
(He talked about it for 30 minutes.)
(Talking about traveling with his mom is unnecessary.)
Shouldn't the conversation get deeper by now?
- Right. - Here's why.
It shouldn't be just a friendly conversation.
I was telling her about my life and what kind of person I am.
At this rate, you'll need two nights to finish filming it.
Talk to her casually like she's your friend.
Are you trying to teach me?
(Jong Kook is quick to notice.)
My goodness.
Is he showing off because he's married?
Is that why?
Did Ji Hyo go down to meet her?
She's trying to keep it less awkward.
Did you talk a lot with him?
Yes.
Do you have questions about Jong Kook?
What kind of women does he like?
Let's see.
He doesn't like women who are too wild.
He likes someone modest.
He also likes someone petite.
- I think you look good together. - Us?
(She's embarrassed.)
Jong Kook is a gentleman.
I think you'll get along.
As you saw, he likes to talk.
I thought so, too.
He's talkative, so he'll talk to you a lot.
- Good luck. - Thank you.
- Hello. - Hello.
Why are you here?
- Why are you here? - Wait.
Come here.
What are your thoughts on Jong Kook?
What are you saying?
Stop it.
- Leave them alone. - This is important.
Leave the two alone.
- Come with me. - Will you go out if he asks?
- Stop it. - I'm leaving.
The conversation should get deeper.
You're running out of time.
Stop it.
When was your last relationship?
(Laughing)
What did Ji Hyo say?
What did she say to you?
- Ask him. - Ask him if he likes sports.
Ask him what kind of women he likes.
- Ask him what he usually does. - Ask him about the women he likes.
What did Ji Hyo say?
(She hesitates to talk.)
What did she say to you?
She told me to ask the type of women you like.
- Me? - What type of...
women do you like and dislike?
(She wants to get to know him better.)
- Me? - Yes.
I want to be with a woman who loves me.
I hope she likes the way I live...
and my perspective on life.
Let's say I play sports.
I prefer women who also play sports.
If we share things in common,
my girlfriend or my wife would be more positive...
about the things I do.
Even though he's on TV, Jong Kook is very serious.
- Yes, he is. - I think he likes her.
I think So Young also likes him.
I'd have made an acrostic poem.
What?
I'd make an acrostic poem with "So Young".
- "So Young"? - Yes.
- "So". - I want you to be mine.
- "Young". - Will you be with me forever?
Such acrostic poem would liven up the mood.
Seok Jin is thinking, too.
- No, I'm not. - He's thinking, too.
After reciting a poem,
he can ask her to do the same with "Jong Kook".
That's right.
Then this is what he'll say.
- Come on, Ji Hyo. "Jong". - Jong Kook.
- "Kook". - I'll call you Kook.
That's right.
- It'll liven up the mood. - It'd be perfect.
Isn't that an old tactic?
- Say, "So Young" for me. - It isn't old.
- Say, "So Young". - "So".
So Young, I'm sorry, but you don't come first place.
- "Young". - Zero place?
Zero place.
Don't finish my sentence.
(Seok Jin is too predictable.)
Can you give her a wink?
This would be great.
You know I'm joking, right?
(It's bound to ruin any date.)
Seok Jin, you need to make a shooting sound.
(The shoot turns all women away.)
He needs to lighten up the mood.
He's asking about her ideal type.
What type of men do you like?
For me,
there isn't an ideal type of men because my mind changes.
Of course it changes.
- Women change their minds often. - Right.
Women fall for the male lead in a popular drama of the month.
I've never liked celebrities.
I said I'm a fan of Jae Seok.
I haven't liked celebrities other than Jae Seok.
That was the case for me, too.
Since I was young, I've never liked celebrities.
(They share something in common.)
You said on TV that your ideal type is Yoon Eun Hye.
(Yes, about that...)
Where did I see it?
(About Eun Hye)
(He's at risk.)
- Yoon Eun Hye? - She mentioned Yoon Eun Hye.
He's close to her.
When they were working together, an article was written about them.
I remember hearing about it. I was in middle school.
(Poor Jong Kook)
(Yoon Eun Hye keeps coming up.)
(He denied her feelings for Eun Hye.)
(It was a lie.)
(Does he still have feelings for Eun Hye?)
(Jong Kook, please tell me the truth.)
When people asked me which celebrity I like,
I always said Eun Hye was the closest to being my ideal type.
However, it's irrelevant to my romantic life.
It's about whom I'm with.
If you were my girlfriend,
you would be the most beautiful person to me.
Even if I see a beautiful female celebrity,
I would think,
"you're more beautiful."
(You're the most beautiful.)
(Her heart flutters.)
(That's a great comment.)
That's what I said.
It's not just what I said. That's what I think.
That's what I think.
I was surprised.
He was much different from what I had expected.
To be honest, I didn't know much about him.
I was surprised by how thoughtful he was.
I want to get to know him better.
(As they open up more, how will their date turn out?)
Like mentioned before,
So Young and Jong Kook will take the car.
Please go ahead.
Shouldn't you carry her since there are many steps?
You should at least carry her.
Jong Kook is trying hard not to lose his temper today.
- I can't get angry today. - Right.
May I make an acrostic poem with "So Young"?
(An acrostic poem?)
That sounds good.
"So".
So Young, I'm sorry, but you don't come first place.
(Is it what they think it is?)
It's not what I think it is, right?
Let's just go.
- No way. - Let's just go.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - I didn't think you knew.
- He didn't think you knew. - I didn't know.
I got scared just now.
- I didn't think you knew. - I apologize on his behalf.
Did you expect what came next?
- Let's just go. - I'm sorry.
Please go ahead first. We'll follow you.
See you.
See you soon.
You're my zero place.
Zero.
- She doesn't even react. - I'm sorry.
- Let's go. - She doesn't react at all.
Let's go.
(It's silent and very awkward.)
Do you usually wear a lot of makeup?
(It's his first question after thinking.)
I'm not good at putting on makeup.
I don't look good with heavy makeup.
I asked not to put on heavy makeup for today.
- I really hated how I looked. - Did you?
But on screen... I saw you briefly on a monitor.
- You looked really pretty. - Really?
(He makes her heart flutter.)
You have nothing to worry about.
Some people I know,
when they're dating someone,
they tell the woman how to dress.
- That happened to me. - Did it?
I hated that so much I did the exact opposite.
I did the exact opposite.
Not exactly the opposite,
- but I retaliated. - I know what you mean.
You have a temper.
(They've grown more comfortable with and closer to each other.)
(Where will this path lead?)
(The couple's evening turns to night.)
- Let's go. - Okay.
It feels like we're ruining their honeymoon.
- We're following them around. - Seriously.
- It's their date. - If they go on a honeymoon,
- we won't tag along. - Where's your family from?
- Yeongil. - Yeongil?
Where's yours from?
My family? Pretty Town.
That was funny. That joke worked.
I'm from Pretty Town.
(What machine is this?)
- Plush toys. - Toys.
I love these machines.
- I'm great at this. - Me, too.
I'm an expert at this.
- Let's see. - I'm awesome at this.
There are many different toys in here.
- What's this for? - Couples love to do this.
- It's game over. - Let's put an end to this.
They can meet again in private.
- Now... - They agreed to.
She let me call her his future wife.
This is the final stage.
The result of this mission decides whether they go on a cruise...
(A romantic dinner on a cruise ship)
Or end up in a duck boat.
We can't ride a duck boat.
We'll see Jong Kook in action.
- Think about it. - No way.
She's freezing cold and you want to put her in a duck boat?
- It's also... - Hwan Jin.
I hate you, I hate you.
Why do you keep doing that?
- You need to try it sometimes. - What for?
Entertain her.
Get ready.
- There's 6. - You have 6 coins.
That means you get six tries on the machine.
Which toy should we get?
- Anything. - Anything.
Anything?
- Yes. - It's not easy.
Get whatever you can for the lady.
We'll see what she wants.
- Pikachu? - Whatever's easy.
- That one, Psyduck. - No, Pikachu.
Get this one.
That one.
Pikachu, yes.
Pikachu, yes. Go for Pikachu.
(Jae Seok said he's an expert, but how good is he really?)
(This can't be that easy...)
- I should play. - He got it.
He got it.
(The claw has Pikachu!)
Shouldn't I be playing?
- He won. - I'm meant to play, not you!
I'm meant to play, not you!
Jong Kook, you get five tries.
I told you I was good.
Have you played this before?
- Aim for this one. - I haven't.
It's random.
Good luck.
- Good luck. - Go for this one.
I'll see if I can get this one.
Try getting that Pikachu.
Be quiet.
- You be quiet. - Go for it.
(I'll go straight for it.)
(This last stage of the date depends on this machine.)
(Will it be a romance like "Titanic" or torture like "12 Years a Slave"?)
(Cautious)
- Hey, hey! - I didn't press it yet.
(The claw dives straight down.)
- I didn't press the button! - You went overtime.
Is there a time limit?
You can't take your time with this.
I asked how many shots I got.
- Don't just go to the gym. - Watch what you're doing.
You have to be careful.
Watch the time limit.
(They might all take the duck boat.)
I'm telling you, that tiger will work.
Perfect.
- A bit more. - It's fine.
It looks okay.
(The claw descends.)
Press the button.
It's working.
(The claw grabs it.)
(Two failures are unacceptable.)
It's not a good hold.
(Come with me, little ducky.)
That was close.
(The claw didn't have a strong enough hold.)
Why did you...
You should've let him do it.
You have three more tries.
- Take us on a cruise ship. - How about this one?
This one might be easy to get.
- I prefer this one. - Get the tiger.
Get out of the way, Mister!
- You wasted a chance. - You're bad luck!
I'm good at this.
- So what? - Did it move?
- Good. - Good.
You might get this one.
No, no, those two...
(The toy slips once again.)
That one?
- There's one on top. - Get the head.
Try to grab its head.
Listen to me. Get the tiger.
Shut your mouth.
- His dark side's coming out. - It is.
You're showing your true colors.
It's about time.
It's time to keep quiet.
Be very careful.
Which tiger?
- The tiger. - The tiger.
No, get this duck's head.
The head.
- The duck? - It's easier now.
- The last shot. - The last shot.
- Don't go for the tiger. - You're taking his side now.
The tiger's too deep in the pile.
She doesn't want to ride the duck boat, either.
- The duck... - I think he'll get it.
This is why you keep spending. You rarely win anything.
(Ducky, will you really not come with me?)
It's a lost cause.
(The duck ascends.)
(The ugly duckling takes flight.)
(Jong Kook aimed for a tiny duck.)
(He who never gives up will ride a cruise ship.)
(It's a fail.)
Why did you drop that?
I told you to get the tiger.
I said tiger.
Let's just all pile into a duck boat.
- What now? - Oh no...
Go for this one now.
- I have one more shot. - It's your last one.
- This is it. - Get the tiger.
It's perfectly located.
- It's not. - Go for...
Go for the bottom half of it.
I have to get the tag on that one.
I don't think you can get it.
So Young said she doesn't think I can get the tiger.
- Try for this one. - I think the tiger's your best bet.
- Get the tiger. - It's either the tiger or Snorlax.
The tiger looks okay.
- The tiger? - It might work.
(They place their final bet on the tiger.)
(This one last game decides how the date will end.)
- I'll go for the tiger. - Okay.
- Can't I have one more shot? - Go a bit further.
A bit to the side.
- I think you'll get it. - Now?
- Grab its bottom. - Come a bit this way.
- No, this is good. - Leave it there.
- You got it. - This is it.
- I told you so. - You got it.
(The die has been cast.)
(Please take the lift, Tiger.)
Look.
You got it.
(The claw has it.)
(They're halfway there. Hang in there, Tiger!)
(They're saved!)
(He got the tiger on his last try.)
You did it!
(I told you so!)
See?
Well done.
Did you see that? I'm an expert.
The tiger got the tiger.
(They recognized each other.)
- It's for you. - What a lovely picture.
- That was close. - They held hands.
That was so close.
- This game... - And so...
they got married and lived...
They got married and lived...
(How embarrassing.)
I told you not to say things like that.
It was the tiger after all.
Did you see that?
- He picked himself. - It was our last coin.
As promised,
you two get to go on the cruise ship.
- What a relief. - I'm so glad.
That was so close.
Let's go.
(The couple board the cruise ship wondering what's in store.)
Why did they decorate the place with a heart?
(Sweet desserts await the couple.)
I'm so sorry about this.
- Romance is good, but it's so cold. - It's okay.
- This wasn't my idea. - Okay.
It wasn't my idea.
It's freezing. You said your feet are cold.
This is terrible.
Use this, too.
- I'm fine. - Please, I don't need it.
- I'm fine. - Okay.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
(Isn't he so sweet?)
I've never seen him this happy.
That's a real smile.
He's open to dating right now.
I've known Jong Kook for a long time...
- and I think he likes her. - He does.
- That's for certain. - He wants to ask her out.
He doesn't like how it's not going in that direction.
(The cruise ship is full of love.)
I never knew Yeouido was this pretty.
- I really like the Han River. - Is that so?
- I go a lot in the summer. - To the Han River?
It's been a while since I've been on the cruise ship though.
I see. People living in Seoul don't go on it.
(They've been here a lot but it feels different today.)
It's darker now...
- so the woman opens up as well. - It turns romantic.
- Should we leave? - Sure.
- We don't have anything to do. - I'm getting jealous.
Why are you getting jealous?
- What are you talking about? - I'm getting jealous.
That was the weirdest thing you said today.
- I don't think so. - Why are you getting jealous?
(He wants to be the sweetest person here.)
(This guy is about to change that.)
- You like sweets, right? - Yes.
- It looks good. - It looks good.
(It's dessert time aboard the cruise.)
I have to put it on the side.
(Swaying)
(It spills.)
Oh, dear.
(What's wrong with my hand?)
Hold on.
He did that on purpose.
- I knew it. That's so old. - That's crafty.
- He has such old style. My gosh. - My gosh.
In movies, they spill things on purpose...
and give the woman a change of clothes.
You offer to wash their clothes, make them change...
Never mind.
(Never mind.)
- You must be old, too. - No way.
- Have some cake. - Sure.
Do you have a favorite song?
"One Man"?
(One Man)
They're both old style.
- I can't listen to this anymore. - They're a good match.
- I can't believe So Young... - They know we're watching.
- said that. - Don't be mean.
We can't stand this.
People might change channels so put on the music video of "TT".
- Did anybody tell you to say this? - No.
That's the only song I remembered.
It could be a different singer.
- "Last Love". - "Lost Love"?
(She picks "Last Love".)
Did anyone tell her to say this?
Why do you ask?
I sing this song once in a while.
- Nobody told me that. - Really?
- No. - Is it really your favorite song?
(This old style couple has a mutual understanding.)
Should I sing it now?
- I can sing. - Sure.
(I'd love to hear it.)
This is driving me nuts. I don't know what I'm doing.
(He stands up reluctantly.)
I'm sorry. I think I need to sing...
for us to move on to the next topic.
In this situation, Jong Kook and men in general...
need something...
- to score big points. - Right.
He has to try his best.
I was lucky to have met you
I was lucky.
(This is the song older men used to score points with ladies.)
That's it.
(Hard-standing charms)
This is where you pull the woman's heartstrings.
The scenery is nice...
so I think it'll be nice to hear him sing.
("Last Love" by Kim Jong Kook)
This is driving me nuts.
Let me start.
(It's a cruise concert just for one woman.)
Thanks for being here today.
(They only met for a short time...)
(but he wants to thank her for being here.)
My heart.
(Rumbling)
- It's the wind. - What's that?
It's the subway.
- Is that a ship? - No, it's the subway.
(The noise makes the song sound more melodic.)
(Why does it have to be now?)
(We didn't want it to be awkward so we got the subway.)
The subway is in the scenery.
She looks happy.
- It's jealous. - She's smiling a lot.
I hope they get pooped on by pigeons.
There's a train passing.
(My goodness!)
My gosh.
How could this happen?
(The subway's always there to lighten up the atmosphere.)
It's incredible.
(The real "Last Love" by Kim Jong Kook)
(It's for the woman...)
(who spent the day with him...)
(despite the cold weather.)
(His voice rings all over Yeouido.)
So Young...
was looking at him.
- Then she must have turned shy. - She must have.
She turned away. You know when they do this?
Don't say anything.
(His calming face melts away all your worries.)
It's like he's on "Inkigayo".
- I mean... - He's trying his best.
(He's trying so hard.)
He has his arm folded like this. It's like he's on "Inkigayo".
(It's a ballad by one man...)
(who's trying desperately to save his blind date.)
Even if you did wrong just like me.
(It's a concert just for one person...)
(aboard the cruise ship.)
They say.
- Love doesn't last forever - This looks nice.
It'll look great when it's edited a little bit.
Are you jealous?
(You're not jealous, right?)
This is what he wants to do.
All men...
- want to be main leads in a drama. - That's right.
Seok Jin will star as "Nose Goblin".
- "Nose Goblin"? - He has a cotton in his nose.
He dies when the bride takes it out for him.
He gets a nose bleed and dies.
(Nose Goblin)
They say.
(The song reaches the climax...)
(as the day comes to an end.)
- You - You.
- Only you - Only you.
(They get immersed too much.)
(My last love)
You.
(He sings with his heart and soul.)
My last love.
From now on.
One thing can't change.
You are my only true love.
(The sweet lyrics make the song even better.)
(Thank you for making a special memory for me.)
I know I can't do this but that made my heart flutter.
It's quite romantic.
He's going to say something now.
I don't.
(Gazing)
Think I can.
- What's wrong with his eyes? - Love again.
- Aren't those the snake's eyes? - Snake's eyes?
(He's gazing on purpose.)
- Aren't those the snake's eyes? - It must be.
(The emotions run deep until the end.)
(That was a successful concert.)
- Was it okay? - Yes, you were great.
I wish it was a better atmosphere.
- I got 100 points. - Gosh.
(He must have tried extra hard.)
(Excellent job!)
- He got the perfect score. - Did he?
That's incredible.
- The machine is on his side. - "And now, I..."
What if So Young starts singing Wax's "Honey"?
(The next stage is by So Young.)
Look at me only.
What about "Tears" by So Chan Whee?
(Another recommendation is "Tears" by So Chan Whee.)
Don't call me a merciless woman.
- And she'll start headbanging. - Gosh.
I'm starting to wish that things don't work out between them.
- I agree. - Me, too.
I want it to end funny.
(The dreamy cruise ship date ends.)
Use this.
(They're gathered.)
- Good. - It's been a while.
(They light up 5 firecrackers for Jong Kook and So Young.)
They're coming.
(Welcome to land.)
What are you doing?
- She's shy. - We're wishing you luck.
(Thanks for the performance.)
- Thanks for the performance. - My last love.
- You saw it? - You even sang the second verse.
- Did you see the subway pass by? - Congratulations.
(It was a humorous serenade thanks to the subway.)
- It's decision time. - That's right.
Jong Kook, I'll ask you...
to get back on the cruise ship.
So Young will give us a call.
If she's willing to go on another date with you,
we'll put heart stickers on your name tag.
If she had a good time...
but felt uncomfortable...
or if she needs to reconsider...
If that's the case,
we'll rip your name tag.
(If So Young says no, they'll rip his name tag.)
- Don't worry. - Do you feel uncomfortable?
I see those dolls got closer already.
Well...
- Gosh. - You will miss each other.
The way they're gazing at each other is very passionate.
It all worked out well.
Stop it. Stay out of it.
(They are already celebrating.)
This will affect my decision-making.
It will?
- It will affect her decision. - Don't you worry.
(It's hard to figure out her decision. What will it be?)
(So Young, let us know what you've decided.)
(Jong Kook, who will wait for her decision, moves inside the cruise.)
My goodness. Everyone's watching.
She will come here to either put a heart on it or remove my name tag.
I thought since it's a TV show, she might feel uncomfortable.
I thought I should accept it well even if she rejects me...
when she had a great time today.
I tried my best to be calm and to expect the least.
No one knows what will happen to us...
but I hope we can have a good relationship.
- Poor Jong Kook. - We must put a heart or...
- She's calling. - She's calling.
Hello?
- Hi, So Young. - Hi.
Have you decided?
Yes, I have.
He told me a lot of things.
He wasn't like what I had in mind.
In fact, I didn't know much about him.
(I saw a new side to him today.)
I bet you gave it a lot of thought.
So what is your decision?
I decided...
(What will her last answer be?)
You took care of me a lot today.
(On this freezing day, he reached out for her hand.)
(He put her name tag on for her.)
(He gave her a stuffed animal which he tried his best to win.)
(He sincerely sang a song for her.)
Thank you for giving me a great time today.
I will see you again.
(She made her decision.)
I understand.
(What does she mean by it?)
That's your decision, right?
(It's hard to figure out through Jae Seok's facial expression.)
(A man awaits for her decision.)
It was good. It was fun.
(After contemplating, she made her decision.)
It was nice.
Hurry.
(Members visit Jong Kook after the call.)
I can't help but smile.
(It's hard to read their faces.)
Who will tell him?
- We really... - Yes?
This sure is funny.
It's only a variety show.
(Is he hinting something?)
- Really. - By the way...
- It doesn't matter what happens. - It's a variety show.
You expressed your feelings about her throughout the day.
This can be a good relationship.
We can get to know each other.
No one knows what will happen.
- You're interested in seeing her? - Yes, I am.
You don't have to meet on a TV show.
She might just not be comfortable on television.
- That's possible. - You're right.
(Did being on the show make her feel uncomfortable?)
You don't have to meet on TV.
(He does something suspicious.)
She might feel pressured.
(Ripping)
(Jae Seok removes his name tag.)
(Hold on, this means...)
(From the beginning, the members made her feel pressured.)
(What are you doing?)
(Throughout the day, their dramatic differences were revealed.)
Get her to talk!
(Their conversation was one-sided.)
(Spilling)
(He spilled a cold beverage on the cruise.)
(Did all these things make her reject me?)
Why don't you put the heart on it?
(He's puzzled.)
What's going on?
Congratulations.
(It was a joke. She chose you.)
- Why is it so windy? - Hey.
What was that?
(So Young said yes and chose Jong Kook.)
It's all blown away.
(It looks like they're all chosen.)
I was convincing myself I will be okay if she rejected me.
What we did today crossed my mind.
- She's coming. - Thank you.
(Here comes the bride of Jong Kook.)
I should give you this, right?
Thank you.
It's cold.
It turned out well.
- It's a happy ending. - First of all,
we shouldn't get ahead of you two.
This was your first time meeting. Keep in touch.
You should meet up some other time and get to know each other.
You will have to figure out on your own.
- Of course. - This is where we stop.
- Congratulations. - We hope your relationship lasts.
(His blind date was a success even though he's not getting married.)
It's Running Man's Member's week.
(The 3rd participant)
(Who will be next?)