(2017 Running Man's 3rd Global Project)
(Half and Half Tour)
(Salar de Uyuni is nature's biggest and clearest mirror.)
(Bora Bora is Venus' island located in the South Pacific Ocean.)
(Rome is the eternal city that has the history of the Roman Empire.)
(Antelope Canyon is a sandstone formation created by rain and wind.)
(Alaska is the home of extreme sports and aurora.)
(Lake Hillier is a romantic lake that is made pink by plankton.)
(Bow River lets the visitors enjoy fly fishing in the Rocky Mountains.)
(Krabi is a fantastic vacation spot where the sky and sea connect.)
(So Min's recommendation)
(Did you think there'd be only paradise ahead of you?)
(There are also hideous vacation places which the staff recommended.)
(8 recommendations from the members and 8 recommendations from the crew)
(Each week, the members have a match to put their names on the roulette.)
(First destination turned out to be the Nevis Swing in New Zealand.)
(Jae Seok, the icon of penalties, got Nevis Swing in New Zealand.)
(Second destination was...)
(Bora Bora, the fantastic vacation spot, which Haha recommended.)
(So Min, the icon of luck, got Bora Bora.)
(Today, which travel destination and member will be chosen?)
(Fall is around the corner at a house wedding hall in Seoul.)
- Hello. - Hello.
I haven't seen heart decorations in a while.
(There are pink hearts with the members' names.)
The broken hearts make me worried.
Where are the broken hearts?
(What are the 2 ominous broken hearts?)
I think they are meant for men.
Kwang Soo, go over there.
What are you talking about?
- You should go over there, too. - Go over there.
Jae Seok and you should go.
Today, we are having Half and Half Project Part Three.
As you have guessed, it will be a Couple Race.
(Half and Half Project Part 2: Couple Race with hearts)
(The single men are excited.)
The weather is perfect for a Couple Race.
Today, the couples will be decided right after the women enter.
- Really? - Right after?
Including Ji Hyo and So Min,
eight women will enter in order.
There will be a lot of women.
I can't believe there will be eight.
(They are ready to captivate men's hearts.)
(The 8 women are waiting to make a grand entrance.)
The two women without male partners...
will take the broken hearts.
Those are for women.
We will have a partner no matter what.
It's 100 percent.
However, there is a special rule in deciding the couples.
(There is a special rule.)
If the man a woman chose already has a partner,
she can shout, "Come out" to her for a chance to be his new partner.
- My goodness. - Really?
Then the man will decide...
after the two women have a simple match.
The woman who loses a partner that way...
moves one space to the right.
If the man on the right has a partner,
she will be forced to move one space to the right.
Wait a minute. I am sorry,
but does that mean I am the worst choice?
Don't be ridiculous.
I will tell you what the order means.
We conducted a popularity vote with the female guests.
All right. Say no more. Say no more.
- Wait a minute. - Don't speak.
Which side is the most popular?
This is the result of a popularity vote.
- Jae Seok got four votes. - Really?
Jong Kook and Haha got one vote each.
- My goodness. - I am relieved.
The rest got zero votes.
(2 people refused to vote.)
Did I get zero votes?
Then why am I standing here? Is it the alphabetical order?
Who do they think they are?
- Seriously. - Let's see who they are.
They are so mean.
The female guests will enter now.
Please come on out.
We need to get the ones who move to the right.
(Here they come.)
(Who is the star of this stylist and groovy music?)
It's a hip hop song.
(Her silhouette is stylish.)
My goodness.
(Here I come, Running Man.)
(With whom are the members impressed?)
(The actress with perfect looks, Lee Elijah)
(She can play a shy girlfriend and a resentful and wicked woman.)
(She walks with confidence and turns like a model.)
You look great.
(She twists her ankle.)
(What was that?)
(The elegant woman shows an unexpected charm.)
What was that?
My goodness.
That's good.
Elijah, that was great.
- That was great. - It was funny.
- That was great. - I loved it.
- Is your ankle okay? - It's okay.
Please say hello to the viewers.
Hello, I am Lee Elijah, an actress.
Elijah.
Is that your real name?
Yes, it is.
Are you from abroad?
No, I am not.
She is from Changwon, South Gyeongsang Province.
- Elijah. - Are you from Changwon?
- I am from Changwon, too. - Really?
- I have lived in Changwon. - You have lived in Changwon.
It's nice to meet you.
(He suddenly speaks in a dialect.)
We are like a family.
You are terrible at speaking in a dialect.
This is the best.
- Elijah. - Yes?
In the past, you have talked about...
- your ideal type. - Really?
She talks about it in a wishy-washy way.
"Someone I can talk to all night long under the stars."
"Star" is the meaning of my wife's name.
(Changwon and the stars make us one.)
My goodness.
You are right.
What is wrong with him?
"Star" is the meaning...
Stop it!
(They speak in a strange dialect.)
You are so bad at it.
Stop it. You have done enough.
- Stop it. - Stop it.
- Stop it. You have done enough. - You are so bad at it.
- Elijah. - Yes?
- Your ideal type remains the same. - Yes.
You want someone you can talk to all night long under the stars.
- Yes, communication is important. - Have you...
recently talked to anyone under the stars?
Have you recently talked to anyone under the stars?
I have talked to myself.
(I have talked to myself.)
- She has her walls up. - I am impressed.
- Her agency readied her thoroughly. - That's not it.
She is old-fashioned.
She and I are in the same agency.
- Really? - It's King Kong Entertainment.
- I am impressed. - I knew it.
The agency takes good care of its artists.
Kwang Soo, you have recently talked to someone under the stars, right?
(Let me ask you this.)
What?
Why are you spouting nonsense?
What is wrong with him?
- Calm down. - What is wrong with him?
It's just a question.
Who will Elijah choose?
Elijah, go.
- What should I do? - Stand next to the one you like.
- That's it. - Seok Jin.
What is going on?
(Is Seok Jin the one Elijah wants to talk to under the stars?)
Where are you going? Hey. Hey!
(Where are you going, Elijah?)
(Running)
She made me look like a fool.
Elijah!
(Elijah chooses Jae Seok.)
Elijah, I am disappointed.
- I am sorry. - It's just as we had expected.
Elijah and I are a couple.
(They are a temporary couple.)
You will be here later.
I won't choose you even if you do.
It's bound to happen.
- It's bound to happen. - You will go that far.
Let's see the next guest.
- Come on in. - Who is the next female guest?
(Who is the next female guest?)
(Her outfit is bright, and her hair is long and straight.)
You chose first.
- "Gashina". - "Gashina".
It's Sun Mi's song. It's Sun Mi!
"Gashina".
(The real Sun Mi appears.)
It's Sun Mi!
(Unbelievable)
(Sun Mi finally visits the show.)
(The sexy queen who makes the heart beat, Sun Mi)
(She is a sexy fighter who has 10 years of experience.)
(Her new song, "Gashina," is top 1 on various music charts.)
Let's go. Let's go.
- Come on. - Hello.
As soon as you made a comeback, your new song, "Gashina,"
- became the talk of the town. - I love the song.
It's a great song.
- The music video is a work of art. - It's artistic.
(She is incredible.)
(Do you mean something like this?)
I watched it before I went to bed last night.
I watched it 20 times yesterday.
- What? - Really?
(Sun Mi's Gun Dance in "Gashina" is fatally beautiful.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- You have watched the dance often. - I know it by heart.
- I have watched it often. - Please show us the dance.
- I have watched it very often. - Music, please.
- I watched it last night, too. - Kwang Soo.
Incorrect. Incorrect.
(He looks like he is having a nervous breakdown.)
- It's one of her dance moves. - It's a different dance.
Next is Haha.
(Next is Haha, the singer.)
You are like Song Min Ho.
(He recreates the Gun Dance nicely.)
Jong Kook, let's go.
Really?
(Time out.)
Jong Kook hasn't watched the music video.
(He ruins the atmosphere.)
- What is wrong with him? - Well,
- that's the reality. - He ruined the atmosphere.
Sun Mi.
"Gashina" is incredibly popular these days.
- Seriously. - The staff can show us the dance.
The entire nation is under the spell of "Gashina".
Any staff member can dance to "Gashina". Play the song.
Kwon Ryeol, come on out.
- Kwon Ryeol. - Anyone can dance to the song.
Anyone can dance to the song.
- Kwon Ryeol. - Who knows the dance?
- You know the dance. Come on. - Everyone does.
(Bang, bang)
(Kwon Ryeol shoots.)
(He dances in a sexy way.)
(Embarrassed)
The popularity of "Gashina"...
made Kwon Ryeol dance like this.
What is wrong with him?
(Sun Mi is the best.)
Sun Mi, it's time to make your choice.
- Sun Mi, go. - Go.
That's it.
Sun Mi, look this way.
This is the dance.
(Is she aiming for Seok Jin?)
(Shooting)
(Maybe next time.)
(She approaches Kwang Soo this time.)
Kwang Soo, she is behind you.
- Kwang Soo. - She's behind you.
Are you leaving?
(Is she leaving or not?)
(She leaves.)
Will she choose Jae Seok again?
(Jae Seok is popular today.)
My goodness.
Wait a minute.
It's no fun over here.
I didn't know Sun Mi would come to me.
What do I need to do?
You need to choose one of them.
- Really? - Yes.
I have to choose one of them.
(Should I choose Sun Mi or Elijah?)
(That is the question.)
All right then. Elijah, please come this way.
Had she chosen Seok Jin...
(Jong Kook and Elijah become a couple.)
Had she chosen Seok Jin or Kwang Soo...
- Elijah. - Yes?
Don't take it personally. You can play games with him today.
- What? - I know. He's strong.
- Of course. - I have a say in this matter.
- Jong Kook is already upset. - Why?
- He's already mad. - It's not that.
- But Elijah is standing right here. - She was pushed down to me though.
All right. Now, Sun Mi and I are a team now.
We'll bring in the next guest. Please come on out!
("Red Flavor"?)
- What is it? - "Red Flavor"?
(It's Hwang Seung Un!)
- It's Hwang Seung Un! - It's Seung Un.
- She was on our show before. - It's Seung Un.
(Hwang Seung Un, the best physique)
(She's a rising star with multiple charms in the film industry.)
(She showed her bubbly, cheerful charms on Running Man before.)
- She's here. - The song is "Red Flavor".
(It's nice to see you again!)
(We're happy to see you too.)
- It's been a while. - Goodness, she's a real looker.
- It's been a while. - Long time no see.
- She joined us a long time ago. - That's right.
I heard that Seung Un...
takes a lot of photos of herself.
- She takes a lot of selfies. - She takes a lot of selfies?
Yes. She likes taking photos of herself and saving them.
"I'm saving it."
- Let's look at a few of her poses. - That'd be awesome.
- Pretend that you're at home. - Pretend you have the selfie stick.
In 1, 2, 3.
"Saving it."
(She poses as she pleases.)
Oh, my.
Goodness, she can bend her back a lot.
Her pose is very distinct from other people's.
Why don't we look at Sun Mi's pose?
- Me? - Yes.
- I bet she'll be great. - You take a lot of photos too.
All right, Sun Mi.
In 1, 2, 3. Clicking.
(Looking confident)
(Looking sexy)
- She's good. - Look at her expression.
- She's a professional. - She's a celebrity indeed.
I like that facial expression.
- She was excellent. - I can see she's very talented.
- Elijah, show us your poses. - Elijah, show us.
- Elijah, go for it! - Elijah...
Elijah, just do the poses you'd normally do.
Be confident. In 1, 2, 3. Clicking.
You should look over there, Elijah.
(She gazes at the camera after the camera shutter sound.)
- Do it when I make the sound. - Which camera do I look at?
- I guess she's drunk. - Do it at the camera shutter sound.
- Are you feeling okay? - Which camera is it?
- We should get her a driver. - I see. That's the camera.
- I'm calling a designated driver. - Let's give this another try.
- Elijah, try again. - We should call the driver.
- Just like this? - That's right.
Start, Elijah. In 1, 2, 3. Clicking.
Do the pose when I say, "clicking".
(Do the pose when I say, "clicking".)
She never listens.
- She's so stubborn. - I mean...
- she has her way of doing things. - Jong Kook, she's headstrong.
Elijah, it seems like you're not listening to me at all.
Do it when I make the sound. Look how Seung Un does it.
- In 1, 2, 3. Clicking. In 1, 2, 3. - I can't multitask.
- That's how you do it. - Now, I get it.
I think Kwang Soo has the best pose among us.
- I agree. - He's the best at it.
- He was a model. - He's tall.
In 1, 2, 3. Clicking. In 1, 2, 3. Clicking.
Hold on. Why...
(It's a busy photoshoot. He doesn't have time to change his poses.)
- Give me time to change my poses. - What?
- We don't have time. - How can I do it so quickly?
- Be grateful you had the chance. - You need to hurry.
- I had a pose in mind. - Goodness, you're unbelievable.
People are lining up for this. All of us want to take photos.
Clicking.
(Take my photo too.)
- Haha, why don't you try it? - That sounds great. Haha, try it.
See how fast he can do this. In 1, 2, 3. Clicking.
(I'm the fastest, and my poses are different from others'.)
Se Chan, it's your turn. Clicking, clicking, clicking.
(Taking photos one after another isn't a problem for me.)
Seung Un will pick now. Play the music!
(Time for Seung Un to choose)
- Please begin. - What should I do?
- You can start now. - Whom should I choose?
You can choose anyone. You'll just play games for a day.
Should I pick him?
(She approaches Seok Jin at the end just like everyone else.)
- Seok Jin is getting his hopes up. - Let's go.
(Will there be a twist?)
- What? - I choose him!
(It looked like she might choose Seok Jin, )
(but she turned around and chose Kwang Soo.)
(I'm finally getting a break.)
Goodness.
- Really? - This happened.
Am I a bus stop or something? Why do they always pass me by?
Seung Un and Kwang Soo will make one team.
(As of now, 3 couples have been formed.)
Let's bring in the next guest.
The matching will continue. Please come on out!
(What is this sad melody?)
(It seemed she wouldn't fall in love again, )
(but she visits Running Man only 3 months after her delivery.)
- It's Baek Z Young. - Z Young!
- Baek Z Young is here. - Z Young.
(Baek Z Young, the queen of singers)
- Z Young. - Oh, my. Z Young.
(She enters as she does ballet elegantly.)
(Z Young, it's so nice to see you.)
Z Young!
(Dancing)
Z Young, you can't dance like that yet.
Z Young is still going strong! She's still awesome!
Goodness.
(She comes back to the show in healthy condition.)
Please come this way.
Congratulations on your delivery.
- Hasn't it been only three months? - I think so.
- It's been exactly three months. - Gosh.
- Can you be on TV? It's too soon. - I'm fine.
When we talk to Z Young,
- we must mention her husband. - I agree.
You said that your husband has a score of 99 points.
I did say that.
- Why did you deduct a point? - "I did say that."
If he's perfect, it'd be boring. So I deducted a point for him.
What about now? Is he keeping the points?
- Now, it's 100 points out of 100. - He got 1 more point.
- He got one more point. - Do you mean that?
- What's wrong with you? - He earned the last point...
with his love for our child.
(He's the perfect husband.)
You married such a great guy.
On the other hand, your husband gave you a low score.
- Seriously? - No, I was kidding.
- You startled me. - She was so surprised.
- She's still very responsive. - He would never do such a thing.
She hasn't changed.
- All right, Z Young. - This is nice.
- She's going to choose her partner. - Let's do this.
- Play the song. - Choose now.
(She starts exploring while looking sorrowful.)
- Z Young, long time no see. - Goodness, he's making me cry.
- Why? - I feel so bad for you.
- Nothing's wrong with me. - You can't understand the rules.
- That's not true. - So I can't choose you.
Z Young!
Just go that way then. Why did you have to tell me that?
Elijah, come out.
- Elijah! - Elijah.
- Elijah, don't go just yet. - Really?
- Jong Kook has to choose. - I know.
Z Young, please come this way.
(Should he protect Elijah who was once abandoned by Jae Seok?)
My friend.
(Whispering)
(What is the secret message he gave Z Young?)
I have to tell her to go?
(Elijah, can you come out now?)
- Tell her to go to Haha. - Really?
- I'm sorry. Please go. - Go to Haha, please.
- She must be so happy. - Elijah.
(Even if she's being pushed down...)
Aren't we both from Changwon? How dare you step on me?
(Haha and Elijah become a couple regardless of their intentions.)
Let's bring in the next guest. Please come on out.
(Even her back looks cute.)
- It's Kei! - Hello!
(Looking cute)
- It's Kei of Lovelyz. - I know her!
(Kei of Lovelyz, master of cute acts)
(She's the representative idol singer with the cutest acts.)
- She's really pretty. - She's really joining us today?
Kei!
(She's cute indeed.)
I think her head looks smaller than last time.
- Really? - Yes.
- Thank you. - Do you know her? Are you close?
- I know her very well. - Stop it, Jae Seok.
Stop pretending to be everyone's friend.
- He knows everyone. - I know her very well.
All right. With Lovelyz's song...
- Their songs are like gems. - Kei, we'll play your song.
Please choose your partner. Play the song.
(Achoo)
(Overreacting)
She's so cute.
- She's cute. - She can dance pretty well.
She can dance.
- She's cute! - She changed instantly.
(Now, she is about to set out.)
(Or not? She starts dancing again.)
- How adorable. - Hold on.
Kei, I'm sorry to stop you. I like that you're dancing.
- It's good, but... - Tell her to stop dancing.
- You need to pick your partner. - I danced too long.
- Did you get that? - Yes.
(She responds to the song right away.)
You must choose your partner now.
- We'll try again. - Okay.
We'll play another song of Lovelyz.
- Kei! - She looks great when she dances.
Play the song for Kei!
(Kei is showing off another cute side of her.)
- I really love this song. - I have something to tell you
I choose you, Jae Seok.
This is Jae Seok's day.
(Excited)
- What's going on? - This isn't fun at all.
Is this some kind of a prank?
What is this?
- Goodness. - I'm envious.
- Unbelievable. - I'm sorry.
That's one of my favorite songs.
Sun Mi is in trouble now. What is she going to do?
Jae Seok is enjoying this.
This is such a dilemma for me.
- Kei. - Enjoy it while it lasts.
(Jae Seok is in a dilemma. The rule is harsh for the guests.)
(What will Jae Seok's decision be?)
- Kei, - Oh, my!
Bye.
- Kei. - Poor Kei.
It's all right, Kei.
Then what happens to me?
- That must feel so awkward. - Do I move one down?
- I don't get to choose? - Just like this?
(All the female guests must move one spot down.)
(What?)
(That means I have to...)
- Everyone will just move down? - Then Elijah will be my partner?
- I didn't have to come out early. - Okay!
- I knew this would happen! - I...
- Se Chan is happy. - I hope we make a good team.
- Welcome. - We'll be a team now.
(Elijah's turn is getting more elegant as she keeps moving down.)
- Okay. - I see.
If Seung Un gets pushed just once...
- You... - This way.
If Seung Un moves once...
You...
- If you move... - I'm sure I'll move more than once.
- Right. - I'll move more than once.
You'll end up here.
(With me, you'll just be watching others.)
- Let's welcome the next guest. - I'm nervous.
(This is...)
I'm nervous.
(The versatile artist, Sol Bi)
- Who is it? - There's one more?
Sol Bi?
(Hi, everyone.)
Gosh.
- Wait. - Hold on.
- We have to change tapes. - Who is it?
(When they're just about to change tapes, )
(Sol Bi enters dramatically.)
- Wait. - We have to change the tape.
We have to change the tape.
Ma'am, we're changing tapes.
- This is embarrassing. - We're sorry.
How embarrassing.
- To imagine that happened to me... - Sorry.
They have to change tapes.
(I put a lot of thought into how to enter.)
Why did she enter right then?
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
Let's go.
(How should I enter this time?)
- Who is it? - Who is it?
(Entering)
(Sol Bi pretends nothing happened.)
It's Sol Bi.
(I feel sorry for her.)
Hi.
(Just go to your place.)
(The sixth guest is Sol Bi.)
- Sol Bi. - Yes.
Please choose...
your partner.
- Yes. - All right.
- We'll play some music. - Yes.
Go to that person.
I have something to say.
- What is it? - What is it?
(It must be something very important.)
I recently shot a movie.
That's why I'm here.
- You can talk about it later. - That's why I'm here.
(Just pick someone.)
- Sol Bi. - You can talk about it in the car.
Hey.
- Hey. - Sol Bi.
Don't talk about it now.
Talk about it later.
When we eat, for example.
- We have a lot of time. - Okay, I'll wait.
- We have a lot of time. - Okay.
- I'm not sure. - Give us some music.
(Sol Bi will choose her partner.)
Here she comes.
(Turning)
You're so pretty. You look like Marilyn Monroe.
(Whom will she choose?)
Move.
(Seung Un, move.)
(Disappointed)
- Smile. - Sure.
- Smile. - I'm so thrilled.
- It's not like that. - Sol Bi, this way.
Sol Bi, come here.
What happens now?
- Seung Un! - Hey.
- Seung Un. - Hey.
Did I do something wrong?
How does it work?
Hey.
What's the rule?
(Kwang Soo was too thrilled.)
"Seung Un, move." And then Sol Bi is sent away.
You two are a team.
(Awkward)
They just had a conflict...
because of what he said.
I feel bad.
(We weren't expecting this.)
They're a spear and a shield.
- Sol Bi. - It's so awkward.
Why didn't you let her finish?
(All female guests have been introduced.)
(It's time to welcome the two female regular members.)
(Peeking)
- It's Ji Hyo. - Ji Hyo.
- Ji Hyo. - Nucksal.
She's dressed in a bohemian style.
She looks like Woo Won Jae.
Woo Won Jae. Nucksal.
- You're so pretty. - You look so cute.
(She is so relaxed.)
- She doesn't like us. - You look so pretty.
Hey, be quiet.
Woo Won Jae.
- Woo Won Jae. - Woo Won Jae.
She's a cute version of him.
Isn't she just a gangster?
Won Jae never does that.
- She just said that. - You've never seen him, have you?
I have.
(I know my hip hop.)
- Ji Hyo. - Yes.
- Please choose a partner. - All right.
- Please start. - Okay.
(Ji Hyo's decision will determine who will end up single.)
Ji Hyo's decision will...
determine who becomes single.
I see.
(Whom will Ji Hyo choose as her partner?)
She's standing in front of Se Chan.
Move.
(Elijah, move.)
- She wants to send Elijah away. - Goodness.
Se Chan, please choose one.
Se Chan.
- One... - I haven't changed my mind.
One, two, three.
(After Na Eun, )
(who will Se Chan choose?)
- Ji Hyo... - Really?
(Ji Hyo)
Go.
(Ji Hyo, go.)
(Ji Hyo becomes a team with Kwang Soo.)
That sounded so decisive.
I'm sorry.
- All right. - What about me?
Seung Un, please stand here.
- I choose Seung Un. - Are they moving?
- Seung Un. - Seung Un.
Sol Bi.
- I don't have a partner? - Sol Bi...
(I thought it was a Couple Race.)
Oh, my gosh.
Sol Bi has no partner now.
Seung Un might...
lose her partner too.
- That's right. - Seung Un too?
If So Min chooses Seok Jin...
- Then... - Then...
- Seok Jin will choose between them. - I'll choose one.
- Right. - I see.
But it's not likely that So Min will choose Seok Jin.
That means Seung Un will have to move.
(Straightforward)
- Don't say that. - Z Young!
Don't say that out loud.
Just keep it to yourself.
Okay. It might not affect me, right?
We all know that.
All right. Let's welcome So Min.
- Please come out! - So Min!
Come on!
(Bouncing)
Magnet Girl.
Parrot, Frog,
Magnet Girl, Idiot...
It's So Min's turn. Give us some music.
- Come pick. - So Min, you're so cute.
Our frog.
- She's so cute. - She's cute.
Our cute frog.
Oh, my.
Our parrot.
- Move. - Me?
Why am I so popular?
Do I look so easy?
(Realization)
Why does everyone pass me by?
There are other guys too.
Do I look that easy?
You're just popular.
Ji Hyo and So Min...
feel most comfortable with Se Chan.
It's an honor.
Se Chan, please choose between So Min and Elijah.
One, two, three.
Elijah...
(Elijah)
Go.
- I knew it. - "Elijah, go?"
- Yes. - What?
Are you serious?
What's with you?
- So Min. - I'm feeling burdened.
(Are you serious?)
(There's someone who is more uncomfortable.)
No.
Why are you turning?
(Don't pretend you're okay.)
The two from King Kong Entertainment are a team now.
Yes. Boss...
(We love you, Boss.)
All teams have been decided.
Seung Un and Sol Bi have no partners right now.
But it's not over yet.
Really?
(It's not over yet?)
We have two male guests too.
(2 male guests are coming.)
(We'll get partners too.)
Give up on me.
Please give up on me.
Will the female guests get to choose?
If the male guests send someone away,
the female guests will choose between the two.
(The girls get to take revenge.)
The male guests will send someone away.
(Whoever the guests are, we don't have much chance.)
All right. Let's welcome the next guest.
- Please come out. - Who is it?
Who is it?
(There are too few guys now.)
(That's why male guests were invited.)
(A romantic song plays.)
(The first male guest)
It's Sung Hoon.
(The handsome guy, Sung Hoon)
(It's Sung Hoon.)
He's so handsome.
(The good kisser with a fit body, Sung Hoon)
He's too handsome.
Sung Hoon has had fan meetings abroad.
He's becoming very popular.
- He's a new prince. - Really?
He's a new prince.
So Min recently...
You made a cameo appearance.
- That's right. - You know him?
Yes.
(So Min seduced Sung Hoon in the drama.)
How was So Min to work with?
She's not normal.
(So Min is not an ordinary girl.)
She isn't.
So Min, how was it to work with Sung Hoon?
It was very romantic.
- Why? - We hadn't met before,
but he pushed me against the wall.
He thinks you're not normal.
(Are you sure it was romantic?)
- It was romantic? - For me, yes.
(Who will Sung Hoon choose?)
Sung Hoon, can you dance?
- Sure. - Okay.
Play the music.
(Shy)
(Excited)
(What?)
(It's a choo, choo train.)
That was unexpected.
What's that?
What are you doing?
What is this move?
It's an idol group's dance.
It's very simple.
What is this?
Can you show us more?
Okay.
Don't be nervous. Please play the music.
(Sung Hoon says it's an idol group's dance.)
(Sung Hoon learned this move from an idol group.)
(They're excited.)
(He shows off his train dance.)
- That's attractive. - That's the idol dance?
(And it's off beat.)
(It doesn't make sense at all.)
(You shouldn't use your looks that way.)
- He's so cute! - Goodness.
- Goodness. - Good job.
- He's so cute. - That was cute.
- I think... - That was cute.
Wait a second. You tried to act a little cute just now, right?
His dance style is...
I'm shocked that idols actually do those dance moves.
- I can't think of anyone. - It can't be compared to any moves.
- I think I can copy it though. - Kei.
You know a lot of idol groups. Tell me which dance move it was.
But it's part of our choreography too.
- Really? - Show us.
- Our... - Are you serious?
Like this and that.
It's similar to this.
I don't think so.
Are you saying it's similar to how he just danced?
Hold on.
- I think we spoiled her. - How's that similar?
- Isn't it similar? - What?
She just promoted her choreography.
(It was just to promote their dance moves.)
Don't put it that way.
It's not like she's not allowed to do that.
- That's enough. - It's okay.
You know what?
He did it in a cute way,
but it's easy to look like an idiot with that dance.
- Totally. - Goodness.
- He's had enough. Let's stop here. - All right.
I'm sorry.
Now, Sung Hoon will choose his partner.
The male members will have to move this time.
- Really? - Do we have to move?
- We have a strong bond here. - All right, music...
- please. - It's unpredictable.
(With whom does Sung Hoon want to partner up?)
(Disappointed)
(Holding out his hand)
(But he walks past them.)
Wait, So Min.
What's wrong with you, So Min?
- What's wrong with you? - She's excited.
Why are you excited?
- Why is she excited? - That must be it.
Come out.
It's me again?
- That must be it. - Come out.
(Flustered)
Hold on. Do all of you think I'm easy?
Do you think I'm easy or what?
Do you think I'm a rest stop or what?
Let's just say you're popular.
- Think about it. - Everyone likes you.
- Don't think of it that way. - It means you're a nice person.
Let's say this is like a long highway.
- He's the rest stop. - You should be the rest stop.
- Se Chan is. - Everyone meets here.
Where you are is...
- If we think this as a highway... - I'm in the middle.
And So Min was so...
I thought So Min was...
- a bride on her wedding day. - Right.
She was waiting for him.
(Standing like a bride waiting for her groom)
(The world's coolest groom and the bride's father)
(So Min had her imaginary wedding.)
She really was waiting for him to come.
(Her imagination came true.)
- But So Min has to choose too. - All right.
- That's right. - So Min.
1, 2, 3.
I choose Sung Hoon.
(You don't need to ask.)
Bye, Se Chan.
(I won't see you off.)
So the male members have to move to their next places.
That means Seok Jin will end up being my partner again.
Sol Bi, strangely...
They'll end up together.
- Sol Bi, you never know. - I have this feeling.
There's one more guest left.
- I'm excited. - I'm excited to find out who.
- Who is it? - Our last guest.
- It must be a male guest. - Goodness.
Sung Hoon has joined us as our guest.
(Who is today's special guest showing up after Sung Hoon?)
Will it be a member of Wanna One?
(Wanna One is hot these days.)
- Wanna One? - Wanna One?
- Wanna One? - Kang Daniel?
- Kang Daniel? - Kang Daniel?
(Kang Daniel is the center of the hottest idol group, Wanna One.)
(He's the star among his older female fans.)
Goodness.
- There's the helicam. - Goodness.
Wanna One!
- Awesome. - I guess it's true.
The helicam is up.
- They don't use that camera often. - The helicam is up.
(They usually don't fly the helicam during the guest appearance.)
I guess it's really Wanna One.
Who is it?
What?
(Wanna One's song is played.)
- Is it really Wanna One? - Really?
(Regardless of gender, everyone shouted their names.)
- It's me - It's me
(The Running Man members mentioned the group so often.)
All right. Who is our last guest?
(The last guest is here to steal the female guests' hearts.)
(Today's last male guest is both sexy and cute.)
(You've waited for long.)
(Are you serious?)
(Tonight's real guest whom everyone waited for)
(It's Cho Daniel.)
(Why did you come out of there?)
(Disappointed)
(Ji Hyo, it's me.)
(He's the star among his older male fans.)
You're too old.
Let's drag him out.
Jae Seok, let's drag him out.
(Cho Sae Ho)
Among all of us,
- Ji Hyo... - Ji Hyo...
is very much disappointed.
She really wanted it to be Kang Daniel.
But I'm determined.
(He's not Kang Daniel, but he's determined.)
(The staff made a mistake.)
- Not Kang Daniel. - He's not Kang Daniel,
- but he's determined. - I am.
Determination runs in my family.
It's possible.
Sae Ho.
- You came out not long ago. - I did.
How about you say goodbye here today?
Say goodbye? Me?
Because you joined us not long ago,
what do you think about not joining us today?
- Is there such a system? - That sounds great.
You won't do that?
- Aren't you busy today? - I have my own circumstances.
- I see. - He has his own circumstances.
All right.
To whom are you doing that?
(He keeps on giving that gesture.)
I'm saving the tree at the back in my heart.
We're invisible to him.
He's looking for something else.
He's not interested in us. He's looking at something else.
Goodness.
(Click)
What was that?
- Goodness! - He took a photo with his eye.
What's wrong with him?
I'll just go home.
(Dispirited)
(But now that you're here, share some funny stories with us.)
Sae Ho,
you came on Running Man not long ago.
I had no idea you'd be joining us today again.
- Now you know. - Yes.
- Are we done shooting? - That was too short.
I was offered to come out by the staff like all the others.
- That's why I'm here today. - If that's really the case,
- who asked you to come out? - To be specific,
it was the scriptwriter, Lim Eun Kyung.
That's right.
So I passed?
- It's sure he was cast officially. - Three more to go.
Pass two more stages, and you're good to be here.
- Really? What stages? - Two more stages to go.
I'm checking just in case. Some idle people...
come to our show when they're not invited.
Are you serious? There were people who did that?
So we need to be strict in checking whether they're our real guests.
Because...
I understand you. Those steps are necessary.
- Right. - Right.
- Sae Ho. - Yes?
Shall we start with an acrostic poem?
- An acrostic poem? - Yes.
(All of a sudden?)
- An acrostic poem? - Hold on.
Write your name with your bottom.
- What? - With my bottom?
I'm sorry,
but Sol Bi...
This isn't a team gathering.
I won't allow that.
They don't write names with their bottoms even during team gatherings.
Why did you ask for it all of a sudden?
Well, I thought he'd do a great job.
When he came out last time, he showed off his "New Face" dance.
That was awesome.
- Na Eun chose him. - He placed first.
(During the 7th year anniversary special)
I heard you prepared something.
- I did? - Yes.
(He wasn't prepared, but he managed to show off the "New Face" dance.)
- You prepared Tae Yang's "Darling"? - I did?
(He prepared to dance to Tae Yang's "Darling".)
It's a new song.
(He's always prepared.)
- I'm not prepared for it. - Goodness.
That song just came out though. He's awesome indeed.
There's nothing about "Darling" in the script.
Save it in your eyes.
I didn't prepare to do the "Darling" dance.
The director even signed up for the service.
I'd like you to not cast me if you're going to be like this.
If you're going to be like this.
Sae Ho, then...
Shall I start?
(He'll still try it.)
- Please start. - All right.
Go for it!
(Sae Ho will dance to Tae Yang's "Darling".)
(The key points are the charismatic dance and the passionate look.)
(You are the hope in all my fears)
It's not bad.
You've got the feeling.
Nice.
You're like Tae Yang.
- You're really like Tae Yang. - You're good.
What?
(The song heads to its climax.)
- What? - He's going to do something.
(Exposing his fair skin)
(My gosh.)
You...
(He's under arrest for obscene performance.)
- You're under arrest. - Goodness.
- You're under arrest. - Why?
What do you mean, why?
Is this "Police" or something?
- Yes. - Are we shooting "Police"?
After a long stakeout,
- I've caught this punk. - You're mistaken.
- What... - Don't worry, everyone.
Isn't this what everyone wears?
Isn't this the kind of inner wear that everyone wears?
(He has the freedom of expression.)
Sae Ho, along with Tae Yang's song as the background,
(It's time for Sae Ho to choose his partner.)
go to someone whom you want to partner up with.
(Sae Ho's choice will change the other couples' fate.)
(What about me, Z Young?)
As if.
(He makes sure he throws in pointless dance moves.)
He can dance well.
- I'm envious. - So am I.
What is this?
Did he choose her?
(He stops in front of Seung Un. He chooses...)
- It's Ji Hyo? - He chose Ji Hyo?
- Kwang Soo, come out! - Is this really happening?
Please make your decision, Ji Hyo.
Okay. You, leave.
- How can she choose so easily? - Why?
- Are you being serious now? - What's wrong with that?
Ji Hyo, you can't do that.
- Sae Ho, come here. - What? Kwang Soo is happy anyway.
All right then.
- Kwang Soo is smiling. - You're so funny.
- Kwang Soo is smiling. - Now, he can smile.
(Current status report on couples)
(With their partners, they begin their mission.)
As you all know,
the mission money is very important in the Half and Half Project Part 2.
Starting now, you can earn additional money with this mission.
The mission, What's Your Charm?, begins now.
(What's Your Charm?)
(Should I show them my charm?)
I like this.
- "What's Your Charm?" - I like this.
You'll hear keywords of your partner's best charms.
Or if you think your partner's charm is better,
you can challenge the couple.
Whoever takes the first place...
will receive 10 dollars as their additional mission money.
- Okay. - 10 dollars?
The key is that you must win...
the game that you said you'd be best at.
All right. Who wants to go first?
Z Young will start us off.
- Me? - Sweet!
What are you good at?
My partner has a lot of things she's good at.
- Like? - First off, she's good at fighting.
(She can be scary.)
(She used to rule the music industry with her fist.)
- She's good indeed. - That's important.
That's important. Fighting is an important skill.
Among many things, she's best at...
- singing sad songs. - She's the best, hands down.
- She's the master of them. - She's the queen.
(Singing songs in the saddest manner)
Whatever the song may be,
- She can make it sound sad. - she makes the song sound sad.
(Z Young is the expert in singing sorrowful songs.)
(Regardless of the genres, she can make anything sound sad.)
- Can you show us a few songs? - Okay.
- Which one should I sing? - He will sing the song...
- Okay. - "Lovely" in the original version.
She will sing the song right after he finishes.
I already feel sad when I hear Jong Kook sing the song.
(Why?)
You do?
I feel sad when you do the dance like this.
When you dance with your shoulders like this,
- that makes me sad. - Should I make yours narrow then?
Just like this?
(I didn't mean it like that.)
Goodness.
Stop it.
- Jong Kook, sing the song first. - I'll sing "Lovely" first?
(We'll listen to the cheerful version first.)
You're lovely from head to toe
(How will Z Young, the queen of sorrow, sing the song?)
I'm proud that you're my lady
This is driving me crazy.
(The lyrics are happy, but her mournful voice is making us cry.)
Just like this
I love you
No!
(He breaks down.)
She's making me cry.
But can't everyone do this if they sing it slowly?
- No! - That's not true.
- That's not true. - No! What's wrong with you?
Sing it then. Why don't you sing it yourself?
- Try singing it then. - I'll sing the same song.
(What's wrong with his mouth?)
What was that?
Whom are you trying to kid?
Let's try singing an upbeat song.
- Let's sing a children's song. - How about this?
- Sing the tadpole song. - Okay.
- Kei, why don't you sing it first? - She can sing it right away.
- Kei, please sing it. - I'll sing it then.
(She's full of cuteness.)
The tadpole was swimming
(She's getting her sadness on.)
It's my turn now.
The foreleg comes out, the hind leg comes out
- Wait. - Jumping
(The verification process is stopped.)
- Wait, this sounded a bit... - No, you got it wrong.
- I was trying to make it sound sad. - But this...
- How is this sad? - You just sang it slowly.
- Why is this weird? - It sounded too erotic.
- You turned it into a weird song. - It's because...
- That was so weird. - Z Young, you breathed heavily.
I felt pressured.
Now, the song became all weird.
- It hurt when the leg came out. - Exactly.
All right. Z Young...
showed that she could make any song into a sad song.
Is there anyone who would like to challenge her?
Sae Ho can do it!
Sae Ho will try now.
I'm not ready yet.
No, Sae Ho can do this.
Ji Hyo is ready to make me try this,
- Sae Ho. - but I'm not ready to try.
We've been rolling for a long time now.
Then can't someone else try first?
- I got it. - Okay.
- Which song will you sing? - I'll sing something else.
- Okay. - I'll sing Wanna One's "Pick Me".
- All right. That's great. - He'll make that sound sad?
- Okay. - That one could be hard.
- You can make that sound sad? - Get ready.
Start.
(He gathers all the sad feelings he has.)
("Pick Me" is a dance song that makes everyone excited.)
(How will Sae Ho sing the song sadly?)
Tonight
(He fails.)
(He fails after singing only one line.)
That didn't sound like Wanna One's song.
- It didn't? - No, it didn't.
(That's the reason why I failed?)
You didn't sound like Wanna One.
- Are you serious? - Yes, I am.
Why do they always put on a skit? Do you guys practice together?
Okay.
- Really? - She's ready.
- I got it. - I'll get going.
- Elijah will try it. - Really?
- She's been preparing this. - No.
- Really? - You can give this a try.
(When the mission started, she tried to bring out her sad emotions.)
Think of the sad feelings you had, and bring them out.
(Don't distract me.)
I'm sorry.
(She'll try singing "Unconditional" as she focuses on her emotion.)
My love for you
(This song has transformed into a sorrowful song.)
My love
For you
(Fail)
- She was out of tune. - No, no.
- I didn't know the song well. - You were out of tune.
- She was out of tune. - We'll accept it.
- She missed a note. - She...
- She has to hit all the notes. - She can't do that.
I was nervous. Truth be told, I was getting nervous this time.
Z Young, it was close.
You might've lost.
I was nervous this time.
- You could've lost. - You're right.
- She sings well though. - I thought I'd lose.
- She can sing. - Right.
It's over now.
- So Min, will you try it? - Me?
- So Min, give this a shot. - Try it.
I have to feel sad for this. Let me poke my eyes.
- She said she'll poke her eyes. - Let me poke my eyes.
(Poke her eyes? She's unusual from the start.)
(She tries to feel sad with the tears she forced to come out.)
- Can I start from the top? - Yes.
(So Min, good luck.)
(How sad will she sound?)
(She's almost sobbing.)
(So Min fails.)
- Even from the start, she was... - What are you doing?
- How can you cry and sing? - I was trying to sound sad.
(Sing without crying.)
(Wailing)
- Is this her drunk? - I think she might be.
(Are you drunk?)
- This is Drunk Singing Method. - I thought she was drunk.
(I'm not drunk.)
(Hiccuping)
(The tadpoles were swimming)
That was her drunk singing method.
(So Min fails as she sounds drunk, not sad.)
- She was too emotional. - I can't force it.
- I think I'm ready now. - Sorry?
- I know how to do this now. - Then do that next time.
- Okay. - Then do that next time.
(He's very nonchalant.)
- I'll be going now. - Okay.
- Really? - One more time.
- Z Young won! - Z Young will take this round.
10 dollars!
(Haha and Z Young win 10 dollars.)
Next up is Seung Un.
(What is her charm?)
Seung Un's charm is...
that she's sexy by nature,
but her real charm is that she can do sexy dance moves.
(Sexy dance moves)
But don't forget that Sun Mi is here.
- Z Young started doing them first. - No, I didn't.
- No. - She's the very first, sexy diva.
Her dance moves are sexy, but they are exciting at the same time.
They are exciting too.
This will be hard then.
You have to do the dance moves too.
- Really? - Yes.
We should look at Seung Un's dance moves first.
Seung Un, please begin.
- I'm so embarrassed. - Her dance will be difference.
- Let's get it. - I'll dance out of excitement.
Drop the beat, drop the beat!
Let's get it.
They are so funny.
Seung Un is good at dancing.
(As soon as the song is played, she transforms into someone else.)
She's so good at dancing.
(After warming up, she releases her excitement as she shakes her head.)
Goodness! She's awesome.
(She's good. This won't be an easy fight.)
- She's no joke. - Her moves are fancy.
(Sliding down)
(She gives them no time to be distracted. She catches their eyes.)
Seung Un is truly good at dancing.
(As they're fascinated by her dance, the battle is forgotten.)
She's born to be a dancer.
(Goodness, Seung Un is showing off her charm.)
(It's time for her to share her excitement with the rest of them.)
Here it comes!
This is the climax. Here it is!
(She begins her sexy shuffle dance.)
She's shuffling.
(She's shuffling? I don't think I can beat her.)
(She has fabulous dance skills.)
She's a great dancer.
(I'll be the winner.)
She was sexy at first and then cute.
- Thank you, Seung Un. - You're right.
What happens?
Do you have to be sexy to win?
She did a great job.
We'll go last.
- Let's see So Min's dance. - Me?
- So suddenly? - Play the music.
- Me? - Here she comes.
- Sexy dance? - You can earn 10 dollars.
- 10 dollars? - Yes.
(Then...)
(I'm here to win the money.)
What?
Wait.
(So Min, what are you doing?)
What?
She's doing great.
Look at her face.
She wants to dance with him.
(Sung Hoon dances for the money too.)
Look at them.
- They're both drunk. - They keep bumping into each other.
(Great teamwork)
What are they doing?
(Does she want me to sit down too?)
(Sung Hoon sits down too.)
(It's becoming weirder and weirder.)
(Sung Hoon dances sitting down.)
(Wait. What is he doing?)
(I'll get going now.)
I'll just give you 10 dollars.
I'll give you.
- Good. - You were sexy.
Sung Hoon told me in the waiting room,
"I'm not going to dance."
(I have my reputation.)
- It was... - He was sexy.
- That was close. - Sung Hoon...
Seung Un is still in first place.
- Sun Mi. - Sun Mi!
Sun Mi.
- Sun Mi. - Come on. Let's get it.
- She's a difficult one. - She is.
She's a great dancer.
The queen is here.
Play the music.
She's different.
- She's different. - Gosh.
She wins.
(Her waves are different.)
(Amazed)
(We win.)
(She dances on the grass.)
It gives me goosebumps.
Oh, my.
I can't watch this.
(It's almost shocking.)
On the grass...
(She keeps sweeping the grass.)
- Amazing. - Somebody stop her.
Somebody stop her.
Sun Mi, that's enough.
That's enough.
(I'm only beginning.)
Hey.
Sun Mi.
I like to dance, but...
(Jae Seok is embarrassed.)
(She finishes with a mild wave.)
That's enough. You win 10 dollars.
We win 10 dollars.
(Sun Mi gave a fabulous performance.)
No one could beat this.
- First of all... - I acknowledge it.
- I admit it. - We have to admit it.
Seung Un did a great job,
but Sun Mi wins. Next is...
Z Young.
Sol Bi, if I'm struggling, you take over.
(I'll do it, but...)
What?
Okay?
You take over.
No one has ever said that.
- You take over. - Okay.
- Okay? - She wants me to take over.
She'll be amazing.
Go up.
- The return of the queen. - The queen.
Here comes Z Young.
(The sexy diva is ready to dance.)
Hurry, and play the music.
Play the music.
Good.
Amazing.
(She makes use of the pole.)
(The sexy diva proves her worth.)
- She's different. - She's so experienced.
(She's different.)
There you go.
(Mom will win the money, my daughter.)
That's right.
- Shake it. - Great.
Keep going.
(Her back aches.)
You take over.
Here comes Sol Bi.
Oh, my. Hold on.
(Sol Bi takes over.)
(Her skirt falls off.)
(The shooting comes to a halt.)
It's an accident. I can't believe this.
- Her skirt fell off. - It's an accident.
- I can't believe this. - What happened?
I didn't mean to do that.
- Hey. - That's not what we meant.
That's not what we meant by "sexy".
It's not.
You shouldn't take off your clothes.
I'm the winner, right?
Gosh, I can't believe this.
I could have taken off my pants.
That's enough.
- Please blur it. - Sol Bi wins.
Right?
Give her 10 dollars. Give her.
Sun Mi, we can't do anything.
The winner of the sexy dance battle is...
Sol Bi.
(Seok Jin and Sol Bi win 10 dollars.)
Now, Kei.
What is her charm?
- She's... - She's so cute.
That's right.
(Cuteness)
She hasn't done this anywhere else.
- Kei came up with this... - She came up with it.
Recently.
It's called, "Honey".
- "Honey"? - "Honey".
Jong Kook is my honey today.
- Me? - Please help me.
- Me? - You're my honey today.
(What will Kei do to Jong Kook?)
- Say, "One, two, three". - Okay.
One, two, three.
I wanted to see Jong Kook so much.
(Jong Kook can't help but smile.)
My heart is about to burst to see him.
(The audience can't take it anymore.)
Give me a kiss on the cheek.
(Give me a kiss on the cheek.)
Otherwise, I will kiss you.
(Oh, my.)
Honey, my honey
My love
She's unbelievable.
My honey, I love you
(She never stops.)
Give her 10 dollars. No one can do that.
(Give her 10 dollars. No one can do that.)
Give her 10 dollars.
I mean it.
- Just give her. - Who wants to try?
- Who would want to do that? - Don't try.
Don't do it.
Don't even try. Kei, you're amazing.
- She's amazing. - I admit it.
- Unbelievable. - Don't do it.
My team can't do it.
- My team will give up too. - I give up.
- I give up. - Sae Ho.
- Sae Ho will try. - Sae Ho?
- Ji Hyo will try. - Sae Ho will try?
- Sae Ho will try. - Okay.
Sae Ho.
- Be as cute as you can. - But...
I don't want to do it.
(Come on, Ji Hyo.)
- Do I have to? - Be as cute as you can.
Don't forget to blink. Do you need my help?
No.
You're okay?
(Sae Ho is ready.)
(Look at him.)
(Blinking)
I wanted to see Ji Hyo so much.
(The girls are looking away.)
Oh, my.
He must be sick.
- My heart is about to burst... - He's sick.
- He just sounds stupid. - He sounds so weird.
I know a guy like him.
- I wanted to sound cute. - It was...
- You went overboard. - not quite right.
- You think so? - It was too much.
- Try again. - Okay.
I wanted to see Ji Hyo...
- Wait. - I said I didn't want to do it.
I said...
You said...
you wanted to do it.
I didn't. Ji Hyo forced me.
- You said you wanted to try. - I see. Did I?
Thank you anyway.
All right. Kei wins.
We get the money.
It was obvious.
It's Sun Mi's turn now.
(It's Sun Mi's turn.)
Sun Mi is good at mimicking animals.
(She's the best at mimicking animals.)
Animal impressions?
I am sure...
we will easily win 10 dollars.
How good is she?
Which bird will you imitate?
I will imitate...
a brown hawk-owl.
A brown hawk-owl?
It's not even a common owl.
I don't know what kind of a sound it makes.
- It's a real bird. - I know what it is.
You will recognize the sound upon hearing it.
She will imitate a brown hawk-owl.
Please be quiet. Let's hear it.
(Hooting)
- I recognize this sound. - It's an owl.
(It's a bit sloppy.)
(Glancing around)
There is more.
She is good.
- I can imitate a cuckoo. - A cuckoo. That's good.
A brown hawk-owl impression wasn't that impressive.
(Cuckoo)
A bird chirped in response.
The birds are gathering around.
(A bird flew in upon hearing the sound.)
(This is a real situation.)
Listen.
- A bird responded. - Keep going.
Sun Mi, keep going.
That bird seems to be angry.
(The queen of communication, Sun Mi)
(Flying away)
Hey.
The birds gathered around.
(Everyone's shocked.)
How does she do that?
Who wants to challenge her?
- Anyone? - Who wants to challenge her?
If there isn't anyone, we will take 10 dollars.
She will imitate a crow.
(Is Z Young stepping up?)
A crow.
(Z Young imitates a crow.)
I can do better.
Can you imitate a crow?
(Can she imitate a crow as well?)
(Cawing)
- What was that? Sun Mi. - Sun Mi.
- Did you really do that? - Gather your wits.
You have done enough.
Sun Mi, you have done enough. The cuckoo impression was enough.
It was enough.
- She shouldn't try anything else. - That's right.
Who can imitate a bird? Can you do it?
- Listen to that. - You heard that, right?
(Screeching)
(It's the perfect timing.)
- You heard that, right? - I did it.
- Did Elijah make that sound? - Yes, she did.
- Did Elijah make that sound? - Yes.
- I did it. - I got goosebumps.
- It was incredible. - Do it again.
Do it again, Elijah.
I need to be in the zone. Wait a minute.
She needs to be in the zone. How cute!
(Look at her.)
(Chirping)
Are you saying you made that sound?
The timing was perfect.
- She is an expert. - Seriously?
She did the perfect bird impression.
- Did Elijah make that sound? - Yes.
- I imitated three birds. - Who is next?
You are good.
(The truth remains to be found.)
- Who is next? - I won't imitate a bird...
but a monkey, gorilla, or an elephant. May I do that?
- Sure. - It's still an animal.
As long as you imitate an animal, it's okay.
Which animal will you imitate first?
- You know the sound elephants make. - An elephant.
(Trumpeting)
(My goodness.)
That's incredible.
(Do you want to hear it again?)
Let's hear it one more time.
(I am an elephant.)
It's an elephant.
(The elephant trumpets proudly.)
- You sound like an elephant. - That's incredible.
It gives me a headache.
I was so surprised.
(From afar, he looks like an elephant.)
- Let's see the next one. - A gorilla.
(Roaring)
- Wait a minute. - An elephant.
(Trumpeting)
An elephant.
A gorilla.
Three elephants.
My goodness.
He is good.
(Three elephants appear.)
He really sounds like an elephant.
He really sounds like one.
- Acknowledge his talent. - The sound of an elephant.
All right. Sae Ho and Sun Mi will have the final match.
Let's have a match between a cuckoo and an elephant.
Sun Mi, you can't back down.
The elephant impression was quite impressive.
All right.
Run forward.
(Trumpeting)
Wait a minute. This elephant...
- You lost your energy. - Seriously.
- The sound became much smaller. - You need to give it...
- your all now. - You did a great job earlier.
- Sae Ho, drink some water. - You did a great job earlier.
Drink some water.
(He lacks the energy after a vigorous warm-up.)
You really sounded like one earlier.
- Why can't you do it now? - I think I can imitate an elephant.
All right.
- Sun Mi will imitate an elephant. - My goodness.
A female elephant.
(Sun Mi attempts to imitate something other than birds.)
(Trumpeting)
(My goodness.)
A cuckoo.
Her cuckoo impression is incredible.
Can you imitate a cuckoo?
(Can Sae Ho imitate a cuckoo?)
(He makes strange noises.)
(Is he hiccuping?)
Sun Mi wins.
What? Is the match over?
It's over.
I got 10 dollars.
(The master of animal impressions, Sun Mi, gets 10 dollars.)
Sung Hoon.
I will tell you what Sung Hoon's charm is.
You can see his wide shoulders, right?
His charm is the power that comes from them.
(He is the best at his show of strength.)
- Shall we arm wrestle? - Shall we arm wrestle?
- No. King of the Hammer. - King of the Hammer.
- King of the Hammer. - Really?
(Is King of the Hammer the game that will verify Sung Hoon's charm?)
(Let's see if Sung Hoon will take the mission money.)
- Sung Hoon will go first... - Okay.
- since he chose the game. - Let's see it.
Let's see what he can do.
He lacks strength these days because he is on a diet.
No practice round, right?
- There is no practice round. - This is the real round.
This is the real round.
(Good luck, Sung Hoon.)
- It's set. - Is it set?
- It rose up. - Now...
Look at his shoulder blades.
His back is very wide.
He will show us what he can do.
I will give it a go.
You only get one chance.
(Judging by his shoulders, he will probably win.)
(Jong Kook looks nervous.)
(Finally, )
(he lifts up the hammer.)
(Hitting)
- All right. - 5, 6, 7.
(What is the score of the man with wide shoulders?)
(He reaches 13 out of 15 stages.)
- 13. - 13.
13.
Are you okay? Don't your hands hurt?
He reached the 13th stage.
His score is 865.
- 865. - Up next...
- is Kwang Soo. - Okay.
I am excited.
- The current score is 865. - Right.
I heard that he was a gunner in the army.
I hammered in the army for a year.
I can't wait to see his score.
For some reason, he looks cool today.
All right.
You look cool.
(Pausing)
- Did you smile in this direction? - For goodness' sake.
- I heard, "You look cool." - Someone said you looked cool.
I heard it from somewhere.
I am serious.
I will do this with seriousness.
He was a gunner in the army.
A gunner must have hammered a lot of stakes into the ground.
This is a matter of pride.
I will give it a go.
(He is determined to win.)
(Missing)
My goodness.
(You are ridiculous.)
You are ridiculous.
I will try again right away.
- Don't turn it into a comedy skit. - I will try again right away.
- I am serious. - Stop it.
- Here I go. - He shouldn't get a second chance.
- I was so surprised. - This isn't a comedy skit.
- What is going on? - Hey.
No one does that at "Comedy Big League", right?
- No one does. - Here I go.
A comedy skit like this one will get you eliminated.
Here I go.
(Kwang Soo tries for the 2nd time.)
(Hitting)
(He slipped.)
You slipped a little.
(He loses with a score of 817.)
You aren't a man.
(What did you say?)
- Se Chan is strong. - He is a dark horse.
(They aren't aware of the aftermath this match will bring.)
- Thank you for your hard work. - Thank you for your hard work.
Seung Un, would you take a picture for us?
- A picture? Okay. - Yes.
- It's for memories. - Yes.
- Let me get a close-up shot. - Are you ready?
- I will get a close-up shot. - Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
(They ask Seung Un to take pictures for them.)
In 1, 2, 3. In 1, 2, 3.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- She took good pictures. - She really did.
- I like this one. - The image quality is great.
What is this? Isn't that Kwang Soo?
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo is watching them.)
(Kwang Soo has always suffered because of Se Chan.)
(Kwang Soo is out for revenge.)
(What is the ending of this drama?)
Up next is Jong Kook.
- Let's go. - Jong Kook.
- My goodness. - Jong Kook, show them.
(I am Thor.)
(Who is stronger, Sung Hoon or Jong Kook?)
- He is Thor. - Seriously.
This is the final round.
- Please. - Let's go.
- Please. - He is Thor.
- Here I go. - Let's go.
Here I go.
(He hits the target at full power.)
(Let me show you the strength of a tiger.)
- This is the final round. - Please.
He exceeded the previous score.
(Can Jong Kook's score beat Sung Hoon's?)
(It's close.)
- That was close. - That was really close.
That was so close. You were awesome.
- In the end, - It's not possible.
- Sung Hoon wins with 865 points. - That was awesome.
(Mission money statistics)
So that concludes What's Your Charm?
We'll get started with the missions for today.
This is Half and Half Project Part 3: Public Enemy Race.
(Half and Half Project Part 3: Public Enemy Race)
(Public Enemy Race?)
Each week, missions were conducted...
with travel destinations recommended by Running Man members and staff.
When Running Man members win, they get to recommend places.
When the staff wins, we get to put places on the roulette.
(Their fate depends on the roulette.)
(The unlucky Jae Seok was picked...)
(to go to New Zealand's Nevis Swing.)
(So Min was picked to go to Polynesia's Bora Bora...)
(that the members recommended.)
(Which destination will make it to the roulette today?)
This is Half and Half Project Part 3: Public Enemy Race.
Each couple picks 2 balls from a box that contains 16 balls.
Written on the balls are the 14 travel destinations,
1 ball that says "times by 2" and another that says "divided by 2".
"Times by 2" and "divided by 2"?
(Each couple gets to pick 2 balls at random.)
The winner for each round is...
the couple that has the most mission money at the end of the race.
The final destination that goes on the roulette...
is on the ball that the winners chose.
(It all depends on the winning team.)
(Which place will get added during the Public Enemy Race?)
Moreover, the winning couple can buy names on the roulette...
with the earned mission money,
and the guest on the winning team gets a huge reward.
A huge reward?
Before we get started with the race, let's pick the balls.
The guests will come forward on behalf of each couple...
- and pick two ball on the table. - All right.
(The 2 balls will have destinations, plus something about the money.)
(They start picking the balls.)
(Contemplating)
(She's not confident.)
(Their hands...)
(will change their partner's fate.)
Each couple can now check what's inside the balls.
If it's something bad, do you have to go there?
That's right.
What's this?
It has a country on it.
- Really? - Yes.
- This. - It's a good place.
It's good?
(It's So Min's recommendation.)
(Krabi is a beautiful island in Thailand.)
(This is a good start.)
(Oh, dear.)
What's that?
(What's this?)
(Brazil's Insano Water Slide)
(It's the staff's recommendation.)
(You get to experience the thrill of Brazil's Insano Water Slide.)
(Is this real?)
Please.
What is it?
(Indonesia's Mount Bromo-Ijen)
(Welcome to your first ever active volcano.)
(Mount Bromo-Ijen is an extreme tour.)
(It's the staff's recommendation.)
(Why did it have to be this?)
My goodness.
(They have one ball left.)
(This has to be good.)
(They need to halve their mission money?)
It's okay.
(If they don't switch their balls, they get half of the mission money.)
(The class of the unlucky member is not breakable.)
It's okay.
- I'm not good at things like this. - What is it?
(The unlucky Kwang Soo checks his balls as well.)
(How did I get this?)
(He gets to double...)
(his mission money.)
- Is that the best option? - It is.
(All 8 couples check their balls.)
Let's take a picture together.
In 1, 2, 3.
(Please let every day be like today.)
(I'm a lady too.)
(Haha makes something for So Min.)
The colors are so nice.
Okay.
(This is a present for you.)
I got it.
- You got it. - My gosh.
- What's this? - Is this what you meant?
It's on the picture too.
(I'll treat you to lunch, Haha.)
It's cute. Do it for Z Young too.
- It's nice. - Here too.
- I got it. - What's that?
(Here's a gift.)
You can do it on the pictures too.
(This is the beauty of couple races.)
(What are you doing, Sae Ho?)
- It looks like an ID photo. - Why?
- You are standing like this. - Am I?
Look there.
(Who takes pictures with their arms by their sides?)
It looks like an ID photo.
- Does it look okay? - It's an ID photo.
(This is not "Reply 1998".)
(His stiff neck muscle is the problem.)
- Do this. - Press this.
(She tries to make it better.)
(Sae Ho has a way of making pictures look like ID photos.)
- The background faded out. - It looks good.
It looks like you're in a foreign place.
(It just looks like an ID photo. He must be contestant number 1.)
This looks good.
The next location is a restaurant.
There are menus in the two cars.
Each car will take four teams. It's first come, first serve.
(It's either Korean table d'hote or samgyetang.)
(What will the members pick?)
Hurry up, Sun Mi.
- Sun Mi. - Hurry, Sol Bi.
Where do we go?
(They run, thinking this may be a mission.)
Where is it?
- Seung Un. - I'm coming.
- This is Korean table d'hote. - Sun Mi.
It's Korean table d'hote.
Sun Mi.
Sun Mi. It's Korean table d'hote.
- Move. - Go in.
Sun Mi. Hurry.
- Can we all get on? - Jae Seok.
Hurry, Sun Mi.
Hurry. Sun Mi.
This is Korean table d'hote, Jong Kook.
Jong Kook.
Hurry, Sun Mi. Where are you?
You can't do that.
Hurry, Sun Mi.
Wait, Jae Seok.
We have to go to the other car.
- Just go. - It's samgyetang.
Today's a good day for Korean table d'hote,
not samgyetang.
(They're disappointed.)
Everybody went to the other car.
This is a good day for stew and Korean table d'hote.
Look here.
These are all the teams with no mission money.
We're all so poor.
We're the poor ones.
- We still have many chances, right? - No.
- No? - No.
- We eat and go home. - Really?
(I just warmed up, and it's almost over?)
- We're done. - Really?
I didn't do much today.
(He feels bad.)
- You did a lot. - Did I?
I don't think I'm having a good day.
- I don't think you are. - You can tell?
- Wasn't I funny? - In which parts?
You know, this and that. I did a variety of things.
- You barely made it on TV. - Is that so?
You can gather the tiny bits.
We should have gotten Korean table d'hote.
(Let me see.)
- Hey. - Yes?
We can switch it.
We can switch the signs in the front.
(They can change the destinations and head to Korean table d'hote?)
I'll go in the front.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo think of a trick.)
Let's go, Kwang Soo.
Will it work?
(He tries to get in without the other team noticing.)
Move over.
(He gets in...)
(and switches the destinations.)
Sir, can you switch these?
(They haven't noticed at all.)
(They show great teamwork.)
(The bus going to Korean table d'hote...)
(becomes a bus going to samgyetang.)
(Kwang Soo changes the signs at the back too.)
(Sir, please put this on for us.)
Did you change it, Jae Seok?
- I did. - Give him a round of applause.
- You're the best. - Hey.
- Why didn't we... - That's right.
Think of this before?
(Will it be a success?)
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook's buses are switched.)
Let's get started.
Samgyetang is also a Korean table d'hote menu.
- Of course. - It is.
Right now,
the other bus has left.
Jae Seok, who was on the other bus,
changed the menu, so we're on our way to the samgyetang place.
(We're going to...)
(have...)
(samgyetang?)
- Why? - How does that make sense?
(They all complain.)
- Did he rip ours? - He ripped them...
and switched them before leaving.
That's not right.
This is not right. He can't rip it.
Let me call him.
(Let's hear what he has to say.)
Hello?
- Jae Seok? - Yes.
It's Jong Kook.
(Why did Jong Kook...)
(call?)
Yes, I know. I recognize your voice.
I guess you're having Korean table d'hote.
(Why...)
(do you get to go there?)
- Yes, we... - We got on the right bus.
We got on the bus.
- Jae Seok? - Yes.
You'll be on the Korean table d'hote menu.
(You'll be on the Korean table d'hote menu.)
(Stir-fried grasshopper will be on the menu.)
What did he say?
- He'll be on the menu? - What?
Jae Seok is a dish?
I'm sorry, but we...
If you're sorry, why did you do that?
What did we do again?
You better gather some people.
(Why do we have to...)
(gather some people?)
We're on our way to tear the Korean table d'hote place down.
- You're going to tear it down? - We don't want samgyetang.
We'll see you at there then.
Okay. That sounds good.
- That's a way. - Come at us.
Only the people who survive at the restaurant get to eat.
- We'll see you there. - Got it?
Let's do this until the end. Let's get it.
Sir?
(This is Jae Seok's idea in the first place.)
(This is his final decision.)
Sir?
Please go to the samgyetang place.
Why? Don't do that.
Why samgyetang?
- No... - I actually like samgyetang.
- Me too. - I'm serious.
I think...
Jae Seok should gather up some courage...
and head for Korean table d'hote.
(Jae Seok, )
(we believe...)
(in you.)
Okay, then let's go for Korean table d'hote.
Let's do that.
(They all decide to go.)
Why did they get on the bus going to samgyetang?
Exactly.
This won't do.
This upsets me.
- Me too. - I don't eat chicken.
Z Young says she doesn't eat chicken. She's pregnant.
(She's pregnant.)
- I'm not pregnant. - Oh, right.
I'm sorry.
- She's not pregnant. - Why would you say that?
- She doing postpartum care. - Right.
Samgyetang might be really good.
That's right.
We'll have a mission on the bus...
with chances of winning additional mission money.
This mission is called Color Cham, Cham, Cham.
(Color Cham, Cham, Cham)
What is that?
It starts with the coloring book...
on the phones you were given.
(It's a coloring game.)
Press the icon that says, "coloring".
- "Coloring". - Please select...
- the cherry picture. - Cherry?
Yes. You can fill the cherries...
with any two colors you want from the colors above.
If you select the colors different from mine, you win.
- Different from yours? - It has to be different.
The one couple that survives wins five dollars.
(Only 1 couple wins 5 dollars.)
(We need that 5 dollars.)
All right. Please pick your colors for the cherries.
That looks good.
We'll do these two.
(Staff picks green and yellow.)
(They have to pick different colors from the staff to win.)
- Which colors should we pick? - Whatever you want.
- I'll reveal mine. - Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3. - Please.
(Please don't be the same.)
Three.
(He reveals the result.)
- Let me see yours. - Yes.
(Ji Hyo and Sae Ho are out.)
If you have yellow or green, you're out.
- I have yellow. - Me too.
We're safe.
(Kwang Soo and Seung Un are out.)
(Jae Seok and Sun Mi pass.)
Let me see yours.
(They picked purple and blue.)
- Let me see yours. - Okay.
You're all out...
except Jae Seok and Sun Mi.
(Jae Seok and Sun Mi win 5 dollars.)
Thank you.
- We're first place. - They have a lot of money already.
- Thank you, Sung Hoon. - They're rich.
You two are so sweet.
(Is this the So Min we know?)
Right, So Min.
- So Min's eyes are so sweet. - She looks so happy.
I've never earned so much money on Running Man before.
- Really? - Yes.
You don't have to press it.
(He's warm unlike the other guys on Running Man.)
(She draws a heart.)
Why are you drawing a heart?
It's love.
She's so lady-like.
(I want to be a lady today.)
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- We're first place. - They have a lot of money already.
This is our official game on the road.
- Let's play... - All right.
Yu Jae Seok's Game.
I know what this is. I've seen it.
You have to give an irrelevant answer to his questions.
- You've seen it, right? - I have.
The rules are simple.
You have to give three irrelevant answers to my questions.
You cannot ask a question back.
How much money do we get?
- The winner gets 5 dollars. - 5 dollars?
- Five dollars. - Let's win, Sae Ho.
- Okay. - Please.
Let's get started. Who wants to go first?
- Kwang Soo. - Okay, I'll go.
He's good in this.
He's really good.
- Watch. - You're right after him, Sun Mi.
- Okay. - Ready, set, go.
What does Seung Un remind you of?
Sundae and tripe.
(Sundae and tripe)
Wait. Sundae and tripe.
I mean... Is this how it goes?
- This won't work? - Kwang Soo.
- That's possible. - It is.
- This won't work? - It's food.
- I'll give you another chance. - Okay.
That was so funny. What do I do?
- Ready. - Okay.
Set, go. What is your girlfriend's nickname?
Diaper.
(Her nickname is Diaper?)
- She must be really young. - What's wrong?
- How old is she? - What happened?
This is so hard.
You can't think ahead. Elijah is next.
She knows this game. She's practiced.
- No, no. - Be comfortable.
Ready.
Set, go. What is your boyfriend's nickname?
(She's buffering.)
Four.
What is your boyfriend's nickname?
(What should I say?)
Four.
Why did it take you so long?
- Why did you take so long? - Why is it wrong?
You can't take time.
I usually speak slow though.
- No way. - That was slow.
I usually say weird things.
I think Elijah was thinking about her boyfriend.
We might get the wrong idea, so please reply right away.
- Sae Ho. - Ready.
Set, go. What was your nickname as a child?
Thank you for your business.
- What's in your bag? - Pigs' feet.
(Really?)
(Pigs' feet are daily necessities.)
That's how you gain weight.
That's why.
- Can I go again? I'm sorry. - You can try again.
- Let's go. - Let's go. Ready.
Set, go. Please say something to your high school teacher.
Beef tripe.
(It's food again.)
- That's so rude. - Beef tripe.
(Beef tripe must be a part of his memory.)
- But this... - It kind of...
- Is that your teacher's nickname? - makes sense.
This must make his teacher feel bad.
- But I... - That's a rude thing to say.
- My question is... - It might be just a game, but...
- I tear up when I think of them. - Me too.
- I don't like this game. - I won't continue playing.
That's just not right.
- During high school, - His teacher probably feels bad.
Our teacher taught us for three years.
They made us into good people.
Can you edit this out? Because I...
- I think he... - We'll just edit you out entirely.
Just give him a finger flick.
You're going to edit me out entirely?
- Yes. - Can you just erase him?
- You're going to edit me out? - Can you erase him from the bus?
- Erase him. - We can't.
I'll give you one last chance, Sae Ho.
I'm sorry.
Ready. Set, go. Please say something to the director of the department.
You're so indecisive.
(He's unstoppable.)
(You don't cast me in shows. You must be indecisive.)
- How rude. - That was too much.
- Who's indecisive? - Who is?
- The director of the department? - How could you?
I don't think so.
Is it because he doesn't give you offers?
Our director is pretty determined.
He's indecisive.
Let's get started.
- Do you want to go, Sung Hoon? - Okay, I'll try it.
Let's go. Whom do you want to invite to your house?
My bag is small.
How many female celebrities do you have on your phone?
I want to go on the plane.
How does your body look after taking a shower?
(Exclaiming)
(He imagined himself...)
(after taking a shower.)
He thought about it. He was serious.
- He did. - He imagined himself...
after taking a shower.
- Why does it have to be showering? - There must be something special.
- What's wrong with taking a shower? - He's secretive.
- What's wrong with taking a shower? - Were you proud?
- What's there to it? - Is there something?
Let's go again. Go.
What object does So Min resemble?
I want to work out my chest.
What commercials do you want to shoot?
- I want to work out my back. - That startled me.
What body part do you wash first when you take a shower?
(Gosh)
(Is it the shower again?)
What's wrong?
He does this every time the shower comes up.
- What's wrong with taking a shower? - What is it?
He must be traumatized.
Let's say this never happened. Can I go again?
- What's wrong? - There's no progress.
Let's go.
(He gets competitive and tries again.)
What do you do first thing in the morning?
We're going at 60km per hour.
When do you think you look the most handsome?
Hangang Park.
What's the first thing you do after taking a bath?
(Gosh)
(Is it bath this time?)
What do you do?
Don't you weigh yourself?
What do you do after taking a bath?
You look too happy.
Do you get happy?
- Do you get really happy? - I didn't know what to say.
- Does it make you happy? - Z Young, do you want to go?
- Me! I'll go. - Okay.
- Z Young. - Go.
What do you call your husband?
Two white hairs.
Really?
(You call your husband "Two white hairs"?)
- Is that what you call him? - You call him that?
- Why? - That's strange.
Do you think this makes sense?
- Give her another chance. - Of course, it does.
- Hold on. - Give her a chance.
We'll give you another chance.
- Z Young is bad at games like this. - I am.
- Plus, she always finds it unfair. - Listen to the question.
I thought it would be easy, but you know me well.
Let's go again.
My questions were carefully selected.
When were you the happiest after getting married?
50 years from now...
(50 years from now?)
That's great.
You can be happy for 50 years.
That's nice.
(Seok Jin tries to take care of it.)
That's great, Z Young.
I don't even know what I'm saying.
You sound so happy.
- She's happy. - I'm jealous.
I didn't know you would ask that.
(Please live happily with Mr. Two White Hairs.)
- Let's go, Kei. - Okay.
All right.
Which Running Man member did you look forward to meeting?
My real name is Kim Ji Yeon.
Which guest are you most afraid of?
I'm so happy to be Lovelyz.
- When do you think you're cute? - I love you, Running Man.
(I love you, Running Man.)
She's so good.
- This is fun. - She did it.
She's good.
- That's awesome. - Okay.
It is.
Right, you get money.
(The bus is almost at the Korean table d'hote restaurant.)
Most importantly,
Jong Kook should be okay, right?
(He starts to feel anxious as they near their destination.)
Luckily...
We're almost done for today.
- That's right. - He likes it.
- What does he like? - He already beat me up enough.
He should let us switch.
- Of course. - This wasn't a penalty.
He just beat me up. He hit me.
- I watched it. - We can take it to court.
Let me see your arm, Kwang Soo.
- It hurts. - It's still red.
(His arm is swollen.)
(What happened between them?)
(The Couple Race becomes...)
(more intense and fiery.)
(Let's see if you or I win.)
(Which couple will survive this war?)
(Where are you touching, Sae Ho?)
(Don't be mistaken.)
(And)
(Final Race of Half and Half Project )
(Darkness surrounds the Running Man members.)
(Let's start playing a game.)
(They get locked up in a prison without any explanation.)
(Only those who escape can survive the ultimate mission.)
(Final Half and Half Project: Roulette Prison)