(The most dangerous deal in the history of Running Man)
(Resting Place)
If members win in the competition against the staff,
they will be provided the resting place.
However, if the members lose,
one of them has to let their house to be the resting place.
(The last struggle to protect their private area)
(Will they gain something or lose something?)
(How would this dangerous deal end?)
(A spring day in March in Seoul)
Thank you for your hard work...
during the Member's Week.
We will start again with a new race.
Today, there is a new staff member...
- who is also off to a new start. - Really?
(Staff off to a new start?)
It's our youngest staff member, Se Mi.
Se Mi.
(Se Mi is...)
(the energizer and the scene stealer of Running Man.)
(She successfully bid Kwang Soo with 10 dollars.)
(She entertained us with her humor and wit.)
(She is the official vitamin of Running Man.)
She is supposed to be having the last shoot...
- with us today. - Really?
- That's why Se Mi is... - I see.
As it happens, she's moving to another place today,
and we will be helping her to move and make a fresh start.
- Move? - To where?
- Why should we help? - She could do it by herself.
- What do you mean? - We have...
helped celebrities move houses before.
But for the staff?
- It's nice to help out, but... - To what extent should we help you?
I really moved yesterday.
My real house.
- Oh, yes. I heard he did. - He moved again.
- It's my ninth move after marriage. - He went to Sinsa-dong.
- So Hyun Woo moved once every year? - He did.
He has five kids of school uniform.
(We will count on Seok Jin, the expert on moving.)
You'll be competing with the staff as you help out her moving.
What kind of race?
If you win, we will provide Se Mi's previous house...
as your new resting place.
(Resting place for Running Man?)
Are you asking the married men to have two houses at once?
Why does it have to be here? I live in Anyang.
I don't even come here.
You live in Anyang, but you work in Gangnam.
I live in Anyang and work in Gangnam, but why here in Mapo?
For these two, it's a nice spot.
- It would be nice for them. - We live in Mapo.
If these two use the resting place, there will be strange rumors.
It will definitely seem strange.
- Right? - We used to be in a love triangle.
- It might seem strange. - It will.
Nowadays, rumors...
- can be a big deal. - It will be endless.
However, if you lose...
and the staff members win,
one of you has to let your house be the resting place.
- We have one here. - His house will do.
Why are you pointing at me?
- It can't be mine. - I live with my parents.
- Me too. - I have my second baby coming.
- My mother in law... - It's the staff against Kwang Soo.
- It's his race again. - When will this stop?
It's Kwang Soo's week again.
(They visit his house out of the blue.)
(Whenever they visit, they devastate his house.)
(I want this nightmare to end this time.)
- Poor Kwang Soo. - You can't.
I'm actually living with a woman.
I don't live alone anymore.
You can no longer come to my house.
- Don't come to my house. - I know this. We can't go there.
I'm going to kick the camera. Don't you dare come to my place.
- Don't even come near my house. - You can't do this to him anymore.
- He's living with a woman? - Stop it already.
- Right now... - I just moved into that house.
That means we have to win by all means.
- Let's win. - We ought to win.
- It's for Kwang Soo's sake. - We must protect Kwang Soo's place.
We should respect Kwang Soo's privacy.
The house you see behind you is Se Mi's house.
- I see. - We'll head there to help her move.
- Isn't it nice to have a home here? - We have to go around then.
Nowadays, it's quite romantic to live in a neighborhood like this.
- A house on the rooftop? - A rooftop house.
- We're on our way. - That must be it.
- I guess this is it. - It's that yellow building.
- It's right here. - It's here. I see her moving stuff.
- Se Mi. - Se Mi. This is where you lived.
This was your house.
Where are you moving to?
I'm moving to a house within the neighborhood.
- You are? - You are wearing a microphone.
- Se Mi. - Look at you, Se Mi.
- Hey. - You put on a microphone.
- You even wore makeup. - Goodness, Se Mi.
You've fully prepared to be on TV.
- Let's go. - You even washed your hair.
You usually wear hats.
I've been on TV for a long time, but I've never...
- been to a writer's house. - It's my first time too.
- Exactly. - Do we have to go this far?
What's more is that I've never helped a writer with her move.
We might see some things you might be embarrassed about.
All right. Let's get moving first. Se Mi.
- Do you live alone? - It's a lady's house.
- It's a bit awkward. - You should've moved on your own.
- It's a bit embarrassing. - The house seems too good to leave.
- Yes, it is too good to leave. - She's even wearing socks.
(What will the race be?)
Did you say she's wearing socks?
Do we go up one more floor?
- Yes, we do. - It must be the rooftop house.
- It's a house you see on dramas. - It does look like one on TV.
- It's a rooftop house! - It's quite charming.
Really?
- Se Mi, is it the rooftop house? - Yes, it is.
- This is nice. - It's charming.
The view here is awesome too.
- It's amazing here. - Here it is.
- You really lived here? - It's a scene from a drama.
(Sky is the ceiling of this romantic rooftop house.)
You can even raise something on the roof.
That will make a nice slide.
There's even a garden.
This is romantic.
- Rooftop houses can be... - We have fantasies about it.
- I agree. - It's really nice.
- Everyone wants to live here once. - This is...
- I want to live here with friends. - So do I.
- We can have a barbecue party. - Right.
- You can even raise a dog. - You can raise a big dog.
- Shall we go in now? - It's this way.
- I've been to a coworker's house. - Right.
- I haven't been to a writer's home. - This is the first time.
Somehow, I feel shy about this.
- Se Mi, you have a clean house. - This is nice.
- Can we go in? - Can we?
This is a cool place.
- You can use this for a drama set. - It's charming.
- It's romantic. - I haven't seen that kind of TV.
- The name tag I signed is there. - Where?
- Where? - Gosh.
- They are Jae Seok and Kwang Soo's. - There they are.
- She doesn't have ours. - She doesn't have the rest.
Se Mi.
- Isn't this really an old TV? - It is.
- I bought this when I first... - I really like this place.
started living on my own. I still watch it.
- Do you really? - Yes, I do.
I haven't seen this kind of TV for so long.
- It works. - No way.
- Do you have a remote control? - Yes. It's right there.
- We can even replay this. - Seriously?
- Look. It's working. - It's better than one in my house.
(It's a unique combination of the old and new.)
She has so many books since she is a writer.
(Books are the must-have items for a writer.)
Hey, I think Se Mi plays guitar.
- What? - Do you play guitar?
- Do you really? - I guess she does.
No way.
- Se Mi, you do play guitar. - It's nice.
The color of her blankets is similar to Kwang Soo's blankets.
- The curtain is nice too. - It is similar to his.
By the way, we get to see Se Mi's stuff.
Her place is quite clean.
- Take your time. - Did you clean it?
- Did you cook a lot too? - What a cute place.
- It's cute and cozy. - I did. I have the rice cooker.
- She has a rice cooker for 1. - Yes, it's for 1 person.
How cute.
The rice cooker is really cute.
- This is how she cooks for herself. - That's correct.
- If she lives alone... - You take care of your body a lot.
- I do. - What are these?
- What are those? - You eat herbal medicine.
- She should. - She ought to have them.
She needs to when she lives alone.
You froze the food waste. You are good at housekeeping.
- Where is that? - She did freeze the food waste.
- Really? - She did?
Hold on. So we have to move everything in here?
We will start moving now.
This is your first mission.
There is a mission?
There are five things Se Mi will dispose of...
when she moves into her new house.
She will throw them out?
I already know what it's going to be.
Your mission is to put everything on the van except the five things.
In order to accomplish your mission,
you must be able to find at least 3 out of 5 things.
- This is... - Things she will discard?
Let's decide on this TV.
We should...
- This is... - We should throw this out.
- No, I think... - Let's get rid of it.
she wants to take this.
- This TV? - I think she wants to bring it too.
- It's because... - You think so?
this is the very first TV she bought when she started to live on her own.
- It is? - This has a sentimental value.
- It could be her guitar. - Is it the bed?
She might throw out the guitar.
- How about the doll? - Could it be the bed?
It's the doll her ex-boyfriend gave.
- She will take the bed, right? - The bed?
- The bed is quite small. - Clothes?
- Will she discard her clothes? - Clothes...
Hey, but isn't this too challenging for a mission?
- How can we read her mind? - Five things?
Don't you think she's going to throw out this curtain?
- Won't she definitely throw it out? - That curtain is...
I think the curtain came with the house.
- No, I think she put this up. - She installed the curtain.
- I have a feeling it's the bed. - You think so too?
I am not so certain.
This is too difficult.
- Won't she throw out this charcoal? - This doll?
- The charcoal? - This is...
I think she will throw this out.
Why would she? She can keep it at home.
She has to buy new one.
- It's collecting dust. - It gets dusty.
Why would this be here?
- That doesn't fit in here. - Doesn't it look out of place?
- It does look like it. - Does it go with this one?
These two don't match the rest of the furniture.
It's a bit wasteful to throw out the chair.
- I think she has a story behind it. - I bet she will throw this out.
- Let's move these first. - Let me get the boxes.
Shall we start with the floor?
- Hey, let's hurry. - It's in there.
- All right. - This is...
(They start with Ji Hyo's sign.)
We will take out these books now.
- Right, the books. - Get me a box.
She still has this book on Stanislavski. I have one too.
What did you say?
Stanislavski.
- Se Mi. - Yes?
Did you major in theater?
I majored in playwriting.
I knew it. I figured you did since you had this book on Stanislavski.
- I see. - So you know about Stanislavski.
- Stop it. - It's driving me crazy.
- Let me tell you about acting... - Come on.
- If you majored in acting... - You said his name so many times.
We only need to know Tchaikovsky.
- Unbelievable. - Stanislavski was...
Knowing Tchaikovsky is enough.
Se Mi. What a shame I didn't know about this sooner.
She has "Status Anxiety" by Alain de Botton.
- I like this writer. - Goodness.
- Se Mi. - Hey, Se Mi.
- I'm going to pack this. - All right.
- I'm going to pack this. - Sure. Go ahead.
Se Mi. Don't just stand there. Help us.
- You don't need these clothes yet. - Pass me that box.
- Can you pass me that box? - All right.
Se Mi. Can you give us a hint for us? Just one hint.
- Shall I give you a hint? - Yes.
I'm so busy that I don't have time to work out.
(She doesn't have time to work out?)
(Does it mean she will throw out things related to her exercise?)
- It's the scale. - That's right.
- It must be the scale. - Yes, it has to be the scale.
The scale is a way to check if she gained weight or not.
- It stresses her out. - You can't throw this out.
- But this is... - She should always check.
Or it could be her running shoes.
The reason why I thought it could be the scale is...
- It's been so long it had been on. - It doesn't work.
- Really? - We'll throw it out.
- Let's get going. - Hey, let's take this.
All right. Give me another box.
- We need slippers for this job. - This is heavier than it looks.
(They start moving her things.)
- In 1, 2... - Okay.
- Hey. - What?
How about throwing out the name tags?
It's because she's leaving Running Man now.
- That doesn't sound right. - Let's get rid of it.
- Do you want to throw these out? - She had to give it to her friend.
Se Mi. I signed this in February, 2016. It's been too long.
I haven't met my friend yet.
- When are you going to see her? - When will you meet her?
- You're moving now. - You don't see your friends.
How could you have not given Da Hae this? I signed this in 2016.
- She's waiting, but I couldn't. - Really?
- Just throw this out. - You should see your friends.
Just throw this away since you are moving.
- Will she take this? - What?
Don't you think she will leave this here?
- I think she will want that. - You think so?
Se Mi. Is there a story behind this chair?
My mom bought this to congratulate me on living alone.
- Your mom bought it? - Yes.
Since your mom bought this for you, it's meaningful.
Don't you like this chair?
(Sure, I like it.)
(I will put this on. I trust you.)
This has to be then.
- We have to bring this out. - Hold on.
We have to unload that thing. Why are we taking that?
- Take what? - That chair.
- We have to take that chair. - No, we shouldn't.
Hey, that chair...
- It's expensive. - It has memories.
Her mom bought it for the 1st time when she was 20 years old.
Is she on good terms with her mom?
Haha. She said they get along well.
We have to take this, right?
I have a feeling about this washing machine.
Let's take the washing machine.
- Should we? - No, she won't take it.
It's possible that she might not want to take it.
Will she take the vacuum?
- Check if it works. - Hold on.
- I'm looking at this... - See if it works or not.
- and this is way too dusty. - Did someone give this to her?
- Look at this part. - Exactly.
Doesn't that imply that she doesn't use this?
This does work, but it doesn't work well.
- This vacuum. - It is too dusty.
- It's dusty. - It doesn't work.
They can't even suck in the hair.
- Are you sure it's hair? - Get rid of this.
- She has to throw this out. - If she doesn't, she has a problem.
- This has to be trashed. - It doesn't work.
- She won't need it. - It's broken. She can't use it.
Leave it.
- Let's leave it. It's weird. - I think it's right to leave it.
It's because Se Mi...
- She's taking the fan. - It works.
(I have to find something to prove my capability.)
- Guitar. - Why is it here?
(Let me see.)
(He gazes at something while they struggle.)
(While everyone is busy,)
(he is investigating alone.)
What are some things here?
She will definitely take things like this mirror.
Of course, she will.
It's a chipmunk.
- We should take the mirror. - I've been watching you.
- Seok Jin, please work. - Wait, Seok Jin.
- Wait a minute. - What's wrong?
I've been watching Seok Jin.
- He doesn't work. - Look.
When we go out of the room, he goes into the room.
When we come back, he leaves the room.
- He doesn't do anything. - Come on, Seok Jin.
- I'm trying to be efficient. - Seriously.
- That's why I'm instructing. - Seok Jin, come and carry this.
- Come here, Seok Jin. - He's not doing any work.
Come and carry this.
I'm helping now.
(He barely works.)
Seok Jin.
What are you doing with that?
(He pretends to work.)
Why don't you take a nap if you have nothing to do?
- What are you doing? - He's going back and forth.
Goodness.
He moved recently, and his wife begged him to stay outside.
- There's nothing to clean. - What do you mean?
- There's so much to clean. - What should I do with this?
She hasn't packed up her clothes. We're in trouble.
(The room is still full of things.)
(It's very messy.)
(Is it time to take initiatives?)
(She starts to work efficiently.)
Se Mi.
She packed some things.
(Things pile up.)
(Ji Hyo takes care of packing.)
(Ji Hyo will help you move with the best service and hard work.)
Okay, Seok Jin.
- Yes? - Take these outside instead.
- Those? - Yes.
These are fragile, so be careful.
Okay.
- Ji Hyo is doing well. - She's so detailed.
- That's good, Ji Hyo. - Thank you, Jae Seok.
(Men carry things outside.)
- Take them out. - Where's Seok Jin?
He's moving the washing machine.
He's exaggerating again.
(He's trying to do the impossible.)
(He takes a peek.)
(I'm moving the washing machine.)
- Look at him. - He's showing off.
- No, I'm not. - He's pretending again.
He knows it's impossible to move it by himself.
He's being conscious of the camera.
Did you make an eye contact with him?
He's not even moving it. This is what he's doing.
(Exact eye contact with the camera)
(He pretends not to look at the camera.)
How can I move it? It's stuck.
Let him move the washing machine.
Let Seok Jin take care of the washing machine.
He'll be there until we finish moving everything out.
(Jae Seok is too smart.)
There was a man like him in the army.
(Seok Jin reminds him of someone.)
I remember those days.
(He reminds you of old memories.)
Come here and move it outside.
What's this?
She might leave it here.
Don't think that just because you don't want to move it.
(He's extremely lazy.)
Don't you think she'll leave it here?
This may be the case for new apartments.
(He starts to talk again.)
The former owner left the curtains.
(It seems like he procrastinates too much.)
- What? - You should do some work.
No one asked you to give a lecture.
What we take is more important.
Get us some water.
- Bring us some water. - Get it yourself.
Everyone, have some water.
- Can we drink it? - Get out of the way, Seok Jin.
Stop getting in the way.
(He gets in the way.)
You asked me for water.
Gosh, he gets in the way all the time.
(Seok Jin starts to do something.)
Turn it like this.
(He's unstable.)
- It doesn't fit. - Wait.
Get out of the way, Seok Jin.
(His lack of experience is obvious.)
- It works if you turn it. - What's the fuss?
(He causes more trouble than help.)
- Keep going. - Holding at the bottom is better.
(He doesn't help at all.)
My goodness.
(He's a nightmare.)
You should hold it like this.
He doesn't do any work.
(Seok Jin only talks.)
There's so much to do, but you aren't doing anything.
- She bought it to fit... - No.
the window size.
- Wait. What should we do? - It's too big.
She took it off.
It's because she wants to take it.
She had to take it off before moving out.
I think she used the same thing in the other room.
It's strange that there are no curtains.
- The blinds are difficult to fit. - We should take them.
What's this? Wait a minute.
Doesn't she exercise at home?
(Jong Kook is happy to find a pink yoga mat.)
Does she exercise at home?
- No, that's not it. - Look.
- Let's throw it away. - She said she doesn't exercise.
- Let's throw it away. - This could be it.
(The second possible item is a yoga mat.)
Let me see. What's that?
(Will she throw it away?)
She won't throw this away.
Se Mi.
- Take the towel. - Are you taking the charcoal?
(Jae Seok is suspicious of the charcoal.)
Se Mi, what are these?
I wear those slippers at home.
Have you used them?
(They look quite old.)
She won't take them.
Do you want to take them or not?
I have to take them.
- You want to take them? - I'll wear them.
Everyone, keep this in mind.
- What? - Se Mi said she'll use them.
- These look unused for a long time. - I don't believe it.
You can use after washing them.
Se Mi, just throw them out.
(We'll get you another pair.)
I'll buy you a new pair.
- What about these? - How about the shoes?
Can we pack them carelessly? They'll get mixed anyway.
Do you want to keep these?
(What's the point in asking?)
(She didn't wear them for a long time.)
- Will you wear them? - Aren't these props?
Ask her if she'll wear them.
Come on.
You don't throw things away, do you?
- Se Mi. - Don't wear them.
- These are too old. - You should throw them away.
You can wear these if you wash them.
Se Mi doesn't wear them.
- Please throw away these boxes. - She wants to take them.
Why do you keep the shoe boxes?
She stores things inside.
Se Mi collects alcohol bottles too.
- Leave her alone. - She's strange.
- Why do you collect these boxes? - She wants to take them too.
Look.
(These are the worst.)
(They look older than Se Mi.)
(They're pink sandals.)
(She likes those shoes.)
Everything is precious to her.
My mother used to wear them in the 60s.
- They're her great-grandmother's. - They're ancient.
My mom wore sandals like these in the 60s.
Please throw them away.
- Se Mi, please. - She wants to take them.
(The sandals look ancient.)
- She wants to take them. - Come on, Se Mi.
My mom wore sandals like these when she was young.
How can you keep these?
They're worn out.
- Throw them away. - They're vintage.
These are too raggedy.
(They can't accept them.)
- Throw them away. - She wants to keep them.
You'd better wear them!
Let her keep them.
They might be meaningful to her.
- What are you talking about? - Wait.
What's this?
- Se Mi. - Is it a snake?
Se Mi, what's this?
I don't know.
- Why do you have it? - Is it from the washing machine?
Are you throwing away the washing machine?
I found it in the house.
(Se Mi's rooftop house is full of mysteries.)
- It reminds me. - This was buried in the drain.
It was standing like this.
I've seen this a long time ago.
(It's incredible.)
(Her rooftop house is full of collections.)
Will she leave the trash bin?
- What? - The trash bin.
This is what I do when I move. Think about it, Ji Hyo.
Most people get a new trash bin when they move to a new place.
It's for a fresh start.
Isn't this too old?
That's not the only thing.
(She's too frugal.)
Let's move the refrigerator.
- Wait. - Let's move it.
(They move the refrigerator that's big and heavy.)
(They also move the washing machine.)
How did you take it out?
- Why couldn't you do it? - That's great.
- That's unbelievable. - In 1, 2.
- Let's lift it. - Okay.
(They move the furniture...)
(that filled Se Mi's old house.)
It's good for Jong Kook who wanted to carry heavy things.
- I know. Do I leave it here? - Yes.
(Seok Jin is on the truck.)
(He continues to talk while working.)
Are we almost done?
(They finish moving out as a team.)
(It looks almost empty.)
Did you leave the five items?
- These look similar. - That's not the one.
(It's time to choose five items to throw away.)
No one ever takes blinds when they move out.
- They don't fit. - Leave them here.
- Here you go. - The vacuum doesn't work.
They won't fit the window.
- She doesn't exercise, right? - No.
(The third item is a pink yoga mat.)
I don't think Se Mi would throw this away.
Of course, she won't throw it away.
- She'll take everything. - I saw her old sandals.
- She won't throw away anything. - This is what will happen.
Once she checks these five items,
she'll take them with her at night.
- I think so. - She'll wake up at night.
She'll come back in the middle of the night.
- That's possible. - I'm being serious.
(Who will win the first mission?)
Let's check the answer.
Here's Lee Se Mi.
(Here's the owner of the house.)
- Here's our writer. - Please come this way.
She won't take the scale.
- Right. - Among the five items,
take the ones you need.
(These are the items Running Man members chose.)
(More than 3 must be what Se Mi wants to throw away.)
Is there any?
Throw it away.
- It's broken. - It doesn't work.
(She takes the old trash bin and the vacuum.)
(They're precious to her.)
- It doesn't work. - Just throw them away.
(It's time to let it go.)
- It doesn't work. - Yes, it does.
- The vacuum doesn't work. - Come on, Se Mi.
It's pointless to use it.
(She's extremely frugal.)
Will she throw away these three items?
- Are we correct? - The three items are correct.
(They clear the first mission.)
- I don't believe it. - Thank goodness.
- Why isn't she taking that? - Among the five items,
she took the two oldest ones.
I don't understand.
- Why would you not take this? - It's brand new.
- Why aren't you taking this? - This is...
I got it as a gift, but I never used it.
- All right. - What are the last two?
Isn't that garbage bin better?
It's the drawer in the shape of a rabbit.
- The one that was here? - Yes, it was there.
That's right. I saw it.
The house I'm moving into is slightly smaller than this.
- It didn't fit. - You have no space.
- It was messy. - Right.
- What about the last one? - It was charcoal.
- I thought it was the nicest one. - Charcoal!
See? I told you.
- Who would take charcoal? - Hold on.
We won anyway. Why are you upset?
- He's right. - We won, so why are you upset?
You're not mad, but I am for some reason.
- What are you doing? - He usually gets mad.
We were happy that we won.
- We should be celebrating. - I agree.
- He's right. - That's right.
- You're so calm. - Of course.
- We have a long way to go. - You're right.
Why aren't you taking the scale?
- It's new. - I don't think...
it fits.
The numbers have nothing to do with your health.
- It doesn't. - They have nothing to do with it.
- People are mistaken. - You're too...
- What? - She said she's leaving it.
- But many people... - You don't have to be so mad.
- I guess you're right. - That's right.
- Don't be so mad. - They're making our lives easier.
- Don't you agree? - It's peaceful.
- Right. - Keep talking it out.
- You don't have to be mad. - I agree.
None of us told him this in seven years.
- Don't you agree? - I guess I do.
- That's right. - We never asked him...
why he always gets mad.
What he said about the charcoal was right.
He was right. I agree with you.
I agree too.
You have successfully completed your first mission.
You have obtained 30 Running Balls.
- Okay. - That's exciting.
- Let's move on. - Okay. Let's go.
- Here we go. - You haven't unpacked yet, right?
- Here we go. - It's a new house.
There isn't much to clean here.
We did it in one shot.
That was...
simple.
- She doesn't have much. - That was faster than I thought.
- That's right. - I want jjajangmyeon.
That sounds good.
I want jjamppong.
Let's have jjamppong.
- I don't know which one I want. - I'm craving it.
Kwang Soo.
(They arrive at Se Mi's new house.)
Jjajangmyeon, jjajangmyeon
This is where she's moving in.
It's...
(There are warm, brick houses and a nice street.)
(It's Se Mi's home.)
Look behind you.
- This is Se Mi's new house. - It's this one?
Your second mission will be happening on your way inside.
It's a mission that has to do with moving customs...
in order to wish her the best luck at her new place.
You must piggyback one member, and their feet can't touch the ground.
You must pass 4 stations in 99 seconds.
At the first station, you must drink salt water. It means to purify.
- We can't just drink water? - Salt water?
- You must pick salt water. - Kwang Soo should do it.
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors. - Go, Kwang Soo.
At the second station, you must throw your shoe in the basket.
At the third station, you must break a gourd with your bottom.
At the last station, you'll be given a question about an object.
You have to enter the house with that object.
You have 99 seconds to complete the mission.
- You have three chances. - I think we can do it.
We can do it.
We'll do a good one.
- Who are we? - Please choose the order.
The salt water station should be done by the unlucky ones.
- That sounds good. - It should be one of us.
- Let's decide. - Rock, paper, scissors!
- It's you. - Do it.
The unlucky one should be doing this.
(Kwang Soo is the unluckiest one here.)
Ready.
We can do it.
Get ready. Set...
(They get ready for "Moving Customs Relay".)
(If they don't win 30 Running Balls, they have to give up their house.)
Get ready. Set...
You have to hurry.
(Is that salt water?)
- Good job. - Is that right?
(Is it salt water or just water?)
(He drinks regular water.)
I knew it. He...
Time's ticking. You must drink salt water.
- It's regular water. - He fails again.
No wonder he's the unlucky one.
Kwang Soo.
Yes, Jae Seok. Hold on.
(It's his third attempt.)
- What's going on? - What's wrong with you?
What do you think you're doing?
You're supposed to drink salt water.
- This won't do. - What's wrong with you?
(What about his fourth try?)
That's right.
It's so salty!
(He passes the 1st station.)
(Next station is throwing a shoe into a basket.)
- Hold this. - Hurry. Hurry.
- Hurry. - You have to be precise.
- Slow down. - Here I come, Ji Hyo.
(They only have 15 seconds left.)
- In 1, 2, 3. - You have to get this.
(Take it, Ji Hyo.)
(Don't worry, Haha.)
(Please...)
- Oh, dear. - Hey.
(That's a home run.)
You were supposed to move faster, Seok Jin.
- Aim here, Haha. - You got it.
- We got it. - Goodness.
(Haha has a bad aim and Seok Jin has weak legs.)
That was a good one.
You are driving me nuts.
Let's focus on the next try.
What's wrong with Seok Jin and Kwang Soo?
Why did you keep missing salt water?
He's really unlucky.
- You're really unlucky. - I'll get it in one try.
It's not supposed to be hard.
- This is difficult. - It's not.
We need you to move faster, Mr. Jee.
I'm trying my best.
- You have to go lower. - He sounds mad.
Why are you calling me like that?
- Mr. Jee. - Aren't you mad?
This is a formal occasion, Mr. Jee.
Let's go.
We can do it.
Set...
(This is their second attempt.)
Let's go. Drink salt water.
- What's wrong with you? - Look at him.
(What's wrong with you?)
- This is strange. - I'll get it this time.
Look at the color. Open your eyes!
(It's just water again.)
- You punk. - Look at the color.
(His eyes move back and forth.)
- What's wrong with me? - What's he doing?
You can do it.
- That's salt. - I think it's the one on the right.
It's the right one. I can see it from far away.
(What about now?)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
My mouth is salty, so I can't tell. Try it. Is it salt water?
(It's salt water.)
- Hey. - Hurry.
This is the most difficult part.
Move fast.
- Give me the rope. - Mr. Jee.
- Lower yourself. - Let's go.
- Give me a good throw. - Lower yourself more.
- That's too far. - Move back.
- That's too far. - You have the other shoe, Haha.
- We can do it. - You have to get it.
- I'll give you a good throw. - You have to get it.
- Hey. - Hey.
(That was an out-of-the-park homer.)
- Why would you throw it so far? - Okay, sorry.
What are they even doing?
Are you playing a game amongst the four of you?
How many seconds? All right.
(Would it be over at the 2nd station again?)
You should have moved.
(Is the 2nd station the hardest?)
- Ji Hyo. - Why are you giving bad throws?
- Let's switch. - Move back, Haha.
Okay. Can you try this?
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Set...
(This is their last attempt.)
(Gagging)
(He drinks salt water on his first try.)
He's the best.
Stop faking it.
(It's the 2nd station again.)
Pass her over, Seok Jin.
- Come over. - You let go of me too early!
Don't rush.
- Seok Jin. - Seok Jin.
- That wasn't nice. - Let's go.
- Use 2 hands. - Get it in 1 try.
I'm ready.
(It's the same pitcher but with a better catcher.)
(He kicks his shoe.)
(We'll get it this time for sure.)
It looks good.
- Shoot. - Use your left shoe.
(That was close.)
Oh, dear. It's driving me nuts.
What are you doing, Seok Jin?
(Please help us.)
- We did it. - What are you doing?
(They finally pass the second station.)
- Hurry. - Who is it? Is it you?
(They get to the 3rd station on their 3rd try.)
Hey. There you go.
- There you go, Kwang Soo. - Okay.
- Do it in one try. - Oh, dear.
(Cracking)
There you go.
(That was a hard drop.)
(She can feel the pain radiating in her bottom.)
(It started in Mapo-gu,)
(and it's shaking up the entire Seoul.)
(It shook the entire Earth.)
- There you go. - Are you all right?
(Thank you for your sacrifice.)
- Are you all right? - I have to give her a piggyback?
Come here, Ji Hyo.
- What's the question. - Give me the question.
- Here's the question. - Is it just for him?
There's an object that's supposed to give you good luck...
if you move into a new place with it.
Find that object and enter the house.
- I have to find it? From here? - What is it?
- What is it? - You have to find it?
- What is it? - Ji Hyo.
Shoes?
(Shoes?)
(What do you bring to a new place?)
- Clock. - What could it be?
- Rice. Isn't this a rice cooker? - Is it here?
- Rice cooker. - Are you sure?
- It is. - It is. I saw it somewhere.
- Really? - I saw it on "I Live Alone".
- All right. - That's what they did.
- Go. - Hurry. Let's go.
- It's a rice cooker. - I think you're right.
- I'm 100 percent sure. - It's right.
- He's right. - Rice cooker.
(They choose a rice cooker.)
(Please... Please...)
Correct.
(Rice is supposed to give you wealth in cultures that eat mainly rice.)
- How did you get it right? - How did you know?
I remember watching it.
(They have 60 Running Balls total, and the staff has 20.)
It's time for lunch.
- There must be more. - Can you take the menu?
It's not a normal menu.
Can you just let us eat?
Don't do this.
(They're really annoyed.)
(They get food according to missions.)
You can't do this on a moving day.
- Let us eat. - This...
We have to eat Set C.
- We have to eat Set B at least. - Set C.
Here are the rules.
It's simple. Do you recognize this?
Is it just once?
If the pirate pops up before you complete a cycle, you get Set A.
- Complete a cycle, Set B. - Set B.
If you complete two cycles, it's Set C.
- Should I go? - Yes.
On your side?
(Jong Kook goes for it.)
(He does it easily.)
(He laughs at the next person to go.)
If the pirate pops up now, I'll be so mad.
- I'll be okay. - I'll stab you with this.
That won't happen.
(I trust you.)
(He always lost in this game.)
(He always makes the pirate pop out.)
(Would he do it again?)
(Clicking)
(Kwang Soo passes.)
- We only have to do it 12 times. - That's right.
- This is nothing. - They were being nice to us.
- This is nothing. - It's not.
You need to be confident with this.
(Jae Seok is the next unluckiest one after Kwang Soo.)
(How is he today?)
See?
(Jae Seok passes.)
Just put it in. There you go.
(Seok Jin passes as well.)
We're good.
(Ji Hyo passes as well.)
- We only have to do it once more. - It's Set B.
Let's go for Set C.
(The pirate pops up.)
(He's guilty.)
Hey!
(You punk!)
(There's no sweet and sour pork, or seafood platter for them.)
Why would you do that? It's you, Jong Kook.
I was going to do the other one, but I picked this one.
- Why would you do that? - Hey.
So we can't have sweet and sour pork?
- You can't. - Can we still have Set B?
My gosh. We almost had it.
- I can't reach the fried rice. - We could have had Set C.
I can smell it.
You're supposed to eat this on moving days.
- It's tasty. - It's delicious.
But seriously, Seok Jin...
is eating too much compared to how little he did.
I agree.
I worked so hard.
Remember when we were moving the washing machine?
(He pretended like he was helping.)
Is the jjamppong good?
(Jjajangmyeon and jjamppong are always good on moving days.)
It's really good.
(It's tasty.)
The soup is good.
(What is the next mission that's waiting for them?)
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
(It's time to do work now.)
Let's move the furniture.
What's this?
There's something here.
The saying goes, if you organize your furniture...
according to topography, they'll bring you luck.
- That's right. - I've heard it.
Bed, sofa, mirror, desk, flower pot, and a desk lamp.
There are six items.
They are essential parts of topography.
Place them wherever you think fits best.
We have invited an expert who'll verify your answers.
A topography expert?
- Here you are again. - Hello.
You told me not to do anything.
(It's Park Sung Joon, the fortune teller.)
(He's a fortune telling idol star, known for his cutting remarks.)
(You should stay low.)
You were so funny. You made us laugh.
I got a cramp.
(Slipping)
(He had his funny side behind his analytic skills.)
(He's Running Man's favorite fortune teller.)
Weren't you the one who got cramps?
(He's returns, looking healthier.)
- Did you get home safely? - Yes.
- He was sitting down for a while. - He collapsed.
If you get 4 out of 6 right, you win.
- Just four? - Do we bring them in?
Shouldn't Seok Jin and I stay still?
- Why? - He told us to.
- You can't. - He told us not to do anything.
You have to stay low.
Get started.
When we go into a house,
we know how beds are usually placed.
Let's just think simply.
Let's take them inside.
(He's stealth.)
(He sneaks in.)
(Seok Jin goes inside with light hands.)
It's good because it's the first floor.
Seok Jin.
- Is he just holding that? - It's just a flower pot.
How could he just take that?
Isn't that selfish?
- Are you holding that by yourself? - I'm okay.
- He is. - I'm all right.
Hold on.
- A mirror should be in the front. - Is it this way?
Do we go this or that way?
- This way. - This way is right.
- In front of the bed... - I would put it in the middle.
You have to face the window.
Isn't it supposed to be by your head?
You're supposed to face the curtain.
The sun shines this way.
Aren't you supposed to face the sun?
No, I think the head should face this way.
It should be this way.
That's what most people do.
Once you walk in,
aren't you supposed to see the headboard?
You're supposed to face it this way.
- This way? - Isn't that what people do?
Look at the power outlet.
This is where you place the television.
It's either of these two. It's this...
- or that. - It's this way.
- It looks stable. - I think it's this way.
- No, it is not. - No,
- the head goes this way. - That's where the head goes.
- No, it's not. - Shouldn't you face the window?
You're supposed to place the headboard...
- by the window. - No, no.
- Let's just hide the bed. - This is right.
I'm sure this is right.
- Let's just try it. - It's this way.
It's good.
- Where's the headboard? - This is not it.
- One person holds while one lifts. - I'll lift.
It's supposed to be the opposite.
(Haha is the expert here.)
- This is basic. - And then...
I think it's right.
Isn't this what people do?
- This is right. - I'm sure.
- This is right. - Is it?
This is what I would do.
- This is right. - Really?
- Would you set it there? - You have to face the window.
- Would you do it there? - The head would go this way.
Like this?
You can place the bed here and have the television there.
Let's try it.
I would do that.
(Should we try it?)
Is this it?
This looks good.
It's not bad, right?
We changed our minds.
What's this now?
- It looks good. - Isn't this better?
What do you think?
You can leave things here.
Rather than arguing over where the headboard goes,
let's think about what people commonly do.
This is the middle ground.
This looks good.
We don't know where to put the sofa.
We have to move the sofa.
Put it here.
(Let's see what they did.)
(Did they place the bed right according to topography?)
I think the desk should go in this room.
- I agree. - Can we put the sofa in this room?
Hey. Move the desk.
- Let's move it. - It has to go in the room.
- The desk goes in this room. - You're right.
- Let's put it here. - Put it in the room.
Why would you put it there?
This is it.
- This is where you do work. - This is it. Put it down.
There you go. This is it.
Like this? There you go.
- It looks all right. - It's not bad.
Right. We have a desk lamp as well.
We can put it there.
(Should we move it by the bed?)
(She places it by the headboard.)
Se Mi.
This... Se Mi.
(Haha sets up the sofa by himself.)
You can place a carpet here and hang out with your friends.
I'm serious.
You can make a home theater here.
That's a good idea.
(She answers reluctantly.)
(Right? Isn't this great?)
What are you doing?
I think it'll be nice to put the television here.
What are you talking about?
- Who would do that? - I'm serious.
It might not be right according to topography...
- Move. Get lost. - You're wrong.
That doesn't make any sense.
Is this a hip-hop music video?
You can place the projector there.
- Move. - That's the new style.
- Put it here. - It goes there. What did I say?
It goes here, and you watch the television.
- No, Seok Jin. Look. - Is that right?
- Place the television here. - How would you do it?
Place the television here,
and you can welcome your visitors.
Who watches the television like this?
This is how you watch it.
Why don't you...
just set it up however you want and live here?
- That's not it. - Come on.
- Don't you get it, Jae Seok? - Let's just do it.
- Where do I put this? - I think the flower...
- should face the entrance. - I agree.
I think it goes here.
- What about this side? - I think this is right.
- What about the mirror, Ji Hyo? - Where should we put it?
It goes here.
You shouldn't see the mirror as soon as you walk in.
Why shouldn't it be there?
He says you shouldn't be able to see it when you open the door.
Why not?
This is good. Look.
- That's a good place. - It's by the bathroom.
You can look at yourself before going out...
- and leave. - Put it there.
- Have you made up your mind? - Put it on the floor.
We made up our minds.
How many do we have to get right?
You must get at least 4 out of 6.
That's not easy.
(How many did they get right so far?)
How does it look?
I watched you as you placed the items.
What Haha said...
- was mostly wrong. - Right.
(Everything Haha said was wrong.)
What's wrong with him?
(Haha was being bossy with his loud voice.)
I'm being serious.
(He was too ambitious without much knowledge.)
(He pretended to know feng shui.)
(He was only a fool.)
Who puts the sofa here and faces that way?
(Wasn't it sensible?)
- That's only what you like. - That's my thought for Haha.
Half of what Jong Kook said was correct.
I was wrong half of the time.
On the other hand, Jae Seok and Ji Hyo...
were almost always correct.
However, you couldn't stay with the plan.
They wouldn't listen to me.
- I agreed with them. - I couldn't stay with the plan.
- How should we arrange things? - We can cooperate.
- Right? - That's why we're a team.
We must work as a team, not as individuals.
- We're a team. - A team.
Among the six items,
there's only one that was correctly arranged.
- Only one? - It must be the bed.
There was one more that was close to being correct.
- It was correct by 70 percent. - There are 2.
In other words, you correctly arranged 1.7 items.
- We failed. - What about in the bedroom?
In the bedroom...
(They arranged 3 items in the bedroom.)
(Nothing was arranged correctly.)
- Nothing was correct. - I knew it.
I told you it should be over there.
The room looks great though.
- Starting now, - It should be over here.
you have five minutes to rearrange.
- The flowers are correct. - Get out of the way.
The bed isn't in the right place.
(Jae Seok raises his voice thanks to the feedback.)
Who put the camera here?
- It was in the corner. - We should move the bed.
(Some of them lower their voices.)
Get out of the way.
- It's the bed. - Move.
(They rearrange the room under Jae Seok's order.)
- Put the desk here. - Okay.
That's perfect.
- This is good. - It looks cozier.
- Right? - This looks good.
- It looks so different. - She can come in the room.
She can unpack here.
- That's right. - That's right.
(The angle is perfect to lie down.)
- This is great. - She can lie down.
- She can say hello to her mom. - "Hello, Mother."
- The window is right there. - She can open the window.
- That's right. - There we go.
(He smiles mysteriously.)
- Let's go. - You only have three minutes left.
You have three minutes.
The sofa is in an awkward place.
It's awkward.
- We should move it this way. - What I said before is correct.
I think this is correct.
Let's move the lamp first.
- I'll put it next to the desk. - Put it here.
There you go.
All we have to do is move the sofa, right?
The sofa should be moved all the way here.
Let's move it then.
- Can we push it in more? - We moved everything together.
I think this is a good place.
Can we put the sofa against this wall?
- That's possible. - Put it there, Ji Hyo.
Put it against this wall.
(They rearrange the sofa according to Ji Hyo's advice.)
- It's better to face the sun. - If you put it there...
- How about this? - What are you doing?
(The men are gullible.)
I think this is cozier.
This is according to feng shui.
It's about facing the sun or not.
- Let it face the sun. - She can drink some coffee here.
- Move out of the way. - Throw away the television.
- She can watch the blue roof. - Right.
Why are you carrying it around?
(The blue roof is good to look at.)
This is the right place.
(They rearrange the sofa.)
- Let's move the flower pot. - It should face the sun.
- The plant needs light. - Shouldn't it be there?
- This is what was wrong. - We should move them there.
- Let's see. - Which direction is the east?
Seok Jin puts them carelessly.
- Okay. - We can put it there.
Look at the plant.
Plants should face the sun.
- Right. - Don't you know that?
When you said that, he laughed.
(Seok Jin should stay quiet.)
He laughed at you.
What do you think of what Seok Jin did?
What he did didn't make a difference.
(His action didn't make a difference.)
I told you not to do anything.
Just stay still.
It's better that you stay still.
- The plant isn't the problem. - It isn't.
- It's the mirror. - It must be the mirror.
Perhaps, the mirror shouldn't be in the living room.
- Put it in the room. - Here.
- Here? - This looks good.
- We finished. - We're done.
(They finish rearranging.)
(How many items are correct?)
He'll review each item.
I'm worried about the plant.
The first item is the flower pot.
Normally, flowers should be...
placed in the kitchen.
(The plant is placed correctly.)
- Close to water? - Yes.
Many people put plants in the kitchen.
We put it in the bedroom instead.
It's also correct to put it in the bedroom.
That's why what Seok Jin did didn't make a difference.
There are sources of water and fire in the kitchen.
Water puts out fire.
The plant needs water, and it burns to make fire.
They create synergy.
That's why it's good to put plants in the kitchen.
- Next is the sofa. - I'm curious about that.
It's best to place the sofa where you can face people...
when they enter the house.
I told you. It must be clearly visible to people.
Is that the right place?
It's good to put it here to invite the family and guests.
It's bad to have your back on people.
- We were wrong. - It's good to put it in the corner.
- That's the best place. - That place was correct.
That's why this is the best place.
It's not completely facing the back.
You can welcome the guests from here.
You can turn to the side.
- You can turn to the side. - It's possible.
When you welcome guests,
the location of the sofa isn't important.
As soon as they come in,
it's better to run towards them.
Based on what you said, the sofa should be here.
(He's lost for words.)
The other items are in the room.
- I'll tell you in the room. - Okay.
- At first, you placed the bed here. - Right.
However, this direction is the south.
- And this is the east. - Right.
It should point southeast.
When you enter the room,
it's best to lie down with the head pointing to the corner.
- You were right. - Yes.
- That's the most stable. - I knew it.
It made me feel comfortable.
The bed is in the right place.
(The bed is in a good place.)
It was exactly right.
Next is the desk.
This is the right location.
(The desk is also correct.)
It's best to put the desk toward the east...
because it's where everything revives.
It's good to keep the door visible from the desk.
- I think it's perfect here. - Don't keep the back to the door.
My instincts told me that this was the perfect place.
(Stop bragging.)
Where were you thinking of putting the mirror?
- We thought of here. - On the wall?
Arranging the mirror there would bring...
- bad luck to Se Mi. - Really?
The worst place to put the mirror is facing the bed.
(No wonder!)
- As such, the mirror should be... - Right.
- It shouldn't face the bed. - I had a mirror facing my bed.
- Then I had nightmares. - Right.
- The mirror can create chaos. - That's right.
- I should rearrange my mirror. - Me too.
The mirror should be placed...
either on the right or the left of the entrance.
This is the right place.
Mirror on the left of the entrance increases your financial luck.
If it's on the right, it increases your luck in honor.
You put the mirror in the wrong place.
It should be near the entrance.
- You got 3 correct. - We got 2 wrong.
You missed two items.
If the lamp is in the right place, you win.
If not, you lose.
Lighting should be...
- in the bedroom. - Right.
Also, it's better to keep the bedroom dark.
It's where people rest and keep their belongings.
However, there was one time...
you placed the lamp correctly.
(They were correct one time.)
(What does that mean?)
(In other words,)
(someone moved it.)
However, someone moved it.
- Was it Seok Jin? - She moved it by herself.
- Was it me? - Ji Hyo...
moved the lamp from the bed to here.
Let's move the lamp first.
(Ji Hyo came to move the lamp alone.)
- It was Ji Hyo. - The lamp is in the wrong place.
(Running Man has 10 Running Balls, and the staff has 30.)
Here's the last mission.
It takes place in Running House,
which can be our new resting place.
You must clear the mission...
in a chicken restaurant, a hair salon, and a yoga academy.
You must obtain the digits of the passcode.
3 teams must clear the mission in 30 minutes.
You succeed when you return to Running House.
- Let's go. - Please go now.
(Let's beat the staff.)
(They take off.)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo: yoga academy)
(Jong Kook and Haha: chicken restaurant)
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo: hair salon)
- Enjoy yoga. - Thank you.
(Each team must obtain a digit.)
- Okay, let's go, everybody. - See you later.
- See you later. - See you later.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo arrive at a yoga academy.)
(What mission awaits them?)
- It should be someone flexible. - I'm not flexible at all.
Here's your mission.
It's called "Namaste Picture Quiz".
- "Namaste"? - Yes.
"Namaste" is Hindi.
Both of you will perform a yoga position.
One of you will draw with a pen in your mouth.
The other must guess what it is.
Here are the poses.
(It's a difficult mission.)
- These look difficult. - These positions are extreme.
They're very popular yoga positions.
We can't do yoga at all.
We'll give you a digit of the passcode if you clear the mission.
(Answer 4 questions in 60 seconds.)
(We hope they answer at least one.)
- 4 out of 6? - Yes.
Kwang Soo, watch carefully.
Let's start now.
(Jae Seok is the drawer.)
Get ready.
(He trembles.)
Set...
("Namaste Picture Quiz" begins.)
(The first word is "piano".)
(Jae Seok begins to draw.)
(Piano)
(He draws without hesitation.)
We don't have much time. Hurry up.
(Kwang Soo is getting anxious.)
(Struggling)
(Focused)
(It's quite realistic.)
- Kwang Soo. - Please hold it higher.
- Piano. - Correct!
(They get the first question right.)
(Jae Seok is unexpectedly talented.)
Jae Seok, you draw better with your mouth than with your hand.
(When he drew with his hand, the drawings turned out terrible.)
(He drew an alien when he was supposed to draw a kangaroo.)
(Jae Seok is usually a terrible drawer.)
Jae Seok is good at everything that makes him use his mouth.
(He draws without hesitation.)
You draw better with your mouth than with your hand.
(Amazed)
I'm done!
(It's a masterpiece.)
- Glasses. - Correct.
How can he draw so well with his mouth?
(His back and teeth start to ache.)
(Grapes)
What is this sound? What are you doing?
You're supposed to be drawing.
We don't have much time.
(The grapes start to take form with unpleasant noises.)
(Time is running out.)
- Kwang Soo. - Yes?
- Kwang Soo. - I can't see it.
- I can't see it. - Look at this.
- Look at this. - I really can't see it.
(Shaking)
Look at that.
Look at the drawing.
- Kwang Soo, look at that. - I really can't see it.
My goodness, this is so frustrating.
Look at the drawing.
- Grapes. - Correct.
(They get the third question right too.)
(They have to get just one more right.)
I'm dizzy.
Jae Seok, my eyes were almost spinning.
(The king of mouth drawing starts another piece.)
Kwang Soo.
TV? Computer? PC?
- What's that? - A pig!
- A pig! - What?
That's the nose of a pig.
Kwang Soo, that's obviously a pig.
(His drawing is minimalistic.)
Do you want me to hit you?
- What are you talking about? - That's obviously a pig.
- That's obviously a pig. - I thought it said, "PC".
- My goodness. - That was so close.
- Kwang Soo, you should do better. - Your drawings were amazing.
I know.
(Their first try failed.)
(Chicken restaurant)
Gosh, it looks so tasty.
(The delicious smell of fried chicken welcomes them.)
Okay.
(Here is the mission.)
"Battle with Customers".
"When someone orders delivery, go to the customer's house."
"Play a game related to chicken against them."
- Are we delivering chicken? - Yes.
What if no one calls within 30 minutes?
- Then you'd fail. - What?
Let me make it clear.
When someone orders delivery, go to the customer's house.
You'll complete the mission if you manage to...
finish the children's song, "Animal Farm".
("Animal Farm"?)
("Animal Farm" is a popular song among children.)
(With all kinds of animals, the lyrics are complicated.)
You have to sing the parts with a hen, a goat, and a calf.
(The customer has to finish the parts Jong Kook and Haha sing.)
(They practice first.)
- It's been such a long time. - Is it "quack, quack"?
Under the pear tree
- Is a goat under the pear tree? - A goat.
(The lyrics sound strange after such a long time.)
(This is too difficult.)
Give us a mission where we have to eat.
There are many foreigners around this area.
A Japanese person wouldn't know this song.
(Hair salon)
- We're here. - We're here.
This is Ji Hyo's territory.
(The others got difficult missions. What about them?)
- Look at this. - What's that?
- Do we sit here? - Just sit here?
Like this?
- Let me give you a mission. - Okay.
The mission is called, "Invisible Texting".
Under your gown,
without looking,
you have to type, "What's the passcode?"
Then you have to send it to me.
If both of you send it without any typos,
you'll get a digit of the passcode.
Every time you fail, we'll put one perm rod...
- on you. - Don't do that.
You should do it. My hair is tied.
- Really? - Yes.
- Please put on your gowns. - I'm wearing hair powder.
(I'm sorry. I didn't know.)
Let's just try.
(Seok Jin, we're sorry.)
All right. It's okay.
(They practice.)
- "What's the passcode?" - "What's the passcode?"
- With a question mark? - Let's do this.
I think I can do it.
You do it.
I'm not sure if I can press the "send" button.
Let's go.
(The phones go under.)
- Let's start if you're ready. - Okay.
(This is their first attempt.)
Start.
(Thumbs, you can do this.)
Where's the space bar?
"What's..."
(They have to rely on their senses.)
"What's the passcode?"
- Did you receive it? - Not yet.
- Not yet? - No.
I pushed the "send" button a hundred times.
- Did you still not get it? - No, I didn't.
I sent it.
- I got one. - Did you?
It's probably correct.
(Did their first try succeed?)
(Not a single typo is allowed.)
There are typos.
(It's full of typos.)
It was almost right, wasn't it?
Mine is a mess.
(She pushed another button instead of the "send" button.)
Send it.
Manager.
Who's the manager?
Hello.
(You'll get a perm rod.)
I think we'll be here until dinner time.
Will we be able to finish it?
(Will they be able to do it by today?)
Has anyone succeeded?
(Remaining time)
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo try for the second time.)
Jae Seok, this time, we'll be able to do it.
Jae Seok, you're talented.
(It's an accurate drawing of a candy.)
- A candy. - Correct.
(They got the first question right.)
(Keep up the good work, Jae Seok.)
(Struggling)
Jae Seok, time is running out.
(Will they be able to finish it within 60 seconds?)
Jae Seok.
(Kwang Soo lifts his body.)
A rabbit.
(The get the second question right.)
(Kwang Soo is already feeling dizzy.)
(Kwang Soo, hang in there.)
(Drawing)
- Are you done? - Yes.
(They have to get just two more questions right.)
A bicycle.
(The get the third question right.)
(It's the last question!)
It's the last one. We're almost there.
(Jae Seok is drawing with all his might.)
Good.
(Kwang Soo, look at this.)
(We don't have much time. You know what this is, right?)
- An apple. - Correct.
(He says the correct answer right away.)
- There you go. - We did it.
We did it.
Great work.
(Jae Seok and Kwang Soo worked well together.)
- It took 50 seconds. - Jae Seok.
It was possible.
This is unbelievable.
I'll give you 1 of the 4 digits.
(They get one digit of the passcode.)
- It's 1. - It's 1.
(One of the digits is 1.)
(Meanwhile)
We might get an unprecedented outcome.
(The phone hasn't rung in 14 minutes.)
If the phone doesn't ring, we fail our mission.
(Someone needs to call.)
Who would order delivery at this hour?
(Silent)
- This is too difficult. - Right?
What is that?
I'm getting scared.
Have you ever thought...
this mission might be in favor of the staff?
- At least once? - Never.
Are you serious?
(Determined)
That was funny.
The original plan was to make you sing the refrain as well.
- How does it go? - What is it like?
(Only the difficult part is left.)
(It's all meaningless if no one calls.)
This song is...
(The phone rings.)
You have a call.
Should I pick up?
It can't be.
We can't take the order.
(Is this a delivery order?)
We have an order.
(Finally, they receive an order.)
- Sir, do we have an order? - Yes.
What did they order?
No bones, half sauce-half original.
I see.
Say that you deliver the food at this hour.
They won't look presentable when they come out to get the food.
- Right. - Aren't I right?
It's possible they might not want to be filmed.
Today, the order...
- came from a cafe. - What?
Is that so?
- I'm glad. - A cafe ordered chicken?
Oh, right. Then it must be for the workers.
I think they will cooperate in filming, right?
This is nice.
(Half of a crispy, fried chicken)
- Let me come with you. - Will you?
All right. Let's head out.
Let's go.
(They set out with no bones, half sauce-half original.)
- This does look delicious. - It does.
(He hugs the chicken.)
It might get cold.
(They deliver the food by the owner's car before it gets cold.)
It goes from hen...
(He's remembering the lyrics.)
Goose is next.
- It's hen, goose, goat, and calf. - Right.
(They are working hard.)
If they are young, they might not know the lyrics.
(They have only 10 minutes left.)
This is it, sir.
- I don't have to come out, right? - Please come with us.
Inside the henhouse.
(Who will receive the fried chicken and sing in return?)
Who ordered fried chicken?
(Who will sing in exchange for fried chicken?)
Did you order fried chicken?
(I ordered, but why are they here?)
This looks delicious.
(He will determine the result of the mission.)
We are...
going to do a mission.
Can you help us?
(If he refuses, the mission fails by default.)
- This is a very simple mission. - What is it?
It's relay singing.
We will sing the beginning, and you can finish the lyrics.
- It's quite simple. - It is. Let's try it.
Let's give this a try.
- It's a children's song. 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
Inside the henhouse
There is a hen
(He gets the first animal correct.)
Next to the doorway
(This is the hard part.)
("Doorway" itself is unfamiliar enough,)
(but on top of that, an uncommon animal, goose, is in the lyrics.)
Next to the doorway
There is a goose
(He gets the second animal correct.)
Under a pear tree
(This is harder than the previous one.)
(A pear tree is strange enough, but there's a goat under it.)
(For a young adult, this line could be the hardest.)
Under a pear tree
(Will he be able to manage this crisis?)
(Under a pear tree)
There is a goat
(How amazing! He gets the third animal correct.)
In the stable
There is a calf
(He's the king of children's songs.)
(They accomplish the mission.)
We did it. We accomplished the mission.
- How did this happen? - We did it.
- How is this possible? - How can this happen?
Do you know this song?
He's amazing.
Thank you so much.
Did you go to kindergarten?
- I did. - You did?
- You are awesome. - He must've learned it there.
- How can this be? - Goodness.
We came here thinking we wouldn't succeed.
Let me buy this chicken.
- Let us buy it. - Enjoy the food.
- Thank you. - It's on us.
- Let us treat you. - Thank you.
- Unbelievable. - How did he guess the animals?
- Do you know this song? - In the stable
There is a calf
Gosh. It's like a national anthem.
(They discover a national anthem.)
(The last destination, Running House)
- Se Mi's house is there. - It's where we started.
Right.
(After accomplishing their mission, Jae Seok and Kwang Soo arrive.)
What is this?
We did it.
(Are we the first ones here?)
(Remaining time)
Other members didn't come yet.
(They should be arriving soon.)
- You have eight minutes left. - Hey, hurry.
(Running)
Hey, you need to hurry.
- What is it? - Hey, run faster.
Wait, we weren't the first ones?
Our mission was really challenging.
- Really? - It was by far the hardest.
- We had to deliver food. - And then?
Press it now.
(It will be a success when Seok Jin and Ji Hyo arrive.)
- Okay! - What did you do there?
Where is Seok Jin?
(Remaining time)
What happened to him?
We don't have much time left.
This is so frustrating.
Aren't you putting too much effort into it?
Excuse me.
Could you just wrap it up?
I can't do this.
Can you shorten the number of words?
Please put more perm rods on them.
- I knew this would happen. - This is too challenging.
My hair is short. I don't have any hair left for that.
This is frustrating.
This is why he irritates me.
- Come on. - Darn Seok Jin.
This time, we will try this.
- What is it? - How about just "passcode?"
Are you serious?
- Just those words, right? - You are certain, right?
- "Passcode?" - With the question mark.
Hold on. Sending it is the problem.
It's hard to send it.
"Passcode?"
(Pressing the send button isn't the only problem.)
You said it just has to be under the gown.
You are not allowed to look.
Why? It's under the gown.
(She focuses with her eyes closed.)
(Pressing)
(She manages to send it without any typos.)
(Ji Hyo succeeds.)
I did it. I did it!
(Passcode?)
(She escapes from the trap of typos.)
(Darn it.)
I need to succeed too.
This is so frustrating.
I only have four letters to type.
Here it goes. I can do it!
(He must succeed now.)
Seok Jin.
All right. What's next?
I typed it three times,
and I sent it.
Seok Jin, you accomplished it as well.
(Seok Jin and Ji Hyo accomplish their mission.)
We did it.
Seok Jin, you succeeded too!
In 8, 7...
(We did it, but the time has run out.)
- In 3, 2... Gosh. - That's it.
- They failed. - Shoot.
Seok Jin.
- Thank you. - Goodness.
Ji Hyo. Hurry.
(Only these two are in a hurry. We have time left, right?)
Where is it? Where?
Is this the building?
Gosh.
What's going on?
You would've looked the same if you went there.
- Ji Hyo. - It suits you.
- This is funny. - It's driving me crazy.
Ji Hyo, what happened? Why do you look like that?
Since one team didn't arrive in time,
I will give you 10 Running Balls.
(They receive 10 Running Balls.)
- What was your mission? - The passcode...
- is 0613. - It's 0613?
The four-digit number represents Se Mi's birthday.
I won't ever forget her birthday.
- So far, the score is 2 to 2. - That's right.
Both teams have 80 Running Balls.
- This is a close match. - All right.
We will open the door and draw the final Running Ball.
- It's 0613. - I'm nervous.
- Ji Hyo. We will get it, right? - The passcode is simple.
- Look at that. - What do we do when we draw it?
We will put them in it and draw from it.
These are all mixed. Please put them into it.
- Kwang Soo... - If the staff wins, it's his place.
- How can you say that right away? - If the staff's Running Ball is...
drawn, it has to be one of your houses.
- Your place is the most convenient. - It's not just about convenience.
We all live with someone.
- You live alone. - We live with our family.
(I might end up moving.)
- Here we go. - Hey, give that to me.
(The draw of fate starts.)
- Here it goes. - All right.
- Here we go. - Okay.
- Let us start. - In 1, 2, 3.
(If they win, this place will be their resting place.)
(If the staff wins, one of the members will sacrifice.)
- Look. - It came out.
- All right. - If it says "Running Man", we win.
If it says "Running Man", you win.
- Do you want to switch? - Kwang Soo.
Please, Jae Seok.
- If we lose, it's Kwang Soo's home. - Yes, it is.
- Hold on. - It will be your house.
In 1, 2...
(This is the last moment of the dangerous deal.)
(What will be the result of this deal?)
Three.
(Running Man's Running Ball is drawn.)
(Hooray! We will seize this resting place.)
- Kwang Soo. - We saved him.
- We saved him. - We did.
- Don't worry. - Your place is safe now.
- No need to worry now. - Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo. - I was so nervous.
I wanted to go to his place.
Congratulations.
- This is good for us. - Right.
The victory goes to you.
(Running Man members take the victory.)
- This will be our resting place. - Thank you.
(I like this resting place.)
Can we use this place whenever we want?
- Yes. - Whenever?
The secret behind Running House...
will be revealed soon.
(The Secret behind Running House?)
(What is the secret behind this rooftop house?)
There's a secret?