(Last week)
(Our family, Kang Han Na and
Heo Kyung-hwan joined us again.)
(And they got 10 different phones.)
(They all picked a phone randomly.)
The time is ticking.
(Each phone has a stopwatch
with different times.)
As soon as your time runs out,
you will be eliminated.
(As soon as their times run out,
they get eliminated immediately.)
(The members who are eliminated...)
(will be the judges
during the race.)
(While they stay in the time circle,
the countdown is paused.)
(The missions continue
in their different times.)
- Jae Suk, three
- Strawberry...
(Jae Suk is a strawberry fool.)
(Hurry. I don't have time.)
(The members who win
get to spin the roulette.)
(Steal the invested time
from another)
(I'll steal time from Suk Jin.)
(Suk Jin is the 1st one
to be eliminated.)
(That's how they got...)
(the 1st judge.)
Do I get no screen time now?
(Countdown Race Final Mission)
(Time Expedition)
It's going to be
Name Tag Elimination.
If you rip off the name tag of
someone who has less time than you,
you get to steal half of their time.
If you rip off the name tag of
someone who has more time than you,
you lose half your time.
Hold on.
- Everybody will come at me.
- Wait up.
The piranhas will rip him apart.
If you hold hands with another
member, your times get combined.
- What?
- If you hold hands?
Let's say Jae Suk has 10 minutes,
and Jong Kook has 70.
If they hold hands,
their times become 80 minutes.
If they rip off So Min's name tag
who has 20 minutes left,
they can steal half
of her 20 minutes.
Each person will earn five minutes.
If they rip off the name tag
of somebody who has 90 minutes left,
Jae Suk and Jong Kook will lose...
half of their respective
remaining times.
It'll be a mess. You'll hold hands
and let go. This sounds fun.
(This sounds fun.)
(The oldest judge is left alone.)
- Suk Jin.
- Why is the judge talking?
- Don't pay any attention.
- What's wrong with him?
- Sir.
- Don't pay any attention.
Your name tags are hidden
inside this building.
If you collect two name tags
of the same person,
their remaining time gets revealed.
If you collect
two of your own name tags,
you earn an additional 10 minutes.
- That's good.
- Inside the building is...
also the special Room of Time.
Room of Time opens without notice
at random locations,
and only one person can use it.
It disappears after use.
In order to use Room of Time,
you must pay a third of your
remaining time as the admission.
My gosh.
It's probably worth it though.
(Current Time Status)
(Se Chan, Kyung-hwan, Han Na, Haha,
Ji Hyo, So Min, Jae Suk)
There are targets beneath me.
I don't have to worry about
Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo, and Jae Suk.
The rest are tricky.
I'm planning to be loyal to Se Chan.
I think Haha took...
Han Na's time
because she was on top.
Jong Kook probably stole
Kyung-hwan's time.
There's a possibility I might win...
by default.
I'm either top 1 or 2.
I'm sure
Kyung-hwan has more time than me.
People who are
on a similar level as me...
are Han Na and Se Chan.
Jong Kook probably has around
1 hour to 1 hour and 10 minutes.
People know I have some time,
so it won't be easy. Jae Suk first.
(He's sure Jae Suk is the last.)
Jae Suk...
(Jae Suk)
Do you have a strategy?
I have no strategy.
I have to hold hands with somebody
before I die.
I have to hold hands with Kwang Soo.
5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
Start the race.
I'm in trouble.
(The countdown starts
with the race.)
I have no time to waste.
The race has begun.
(Jae Suk)
Gosh, I have to hold
hands with someone.
Where's the entrance?
(Jae Suk might become
a judge in 1 minute.)
(Jae Suk)
Where are they?
Han Na.
- Han Na.
- Why?
- Han Na. Hold my hand.
- Yes?
- Why? What's going on?
- Please help me.
What is going on?
- Han Na.
- Let's go rip off a name tag.
- That's right. You need me too.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Cool.
- There they are.
- Hang on.
What? Are you two joining hands?
It's no use joining hands when
both of you don't have much time.
- That's not true.
- Don't listen to him.
- We are rich.
- That's right.
- We have plenty of time.
- We can win.
We will win
if they fight against them.
- 10.
- What?
- 9, 8,
- What's going on?
- Seven...
- I guess it's Jae Suk.
We should find a name tag.
(Jae Suk has only 10 seconds left.)
- How do we get to the 16th floor?
- 10, 9...
- What's that?
- What?
- Seven...
- We're holding hands.
Six.
- We joined hands together.
- Five.
- Four.
- I'm holding her hand.
Three.
- What?
- Jae Suk is out.
I'm holding her hand though?
(Yoo Jae Suk is out
in 1 minute and 40 seconds.)
You should've
ripped off her name tag.
Good one, Jae Suk.
He's out.
You're out.
You're a judge now.
Holding hands doesn't work?
I had to rip off her name tag?
I see. You found the wrong person.
Yoo Jae Suk is out.
What?
(What? The race has just begun.)
He's out for good?
So it was true.
He just showed
his real intention like that.
Gosh.
You look good in the uniform.
You look great.
Mind your own business.
You look good.
(Watching the judge)
- You look good in yellow.
- Gosh.
Where should I go now?
Jae Suk,
another judge Suk Jin is...
- now setting the Room of Secret.
- Okay.
Once you go to him,
he will tell you what to do.
Wait.
Am I supposed to get
instructions from Suk Jin?
Yes. Go ask Suk Jin
about what to do.
Where is Suk Jin?
- Hello?
- Where are you, Boss?
- Are you out?
- Yes.
I'm out of the race.
- Come over here.
- Is it the 14th floor?
Okay. I should go to the 14th floor.
Hey. Will you hurry?
(Suk Jin is acting
like an old fossil already.)
Do you think this is a joke?
Who told you to sit down?
Stand still there.
My goodness.
(The judge is slacking off already.)
I can't believe this.
- Hey.
- We're the same judge.
I'm judge number one.
I'm number two.
You should organize these.
- They're not organized.
- What should I do?
You should organize
things like this.
(He sets an example,
unlike his tone.)
You can do that.
We have to manage the Room of Time.
What?
We are the managers
of the Room of Time.
We're not supposed to loaf around.
I'm not loafing around.
We have to manage the Room of Time.
- They will be spinning a roulette.
- And?
And the time they have...
- Hey.
- What?
I'm talking now.
I'm just eating this while you talk.
Put it down. I said put it down.
Put it down or share it with me.
(Intimidating)
Thanks.
We also...
have to clean up the Room of Time.
That's your job.
- Me?
- You should clean up the room.
It's not like I became
number one for no reason.
I used to serve
my seniors very well.
I cleaned up
the Room of Time for five years.
I've done it for a long time.
Gosh. Who will be number three?
Shall we catch Han Na?
Shall we?
- We can get half of her time.
- We can do that.
We should go after Han Na...
because she has just
as much time as me.
That's why I'm joining
hands with you.
You can get some time
and I can get some too.
Then you can...
leave me right away.
I'll catch you right away.
(I will catch you
after catching Han Na.)
(Kyung-hwan's ultimatum)
As soon as we catch Han Na,
you should run away.
Okay?
- I don't know how I will change.
- I don't want to run away though.
You have no choice. I'm a zombie.
- You have to run away.
- Okay.
(Haha and Ji Hyo meet secretly
with not much time.)
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
You're doing good with time, right?
She's safe, right?
- I'm doing okay.
- I know.
- I'm good.
- We both are from Mapo-gu.
I think we should hold hands, right?
(Right at the moment...)
There's Jong Kook.
Let's go catch him.
(Jong Kook, Ji Hyo,
Kyung-hwan, Haha)
Haha has no time.
He doesn't have much time.
Haha doesn't have much time, right?
Who is that?
It's Kyung-hwan.
- Even if they join hands...
- They can't beat us anyway.
Come here.
It's Kyung-hwan. We have to run.
(It's Kyung-hwan and Jong Kook.
Run away!)
Come over here.
Bring the beggar.
(The friends
from Mapo-gu scatter.)
Stop.
(He runs upstairs at full speed.)
Did they leave?
(Snatching)
Gosh, what was that?
Where were you?
Hang on.
(Jong Kook ripped off
Haha's name tag.)
(If Jong Kook has more time than
Haha, he gets half of Haha's time.)
The countdown is paused.
Did he follow me all the way?
(Haha has quite a bit of time left.)
(What's the result?)
Haha lost half of his time.
(Jong Kook stole
half of Haha's time.)
Hang on.
- Does he have more time than me?
- Yes.
Do you think I don't?
I saw what you were doing.
Okay. I don't know
how much time I've gathered.
(He worked really hard
to collect the time.)
You should come to me.
Kyung-hwan, you should come to me.
- Kyung-hwan, join hands with me.
- What's going on here?
Ji Hyo, you should
hold hands with me.
Kwang Soo.
Why don't you come to me?
If you and I work together...
But I think it's either
Se Chan or Han Na who is leading.
Gosh.
I've always had a lot of time.
Does Kyung-hwan have
a lot of time? I guess he does.
This is the lobby.
We should take the elevator
and go upstairs first.
Let's take the elevator.
We should go upstairs.
Let's go after Kyung-hwan.
Let's join hands together.
Rip off Kyung-hwan's name tag.
- Wait. I should be scared of him.
- Hurry.
(He runs away immediately.)
Se Chan is too strong.
We should rip it off. Hurry.
(Kyung-hwan gets cold feet
and runs away.)
I can't do this.
(Did he grab
Kyung-hwan's name tag?)
(But he missed the big fish
by a second.)
(The chase continues.)
Jong Kook.
- Come here.
- Hurry.
(Kyung-hwan and Jong Kook
are joining hands together.)
(The situation has turned
in their favor now.)
Run. Hurry.
- Go away.
- Grab her.
Get her name tag.
We don't know yet. Just rip it off.
We need one more person.
Kwang Soo, come over here.
- Come here.
- Go to Kwang Soo.
Join hands with Kwang Soo.
I did it.
(He ripped off Se Chan's name tag.)
- I took it off.
- We did it.
Who ripped whose name tag?
Jong Kook and Kyung-hwan...
ripped off Se Chan
and Ji Hyo's name tags.
- Gosh, it hurts.
- Okay.
I don't know who will win.
- Se Chan got 100 minutes earlier.
- I know.
I have more time than you think.
How much time do I lose
if he has more than me?
- Is it half?
- I can't tell you that now.
(Whoever wins, the losing team
will lose more than an hour.)
(Who is losing their time?)
Anyway,
Kyung-hwan and Jong Kook
get more time.
We won!
(Kyung-hwan and Jong Kook
get more time.)
This is amazing.
(How much time
does Jong Kook have then?)
(Jong Kook picked the phone
that was left.)
Is it number five? Okay.
(Luckily, he got
2 hours and 50 minutes.)
The last one.
(He has had a lot of time
from the beginning.)
(And he got only good ones
from spinning the roulette.)
(Steal 20 minutes and the invested
time from the top 1)
(That's how
the time monster was born.)
(But he doesn't even know
that he has a lot of time.)
Kyung-hwan and Jong Kook
get more time.
We won!
- Really?
- This is amazing.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo
lost their time.)
- Gosh, Jong Kook.
- Hey.
You should be nice to me.
Thank you, Jong Kook. Just go.
- That's not what I meant.
- Just go.
Thank you.
Don't rip off my name tag then.
Leave me alone until the end.
I told you.
I got bitten by a zombie.
- I will change soon.
- What?
I helped you.
I won't rip off your name tag.
But you should go
stand on your own feet.
- Leave me.
- I know.
I will see you at the top.
(They promise to meet at the top.)
(Current Time Status)
(At the moment,
in the judges' office)
- I shouldn't be here now.
- Who ripped off your name tag?
I just ran out of time.
- I had only about two minutes.
- You ran out of time.
There will be more members
coming in here soon.
There will be more judges
than members later.
Judge number 1 and 2.
Please move
to the first Room of Secret.
Once you get there,
we will announce...
that the first
Room of Secret is open.
Who will be the main judge?
- I'm the main judge.
- I see.
It depends on who works better.
Go open the door.
Make it say it's open.
Hey, Judge number two.
(Yelling)
Flip it, so it says it's open.
(While Judge No. 1
yells at Judge No. 2,)
Good.
(Room of Time has opened.)
(Room of Time opens without notice
in random locations.)
(Only one person can use it.
And it disappears after use.)
(They pay a third of their remaining
time as the admission fee.)
The first Room of Time is open.
The Room of Time is open.
- Room of Time.
- I need to go there.
You should go there
and bet your life.
Where's the Room of Time?
I have to go to the Room of Time.
I need to go there.
Do I just look for the Room of Time?
(Kwang Soo)
I will be doomed without it.
(Who will be the first member
to use Room of Time?)
I should go to the Room of Time.
It's down there. It's open.
It's open now.
Jae Suk. Judge.
Hey, it's open.
Hurry.
It's me.
Hang on.
- It costs a third of your time.
- Okay. I'll pay.
- You should pay more than that.
- What? Why?
(I've never seen a judge like him.)
(It's a collaboration
of threat and intimidation.)
You should pay half of what you got.
Why?
- Get in.
- You're the judges.
- Go in.
- Okay.
- I will pay a third of my time.
- Hey, wait.
Spin it in front of us. We're bored.
- Now.
- Move.
- Can they do that?
- I'm Judge No. 1.
- Why are you being like this?
- Just spin it.
(He pays 10 minutes
as the admission fee.)
Gosh.
(Will Haha be able to make
a big fortune with a spin?)
Let's see what he gets.
Steal half of the time
from a person chosen randomly.
- Please.
- We have to keep watch.
Switching time is the best one.
- Right.
- Go ahead.
I want switch time with a person
of your choice. Please.
You have only one chance.
- Please.
- It's the dud.
(What's the result of the roulette?)
It's a dud.
(Switch time
with a person of your choice)
- Okay!
- Seriously?
(He managed to get "Switch time
with a person of your choice.")
Okay!
- Okay.
- You're so lucky.
- Who would you like to switch with?
- Me?
I think Kyung-hwan
has a lot of time.
Han Na has more time. She took
1 hour and 50 minutes from me.
- Kang Han Na.
- Han Na is in trouble.
- I feel bad for her.
I'm sorry, Han Na.
Han Na, I will help you.
Gosh, Han Na.
I'm so glad that you picked Han Na.
(Haha switched time with Han Na.)
(It's done!)
Hey, the five of you!
I'm in the lobby.
(He finally straightens up his
shoulders and raises his voice.)
(He forgets about the past
and becomes triumphant.)
That doesn't make sense.
In Room of Time,
Haha switched his time...
with yours.
(Shocked)
- How much time do I have?
- Now you have...
18 minutes and 47 seconds.
(Han Na)
Haha!
Han Na, hello.
- You...
- I can't believe this.
What do I do?
(Han Na has become
a timeless beggar in an instant.)
What do I do?
Why?
What?
Why are you following me
around the whole time?
Let's end things
for those with little time.
I'll hold your hand.
(The zombie is putting on airs.)
- I'm helping you this once.
- Thank you.
Now...
To be honest,
there's something you need
to tell me.
(He talks
in a condescending manner.)
Tell me how much time you have.
Because I can assure you,
you can't beat me.
How much time do you have?
20 minutes.
You're so poor.
Gosh, she's dirt poor.
Are you serious?
You'll die out on your own.
Hold on.
Hey, hey. Come here.
(They meet Kwang Soo and Se Chan.)
Hold on a minute.
This is tricky.
This is.
Se Chan, you lost
half of your time, right?
Yes.
Okay, and you haven't gotten
attacked, right?
- Right.
- Ji Hyo, listen to me.
We're going to save you.
Join hands with us
and let's eliminate him.
(Join hands with us
and let's eliminate him.)
(He wants to join hands with her.)
What do you say?
Forget about him. He's just a guest.
- That's right.
- Let the members become one.
- Let's show him.
- He's a mere guest.
(When things are rough,
they always say this.)
(Should I or should I not?)
During my entire time here,
this is the moment...
when they've looked
the least confident.
- I'm serious.
- He does have a lot of time.
- He does. We might not beat him.
- We might not beat him.
But still, let's beat
our guest for today.
No. Don't forget our promise.
- Hey.
- Let's beat them...
- Hear me out.
- and survive.
Many drops make a shower.
Will you also be willing to save me?
If you do, I'll let go of his hand
and join you.
(During the critical time,
he betrays his own member.)
Get him! Get him!
- You little...
- Eliminate him!
We'll win for sure.
You jerks!
From the way I see it,
you'll look better in yellow.
He looks pathetic.
(Kwang Soo, Kyung-hwan,
and Ji Hyo receive 7 minutes each.)
Anyway...
Please give us our minutes...
- and let's go.
- How much time do I have left?
(Se Chan)
Hey, I still have some time.
Me too.
Do you three want to try
eliminating me?
- Do you have that much?
- How much will that be?
- What?
- Try it.
You want us three
to try eliminating you?
Give me a chance.
If you join me,
I'll eliminate him myself.
He probably has about three minutes.
I've never been this laidback
while on this show.
- He looks awesome.
- We can beat him.
(They grab Kyung-hwan.)
(They rip his name tag.)
(The three confidently remove
Kyung-hwan's name tag.)
You made a mistake.
- No, I doubt it.
- I know two of your times.
- Let me calculate it.
- Come here.
- Let's calculate this.
- They ganged up on me.
I'm speechless.
- What is it?
- That was intentional, right?
- That was, right?
- No.
I shouldn't have joined hands.
It feels like three kids
have punched Fyodor in the back.
No, we have enough time.
If he gets our time,
nobody will be able to beat him.
Tell us. Who lost?
(What is the result?)
Kyung-hwan lost.
- Okay!
- What?
(He loses 1 hour and 25 minutes.)
All right, then.
Hold on.
I lost?
(Ji Hyo: 23 minutes,
Se Chan: 17 minutes,)
(Kyung-hwan:
2 hours and 50 minutes)
(So how much time
does Kwang Soo have?)
Han Na.
- Yes?
- I lost?
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
(While Kwang Soo is distracted,)
(Se Chan gives Kyung-hwan a sign.)
(And the four team up.)
Hurry!
- Hurry! Rip it!
- I did it!
(In a blink of an eye,)
(they remove Kwang Soo's name tag.)
I did it!
(He falls.)
They were calculating our times.
Come on. Hey!
We got his name tag.
- They were calculating our times.
- We did it.
- No.
- Hey!
- They already finished.
- They finished.
- They were calculating.
They were calculating.
- They finished.
- Wait.
- We know you've lost.
We know you've lost.
They're so inhumane. Okay.
We four joined hands.
- It was us four.
- It was.
Kyung-hwan, Ji Hyo,
Se Chan, and Han Na...
- eliminated Kwang Soo.
- Yes.
(Their times put together
is about 3 hours and 16 minutes.)
(He needs to have more than that
in order to not getting deducted.)
Since Kwang Soo had more time...
- Okay!
- What?
(Does he have more time
than the four put together?)
Wait. Seriously?
- That's impossible. How?
- Come here.
- All of you.
- Wait.
- How much did you have?
- Come here, all of you.
- Stand up.
- Hold on.
(How much time did he have?)
I don't have that much time.
(He acted as if he didn't have
much time from the beginning.)
(How much time did his phone have?)
(Kwang Soo)
In the beginning,
I was pretty sure I came first.
There are three cameras
following him.
Since there are these many cameras,
I feel like I could eliminate
just about everyone today.
They give me such confidence
and strength.
They really do.
Gosh.
I must win today.
(How dare you join hands
behind my back?)
- Stand up.
- Hold on.
- Will you not listen to me?
- Seriously?
- Will you not?
- I'll stand up first.
- You're first. Who's next?
- Me.
- Who's third?
Come here.
Hold on.
You've been acting up.
- That's not it.
- Okay?
- I was telling you the truth.
- You've been acting up.
Are you sure
you calculated correctly?
Han Na and I joined hands.
Those who need to go, go.
I bet you two will be wearing yellow
sooner than later.
- What did you say?
- It was Se Chan.
He schemed this.
- Let's go.
- Try me.
You're so rich.
- You have so much time.
- Come on.
- I had no intention of doing that.
- Han Na.
- How is this possible?
- He must have about four hours.
It's more than that.
Kwang Soo was deceiving us
all along.
They're having a conflict.
(Haha has been watching.)
Who got eliminated?
Hey, you keep wandering around us.
Be quiet.
- Just leave.
- We're playing here. Leave.
- We're also part of it.
- Go away.
- Go.
- They're...
- Why are you here?
- They're having a conflict.
Go.
- Go.
- I'm playing the game!
Go away.
- Go.
- I'm playing the game.
Don't be ridiculous. Just go.
Don't trespass our area. Go away.
This is so irritating.
Go away.
I know you just want to get
to the Room of Time first.
Just go!
How much time do I have?
I think I might die
while walking around.
(Let's eliminate him.)
- He's nothing.
- I think I might die...
Let's just do it.
(They rip off his name tag.)
She wanted me to do it.
(Kyung-hwan and Ji Hyo
successfully eliminate Se Chan.)
Why would you eliminate
a small fry like me?
- She wanted me to.
- I'm just a small fry.
- Ji Hyo wanted me to.
- What were you expecting?
Since you were going to die anyway,
we wanted to speed that up.
Okay.
She said, "Let's eliminate him."
My name tag got ripped off
so many times. Fine, keep going.
- You may go now.
- I'll be going now.
Please bring a camera over here.
- Over here.
- Why?
- You should shoot me flipping this.
- Don't give it to him.
(He wants to have
his own screen time.)
The Room of Time is open.
(I got my own screen time.)
- The second Room of Time is open.
- What?
Isn't it over there?
(So Min immediately begins
searching for it.)
Is that open?
Or is it locked?
Is it open?
- It's not this one.
- That one's closed.
The second Room of Time is open.
(Haha already knows where it is.)
It's Haha again.
(He arrives at the Room of Time.)
- He knew we were here.
- You can't come here.
- Why not?
- You can't.
- No, you should leave.
- You need to leave.
- You've already entered it once.
- You can't go again.
What kind of rule is that?
- Go away.
- This is my only hope.
- No.
- Try going in there.
- You've already done it.
- You can't.
Everyone is given equal opportunity.
- No.
- It's based on what we want.
- There's no re-entry?
We're in charge of this,
and we say no.
- There are rules to this.
- No.
There are none. Leave.
- I have no hope right now.
- Leave.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're in first place.
I'm not.
What do you get if you win?
- What do you get?
- It's something good.
- I'll split it with you guys.
- Will you split it?
Trust me.
- You'll split it into three?
- Yes, I will.
- Trust me.
- He may...
He may be easily convinced,
but not me.
This is my place.
- What do you mean?
- You're my junior.
- Get out.
- I'm your senior.
I don't get why I can't go inside.
You were acting sly
by roaming around this area.
I wasn't being sly! I was watching
the conflict down there!
You disturbed me!
- The Room of Time is here!
- Get out.
Come on.
Get out!
- Hey.
- Get out! Okay, I'm in.
One-third of your time
has been taken.
- One-third?
- Is he inside?
- All right.
Is he inside?
- You should've hurried.
- You should've.
We were stopping him.
He just went inside.
- All right.
- Spin the roulette just once.
- I want my time to double.
- Spin it.
(Haha spins the roulette.)
(Which outcome will he receive?)
This way, I have hope.
(Switch time with a person
of your choice.)
- "Switch time..."
- That's it.
"with a person of your choice."
Switch time with a person
of your choice.
This is a bit tricky.
- It is.
- He has enough time.
- He needs to pick someone.
- This is tricky.
Do I have to do this?
- Yes.
- You must.
Isn't he done?
- He is. Get out.
- I haven't chosen yet.
- Chosen what?
- I have to choose a member.
- Get out.
- I haven't picked someone yet.
- You can switch with someone?
- Yes.
(He runs the risk
of shortening his current time.)
How many hours did he have?
When I was down there,
I was stripped of my time.
Was he? Did you see it?
The others must've ripped off
your name tag several times.
Many times.
How much time does Kwang Soo have?
- Guess.
- Kwang Soo?
Five of us ganged up on him,
but we lost.
He's the strongest.
He took all my time away.
I have my trust in you.
- Get out.
- Even Kyung-hwan can't beat him?
(After hearing their testimonies...)
Lee Kwang Soo.
- Your times have been swapped.
- Okay.
Seriously?
Haha had the chance to swap times.
And he chose you...
to swap times with.
(Swearing)
(Kwang Soo)
You've now received his time.
(His glory days are past him.)
(Haha suddenly becomes
very wealthy.)
Haha.
Haha, brother. Please help me.
Haha, please.
You...
Haha, me too.
What about you?
There's no point in taking hers.
- Hold on.
- Just do something.
I'll leave you to it then.
- Sort things out yourselves.
- Sure.
- Wait.
- I'll only take in one person.
- Only one.
- Han Na, rip So Min's name tag off.
- You guys are nothing.
- Can you?
Can you believe my luck?
(The little ones
begin their own war.)
What now?
(The two sisters join forces.)
You two...
(The puny girls charge forward!)
Guys, please.
No, not mine.
I ripped off his name tag!
(Han Na, So Min, Se Chan)
It won't do you any good.
Pause, everyone. Han Na
ripped off Se Chan's name tag.
It won't do you any good.
Why would you take
my non-existing time?
Anyway, you stole Se Chan's time.
(They each added
1 minute and 10 seconds.)
What a relief.
- We did it.
- My gosh.
- Over here.
- Come over here.
Guys.
I'll tell you the time I had.
I only had two minutes left.
Can you please take my hand?
Give me at least five more minutes.
Hold on. Which floor?
- 14th floor.
- 14th? I don't have the time...
to make it up there.
- Hold on.
- How much time do you have left?
- Hurry. Where's Han Na?
- I'll take yours.
No, wait. Where's Han Na?
- Let me take yours instead.
- Where's Han Na?
(Why bother living
such an exhausting life?)
- Where's Han Na?
- Take So Min's for now.
I took So Min's.
Se Chan, you lost half of your time.
- Why?
- Se Chan.
(He ripped So Min's name tag off
when she had more time.)
Nice. Is my time still intact?
- Yes.
- Then I should get going.
Hold on.
Wait.
Se Chan, you have 40 seconds left.
Call the person you miss the most.
(Call the person you miss the most.)
- Go on.
- There's no one to call.
I'll be back in the next round then.
- Sure.
- Get back to us soon.
- I'll see you later.
- Sure.
Meet us on the eighth floor.
(Hold on!)
(Kwang Soo spots an envelope
with a name on it.)
I have Jong Kook's name tag!
(He obtains Jong Kook's name tag.)
(He finds Jong Kook's name tag
once again.)
I found two name tags
with Jong Kook's name.
If you find two name tags
in the same name,
that person's remaining time
will be revealed.
Kwang Soo, we'll let you know
Jong Kook's remaining time.
It's 3 hours and 46 minutes.
(Jong Kook is in 1st place
with 3 hours and 46 minutes.)
3 hours and 46 minutes?
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo!)
Let's rip off Jong Kook's name tag.
Let's rip off Jong Kook's
name tag together.
I heard how much time
Jong Kook has left.
- I heard it.
- And?
If we make an attack together...
(Ji Hyo joins forces too.)
Hold on, guys. Just hear me out.
- Sure, go ahead.
- If we turn against each other,
- Jong Kook will win.
- Do you have my name tag?
No, I don't.
Haha, we know the time
each of us has left.
- Right.
- It wasn't on purpose but...
Did you spin the wheel then?
- I didn't.
- Let me rip off your name tag.
You can have these.
- They don't have much time left.
- We're the Three Musketeers.
- Hold on.
- Just this once.
We'll share the time.
Charlie's Angels, do your thing.
(Charlie's Angels, do your thing.)
Rip his name tag off.
(Haha charges at Kwang Soo.)
Get him!
- Take him.
- Get his hand.
- Get him.
- Hold on a second.
Wait. Gosh.
They're all upstairs.
I see Kwang Soo.
(And watching everything unravel...)
(is Jong Kook who's in 1st place.)
(Kwang Soo versus
Haha and Charlie's Angels)
Wait. Gosh.
We need to get Kwang Soo.
We...
(But at that moment)
(Their hands weren't touching.)
We need to get Kwang Soo.
(Ripping)
Okay.
(Haha rips Kwang Soo's name tag
without holding hands.)
I got it.
- What now?
- They ripped my name tag off!
- They did?
- Oh, no.
What's going on?
- They cornered me.
- Exactly.
Haha ripped it off
by himself though.
(Their hands weren't held,
so only Haha gets Kwang Soo's time.)
No way.
(Kwang Soo, Haha)
Unbelievable. You'll have
a chance against Jong Kook now.
(Haha's in 2nd place while
Jong Kook's in 1st place.)
- Our last hope is gone.
- I'm done too.
- Me too.
- Charlie's Angels are over.
Charlie's Angels?
It ended five minutes
after being formed.
- Honestly...
- Where's the yellow jacket?
So Min, please change into
the yellow uniform.
Is it over for you?
Also, Han Na is out too.
- Really?
- Already?
Please leave with So Min.
Is Ji Hyo still in the game?
It's now the dynamic duo.
Ji Hyo, I hope you survive.
- I'm not sure but...
- It'll be over soon for me too.
- My time's almost up as well.
- It was swapped.
Hold on. Is anyone downstairs?
(He shows Ji Hyo
how much time she has left.)
(She only has 6 minutes left.)
What is it? How much time
do you have left?
It's time for me
to dress in yellow too.
How much time do you have left?
Six minutes.
(Six minutes.)
(Oh, dear)
(It's over for me, Haha.)
Shouldn't you find a way?
(No, don't lose hope.)
(Ripping off)
(Startled)
(Haha, Ji Hyo)
(Haha steals half
of what Ji Hyo has.)
I only had six minutes left!
- Right.
- Six minutes!
I have to take the elevator,
but I don't have enough time.
Let me save three minutes.
Why can't you let me have
three minutes?
Are you serious?
You jerk.
How dare you mug the poor!
Unbelievable.
Guys, let's head out.
- No way.
- I earned three minutes.
- Let's go.
- You jerk!
(Haha obtains time to take
the elevator and leaves.)
Unbelievable.
(Ji Hyo has nothing left.)
Do I only have three minutes now?
Don't worry.
I don't hurt those
who are hanging by a thread.
It's really over for me.
I'm done for.
I know that but...
Isn't Haha untouchable now?
He even took three minutes from me.
What? So you only have
three minutes left now?
Exactly!
Get your last minute
of sunshine then.
Darn.
Why are you here in the shade?
Go ahead. You did very well today.
I can't believe
I had to be consoled by him.
(Ji Hyo)
Unbelievable.
Ji Hyo, your time is up.
(Ji Hyo)
(Her elimination is imminent.)
(Thankfully,
the sun is there to shine on her.)
Give me the yellow uniform.
Gosh.
(Ji Hyo is out!)
No...
(Ji Hyo)
(Jong Kook, Haha,
Kyung-hwan, Kwang Soo)
Open it.
(Suk Jin has seniority.)
(The two head over
to open another Room of Time.)
Number 59. What is it?
Number 59.
(Jae Suk takes a step to the side.)
(Trotting)
There aren't any cameras in there.
Suk Jin, wait for your camera!
What is it?
(He has a hard time opening a door.)
Why aren't you following me?
I have seniority here.
Why would you stay with Jae Suk...
- when I have seniority?
- This is hilarious.
Why didn't they follow you inside?
- Why are you lurking around?
- Kyung-hwan, it's you.
- Hi.
- Unbelievable.
It's me.
- What are you two doing here?
- What good will knowing it do?
- You'll be joining us soon anyway.
- It's not what I meant.
(Don't poke the bear
when he's already upset.)
Why are you trying to know
so many things?
What we do is different
from what you do.
- But...
- Don't interfere with our work.
- Well...
- We won't interfere with yours.
Why are you trudging
along the halls though?
- Shouldn't you be working alone?
- Trudging?
What do you know about
what we do anyway?
How many cameras
do you have on your tail?
How many cameras?
I see four, so what?
Is this the place?
I guess not.
You must be creating a Room of Time.
- Is this the place?
- Is it your job...
to make a Room of Time?
(Busted)
If you follow us...
Where are you going?
(Why do they keep
lurking around this place?)
Where's room number 59?
(The manager can't locate
the Room of Time.)
This is the place. Here we go.
(Found it!)
Here it is. Room number 59.
Hello.
Hello, fellow judges.
This isn't good.
Where is the Room of Time?
Where's the Room of Time?
Where is it?
(They wish to find the room first
and change their lives around.)
(Who will be the first
to arrive at the Room of Time?)
Gosh.
And open!
(The Room of Time is open.)
Good.
The third Room of Time is now open.
(The third Room of Time
is now open.)
I want to be untouchable.
That's all I want.
This is the scariest place
that exists right now.
- Don't you think so?
- Be careful, all right?
This is where you
bring your juniors to scold.
- It's the scariest place of all.
- I know.
(He spies on the judges.)
(Who's the first one
to be at the Room of Time?)
It's why I telling you
to be careful.
What are you talking about?
What is this anyway?
It's like they came here to chat.
I'm loving this location.
Do you remember...
the hallway scene from "Oldboy"?
It's exactly like that hallway.
I could fight 20 men here.
I'd rather get some rest,
so please don't talk to me.
(I'd rather get some rest,
so please don't talk to me.)
Unbelievable.
Got it?
You have no respect
for your seniors.
- What?
- This is why...
those with seniority
should educate their juniors.
Why though?
Guys, congratulations
on the opening.
(Guys, congratulations
on the opening.)
What?
Congratulations.
I heard that a Room of Time
has been opened.
- Hey.
- Stop following us around.
- We won't allow you.
- You're not allowed.
- Leave.
- Stop him.
- This is cheating.
- You can't do this.
We won't allow you to go in.
The Room of Time
isn't some joke, you know.
Why is it only sought out
by the cheaters?
This isn't an easy place to find.
Are you judges former thugs?
You can't block my way.
Former thugs?
You're abusing your power.
You have to beat us both
in a game of rock-paper-scissors.
That's absurd.
- That's the rule.
- No way.
Why not?
- Rock-paper-scissors
(Kyung-hwan wins.)
- Move.
- What? You lost?
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kyung-hwan wins again.)
- Go ahead.
- He won.
(Darn...)
All right.
(He managed to clear
the made-up rule.)
I can't believe we both lost.
Gosh, seriously.
If I don't do this,
I won't be able to win.
A third of your time
will be taken away.
- A third of your time...
- "A person of your choice..."
"Steal half of the time
from a person chosen randomly."
Gosh, Kyung-hwan.
You need more screen time.
(The boring man is determined.)
(What will the roulette give him?)
"Steal half of the time
from a person chosen randomly."
I want Haha or Jong Kook.
(He can steal half of the time from
the member whose name he draws.)
I want Haha or Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook and Haha
have the most amount of time.)
I want Haha or Jong Kook.
(He gets Jong Kook,
who is in 1st place.)
I got Jong Kook.
Kyung-hwan drew a name...
Kyung-hwan stole half of your time.
Gosh.
He already had a lot of time.
Why did he do that?
(Jong Kook: 1st to 3rd place,
Kyung-hwan: 3rd to 2nd place)
Really? But I'm still at the top.
(Haha jumps to 1st place.)
(Also, Kwang Soo is now
way behind the others.)
- Suk Jin, where are you?
- Hi.
Are we on the 8th floor? The 9th?
(Kwang Soo is talking to Judge Jee.)
You guys can open the Room of Time,
right?
I'm the one who manages it.
- Okay.
- I'm the boss.
Okay, I'll pay you a visit
right now.
(Polite)
You'll pay me a visit?
Which floor is this?
- Come to the eighth floor.
- Yes, I'll be right there.
Thank you.
He must be up to something.
Kwang Soo knows the Room of Time
is where we are.
That's not it.
- He must have something to say.
- What do you mean?
He said he'd pay me a visit.
He wants to use the Room of Time.
Gosh, I can't believe him.
You don't even know the rules?
Did you stop caring
two and a half hours ago?
Let's hear him out first.
- He must have a reason.
- Then...
Se Chan and I will go up
to the ninth floor.
Suk Jin, you stay here...
- so that Kwang Soo can't follow us.
- Okay.
- You guys go ahead. Take this.
- We'll go up.
We have a very important role.
- You're like a team manager.
- Exactly.
I'm in charge of
the overall arrangement.
- Hi.
- Where...
- He's in there.
- Our boss is in there.
- Go to our boss.
- You did a great job.
- Of course.
(Flattering)
I'm sorry I'm late.
How do I look?
I wish you a happy new year.
All right.
It's been a while
since New Year's Day,
but I never got to bow to you then.
How much time do you have left?
I have only about 20 minutes left.
(Laughing)
I thought you had a lot of time.
I used to,
but in the end,
Haha switched his time with mine.
(Haha left Kwang Soo
with almost no time.)
I was right there, so I know.
- I'm the one who manages.
- That's right.
- I opened four rooms myself.
- You're right.
Who do you think opened
all the Rooms of Time?
- You did, Boss.
- Right?
- I always feel close to you.
- Feeling!
- Intuition!
- Cross!
(Feeling! Intuition! Cross!)
- Fine, I'll tell you where it is.
- Okay.
Wait.
Where did it go?
Oh, here it is.
(Kwang Soo wants to complain
but holds back.)
(Laughing)
I'll tell you where it is.
Rush there right now.
- Okay.
- But let's split it 60-40.
Take it or leave it.
I take 60.
(The negotiation is
about to break down.)
(Nervous)
- Oh, my.
- My goodness.
- You startled me.
- You look startled too.
I didn't know it was mere judges.
"Mere judges"?
- I had no idea.
- He arranges the whole thing.
- I set the whole thing up.
- Really?
How did you know
we were coming here?
I had a feeling there would be
something in the outdoor garden,
and I found the Room of Time here.
If I don't get ahead now...
If I tell them not to open it,
they can't.
- Should I wait there?
- I don't let everyone in.
- I'm sorry.
- This is driving me crazy.
This is my only shot.
- It's open.
- Okay!
- Is that it?
- It's open.
(The 4th Room of Time is open.)
The fourth Room of Time is open.
- All right.
- Wish me luck.
I wish you good luck.
Is that it?
The fourth Room of Time is open.
- Go to the ninth floor. Run!
- Okay.
- The garden on the ninth floor!
- Okay!
(I have to get in this time!)
"Switch time with a person
of your choice."
(But Jong Kook already entered
by paying a third of his time.)
(Will he get "Switch time
with a person of your choice"?)
(He got it!)
(Switch time with a person
of your choice.)
- You can switch time with someone.
- I got it for real.
It happened for real.
(Jong Kook can now switch time
with a person of his choice.)
(If he switches with Haha,
he can go back up to 1st place.)
I got it for real.
It happened for real.
Hold on.
"Steal half of the time
from a person chosen randomly."
Did Kyung-hwan get me?
(In the 3rd Room of Time)
He did?
(Kyung-hwan took
an hour and 50 minutes from him.)
(In the beginning of the race,
in the lobby...)
Be nice to me.
I got bitten by a zombie.
I might transform.
(Kyung-hwan was only pretending
to have a lot of time...)
(when he told Jong Kook
to run away.)
(Who will Jong Kook choose?)
I'll switch time with Kyung-hwan.
(Confident)
(He wants to switch time with
Kyung-hwan, who is in 2nd place.)
Jong Kook switched time with you.
He did?
He's so stupid.
(Why didn't he switch with Haha,
who is in 1st place?)
How much time do I have now?
Is that all?
Gosh!
He fooled me!
(Kyung-hwan, Jong Kook)
Why was I believing
Kyung-hwan had a lot of time?
(Kwang Soo runs to the Room of Time
a little late.)
Hey.
I was...
- Did you come here alone?
- Yes.
Why? Why did you rush here?
I'll be on my way.
(Where do you think you're going?)
Please!
(Kwang Soo, Jong Kook,)
(Kwang Soo's name tag is
ripped off.)
(Kwang Soo's 8 minutes and
39 seconds goes to Jong Kook.)
(Why did he even come here?)
Hey!
- Why did you...
- Gosh!
run straight to me?
I was actually a bit frustrated
after making a bad choice.
And you showed up.
Is the Room of Time over?
The fourth Room of Time is over.
(Haha, Jong Kook,
Kyung-hwan, Kwang Soo)
There's only one Room of Time left.
- There will be a twist.
- It's the last one.
We have the upper hand now.
(All of a sudden)
Why do we have the upper hand?
- We don't have much authority.
- Why not?
Just have a snack.
- Have a snack.
- I can take care of it.
Now that we have more people,
he seems to think
we can do something.
Wait and see.
It's not like that.
Here they come. Han Na and So Min.
(The new judges,
So Min and Han Na, join.)
Hurry up, the 4th and 5th judges!
Hello!
(Polite)
All right. Introduce yourselves.
- Hello.
- He's the first judge.
- He is in charge of arrangements.
- Have a seat.
- Let me give you...
- A little orientation?
- I'll give you a brief orientation.
- It's nothing much.
- Mr. Yu!
Let us start the drinking ceremony.
(A drinking ceremony,
all of a sudden?)
Stop it. We don't do that.
We don't do that.
I don't drink.
We don't do this kind of thing.
(The newbies are misled.)
- You just want to drink, right?
- We don't do that.
We stopped doing
a drinking ceremony a long time ago.
- We'll start a talent show now.
- Stop it.
Stop it now.
Also,
we're not at the center
of attention here.
- We're...
- We're on the sidelines.
We're on the sidelines.
Let's go up to the 13th floor
and open...
No, why don't we...
- Let's go.
- Okay.
(They get going.)
- Hey.
- Let's go.
- If we go up now.
- We have to get going.
- Let's go.
- Guys.
- Guys!
- Hurry up.
If we go up now, we'll get caught.
Come on.
I should go downstairs and see...
(Haha is looking
for the other members.)
I have to...
(Haha runs into Kwang Soo
who is barely alive.)
Come here.
- Do you want to join me or not?
- I want to.
You need time, don't you?
Follow me. I'll keep my hands
behind me.
(Kwang Soo has
neither time nor choice.)
Hurry up and push the button.
(I'll do as you say.)
Do you know where
the last Room of Time is?
- Suk Jin does.
- Okay.
If you and I hold hands...
Let me see.
How much time do you have?
50 minutes? 40 minutes?
- Yes. I'm worth it.
- You have 40 minutes?
Okay, let's stick together.
Come here. Stop looking away.
- Don't try to run away.
- Of course not.
- I'll be right back.
- Come here. Where are you going?
I need to find a name tag.
(Didn't you say you had 40 minutes?)
To be honest, I have
only about three minutes left.
(To be honest, I have
only about three minutes left.)
- You have only three minutes left?
- I'll be right back.
I'm sorry.
- I just want 10 more minutes.
- Hurry up.
(Haha is like a fisherman
releasing young fish.)
- Thank you!
- Are you looking for your name tag?
- Come here.
- Okay.
- Sir!
- Is this what you're looking for?
(Is this what you're looking for?)
- Sir!
- Is this what you're looking for?
Sir! If you give it to me...
If you give it to me...
- Is this what you're looking for?
- Just give me 10 minutes.
- Is this it?
- Yes. Give me 10 minutes.
- Do you have mine?
- No. I only have the others'.
- You were looking for this?
- This is driving me crazy.
- I'll give it to you if I find it.
- You can't find it anywhere, right?
(Thanks to Haha,
Kwang Soo gets 10 more minutes.)
(Kyung-hwan is in an elevator.)
Hey.
Why did you have to pretend?
You didn't have much time.
I should have switched with Haha!
I switched with you because
I thought you had a lot of time.
Why did you pretend?
You had less time than I did.
You did too.
What are you talking about?
I had plenty of time.
I had more than 3 hours.
I had almost 4 hours.
- Let's...
- You had almost nothing.
- Kwang Soo...
- Give me half of your time.
- Hold on.
- Come here!
- Wait.
- Gosh.
- Come here!
- Wait.
Gosh.
(Jong Kook gets 31 minutes.)
You had almost no time.
You were only pretending.
(Frustrated)
You had nothing.
Come here. We have to
work together to get Haha.
Why did I take your time away?
Because of you... Hold my hand.
Then let's go...
He's here. Jong Kook is here.
Jong Kook.
We can beat him if we join forces.
He is right. Why would you side
with him, you fool?
That's right. Come here.
- Let's hold hands.
- All right.
Think about it.
(But I gave you a name tag.)
Hold on.
(Kwang Soo switches allegiance
right away.)
Hold on. For goodness' sake.
(His eyes change.)
- You are right.
- Hold on.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Hurry up and rip his name tag.
- Hold on.
- We need to bring him down.
- Hold on. Hold on.
- Hurry up and hold him.
Rip off his name tag.
We don't need to listen to him.
(They spring to action
without hesitation.)
Rip off his name tag.
We don't need to listen to him.
(They grab at
each other's name tag.)
(Ripping)
(Haha removed
Kyung-hwan's name tag first.)
You kneeled in front of me
this whole time too.
Who knew
people could change so much?
- Seriously.
- What are those people?
What are those people?
Gosh, they startled me.
(What are those people?)
- Hey.
- What are those people?
- Gosh, they startled me.
- Hey.
"Minions" or "Us."
You guys look like the Minions.
"Us."
- "Us."
- We remind you of "Us," right?
I was so startled.
("Us")
You look so scary.
- "Us."
- What is going on?
We are moving toward
the grand finale.
- The result is out.
- Okay.
Haha removed Kyung-hwan's name tag.
(The result could change
the ranking.)
- Haha lost half of his time.
- Yes!
(The trio's combined time
was greater than Haha's.)
(They succeeded
to keep Haha in check.)
- Okay, okay. I get it.
- Haha just lost his time.
(Haha loses 1 hour and 15 minutes.)
(Haha, Jong Kook,
Kyung-hwan, and Kwang Soo)
Now, it all depends on when we open
the Room of Time.
This place is so pretty.
Here.
(The last Room of Time could change
the final outcome.)
- How unique!
- It all depends on when we open it.
When should we open it?
Let's follow the judges.
They are up to something.
As we passed by them earlier...
Guys.
This isn't how you do things.
You should wait on the first judge.
The fifth Room of Time is open.
It's open. Go in.
- Kwang Soo.
- It isn't open yet.
(Kwang Soo charges upon hearing
that it's open.)
It isn't open yet.
- It isn't open yet.
- You can't go in yet.
- Is it closed?
- Go in.
- It's closed.
You need to spin the roulette
anyway.
How could you be so rude to us
by running off without a thank you?
- Thank you.
- You were kneeling earlier.
I think I have 1 or 2 minutes left.
- Do you have two minutes left?
- Yes.
- So...
- Shall we wait three minutes?
Please give me a chance.
It would be entertaining
if Kwang Soo gets eliminated.
- The two of us...
- Kwang Soo is out.
(As soon as Jong Kook finishes
his sentence,)
(an entertaining situation occurs.)
(I said I don't have much time.)
- Hey.
- Congratulations.
You are done.
Go and change.
This is scary.
I started the day
with 3 hours and 30 minutes.
Go and change.
- An hour ago, he had 4 hours.
- The uniform is on the 14th floor.
I had four hours.
Listen. All of the judges...
- had a lot of time.
- You have a point.
- Nothing is permanent.
- You are right.
- Go.
- Go to the 14th floor.
- I will go and change.
- Okay.
It's one floor above.
(Haha, Jong Kook, and Kyung-hwan)
Let me enter the Room of Time.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- I shouldn't go too easy on you.
- We will open the room.
- Go ahead.
(The final outcome depends on
who enters the room.)
(The last Room of Time opens.)
The fifth Room of Time is open.
Whoever enters the room will win.
- The chance is high.
- It depends on the roulette.
- It does depend on the roulette.
- Rock-paper-scissors
(It's the last Room of Time.)
Rock-paper-scissors
(Kyung-hwan wins.)
Are you just going to let him enter?
- I am not the type to fight.
- He could get a dud.
That's right.
Here I go.
(He used his time
as the admission fee.)
Here I go.
(Kyung-hwan spun the roulette.)
(What will be the result
of his last chance?)
(Steal half of the time
from a person chosen randomly.)
Steal half of the time
from a person chosen randomly.
What?
(Steal half of the time
from a person chosen randomly?)
One of the slips has
Jong Kook's name.
You should steal Jong Kook's time
and rip off Haha's name tag.
(If he steals Haha's time,
he gets 35 minutes.)
(But it's not enough
to make him the top 1.)
(If he steals Jong Kook's time,
he gets 1 hour and 10 minutes.)
- That way, you will win.
- That's right.
(With half of Jong Kook's time,
he will be the top 1.)
Hurry up, will you?
(Kyung-hwan got...)
- Junior judge.
- That's right.
(Jong Kook!)
(Kyung-hwan gained
1 hour and 30 minutes.)
(Jong Kook lost
(With half of Jong Kook's time,
Kyung-hwan became the top 1!)
I have no hope. Hold on.
Should I team up with Haha
and remove Kyung-hwan's name tag?
No. Hold on.
If I team up with Haha
and remove Kyung-hwan's name tag...
(What should I do?)
How much time does Haha have?
I need to find Haha.
(Haha gets a call.)
Jong Kook.
Let's team up
and take out Kyung-hwan.
- Okay.
- Then we can have a face-off.
- Come down to the 9th floor.
- The 9th floor? Okay.
- Okay. Come to the back door.
- Okay.
(He quickly moves to the location.)
Kyung-hwan.
Jong Kook called me and suggested
that we take you out.
It will be a fight
between the two of you anyway.
- So...
- Hurry up, Haha.
Haha.
Hurry up.
Yes. Jong Kook is here.
Jong Kook.
I will go to the ninth floor.
(Kyung-hwan moves
to the meeting place.)
- We can join forces.
- Let's go.
I guess I can take you out
then go after him.
- Let me take off your name tag.
- This is exhausting.
Jong Kook.
(Kyung-hwan arrives!)
Hey.
- Jong Kook.
- Couldn't you hold on?
What do you mean?
I did that so far.
Jong Kook.
- Listen.
- Let's stop.
Let's stop.
Jong Kook doesn't have much time.
- What?
- Why do you have so little time?
Haha, come to me.
- It can't be helped.
- Okay.
- We need to finish this.
- I am sorry.
(Did Haha choose to side
with Kyung-hwan?)
It can't be helped.
We need to finish this.
Haha, hold my hand.
- Okay. I am done anyway.
- Yes.
(Is he giving up?)
Fine. Rip off my name tag.
- What?
- Rip off my name tag.
Should I do it here?
- Go ahead.
- Why would you do it elsewhere?
(His hand goes
for Jong Kook's name tag.)
The race is over.
- What happened?
- The race is over.
Kyung-hwan, what happened?
- Did Kyung-hwan win?
- I finally made it on Running Man.
- Did you make it?
- He is really cool.
Seeing as how you moved to the side,
you can't be the winner.
I don't think you won.
- Jong Kook, did you win?
- He rose from the bottom.
Congratulations. The final winner
of the Countdown Race is...
- Kim Jong Kook.
- How?
(The winner is Jong Kook,
not Kyung-hwan.)
How about this?
I rip off your name tag
about two times.
Then I get more time, right?
Then you team up with Kyung-hwan
without much time.
When Kyung-hwan
confidently rips off your name tag,
I will rip off his name tag.
How does that sound?
What do I get out of this?
- I will give you the prize.
- Really?
I will gain honor
and you will gain the prize.
- "Show Me the Money"!
- Yes.
- How does that sound?
- This is a pretty good deal.
Right?
(Haha, Jong Kook)
Rip off my name tag. Take my time.
(Haha lost 33 minutes
and Jong Kook gained 33 minutes.)
(He transferred time
to Jong Kook as promised.)
Gosh, I don't even know.
(Haha lost 16 minutes
and Jong Kook gained 16 minutes.)
(When Kyung-hwan moved in
to rip off Jong Kook's name tag)
Haha.
What are you doing?
(Jong Kook had more time
than Kyung-hwan.)
What are you doing?
(Jong Kook attacked
without hesitation.)
What are you doing?
(Ripping)
(He gained Kyung-hwan's time
and became the winner.)
The Room of Time is closed.
Since Jong Kook has more time...
than the rest of the members'
combined time,
we will end the race.
- Yes!
- I didn't know it would be so good.
It's Korean beef!
I didn't know
the prize would be Korean beef.
This is better than honor.
Let's have Han Na and Kyung-hwan
in the center.
- Come here.
- Kyung-hwan looks happy.
- Kyung-hwan.
- He thinks he was funny today.
They are like a family...
who always join us for Running Man.
We thank...
- Kyung-hwan...
- Thank you.
- and Han Na.
- Hello.
I was shocked when I took
a shower after the last shoot.
- Why?
- My thigh was bruised.
The strawberry game.
- You played too much of it.
- My palms hurt so much.
I was wondering
how I got that bruise.
You kept on criticizing yourself.
"Jae Suk".
When his name was called,
he went straight from this to this.
(Young Gu mode)
St-raw-berry, st-raw-berry
(He's an experienced comedian,
but he still gets really nervous.)
- Jae Suk is so...
- He was so bad.
There are two guests
who will be joining you.
- Really?
Come on out, guests.
Let's welcome them.
Gosh, Shin Hae Sun.
Hello.
Jong Ok.
Hae Sun.
(She can play roles
that are both charming...)
(and require deep emotions.)
(Actress Shin Hae Sun is
the hitmaker of films and dramas.)
(With 35 years of experience,)
(she plays a wide range of roles.)
(Bae Jong Ok is Korea's favorite
girl crush actress.)
- Hae Sun.
- Hello.
- How have you been?
- Come this way.
Hello.
- Jong Ok.
- Nice seeing you again, Kwang Soo.
- Long time, no see.
- It's been a long time.
- Hello.
It's very nice seeing you two.
She hasn't changed at all.
Please say hi first.
- Please say hi formally.
- Should I go first?
- Yes, go first.
- This is fascinating.
- Where should I look?
- Doesn't matter.
I see.
(He's mean to outsiders.)
- Hold on.
- Why would you say that?
You're being mean to guests.
- You were so rude.
- "Doesn't matter."
- Why would you say that?
- Don't be hurt.
I won't.
It's because he's an old fossil.
(Goodness)
- What's wrong?
- I'm in a daze.
- That was nothing.
- Stop it.
(That was nothing.)
(Old fossil Jee's
harsh variety show training)
- What's wrong with him?
- Why are you intimidating her?
Stop it.
Should I make him faint?
Why are you being mean?
I wanted to make her
feel comfortable.
These two starred...
in a movie called "Innocence."
Can you tell us
what the movie is about?
(Tap)
Sure.
(Her right hand is
the helping hand.)
You have strict rules.
I think Hae Sun...
Hae Sun handed it to her in
two hands, and she tossed it back.
- "You do it."
- "Take care of it."
They have strict rules.
She's an aide.
Jong Ok doesn't
beat around the bush.
She's very direct, right?
- Right.
- Yes.
She's very cool and friendly.
Is that right?
You look very intimidated.
No.
- Hae Sun.
- That's not true.
- Tell us.
- You don't look natural.
- That's so not true.
- You don't look close.
She was standing a foot away,
but when the topic was
about her and Jong Ok,
she was like, "That's not true."
- You saw her. She brushed her away.
- I know.
It's not like that.
"Innocence" is a movie...
about a lawyer
who defends her mom...
who has been falsely accused
of murder.
It's a story between
the mother and daughter.
- We have to watch this.
- You're mother and daughter.
I'm the lawyer.
Is it going to be released
at the same time as "Intruder"?
- March.
- Really?
March.
When?
In March too.
Oh, gosh.
It'll be great
if both movies do well.
- That'll be good.
- We'll both do good.
Both movies have to do well.
- Let's watch both.
- Sure.
Moo Yul.
- Moo Yul.
- Come on the show.
- Why is he not here?
- I don't know.
- He has to go around.
- Come on the show.
"Moo Yul".
Why is he not here?
This is Jong Ok's first time
on Running Man.
How do you feel?
I don't know if I can chase you.
- I feel very pressured,
- Is that right?
but I have Suk Jin,
so I think it'll be okay.
We'll walk when others run.
Yes, we'll walk.
Move your upper body fast and walk.
When you can't think,
lean on the young people.
Of course. Listen carefully
and catch what they say.
Say it like it was your idea.
That's good.
- That's what he did.
- He knew.
He knew and acted that way.
Omit what they say
and add your own lines.
You'll look smart.
You just need three of those.
I guess he doesn't watch himself.
What?
- They don't omit anything.
- I know.
I guess he doesn't read
the comments either.
Stop it.
Hae Sun is here with Jong Ok.
You don't look in that direction.
- No, I don't know where to look.
- Why not?
I never made eye contact with her.
- Me neither.
- She didn't look in that direction.
I didn't see beyond this.
I'm actually more comfortable
on this side.
- Right?
- I know what you mean.
- That side is more comfortable.
Their looks are below average,
so our side is more comfortable.
I agree.
I'm looking straight ahead,
and I feel at ease.
I see.
The back of his head
also makes me feel at ease.
- The back of his head?
- Hey, thanks.
(You make me feel at ease too.)
Thanks for making me feel at ease.
- Because of me?
- Yes, I only stand next to you.
No wonder.
The two pairs on Running Man.
What?
- Two pairs?
- Such comfortable people.
- Ridiculous.
- This is driving me nuts.
- Protuberant Brothers.
- Goodness.
What Protuberant Brothers?
Protuberant Brothers.
Today is the Indoor Special Part 2:
- Decide Bag, Innocence Race.
- Innocence Race.
When actors are guests,
they are moved here.
- The title.
- Our title is...
- related to the movie title.
- It's great.
We're good with play on words.
It doesn't sound bad either.
Decide Bag.
Decide Bag, Innocence Race
will be played in two teams.
The two teams are
Team Jong Ok and Team Hae Sun.
As you see,
in the good and bad zones,
there are 30 bags each.
The good zone has 19 plus values,
9 minus values, 1 switch chance,
and 1 double chance.
There are 30 bags in total.
In contrast, the bad zone has...
9 plus values, 19 minus values,
1 switch chance,
and 1 double chance.
There are 30 bags as well.
The chance to switch sounds good.
After playing three rounds of games,
the winning team can each choose
a bag from the good zone.
The losing team has to choose a bag
from the bad zone.
(Each member of the losing team
chooses a bag from the bad zone.)
After each round, the rankings
and your amount will be revealed.
At the end of the race,
1st and 2nd places
with the most money will win prizes.
The last two will
receive punishments.
The punishments are back.
Before we start, you'll play games
to earn your seed money.
Let's go to a different location,
and I'll explain the rules to you.
- Okay.
(They go somewhere else
to earn seed money.)
I don't want to doubt other people.
- I'm innocent.
- I'm already innocent.
I'm completely innocent.
There's a love square here.
What love square?
You two have some chemistry.
(Se Chan and So Min have chemistry.)
Jong Kook and Se Chan have
some chemistry.
We have some chemistry too.
- Suk Jin is an island.
- That's one-sided chemistry.
(Suk Jin is an island.)
It's one-sided.
It's a one-sided chemistry.
One-sided.
Lone island.
He's a lone island.
My gosh.
He's by himself.
You guys are ridiculous.
Why are our cars here too?
Our cars are all here.
The license plates are covered too.
- That's true.
- True.
(Vehicles are lined up.)
- Our names are on them.
- Right. Our names are on them.
Our names are on them.
Here's the mission to obtain
your individual seed money.
Ten cars that belong to you all
are lined up behind you.
You must get in the car
that's not yours.
You have 10 minutes...
to either steal something
inside the car or not.
That's up to you.
However,
members with the minority decision
will earn more money.
Minority decision.
- This is a mental game.
- This is going to drive me nuts.
If the side that stole the items
is the minority,
you will earn five dollars...
- per item.
- Per item?
It's better to steal more items.
Right. If you steal 20 items,
how much do you get?
- 2 times 5...
- 100 dollars?
100 dollars.
It's not 1,000 dollars, Kwang Soo.
- You asked suddenly.
- It's 100 dollars.
If the side that didn't steal
anything is the minority,
each person will get 50 dollars.
(They will get 50 dollars each.)
What am I supposed to do?
The side
that's not part of the minority...
will get 10 dollars each.
If you bring multiple same items,
they count as one.
Dress shoes and sneakers count
as one each,
but 2 toothbrushes count for 1 only.
It's not easy to steal things
from Jong Ok's car.
- Suk Jin too.
- Why?
You don't know
what you're going to find.
There'll be nothing to steal
from Suk Jin's car.
Kwang Soo and So Min...
- I won't steal.
- 100 percent they will.
They will steal
regardless of their intentions.
- They will steal.
- No.
- It's their instinct.
- They're greedy.
- Their hands move first.
- It's a habit.
I'm most curious about Jong Ok.
- I know.
- Let's watch her.
I wonder
if she's going to steal or not.
Maybe she'll return
with her hands full.
Imagine her walking back
with a tire.
Or a steering wheel.
What about you, Hae Sun?
What about me?
- Do you usually steal?
- What kind of a question is that?
She can't tell the truth
if she does.
I meant...
You always wear
those life jackets too.
- Life jackets.
- I want to save you.
I remember stealing
my friend's eraser when I was young.
We haven't heard
Hae Sun's response yet.
- I know.
- Be quiet.
- Stop it.
- I don't think we'll hear it.
Stop.
This is a battlefield.
How do you think you'll be?
Thank you for
giving me the opportunity.
Don't say something like that,
Hae Sun.
- Is it an award acceptance speech?
- Just talk.
I think I'll steal.
- Really?
- That's her style.
I heard that...
Jong Ok and Hae Sun have one scene
together in the movie.
(They have one scene together
in the movie.)
Scenes where they overlap?
No wonder they're so awkward
with each other.
- Only one scene?
- I was watching them,
- and they didn't look too close.
- They looked awkward.
We're not close.
We're mother and daughter
who cut ties with each other.
- We cut ties.
- They looked cool.
We predicted correctly.
- That's true.
- You were right.
- Right, they're awkward.
- Did you feel it?
- It was so obvious.
- We were awkward with each other.
Hae Sun might be...
more comfortable with me
than Jong Ok right now.
Why would she feel more comfortable
around you?
She and I met three times
on different TV shows.
- Your face is comforting.
- That's right.
His face is the most comforting.
I heard a sad story on my way here.
- What?
- I won't name the TV show.
The two movies' promotion period
overlapped.
- So it was Jong Ok and Hae Sun...
- Go on.
(Jong Ok and Hae Sun's "Innocence")
versus Ji Hyo and Moo Yul.
Their movies will be released
at the same time. It's quite sad.
- You will get teary-eyed.
- Don't laugh.
Ji Hyo and Moo Yul wanted to promote
their movie on a certain show,
but they...
(But they...)
(got turned down.)
(Emotional)
- They got turned down.
- Both movies will be a hit.
Ji Hyo made one comment.
"We won't promote our movie."
("We won't promote our movie.")
- My goodness.
- TV shows can't help but choose...
when two movies are released
around the same time.
- Jong Ok needs this too.
- Both movies will be a hit.
- Let's go!
- Good luck!
- Moo Yul, let's work hard.
Choi Moo Yul, let's go!
(Choi Moo Yul, let's go!)
It's Kim Moo Yul.
(Ji Hyo chimes in hurriedly.)
- What?
- Jae Suk.
- What is wrong with you?
- It's Kim Moo Yul.
Okay.
I am sorry, Moo Yul.
I was only trying to help.
I hope I didn't hurt your feelings.
I am sorry.
"Innocence," let's go.
"Intruder," let's go.
Run to the vehicle
when you hear the whistle.
Get ready.
- Let's go.
- I am torn.
Will more people steal
or leave things as they are?
I won't go to Suk Jin's vehicle.
- There are no items.
- In that vehicle,
- you will only find an e-cigarette.
- That's right.
(He is a poor man.)
I won't go to Suk Jin's vehicle.
Let's begin. Get ready.
- Set.
- I will go to any car.
- Suk Jin.
- Yes?
I didn't say "Go."
What are you doing?
I would have arrived last anyway.
If you hesitate,
only Suk Jin's car will remain.
Get ready.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Set.
(Set, go!)
(Running)
- What should I do?
- Jong Ok.
- No.
- Hold on.
(Jong Ok enters Haha's car.)
I should enter Suk Jin's car.
There is nothing in here.
I see that he is poor.
What is this?
My goodness.
(Kwang Soo enters Jong Kook's car;
Jae Suk enters Kwang Soo's car.)
Look at what Kwang Soo has!
For goodness' sake.
- Kwang Soo is a nuisance.
- What?
- Jae Suk, that's...
- What is this?
(It's a princess mirror.)
What is this?
It's such a big mirror.
Why doesn't he carry around
a smaller mirror?
Why did Kwang Soo leave
his wallet in here?
Gosh, Kwang Soo...
He has 23 dollars in his wallet.
(He has a lot of self-love
and not much money.)
There are so many things
in this car.
I should steal 10 things...
at the very least.
(Kwang Soo decides to become
a big-time thief.)
Even if I am not the minority,
I should do my best.
(Jong Kook's car)
(He is emptying the car.)
I feel like a real thief.
This is a bankbook.
- Your fly is open.
- What?
(Stealing diligently
made his pants become unzipped.)
I am sorry.
Viewers,
it's a secret that my fly was open.
I feel bad about
going through an actress's bag.
She is reading a book.
(He finds a book!)
"The Long, Long Life of Trees."
(The title is
"The Long, Long Life of Trees.")
(He isn't interested in the book.)
(Suk Jin only reads it briefly.)
I should take one.
Did I put in the whole thing?
(The newbie of variety shows
is figuring things out.)
He is stealing.
(Se Chan's car)
(I need to be the minority.)
I'm not going to steal.
I am sorry.
(Haha's car)
I will get bread.
(Jong Ok steals bread
from Haha's car.)
(She looks around for more items.)
So you are done.
There is nothing more to steal.
Isn't this a hand sanitizer?
It's a hand sanitizer.
I will steal it.
Hand sanitizers
are hard to come by these days.
(Jong Ok steals everyday items.)
(Happy)
Who was Haha?
Haha.
(After stealing, she asks,
"Who was Haha?")
- Haha is...
- Is he the one in a hat?
- The one who was at the very end.
- The right end.
That's right.
I got confused for a second.
(I remember now.)
How many items is he stealing?
Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo became a big-time thief.)
(It looks like
he wants to set Guinness record.)
(Jong Kook's car)
(He's stealing a lot of items.)
(He gets an extra vest as well.)
Five,
(Times comes to an end.)
(The old thief returns hurriedly.)
One.
- Time's up.
- Where is everyone?
Now,
stop and come on out.
Everyone stole items.
This is bad.
We can't be the minority.
- Everyone stole items.
- I had no choice.
There are too many thieves.
We aren't the minority.
Everyone stole things.
This is unbelievable.
- I shouldn't have stolen things.
- I have a question for Jong Kook.
- Okay.
Do you apply eyeliner every day?
(It's a shocking revelation.)
(He found an eyeliner
in Jong Kook's car.)
- I found an eyeliner...
- Hey.
on your seat.
What is this about?
Jong Kook, close your eyes.
Why would I apply eyeliner?
Whose is it?
- Whose is it?
- You want your eyes to look bigger.
- No!
- It was on your seat.
- He applies eyeliner.
- It must be Gap Jin's.
- Gap Jin must apply eyeliner.
- Let me see your eyes.
- What is this?
- He isn't wearing eyeliner.
I don't wear makeup.
- It's an eyeliner.
- An eyeliner.
- I don't wear makeup.
- Kwang Soo.
I put 50 dollars in your wallet.
(Kwang Soo, you should have
50 dollars in your wallet.)
Jae Suk, why would you say that?
- You...
- It's not like that.
- You only had 23 dollars.
- I ran out of cash.
You should carry around some cash.
I put 50 dollars in your wallet.
- You should have that much.
- Thank you, Jae Suk.
Jong Ok has
a lot of health food in her car.
(Staring)
Jong Ok, is that your bag?
- No, no.
- Isn't this her bag?
- No.
- It's...
(It's not a designer bag.)
(It's a back cushion.)
(It looks like a designer bag.)
- I thought it was a bag.
- It looks like one.
It isn't a bag.
- You thought it was a designer bag.
- Yes, I did.
I was like,
"Why did Suk Jin steal her bag?"
It thought it was a designer bag.
Let me tell you about
Suk Jin's car.
(Jong Kook reveals something
in Suk Jin's car.)
By the driver's seat,
he has a cute photo of himself.
By the passenger seat,
- he has a photo of So Min.
- What?
(It's very shocking.)
- Really?
- Stop joking.
- A photo of me?
- I am dead serious.
- Is he crazy?
- In Suk Jin's car?
- I am dead serious. Go and check.
- Stop joking.
- Why?
- I mean...
- Are you serious?
- I am serious.
- Is he crazy?
- Do you really like So Min?
I had no idea. Stop joking.
I am not joking!
There is a photo of So Min!
- Really?
- Go and check.
- He must be out of his mind.
- Really?
- That's just wrong.
- Go and check.
- Are you serious?
- Suk Jin, do you really like me?
- What are you going to do?
- It's true! I see So Min's photo!
- Where?
- It's here.
- I was telling the truth.
- It's true! I see So Min's photo!
- Where?
- It's here.
- I was telling the truth.
(So Min's photo)
(There are Suk Jin's photo
and So Min's photo...)
(at the driver's seat
and passenger's seat.)
Who put it there?
- Who pulled this prank on me?
- He must be out of his mind.
It's not a prank!
- I saw it when I entered.
- Is this for real?
- What is this? Can they air this?
- He must be out of his mind.
It's no wonder
he gets so jealous of Se Chan.
He always picks on Se Chan.
I told you, So Min.
- You pulled this prank, right?
- Why would I do that?
I don't like this either.
Why would I do that?
I don't even sit there.
I always sit
behind the passenger's seat.
- I never look at the compartment.
- He looks from afar.
- I had never seen it before.
- Hey.
Why am I so popular?
Also,
did you buy...
- a women's bag recently?
- Why would I do that?
- What?
- Is there a women's bag?
There is a receipt
for a women's designer bag.
This is no joke.
- Watch what you say!
- What is going on?
(Did Suk Jin buy
a women's designer bag?)
- Watch what you say!
- What is going on?
- I am serious!
- Stop joking.
- What?
Stay right there.
Suk Jin must be out of his mind.
- What is going on?
- Listen.
I don't use that car!
- I just ride it for work.
- What kind of life is he living?
It's not my car, okay?
- This is driving me crazy.
- Who pulled this prank?
- Suk Jin.
- What?
"The luxury goods section
of a department store."
- "A women's bag."
- My goodness.
(A receipt for a women's bag
was found at Suk Jin's car.)
- It's expensive too.
- I never bought it.
- Hold on.
- See whose card was used!
See whose card was used!
- I mean...
- This is for real.
It wasn't my card.
If you are having an affair,
come clean right now.
Suk Jin must be out of his mind.
Then why do you have this
in your car?
Are you saying
your manager bought it?
I am sure he did. Give it to me.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin's wife!
I am sure his wife received it.
You did, right?
- This is insane.
- Suk Jin is in a lot of trouble.
I have a question.
I have never seen
this powder before.
- Tumeric?
- What is that?
- It's a root vegetable.
- A root vegetable?
Suk Jin! Trying to change
the subject won't work.
Give us an explanation about
the bag and So Min's photo.
(Jae Suk asks for an explanation.)
- This is driving me crazy.
- Who cares about tumeric?
I am innocent.
So Min, why did you put
your photo there?
I remember So Min with that handbag.
No way.
(Shaking)
- This can't be!
- I don't have that handbag.
- No!
I swear I just found out
her picture was there.
- I don't have the bag.
- I swear.
I don't have that handbag.
I don't even want to think about it,
so don't even mention it!
- Hold on.
- I knew.
- I didn't do it.
- What were you doing?
I know my manager did it.
Why are you rude to Se Chan
these days?
- He hit my joint this morning.
- I know.
I didn't hit you, you punk.
(He is kind of rough.)
Suk Jin looked at me and said,
"You lost a lot of weight."
"Why did you lose so much weight?"
(He tried to sound cute
and used his nasal voice.)
Really?
(He can't deny this.)
- This is insane.
- Cut it out.
This is
how the truth gets distorted.
- That was a confession.
- You heard him.
I heard him,
so I asked why he was saying that.
- I know.
- It was annoying.
I'm entirely innocent.
My wife...
knows the truth.
- She knows everything.
- Fine.
If it's the truth, say it.
We can edit it out.
Don't edit it out.
I have nothing to hide.
- The handbag...
- My picture...
What about the handbag?
Don't edit it out.
He says that now,
and he'll go to Chul Min later
and say, "Edit it out."
(Chul Min is the main producer.)
We'll watch this episode
in two weeks,
and if this is not on it,
you called.
You can include this.
- We're going to watch this.
- She has nothing to do with me.
"Mr. Noh, I'm in trouble."
(The CEO of Suk Jin's agency)
(He'll ask for help from his CEO.)
He'll clean up everything.
"Not this."
(It concludes
as a mere coincidence.)
This is driving me nuts.
Who was in my car?
- Me.
- Were you?
- What did you take?
- I took what I needed.
- Like what?
- Hand sanitizers are...
expensive these days.
He had this.
- You don't get to take it.
- She actually stole it.
She actually stole it.
- You don't get to keep it.
- Why did you steal it?
- I thought I could take it.
- No, Jong Ok.
You'll get arrested for it.
We have to return these.
- She took some bread too.
- Where's the bread from?
There was bread,
so I was going to eat some.
- You can have it.
- Have some.
You can have it.
If we can't take this,
let's use this throughout the day.
- Use it.
- I'm sorry,
but can we check your pockets
before you leave?
(She has a bad habit.)
She actually stole it.
I thought
we could actually take this.
- We can use it.
- She's so simple.
Go ahead.
- What did you take, Ji Hyo?
- I was inside Hae Sun's car.
You have a lot of things.
- My car is really dirty.
- She had so many things.
Did you steal her handbag?
Hae Sun's...
- Socks?
- She had one sock.
- It's not mine.
- Where is the other one?
It's not mine.
This.
- It's her stylist's.
- What's that?
- Really?
- It's not mine.
My bad.
Why did you bring her stylist's bag?
This bag is filled with things
that can't be aired on TV.
I also have a question.
- Why do you have a screwdriver?
- Why was that there?
I don't know.
Only professional car thieves
carry that.
- She's going to rob a place.
- Only car thieves carry that.
I know.
When car doors don't open,
- you can use this.
- Right.
Professional car thieves carry it.
- I've never seen these items.
- It's straight.
This too.
- You spray it up your nose.
- This too.
- That's embarrassing.
- She has rhinitis.
- You spray it up your nose.
- Rhinitis.
How do you use this?
- Do you do this?
- Yes.
(That's a bad demonstration.)
(Like this.)
- Is that what you do?
- I'm curious.
Hae Sun was slightly mad.
- She was glaring at me.
- She was.
- "Yes. Like this."
- My bad.
(Keep my rhinitis a secret.)
She was mad.
I have so many things in my pocket.
What do you have?
I stole your socks and tights.
I don't have tights.
I don't wear them.
Whose tights are these?
(He's flustered.)
- My stylist's.
- This.
Why did you take her stylist's?
It's not mine.
- My bad.
- Gosh.
- Why did you take the tights?
- That's what I saw.
It's weird for you
to steal my tights.
- I took what I saw.
- You should steal my heart, punk.
(Steal my heart, not the tights.)
(You can be the thief of my heart.)
Steal her heart, punk.
- Steal her heart.
- "You should steal my heart, punk."
(Se Chan is the thief
of So Min's heart.)
Which car were you in, So Min?
Ji Hyo's.
Her car had nothing.
Nothing. Her slippers and car keys.
There was something else though.
What?
(What is it?)
- There was a lighter.
- What?
Hey!
This is real, so please blur it out.
- That is not mine!
- It might burst.
(That is not mine!)
I told you not to smoke in the car,
you punk!
- It might burst.
- It has her name on it.
(He frames her.)
It's her stylist's.
- I told you not to do it!
- Ji Hyo.
- I'm sorry.
- Look at this too.
Look at how many toothbrushes
she has.
Quiet.
- Quiet.
(Gosh...)
Jong Ok,
can I borrow the hand sanitizer?
(Hand sanitizer from Haha's car)
- You need some?
- Great.
I hope you're healthy.
(Ji Hyo, be healthy.)
Haha, whose car were you in?
I have so many.
- What did you take?
- Is it Jae Suk's?
This first.
He studies the game of Go.
- Really?
- He studies Go in the morning.
- He's a typical old fossil.
- Old fossil.
- A typical old fossil.
- True old fossil.
What an old fossil.
Apgujeong Super Oldie.
(Yoo Jae Suk,
Apgujeong Super Oldie)
He had a lot of these too.
Yu San Seul.
- CD?
- Yu San Seul.
I really wanted this.
- You really like it.
- I really want it.
There were also many untitled DVDs,
but I didn't take those.
(He frames Jae Suk.)
(There were DVD's
with adult content...)
(stacked in Jae Suk's car.)
Stop being ridiculous!
He still has that habit.
There was a large TV inside.
You're insane.
I saw those,
- but I didn't take them.
- Stop being ridiculous.
- Does he still watch the DVD?
- Do you still watch it?
I don't watch it.
- I don't watch it.
- It's on USBs now.
It's compact now.
Are you innocent?
- Do you watch it off a USB?
- How do you know?
You watch it off a USB.
What else is there?
- Do you watch it on a USB?
- Movies.
- Why are you making a confession?
- A USB?
- What was that?
- Do you watch it?
- Movies.
- It's 2020.
- What are you saying?
- Movies.
- How many can you fit in it?
What did you bring?
Jong Kook's...
There's nothing inside your car.
I took everything.
Hey. What did you take?
Well,
- I wanted more money.
- He took Gap Jin's things too.
- He took everything.
- What's in your belly?
- What's that?
It's his instinct.
- Kwang Soo, don't be like this.
- What is it?
- He stole a lot of things.
I'm sorry, Jong Kook.
(Spilling)
Well...
Goodness.
(That's just from his belly.)
- My gosh.
- Why do you do this?
- Because everything counts.
- Seriously.
He stole everything.
- A bracelet too.
- It'll be a hassle.
That rascal.
- When will you clean all this up?
- When will you clean it up?
You have to clean this up.
- It's endless.
- How did you take all those?
He's so tiring.
- My gosh.
- He's so tiring to have around.
Put these back now.
- Clean these up.
- Put them back.
Put them back. What did you do?
You robbed his car.
So the minority group goes
to those who didn't steal.
Hae Sun and Jong Kook get
50 dollars each.
(Hae Sun and Jong Kook didn't steal
anything, so they get 50 each.)
Thank you.
I considered not stealing as well.
Right, that's for us.
- We only get 10 dollars.
- I shouldn't have stolen anything.
They still give us 10 dollars.
You obtained your seed money,
so we have to decide the teams.
The two guests are the captains.
Do rock-paper-scissors...
- All right.
- and the winner picks.
(Team Jong Ok, Team Hae Sun)
So Min will be uncomfortable
on this team.
Why?
- Because of you.
- You're wrong!
Will you be okay?
Give him back the designer bag.
(The foolish love story
doesn't die down.)
(Good luck, Suk Jin!)
(And it isn't over yet.)
(Meanwhile,
he has to lie down alone,)
(and he can't hold back
his laughter.)
Good job!
(In order to win, you must hide
your movements and expressions.)
(However,)
(a guilty person is found.)
(In order to protect their
seed money,)
(they must trick
and lie to each other.)
(Until your lies become a reality)
(We'll trick everybody
until the end.)
(Decide! Bag, Part Two)