- Hello.
Ji Hyo.
- She's ready to hit the slopes.
- Ji Hyo.
Hey.
- Come here.
- She's going to a bathhouse.
- What are you talking about?
- Cavewoman Ji Hyo.
- Come here.
- Come on here, Ji Hyo.
Cavewoman Ji Hyo, come here.
You're precious...
in Running Man.
Don't say things like that.
- That's too much.
- If it's strange, they can edit it.
- Ji Hyo would feel offended.
- Why would she?
Too much attention can
make her feel daunted.
- Right, Ji Hyo?
- Yes.
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo draws the line.)
He's getting criticized
from the beginning.
What did I do wrong?
- Hey, I just thought...
- What did I do?
you were an answering robot.
- "Yes."
- She sounds like a robot.
(I can't answer that question.)
- And today...
- Yes.
Last weekend,
something happened to Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo is not here.
- There's unfortunate news.
- I feel bad for him.
Kwang Soo was in a car accident.
And he broke his ankle.
Unfortunately, he couldn't
join us in this show today.
That's right.
He needs to have surgery.
He called me a lot.
He said, "I'm going
to the bathroom now."
- I guess he felt bad.
- I know.
Suk Jin also broke...
his ankle before.
When? On a TV show?
- It was in the early 2000s.
- A metal pin...
But there were
no articles about it.
Was it newspaper back then?
- But...
- No one knew about it.
- There were articles about it.
- Newspaper?
- There were articles.
- Really?
In some kind of tabloid.
(He's a living modern heritage.)
- There were articles.
- He was called Comedian A.
Hey, it's not like I did
something wrong.
While he was shooting a show...
(He sounds like an old man.)
We hope Kwang Soo will get better
soon. It will take a while though.
- Please don't worry about him.
- Kwang Soo will be back soon...
- Yes.
- with a bright smile.
And we have Cavewoman Ji Hyo
who lives under a rock.
(Cavewoman Ji Hyo is
her new popular character.)
- She's popular.
- She's really popular these days.
- Right.
- Me?
- Am I popular?
- Cavewoman Ji Hyo.
- Don't you go on the Internet?
- Hasn't anyone mentioned it to you?
- I had no idea.
- She doesn't even know it.
She doesn't know it either.
I guess she does live under a rock.
Look at her outfit today.
That's what Kim Hye Soo used to wear
in the drama, "One of a Pair."
- "One of a Pair"?
- That's not true.
- It sounds like she's an old woman.
- That's a very old drama.
I was going to say that.
This was popular at ski resorts
back in the 90s.
- That's not true.
- The headband.
It looks really old.
Good. Even her fashion is getting
far from the trend.
Her wall is getting higher.
Good. I like that.
- It's "newtro."
- She lives under a rock.
- Ji Hyo.
- "Newtro"?
Good. I like her new character.
Let me introduce today's guests
who will join you today.
- Okay.
- Please come on out.
(Who are they?)
Please come on out.
- Today... My gosh.
- Who are they?
- Hello.
This is amazing.
(Kang Tae Oh, Lee Na Eun, Yura)
- Yura.
- It's Yura.
(Yura was a member of Girl's Day
with sexy charm.)
(Now she's back as an actress.)
(Na Eun is
the pretty center of April.)
(And she turned into an actress
being loved by teenagers.)
(A monstrous actor
with charisma, Kang Tae Oh)
(He showed off his poppin dance
in Episode 483.)
(He's a new all-around player
for variety shows.)
(Kang Tae Oh)
He's good.
(Yura, Na Eun, and Tae Oh
are here in Running Man.)
Yura, you haven't changed.
Thank you for coming here today.
- Tae Oh.
- He's here again.
- Nice to see you.
Come here to the middle.
- It's Na Hee.
- Hey, Na Hee.
Na Hee, come here.
(She took 5th place with her
powerful voice in "Miss Trot".)
They all are very popular
these days.
- This is amazing.
- That's right.
Yura. Gosh, Yura.
- Yura.
- What about me?
You've become prettier.
- You look amazing.
- Thank you.
- I knew it.
- Look at her fashion. It's modern.
- Modern?
- Did you say modern?
- It looks modern.
- Why would you say that?
Ji Hyo would feel
embarrassed to hear that.
Stand next to me.
Then you'll look modern.
It looks like
she's from 20 years ago.
Ji Hyo, you look like a bandit
from a distance.
Ji Hyo.
- You need a big chunk of meat.
- "Chunk of meat".
So...
I'm sorry.
Suk Jin is not feeling good today.
- That's right.
- You will have a hard time.
Are you putting too much energy
into your personal broadcasting?
- That's not true.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Tell us how you've been doing.
Well...
I've been getting some rest.
- The whole time?
- I got some rest.
And I had some time
for self-improvement.
Self-improvement?
What did you do
for self-improvement?
- What did you do?
- Actually,
it means...
she stayed at home.
What did you do
for self-improvement?
For example, I studied English.
- Say something in English.
- No, I can't.
- Hey, Suk Jin.
- What?
She's just getting back...
to appearing on TV shows
after a long time.
And you ask her to speak in English?
She said she studied
English at home.
- That's too much.
- Hey, I'm just...
trying to spice things up
to make it fun.
(It more fun this way.)
Spice things up?
But you're not doing it right.
Why are you cursing at me?
He's become rough.
- He has a temper.
- I know.
He's changed
since he started his own channel.
- I'm very disappointed.
- Why?
I thought he never got mad.
I don't have a temper.
- Seriously...
- I'm smiling now.
- I'm not upset.
- You're throwing a tantrum.
I'm not throwing
a tantrum, you punk.
- He lost his temper again.
- I'm smiling now.
- You do sound upset now.
- No, I'm not.
(I'm not upset.)
Next, we have Na Eun here.
(She's a good singer and actress,
Na Eun of April.)
Na Eun is...
- the host of "Inkigayo."
- She's really good.
She's been in many famous TV shows.
"Inkigayo"?
Oh, that's right.
- That's right.
- I used to host "Inkigayo" too.
Did you do that?
(Ji Hyo was the host of "Inkigayo"
from 2007 to 2008.)
Hee Chul.
"Music Core"... I mean...
(Did she say "Music Core" in SBS?)
It's Inkigayo.
- How does it feel...
- Inkigayo!
(She zoned out there too.)
- She hosted "Inkigayo."
- I see.
Are you sure it wasn't "Best 20"?
Wasn't it "Gayo Top 10"?
- I thought it was "Gayo Top 10."
- That's what Jong Kook did.
Jong Kook did it?
I used to appear in "Gayo Top 10."
He was in the show.
I'm in the picture the cast
took together on the last day.
Really?
- With Son Beom Soo?
- Son Beom Soo?
(He was in the last episode of
"Gayo Top 10" with Beom Soo.)
He's really old.
(Turbo was a 1st place nominee
in the last episode.)
(Gayo Top 10, Final Results)
(Unfortunately, Turbo couldn't
take 1st place in the last episode.)
(Depressed)
I still remember the last episode.
That's amazing.
Next up is Tae Oh.
He's our friend.
- It's Tae Oh.
- Tae Oh...
- is a good dancer.
- His dance.
He danced with his neck.
That was great.
I heard Tae Oh...
- prepared something upgraded.
- Really?
- Did you prepare something?
- Let's watch it together.
I feel a lot of pressure.
- He did this.
- I'm a big fan.
Show us the dance.
Right.
He was really good back then.
- Catallena
- Good.
(He warms up himself
with extraordinary moves.)
- Look at that.
- Start it.
Let's go.
(It begins now.)
My gosh.
That's good.
(Face poppin)
- What is he doing?
- Push it harder.
(Crumpling his face)
What's that? What are you doing?
What's that?
What kind of dance is it?
(They've never seen
dance moves like that before.)
(Then he starts doing
his signature dance.)
(Creaking)
(They all burst into laughter
watching him dance.)
That was nice.
I liked it.
- Gosh, it was...
- That was nice.
- I liked it.
- That's new.
- How does he do that?
- It's like a pantomime.
Gosh, it was...
- That was nice.
- Seriously,
entertainers like us should
reflect on ourselves.
- It was like a pantomime.
- It's like a pantomime.
I think he's a good replacement
for Kwang Soo.
(They have the same jaw.)
He's too handsome
to replace Kwang Soo.
That's true. He's too handsome.
That's right. He's good-looking.
Next up is Na Hee.
(Singer-comedian Na Hee
took 5th place in "Miss Trot.")
She's been working
with her mini-album.
We should hear her sing.
- Na Hee, please sing for us.
- Go ahead and sing.
- Shout it out.
- Show us.
I need you to respond to me.
("Fox and Wolf" by Kim Na Hee)
(Singing)
Sing with me!
I will only love you
(She fascinates everyone
making heart shapes.)
(She's good.)
She makes unique gestures.
(Her gestures steal
the hearts of the audience.)
(I will love you)
- Thank you.
She sings so well.
I couldn't help but notice
that she keeps making heart shapes.
- I do it without thinking.
- I see.
She turns her wrist like this.
Jae Suk, that's an L.
It's an L.
- Jae Suk.
- It's not a heart.
What is this?
(Flustered)
You just did this.
What is this?
You're not feeling very well today,
so just keep quiet.
(You're not feeling
very well today, remember?)
He told Suk Jin to stay quiet.
"You're not feeling well,
so just stay quiet."
Why are you being like that?
- You should rest.
- All I did was this.
He's trying to fill
Kwang Soo's absence.
Before we start the race,
we will pair up with a partner.
- Is it a couple race?
- 2, 4, and 5.
So there will be one man left.
- I know.
- There will be one man left.
You will decide your partner
with Dice of Love.
The six male members
will line up in order,
and the five female members
will throw the dice in turn.
And they will become a couple
with a man with the same number.
- I see.
- Okay.
- We should be careful lining up.
- So this is a random game.
- Please roll the dice now.
- Who should go first then?
- Should we go by age?
- Just stay still.
- Don't try to do anything.
- The men should line up.
The men should stand in line.
Let's play the rock-paper-scissors
and decide the order.
- Good.
- In order of good looks.
In order of good looks?
Ji Hyo wants you to stand
in order of good looks.
In order of good looks?
Then Tae Oh is in the right place.
- That's right.
- Jae Suk, come over here.
- This is about right.
- Come here.
- This is close.
- Jae Suk.
- It's about right.
- Come here.
- This is good.
- You should come.
We all are similar.
Let me judge it with a cool head.
- Jong Kook, move ahead.
- It's okay.
- Just go.
- Right.
Why are we doing this?
Why are you being like this to me?
- What did I do?
- Come here.
You should go over there.
- This is ridiculous.
- Just go.
- Gosh, you...
- Jae Suk.
Se Chan, say something.
- You should go backward.
- You can't be here.
(Move over, Jae Suk.)
You should go over there.
- Gosh.
- Move over, Suk Jin.
You two should be over there.
I can't believe this.
- All right. It's okay.
- This is right.
This is disappointing.
- Let me throw it.
- I have no choice.
1, 2, and 3.
(Which male member
will be Ji Hyo's partner?)
Number five.
(Number 5 is...)
It's Suk Jin.
- You picked a good one.
- Go to her.
You two look like a couple.
Did you see Suk Jin's face?
Since Ji Hyo picked him...
(Clenching his teeth)
- He's really funny.
- That's great.
- All right.
- You two look good together.
- It's Na Hee's turn.
- Na Hee.
- I'm number three.
- There's no number five.
- It's six.
- Jae Suk.
I'm Na Hee's partner.
- This was apart.
Na Hee and I are a couple.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
(Who will be a couple with Yura?)
- Number 4.
(Se Chan is picked.)
(Smiling broadly)
Se Chan is excited.
I guess Se Chan feels
comfortable around her.
(Frustrated)
So Min is upset,
but she's holding back her anger.
That's not it. Please...
I hope it will be number one.
Number one?
Okay. Number one.
Let's do this. They are numbers
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, and 6.
- Number 1 to 6.
- So you're number 1 or 4.
- Number 4 is also Tae Oh.
- Pick 1 or 4.
Please.
Number four.
(As So Min wishes,)
(will she pick 1 or 4
and become a couple with Tae Oh?)
Please.
Number four.
(Number 1)
(It's a party.)
She's really happy.
- This is fate.
- How did this happen?
That's amazing.
(Why is he dancing?)
Se Chan is pretending to like it.
Did you see that?
(He's caught.)
- I saw it.
- Did you?
- You saw that, right?
- He was dancing like this.
- That's not what he usually does.
- It's strange.
Stop it.
(She's just happy.)
All right. Jong Kook is...
- numbers 1, 3, or 5.
- Odd numbers.
- Odd numbers and even numbers.
- Haha is...
numbers 2, 4, or 6.
(Na Eun is the last female number.)
(Na Eun's choice will decide
who will go solo.)
Where is it going?
(Who will go solo?
Is it Jong Kook or Haha?)
One of them will be left alone.
Gosh, where is it going?
- Gosh, this is...
- What's the number?
- It's 3.
- 3!
(It's number 3.)
Number three.
It's Jong Kook.
(That means Haha is going solo.)
Haha is alone.
I wish Kwang Soo was here.
He likes it.
Okay.
I'm so unlucky.
(I'm so unlucky.)
I have no luck.
Nothing goes as I intended.
(They are done
picking their partners.)
(Couples)
Today, you will throw the dice,
and the number you get...
will decide prize or punishment.
It's Indoor Special Part 3:
Throw Double or Nothing.
I like things like this.
Three couples will win 20 dollars
each in each round.
After each round ends,
all couples get a chance...
to throw dice
and win additional prize money.
Really?
What is that?
Repeated numbers
eliminate the couples.
Repeated numbers or one
Each couple will
roll the dice in turn.
If you meet the condition,
you will get prize money.
If you don't meet the condition,
you will be eliminated.
If you meet the condition
and survive,
you can decide whether
to continue or to stop.
If you choose to stop, it's over
with the prize money you win.
If you choose to continue,
you can try the next step.
If you succeed,
you will get prize money.
And if you fail, you will lose
all the prize money you've saved.
(If they fail, they will lose
all the prize money they've saved.)
The couple with the largest amount
of money will get a prize.
And the ones with the lowest amount
of money will suffer a penalty.
(The last 2 couples
will receive penalties.)
First, let's divide the team
into groups of 6 and 5.
Na Eun.
- Haha.
- Thanks.
You'll be teamed up
with the same colors.
- Red?
- Oh, no.
- Blue.
- Okay!
- We're too weak.
- I love this team.
- We're in trouble.
- I love this.
For the first mission,
you'll need to find your opponents
without laughing.
It's called
Don't Laugh Hide-and-Seek.
This must be one of those
"don't laugh" games.
The defending team of six
will get a makeover...
and hide within five minutes.
The other team...
will have to find them
in the given time.
If you smile or cry
once the game starts,
you'll be eliminated.
Both teams will take turns.
The team that finds
the most opposing members...
wins.
Please change
into your uniforms now.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Do we have to wear these vests?
- Yes, you have to wear it inside.
Why did we come in this way?
Sure.
(She hands her jacket to him.)
Everyone likes to hand
their clothes to me.
It's as if I'm a hanger.
(Let's find out.)
(She naturally handed it over
to him.)
(They gave it to him.)
I've carried as many as seven items.
I have.
She must've done it often.
It was natural.
- You seemed like her butler.
- Right?
It was natural for both of us.
(You make me feel comfortable.)
Will we get full makeovers?
- Will the attacking team...
- The defending team.
Right. All of them?
What should I do?
There are many options.
What could be funny?
I think that headband
would be funny.
(It would be hilarious for sure.)
You wouldn't need to do anything,
and they'd all laugh.
The first mission is called...
Offense and Defense
Don't Laugh Hide-and-Seek.
"Don't Laugh".
It's easy. It's just hide-and-seek.
The defending team will hide.
The attacking team will be given...
20 minutes to find them as couples.
They will have to touch them.
However, if the attacking team
laughs while seeking them,
they'll be eliminated.
Even if one partner laughs,
both of you will be eliminated.
After that, the next couple will go.
The couple who finds
the most members wins.
If you find all of them,
we'll give you five extra points.
- Do you laugh easily?
- I really do.
You do?
(She answers cheerfully.)
That's not good.
- You can't be like that.
- You're giving me hope, Na Eun.
Pick which team will go first.
Who will hide first?
We'll look for you guys first.
- You will?
- Okay.
- We'll be the attacking team.
I think it'll be wiser
to make them laugh first.
- Right?
- Team Blue will hide first.
Go on.
Instead of trying to make
your disguise look funny,
you should make the situation funny.
How about this?
They open a cabinet,
and Se Chan and I
are kissing inside.
Yes.
(That was an unexpected idea.)
- What do you mean?
- Yes.
- That would be hilarious.
- That would be.
That's funnier than getting
a funny makeover.
- I told you.
- Imagine them opening the door...
You'll look like a couple.
- Go over there.
- Hey.
- You'll look like a couple.
- You don't think Haha will laugh?
Of course, he will.
You need to make them laugh.
(They arrive at the dressing room.)
(There are various tools.)
(What kinds of makeovers
will they get?)
Which class are you in?
- Class of 28.
- I see.
- What about you?
- Class of 10.
"Class of 10"?
(He's like an aged junior.)
- You?
- Class of 07.
He's my senior.
He's pretty much your grandpa.
No. He's...
- I'm much higher than him.
- Don't be absurd.
We knew each other
before we even debuted.
- That's irrelevant.
- This punk knew me beforehand.
So... You shouldn't address me
like that.
- I'm sorry.
- This is a public place.
- You shouldn't say that.
I'm sorry for making you
feel uncomfortable.
When I was a newbie,
my seniors had
a misunderstanding about me.
- Why?
- They said I wasn't polite.
How did you greet them?
- This is how newbies say hi.
- It's like this.
- "Hello!"
- "Hello."
- I couldn't do that.
- You didn't have to shout.
"Hello." They were like this.
- "I'm fine." But he did this.
- But I...
"Hello."
(This was back when
he was a newbie.)
"Hello. Oh, hello."
They thought I was being impudent.
(Team Blue is getting dressed up.)
(What?)
(Is he coloring his lips
with a marker?)
Will this wash off?
- What are you doing?
- Will this?
Why are you coloring your lips
with that? We have lipstick.
- You do?
- Yes. Here you go.
(He's so clumsy.)
There's a variety of things.
(Yura is fascinated with the wigs.)
You'd look hilarious with that on.
- This isn't easy.
- What is that?
- Pippi Longstocking.
- Wear this.
- What's that? Should I?
- Yes.
- I think it's too small for you.
- We need to color our faces.
- Right?
(He's transformed.)
(Na Eun collapses
after seeing such a unique sight...)
(for the first time.)
Do I look funny?
- She really does laugh a lot.
- It's gone.
- What should I do?
- What should I do? It's so funny.
I think I'd laugh if, for example,
Na Eun went through so much
to look funny.
That would make me laugh.
We have only Ji Hyo to rely on.
We trust you.
(Sighing)
- What's wrong?
- That's the first thing...
you said here.
You'd look hilarious just smoking.
(He tries to frame her.)
(Do they really joke around
like this?)
That would be perfect.
I'll wear that headband
and cross my legs.
(She plays along with it.)
- I bet they'll all laugh.
- That'd be hilarious.
"Come here."
So Min looks amazing. I knew it.
- What is that?
- It better be funny.
- Hold on.
- It better be.
I trust Se Chan.
You better make me look funny.
What is she?
- Are you sure about this?
- Yes.
Why did she do that?
- It's not funny.
- I've only just begun.
(What is this?)
- Hey.
- You and I will be a team.
- I'll do the same.
- What is this? I don't look funny.
I need to use black now.
- So what in the world is she?
- What am I?
I'll make up one once I finish.
What?
(He's just doing it as he goes.)
- See? It's working.
- Come on.
- It's not even funny.
- Hold on.
- It's not funny.
- What is that?
No.
- No, So Min.
- What is this?
See? They're smirking.
Do we have no dresses?
- Give me the mirror.
- It'd look funny.
Am I done?
Hold on. We need to match.
(She's not happy anymore.)
What is this?
Look at our directors' faces.
They usually laugh a lot.
(Meanwhile...)
Don't I look funny?
Don't I?
(She's happy
with her first attempt.)
Do I not?
We'll be...
Okay? I'll give you a sign.
If we were going to do that,
this wasn't necessary.
- It's more fun this way.
- No, it's not.
- Jong Kook.
- Look at us.
- Will you turn on some music?
- Isn't this nice?
- It is.
- It is, right?
- Yes.
You have one minute remaining.
We need to hide.
- Do we hide anywhere we want?
- Let's hide.
(Team Blue is done.)
(Now, they just need to hide.)
Excuse me, but do you mind
if I hid in here?
I'll hide here.
- Like this.
- I'll cover you up. Hold on.
Are you done? Here we go.
10,
9, 8,
7, 6,
5, 4,
three,
two,
one.
First couple, please come in.
- We'll go first.
- Since you guys laugh the most?
- Right.
- Good luck.
- We'll go first.
Good luck.
Goodness, Na Hee.
(He's nervous already.)
I laugh so easily.
You smile easily as well.
This isn't good.
You smile all the time.
There aren't many places to hide.
How about in here?
- There are people working.
- I think they're in here.
There are people working.
(Na Eun is hiding under this desk.)
(She could get caught already.)
Is someone in there?
How should I move?
(I can't get caught already.)
(Something smells fishy in here.)
(Suddenly,)
(they hear music.)
(Na Eun is safe.)
(They look for the source
of the music.)
Wait.
This music is already
making me laugh.
Hey.
- Na Hee, I'm about to laugh.
- Yes?
No. I'm going to hold it in.
I'll slap myself to keep it in.
(Why is the soundtrack
for "Ghost" playing?)
(This sexy music leads them...)
(to this couple suffering
from jaundice.)
I did expect something like this.
(They look very passionate.)
(He bursts out laughing.)
(He bursts out laughing,
and they fail.)
(Did they have to go this far?)
Are you seriously going
to be like this?
Na Hee, what should I do?
Goodness. I did expect something.
I did, but I couldn't hold back.
Are you serious?
- This is cheating.
- Are you serious?
(Their makeover was worth it.)
- You've failed!
- You guys...
- You may leave.
- Na Hee.
You can't tell the others.
- You can't let them know.
- Don't tell the others.
- Na Hee, don't tell the others.
- The music...
Goodness.
I started laughing
the moment I heard the music.
I predicted
something like this though.
Even if you didn't laugh...
- You would've?
- Yes.
My eyes were brimming with tears.
(After the storm...)
(comes a moment to reflect.)
Se Chan, tell Kwang Soo
to come back soon.
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo...
- We're trying this hard.
- Hurry back.
- Come back to us.
I had to paint my face
because you weren't here.
You and I were supposed to do this,
but So Min had to take your place.
(They miss Kwang Soo
even more today.)
(They realize it was spring
only after the flowers withered.)
I'm sorry.
We miss you.
(Kwang Soo, we miss you.)
Is it over already for them?
Unbelievable.
- It's over?
- Seriously?
Are you kidding me?
You're laughing?
- After what you did?
- Why are you still laughing?
- Sorry.
- Unbelievable.
I predicted their move but...
But it was still funny.
You need to prepare yourselves.
Wait, hold on a second, Ji Hyo.
Slap each other.
(Desperate measures
for Suk Jin and Ji Hyo)
(Let's make each other angry.)
(Are you ready, Suk Jin?)
Hey.
Let's go!
(He bursts into laughter
thanks to his partner's support.)
Let's get going.
You made me laugh even more.
We only have 20 minutes.
Hold back your laughter.
- Let's hold our laughter.
- That was nice, Ji Hyo.
That was nice.
- Good job.
- Punch me in the stomach.
- Go on.
- For real?
- Make me furious.
- Furious?
I'm not kidding.
Hold your jacket open.
(Groaning)
(She hits him hard
in the lower abdomen.)
(Was I too harsh?)
You hit my bladder.
Na Hee never does anything
half-heartedly.
- She never does.
- Okay, I'm mad now.
- It's not her style.
- Thanks, Na Hee.
Sure thing. Good luck.
- Let's go!
- Go for it.
Are they hiding?
(They carefully search
for the other team.)
Are we supposed to find them?
I thought that someone would be
disguised as a member of the staff.
Isn't this someone?
- The staff...
- No?
No, he's actually a staff member.
Found him.
You startled me.
(They spot Jong Kook
behind the pillar.)
Are you Annabelle?
Found him.
(Peekaboo!)
(He turns away.)
I found him.
Suk Jin is out.
- What?
- Suk Jin is out.
Seriously?
You...
What on earth are you wearing?
- Isn't it adorable?
- I locked eyes with him.
Jong Kook caught me off guard.
(My baby, we did it.)
Haha, go ahead.
- Go on.
- Why can't you hold your laughter?
I guess you could hold it.
It's easier since I'm alone.
- Since you're alone...
- It's doable.
- Wish me luck.
- Good luck!
Find them all to win five points.
Hold on.
Why do I suddenly want to laugh?
Ji Hyo, slap me.
I can't hold my laughter.
- Have Na Hee do it.
- Not Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo's slap will only
make you laugh.
- Didn't it make you angry?
- It did.
Then hit the back of my head.
- How?
- Make sure...
we all hear it loud and clear.
(Na Hee's good at
taking instructions.)
(Thump!)
(What?)
(His laughter is long gone.)
(She smacked him hard
like he wanted.)
You're angry, right?
- That's how Na Hee is.
- Get going.
My stomach...
Good luck.
It was like
she drove a hole through mine.
- Na Hee, good job.
- Was it your fist?
Good one. I loved it.
Na Hee's got the hang
of these comedy sketches now.
- Exactly.
- She knows how to make it work.
She's aware of the force
she should put in.
- Na Hee...
- You know how it should be done.
(Haha found Na Eun and Yura
without laughing.)
What did they find so hilarious?
(Haha found Na Eun and Yura
without laughing.)
(However, the yellow ghosts
made him burst out laughing.)
You two are crazy! My gosh.
I can't believe you two.
(Thanks to So Min and Se Chan,)
(Team Blue ends
their defense round.)
Unbelievable.
Na Eun only looks cute.
Na Eun, your disguise
only looks cute.
- But...
- I thought it was funny.
They all look cute, right?
I saw him and the doll.
That's when I couldn't
hold my laughter.
- The others...
- He didn't have to do anything.
- They all...
- Isn't it hilarious...
how the baby doll is smiling?
- It's smiling.
- My baby.
- This isn't an easy one.
- Tell me about it.
I was standing behind the pillar.
He was standing behind a pillar.
I turned towards him
and there he was.
- Right.
- Anyone would've laughed.
- So where's Tae Oh?
- Tae Oh?
- Is he still hiding?
- Tae Oh...
- Did everyone forget about him?
- Did we forget about him?
- Is that it?
(Meanwhile, under the table
in the director's office)
(Why isn't anyone coming?)
I think it's over.
Is it?
You can come out now.
(The game ended
with him under the table.)
Is it our turn now?
- Let's go.
- You'll see.
- Listen.
- You'd better be ready.
- Sure.
- Make it good, okay?
- Here.
- Jae Suk...
Jae Suk!
- Jae Suk!
- What?
- I have an idea.
- What is it?
Dress up like Choi Young In.
(Choi Young In,
Director of Variety Department)
- Director Choi?
- She's in her office.
- Got it.
- Sounds fun.
- I'll...
- It sounds like fun.
I'll dress up like Director Choi.
- It'll be hilarious.
- Borrow her glasses.
That'll be funny.
Director Choi.
- That's all you have to do.
- Director Choi.
You look exactly like her!
- Here you go.
- That's the best.
Borrow her glasses.
Would she lend me those?
(He heads out to borrow
her glasses and clothes.)
(Meanwhile, Team Blue...)
That's cute.
(Jong Kook is in love
with his baby.)
Look at how Jong Kook
doting on the baby.
I'll play with kids really well.
I never get exhausted.
The kids will get exhausted instead.
I should think about
having a kid of my own.
Kwang Soo's not here,
so I should step up.
How? Yes, go for it.
(The others are working
on their disguise.)
Ji Hyo's hilarious.
She is of an acting background.
(They make the final touches.)
I've tried everything else.
How hilarious.
Those who don't easily laugh
should go last.
Tae Oh and Jong Kook.
- Sure.
- Jong Kook,
are you taking the baby with you?
If you do, I'll laugh.
I'll leave it behind.
- Its eyebrows.
- You're worried...
that I'll make you laugh, right?
I was thinking
about taking it with me.
- Please don't.
- No?
It's too hilarious.
Are you all hidden?
Let's begin the game.
5, 4...
(The members of Team Red
are scattered.)
Three...
(Will they be able
to successfully play defense?)
Two...
(Director Choi was absent,
so Jae Suk changed his disguise.)
One. The first couple can enter.
- We'll set the tone.
- Sure.
Right, show them how it's done.
We'll go next. You and Na Eun...
- can be our last resort.
- Sure.
Hold on. Let me get ready.
Laugh right now then.
(Laughing)
You're the one
who's making me laugh.
- Right, just get it all out.
- Got it.
(Tae Oh and So Min seem unstable.)
Pinch me when I'm about to laugh.
Sure. Meanwhile, I won't laugh.
Okay, then stay a few steps
in front of me.
- Got it.
- All right.
I doubt they'll be hiding though.
They'd want to make us laugh.
(Where is everyone?)
Here.
(Lips are held tight.)
(Hello!)
(Running)
(The blue avatar boy loves to run.)
(They're close to laughing.)
(A U-turn)
(They're challenged once again.)
(Dashing)
(He loves to run.)
Tae Oh, touch him.
- Tag him.
- We have to tag him, right?
We have to. Get going.
Get over there and touch him.
(While the avatar boy
is at a halt...)
(So Min...)
(So Min tags Haha.)
(There are only 4 people left.)
- Did you do it?
- Yes. Let's go.
(They managed to get past Haha.)
(Lips are held tight.)
You said you don't laugh easily.
I've got a runny nose.
(He doesn't laugh,
but he has a runny nose?)
Gosh, Haha.
I was close to losing it.
Haha...
Wait. What's that?
(They suddenly hear a song playing.)
Someone's here. What are they doing?
(Isn't this "Any song" by ZICO?)
Hold on.
(Hipster ZICO)
(The disgusting Big Nosed Suk Jin)
(Suk Jin starts to dance...)
(and someone joins him.)
(Ji Hyo steals the attention.)
(What on earth is that?)
You've got to be kidding me, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo, you got them!
(She keeps a straight face.)
(Fully satisfied)
Our plan worked!
How can you not laugh at this?
Gosh, Ji Hyo. What are you doing?
What's up with you today?
No way.
- Almost everyone will laugh.
- Ji Hyo...
Just look at Ji Hyo!
- No one can top this.
- Hold on.
Are you all right?
What's wrong?
What happened to you? Are you drunk?
What's with you?
So Min, Tae Oh, you're out.
You can't tell your teammates
about what you saw.
I could deal with Suk Jin,
- but Ji Hyo...
- That was our plan.
Haha's the one who got me.
(Please look forward
to his fine work.)
I almost cried when I saw Haha.
Wait, where's Jae Suk?
(Music suddenly plays.)
(Someone is waiting.)
(Where is this music coming from?)
Jae Suk must have
prepared something.
(Is it Jae Suk?)
(So Min bursts out laughing
right away.)
You can't play music. It's cheating.
(Jae Suk shows up
with the sweet song, "Y" playing.)
It's cheating!
It's definitely cheating.
(Jae Suk gets into the groove.)
You can't use music!
(The half-man half-llama creature
walks down the runway.)
(Swaying)
(All his four legs move
to the rhythm elegantly.)
No, Ji Hyo was still funnier.
Ji Hyo was even funnier.
- No one could beat her.
- She was incredible.
(Immersed)
- What happened? You laughed, right?
- It was so funny.
Our team has no chance. It's over.
- Is it that bad?
- It's over.
- Are they stronger than us?
- Yes, they are.
Are they taking this seriously?
- Every one of them is hilarious.
- They are?
Really?
- The second couple,
- What should I do?
please enter.
- To be honest, I cried, Se Chan.
- Let me try.
- We'll try.
- You can do this.
You guys try.
How funny can it be?
We're angry right now.
- I'm really annoyed
- Get angry.
- Yang Se Hyeong!
- "Yang Se Hyeong"?
- Did you say, "Yang Se Hyeong"?
- Isn't that your name?
- Let's go.
- You're unknown.
I'm unknown?
(Angry)
- Hey.
- Yuri!
- "Yuri"?
- Go, Yuri.
- You're laughing?
- You shouldn't laugh.
- Go!
- Stop laughing.
- She thinks that's funny?
This is not good.
She thinks that's funny?
(We should never laugh.)
I think I'll laugh at
the most basic things. We're ready.
- Okay, go.
- Let's go.
Stay close to me.
(They see someone
as soon as they turn the corner.)
Hold on.
Wait.
(Someone is there!)
What's that?
(His position looks extraordinary.)
Is that Haha?
It's Haha.
- I think I'll laugh.
- Hold it back.
We have to hold it back.
I thought they would all be
hiding somewhere.
(Haha is ready to run.)
What is he doing? He's going to run.
(Peekaboo!)
(The avatar marathoner
runs down the hallway.)
(The 1st crisis)
(Running)
(Being too focused on looking funny,
Haha touches Yura by accident.)
(He continues running.)
(The avatar boy doesn't realize
that he's eliminated.)
(Se Chan and Yura manage
to overcome the crisis.)
(Am I eliminated?)
I'm acting right now.
I'm shooting a drama.
I'm angry.
I don't know how to laugh.
I'm a person who can't laugh.
Where are they? Where did Haha go?
(Yura is imagining
she's acting right now.)
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo)
(Suk Jin is waiting for them,
tapping on his nose.)
Is this a haunted house?
(Se Chan holds back his laughter.)
(Suk Jin dances to "Any Song.")
(Again, he is joined by...)
(Hong Du Kkae's wife who
is wearing a blue headband.)
(Se Chan bursts out laughing.)
(Yura's lips twitch too.)
Do you have to go this far?
(The dancers keep straight faces.)
They don't even know the dance!
(They have no clue.)
(Ignoring)
(Suk Jin, Hong Du Kkae's wife,
ZICO, Han Na)
Neither of them knows the dance!
Gosh, we can't beat them.
(These creative dancers
are improvising.)
They planned it very well.
What is this?
They don't even know the dance!
You can't dance to this song
if you don't know it! It's cheating!
(The straight-faced dancer leaves.)
What do you think of Ji Hyo?
Isn't her make-up realistic?
- What is this?
- You can't beat her, can you?
Isn't it so realistic?
You even prepared a headband?
This time...
Let's say we didn't laugh there.
Where's Jae Suk? I want to see him.
We can never beat them.
- Let's look for Jae Suk.
- Jae Suk...
- Where's Jae Suk?
- Where is he?
(Swaying)
(4-leg swag)
This is not okay!
We can't beat that. What is that?
He plays "Y" by Freestyle?
That's insane.
- He even plays music.
- We can't beat this.
Ji Hyo, I'm proud of you.
I think we should switch
with Jae Suk.
- They laugh there, right?
- Yes, totally.
They should enter from here
this time.
- Or... Jae Suk!
- Yes?
How about we switch places?
- Jae Suk should be here?
- Yes.
Gosh, Jong Kook.
- They're hilarious, aren't they?
- I cried.
I cried too.
I cried for real.
It makes you cry.
I think we laughed
at the same place as they did.
Like I said,
when someone acts out of character,
you become worried.
I'm worried right now.
You know who I mean, right?
Ji Hyo must have done
something unexpected.
What's funny is that...
- she doesn't even know the dance.
- Exactly.
- All right.
- Okay.
You can do this!
Please pass three people.
Just pass three people.
- We can do this.
- Na Eun, let's pass three people.
(Will Jong Kook and Na Eun manage
to hold back their laughter?)
- Brace yourself.
- I'm not going to laugh.
It's not going to be funny.
It's just make-up.
(They control their minds.)
(A moment later)
The winning team is...
(Who wins, Team Blue or Team Red?)
Team Blue.
Each member gets 20 dollars.
(Team Blue wins.)
- We lost?
- Yes.
Jong Kook didn't laugh, so we won.
I didn't think it was funny.
(Even though Team Red was hilarious,
they lost the game.)
- Can you hold back your laughter?
- Of course.
(Jong Kook and Na Eun
are playing the game.)
This is not funny.
(They pass the blue-faced
marathoner easily.)
(Embarrassed)
Did we touch him?
- We didn't.
- We should touch him.
(They suddenly change
their direction.)
We're used to this.
- This way.
- We should touch them first.
What are you doing?
You're going to dance
to "Any Song", right?
(They touch Jae Suk,
Na Hee, and Haha.)
- Did you touch him?
- Yes.
You're good at this!
- You're good.
- Okay!
When you changed your direction
to touch Haha, our plan was ruined.
(Jong Kook and Na Eun win easily
by changing direction.)
- They changed direction?
- Yes.
Too bad.
- The thing is...
- It's not over yet.
(The llama shouts.)
What do you mean?
Who are you?
- It's not over yet.
- Your face...
Where are you going?
Hey, where are you going?
- Hey.
- It's not over yet.
Where are you going?
- Hey!
- Where are you going?
(Where is he going?)
Where are you going?
(The llama gets in the elevator
without permission.)
Where is he going?
There aren't even any cameramen
following him.
There aren't even any cameramen!
Is he angry because I didn't laugh?
All of a sudden?
Did Jae Suk really leave?
Is he gone?
- The llama is back.
- Is he?
What is he doing?
What's with him?
Where were you?
Why did you leave
in the middle of the shoot?
(The half-man half-llama creature
is freestyling.)
He's still playing "Y" by Freestyle.
- He looks so ugly, by the way.
- He's still playing that song.
- Gosh, you're a mess.
- Where were you?
If this competition had been
about looking ugly,
we would have won.
You would have won first place.
- Seriously.
- You're incredible.
The couple with the biggest amount
of money wins a prize.
The couple with the smallest amount
of money...
- will receive a penalty.
- There's a penalty?
Let's throw the dice now.
The couples who
don't get a repeated number...
win 10 dollars and get to decide...
whether or not
to move on to the next stage.
- So we start at Stage 1?
- We always start at Stage 1?
- Okay.
- That sounds fun.
- We'll go first.
- Okay.
1, 2...
(Repeated numbers
eliminate the couples.)
It's 4.
If any couples get 4,
we'll be eliminated together.
(Any couples who throw 4
will be eliminated.)
- If you get 4, you're out.
- It's easy to get 4.
Who's Na Hee's partner?
- It's me.
- It's Jae Suk.
(It's Jae Suk and Na Hee's turn.)
Take your costume off now!
(It gets in the way.)
Jae Suk!
After all that effort,
he's disappointed by the fact
that not many people saw it.
- I should avoid the same number.
- If you get 4, you're out.
- If I get 4, I'm out?
- Yes.
If I don't, I survive.
(Repeated numbers
eliminate the couples.)
(Will he manage not to get 4
and pass Stage 1?)
It's 3!
(He gets 3 and survives for now.)
If anyone throws 3 or 4,
he or she is out, right?
If you get 3 or 4, you're out.
And I'll be out too, right?
Yes. If anyone gets 4.
(Will Tae Oh get something else
than 3 or 4?)
- It's 5.
- Okay!
(He gets 5 and survives for now.)
- Good job.
Yura, we should get 1...
- We need 1 or 6.
- You should get 6.
- 1 or 6?
- 1, 2, or 6.
- What did they just get?
- They got 5.
Just avoid 4.
We need 1 or 6.
(Se Chan and Yura have
a 50-percent chance to survive.)
We need 1 or 6.
(What's the result?)
- It's 6!
- Okay.
(They get 6 and survive for now.)
- It's 6!
- Okay.
- What?
It rolled many times.
They'll definitely fail.
This is not good.
- Na Eun, you should throw it.
- Me?
You do it.
I...
Please.
(They need to throw 1 or 2
to pass Stage 1.)
Please, 1.
It's 2.
(She got 2?)
(You did it?)
It's 2.
How did you do that?
We got 2, 3, 4, 5, and 6.
- Na Eun!
- You need to throw 1 now.
Unbelievable.
- Throw 1!
- You need 1!
(If Haha throws 1,
everyone will be happy.)
- You'll be surprised.
- Throw 1!
Throw 1, and it'll be perfect.
(Haha is going
to make it or break it.)
(After five successes in a row,
how will Haha do?)
It'll be incredible if he throws 1.
Don't throw 2.
(He throws 2 and fails.)
Who else got 2?
(Jong Kook, Na Eun,
and Haha are eliminated.)
Who else got 2?
You got 2?
I eliminated you guys.
(Haha manages
to eliminate one couple.)
You guys are eliminated.
The rest of you get to decide
whether or not to go on.
- We should!
- You should.
You should.
(Repeated numbers or 1
eliminate the couples.)
- Go.
- Let's go.
- All right.
(We won't sit out.)
Na Hee, let's do this.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
Avoid one or repeated numbers.
1, 2. Let's go.
(Will Ji Hyo and Suk Jin succeed
Stage 2?)
One. They are out.
(They lose 10 dollars
they won on Stage 1.)
They are out.
(Repeated numbers or 1
eliminate the couples.)
(It's a festival for the rest.)
(They enjoy another's failure more
than their own success.)
- All right.
- How did we get one?
I just need to avoid getting one.
(It's So Min's turn.)
She will get 1.
(Repeated numbers or 1
eliminate the couples.)
- 1!
(It's 1 again.)
- Everyone is so happy.
- I can't believe it.
(They showed everyone
the result of excessive greed.)
Everyone laughed the loudest.
Please let me avoid 1.
- One.
- Okay.
(They survived with 2.)
It's usually hard to get one.
- That's good.
- Seriously.
- Three.
- Okay.
(Se Chan and Yura succeed
Stage 2 as well.)
(Se Chan and Yura;
Jae Suk and Na Hee got 20 dollars.)
Will the two surviving teams
receive 20 dollars or keep going?
- Keep going.
- We will keep going.
"Odd numbers eliminate the couples."
You just need to get an even number.
Keep going.
Aren't you going to move on
to the next stage?
- You should. You should.
- Are you a coward?
If you are a coward, stop here.
- Let's keep going!
- Yes!
You made the right call.
- Just get an even number.
- An even number?
- Yes.
I hope they get an odd number.
Aren't the stakes too high
for Jae Suk to throw the dice?
- Are you sure that's wise?
- Na Hee, do you want to throw it?
Na Hee, we need an even number.
Throw it high.
- Throw it high. There you go.
- Okay.
(She throws the dice for Stage 3
with energy.)
(Odd numbers eliminate the couples.)
(They will get 40 dollars
if the number is even.)
(What will be the result?)
Okay!
(They succeed Stage 3.)
(Jae Suk and Na Hee hit
the jackpot.)
Okay. All right.
- All right, Yura.
- Me?
- You should throw it.
- Okay.
Throw it high.
- All right.
- Please.
- Okay.
- Throw it high.
- Let's go.
(They will win 40 dollars
if they get an even number.)
(Se Chan and Yura succeed
Stage 3 as well.)
Let's keep going!
(We won 40 dollars.)
Will you stop here
and receive 40 dollars?
- Keep going!
- Hold on.
(They are on a roll.)
- Keep going!
(In unison)
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
You just need to get 5 or 6.
The chance of success is higher.
Keep going!
(Jae Suk makes a decision
as people ask them to keep going.)
Stop!
(What?)
(Stop?)
You just need 5 or 6.
- The chance of success is higher.
- We won't get those numbers.
- No, it isn't.
- Suk Jin.
- Will you stop here?
- Yes.
You won 40 dollars.
- What will you do?
- Hold on.
- You have to keep going.
- Keep going.
Yura is on a roll.
- You have to keep going, Se Chan.
- Keep going.
5 or 6.
Let's keep going!
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
(Se Chan and Yura decided
to give Stage 4 a try.)
Let's do this.
- Okay.
- This is Stage Four.
Stage Four.
- You need to get 5 or 6.
- 5 or 6.
You need 5 or 6.
(They will win 80 dollars
if they get 5 or 6.)
The probability is too low.
- Here I go.
- All right.
- Please.
- Here I go.
(She finally throws the dice
in Stage 4.)
(She fails if she gets 1 through 4.)
(Will Yura succeed to get 5 or 6?)
Please.
(She gets 5!)
You did it!
(They truly hit the jackpot!)
(Their jaws drop.)
You did it! Now, we will stay!
Keep going!
(They decided to stay.)
- Go where?
- Hold on.
- Will you stay now?
- Yes.
- Let's stay. Let's stay.
- It can't be helped.
There is no way we can get
the number we pick.
- Will you stay now?
- Stay!
- You won 80 dollars.
That was impressive.
- That was impressive.
- That was quite a feat.
Se Chan and Yura are
in first place.
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo and Haha are...
- in last place.
- Okay.
(The total amount of money)
Ji Hyo, I have a personal favor
to ask of you.
Would you please wear
the hairband today?
Please wear it next week too.
- Her hairband had a retro vibe.
- That's right.
Why don't you wear
a ski outfit next week?
It won't be fun
if I do everything at once.
Ji Hyo's character...
Haha, you are too excessive.
- I just want to see it.
- You should stop.
- Seriously.
- You are always like that.
You ruined the romance
between me and Se Chan.
You ruined so many romances.
- It's not like that.
- He makes everyone uncomfortable.
So many couples came to be
because of me.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Seriously.
Nothing will work with your tactics.
So many couples came to be
because of me.
Some of them
are still happily married.
You once ruined Jong Kook's romance
for real, right?
- Right?
- I was too bored back then.
(Haha is scary when he is bored.)
- He ruined Jong Kook's romance.
- Haha's biggest problem is...
that he gets too invested.
Seriously.
- He does it for fun.
- That's right.
Romances get ruined
because he gets too invested.
If it's a drama, you need to wait
until the sixth episode.
He wants to see the conclusion
in the second episode.
What does he want to see
in the rest of the episodes?
I guess married couples are one...
- because Byul keeps texting me.
- What does she say?
"Seeing you and Se Chan
makes my heart flutter."
She is ridiculous.
I was like,
"Byul, don't be ridiculous."
"Don't be like that, So Min.
Did you make up your mind?"
She keeps sending me those texts.
Byul wasn't like that
back in the days.
Haha ruined her.
For goodness' sake.
I think it's better than any drama.
(He is watching his favorite drama.)
It makes my heart flutter.
It's insane.
There are many things.
What is that?
- Ramyeon.
- Cilantro.
Ramyeon.
One of the options is stinky tofu.
The winners of this mission
will win...
a meal and 20 dollars.
It's Crash Landing of Cards.
It's named after our favorite drama.
"It's okay."
You will play the game 6 against 5.
Each team will throw 12 cards
alternatively...
and win the dishes they land on.
You will have lunch
with those dishes only.
If you cover a card
with another card,
the bottom card won't count,
and the card on top can move
to the desired spot.
A card that lands on a blue square
will win you a point.
A card that lands on a red square
or outside the menu board...
- will lose you a point.
- The red squares are bad.
We will be fine
as long as we avoid stinky tofu.
Fermented skate will be bad too.
I prefer fermented skate.
Me too. I would die
if I eat stinky tofu.
We need to divide the group
into teams of 6 and 5.
- You are good at this.
- We have good members.
Would it be okay if we practice?
- No.
No? Okay. I got it.
- You said no.
- No.
- Okay.
- Okay. You said no.
- Never.
That's Jong Kook's favorite line.
"No? Okay."
- "You said no."
- Okay.
I love it when someone says no.
Okay.
Who should go first?
Yura, do you want to go first?
- You are lucky right now.
- Give it a go, Yura.
You have good energy right now.
- I think I will do badly.
- It's okay.
You have two cards anyway.
Yura.
- Which one do you want?
- Throw comfortably.
- Throw it anywhere.
- Ribeye or braised kimchi.
- Here I go.
- That's good.
- Fermented skate.
(She gets fermented skate, chicken,
ribeye, and stinky tofu.)
- That's good.
- Fermented skate.
Fermented skate, stinky tofu,
and ribeye.
- Three.
- You got stinky tofu too.
- Chicken.
- You got...
fermented skate, chicken,
ribeye, and stinky tofu.
- The current score is 0.
- I will go first.
Cover the card and get ribeye.
- Let's aim for rolled omelet first.
- Jae Suk.
Let's aim for braised kimchi first.
- Braised kimchi?
- Yes.
Let's eat rolled omelet.
Jae Suk.
We have vastly different tastes.
- I don't want rolled omelet.
- This is my card.
Raise your hand if you want
braised kimchi.
Everyone wants braised kimchi.
Raise your hand if you want
rolled omelet.
See?
I hate to break it to you,
but you won't get the dish anyway.
(I hate to break it to you,
but you won't get the dish anyway.)
Seriously.
- How would you know?
- Don't waste your energy.
- Just throw the card.
- I will aim for ramyeon.
- Okay.
- I am okay with ramyeon.
- Ramyeon.
- Avoid cilantro. I can't eat it.
- I love cilantro.
I can't eat cilantro.
Hold on.
Let's aim for rolled omelet.
For goodness' sake.
- We don't have the same tastes.
- Seriously.
This is the worst.
Someone else should go first.
(I can't stand it.)
(I won't do this.)
- For goodness' sake.
- Hurry up and throw the card.
Let me aim for what I want.
- Aim for what you want.
- Let him eat rolled omelet.
Let's go for the rolled omelet.
(He gets ramyeon, cilantro,
and rolled omelet.)
(They get 1 point in total.)
- Ramyeon, rolled omelet, cilantro.
- Plus 1 point.
- 1 point.
- It's one point, right?
- Yes.
This combination is not bad
except for the cilantro.
- Who's next? So Min?
- So Min?
- So Min, let's have braised kimchi.
- Cover this up.
Cover it up.
- Should I cover it up?
- Writer Jeon.
(Look at me, Writer Jeon.)
(Looking)
(She makes eye contact with him...)
(and laughs.)
- Writer Jeon.
Strangely, I'm drawn to him.
He looks interesting.
(I'm drawn to him.
He looks interesting.)
("Fantastic Faces
and Where to Find Them" by Jae Suk)
Just saying.
Writer Jeon. Writer Jeon!
(She ignores Jae Suk
and throws her card.)
- Writer Jeon.
- Writer Jeon!
Chocolate.
- Chocolate?
- You can eat ribeye with chocolate.
- It's not bad. It's edible.
- It's not.
- It's edible.
- Dessert.
All right.
(Na Hee, Ji Hyo,
Se Chan, and Na Eun go after.)
I can reach this easily.
- What?
- Don't cross the line.
Oh, gosh.
- He went over too much.
- It'll work.
(Tapping)
(What did he just do?)
- Timid revenge.
- That doesn't look painful at all.
Timid revenge.
What did you just do?
I was stretching.
- I see.
- That was a weird stretch.
Bring it back.
If you keep doing that,
you'll get into trouble this year.
(He warns Jong Kook
without making eye contact.)
- He's not even looking.
- He's just talking.
- You'll get into trouble this year.
- He's mumbling to himself.
My elbow will be striking you
before I realize.
(His elbow is probably soft
like water.)
He didn't even say,
"I'll punish you."
"You'll get into trouble this year."
My gosh.
- You can get to the ribeye.
- That's what I'm going for.
(Suk Jin throws his card
after warning Jong Kook.)
(I'm going for the ribeye.)
Is it fermented skate?
Ribeye.
(He's at the boundary between
fermented skate and ribeye.)
It's touching it.
Fermented skate and ribeye.
This is difficult.
Zero points.
- Come on.
- They'll take it out.
- This is difficult.
- My teammates are awful.
It was in between
fermented skate and ribeye.
What should I do?
Leggings, hurry up.
These are not leggings.
These are shorts.
Tights.
This is easy to reach.
Suk Jin did it too.
(That's random.)
(What's he doing?)
(Rolling)
What are you doing?
Why did you kick the camera?
Why are you so hyper today?
Hold on.
- He's angry.
- What were you doing?
Why are you mad?
- He's hyper even without Kwang Soo.
- What was that?
- What was that about?
- Why are you mad?
The camera was on,
so I wanted to take
a water bottle swiftly.
Why did you go on the elevator?
I'm just curious.
Why did you go on it?
What was your thought process?
(The game continues.)
- Ribeye!
- Ribeye.
It's okay. It's not bad.
It's their turn.
(They're tied 2 to 2
with 1 person left on each team.)
- This won't work.
- Tae Oh.
- What should I do?
- Ribeye.
- Should I try the ribeye?
Ribeye.
Should I try for the ribeye
and cover that up?
That middle spot is the best.
- The middle.
- Don't you think...
the atmosphere is different?
When it was Se Chan's turn,
Yura and Na Eun didn't do anything.
When it's Tae Oh's turn,
they're cheering.
(When it was Se Chan's turn,)
(they looked from a distance
and weren't interested.)
- I was hurt.
- When it was your turn.
- They didn't do anything.
- I paid attention.
Right.
- This one.
- That's why So Min likes Se Chan.
I have no competitors.
She has no competitors.
Both cilantro and rolled omelet.
Okay.
- Do you want all four?
- Yes.
Do whatever you want.
(Smiling)
- Do you want all four?
- Yes.
(Sweet guy Tae Oh)
I just want the ribeye.
- What do you want to eat?
- Ribeye.
What do you think you're doing?
(They're like lead characters
in a drama.)
- What do you want to eat?
- Ribeye? Okay.
Just that?
(Season 2...)
(of Romance in Running Man
starts in the middle of the game.)
(What's going on here?)
- Do whatever you want.
- I guess you're confident.
I guess so.
- What's going on?
- What do you think you're doing?
- Good.
- Ribeye.
- No dating!
- Just that?
(No dating!)
(Supporting character 1 explodes.)
No dating!
- Focus. Focus on the game!
- No dating!
I hope he throws it out of bounds.
Go for the stinky tofu
or the cilantro.
(Amid the distraction,)
(will he land on the ribeye?)
Oh, dear.
(He touched two cards.)
- Good job.
- I touched two cards.
- It's not bad.
There's still the fried chicken.
Thanks for taking away
the fermented skate.
- We don't have the fermented skate.
- Thanks for that.
Both are gone.
- We still have the fried chicken.
- The ones on the bottom are gone.
Go for the ribeye.
- At the far end.
- The far end?
Past ribeye.
He might get stinky tofu too,
so isn't the center better?
- No, the far end.
- I think he can do it.
Should I make it stand?
(Should I make it stand?)
You can't make it stand.
Why would you make it stand?
- Here.
- A little bit closer.
- A little bit closer?
- That's good.
Since Kwang Soo is away,
he wants to be Kwang Soo now.
(Imitation of Kwang Soo)
You have to clean that up, Tae Oh.
Right.
You're supposed to
clean after yourself.
That's the rule here.
I'm going next.
- My team.
- You can go.
Where do you want me to aim?
Can you get what you want?
Cover the ribeye.
- Should I cover the ribeye?
- Yes.
- Ribeye.
- Don't worry.
Jae Suk's on our side.
He's on our side.
He's stinky tofu.
Jae Suk, you have to cover it up.
- Jae Suk.
- Actually,
I can throw it this way
and stop this side.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Cover it up.
- On top of the ribeye...
- This direction.
You'll cover the ribeye
or jjajangmyeon.
- Correct.
- Bluffing.
Yes, he's bluffing.
Pretending to be fluent.
The ribeye?
- He's pretending to be fluent.
- Fermented skate.
- Let's go, stinky tofu.
- Bluffing.
Where are you aiming?
Are you aiming at the pupa?
You're pointing at the pupa.
My team is driving me nuts.
- I like your facial expression.
- All right.
Confidence.
Get ready to cheer.
(Cheering)
He told us to get ready.
- That was practice.
- Get ready to cheer.
Yu San Seul.
(Can he kill 2 birds with 1 stone
and turn the game around?)
(Please...)
Yu San Seul.
(He got the cilantro
and the fermented skate.)
- He didn't get there.
- Here?
- I almost got it.
- Hold on.
You almost covered it.
That was close.
- Jae Suk sounds...
- I can't believe you blew it.
so disappointed.
Let's go again.
Here's the final result.
If you look closely,
this is touching the cilantro.
I got two.
- It's touching.
- It is.
- This is touching for sure.
- For sure.
- I agree.
- These ones.
Hey. If you touch it,
you'll get in trouble.
(Hey. If you touch it,
you'll get in trouble.)
(Suk Jin, class leader
and guest teaser)
You're so strict.
- You'll get in trouble.
- I think he's mad. Are you mad?
3 points for Team Blue and 2 for
Team Red, so Team Blue wins.
The winning team gets 20 dollars.
- We didn't even win once.
- We keep winning.
- We went out of bounds a lot.
- We won.
Nice.
You'll get the food
you've landed on.
I'm happy about the ribeye.
This is actually ribeye.
- Jae Suk loves ramyeon.
- That looks good.
What should I do?
- Smell the fermented skate.
- It's strong.
The smell is overpowering.
- The smell is so strong.
Can you come this way?
I can't handle the fermented skate.
"Can you come this way?"
It's so strong.
(It's time to eat.)
I got it.
Braised kimchi is amazing.
Braised kimchi.
This is amazing.
(Haha and Jong Kook grill the meat.)
This is a coincidence,
but the two barbecue restaurant
owners are grilling the meat.
Mr. Kim.
Mr. Ha is doing a good job.
You should come to the restaurant
and grill the meat!
How strange.
I'll try it.
(She tries the meat
Jong Kook grilled.)
You grilled it so well.
I own a barbecue restaurant.
(He confesses.)
Meat restaurant owner.
That was the most touching thing
I heard him say.
You're not embarrassed anymore.
For the final mission,
both partners have to do well.
It's When Pull-up Bar King
Meets Quiz King.
What's that?
(Final Mission: When Pull-up Bar
King Meets Quiz King)
It's a quiz? I'm done.
You have to hang onto
the pull-up bar and answer the quiz.
Each team has three couples,
and one couple from each team
will compete at a time.
While one person is
hanging onto the pull-up bar,
the other person has to play
the Initial Consonant Game and win.
- We have to be fast.
- The person playing the game...
has to provide six words that match
the consonants and the categories...
in the correct order
within five seconds.
Whenever the person
playing the game is wrong,
the person on the pull-up bar will
get sprayed by water guns...
from the other team.
As soon as the person
on the pull-up bar lets go,
that couple loses.
The team that takes
3 out of 5 rounds wins.
Here's an example.
- What's that?
- A country that starts with giyeok.
- For this,
- Ghana.
Ghana and "go".
- What?
- "Go" for English.
- Go.
- Norway.
- The Netherlands.
"Nature" for English.
- "Nature".
- I think I can do that.
France and "freedom".
I see.
This is hard.
Let's divide the teams.
The team with five people
will be at a disadvantage.
I hope...
- I don't get the same team again.
- I'm in last place.
We were on Team Red the whole time.
Gosh, again?
- Please.
- All right.
- I'm red.
(Haha picked red.)
- Red.
- Okay.
- I got blue.
- Blue!
- Okay.
- We got red.
- These are the teams.
- Red, go that way.
- Are you red?
- Are you blue?
- Yes.
Good.
- We won.
- Good.
(Team Red and Team Blue)
This is good.
Our captain is useless.
I'm not useless.
You are. Why are you on this team?
- Stop, dumbhead.
- We're in trouble.
- I'll help you.
- Haha's team always loses.
- We're so bad.
- Let's go.
- Are you good at English?
- English?
I am good
at listening comprehension.
Do foreign words count as English?
- Kimchi.
- My goodness.
- Hey.
- What did you say just now?
- What is wrong with him?
- Why?
Do you know what he said?
- What did he say?
- It was so bad...
- that I got goosebumps.
- What did he say?
So you want to pronounce it
as a foreigner would.
- Kimchi.
- Does it count?
- Of course not.
- Then saying...
the bar strangely should count too.
- Chair.
- Of course not.
Floor.
- Kimchi is a pronoun.
Look at their sorry state.
My goodness.
- They are showing their ignorance.
- They are a mess.
He is the team leader.
Don't look down on him.
- Am I the team leader?
- Yes.
- Team Leader Haha.
- Yes!
He looks weak.
Team Young Boys...
I mean, Team Red...
- Team Young Boys!
- Team Young Boys.
"Young Boys"?
- You are 42 years old.
- Haha.
You should keep your mouth shut.
(Laughing)
(He is an old boy.)
- An old boy.
- You should keep your mouth shut.
A couple from each team
should come forward.
That couple should be...
- Suk Jin and Ji Hyo.
- That's right.
- Show them our color.
- Okay.
So Min and Tae Oh should go first.
- This is bad. What should I do?
- That would be the best.
Yura, aim for the face.
(Yura will shoot the water gun
at the other team.)
(Aiming)
(Why is she aiming at So Min,
a member of her team?)
How am I supposed
to shoot at So Min?
- Me? You aren't supposed to.
- Don't shoot at So Min.
(You aren't supposed to.)
(She quickly changes her target.)
Are you okay with shooting at me?
- Yura.
- That's too bad.
That would have been very funny.
Yura.
- Shoot at the old man.
- Are you okay with shooting at me?
Shoot at the old man with ease.
It's time for the male members
to grab on to the bar.
- Suk Jin, let's go.
- Start.
Get ready,
set, go.
(They begin.)
No, no. You need to hang
from your hands.
You can't do that. Let's start over.
(That's cheating.)
(The crew removes the platform.)
- Be quiet.
- Bring it back!
(Hanging)
Hey! That's too soon!
Bring it back!
(He raises his voice
because he is in a hurry.)
Let's start over.
You can't do that.
- You can't pull yourself up.
- I am sorry.
I used up my strength.
- You shouldn't cheat.
- I am sorry.
Suk Jin, you should go home.
You exhausted your energy.
I'm out of strength.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Get ready, set, go.
(Animal
and Four-syllable movie title)
Four-syllable movie title?
- Four-syllable movie title?
- Let me answer.
- 5, 4,
- Snake, "Grinding".
3, 2,
- "Grinding"?
- one.
Do I need to answer all of them?
That's right.
(So Min's partner at the pull-up bar
suffers the penalty.)
Let me answer.
- 5, 4...
- Snake, "Bonobono".
- "Bonobono"?
- It needs to be a movie title.
- Let me answer.
- Snake.
- "Foolish Brothers".
- Four...
"Just Do It".
Gosh, what starts with bieup?
- Let me answer.
- Five...
- What did you say earlier?
- Hey!
- Snake.
- Two...
- Hey!
- Snake.
- One.
- "Foolish Brothers", Cheetah.
Let me answer.
(Dropping)
Snake, "The Unjust".
I can't do it.
Team Blue failed.
- Did we win?
You won.
(Team Red wins 1 point.)
We can win
by hanging onto the pull-up bar.
I can't believe Suk Jin.
This isn't easy.
It's so hard.
- It's hard.
Start from the side.
- The side?
- Yes.
- Are you doing it again?
Haha doesn't have a partner.
It won't be easy.
- Na Eun, we need to win.
- Okay.
We can do this.
You can hang from the pull-up bar
as long as your feet are in the air.
- You can pull yourself up.
- Really?
Get ready, set, go.
Object?
Let me answer.
- That's it.
- Five,
- 4, 3,
- Lunchbox, donut,
- 2, 1.
- blanket...
(Time's up.)
(So Min shoots the water gun.)
(She shoots at his armpits.)
Gosh, So Min is the worst.
(So Min is like Kwang Soo.)
Let me answer. Donut, donuts,
- blanket, English,
- Two,
- wall...
- Time's up!
(Time's up.)
(Trying to hang on)
- He is going up.
- You should do the same.
- Me! Let me answer!
- Five,
- 4, 3,
- Circle. Hold on. What was...
- Incorrect.
- 2, 1.
(Time's up.)
(Shooting water gun)
Stop it, So Min!
(Is it a bidet?)
So Min!
(She is having fun.)
Gosh, So Min is the worst.
- Let me answer.
- Five,
- 4, 3,
- Lunchbox, donuts, blanket,
- 2, 1.
- and... Hold on. Blanket.
(Incorrect)
So Min is the worst.
(She is shooting water
into Jong Kook's shoes.)
So Min.
- My shoes are soaking.
- Let me answer. Lunchbox, door,
- blanket, English,
- 4, 3,
- wall, body.
- two...
Nice!
(He got all 6 words.)
- Body!
Body!
That's good. Let's go.
Even my underwear is wet.
Jong Kook, is your underwear wet?
Gosh, So Min.
(I am in trouble.)
Let's have the female members
go up this time.
You can put your feet up
on the pull-up bar.
Do what's comfortable.
Will I be able to do it?
(Speaking quietly)
Oh, So Min.
You're going up there? Great.
Jong Kook.
Although Kwang Soo isn't here today,
you filled his position perfectly.
Please don't be like that.
- I will do it.
- Go ahead.
Why are the women going up
all of a sudden?
(I must ask.)
Everyone must participate.
Kwang Soo, hurry up and come back.
I miss you.
Get ready...
- Set, go.
- My goodness.
That's good.
That's a secure position.
Set, go.
(Four-character idiom and singer)
- Singer? Four-character idiom?
- It will be hard.
Which singer's name starts
with giyeok?
Let me answer.
- 5, 4,
- Gojingamrae.
3, 2,
- one.
- Kim Bum Soo.
(Time's up.)
(It's Jong Kook's water gun time.)
Let me answer.
(He cleanses her nostrils.)
He shot into my nostrils!
(He shot into her nostrils.)
- Let me answer. Gojingamrae,
- 5, 4,
- Kim Bum Soo, Polaris...
- 3, 2,
- "Polaris"?
- That's not a four-character idiom.
(Is "Polaris"
a four-character idiom?)
Isn't it a four-character idiom?
- Let me answer.
- Five,
- 4, 3,
- Gojingamrae, Kim Bum Soo,
- two...
- the Qing invasion of Joseon.
(The Qing invasion of Joseon?)
"The Qing invasion of Joseon"?
What is up with you?
"The Qing invasion of Joseon"!
(Tae Oh's creative answer
makes So Min's armpits sweat.)
I think I can do better than him.
What are some examples?
- I am bad at four-character idioms.
- Four-character idioms.
Tae Oh, hurry up. Hurry up.
What are some four-character idioms?
- Baek... Byeok... Byeokje...
- Haha.
Byeok Galbi?
Gojingamrae.
- Let me answer.
- Tae Oh, hurry up.
- Gojingamrae, Kim Bum Soo,
- 5, 4, 3,
- 2, 1.
- What was it?
(Time's up.)
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Let me answer.
Gojingamrae, Kim Bum Soo,
- Bungwooyusin, Baek Jong Won...
- 3, 2...
Baek Jong Won...
- Baek Jong Won?
- Baek Jong Won!
For goodness' sake.
You are the worst.
- Hello, I am Baek Jong Won.
- You are the worst.
Let me answer.
Gojingamrae, Kim Bum Soo...
Bungwooyusin,
- Baek Jong Won...
- Let me answer.
(They keep bringing up
Baek Jong Won.)
Why do you keep saying
Baek Jong Won?
Tae Oh!
How did CEO Baek Jong Won become
a singer?
Let me answer.
Gojingamrae, Kim Bum Soo,
Bungwooyusin, Baek Z Young,
Juju Club...
(Juju Club?)
- Juju Club?
- Juju Club!
Is Juju Club a four-character idiom?
I am slipping.
- Are you at your limit?
- Yes.
Come on down.
- My goodness.
- It's over.
Jipijigi, Juju Club.
- We won.
- It's over.
- We won. We won.
- We won.
My mind went blank when I sat here.
Jong Kook is incredible.
- I look completely dry, right?
- Yes.
My feet are soaking wet.
The water went into my nose
and came out through my mouth.
Your armpits are sweating too.
- Oh, this?
- Yes.
This time,
- we will go.
- Okay.
- Will you go this time?
- Yura.
- I will answer the question.
(Se Chan and Yura are up.)
- Against Jae Suk...
- Hey.
Yura, even if you hold on,
I won't be able to beat Jae Suk.
- I should memorize his answer.
- That's right.
- Just wait.
- In the end...
- I will just think of the last one.
You're not on my team. I am sorry.
- Jong Kook.
- Suddenly...
(Belated realization)
- Jong Kook.
- Suddenly...
You always think
Se Chan is on your side.
- I got confused.
- You are on my team.
You are right. I got confused.
(In Jong Kook's head,
his favorite member is in his team.)
- Okay.
- I will wait until the end.
I do everything by calculation.
- Go with the flow.
- That's not how I work.
- 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
- I think first.
You need to go with the flow.
Only amateurs yell out answers
from the start.
You need to look at the forest,
not the trees.
- Se Chan.
- You need to look ahead.
- Baek Jong Won was ridiculous.
- Jae Suk isn't that great.
- I know he is bad.
- Let's do this.
I go when I have
the right judgment in my head.
Get ready, set, go.
Good. That's good.
Okay. Gosh, English is my weakness.
I prefer four-character idioms.
Let me answer.
"La La Land", landmark...
Giyeok? Giyeok?
My goodness. You shouldn't put...
You shouldn't put water in my ears.
Which movie title starts
with giyeok?
- Okay.
- Giyeok.
All right. Let me answer.
"La La Land", radio...
He is going so slowly.
(Has this video been slowed down?)
Here I go. Let me answer.
"La La Land", radio,
- "A Violent Prosecutor", go,
- 3, 2, 1.
That's not how you do it.
- You need to stay calm.
- I was close.
You need to stay calm. All right.
Bieup?
- There is one.
- Let me answer.
- "La La Land", radio...
- 5, 4...
- Let's start over.
- Let me answer. Radio... No!
- 5, 4...
- Let me answer.
- Incorrect.
(Jae Suk begins to cheat
because he is nervous.)
- What was that?
- You just need the last two.
- I am almost there.
- Let me answer.
"La La Land", radio,
- Go Doo Shim.
(Go Doo Shim)
Let me answer.
"La La Land", radio,
"A Violent Prosecutor",
and thank you.
No!
Let me answer.
"La La Land", thank you...
Thank you.
(He confesses.)
- What's wrong with you?
- Slow down.
(He calms himself down.)
- Let me answer.
- Sexy.
Let me answer. "La La Land", radio,
"A Violent Prosecutor"...
(Jae Suk covers Se Chan's mouth.)
You can't do this.
He can't do that.
- What was that for?
- He can't do this.
- Don't disturb him!
- Go ahead.
(Dangling)
My bad.
- You have to finish it.
- Na Hee, are you all right?
- I'm okay.
- She's okay.
I'm okay so far.
- Let me answer.
"La La Land", radio,
"A Violent Prosecutor"...
(Squeezing)
Hurry up.
Let me answer. "La La Land",
radio, "A Violent Prosecutor"...
("La La Land", radio,
"A Violent Prosecutor"...)
(Pressing)
(Groaning)
Let me answer.
"La La Land", radio,
"A Violent Prosecutor", go,
"King of Mask Singer"...
("King of Mask Singer" is
incorrect.)
2, 3. Hold on.
- Let me breathe.
- Okay.
- Start.
- Two...
I'm at 2. 2, 3.
"La La Land", radio,
"A Violent Prosecutor", go,
"The Unjust", and body.
Good job!
(4-syllable movie titles, English)
(He overcame Jae Suk's disruption
and won.)
Did Se Chan win?
- We did it.
- It's okay.
- They can't win.
My goodness.
- Se Chan beat Jae Suk.
- Good job, Na Hee.
- Good job.
- You did well.
- Good work.
- I thought we were going to lose.
Se Chan beat Jae Suk.
- Good job.
- You beat Jae Suk.
- That concludes the game.
- Is it over?
It's over.
Team Red will get 20 dollars each.
Yes!
It's okay. We'll roll the dice well.
Let's move onto the final dice roll.
(How will the orders change
after the dice rolling?)
(Each Couple's Amount)
(Se Chan and Yura in 1st place,
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo in last place)
Let's get started.
First place takes
a Korean beef set today.
- Korean beef set?
- We get a Korean beef set.
Let's go in order.
Back and forth?
- From first place.
- Sure.
I'll go.
(What's Se Chan and Yura's
first number?)
- Good.
- It was the wrong choice.
- Two.
- Good.
(They collect 10 dollars
and have a total of 150 dollars.)
- So Min.
- So Min never gets second place.
It must be Tae Oh.
Good luck.
- So Min went too far.
- Two.
- 1.
- Is it 1 again?
- Third place.
- Jong Kook.
- Why?
- Why do I always get one?
- Na Eun.
- I have a good feeling.
Don't be discouraged.
- Good.
- You can drop a digit.
What should I avoid?
1 and 2.
I doubt you'll get those numbers.
You won't get those. Don't worry.
You should have been more confident.
Okay!
- I did it.
- You did it.
You did it.
1, 2, and 6?
I don't have room for mistakes.
3, 4 or 5.
You never know with him.
(Can he beat the 50 percent chance
and avoid 1, 2, and 6?)
- 3, 4 or 5.
- You never know with him.
All right. Eliminated.
(2 was a repeat,
so he's eliminated.)
- All right. Eliminated.
- Did you get two?
- It's okay.
- I can't believe it.
We're done.
It's my turn.
(There are 2 teams eliminated,
and Haha is currently in 5th place.)
(He was the solo competitor.
What did he roll?)
- What would it be?
- It's okay.
Yes!
(He passes Stage 1 with 5.)
- Haha survived.
- It's okay.
- In a row.
- Suk Jin.
You have to go.
He'll be in last place
if he fails, right?
- You need 3.
- I need 3 or 4.
This is so hard.
- As long as he doesn't get six.
- I hope he doesn't.
It's three. I got it earlier.
- Three.
- Okay.
(He rolls it with confidence
and heads it.)
(Was his header a good move?)
- Three.
- Okay.
- Four!
- He survived.
- Okay.
(They went from 0 to 10 dollars.)
I survived.
- Should I go again?
- I survived.
Except for Se Chan
and Jae Suk's teams,
everybody else has to decide
what they're going to do.
I have to keep going.
We're in danger.
- We'll keep going.
- Go for it, Tae Oh.
Show them, Tae Oh.
Let's turn this game around.
- I have to avoid 1, right?
- 1 or repeated numbers.
(In order to pass Stage 2,
he has to avoid 1 and repeats.)
- Let's turn this game around.
- All right.
Avoid one.
Is it going to be Haha or us?
(What will Tae Oh and So Min get
in Stage 2?)
- Okay.
- Good job.
It's three.
(They're good for now with 3.)
What is it?
- Three.
- Next.
I want to turn this around.
I'll be upset if that happens.
Are you keep going, Jong Kook?
- We'll stop.
- You're stopping? Okay.
(They're realistic
and want to avoid the penalty.)
He's being safe.
Both of us.
- Keep going or give up.
- I have 30 dollars, right?
If Haha...
- You can give up.
- It's one or the other.
If you definitely want to win,
then go for it.
If you stop, you might lose.
I think stopping might be better.
Still go for it.
I'll...
(Depending on his decision,
last place might change.)
(What does Haha decide to do?)
I'll stop.
(He stops at 30 dollars.)
Okay.
If he wins, we'll be tied.
He might keep going. You never know.
What do I need?
- Everything but 1 or 3.
- As long as it's not 1 or 3!
(Repeated numbers or 1
eliminate the couples.)
(He's eliminated if he gets 1
or Tae Oh's 3.)
Good job.
- Please!
- He'll confirm it.
- 1 or 3.
- Haha is taking his chance.
(If he gets a number other than
1 or 3, last place will change.)
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are currently
in last place. What is the result?)
(He's eliminated with 1.)
(I survived!)
(Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are confirmed
for the penalty.)
I told you.
All right!
I'm not alone!
It's confirmed.
(This is a solo paradise
and a couple's nightmare.)
Success!
I did it!
Success.
This is so much fun.
I should have told Ji Hyo
to roll the dice.
- That was a clean finish.
- We have to keep going.
This is great.
I'm okay with the penalty.
So Min, are you going to stop...
- or keep going?
- We should keep going.
- We'll keep going.
- Clench first place.
First place might change too.
Yura, we're pretty safe.
I'll be mad
if we drop to second place.
Be confident.
(He needs an even number
to pass Stage 3.)
(Can So Min and Tae Oh
turn the game around?)
(If they land on an even number,
they collect 40 dollars right away.)
(They succeeded Stage 3.)
I did it!
(How could this be?)
- You have to keep going.
- Go.
If you get 5 or 6,
you jump to 1st place.
- If you get 5 or 6.
- I'll keep going.
If you get 5 or 6,
you jump to 1st place.
- What's going on? This is crazy.
- I know.
Will So Min stop Se Chan?
- I'll go.
- Throw it up high.
- Tae Oh.
- High.
(This is the last roll of the day.)
Will she stop him?
(1st place will
depend on this roll.)
(If it lands on 5 or 6, So Min
and Tae Oh will clench 1st place.)
(They fail to turn the game around.)
(That was close.)
That was close.
I didn't throw it high enough.
(Se Chan and Yura win.)
- Yura.
- First place winners are...
Se Chan and Yura.
Suk Jin and Ji Hyo are
in last place.
(He holds his hands up.)
(It's time for
the prize and the penalty.)
Yura is Princess Pyeonggang today.
- Good job, Yura.
- We were a good match.
You transformed Ondal the fool.
I love beef so much
that my fanclub is called Marbling.
- Is that right?
- And I won this.
Yura is a big eater.
- I know.
- I agree.
Anyway, I would like to thank
the four guests.
Thank you!
Are there any guests
who are curious to experience this?
- Hurry up.
- Sure.
- I won't waste time.
- We have to accept the penalty.
- Moreover, I hope Kwang Soo...
- Right.
recovers and joins us soon.
- We'll be waiting for him.
- Depending on his condition,
- Correct.
we'll see when he can get back.
I hope he returns in full health.
Also, Producer Jung Chul Min...
and Writer Mi Yeon.
These are staff members who have
been on Running Man for a long time.
They're going to be joining
a different show.
- Thank you for all your hard work.
- Thank you!
(Great work, everybody.)
All right.
I talked so much
with those two standing there.
It's scarier
when you have to wait for it.
- I agree.
- They're still waiting.
- Let's get this done.
- Sure.
Chul Min, is there anything
you'd like to say?
(Goodness)
Thank you for everything.
I'll see you again on
a different show. Thank you.
- That's it.
- All right.
Good work, Writer Ji Young.
Stop it! Let me take the penalty!
Wait up.
Gosh, he knows what I don't like.
He keeps on doing what I don't like.
(Why do you keep going?)
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
All right. 1, 2, 3.
(It's green whipped cream today.)
You're Shrek. That was good aim.
Great work.
(Thank you, Tae Oh, Na Hee,
Yura, and Na Eun of April.)
(Running University
Membership Training: Indoors)
(Returning student Im Soo Hyang,
Expelled student Jo Byeong Gyu)
(They attend class.)
(They're excited,)
(but there's nothing set in stone.)
(Make a schedule for MT.)
(Their project is back
to square one.)
(They fail to save it.)
(Does his ambitious presentation
succeed?)
(Zero point for you)
(Laughing)
(Do-it-yourself
Running Man MT is here!)
(Only the emcee can lead.)
("Emceeing Over Flowers".
Flowers 3 will decide everything!)
(Will Running University students
submit to them?)
Wait.
(There's also
a mysterious gas leak incident.)
(What will happen at Running MT?)
(Do Whatever You Want! Running MT)