(This episode was shot on August 4
after checking the temperature...)
(of all the staff members
and disinfecting the whole area.)
Hello.
(So Min is the first to arrive
as always.)
Hello.
What are you
doing in here, So Min?
I don't know.
I was told to stay here.
- This way.
- Where?
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Hi.
The opening is rather simple today.
I know. No one's here.
What are you doing?
What are you waiting for?
(Everyone's here
including Suk Jin.)
Are you wearing cologne?
I just put it on. Do you smell it?
Yes. It stinks.
- A little later...
- "It stinks"?
Suk Jin, I said I would...
It really stinks.
- Suk Jin.
- Nice.
That was a good one.
That's because I just put it on.
When you wear cologne...
- Gosh, Suk Jin. Seriously.
- It's bad.
- It really stinks.
- They don't like it.
- The thing is...
I should wait a while
after spraying it.
Gosh, I don't like the smell.
Suk Jin, your pants are ripped.
You know it's part of the design.
You need to stitch it.
- It's part of the design.
- It's too big though.
That's how it is.
Do you not know about fashion?
- This is what New Yorkers wear.
- You need to be bold.
You've never been
to New York though.
I'd like to go there.
(I'd like to go there.)
(He follows the fashion of New York
that he's never been to.)
- You didn't even go there?
- I will.
You've been to Las Vegas, right?
I have. I drove from LA
to Las Vegas.
I've never been there before.
It was really fun. I think
Ji Hyo and So Min will be...
really popular in Vegas.
- Why?
- They like Asian girls.
They do. They wink a lot.
- Really?
- When I went to Europe,
a lot of guys winked at me
at a market.
And they'd think you're young.
"Oh no. Thank you." I said.
- Oh, dear.
- And what did they say?
"Thank you so much.
Hello. Come here."
- Really?
- I did this.
I'm sure she showed some responses.
- I know.
- That's why they winked.
I almost shut my eyes as I smile.
How?
(Smiling)
(She smiles in her eyes
until she gets a tic.)
You're unbelievable.
They must've been tired.
And you fall and bump all the time.
- Because you keep your eyes shut.
- That's funny.
(She's Love Frog
who's blinded by love.)
He's back with a drawn face.
You look handsome.
He looks better
after losing some weight.
- Gosh, no.
- So Min, what's...
with the makeup on your cheeks?
Did you do that for Se Chan?
She's been like that
since yesterday.
So Min said she'd go
take care of you.
She said she'd be his caregiver.
- No way.
- But he told me not to come.
Why is that?
I didn't want her to see me.
Why? Did you get a foley catheter?
- Gosh, it's not like that.
- Did you get a foley catheter?
(He feels dizzy
hearing about foley catheter.)
Why would you say that?
- Stop it.
- That's uncalled for.
- You're mean.
- That's ridiculous.
- It wasn't like that?
- Why would he get foley catheter?
- That's not it.
- My gosh.
Your legs are getting
darker and darker, Kwang Soo.
- Did you get tanned?
- He's shooting "Sea God" now.
- "Sea God"?
- It's "The Pirates".
- Did you say "Sea God"?
- What's "Sea God"?
It's a drama about Jang Bo Go.
Isn't it "Sea God"?
Why do you keep saying that?
Why would you do that?
Wasn't the title "Sea God"?
Are you a pirate in "The Pirates"?
- I am a pirate.
- I see.
Then you should pull out some teeth.
Why would I pull out my teeth?
That's what pirates do.
Like Jack Sparrow.
If you're a pirate,
you should pull out a few teeth.
You should have one eye
if you're pirate.
Why would I lose
my eye and teeth?
I think it would work...
if he colored his teeth black.
Just paint them black
like a comedy show.
- Give it a try.
- Gosh, no.
- That's what comedians do.
- It's nothing like that.
Who is the lead actor?
Well... It features Kang Ha Neul.
- Oh, right.
- Ha Neul?
- It will be successful.
- That sounds fun.
I know. It must be fun.
And it also features me.
- Do you play a lead role?
- Is Ha Neul the lead actor?
Are you Ha Neul's friend?
Ha Neul...
That jerk...
(He explodes with anger.)
He says that
every time I start a movie.
(The best supporting actor
loses his temper.)
He asks if you're the lead's friend.
You must be the best friend
of Ha Neul's girlfriend.
You have a secret crush
on Ha Neul's girlfriend.
And you die for her, right?
And you like her.
Actually that's true.
So I can't yell at him.
- It's true.
- I'm his friend...
- and underling.
- It's all correct.
- His underling?
- Underling.
- His friend and underling.
- Now we know the full story.
Let me tell you
about the rules then.
- Okay. Tell us.
- All right.
Once you get into the studio,
there will be rooms
numbered from 1 to 8.
- Is that so?
- Okay.
Among 8 rooms, pick 1...
and go inside.
- Really?
- Do we go in?
Suk Jin, you're closest
to the door, so go ahead first.
I don't want to go first.
- Really? Then I'll go.
- Yes.
Now I want to go first.
(He changes his mind suddenly.)
Why do you keep changing your mind?
What's with you?
- It's because he gets jealous.
- I know.
- So Min, go first.
- Okay.
Don't come into my room.
I like number three.
Hello.
(What will be inside the studio?)
What's going on today?
Are these rooms?
(Connected by 8 rooms)
Does everyone get a room?
(It's a huge octagonal set.)
(Each room has a karaoke machine...)
(and various karaoke items.)
Can no one else come
into the same room?
Can no one else come in
if I say that it's occupied?
Do I get to use it alone?
I'll pick number four.
- Turn over the sign and go inside.
- Okay.
(She picks number 4
without thinking hard.)
What's this?
(What? It's a karaoke room.)
This is amazing.
Let's see. Which one shall I go in?
Come inside the one next to mine.
All right.
I pick this one.
(Jae Suk picks room number 1.)
What's this?
This one.
(Haha picks number 3
next to So Min's.)
Next in line, please go.
(The remaining 5 members
pick their rooms.)
(1. Jae Suk, 2. Se Chan, 3. Haha,
4. So Min, 5. Ji Hyo, 6. Suk Jin)
(7. Jong Kook, 8. Kwang Soo)
Everyone.
(The rules are given
as soon as everyone enters a room.)
After singing a song of your choice
entirely,
check your score.
Saying your true score
may be disadvantageous,
so be careful
when you report your score.
What do you mean?
We shouldn't say it?
First, sing a song of your choice
up to the second verse...
and check your score.
(Singing)
(A creepy intro of "Aloha" by Cool)
(A candle under a dark light)
(He starts the song offbeat.)
(What song did So Min choose?)
(Like Jae Suk, she picks a song
by Cool named "Sending My Love".)
(Bouncing of the 90's)
(She gets emotional
on an empty stomach at 9 a.m.)
(Another person
who's getting too emotional)
This is my favorite song.
(Jong Kook picks
"The More I Love" by Boohwal.)
(Suk Jin also picks a slow song.)
(Haha picks a hip-hop song
like a hip-hop artist.)
(Ji Hyo picks a fast trot song.)
(Se Chan picks Haha's song.)
(All members finish picking a song.)
(Running Man's
solo coin karaoke is open.)
(Yes)
(Rowdy Haha gets excited
from the start.)
(He raps like the old days.)
(He sings
after rapping passionately.)
(He's out of tune.)
(I'm a rapper.)
(Se Chan's homage to Haha's song)
(Shouting)
(His priority is showing off his
personal charm instead of singing.)
(Jae Suk concentrates on singing
with composure.)
(Banging)
(Loud sounds)
What? What is it?
Stop it.
Stop what?
(Jae Suk interrupts.)
I'm getting emotional.
(He reimmerses in it right away.)
(So Min is also immersed
in singing.)
(I'm afraid)
(Of having to meet someone)
(She makes exaggerated gestures
irrelevant to the score.)
(Sorrowful)
(Instead of singing well, emotional
So Min makes a music video.)
(Lifting her head)
(I want to be alone.)
(Sometimes, I cry.)
(Despite other members'
low-quality performance,)
(Jong Kook's sweet voice is
pleasant to our ears.)
(Only his expression of emotions
is high-quality.)
(Banging)
What's wrong with him?
Be quiet.
(He finishes singing in anger.)
"Wow, that's surprising."
I got 100 points.
"You're a singer."
Wow.
(As no one knows
what the mission is,)
I got 100 points.
(everyone is boasting
about their high scores.)
Everyone, the score
on the karaoke machine is...
your current score.
However, one person pressed cancel
by mistake,
who will get zero points.
Who was it?
Is it okay as long as
you saw your score?
Within 10 minutes,
choose whether or not to open
the door locked on both sides.
Based on which doors open,
members who meet make a team.
You're better off
the higher your average score is.
If you think the one next to you
has a higher score, you'd better...
open and be on the same team.
About 3 to 4 rooms
can come together.
Kwang Soo picked a song
that's easy to get a high score.
I got a high score, Jong Kook.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Jae Suk.
- Hey, Se Chan.
- I sang very well.
- Se Chan.
- I got a high score.
- You know...
- Right.
- Se Chan.
- Wait.
Open up.
Okay.
- It's open. Is your score high?
- Okay.
- And you? What's the score?
- It's high.
It's quite high,
but I can't tell you.
- First...
- You didn't cancel, did you?
- No, mine is over 90 points.
- Right?
- Kwang Soo?
- Yes?
Let's do it.
- Open up.
- Open it. I'm willing to...
It's impossible...
- that you got a low score.
- Yours is definitely high.
I heard your singing.
Okay, I definitely think
you got a high score.
Let's do it, you punk.
- Okay!
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook
become a team.)
Did you get a high score?
- I did.
- Really?
It worked.
(While the members make teams)
- Mine is high.
- It wasn't you, right?
I got a high score.
- Who's next to you?
- Suk Jin.
No.
(She stops right away.)
- You don't think so?
- No.
No way.
I didn't press cancel.
- Did you hear him sing?
- I did.
Jong Kook, who's next to you?
I think it's Suk Jin.
- I bet he pressed cancel.
- Him?
I didn't press cancel.
- Honestly,
- I promise.
now that I'm on Jong Kook's team,
I won't be last.
- We'll definitely place first.
- The question is...
- whether to take on baggage or not.
- Right.
What baggage?
- Suk Jin.
- I just can't tell you... Gosh.
Isn't that how he acts
when he's lying?
- Haha.
- What song did you sing, So Min?
- I teamed up with Ji Hyo. Come on.
Ji Hyo got a high score
by singing...
"Love Battery".
- Did she score high?
- Yes.
Yes, I did.
(After hearing
about Ji Hyo's score...)
Let's go.
Hey, Se Chan.
We got high scores.
- We did.
- Really?
- Open up.
- Let's open it.
- Okay.
- Neither of us pressed cancel.
- No, right?
- No.
Ji Hyo sang "Love Battery".
Time is up.
The ones who opened the door
and shared...
will average their scores.
Please come out.
The teams are
made of 2, 1, and 5 members.
Five members?
Did all of them team up?
- We're all a team.
- Really?
I'll announce the individual scores.
Haha scored...
72 points.
- That's low.
I told you that
we shouldn't open the door.
Next, So Min scored...
86 points.
- What?
- It isn't so bad.
- She didn't score high.
- It's Ji Hyo.
Since they trained to be singers,
they should sing well.
Next, Ji Hyo scored 80 points.
- What?
- But you sang "Love Battery".
Why did you say that it was high?
Since it was 80 points.
(Other members got fooled.)
Jae Suk scored...
- 87 points.
- That's right.
- It's not bad.
- Really? I heard you sing.
I sang effortlessly.
You should've had scored over 90.
Se Chan scored...
- zero.
- Darn it.
Se Chan scored zero.
Darn it.
I pressed it by mistake.
Was it you?
My score didn't come up.
I pressed the wrong key. I'm sorry.
That's huge. We got fooled.
I sang passionately,
but I didn't get a score.
Jong Kook scored 75 points.
- That's not high.
- It's low.
- I couldn't hear the accompaniment.
- It's lower than I thought.
- What about Kwang Soo?
- Kwang Soo scored...
44 points.
- I was...
- What?
(What?)
There's something wrong
with the machine.
- There's no way.
- It was my favorite song.
(Sad truth behind Kwang Soo's score)
(He sang his favorite song
with emotions.)
(It was a solo concert
full of emotions.)
(However, the result was a failure.)
(He's lying.)
(He got stabbed
by his favorite song.)
Why didn't you sing...
It's because Jae Suk kept knocking
and told me to be quiet.
He kept interrupting my singing.
- What's the average?
- That's why I got 44.
Suk Jin is the only one
on his team.
His score is 88 points.
- It's the highest.
- He placed first.
- You placed first.
- I know.
Petty Gang is doing so well
these days.
- It's Petty Gang.
- Petty Gang?
I want to join Petty Gang.
You're already part of it.
The team's average score is
important in today's race.
It's Cut Off to Survive.
Team members will be connected
in a few minutes,
and you'll proceed
with the missions.
The team with the highest
average score in the mission...
- will get a benefit.
- Really?
The one with the highest score
on that team gets to choose.
The winner of the winning team
gets a benefit.
You can get the lock's passcode,
add a lock to a team member,
or make someone in another team
join your team.
(The 1st place in the winning team
chooses 1 of the 3 benefits.)
For example, if the keyword for
the next mission is "flexibility",
you should recruit someone
who seems to be flexible.
- You'll tell us the keyword?
- Yes.
And you should remove a person
who isn't flexible from your team.
The team with the highest average
score at the end wins the race...
and receives the prize.
We just have to choose
the right members.
However, the team with the lowest
average score at each mission...
receives penalty balls with the team
members' names on them.
At the end, two members will be
randomly chosen to get penalties.
That means each of you
just got a penalty ball.
- What?
- You two...
- Already?
- You two came in last.
(Glaring)
We can do well from now on.
- I'm glad I teamed up with you.
- Me too.
How we'll do next is what matters.
I've never seen anyone get
under 50 points at karaoke...
- in my whole life.
- It was my first time too.
- Wasn't it because of his face?
- Exactly.
- What's wrong with my face?
- Because he has long hair, I think.
Could it be because he's too tall?
You got something on me
after a long time.
- No.
- You look so happy now.
Karaoke machines these days
have facial recognition.
- The machine didn't like him.
- Facial recognition, my foot.
- Your appearance and gestures...
- What are you talking about?
- are included in the criteria.
- The machine didn't like him.
We'll let the only member
of the winning team Suk Jin...
- choose the benefit right now.
- Okay.
- Awesome, Petty.
- Petty Gang.
- That's incredible.
- You're awesome, Petty.
- Petty Gang is the best.
- Petty is awesome.
- I want to join Petty Gang.
- The time has come.
- The next mission's keyword is...
- Yes.
"Courage".
It won't be me.
Suk Jin, you can either
tie yourself to someone...
- or remove someone from a team.
- I see.
- I should be the one...
- When I think about courage,
- these two are the worst.
- They're the worst.
You can't have someone in your team
just because you break a tie.
- I know. It doesn't work that way.
- Hey, be quiet.
We need to explain the rules to him.
- Suk Jin is talking right now.
- He doesn't understand the rules...
- He knows the rules.
- Okay.
- It'd be great to make him...
- Exactly.
- come in last.
- Good. But Kwang Soo...
- Okay. I'll break them up.
- Are you serious?
- Okay.
- Nice.
Nice, Suk Jin.
Okay. I'll break them up.
- Are you serious?
- Okay.
- Nice, Suk Jin.
- Now, they have to make a choice.
- No, it's over.
- It's over?
The three of you will
play the game individually.
- That's right.
- Really?
- My goodness.
- Thank you for breaking us up.
- I won't forget this.
- Why did you...
break us up when you didn't even
understand the rules?
- I won't forget this.
- Wait.
He didn't even understand the rules.
Won't they choose a team...
- after they break up?
- Jae Suk wouldn't let me tell him.
- I won't forget this.
- Why would you do that?
- We'll tether you to each other.
- I said, that's not how it works.
What's going on?
They're tying me up.
Jae Suk, I think
we'll go up in the air.
- Why...
- I think we'll go up in the air.
- I don't want to do that.
- I think they're tethering us.
- They're tethering you together.
- Oh, I see.
Haha and Jae Suk
are already scared.
Please wait in the waiting room
while we're preparing...
- for the next mission.
- Okay.
I ended up being tethered
to them. Gosh.
- I'll go to the bathroom.
- It's uncomfortable.
(They moved to another place
for their first courage test.)
(What could be the courage test?)
- What's that?
- It's tall.
- What is this?
- That's so tall.
- I can't do this.
- What is this?
(It's large enough
to fill the studio.)
The stairs are so steep.
- Are we going to go up there?
- What is this anyway?
(If you go up the stairs
as tall as a two-story building,)
Oh, my gosh.
(you'll see a long
polystyrene foam diving board.)
(What kind of test will be held
in this place?)
- Is this a courage test?
- It's made of polystyrene foam.
Come over here. Come up here.
(What could this be?)
This is amazing.
So, we walk on it as far as we can
without breaking it?
Let's sit here.
- Is it edible?
- Se Chan.
- Haha, come here.
- Hey, So Min.
- So Min.
- It's too high.
- So Min, come here already.
- It's not edible.
- It's shallower than I thought.
- Come and sit here.
Just come here.
That would break if I stand on it.
But it's quite shallow.
Jae Suk, it's shallow.
Everyone, the first mission
that requires courage is...
Put a Sticker
on the Edge of a Cliff.
We'll have to put a sticker on it.
It looks so scary.
You will decide the order
and try it one by one.
What you have to do is to go up
on that diving tower...
and put a sticker at the farthest
spot you can reach on the platform.
The location of your sticker
decides your individual score.
If the platform breaks
before you put the sticker on it,
you get no point.
We'll calculate the average score
of each team,
and the team with the highest score
will get a benefit,
and the last place team
will get penalty balls.
So, they'll calculate
the average score?
Yes, and for us, the individual
scores will be our team scores.
Is it okay if it breaks
after I put my sticker on it?
It's okay as long as you put
a sticker on it.
(They get a score if their stickers
are on the platform.)
Many of our staff members
tried the game.
It's perfectly safe, and some of us
reached to the edge.
- To the edge?
- Yes.
Okay. I got it.
Hey, you guys should watch me
do that. I'm telling you...
- Hey.
- Calm down.
- What's there to watch?
- Just don't pee your pants.
- Exactly.
- Do you need a chamber pot?
- Please give him a diaper.
I'll make sure to watch you.
Gosh, this is driving me insane.
As for the order, we calculated
the average age of each team.
You'll try in the order of age
from the youngest.
- From the youngest?
- First up is Kwang Soo.
Why? I...
- Is he younger than me?
- What about Se Chan and So Min?
The average age of their team
is 40.2.
You shouldn't be rude to me
as I'm older than you.
- We're all older than you.
- We're older than you.
- They're all older than you.
- Stop acting up.
- How dare you?
- Be polite to us.
- What are you looking at?
- How dare you act up?
- I wanted to see others first.
- Go on.
- Go now.
- Don't part your hair like that!
- Shave the back of your head.
- Kwang Soo.
- Yes?
- You forgot the helmet.
- Do we need a helmet too?
- Just in case.
It might break even if you want to
go farther.
Exactly. That's why.
- If it breaks...
- Put it on once you hear a crack.
Right.
I will pull this off no matter what.
(This mission is important to him
as he already got a penalty ball.)
So I can team up with him again.
(He seems highly motivated.)
It feels higher than I expected.
(Unlike how it felt on the floor,
4m feel so scary.)
(All he can do is sigh
as he looks down.)
Hey, it's high, right?
- It's too high.
- Right? It's high.
Of course, it feels higher up there.
- As you can see,
- It's very tall.
- it's as tall as the lighting.
- Exactly.
- He's tall, so it must feel higher.
Kwang Soo, try to take a step on it.
(Kwang Soo froze
and won't even budge.)
- I don't think I can do this.
- Try standing on it.
- Give it a try.
- Put your feet on it.
Try stepping on it for now.
Right. Put your feet on it.
Try stepping on it.
Go on.
Why are you being so scared?
- Move. Come on.
- Show us. You're the youngest.
- It won't break. Trust me.
- Oh, my.
- Gosh, seriously.
- It'll break.
- It'll break. Oh, no.
- If it breaks, it's over.
- It's shaking.
- Hey, hey, stop.
- Gosh.
- Oh, no.
- It's shaking.
- Hey, hey, stop.
- Gosh.
- That must be scary.
(As the diving platform shakes,
Kwang Soo is shaking too.)
- I don't think we can do this.
- Go, Kwang Soo.
- Let's go!
- You can do it!
- I can do this.
- Hey, hey.
You put only your right foot,
and it wobbled.
You don't drag it on like that
these days.
You can just roll over, put your
sticker on it, and come down.
- It's bending.
- Gosh. It's wobbling.
(It's wobbling even more.)
- It's wobbling.
- My gosh.
(Gosh, It's wobbling.)
- I only put one foot on it.
- Is it okay?
- I didn't even stand on it.
- This is crazy.
- Exactly.
- It wobbles too much.
- It's scary.
- Flex your lower body.
Wait. Lie down on the platform.
- Lie down on your belly.
- Yes.
- That's good.
- Try crawling.
- You shouldn't... Hey, hey.
You should move forward.
What's wrong with you?
You're a pirate.
That has nothing to do with this.
- You're a pirate.
- "Sea God".
- It's not "Sea God".
- Come on, Jang Bo Go.
- He can't seem to move.
- Sea otter.
- Kwang Soo, give it a try.
- The staff say...
it's safe up to 1m.
- Come down if you'll be like that.
- Just give up.
(Booing)
I'm bored.
It's really boring.
Kwang Soo, the viewers will switch
the channel. You can't be like this.
"I'll watch another show."
- He's really scared.
- Please.
- Please don't switch the channel.
- It must feel different...
- I really want to do this.
- if you go up there.
- Go up there.
- You should try this.
Please don't switch the channel.
Please give me a second.
I want to do this. I really do.
- This isn't what I expected.
- They're switching the channel.
This is what makes people
want to switch the channel.
Take your hand off
and see what happens.
Put your elbow on it
to see if it's safe.
- It's safe.
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
Keep moving.
You'll be okay up to that point.
It's safe.
(Coughing)
They're laughing hard.
- He's going to throw up.
- He's about to throw up.
Shall I bring you a bucket?
Exactly. He's going to throw up.
He's drooling.
Kwang Soo, the cranes are moving
around so busily because of you.
- Look at them. Come on.
- The writers are dozing off.
They're even moving the cranes
because you won't move.
The cameraman who's controlling
the crane is working hard for you.
Hey, wink at the crane camera.
- Wink at the camera.
- Move already.
You're running out of time...
(The camera froze.)
That was funny.
Hey, you have 30 seconds left.
- He's moving.
- Lie on the platform.
- Lie down. Good.
- Lie down.
- Lie down slowly.
- Lie on your belly.
(He's moving slowly.)
He's lying down.
(Snapping)
(Everyone got surprised.)
What was that? What happened?
He's lying down.
(Screaming)
- He went back.
- What was that?
We were all nervous.
Hey, it broke right away.
We were nervous too.
- What happened?
- It broke.
- My gosh.
- My hands are sweating.
- It broke right away.
- We were nervous too.
It broke...
The longer time you take,
the more likely you are to fall off.
- Get it over with.
- Exactly.
Run to the 3m point
without stopping.
- Here he goes.
- Okay.
I know how I should do it.
I doubt it.
(Is this the plan he came up with?)
You'll fall head-first
if you crawl like that.
- That's right.
- Oh, no.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Kwang Soo, come on.
You're quite close to the 2m point.
- He can do that because he's tall.
- Exactly.
Go a little farther.
Your thighs will be scraped
because you're wearing shorts.
You shouldn't have put on shorts.
- Wear long pants on variety shows.
- What is he doing?
- Your thighs will be scraped
- Shut your mouths, you jerks.
(He burst out in anger in the end.)
Shut it!
Just shut it, please.
- Wear long pants on variety shows.
- He's wearing shorts...
- Gosh. I'm so stressed out.
- that look like underwear.
- They're too short.
- Why did you put on shorts?
Are you going cycling or something?
Are they knickers or what?
You wear shorts like that
only when you ride a bicycle.
He's about to start drooling.
Look at his face.
There he goes. He's panicking.
- Good.
- You should move forward now.
- Move already.
Move forward no matter what.
- His face like a fool is the best.
- Indeed.
- It's wobbling.
- Look at his face.
He's the best in Korea.
(He's the best in Korea when it
comes to a face like a fool.)
- He should move forward.
- Yes.
- You should go farther than that.
- You've been up there too long.
Can you count to three for me?
- Shall we count to 3 for you?
- Count to 3 for me.
- Please do it for me.
- Okay. Get ready.
- 1.
(The platform has already
become weak.)
- 2.
(It's important for him
to move quickly.)
Three.
(Could Kwang Soo pull it off?)
(Snapping)
He fell off.
(He seemed to move quickly.)
(But he fell off right away.)
(The pirate met his fate
in the air.)
No, it fell.
- He couldn't put it.
- He couldn't do it.
He couldn't do it.
He's gone.
- He's gone.
- Where did he go?
- Hey.
- Kwang Soo. Crawl out.
Kwang Soo.
He couldn't do it.
- What's that, by the way?
- He couldn't do it.
He flew away.
- He sweated too much.
- It's not sticky.
See? I told you to hurry up.
Kwang Soo failed.
Kwang Soo went pretty far though.
- Let's go.
- Let's get it over with.
- Go up.
This is crazy.
It's way too high. Gosh.
- Isn't it high?
- The cracking sound drove me crazy.
- It's high.
- It's high, Kwang Soo.
- Oh, my.
- It's different.
I told you. It's different
from looking down here.
- Can I try any method?
- It's too high.
- It feels different.
- It's too scary.
- You shouldn't hesitate.
- You said you'll show us.
I'm not even kidding.
I'm not confident.
Hey. Move aside.
What if I get scared
and pull you down with me?
- Okay?
- You're thinking that far?
Is it that bad?
You were so confident before.
Take his glasses.
Where did your confidence go?
This is crazy.
Is it over if it breaks?
We'll replace it.
But we won't place it
if it's only a crack.
- You won't?
- No?
If it cracks,
you should kill yourself.
But that sound might be from me.
- That's what I mean.
- I'll check.
- You should listen to it carefully.
- Okay.
If it's from me, pull me out.
Of course.
I'll get into action right away.
He's the national coward.
- It's...
- Move slowly.
It's all right. You're light.
It wouldn't support me.
He's scared for real.
- He's going like this.
- Jae Suk.
(His body is trembling.)
I've never seen that face before.
- Who are you?
(I'm a coward.)
I don't feel good up here.
This is like Nevis Swing.
It's no joke.
Hey. Don't be ridiculous.
Jae Suk. It's okay up to here.
Hey. Slap me in the face.
(They react immediately
to his request.)
- Seriously.
- Pull yourself together.
- You can do it.
- Hey.
Who was that?
Who hit me?
Because I'm scared.
- I'm sweating so much.
- Hey.
They're spending more time
than Kwang Soo.
Who said something about
changing the channel?
I'm sorry.
(Dear viewers)
- Where are you looking at?
- I'm sorry.
I can't do it. It's too scary.
- Give up then.
- It feels different from up there.
It works better for us.
Jae Suk. I weigh 82kg.
Who are you?
(Who are you?)
I'm your brother.
I'm sorry. I can't see.
I'm quite sensitive right now.
I should hurry up.
I can't spend too much time.
What's he doing?
You've already spent too much time.
Hey. Who are you?
I'm your brother!
I'm sorry. I can't see.
Gosh.
It's funny
how he's talking to himself.
"I shouldn't spend too much time."
He keeps saying that.
This is really scary.
When we tried it,
it's best to crawl.
Who are you?
I'm the producer.
(Who are you?)
(I'm the producer.)
I'm sorry. My apologies.
I can't see.
Don't take it personally.
- "I'm the producer."
- I'm quite sensitive right now.
- That was funny.
- It's because I can't see.
- I'm sorry.
- Well said!
- I can't see anything.
If you stay here, it won't stick.
It's driving me crazy. Jae Suk...
- You got it.
- It's not breaking.
You got it, Jae Suk.
Just stretch your arm.
- You can get to 2m.
- It's 2m.
- Put it there.
- That's right. Nice posture.
- That's good.
- Go.
- That's perfect.
- It's "Gang".
- Play "Gang".
- Play it.
Play "Gang".
(Unlike the flashy beat of "Gang",)
(he's moving only his fingers.)
Run. Now is the time.
- Gosh.
- Put the sticker first.
Put it there first.
Gosh, wait!
(Making him brave forcibly)
- Put the sticker, Jae Suk.
- Gosh.
- Get the sticker ready.
- Put the sticker. Move forward.
- Hey.
- Put the sticker.
- I can't.
- Stretch your arm.
- Put the sticker. That's all.
- That's all you need to do.
- It's hard to put the sticker.
- Do it.
(He's sublimating his fear
with a scream.)
- You got it. Just stretch your arm.
- That's making me nervous.
Stretch your arm.
You're almost there.
- It's breaking.
- Don't push me.
(Cracking)
(The styrofoam is about to break.)
- Push him.
- Don't push me.
(Meltdown)
- A little more.
- Put the sticker on!
- Just a little more.
- Little more.
Just a little more.
Put the sticker. A little more.
(Supporting Jae Suk from the back)
- Are you insane?
- Move forward.
Just put it.
(He's moving forward
regardless of his will.)
- Put it.
- It's 3m.
- Put the sticker.
- Put it.
Put the sticker and come back.
(Put the sticker and come back.)
- Jae Suk. Come back.
- How can I go back?
Put the sticker and come back.
- He did it.
- Break it.
- Come back.
- Come back here.
- Put the sticker.
(He put the sticker successfully.)
- He did it.
- Come back now.
Why doesn't it break?
- I'll help you.
- Wait. Jae Suk. Is it scary?
I'm dead here.
(Goodbye then.)
(He dies
after completing the mission.)
Jae Suk.
- He put the sticker.
- It's 3m.
(I did my best.)
Haha, that was so funny.
Jae Suk. Rest in peace.
Rest in peace.
Did you see that?
- See what?
Goodness.
- That was very scary.
- It's approved.
Since you put the sticker,
we'll put up a new board.
Jae Suk's record is 2.94m.
That's close to 3m. I should've
put the sticker before falling.
Ji Hyo. Did you see how I did it?
- Isn't it scary?
- It's okay. It's safe.
Are you going? Okay.
It was all for the show.
Come on.
He's acting proud.
That was very elaborate acting.
Let's go.
- It was okay up to 1m.
- Ji Hyo. Crawl like me.
It feels different.
- Ji Hyo is the ace.
- She's really brave.
I think she's the coolest.
She even jumped in Macao.
Bungee jumping in Macao...
- 3, 2...
(It was Episode 133.)
(Ji Hyo jumped from 338m high
Macao Tower without hesitation.)
(In fact, she was smiling.)
(This is way too easy for her.)
She's not wasting any time.
She's moving by herself.
You should stretch your arm.
Put the sticker
when you're about to fall.
- What's gotten into you?
- Look at her.
You can go further.
(Relaxed)
- She got pretty far.
- She can go further.
(She passes Jae Suk's record.)
You got it.
- Don't go further.
- You got it.
(The diving board broke
when she put the sticker.)
(Did the sticker stay?)
She did it, but that must've been
very scary.
- Ji Hyo.
- You scared me, Ji Hyo.
Are you okay?
- She...
- I mean...
(He's helping Ji Hyo.)
- Are you okay?
- I mean...
Are you okay?
(Dragging)
- Ji Hyo.
- Hey.
(Towing service by kind Kwang Soo)
Are you all right?
I said I'm okay.
She's okay.
(Luckily, Ji Hyo is okay.)
What a relief. She's okay.
- Did it hurt when you fell?
- It was okay.
It doesn't hurt.
Hey. You saw me.
You cried.
- Hey.
- You were sobbing.
You saw how I did it.
Se Chan's pretty brave.
I know. He's good at
something like this.
- See? He's sitting down.
- That's amazing.
Se Chan. Just look forward.
I'll move with courage.
(He catches his breath.)
(Glancing)
(He moves without hesitation.)
- Put the sticker.
- You have to do it now.
(He walked to the end at once
and put the sticker.)
- Put the sticker.
- You have to do it now.
- He couldn't do it.
(He dropped the sticker.)
(Spinning)
- He couldn't do it.
- No?
- He couldn't put the sticker.
(Devastated)
- I was almost there.
- Why did you...
If you fall
when you're about to put it,
- you can't put the sticker.
- No.
- You have to hurry up.
- Se Chan.
You keep bringing the average down.
I'm sorry.
That was so close.
I don't think I can do it.
Honestly, I think I'm going to
wet my pants.
If I wet my pants,
it can't be on air, right?
They can blur it.
If I wet my pants, will it be aired?
That part will be edited out.
Only that part? I'm not even joking.
I think I'm going to wet my pants.
- Go to the restroom.
- That's not it.
I think I'm going to wet my pants
because I'm too scared.
So Min. Put the sticker
from here then.
- Right. You could do that.
- You could try that.
- Then...
- That's what I'm going to do.
I don't want to look like a coward.
I'm going to look like a coward.
So Min. Do it.
Go.
If you put the sticker at 1m...
If you're not going to do it,
let us know in advance.
Just try to the point
you can pull off.
- She can do it.
- I'm light.
I'm light. See? I'm light.
- Now, go.
- Just move one foot. You can do it.
You can lie down. It was okay
when I lied down up to 2m.
My heart is racing so fast.
So Min. If your heart is
running fast,
that means a good blood circulation.
- It means you're healthy.
- Right.
Lie down. That's right.
My heart is racing so fast.
It's not even slanted.
- It's fine because you're light.
- Because I'm light.
I went all the way to the end.
Lie down. That's right.
- You have to increase the average.
- You can move. You won't break it.
- It won't break.
- That's good.
You're moving like water.
Stretch your arm first, So Min.
Stretch your arm and...
- Get ready to put the sticker.
- You should get ready.
Haha. You should push her.
No. Don't.
- I won't. I shouldn't do it on her.
- He won't do it.
- She's crying!
- No.
- Don't cry.
- I'm not.
I'm not crying.
Do I look like I'm crying?
Look at me. I'm not crying.
- You're about to cry.
- But...
I'm smiling.
(She's between a smile and tears.)
Don't push me. Haha. Don't push me.
- I'm not.
- There's no one behind you.
If you push me, I won't ever
see you again. I'll unfollow you.
(Taking over a new leaf)
(Cracking)
- Hey.
- Wait.
- It just cracked.
- Hold on.
- Hang on.
- Moving backward is more dangerous.
- You should move forward.
- Keep going.
Hang on.
Wait. Wait a second.
My goal is...
about 2m. I'll put this on over 2m.
- Just stretch out your arm.
- You're nearly there.
Move a little more.
It's 2m 40cm.
So Min, come a little more.
(She reaches out her arm.)
She should make it
as long as possible.
Imagine that Dong Jun
is at the edge.
(Come over here, So Min.)
(Moving forward)
- Stretch your arm.
- Dong Jun!
I'm coming.
- Dong Jun.
- It's 3m.
It's 3m now.
- Good.
- Dong Jun.
How could she be so brave?
So Min, come back.
- Good.
- Dong Jun.
- All right. A little more.
That's very good.
- Good.
- You have 1m left.
Dong Jun, I'm coming.
(The second cracking)
- Dong Jun.
- Oh, no.
- It cracked again. Put it on.
- Go ahead and put it on.
- Put it on and come back.
- Just do it now.
So Min, just put it on there.
- Go ahead and stick it.
- Stick it there.
- I think you can come back.
- It's not breaking.
You can still come back.
That's good. You can
put it on there, So Min.
Yours is the furthest, So Min.
(How is it possible?)
Once you stick it,
yours will be the furthest.
Be careful.
(She puts her sticker
past Ji Hyo's.)
You should come back.
How can I go back?
- Do you need help?
- Just push me off.
- So Min, do you want my help?
- Just...
push me off.
Just kill me.
(Just kill me.)
- Why would they kill you?
- Kill me.
- Se Chan.
- What?
Go ahead and kill me. Hurry.
(She asks her friend Se Chan
the last favor.)
- It will be over soon.
- Push the edge.
- Take care.
- I'll pull you from here.
We can pull you from here.
- Be happy.
- My gosh.
(She wishes her friend happiness
like a scene from a movie.)
Oh, no.
(She falls down bravely.)
(She overcame her fear
with the power of love.)
You fell down safely.
- So Min, you're in first place.
- Am I?
She's unbelievable.
I could do it thanks to Dong Jun.
I owe it to Dong Jun.
So Min's record is 330cm.
- That's great.
- Thank you.
Next up is Haha.
Haha.
Haha, hurry.
Haha, it's no big deal.
Seriously, it's nothing.
This is what I'm going to do.
- I'll jump high...
- There you go.
and put on the sticker
before falling down.
- Okay. That's cool.
- But this will be...
- It's a good idea.
- just fine.
- Okay.
- Exactly.
- That would be really cool.
- Go ahead and do it.
Just do it.
- If you make it...
- It'll be so cool.
I guess my record would be about 3m.
Who are you talking to?
- My hands are sweating.
- Who is he talking to now?
Is someone up there?
Are you seeing things?
And this will be fine.
It will be fine.
(But I don't think I'll be fine.)
It's his wish.
I will save time to replace it.
- He's hypnotizing himself.
- What is he saying?
Who is he talking to?
So you will jump to the edge
and put on the sticker.
- Give me 10 seconds.
- Look at his face.
Who is he talking to?
- Is someone up there?
- You have five seconds left.
- There he goes.
- Four.
- Three.
- Don't. I'll count down myself.
(Deadly pale)
- I'm sorry.
- Or I'd run up there.
I'll jump as you get here.
Come running now.
Is that so?
He needs someone to follow him.
That will work.
- Someone's following you.
- Look back.
- It's a murderer.
You have to jump!
- Haha!
- There he is.
- Haha.
- He's almost there.
He's coming.
Haha.
- He will push you from the back.
- He's a murderer.
(He jumped.)
(The coward soars up
in a fierce chase.)
(Did Haha put on the sticker
before falling off like he said?)
- What was that?
- What?
- Did he put it on?
- Did it stick?
It did.
(Unbelievable)
(He managed to put
the sticker on the board.)
(He flew up like a butterfly
and stung like a bee.)
(It is almost 3m.)
- Really?
- What did he do?
- It worked.
- That was unique.
Haha, well done.
- You did it.
- It's fine.
I saved you some time to replace it.
- That was really cool.
- You did it, Haha.
That was amazing.
Was it cool?
(Haha's record is 280cm.)
- Is it my turn?
- Yes.
He seems so relaxed.
I think he will just smash it.
He doesn't seem nervous at all.
- Do I stick it?
- Are you going to jump?
Will you jump just like that?
- What?
- What's with him?
I'll jump from here.
I'll jump to the side like Haha did.
Jong Kook, I think...
it will be really cool...
if you jump
and turn around like this.
Will you stay quiet?
- Jump and...
- That's ridiculous.
You turn around
and put the sticker on 3m.
That doesn't make sense.
Are you a stunt man or something?
Let me start.
(He checks the landing spot.)
- He's unbelievable.
- He doesn't seem afraid at all.
Here I go.
1, 2,
- He's not afraid.
- and 3.
(He jumps right away.)
(He jumps lightly and puts
the sticker on the exact spot.)
- It didn't even break.
- He didn't break it.
What's his record?
Did it stick?
It's 320cm.
Suk Jin will use this
as it is, right?
- I heard it crack.
- It snapped.
- Aren't you replacing it?
- It stuck.
He should use it as it is.
It snapped.
Two people used it already.
- No.
- I made that sound.
Snap. Snap. I made that sound.
- Two people used it already.
- Petty Gang!
- Two people jumped off the board.
- Petty Gang.
They're out of boards now.
Darn it.
Petty is coming.
Do you have a saw?
I should saw it a little.
It's slanted. Two people used it.
- It's always like that.
- No.
This isn't right.
It's not that bad.
That's how it always looks.
Gosh, this is too high.
Wouldn't I get hurt as I fall down?
- It's okay. It doesn't hurt.
- No. No one got hurt.
- Gosh, it snapped.
- It's soft down here.
- There's something no one tried.
- What?
Rolling.
That's ridiculous.
(He sets up his bristles.)
Why are you swearing at me?
- I'm sorry.
- It was just an idea.
I'm sorry. I get it.
I love you.
- What?
- What's going on?
He will use his foot.
(Why is he taking off his shoes?)
All right. You should do that.
(He will stretch out his leg
and puts the sticker.)
I'm sure he will get a cramp
in his toes.
(The boss of Petty Gang
came up with a brilliant idea.)
- I agree.
- I'm 100 percent sure.
Suk Jin is...
I can tell he studied business
administration at Ajou University.
He's really different.
- He's something else.
- Like how?
He's a genius
in business administration.
He plays games
in a whole different way.
We will play H.O.T's song.
And you can move forward
jumping on your buttocks.
(Jumping)
- To H.O.T's song.
- Good.
You can dance like Moon Hee Joon.
It's creaking already.
Suk Jin, raise your arms.
- There you go.
- It's done.
Jump on your buttocks.
(As the music starts...)
(Dancing)
He's dancing to the rhythm.
- He's getting into the rhythm.
- Hey.
I'm not in the mood for that.
Isn't this it?
- I'm not in the mood for that.
- I'll play something else.
I don't think I can do this
with my foot.
It won't work.
- All right. It's done.
- It's "Gang".
- You can do this.
- There you go.
- This is it.
- He's clenching his teeth.
- He's coming.
- You're cool.
Just do it at one go.
- Go.
- He's moving.
(He crawls forward
and puts the sticker.)
He did it.
- He did it.
- It stuck.
You were like Kwang Soo.
It's 290cm.
I did it anyway.
Petty Gang is impressive.
(It's the dignity
of the boss of Petty Gang.)
I want to join Petty Gang.
(He doesn't really mean it.)
- You're lying, right?
- Yes.
(Asking quietly)
Guys, the first mission is over.
- The first place is...
- We don't know it yet.
Jong Kook with the record of 315cm.
- Okay.
- Where did I put it?
- It's your fault.
- It's his personal record.
The second place is Suk Jin
with the record of 280cm.
Oh, dear.
Petty Gang is really cool.
The third place is the five members
with the record of 244.8cm.
- Oh, no.
- I'm really sorry.
My sticker didn't stick.
And Kwang Soo is the last.
What do they do with the last?
Are you the last?
You failed to stick it, right?
Kwang Soo has just
got one more penalty ball.
Jong Kook will hear the keyword
and decide what to do.
Whether you will cut it or not.
The next keyword is...
- a car game.
- What?
- A car?
- It's a game played in a car.
In a car?
A car game wouldn't be easy.
It won't be easy.
It must be difficult.
It's better to do it alone.
- I think playing alone is better.
- That's better.
Cut it like this.
- Split us.
- You can split us like this.
- Split us here.
- Okay.
I'll split them like this.
- Thank you.
- Kwang Soo will lose anyway.
Let's move to the next
destination to eat then.
Playing alone is better.
(They will play a game in the car
heading to the restaurant.)
Are you hungry, guys?
- Yes.
- I'm starving.
You're eating grilled beef patties.
What's grilled beef patties?
It's like tteok galbi
made with beef.
- Tteok galbi?
- That sounds great.
But it's not that you all
will get to eat it.
You will play games
and get the food accordingly.
Does it have something to do
with cutting off again?
- Sure.
- It's the same.
- With the average?
- Yes.
- We have to do this well.
- We have to eat.
Here's the second mission.
It's Losing Rock-Paper-Scissors.
You will take turns
to play the game.
It's worth a try.
- I'm good at losing.
- The rules are simple.
I'll say rock-paper-scissors, go.
I'll say "go".
And I will play first.
And you will play to lose
as I say "go".
(The members should see what
the PD shows and lose the game.)
- It's simple.
- I think I'm good at this.
- That's easy.
- I've done it before.
You want us to eat.
You will get points
as many times as you lose.
- Okay.
- That's not difficult.
- It's easy.
- So I should show paper?
You should lose.
Should I show rock
as he says "go"?
- Jae Suk, you go first.
- Okay.
You have to lose to the director.
- This is so easy.
- As you say "go"?
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- There you go.
- I see.
Kwang Soo, stay quiet.
- I'm playing a game here.
- Seriously.
Kwang Soo, can't you see
that I'm playing a game here?
You'll fail anyway.
You'll see. I'm good at this.
- I'm good at losing.
- But I bet you'll win.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
(Jae Suk proudly wins
when he should lose.)
It should've been scissors.
- He's out, right?
- Right.
- You need to lose.
- Let me try again.
- I'll play again.
- What do you mean?
- Let me go again.
- You're out.
- We'll all get another chance then.
- I'll go again.
You can't do that.
- Unbelievable.
- Okay, let's do this.
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- Go.
(Se Chan succeeds.)
- Okay.
- Good.
- Nice one.
- That's one point.
- One point.
- We need to lose.
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- Go.
(He wins.)
- Seriously?
- It's not as easy as it seems.
- Are you kidding me?
- It's not easy.
- It's not that easy.
- Exactly.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Are you kidding me?
- It's not easy.
- Not at all.
Why would they have made
a game out of this?
- You only have a split second.
- It's not easy.
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- See?
- You failed.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
See?
Is it that hard?
It's not that easy.
- Jong Kook, you're next.
- Got it.
Watch and learn.
"Losing is winning"
has always been my motto.
(How many rounds
will Jong Kook be able to win?)
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- Go.
(Paper!)
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- Go.
(He wins the match
after shouting "go.")
(How adorable.)
- He was slightly late too.
- It's not easy.
- He was late.
- I lost all our practice rounds.
I'm just wired to win.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
(Kwang Soo loses with paper.)
- Okay!
- But you won.
- What?
- I had rock.
- He wasn't playing you.
- What are you talking about?
Unbelievable.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
Okay!
- He's good at this.
- He's quite good.
It needs to be played faster.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
Okay!
- Gosh.
- He's really good at this.
- He's good at losing.
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- He already has four points.
(He finally finds a game
he's good at.)
I won four points.
I don't want to win. I want to lose.
I've set everything aside.
- I want to lose.
- Hold on.
Your eyes are full of greed.
- You'll win in the first round.
- Your eyes are full of greed.
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- Go.
(So Min: scissors, Director: rock)
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- Go.
(She loses the first round
with scissors.)
- You were a bit slow.
- Exactly.
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
(She succeeds
in the next round too.)
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
(She succeeds in the 3rd round too.)
- Get one more point for us.
- My gosh.
- I've let it all down.
- We only need a point to lead.
I've set a lot of my greed aside.
- I can't believe I couldn't lose.
- I'm just a loser.
I'm a complete loser.
Play or lose.
It should be
"Rock-paper-scissors, go."
Go ahead.
- Don't change it up.
- Pick up the speed though.
Teach him a lesson.
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- Rock!
(Rock!)
(She fails to lose another round.)
Nice!
- Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- Rock!
(Smack!)
- What...
- It's your fault!
- He was helping you.
- I told you what to put out.
He told you the right answer.
The right one was rock.
- Is this allowed?
- Why do it anyway?
She should've been able to focus.
He made me lose my focus.
Still, she scored three points.
We're in the lead, right?
- Just memorize it, okay?
- Ji Hyo will fail for sure.
Don't you dare win.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
(She easily manages
to lose the first round.)
- Okay.
- She's good at this.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
- That's 1 point.
- She got 1 point.
It's our turn now.
- Can we get another turn?
- Let's try that again.
- Exactly.
- We now know how it's done.
We've got the hang of it now.
- Sure.
- All right.
- We know how to play it now.
- The points will be added.
- Okay.
- We have to lose.
Just watch. I'm done playing nice.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
You failed.
- Seriously?
- What was that?
You're superb at playing games.
- Hold on.
- You're superb at playing games.
- Give me another chance.
- We didn't expect you to win.
- Another chance?
- Come on.
- Give me another chance.
- No way.
Let me try again.
- We should move on.
- Hold on.
Are you being this way now that
"Infinite Challenge" is over?
- Hold on.
- What?
- That's out of the blue.
- What was that?
Why would you suddenly
mention "Infinite Challenge"?
What's wrong with you?
- Why would you mention that show?
- All I want is another chance.
Hold on!
What did you mean by that?
Will the show be revived?
No, that's not it.
Jong Kook, you're next.
Hold on second. Let me focus!
I've got this! I'm ready.
- You only have to lose.
- Got it.
Rock-paper-scissors, go.
You failed.
Rock-paper-scissors, go
- He can't lose.
- He can't.
- He's wired to win.
- Losing is not in his DNA.
- Exactly.
- All right, guys.
In first place is Kwang Soo
with four points.
Okay!
In second place
with only 0.5 points behind are...
(Kwang Soo: 4 points)
Haha, So Min, and Ji Hyo.
Wait, don't we have a point?
- No, you have 0.5 points.
- Right, we have to divide it.
That puts you in third place.
The remaining two
both have zero points,
but Suk Jin is last.
Let's grab some lunch then.
(What will they receive
for today's lunch?)
- It's not for me though.
- What's this?
Check this out!
Was this for today's lunch?
(Juicy grilled beef patties)
No way.
Look.
What is all this?
Must 2nd, 3rd, and 4th place share?
(The team in 5th place
doesn't get any patties.)
The ranking hasn't been fixed
just yet though.
- What?
- Why not?
The one in first place
can shift things around.
That's right!
If I choose a team,
will that team...
be able to eat with me?
We'll calculate the average.
Kwang Soo.
- Kwang Soo...
- Come on.
You're better off with us since
they already have three people.
Join me,
and you'll still be in first place.
Can he choose to be his own team?
- You'll still be in first place.
- Kwang Soo.
- I...
- Cut this tie.
I'll team up Jong Kook and Suk Jin.
- Those two?
- Us two?
I'll team up Jong Kook and Suk Jin.
- Those two?
- Us two?
You'll be the team
in last place and eat that.
- Okay.
- What did you say?
(What did you say?)
- Consider the next game too.
- That's why I teamed them up.
- Okay.
- Am I getting a penalty ball?
- Nice!
- And Suk Jin too.
- Good one.
- We should end Kwang Soo.
Jong Kook, we should end him.
Today, my target is Kwang Soo.
Kwang Soo...
I'll make sure he suffers
a physical injury today.
May I change my mind?
You made up your mind...
without listening to
what the next game is.
Just you wait and see.
What you'll need is
a survival skill.
(Requirements for the next game:
Survival skill)
It's not bad for me.
I lucked out in a way.
(His life is under threat.)
Here it comes.
(Lunch time)
- Kwang Soo, enjoy.
- Right.
- I'm only playing by the rules.
- There's more than one.
- It must've been just cooked.
- It's really good.
This is just the story of my life.
Even here, I've been given fish.
(Only Suk Jin and Jong Kook
miss out on the patties.)
(Kwang Soo gets up.)
It's really good though.
This...
It's quite good.
(He realizes the danger he's in
and delivers patties to Jong Kook.)
(You know how I feel, right?)
He got some on your arm.
(Kwang Soo got sauce
on Jong Kook's arm?)
You should wipe it off.
(Kwang Soo goes back
without realizing it.)
He got sauce on my arm.
Why are you eating my patties?
Why...
(During that time,
the two sisters stole his food.)
(He gets sauce on Jong Kook
and has his food stolen by the two.)
(What will happen to Kwang Soo
in the final round?)
(After lunch...)
I think I see water guns.
No way. Wait, what's this?
That's my son's favorite.
Hold on. Those are water guns.
This must be it.
It's better to be
a one-man team then.
Being in a group is worse.
It'll be uncomfortable
to be tethered to each other.
Here's the last game of the day.
The last game is all about
being the last man standing.
This is the Survival Balloon War.
(Final game: Survival Balloon War)
The game will consist
of two 20-minute halves.
- Each team will have 30 bullets.
- Good.
And you'll wear a vest
with five balloon attached to it.
If all of your balloons are popped,
you'll be eliminated.
The one eliminated
must give up his or her gun...
but still run around with the team.
(Once eliminated,
the gun must be given back.)
Even if all of your balloons
get popped,
you'll have to stay tethered
to your team but without a gun.
- Must I drag him along with me?
- Yes.
What do you mean
you'll drag him along?
- Hold on.
- Drag him along?
- Must you say it like that?
- That's how it'll be.
Don't be like that.
I can shoot at first, you know.
- But still...
- "I can shoot you!"
(He expresses his enthusiasm
with a line from "Tazza".)
I'm talking about after
you're eliminated.
- "I can shoot you!"
- I can!
- Unbelievable.
- Each team will get 30 bullets,
so how you divide them
is important.
We shouldn't waste them.
You can pick up the bullets
shot by an opponent.
That's not bad.
And during the race,
you should also...
There are 100 table tennis balls
hidden in the building.
The more balls you find,
the more points you get.
- My goodness.
- I see.
When only one team is left,
the round ends.
And each member of the winning team
will receive 10 table tennis balls.
- 100 in total?
- Playing individually won't matter.
- Kwang Soo is alone.
- At the end of the race,
the number of the balls...
There are three people on my team.
Will the number of the balls...
we found be tallied?
No, we'll calculate
the average number.
But the winner in the winning team
will choose a benefit.
- If you find the most balls...
- That's right.
- We should find a lot of balls.
- Correct.
Now, please move to
your starting place.
Okay.
(Each team will move to
their starting place.)
The more we find, the better for us
because we have many members.
(They have many balloons
as they're a team of many people.)
I'm counting on you two.
I played with this toy
with Dream so many times.
- You must be good at using it.
- Haha, but this...
We shouldn't pop
each other's balloons.
Of course. We should keep
as many of them as possible.
- As many as possible.
- Yes.
You got a penalty ball, right?
- You got one too, right?
- Yes, I did.
- So did Kwang Soo, right?
- Who didn't?
We should eliminate
those who didn't get any.
- That'd be So Min's team.
- Exactly.
We should eliminate them all first.
I think we should shoot the target
together.
So that at least one of us
gets the target.
- If I go this way, you go that way.
- Exactly.
It'll be most advantageous
for Kwang Soo.
He's playing individually.
It was a good strategy.
It was good that I made those two
into one team.
(The one-man team is
fully satisfied.)
Gosh. This won't work.
(He has fewer balloons,
but better mobility.)
Okay. Good. I'm ready.
I know it doesn't hurt.
(He's showing off his skill
by shooting the staff.)
Just wait and see
who will survive to the end.
(The lonely killer Kwang Soo
is ready for the battle.)
I'll show you what I can do.
I'm serious.
The race begins in five seconds.
5, 4, 3...
(They must survive long
and find many balls.)
Two.
One. The race begins now.
The race starts.
(The race starts.)
I should find
table tennis balls too.
(The team that finds the most balls
before losing the balloons wins.)
- I get more points if I find balls.
- Correct.
I'm going to find
some table tennis balls.
At the store... Oh, there it is.
(Oh, there it is.)
(He found the first table tennis
ball behind the bulletin board.)
Put it in the bag.
I have this weird feeling.
I have a feeling that I'm going to
surprise everyone.
(He only found 1 out of 100 balls.)
(But he seems so confident.)
(He pressed the top floor
with confidence.)
Hiding yourself from your enemies
is important in a battle like this.
And always take over
the highest ground.
(Lee Kwang Soo,
100 percent confident)
It's hard to shoot from below.
However...
You can see the back of your enemies
from above.
(Winking)
(He arrived on the top floor
while talking big.)
What is this place?
- It's locked.
- What?
(The door is locked.)
Everyone, what I said earlier
was a joke.
(Everyone, what I said earlier
was a joke.)
- It already left.
- Darn it.
(He was going to go back down,
but it was too late.)
(While Kwang Soo failed
to use his mobility...)
I can't even walk fast because
I'm afraid I might pop a balloon.
I know.
100 balls are a lot.
- Look closely.
- Okay.
I found a table tennis ball.
- Where is it?
- Okay.
It's on the camera holder. Okay.
Okay.
Things are going smoothly.
It's good.
How about we share
the balls evenly?
- Okay.
- Let's do that.
Let's share them.
(Haha's team members are searching
for table tennis balls.)
- Okay.
- We can't steal balls, right?
Correct.
- There's another one.
- Hey, there... Good.
- You're good at finding it.
- I want one too.
- There it is.
(There it is.)
I want one too. It's mine.
It's my turn, Haha.
- Stop it.
- It's mine.
- It's all about trust.
- It's my turn.
- My gosh.
- All right. Wait.
I'm supposed to have it.
Okay, So Min. All right.
I'll compete against you
if you keep going like this.
You two are being too sensitive.
Why would you say such a thing?
- We're a team.
- We can take turns to have a ball.
- Is there another one?
- We agreed to share them.
- Aren't you going to share them?
- Of course, I'll share them.
(Ji Hyo is betraying them.)
Hey, stop. Wait.
(Ji Hyo who has no intention of
sharing balls is walking forward.)
She's dragging us both.
- I found one.
- Gosh, seriously.
(They're trying to stop her,
but she's monstrously strong.)
A table tennis ball.
(The monstrous strength
created for a table tennis ball)
- Hey. We can share...
- You might pop the balloons.
(She fell behind
while showing off her strength.)
(She could've lost balloons
while getting a ball.)
Let's find them first
and share them later.
(Unlike what she said, she doesn't
seem to want to share them.)
There must be
a few around here, right?
I thought so too,
but I couldn't find any.
Let's keep searching.
Left or right?
Left. Let's go to the left.
- Here it is. What did I tell you?
- Come over here.
(They walked
in the opposite directions.)
(While Jong Kook found a ball...)
- He never listens to me.
- I can't pull him toward me.
- Hey!
- Come here, Suk Jin.
Come on.
- Hey, but I want to...
- Suk Jin.
- Search places like this.
- There...
- There's another one here.
- Gosh.
- He's driving me insane.
- Look.
- Why won't you look in there?
- Wait.
Why are you taking all the balls?
Come here.
- Suk Jin, come this way first.
- Why that little...
If we go that way,
you'll take another ball.
- Let's search there first.
- You'll take it again.
Come here. There's more here.
I want to...
Let's keep going this way.
Fine. I'm coming.
- Hey. Wait.
- Let's go.
- Let's shoot them together.
(While they're distracted,
Team White starts the attack.)
Wait up.
Suk Jin, someone is coming.
They're coming.
Behind us.
Jae Suk is coming towards us.
Get ready.
(The ambush failed.
They should fight head-on.)
Get ready.
You want a fight?
Jae Suk, let's find
table tennis balls first.
Once any one of us shoots,
it will be a total chaos.
- Exactly.
- Hey.
- We won't just die for nothing.
- Don't shoot.
- I'm just saying...
We don't have to do this.
If you start shooting,
we will shoot you too.
What? Are you going to shoot us?
- We'll shoot back.
- What?
(At that moment,
a bullet was shot!)
- What happened?
- Gosh.
- Look at that.
- Are you going to shoot us?
(The lonely killer showed up!)
(Kwang Soo ambushed them
using his mobility.)
(He's actually taken aback.)
He's going to use up his bullets.
(He only wasted his bullets
and retreated.)
- Stop.
- We won't shoot at each other.
- Why not?
- Let's pick up those bullets.
Let's go.
(They picked up the bullets
keeping an eye on each other.)
(The toy gun war is
about to break out.)
(Peace didn't last long.)
(The two teams started
shooting at each other.)
You're shooting us?
(While Suk Jin was moving around
being flustered...)
- I'm going to shoot.
- What?
(Pop)
(Jong Kook's balloon popped
because of the bullet in his hand.)
(He became more aggressive without
knowing he popped it himself.)
(Nothing can stop them now.)
- I'm going to shoot.
- What?
(Jae Suk hit
one of Suk Jin's balloons.)
Why would they pop so easily?
(The protruding mouth brothers
are on a roll.)
Suk Jin, I'll be in the front.
(Another balloon on Jong Kook's back
popped.)
(He's at the highest anger level.)
They won't pop.
(He moved forward while attacking
without looking behind.)
(While he was attacking them,)
(he lost two more balloons.)
- Take this.
- Hey.
Jong Kook, you have
only one balloon left. Stop.
You have only one balloon left.
You'll be eliminated
if you lose all. Wait.
- Let's step backwards.
- Okay.
(Team White is making
a strategic retreat.)
(While the two teams repeat
attack and retreat...)
- Let's step backwards.
- Okay.
(While the two teams repeat
attack and retreat...)
(The lonely killer Kwang Soo is
approaching them from behind.)
(Kwang Soo came to attack them!)
(Kwang Soo is here!)
- Jae Suk, Kwang Soo is coming.
- Attack!
(Pop)
(Unlike his confidence
and high spirit,)
(he lost three balloons
in an instant.)
Gosh. What is this? Darn it.
(He achieved nothing
from his second ambush either.)
(He's trying to run away.)
(He failed to run away as well
as he got caught in the tether.)
(And he lost 1 of the 2 balloons
he has left.)
What was that?
- Wait.
- He has one balloon left.
I won't shoot.
- Almost all balloons popped.
- What is this?
What was that?
(I surrender unconditionally.)
- Okay. You have only one left.
- Don't shoot.
Give us a few bullets in return.
- I'll give you my bullets.
- How many will you give us?
- Give me your bullets. Go now.
Share with him.
We'll keep you alive
to make the show interesting.
(The killer became pitiful.)
(He has only one balloon left.)
- He has just one left.
- I...
It's over when it pops.
- All right.
- I'll be sent to the jail.
- Okay.
- I won't shoot.
I'll go to that team.
- Good.
- I'll attack them instead.
Darn it.
(As a result of his 2nd ambush,
he lost 4 while they lost 0.)
(He surprised everyone
just as he said earlier.)
This is driving me insane.
Shall we go to the bridge?
How many balls did you find?
(How many balls did you find?)
Your bag is full.
I don't have many.
(Their comradeship is long gone.)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
(Startled)
- I'm sorry.
- Why...
Why did you aim at her
when she just works in the building?
- It's because I was nervous.
- Haha.
Gosh. No, no.
(They almost got into big trouble.)
- I saved your balloons.
- Thank goodness.
That startled me.
The doors close so quickly.
Hurry up. Come on.
We must be their target.
I have a feeling that someone
will be there.
(Will they be able to
fight properly?)
- That was intense.
- Indeed.
However, our fight
against Jong Kook's team...
will be beneficial to Haha's team.
(Someone showed up
in front of them.)
(It's Kwang Soo
who has only one balloon.)
I have only one balloon left.
If you have only one left...
Come with us
to destroy So Min's team.
- Jae Suk, please.
- What?
Don't shoot. I have only one left.
Okay.
Give us one ball for letting you go.
I could've just run, but I'll
trust you and give you this.
- Okay. I promise.
- You have to shoot them.
- That's why I'm giving you.
- Go now.
Just go. Go away
before I change my mind.
I was just checking my gun.
I'm sorry.
(I was just checking my gun.
I'm sorry.)
I was checking if it works well.
- It works well. You can go now.
- Go. Go now.
Go on.
I only lost my table tennis ball.
(How did I end up like this?)
Let's stay inside the building.
It's too hot outside.
(Team Orange is also looking
for the three siblings.)
- My goodness, hello.
- I am sorry.
(Awkward)
(They suddenly feel embarrassed.)
I am carrying around a toy gun
at the age of 45.
(They look back upon themselves
with a toy gun in their hands.)
This is embarrassing.
- Combined, our ages make 100 years.
- 100 years.
If kids run around like this,
I should go, "Hey."
- "What are you punks doing?"
- "You punks."
- "Don't get hurt."
- I am at the age to say that.
I am carrying a toy gun and yelling,
"Shoot! Don't shoot!"
(The duo became absorbed in the game
like the actors in an action movie.)
- "Don't shoot!"
- Seriously.
- Despite my age, this is fun.
- This is fun.
- Don't you agree?
- Yes.
- Kids must love it so much more.
- Seriously.
It's just hard to do this
someplace else.
Where are the others?
I don't see anyone.
(Meanwhile, the trio)
I see someone! It's Kwang Soo!
Kwang Soo is telling the others
about us.
We will lose.
Hold on. Kwang Soo doesn't have
any balloons.
- He doesn't have any balloons.
- We can take him out.
- He has 1 balloon.
We can pop it.
- We can pop it.
- Come here.
- Let's hide for now.
Here come the gunmen!
Make way!
- Bang, bang, bang!
- Bang!
Why don't we take out Jong Kook
first?
(They lose their fighting spirit.)
There is no need for us to fight.
We...
Be careful.
(Jae Suk's accuracy rate
is at 100 percent.)
(The 3 cowards become startled.)
Be careful.
(Their combat style is as forward
as their mouths are protruding.)
Hey. Hey.
(Se Chan sets out to take out
Kwang Soo with 1 balloon.)
Come here!
Kwang Soo, watch out.
(He strikes back!)
(The gunmen with protruding mouths
are surrounded.)
Pick them up.
They are running away.
- Pick them up.
- They are running away.
- Let's fall back for now.
- Let's go.
(Let's fall back for now!)
Okay. Okay.
- The bullets.
- Pick them up.
I have one left.
- Do you have one left? This is bad.
- Yes.
The first half came to an end.
Please wait for the second half.
- Okay.
- The first half ended.
- Let's go.
Let's go downstairs.
(They start over with 5 balloons
in the 2nd half.)
For the second half,
please move to your spot.
Do you have tape?
It's not advantageous to be alone.
(Kwang Soo looks for tape
as soon as the second half begins.)
(He is wrapping up his balloon.)
As insurance, I will make a balloon
that doesn't pop.
(Popping)
(What?)
(What was that sound?)
It didn't pop.
This balloon is simply a bit small.
It's a small balloon.
(Wrinkly)
Kwang Soo, one of your balloons
popped.
You have four balloons left.
(He ends up starting
with 4 balloons.)
The race starts.
- Let's go.
- The second half starts.
I am sure they are talking about us.
- We are...
- The legendary gunmen.
We are the legendary gunmen.
You have the least number
of table tennis balls.
- Really?
- For goodness' sake.
Don't be an amateur.
- We can turn the tables.
- That's right.
We can wipe everyone out.
Don't be a coward.
I don't think they are here.
No, they must be here somewhere.
Let's search again.
Are table tennis balls important?
- They are like points, right?
- They are like points.
They are very important.
After the race, they determine
the rankings with them.
- You either take out an opponent...
- Okay.
(He gets 1 table tennis ball.)
You either take out an opponent...
I don't calculate those things.
(A good thing
about teaming up with Suk Jin)
These punks.
How are you so good at finding them?
You should tell me.
What was I supposed to do?
- It wasn't there before.
- It was right in front of my eyes.
How did it suddenly pop up?
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo)
(He hasn't learned his lesson
even after popping one balloon.)
(In the end, he makes
a bulletproof balloon.)
It's done.
I did it. Okay.
(I will win today.)
It's Kwang Soo.
(Haha and the others appear.)
- You have no table tennis balls.
- I am alone.
(I am alone.)
I am alone.
Are you going to shoot at me?
(The two teams confront each other.)
- Jae Suk, Kwang Soo is here.
- Jae Suk.
(The ineffective gunmen appear.)
Let's attack together.
There we go.
- Jae Suk.
- Let's join forces.
It would be better
to take Kwang Soo out first.
- He is at an advantage.
- I am not at an advantage!
You saw it earlier!
I am not at an advantage!
We will be your ally
if you give us a table tennis ball.
(A small reward can move
these two gunmen.)
Jae Suk.
(Popping)
(1 shot, 1 balloon)
(Everyone becomes excited
while holding a toy gun.)
Move to the back.
(Kwang Soo becomes annoyed
and attacks So Min.)
(At that moment,)
(there is one man on Running Man
who is good with toy guns,)
(Yoo Jae Suk.)
(Popping)
What are you doing?
Who are you shooting?
(Jae Suk's next target)
- What?
- I got two balloons.
(He shot Haha's balloon
from a distance.)
- What?
- I got two balloons.
(He popped 2 balloons
with 1 bullet.)
You got that on the camera, right?
(You got that on the camera, right?)
We are the legendary gunmen.
(Dream's father
becomes intimidated.)
(Thinking)
- I will go to you.
- Okay.
(At that moment,)
(So Min comes forward
with a barricade.)
(Se Chan becomes flustered.)
(He fires multiple bullets,)
(but her barricade is 100 percent
effective in blocking the bullets.)
(Kwang Soo fires off bullets
as well.)
Jae Suk, I am out of bullets.
I am leaving.
Jae Suk, finish him off.
Hold on.
(I will spare Kwang Soo
since he is an ally.)
Now is the time! Shoot!
Shoot! He is out of bullets!
(Jae Suk is out of bullets,
so the trio attacks in full force.)
(Popping)
- What?
- I didn't shoot.
I am out of bullets.
(But too many of their balloons
are getting popped.)
What is going on?
(They forgot...)
(that Kwang Soo never changes.)
- That little...
(You can imagine what he did
from his satisfied face.)
(Creeping up)
- What?
- I didn't shoot.
I am out of bullets.
(After saying that,
he began to shoot.)
(He popped three balloons.)
(After an act of betrayal,
he runs away with a smile.)
(He causes a major accident
and becomes a public enemy.)
Let's wait
until their bullets run out.
It's a face-off.
(He became interested
in a toy gunfight in his 50s.)
Corner them!
- All right.
- This is good.
(Trio versus The 100-year-old duo)
Corner them.
We were sneaking up on them.
We need to finish them off first.
- Corner them.
- We need to finish them off first.
Corner them.
(However)
- Out.
(Se Chan is out.)
(Haha changes the target
and takes out Se Chan.)
What?
(He becomes the first person
to be eliminated.)
Se Chan.
If all of your balloons are popped,
you'll be eliminated.
You won't be able to shoot anymore.
(He resorts to picking up bullets.)
(Jae Suk becomes angry
that Se Chan is out.)
(He succeeds to avenge Se Chan.)
Haha is out.
- I am out.
- Haha is out.
- Haha, put your gun down.
- Okay.
(He shoots Ji Hyo's balloon too.)
Ji Hyo is out.
We are the legendary gunmen.
- What should I do?
- Pick up the bullets.
- Shoot. Shoot.
- Haha, give me an umbrella.
Is this "Kingsman"?
(Jong Kook jumps in.)
Hurry up.
Okay. I got it.
(So Min is out.)
So Min is out.
(All the members of the trio
are out.)
You nasty...
(Jong Kook, the nasty man)
(They become the first team
to enter the prison.)
- Let's go.
- It was fun.
We were cool.
Kwang Soo shot at us from the back.
Is it allowed to wrap the balloon
with tape?
- For goodness' sake.
- That's cheating.
- Did Kwang Soo tape his balloon?
- Yes.
- Why does he do that?
- He is so strange.
It's just wrong
to tape your balloon.
(Kwang Soo was on a stakeout.)
(Kwang Soo ambushes them
because he never fights fair.)
He was hiding here.
Kwang Soo!
(He shoots freely.)
(The man with a bulletproof balloon)
It won't pop.
(He runs away
after firing off bullets.)
(Team White hears them belatedly.)
- What?
- It won't pop.
He was hiding here.
- Should I kill him?
- This won't do.
He was hiding here.
- I can go to him and...
- I have an idea.
If you go this way,
we will corner him downstairs.
Since his balloon is taped,
we need to overpower him.
We can't pop it with our hands.
- Find a spot that isn't taped...
- Okay.
- and press the gun against it.
- We will go this way.
- Okay?
- Okay. I got it.
We need to get him.
(Kwang Soo became
everyone's target.)
(Crashing)
(He crashes into a locked door.)
(Groaning)
I am injured.
Kwang Soo is over there.
- Where?
- Over there. He's over there.
- Kwang Soo is over there.
- I see him.
- Hold on.
- He is crawling.
(It's Jong Kook.)
(Kwang Soo runs upstairs.)
Kwang Soo is on the second floor.
- The 2nd floor?
- He is on the 2nd floor.
- We will hide here.
- Kwang Soo is on the second floor.
Go to the staircase.
Suk Jin, come behind me.
- He saw me.
- Come behind me.
- Why?
Hey.
Why are you taking
all the table tennis balls?
I told you to come behind me.
Why won't you listen?
(What?)
(Did he pop Jong Kook's balloon?)
(He attacks his team member
with unfocused eyes.)
- Are you crazy?
- I was angry.
- I am sorry.
- Come here.
I am sorry.
I was out of my mind.
He shot me!
You should have given me one.
He should have given me 1 ball
after taking 3 balls, right?
You still shouldn't shoot Jong Kook.
I exploded.
(Suk Jin's attack buys Kwang Soo
some time.)
(Panting, he heads somewhere.)
(The rooftop?)
- All right.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Here.
- Where?
- Come here.
- The door is open.
- Where?
- Here.
Let's go.
Drive him downstairs.
(The man they have been looking for,
Kwang Soo is there.)
You aren't luring us, are you?
- Where is he?
- I think he is at the rooftop.
Is he at the rooftop?
Gosh, Suk Jin!
(Why was he aiming at Jae Suk?)
What's wrong with you?
(Jae Suk is so surprised...)
(that he attacks Suk Jin.)
- What's wrong with you?
- Why did you shoot me?
- I didn't shoot you.
- You were about to.
I wasn't going to shoot you.
I simply aimed my gun at you.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- I simply aimed like this.
- Hey.
- Suk Jin!
- It popped. You are out!
- What are you doing?
Hey.
(Jae Suk is out.)
- You are out.
- Jae Suk and Se Chan are out.
- What was that?
- I mean...
- We were going to get Kwang Soo.
I simply aimed at you,
but you popped my balloon.
Why did you...
I simply aimed at you,
but you popped my balloon.
You are out.
Suk Jin is a bit strange.
He is absolutely insane.
I mean...
(Meanwhile,
Kwang Soo, the wanted man,)
(is going
where he hasn't gone before.)
(Hurry over here, Jong Kook.)
(Now, it's 2 against 1.)
- He is here.
- Up here?
- Where?
- No, he isn't here.
- Where is he? He must be up there.
Where is he? He must be up there.
Come on down so that we can fight.
It's over, Kwang Soo.
Let's end this.
Suk Jin, your balloons are showing.
You fool!
(Suk Jin is so absorbed
that he gets ahead of himself.)
(His strategy...)
(of taking the high ground
finally shines.)
(Why aren't they coming out?)
(He throws a table tennis ball
as bait.)
(It's aimed at Suk Jin
since he never picked one up.)
- It's a table tennis ball.
- Don't do it.
- He wants us to pick it up.
- My goodness.
- Did you only figure it out now?
He wants us to pick it up.
That weasel.
You are the only one
who didn't know that he is a weasel.
(This won't do.)
(Screaming)
(Jong Kook is a perfect shooter
even from the bottom.)
(He is blocking the bullets
with his face.)
For goodness' sake.
(His strategy
of taking the high ground fails.)
(Kwang Soo took a heavy blow.)
(He begins to think of a trick.)
Let's do this.
Let's do this today.
I will win for sure.
(Panting)
What a long fight.
It's lonely to be by myself,
(It's lonely to be by myself.)
but it does give me
a certain advantage.
(From the start,
Kwang Soo was overly absorbed.)
(He said many ridiculous things.)
(Becoming cowardly
is the only way to survive alone.)
(That way, he managed to survive
for 40 minutes.)
(Now, I will put an end to this.)
- There he is.
- Where?
- What does he want to do?
- He is over there.
(Why does he have to be
the last one remaining?)
(Breathing hard)
Okay. This is the only way.
- Come here.
- Now that we are here...
Look at that taped balloon.
Is that bulletproof or something?
I have a lot of bullets.
(I have a lot of bullets.)
My balloon is covered.
(The only way
of popping that balloon is...)
(physical force.)
(Confrontation)
(The two of them run forward
to pop Kwang Soo's balloon.)
(Kwang Soo awaits them.)
(Who will be the winner
of this match?)
The race has ended.
The final result is out.
The first place holder
of the winning team...
can either remove
all of his penalty balls...
or share a small prize...
with the team members.
For your information,
the winning team...
(The winning team...)
(can either remove the penalty balls
or share the prize.)
has members with an average
of 14 table tennis balls,
Jong Kook and Suk Jin.
- We have a lot.
- Yes!
(The 100-year-old duo has an average
of 14 table tennis balls.)
- 14?
(There is a reason why
Kwang Soo lost.)
(During the last confrontation
a moment ago)
This is the only way.
(During the last confrontation
a moment ago)
(What?)
He can't shoot.
- He can't shoot.
- Hold on.
- Hurry up.
(Thus, Kwang Soo's day ended
as comedy.)
Hold on. Hold on.
- Here.
- Shoot, you jerks!
- Step on it!
- Which part isn't taped?
Do you want me to use a real gun?
It's impossible to pop this balloon.
(In the end,)
(he breaks the rules again.)
You need to use your gun.
- It came off.
- You are out.
(He pops the balloon
in a relaxed way.)
I popped it. I popped it.
- He is absolutely ridiculous.
- Seriously.
(After a prolonged confrontation)
I circled the rooftop three times.
(The duo receives 10 tennis balls
each and takes the 1st place.)
I picked up many balls
and raised the average.
- I picked up many balls.
- He picked up many balls.
In the team, Jong Kook takes
1st place with 18 balls.
(In the team, Jong Kook takes
1st place with 18 balls.)
Is that so?
You can take out
all of your penalty balls...
- or share a prize.
- But both of us won.
- No.
- He has more table tennis balls.
- I will take out my penalty balls.
No.
(I will take out my penalty balls.)
- Of course.
- Don't do that.
I will take them out.
- He didn't even think about it.
- That was neat.
I will take them out. Thank you.
The member at the bottom place is...
- Kwang Soo.
- What?
(Kwang Soo has the least number
of table tennis balls.)
Am I at the bottom place?
What is wrong with you?
I will pick two members.
(2 selected members will receive
the penalty.)
(Which 2 members...)
I will pick two balls.
(will receive the penalty
at the end of a long day?)
I got Kwang Soo and Kwang Soo.
(Kwang Soo gets selected twice.)
(Kwang Soo is one of them.)
Okay.
- He should get the penalty twice.
- Shouldn't you pick one more?
- In that case...
- You should pick one more.
You should pick one more.
(The next penalty ball)
- Kwang Soo.
- Pick one more.
Then it's over.
- Suk Jin remains.
Why?
Suk Jin remains.
(Suk Jin's penalty ball
gets chosen.)
(Despite winning,
he gets the penalty.)
How did this happen?
Two people need to receive
the penalty.
(Suk Jin and Jong Kook
were the only ones.)
You received a penalty ball earlier
for taking the fifth place.
Gosh, Kwang Soo.
Why didn't you say from the start
that it will be the two of us?
Why did you pick the balls?
Are there no more balls?
- It was meaningless.
- 3 for me and 1 for Suk Jin?
I will tell you what the penalty is.
- Today, the penalty is...
- Salt?
retrieving all the bullets...
while wearing the tether
before you go home.
- Okay.
- Oh, my goodness.
- We won't even get screen time.
As we do it,
the ending credits will roll up.
I even climbed up the ladder
at the rooftop and shot.
As for the rest of you,
thank you for your hard work.
Let's go!
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Bye.
Thank goodness
I didn't get a penalty ball.
- There is 1.
- There is 1. Let's pick it up.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- One.
Here.
There are many here.
Had I won...
(He wishes he hadn't fallen down.)
Didn't you shoot over there?
(While the task takes long,
they don't get much screen time.)
- There it is. Down there.
- Where?
- There it is.
- Good.
There it is.
- Okay.
- 28 bullets.
- We succeeded.
- You are done.
(The worst penalty ends.)
- We succeeded. Feeling!
- Intuition! Cross!
(Feeling! Intuition! Cross!)
(We introduce the students
of the Brahms Music School.)
(Park Eun Bin, Kim Min Jae,
Park Ji Hyun, and Kim Sung Cheol)
(For musical knowledge,
all of them take a test on music.)
(The peaceful atmosphere changes.)
(Everything was a competition.)
(Everyone who took the test...)
(is your rival!)
You are less than human.
(Behind the school building,)
(the music students fight by grade!)
(Figure out the changing grades...)
(and survive alone!)
(It's not easy to move up a grade.)
(To join forces,)
(find an upperclassman
and form an alliance.)
(Don't trust anyone!)
(What will become
of the fierce competition?)
(Do You Like Being Number 1?)