- Hello.
- Hi.
We should move as little as possible
on a day like this.
- Hello.
- I'm glad we're under the shade.
- It's really hot today.
- It's scorching hot.
We'd get a sunburn.
I know. I was in the sun
just for a moment.
It's going to be really hot.
It's like a calm before the storm.
What? A calm before the storm?
Did you just say
a four-character idiom?
What does this have to do
with a calm before the storm?
A calm before the storm means
before something happens.
- It's...
- Is it correct or not?
Is it appropriate
for this situation or not?
- It's not.
- A calm before the storm?
- Isn't it correct?
- It means...
something big is happening soon.
- I mean...
- It's quiet before it happens.
About 30 people here
are on Jong Kook's side.
What? That's what
a calm before the storm means.
- Hello.
- It's very hot now.
You can't say it's
a calm before the storm.
So the monsoon front...
Ji Hyo!
(Ji Hyo!)
(He escapes the crisis
by saying hello too loud.)
(I'm just excited to see her.)
- Hello, Ji Hyo.
- You're here.
- I thought she was someone else.
- What?
Today, we're having...
the second part of the race
that viewers wanted to see...
which will decide members to receive
the penalty during the live show.
What?
- It's the Reincarnation episode.
- Reincarnation?
- It's a really old one.
- Right?
- It was a long time ago.
(The Reincarnation episode
from 2013?)
(It was a race set in the 1930s.)
(Later on, the members were
born again in 2013.)
(And there was a secret
behind their reincarnation.)
(They were born again
as different members.)
(They figured out their identities
from the race of the 1930s.)
(Haha won the race
and got the treasure chest.)
(The Reincarnation episode will
be remade for 2020 today.)
(Part 1 of the race that viewers
wanted to see, Superpower)
(Part 2 of the race that viewers
wanted to see, Reincarnation)
(The live show on July 12)
We did the episode a long time ago.
We were independence fighters.
- Right.
- Exactly.
We were born again
after crossing some line.
- Right.
- I barely remember it.
We were born again
after crossing some line.
You know what?
- Exactly.
- I don't remember.
I think I won the race.
We weren't there, right?
- We weren't there, were we?
- I barely remember that.
- I feel left out.
- I had no idea.
I just thought reincarnation
sounded so cool.
Me too. I thought they were
talking about the Grim Reaper.
- Me too.
- Today, you are...
going on the Reincarnation Camp
as reincarnations.
- The Reincarnation Camp?
- Yes.
And you will have a guide
who will take you to the camp.
- A guide?
- We have a guide.
I see.
- Is someone getting off the bus?
- That's what it says on the bus.
- What does it say?
- "The 1st Reincarnation Camp".
It says welcome.
- The guide is getting off soon.
- Is someone getting off?
(Who's the camp guide
getting off the bus?)
- She just got off.
- She's here.
Who is it?
It's SUNMI. She's SUNMI.
- SUNMI.
- Hello, SUNMI.
- SUNMI is here?
- Why did SUNMI get off?
- SUNMI is...
- our guide.
- She's our guide.
She's the reincarnation guide.
Hey, SUNMI.
- It's SUNMI.
- I'm...
your guide
for the Reincarnation Camp.
- Are you?
- You're the guide.
- It's nice to see you.
- Did you come here alone?
No. We have other members
on the bus now.
Really? Let's get on the bus.
(Are there more campers on the bus?)
- Are there more people?
- What? My gosh.
What? My gosh. ZICO!
- Hello.
- What's going on?
Hello.
- Today...
- Hello.
- What is Cho Sae Ho doing here?
Hello.
- Hey, Do Hyun.
- What are you doing here?
- Hello.
- Hey, Do Hyun.
- Long time no see.
- Do Hyun is here too.
- Do Hyun.
Jo Young Gu is here.
What is Jo Sae Ho doing here?
Hello, Jo Young Gu.
I'm not Young Gu.
Oh, he's not Jo Young Gu.
Is Young Gu here?
- This is the Reincarnation Camp.
- Okay.
I'd like you to make
good memories on your way.
So your guide, SUNMI,
will take pictures of you.
She's the guide.
And the crew members will
join you as well.
Why are we taking pictures
all of a sudden?
Is something going on?
You have to hold the name tag.
You shouldn't take a picture alone.
- Why not?
- Look at the camera.
What?
Are we taking pictures
for no reason?
Where are we going?
Guys.
Like I said, this is
the Reincarnation Camp.
You guys have been reincarnated
from previous episodes.
- I see.
- And you all know...
- which episode you are from.
- Yes.
Since SUNMI has never
been eliminated before,
she will be the camp guide
for you guys today.
- Really?
- She's never been eliminated.
Is that true?
- You've never been eliminated?
- I haven't.
That's amazing.
I got eliminated
in the Hades episode.
- That's right.
- I remember that.
The one that featured Sung Dong Il.
- I died there.
- There was Bae Seong Woo.
- Actors from "Metamorphosis".
- Sung Dong Il was there.
They burned my chair.
- That's right.
- It was Jae Suk.
- Exactly.
- Right?
- I remember that.
- Ji Hyo...
threw a tantrum for real.
- I remember that.
- Right.
I'm still upset about it.
She's still upset.
I'm still upset.
What about you, ZICO?
I bet it was recent.
Yes. I recently got killed
three times...
- by one person.
- Oh, right.
- I remember that.
- It was Jong Kook.
- It was me.
- By one person.
(In episode 496, he got killed
three times by Jong Kook.)
I can't believe this.
Just by the one person?
I still resent him for that.
- I see.
- You resent me?
So Min, what about you?
I was reincarnated
from a recent episode too.
Se Chan eliminated me
in Gujeon Village.
- The scarecrow episode?
- Yes, the scarecrow.
He ripped off my name tag.
- That's right.
- It was my first episode back.
That's right. I'm sorry.
(Se Chan ripped off her name tag
her first episode back.)
(Even Se Chan was flustered.)
- I'm sorry.
- My time was cut short.
I'm really sorry about that.
Suk Jin, what about you?
- Jee-rasoni.
- It was on the 10th episode.
Cha Tae Hyun was a guest back then.
I was hiding inside the elevator.
- As soon as the doors opened...
- Right.
I pressed the close button,
but you opened them from outside.
It was the day
I received back surgery.
For me, it was during
the Battle of Supernaturals...
when Kwang Soo was dressed
as the humanoid from "Avatar".
I ripped off your name tag,
but you could bounce it back.
- That's right!
- I was eliminated instead.
That's the episode
I'm reincarnated from.
- It's recent for me too.
- When was it?
Hyo Seong and Kwang Soo...
- I remember.
- They were directors.
- Exactly.
- That episode.
- I remember too.
- That's right.
- They tricked me.
- Exactly.
We've been eliminated
in the most dramatic ways.
Everyone at the camp...
must solve the secret
to their reincarnation.
Someone from the losing team
will receive the penalty.
We're to solve
the secret of the reincarnation?
- Sounds like fun.
- We must unlock the secret.
- Jong Kook...
- Would you like some?
I feel like we were asked back
for a special installment.
- Yes, the 10th anniversary.
- It's a special episode.
Sae Ho, you're joining us
on a special episode?
Tell me about it.
- I can't believe it.
- It's nothing to celebrate.
- You squeezed your way in.
- I'm just grateful.
There's no need to congratulate me.
- But having this chance...
- I didn't know Sae Ho was here.
I didn't know that he was here.
So Min didn't even know
that you were here.
- I didn't realize it.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- You saw me a second ago.
- But...
- Anyway, now you know.
- Your body shrank...
along with your presence.
- Gosh.
- Yes, attack him.
- I mean...
- Do you know why I lost weight?
- Why?
- This is upsetting, you know.
- Why did you lose weight?
Because I wanted you
to see a new side of me.
(He says the most cringy line ever.)
- It makes me sick.
- Seriously?
(They all feel like vomiting.)
So Min likes it though.
Do you still not get it, So Min?
She's loving it.
- So Min?
- Why are you being a fool?
She fell for that line.
Can't you see that the song
was written for you?
Then why did you
turn me down back then?
Because you could've
turned me down,
and I didn't want to get hurt.
- What?
- What's going on?
If this is made into a web series,
about 20 people will watch it.
- Just us.
- Yes, just the people here.
- To make fun of them.
- Exactly.
I'm curious as to
what'll happen though.
- Are we at the location?
- I think we are.
- I think we're there.
- Where are we?
- Gosh.
- It's like a lodging.
- It's a lodging?
- This is nice.
- I see grass.
- Goodness, what's this place?
Grass?
- What will we be doing?
- It's going to be a hot day.
- Let's head inside.
- Let's go!
(Will they be able
to unlock the secret?)
Welcome to
the 2020 Reincarnation Camp.
(They safely arrive at
the Reincarnation Camp.)
We've been reincarnated!
Before we begin the camp activities,
we should hear the new songs
released by both artists.
- Right.
- Their new songs.
- "Summer Hate".
- By ZICO.
- I can't wait for the choreography.
- I'm excited.
I'm definitely taking part
in the challenge this time.
("Summer Hate" by ZICO)
- Nice.
- It's light and simple.
- Like this.
- Look at that.
- I love that move.
- He's adorable.
I love this.
- Nice one.
- It's so cute.
Whoever loses the game
of rock-paper-scissors...
I see.
We should all participate
in the dance challenge.
How nice.
(The fanning adds
to the fun vibe of the song.)
That was nice.
I liked this move especially.
It could be turned...
- into a dance challenge.
- Exactly.
- Many will do it.
- Kwang Soo, you looked good.
Nicely done.
(Flailing)
Nice.
That was great. Next up is SUNMI.
No way, it's SUNMI!
Her new song is...
- "Pporappippam".
- Ppam!
("Pporappippam" by SUNMI)
It has her unique flair to it.
(SUNMI's vibe fits
the hipster beat.)
- She seems so relaxed.
- Pporappippam!
I knew it.
(Even Kwang Soo
is swaying his hips.)
(The summer night song
makes you want to do body rolls.)
Let's try it.
- Pporappippam!
("Pporappippam" is perfect
for a dreamy summer night.)
Pporappippam!
- Pporappippam!
Aren't the two songs
going head to head?
- Yes, they're in a battle.
- The song is incredible.
Nice.
Next is Sae Ho.
You're a member of
the group ChoNam Zone,
and you recently released
a new song.
- A new song?
- Yes.
- It's been quite a while though.
- Let us hear it anyway.
"Why Are You Stupid?"
is the title of the song.
Are you sure it's not
"What's Wrong with Your Face?"
- No, it's not.
- Isn't it?
- It's not...
- "Droopy Face"?
No, that's not it either.
The moment you started to talk,
the five of them started attacking.
- We've been dying over here.
- We're closing in on him too.
- "Droopy Face".
- We needed to vent.
This may be
slightly inappropriate to ask,
but were you officially asked
to be on the show...
or did you come here
without being invited?
Who in their right mind...
would come here
without officially being asked?
- Because...
- Would I...
- You never know.
- You could've been passing by.
- Are you sure?
- I agreed on the payment too.
- Do you get paid to be here?
- What?
Why would I be here
if I'm not getting paid?
- How much were you offered?
- How much?
I'm afraid I can't say.
(He'd rather plead the Fifth.)
Then we'll respect your wishes.
- Okay.
- Let's move on.
- So, guys...
- Is that it?
- Hold on a second.
- Sae Ho wants a longer interview.
The first class of
the 2020 Reincarnation Camp...
is called
My Glorious Past Envelopes Me.
- What?
- You will compete in a quiz...
after being split up
into 4 teams of 3.
It's a quiz.
Each team will choose
two members to represent them.
While sitting on the chair,
they will press the button...
with their foot to get a chance
to answer the question.
With our foot?
The third teammate
will poke as many swords...
as the team would like to bet.
If the pirate stays in,
your bet will be placed.
- Okay.
- If the team answers correctly,
the bet you placed
will be converted into points.
- We played this before.
- If you get the question wrong...
or the pirate pops out,
points will be deducted,
and the chair
will flip over backward.
- Got it.
- Sounds difficult.
After the scores are tallied,
the top two teams
will be served a meal.
The remaining two teams...
will have to find food
that's been stashed away.
We must find them ourselves?
- Seriously?
- In this hot weather?
- It's hot outside.
- Food that's on the floor?
The four guests
will be the team captains.
- Really?
- Yes.
Please choose a color out of...
red, green, blue, and yellow.
Please choose one each.
I guess we've been split up fairly.
Here's the first question.
In 2008, on a variety show,
Suk Jin said that his wife
seemed like...
a character from this movie...
when she peeled fruit for him
10 minutes after an argument.
What's the name of this movie?
Of course, I know this.
I should've been in the chair.
I know the answer for sure.
I said it on "Happy Together".
- I don't remember.
- Don't you remember, Jae Suk?
I don't remember the title.
Can I give you a hint?
It's a foreign film.
(Team ZICO presses the button
as soon as they hear the hint.)
So Min, please place your bet.
I'll go with four.
- Four?
- Sounds reasonable, right?
- You're playing it too safe.
- It's only the first question.
(If the pirate stays and the answer
is correct, they win 4 points.)
(If the pirate pops out,
the other two will pay the price.)
- Have some faith in me.
- Please pop out.
- Trust me.
- Let it pop out.
You can trust me.
(She only has one left to stick in.)
- I think she did it.
- Okay!
- Okay, good.
- See?
ZICO and Kwang Soo,
what's the answer?
- Dr. Hannibal Lecter...
- in "The Silence of the Lambs".
(Is the answer Dr. Hannibal Lecter?)
Dr. Hannibal Lecter?
- What a relief.
- I doubt it.
- The chairs...
- Will we be flipped over?
What...
(The wrong answer
has their chairs flip over.)
Nicely done. Nice.
(Those watching are satisfied.)
- My gosh.
- Nicely done.
Look how ugly Kwang Soo is.
- Look how ugly he is.
- Right?
You're super ugly.
I didn't expect that at all.
I thought it'd at least be slower.
Suk Jin, give them another hint.
It's a foreign film,
and the main character is female.
It has to be a famous movie.
- Yes?
- I know. I remember now.
- Place your bet.
- We bet five.
- Okay.
- It's game over now.
(Jae Suk was the host
of that variety show.)
Okay.
(Jae Suk was the host
of that variety show.)
- What...
- Are you kidding me?
(The pirate pops out
on the first try.)
What on earth are you doing?
- Wait!
- Was that the first one?
Can this actually happen?
Was that the first one?
(They lose a point
for failing to place their bet.)
- Nice!
- It was on my first try.
Here's the keyword.
A remote house.
- Yes, I know.
- Go for it.
- We were first.
- Sure.
- Five.
- I'm not sure if I can do it.
- Just do it.
- Okay, five.
(Please don't fail this time.)
- Please.
- Let the pirate pop out.
- It's the last one.
- Haha, please.
- Pirate, please pop out.
- Let it pop out.
- He's on the last one.
- Jae Suk knows the answer.
Please...
- Seriously?
- Nice!
- Are you kidding me?
- Is this a joke?
- You only had one left.
You had so many slots
to choose from.
Are you kidding me?
What...
This is insane.
Place a smaller bet then.
- Okay.
- Good.
- All right.
- Go with five.
- 5.
- We'll bet 5.
- It should be at least five.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Nice!
- What's the answer?
- Let us answer.
In 1, 2, 3.
- "Misery".
(If the answer is correct,
they'll win 5 points.)
It's correct!
- Okay.
- Nice.
("Misery" was the movie
his wife reminded him of.)
I knew it before
you gave us the hint.
- "Misery".
- Of course.
Right, the remote house.
Here's the next question.
In 2006, at the age of 28,
Haha said that...
he'd want nothing more
than for this...
- to be written on his tombstone.
- It's too difficult.
What did he want as his epitaph?
- This is too difficult.
- An epitaph at 28?
- An epitaph?
What did you say?
- In 2006?
- Is it a famous saying?
- Or...
- He partly used a famous saying.
- I guess...
- Right.
- he tried to copy something.
- Back then...
Also, it includes "Ha Dong Hoon".
It's already annoying.
(I don't know what it is,
but it's annoying.)
Is my name annoying?
That's not what I mean.
The epitaph...
(Team Do Hyun gives it a go.)
- "The versatile entertainer..."
- What's your answer?
- Okay.
- I don't remember it at all.
We bet 10.
(Team Do Hyun bets 10.)
- Are you sure, Do Hyun?
- Yes.
- It'll pop up.
- He wants to fail.
- Stick in hard.
- It'll pop up.
- That's enough.
- Stop.
- Okay, okay.
Do Hyun, stop now.
- Stop, you punk!
- Do Hyun, stop.
- Okay, okay.
- Seven.
That's enough. You can stop now.
- He's good.
- That's enough.
- You can stop.
- He won't stop until it pops up.
Eight.
(He really kept going
until it popped up.)
- Okay!
Eight.
(We told you to stop.)
Okay!
Good job!
Gosh, my hair is almost dry though.
Do you have any idea?
We all have negative points.
What is this?
(Team Do Hyun loses 8 points.)
Let's try it.
Let me answer. We bet five.
- Be confident.
- It's okay.
Make it pop up, ZICO.
It makes me so nervous
when they stick them in.
There are two left.
- There you go.
- I hope it'll pop up.
(He has to stick in just one more.)
- There you go.
- Okay!
(Team ZICO successfully bets 5.)
But it's a hard question.
It's hard.
"Here lies the versatile artist,
Ha Dong Hoon."
(Here lies the versatile artist,
Ha Dong Hoon.)
- That can't be it.
- That's wrong.
He can't have said, "artist",
back in 2006.
- Kwang Soo, think some more.
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
- You got ahead of yourself.
- Kwang Soo.
(They calmly wait for the penalty.)
(What?)
(Kwang Soo pours his water
into So Min's bowl.)
(Amazed)
- It was wrong.
- What happened?
He's a genius.
- He's a genius.
- It's not "versatile artist"?
- That's incredible.
- He's the worst.
It's not "the versatile artist,
Ha Dong Hoon"?
- Do you want to switch?
- What? No.
We should continue.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
That feels nice.
- Do you allow this?
- Why?
(She's soaking her feet.)
This feels really nice.
What's wrong?
- It'll go to her face anyway.
- Yes, it'll go to my face anyway.
This is nice.
(Kwang Soo suddenly starts
washing his face.)
(Culture shock)
- Gosh.
- No!
- He's the worst.
- The water is so dirty.
- Come on.
(He is ready for war.)
Let me do something funny too.
- We know the answer this time.
- What?
Yes, we know the answer.
Pop up!
- Please.
- We know the answer.
- Make it pop up, ZICO!
- We know it.
We'll get it right this time.
- ZICO, there are two left.
- We know it.
It's popping up.
There you go.
(This is a signal of war.)
(Sighing)
- I told you.
- I can't wait.
What are you going to do? Oh, no.
I can't wait.
- What are you going to do? Oh, no.
- The water is dirty.
Oh, no.
- She soaked her feet in it.
- Let's see it.
(They washed
their feet and face in it.)
Hold on.
(The two moths sense their fate.)
The chairs. Team Three.
- Let's not do it.
- 1, 2,
- Let's not...
- three.
Exactly.
(The negotiation breaks down.)
(They splash water on themselves.)
(It's a catastrophe.)
Gosh.
That's so funny.
(They're equally soaked now.)
- Let us try.
- It's our turn, right?
- Yes.
- We'll bet three.
It's our turn.
- Okay.
- I think they know the answer.
- "Here lies..."
- "actor and rapper Ha Dong Hoon."
It's correct, right?
(If it's correct,
they win 3 points.)
"Actor and rapper".
(Correct)
(Team Sae Ho gets
another question right.)
We got it right?
- Unbelievable.
- We got it right?
(They're surprised themselves.)
- I'm good at this.
- We got it right?
Reincarnation Camp. Here are
the results of the first mission.
- First place, Team Sae Ho.
- Okay!
- Second place, Team ZICO.
Third place, Team SUNMI.
Fourth place, Team Do Hyun.
- Team SUNMI, find cup noodles.
- I love cup noodles.
Team Do Hyun, find rice and kimchi.
Before we go, SUNMI has
something for you.
- What is it?
- I have bracelets for you.
- Please wear them.
- What is it?
There are bracelets?
They'll help you find the secret...
- of your reincarnations.
- Really?
It's so cute and tiny.
It's not product placement.
- It's not?
- No.
- It has a touch screen.
- It's not product placement.
- It's not?
- Is it family-friendly?
It's not product placement.
- It's not product placement.
- It is family-friendly.
SUNMI, please hand out
the photos you took earlier.
- Okay.
- Really?
- I'll hand out the photos.
- Can we keep them?
- Yes.
- Sae Ho.
(The photos are handed out.)
- Thank you.
- That's a good one.
Why are you giving them to us?
(Why do you give us photos
before eating?)
Is it a gift?
Teams in 3rd and 4th places,
please get going.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go eat.
- It looks delicious.
- Oh, my.
(Teams in 1st and 2nd place
get 3-layer lunchboxes.)
- It's still warm.
- It's tasty.
- I must have been hungry.
- Me too.
It's delicious.
It's nice to win.
(While they enjoy
their lunchboxes...)
- Ramyeon is the best on a hot day.
- I know.
Slurping the hot soup in the heat...
The temperatures will go up
to 36°C today.
- That's crazy.
- It calls for...
- some hot noodles.
- Cup noodles.
- What's this place?
- Is this it?
I guess so.
This is it.
- Here's the kimchi.
- We only get kimchi?
- Oh, there's rice too.
- We get rice and kimchi.
My goodness.
If only we had ramyeon too.
I found ramyeon!
Oh, there it is.
- We can just have this.
- Is this it?
I think so.
I was so shocked
when you turned out to be a spy.
- You were?
- Yes.
I bet we played a big part...
in you starting on that drama.
I agree.
- Are you surprised?
- No.
(The two members brag shamelessly.)
Will it be you and me next week?
What?
(They're attacked by
mysterious creatures.)
What?
(Startled)
(The Reincarnation Camp
is taken over...)
(by a swarm of zombies.)
(There are zombies everywhere.)
(Flustered)
- Hey, close the door.
- Close the door.
Close the door.
Gosh, I was so startled.
I almost got an upset stomach.
(They can't figure out
what's going on.)
Gosh.
What is this?
(What is going on here?)
What's going on? Who are they?
(Team SUNMI is
getting ready to eat.)
- Gosh!
(They're attacked by zombies too.)
(SUNMI freezes.)
(All of a sudden,
zombies appear everywhere.)
(What's going on
at the Reincarnation Camp?)
(Startled)
What?
What's going on?
What is that?
What's going on? What happened?
(Scared)
(Zombies appear everywhere
at the Reincarnation Camp.)
- Do you like...
- What happened?
(Team Sae Ho and Team ZICO
hear the siren too.)
Is that a siren?
(Why is the siren going off?)
- Ji Hyo, something arrived.
- Something arrived?
- News arrived.
- What is it?
(A video is sent to their phones.)
- It's a video.
Breaking news. A swarm of
zombies that can spread viruses...
appeared at the Running Man
Reincarnation Camp.
A swarm of zombies...
(Zombies Appear
at the Reincarnation Camp)
(A swarm of zombies)
- Gosh.
- Darn it.
Zombies appeared?
(Now?)
These zombies have excellent
intelligence and physical abilities.
Shockingly, they can spread
zombie viruses...
by ripping off humans' name tags.
Did the other guys
turn into zombies?
Really?
They're known to have
a keen sense of hearing and smell.
Due to their keen sense of smell,
you can keep them off
for 10 seconds...
by using hand sanitizers
and shouting, "Hurray!"
Make sure you have
enough hand sanitizers.
- They have a keen sense of smell.
- Our food...
(You can keep them off
by using hand sanitizers.)
- We need hand sanitizers.
An ambulance will arrive at 4 p.m...
for the survivors.
All survivors watching this...
are required to gather in the
seminar room of the safe zone.
(They're required to gather
in the seminar room.)
Until 4 p.m... It's 1:53 p.m. now.
All right.
Let's try to make a noise
over there.
- Let's throw a pack of wet wipes.
- Let's try this.
Shall we try throwing this?
Give it to me.
(Will the zombies react
to the noise?)
(It drops with a noise.)
Let's hurry. That way.
(The three escape
while the zombies are distracted.)
There are zombies everywhere.
- Gosh, why are there so many?
- What should we do?
(Zombies are all over the place.)
Guys, look.
- What is it? A hand sanitizer?
- It's a hand sanitizer.
Really?
(Hand sanitizers can keep off
the zombies for 10 seconds.)
(After throwing a rock
to distract the zombies,)
(Jae Suk tiptoes away.)
There are so many.
(They can't decide what to do
with the zombies standing so near.)
(He carefully walks toward
the safe zone.)
Is there something there, Ji Hyo?
- I found it.
- There's only one.
- Did you find it?
- There's one here.
- Gosh, I'm sweating.
- Is one enough?
(There's a zombie in every street.)
There's a zombie over there.
Gosh. Go away! Hey!
We found it.
- Hold on.
- Don't scream.
Don't scream.
How are we supposed to go?
(The zombies gathered
at Ji Hyo's screams.)
- Oh, no.
- The zombies can't run.
We almost got away.
(If you use hand sanitizer
and yell "Hurray",)
(the zombies can't approach you
for 10 seconds.)
Hurray. Hurray.
Hurray.
(They passed the zombies
thanks to the hand sanitizers.)
What?
- Hurray! Hurray!
- Hurry.
- Hurray!
- Let's get out of here!
- Don't come near me!
Hurray!
(The hand sanitizer
is only effective for 10 seconds.)
- Hurray!
- Come here!
SUNMI, come here. Ji Hyo!
Where are you going? Hey!
How can you just leave me here?
We lost Ji Hyo.
Let's ditch her for now.
(Se Chan, SUNMI, Ji Hyo)
(Se Chan and SUNMI head to the
safe zone after ditching Ji Hyo.)
- Hey.
- What?
This is not the time to be eating.
(Jae Suk barely gets to the Safe
Zone after escaping the zombies.)
- You're not a zombie, right?
- Hey.
- You're not a zombie?
- You're a zombie now, right?
You're not a zombie?
(Groaning)
He's not. If he's doing this,
he's not a zombie.
He's not.
He's not a zombie.
(He pretends to be a zombie...)
(and heads straight to the food.)
What kind of zombie eats bread?
What is he doing?
Why is he eating a sandwich?
Hey.
What kind of zombie eats bread?
How did you know
there were zombies?
- We saw it on the news.
- We were sent a video.
Do Hyun is here.
- What's going on?
- Why is he coming in like a zombie?
He's a zombie.
Look at his expression.
- Are you a zombie?
- What happened?
(Did something happen to Do Hyun
on his way here?)
They seem weird.
What's this box?
What's in this box?
Come here and take a look.
- Hold on.
- What is it?
Is there something there?
What is it?
There's something inside the box.
- What is it?
- They're eyes.
Did you say "eyes"?
What is that? What is it?
- What is that?
- What is it?
- There's a memo.
- There's something written on here.
(There's something written
on here.)
"How to use the Judgment Stand".
"Judgment Stand"?
"The zombies are divided into
low-class and high-class zombies."
"High-class zombies look
and act like normal humans,"
- "and low-class zombies don't."
- I told you.
- Is that so?
- I had no idea.
There must be high-class zombies
among us.
After voting to choose the most
suspicious person,
you can put them in the Judgment
Stand to find out who they are.
There's a caste system
among zombies?
If you find the Judgment Tickets
hidden around this place,
the Judgment Stand opens.
You have to write the name of
the most suspicious person...
on the zombie eyes and submit them.
"If the person in the Judgment Stand
is a high-class zombie,"
"they will be removed from
the safe zone immediately."
- It would be upsetting.
- "They'll be a low-class zombie."
- The zombie would be upset.
- See? I told you.
There must be a zombie among
these three people.
- One of them must be a zombie.
- You're right.
- If you're infected with the virus,
- Hey.
- your wristband will vibrate.
- I see.
(If you get infected with the zombie
virus, your wristband will vibrate.)
"If you take the vaccine within
10 minutes of getting infected,"
"you'll be cured."
"If you don't take the vaccine
in 10 minutes,"
"you'll become a high-class zombie."
(How you become a high-class zombie)
"Be aware that if a low-class zombie
rips your name tag off,"
"you will automatically become
a low-class zombie."
"Nobody is allowed to rip off name
tags except for low-class zombies."
Jae Suk and Haha are
high-class zombies,
so they are acting like us and not
ripping off our name tags, right?
That's why they came in here
and ate something.
Right.
Zombies can't come in here though.
They said high-class zombies
are the same as humans.
How did you...
- There's a zombie among us.
- They are the same as humans, so...
I know we seem suspicious
in this situation.
- Yes, since you came from outside.
- What is this monitor?
I think it's Jae Suk.
Gosh, ZICO. You're driving me crazy.
- Seriously.
- A rapper who acts.
I also think...
(What?)
- You need a ticket.
- It's there.
(He saw something on the monitor
and took out the cord quickly.)
He just took out the cord.
What is it?
- What is it?
- Why?
- Why did you do that?
- Why did he unplug it?
- What is it?
- Why did you do that?
- Why'd you unplug it? What is it?
- Hey.
- Why'd you unplug it?
- What are you up to now?
- Was there was something on here?
- Why did you take it out?
Are you a zombie?
You're a zombie, aren't you?
It's not because I'm a zombie.
- Then why did you take it out?
- Why did you unplug it?
It said that there are 10 humans.
(It said that there are 10 humans.)
That's what was on the monitor.
(12 people came to the Reincarnation
Camp, but only 10 are humans.)
It says "10 humans" on the monitor.
(12 people came to the Reincarnation
Camp, but only 10 are humans.)
(That means 2 of them are zombies.)
That means that since
there are 11 of us,
there's a high-class zombie
among us.
Why did you unplug it?
Why did you unplug it? Tell us.
First...
- Come over here.
- It could be a clue.
Don't say "first".
Tell us why you unplugged it.
Everyone was standing here,
and I saw him.
- No, it's not that.
- Get over here.
I wanted to think first.
- Guys.
What is it?
There's a swarm of zombies outside.
- Are there really zombies?
- There are a lot of them.
- There are 10 humans among us.
- SUNMI,
- There are two zombies among us.
- did you find the hand sanitizers?
- We found them.
- We have to find them?
Kwang Soo is suspicious,
so he should go look for tickets.
- I have no reason to leave.
- I received something.
I'm telling you.
(I received something.)
- You're a zombie.
- You got infected.
- He's a zombie. What is this?
- Is he a zombie?
- Why is your wristband ringing?
- What's going on?
(They said you'd get a signal on
your wristband if you got infected.)
What's going on?
- What?
- Is it Ji Hyo?
Are you sure it's not a call
telling you that you're infected?
- That's right.
- He got infected.
Both of them.
- I didn't get a call.
- They said...
we'd get a signal on our wristband
if we got infected.
- I didn't get a signal.
- You must be infected.
- That must be it.
- Have you become a zombie?
- Everyone.
- Yes?
This is a reincarnation special
as well as a zombie special.
It's about zombies.
You saw the Judgment Stand, right?
- There are two types of zombies.
- Right.
If you don't take a vaccine within
10 minutes of getting infected,
- you'll become a zombie.
- Go take the vaccine.
Go look for the vaccine.
If you don't take it in 10 minutes,
you'll get infected.
- What? The vaccine?
- The vaccine.
Go look for the vaccine.
By myself?
Can you come with me, Sae Ho?
- Why would I?
- You're a zombie.
- You're already a zombie.
- Come with me.
- You're a zombie.
- Why would I go with you?
- I'm asking because I'm scared.
Go with Kwang Soo.
- I shouldn't go with him.
- Since Kwang So is a zombie,
- No.
- go with him.
- Let's go together.
- I don't want...
- Kwang Soo knows the hint.
- Why would I go with you?
- You're a zombie.
- You could come with me.
Just start walking like a zombie
in 10 minutes.
- Come with me!
- Go look for the vaccine!
- Ji Hyo's here! Go look for it.
- The zombie is here.
(Ji Hyo, whom Se Chan ditched,
arrives while they fight.)
- Another zombie is here.
- Hey.
- What?
- How can you ditch me like that?
- The situation is bad here.
- You guys are so mean.
Ji Hyo, I became a zombie.
- You?
- Yes.
They said he's a zombie.
- Why are you a zombie?
- He got infected.
I squeezed this out.
- I'm going to look for the vaccine.
- You need to take it now.
When did I get infected?
Did I get bitten?
I think I'm going to end up
becoming a zombie.
(He leaves
the safe zone by himself.)
(Outside the safe zone,
there are zombies everywhere.)
- The zombies...
- Gosh, that surprised me.
(That surprised me.)
There are so many outside.
- Really?
- You'll be eliminated...
if the zombies rip off
your name tag.
The zombies are different
from before.
- They're smarter.
- If we get our name tags...
ripped off by them, we're out.
- If they rip it off, we're out?
- Of course.
(You become a low-class zombie if
one of them rips your name tag off.)
Then you become a zombie.
- Hold on. Se Chan...
- If they rip off your name tag,
you become a low-class zombie.
They can hear us.
- Look at them.
- They can hear us.
They're sensitive
to sound and smells.
(They can't come into
the safe zone.)
(Banging)
Stop it. Don't goof off like that.
Stop fooling around!
(I'm scared,
so stop fooling around.)
(Zombie lover, Mr. Jee, is fearless
thanks to the safe zone.)
- My gosh, Suk Jin is...
- In movies, people like him...
Let's wait for our chance
and push him out.
It'll be like the movies,
and you'll be the first to die.
(Charge!)
- Hold on.
- Push him out.
- Haha. Don't push me out.
Push him out.
(They grab on to
the zombie lover...)
(and push him out
into the zombie den.)
- Let's do this.
- Push him out.
- Hey.
(The zombies approach one at a time
when they hear the sound.)
We pushed him out.
Oh, my.
No.
No!
- No!
- They got him!
(The person in a green hat, Mr. Jee,
is being chased by zombies.)
- Oh, my!
- They ripped his name tag off.
No.
No!
(He's the 1st person to get eaten,)
(and the 1st person
to be sacrificed.)
- They ripped his name tag off.
- It's over.
- Is that it?
- Oh, my gosh.
- It was right in front of our eyes.
(The end.)
- What is this?
- It's over.
- What's happening to Suk Jin?
- What are we going to do?
- Suk Jin!
- My gosh.
I had no idea it would be like this.
- My gosh, that was scary.
- This...
We did this to him.
- It's not that.
- But he kept fooling around.
He kept playing games with them.
- They just ended him.
- Hey.
- You guys...
- He's done for.
- They completely devoured him.
- You guys...
He kept goofing off.
- I'm done. What happens next?
- So...
My gosh, those punks.
(It's only been 10 minutes since
they started, but he's a zombie.)
Zombie. Big Nose. Zombie.
(You scared me.)
Zombie.
Zombie. I'm a zombie.
I'm Big Nose. I just got infected.
(He tells everyone that he got
infected in case they didn't know.)
My gosh. Zombie.
Everyone, the zombie amongst you
can infect you in any way.
- Really?
- You must look for the vaccine.
Can we find a vaccine in here?
There aren't any in here.
- Really?
- We have to go out?
We have to go out.
We can't go out right now.
- That zombie is the scariest.
- They can't come in.
That zombie is the scariest.
- He's afraid of that zombie.
- That zombie is the scariest.
I'm really scared.
If you give me hand sanitizer,
I'll make them stop.
- A zombie is...
- Okay.
If someone gives me hand sanitizer.
I get the hand sanitizer,
- put it on, and yell "hurray".
- Put it on and help Se Chan,
so he can come back here.
If you shout "hurray",
you can stop them for 10 seconds.
Find Se Chan first.
Don't shut the door.
We should.
We never know what will happen.
- Just in case.
- They can't come in anyway.
- Close it after I run away.
- Okay.
- Okay. We'll leave it open.
- Go.
(He barely took a step forward.)
Go find Se Chan.
(Screaming)
- My gosh that scared me.
- You surprised me.
- Hurry up.
- Come in!
- Come in.
Why are you locking the door?
Why are you locking it?
(Why did you lock the door?)
- I'm alive.
- How did you get in here?
- How did you come?
I'm alive.
How did you get in here?
- Where were you?
- I took the red potion.
- A red potion?
- Yes.
Hang on.
Can high-class zombies
come into the safe zone?
I heard it's a blue potion.
No, it's red.
I'm sure they said
the potion is blue.
- I heard it's blue.
- What I had was red.
What I heard was blue.
What I had was red.
(Se Chan says he took
the red vaccine. Is it true?)
You should go check it. It's red.
- Hang on.
- What?
What is it?
- What's that?
- Look at this.
- What is it?
- Se Chan is back.
(Jae Suk has some
mysterious file in his hands.)
(The list of Reincarnation Campers?)
I should take a look
around this place.
I can't waste time
looking at the zombies there.
(While they were preoccupied with
zombies, Jae Suk searched around.)
What is this?
The list of Reincarnation Campers?
(He found the list of campers.)
What is this?
- What's that thing?
- What is it?
Look.
(In the list...)
This is the list of
the Reincarnation Camp attendees.
There are Human Antibody
and Parent Zombie.
(There are Human Antibody
and Parent Zombie.)
(Human, Human Antibody,
Parent Zombie)
This is the list of
the Reincarnation Camp attendees.
There are Human Antibody
and Parent Zombie.
(Human Antibody and Parent Zombie?)
- Parent Zombie?
- There's Human Antibody?
Human Antibody...
literally has an antibody...
- Is it okay to get bitten?
- to Parent Zombie.
And this is
the condition of winning.
It's the condition
of winning for humans.
We should find out Parent Zombie...
- and eliminate it.
- We should get rid of it.
Three of us will get
in the ambulance...
that's coming at 4 p.m.
So three humans will get
in the ambulance.
And this is
what we should do to win.
(Condition 1, Human Antibody
must get in the ambulance.)
And Parent Zombie must
not be in the ambulance.
(Humans win.)
But...
Low-class zombies
can't get in the ambulance.
- Do we need to find Parent Zombie?
- Hang on.
- Calm down.
- Okay.
- I just asked one question.
- Don't get so excited.
If you keep doing this,
we all will die.
- Keep calm.
- Okay.
- In short...
- Only three of us will survive?
we just need to keep
Parent Zombie from the ambulance.
(Protect Human Antibody
and eliminate Parent Zombie.)
And Human Antibody is not safe.
If Parent Zombie...
can eliminate Human Antibody,
- Is it over like that?
- the race is over.
So we must stop that from happening.
Human Antibody shouldn't
reveal its identity.
Hang on. If Se Chan was infected,
it means someone has been...
- It means there's someone.
- with us the whole time.
Something was done.
SUNMI and Ji Hyo...
- are his team.
- They are my team.
(SUNMI and Ji Hyo were
in the same team with Se Chan.)
- Then we should...
- What about the bus?
I was sitting
next to Haha on the bus.
(Haha was sitting
next to Se Chan on the bus.)
I was sitting
next to Haha on the bus.
(Me?)
- It was Haha.
- Okay.
Were you sitting with Haha
on the bus?
Okay.
- Go ahead and pick me.
- There are two zombies...
I told you I'm human.
There's one.
- Don't regret your choice.
- We should go out.
We should go out and find
the ticket to Judgment Stand.
- I wasn't touching it.
- I guess you're right.
For now,
we should go out and get it.
(They start to search around
the place, walking stealthily.)
You're not Parent Zombie, are you?
I'm nothing. I'm serious.
Se Chan, come here.
You were infected. It means...
- there's something on your body...
- Is it checked?
or your name tag.
So the zombie did something...
- to infect you.
- Exactly.
What's the picture you got?
- Is that it?
- SUNMI took this picture.
SUNMI took this too.
She took this picture.
And there was something
strange about Haha.
I was sitting here.
But he told me to sit here instead.
- Really?
- He kept saying that.
That's not what Haha usually says.
Haha is being strange.
There's Haha in the picture, right?
- Haha is strange.
- We should find Haha.
- Haha is in all the pictures.
- Wait.
Hang on. Jong Kook,
we should check other pictures too.
All the pictures have Haha in them.
- His back and everything.
- Really?
Once we find the Judgment Stand,
we should put him on the stand.
That's what I'm thinking about.
(The members go out
and look for the Judgment Ticket.)
What is this?
Hey, it says Vaccine Room.
(Vaccine Room)
(If you complete the mission
in the room, you get 1 vaccine.)
- What do you mean?
- Hey, let's go in there.
(Safe Zone, Vaccine Room)
Hey, let's go in there.
(They carefully open the door
of Vaccine Room.)
- Look. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, and 7.
- You shouldn't make a sound.
Low-class zombies
might come running.
We should go get the vaccine.
We shouldn't step
on the broken board.
It's a mission.
- Hang on.
- There are zombies.
The potion is blue.
(The potion is blue?)
(Se Chan said he just
took the vaccine.)
(And he said the potion was red.)
The potion is blue.
You're being really strange.
- What's going on?
- My gosh.
- I'm sure he's lying.
- I think so.
I'm sure it was a lie.
Let's go, Mr. High-class Zombie.
(Meanwhile, Kwang Soo is looking
for the Judgment Ticket.)
(He walks carefully
holding his breath.)
(Flinching)
(Right at the moment!)
(Kwang Soo found something
between two trees.)
"If you insert the ticket, you can
reveal one person's identity."
(He got the Judgment Ticket.)
(With this ticket, he can
figure out one person's identity.)
(He rushes to the safe zone
that has the Judgment Stand.)
Was that the Judgment Stand?
(He rushes to the safe zone
that has the Judgment Stand.)
"If you insert the ticket, you can
reveal one person's identity."
(He inserts the ticket.)
(Number of humans, 8)
(There are 8 humans?)
Suk Jin is out.
(There were 10 humans before.)
One more human is infected.
(Who's the additional zombie?)
(High-class zombie)
The Judgment Stand is open.
Attendees of the Reincarnation Camp,
please gather around.
You were here.
- I found a ticket.
- It was you.
I found a ticket and inserted it.
- Did you find the ticket?
- I did.
- What? 8 humans?
- There are only 8 humans.
- You want to hide your identity.
- I know. He has changed.
- He's changed.
- Because...
One of them is Suk Jin.
- And...
- And there's one more.
- He became a high-class zombie.
- Okay. It's done.
- Did you find the ticket?
- I found it.
- He found the ticket...
- Okay.
- and the zombie.
- I found the zombie too.
The potion is blue.
Let's begin the first judgment.
What if I'm picked here?
If you're picked
and turn out to be human,
the ticket becomes invalid.
There aren't many tickets.
We should use this ticket carefully.
(If they pick Parent Zombie,
humans win the race.)
- I'm sure it's him.
- Write it down.
- Se Chan is obviously a zombie.
- Write down Se Chan's name.
- Can I write a name I want?
- Just write Se Chan's name.
I witnessed it first hand.
I saw it.
The result is in.
Out of 11 votes,
Se Chan got nine votes.
Please get in there.
I knew it. I'm sure it's Se Chan.
(Se Chan is the one
to go in the Judgment Stand.)
- Okay.
- He said he had a red potion.
If Se Chan turns out to be human,
this ticket will be invalid.
What if he's a zombie?
If he's a zombie, he will
turn into a low-class zombie.
And he will be dragged out.
I said I had the red potion.
It should've been a blue potion.
- There's a room with a red potion.
- What?
There's a room with a red potion.
Please show us Se Chan's identity.
(If what he says is true,
he must've been cured.)
1, 2...
(Se Chan got the most votes.
What's his identity?)
Three.
He's a zombie.
(Zombie!)
- He's a zombie.
- Look at him.
(Se Chan was a high-class zombie.)
I need the vaccine.
(After Se Chan got infected, he ran
around looking for the vaccine.)
I'm infected.
(He failed to find
the vaccine in 10 minutes.)
(And he became a high-class zombie.)
Is it a bad one?
I knew it.
Can we continue now?
- You zombie.
- My gosh.
- What happens to Se Chan now?
- He's a low-class zombie.
He said there's a room
with red potion.
He's become a low-class zombie.
- Am I leaving just like this?
- He'll stay with Suk Jin.
I can get out of here
and walk myself.
- No.
- He's a low-class zombie now.
Are they dragging me like this?
He's a low-class zombie.
If he gets caught, does he
become a low-class zombie?
So there's a high-class zombie...
- in here.
- There's one left.
And the high-class zombie
will do something to us.
We should be careful.
Now I want you to go out
to find the next ticket and vaccine.
- Vaccine?
- Let's go together.
We should go out again.
- I don't want to go out.
- What? There's no zombie out there.
(While there was no one around,
the zombies disappeared.)
I think we can go out.
- Now...
- Suk Jin.
I'm sorry.
(Suk Jin who lost
his name tag to the zombies...)
(has become the low-class zombie.)
(This is what a comedian with
29 years of experience has got.)
Big Nose.
(He runs into his friend
for the first time.)
Nice to meet you.
Isn't he Suk Jin?
(Big Nose Zombie is showing
his enthusiastic performance.)
Me.
Why do you keep wearing
makeup since last week?
(His face looks good
with the zombie makeup.)
- I'm a low-class zombie.
- Zombie?
(Dumbfounded)
(Haha is looking
for the Judgment Ticket.)
(What is this place?)
(The container is full of zombies.)
(Is there a Judgment Ticket
in this place?)
(My goodness.)
(He opens the door carefully.)
(Clattering)
(The zombies respond
to the sound immediately.)
(They walk slowly toward the sound.)
(The zombies go into the room
following the sound.)
(When the zombies are in the room,)
(he closes the door right away.)
(Rattling)
(Let us out!)
(Haha blocks the door
with desperation.)
(Meanwhile, the zombies calm down.)
(He used his quick wits
to avert a crisis.)
(Is there something in here?)
(When Haha finds something,)
(the zombies start
swarming the place again.)
(Startled)
(My goodness.)
What is it?
What is this place?
(What is this place?)
(What is the purpose of this place?)
(While Kwang Soo is scared,)
(Haha enters a mysterious room.)
(What is this room?)
(Vaccine Room)
(You succeed
if you retrieve the vaccine...)
(without sounding the bells.)
(So that the zombies
won't swarm in,)
(avoid sounding the bells...)
(and retrieve the vaccine.)
Okay. There is the blue potion.
(How do I get through this?)
That jerk! How dare he rip off...
my name tag?
(Haha moves past the lasers
carefully.)
(He keeps his movements minimal
to avoid making a sound.)
(The vaccine
is right in front of him!)
(Ringing)
(Haha touched the bell
right in front of the vaccine.)
My name tag.
Big Nose.
(The zombies swarm like crazy.)
(Groaning)
(No, I am almost there.)
Jeon So...
(His zombie performance
is cringeworthy.)
Jeon So Min.
(What is up with him?)
(Groaning)
Can't I go inside?
My goodness.
(He retrieves the vaccine
while Big Nose Zombie struggles.)
I don't need to take it now, right?
(Big Nose Zombie continues
to put on a performance,)
(but the reality hits him
when Kwang Soo takes out a camera.)
(Embarrassed)
(I want to be alone.)
(Let's take a photo together.)
Cheese.
(Laughing)
(Haha bursts out laughing
without thinking.)
(Big Nose Zombie awakens.)
(The zombies who were outside join.)
- Hurray!
- Okay!
(So Min quickly escapes
after using the hand sanitizer.)
Haha! Rip it off!
Rip it off! Rip it off!
(The zombies become mad
upon seeing the prey.)
Rip it off!
(The zombies surround Haha.)
Rip it off! Rip it off!
Hurray!
(The zombies pause
due to the hand sanitizer.)
(Haha escapes with the vaccine.)
(Thank goodness.)
(ZICO is looking
for the Judgment Ticket.)
(He finds something.)
What is this?
(He found the UV flashlight!)
(What is this flashlight for?)
What is this?
It's hot.
(Meanwhile, Se Chan Zombie
got his makeup done.)
Stay in the shade.
Stay in the shade. It's hot.
The zombies up there have it easy.
They have it easy
due to the air conditioner.
(The cool working environment)
It's cool there.
(Kwang Soo and Ji Hyo
run into each other.)
- Did you find a hint?
- No.
- I don't get what's going on.
- We need to find a hint.
I don't get what's going on.
(Laughing)
- You are tired, right?
- Yes.
Wake up! What are you doing?
- Wake up!
- But...
- I will try.
- When did you go to bed last night?
- I went to bed in the morning.
- For goodness' sake. Drink coffee.
- All right.
- You will be a zombie at this rate.
All right. I haven't become one.
If you don't wake up,
you will have to wear makeup...
and walk around
without a moment of rest.
- Get ahold of yourself.
- Okay. Okay.
SUNMI, did you find something?
- No, I didn't. But there is...
- Are you a zombie?
a setup like "Mission: Impossible".
Why are you so down?
What's the problem? Say something
(He is 5 seconds from passing out
due to the heat.)
A fling?
(This zombie is nosy.)
- A fling?
- No.
- Love.
- A fling?
- No fling. Love.
- A crush.
A crush.
- Gosh, we will burn to death.
- What?
(These two zombies are exhausted
due to the heat.)
Zombies like shades too.
(Kwang Soo and Sae Ho
are searching diligently.)
I think there was something here.
What?
(A glass bottle?)
(A mysterious note
is inside the glass bottle!)
(While Kwang Soo is looking away,)
(he takes out the note...)
(and leaves the glass bottle.)
- What are you doing?
- There is a glass bottle.
- What?
- A glass bottle.
- What is it?
- A glass bottle. It was here.
It has the R sticker.
(What is this in his back pocket?)
Hold on.
What is it?
Sae Ho, we came
all the way here together.
- Hold on.
- Don't be like that.
- What is it?
- All right.
We can't show Jae Suk.
Let's take a look by ourselves.
- What is it?
- There he comes.
I will show you. I mean it.
Stay with me, okay?
Pretend not to know anything.
We can't show Jae Suk.
- I will show you.
- You guys, come here.
- What did you find?
- It was here.
There is nothing inside.
- Let's see.
- It looks like this.
(He shows Jae Suk
the empty glass bottle.)
- I bet someone ate what's inside.
- That must be the case.
I bet someone took what's inside.
Maybe it was a potion.
I don't know.
(Sae Ho leaves
because he is nervous.)
Maybe someone took a potion.
Sae Ho put something
in his back pocket.
He told me he will show me
if I don't say anything to you.
What are you talking about?
- He put it in his back pocket.
- Let's see.
Why do I need to share it?
Are you going to be that way?
We need to survive this together.
Are you human or not?
- I am human.
- You are human.
Jae Suk, he keeps farting
as he passes the zombies.
- He actually farts.
- What?
- Are you going to be that way?
- Should I fart right now?
- I can fart right now.
- Do it.
- Is it okay if I fart?
- Listen.
I can fart right now.
- I can fart right now.
- He keeps doing that.
(He gathers his energy
and passes gas.)
- Are you crazy?
- It's ridiculous.
I told you that I can fart.
- Are you crazy?
- It's ridiculous.
You should go to the restroom
and check.
Judging from the sound...
- I am 100 percent sure.
- No.
Hold on. So Min is coming.
Let's hurry up and take a look.
(So Min smells something
and approaches them.)
(What does it say?)
(Instructions on the Photo Room)
(If you insert a Polaroid,)
(you can check how many zombies
are in the photo.)
The guide, SUNMI, can take photos.
(SUNMI had a Polaroid camera.)
(She took photos on the bus.)
(She continued to take photos
upon arrival.)
If we insert a Polaroid,
we can see how many zombies
are in the photo.
- Where are the photos?
- Sae Ho.
- At the cafe...
- The photos...
- I don't have any photos.
- I know where they are!
Earlier, I saw... I am not joking.
There is a photo studio.
- I saw it.
- I saw it too. I know where it is.
It was closed.
What is this place?
(10 minutes ago)
(Jae Suk found the Photo Room
in a secluded place!)
In and out?
What is this?
What does that mean?
(Inserting a photo helps you discern
who the zombies are.)
Let's go.
(The four of them head
to the Photo Room.)
(She finds a mysterious tablet PC!)
(She carefully opens it.)
I found something.
(With a scream,)
My goodness.
(SUNMI becomes a low-class zombie!)
I will insert it first.
Will you see how it works? Okay.
(Jae Suk inserts the photo he had.)
Does he have to see the result
by himself?
How many zombies are there?
- I think he can see it with us.
- I couldn't find it.
I need to find the ticket to know.
(How many zombies are
in the group photo of 12 people?)
He said something else.
- It's out.
- No way.
- What is it?
- Jae Suk.
(There are 6 zombies.)
- There are 6 zombies.
- 6 zombies?
- What are we going to do?
- Really?
- How...
- Look at this.
There are six zombies.
- Then...
- So many of us are zombies.
- There are six zombies.
- This is insane.
That means
there are six people left.
This is insane.
- Why are there so many zombies?
- I guess...
more people got infected.
Did more people get infected?
I guess Parent Zombie got to work.
- Se Chan,
- There are six zombies in here.
- Suk Jin...
and Se Chan.
Then there are four more zombies.
There is 1 Parent Zombie,
so 3 people got infected.
There is everyone
in the photo, right?
Do Hyun, insert your photo.
Insert your photo.
- Insert your photo.
- My goodness.
Those who became zombies...
could pretend to be not infected.
- That's right.
- This is insane.
(There are 9 people in the photo.)
I was expectant.
Did I tell you about it?
- Many people are in the photo.
- Is the result out?
Is the result out?
Did you get the number?
- 5 zombies.
- 5 zombies?
(There are 5 zombies in the photo!)
- Hold on.
- Who aren't in this photo?
- Let's see.
- Five zombies?
Let's check.
(The number of zombies: 5)
Put an X.
- Name those who aren't in here.
- Those who aren't in here.
I am not in the photo.
- I am not in the photo.
- I am not in it either.
- Jae Suk isn't in it.
- I am not in it.
- You are in it.
- Am I in it?
You are in it.
- You are barely visible.
- How about ZICO?
- ZICO is in it.
- Se Chan isn't in it.
- And Do Hyun is in there.
Se Chan isn't in it.
Se Chan is a zombie.
- Hold on.
- If there are five zombies,
those who aren't in the photo
are human.
- That's right.
- What?
Those who aren't in the photo
are human.
Kwang Soo, you are human.
- It's 100 percent.
- Se Chan isn't in this photo.
If we include Se Chan,
we get six zombies.
- You aren't in this photo.
- No.
If we think about it...
Kwang Soo isn't a zombie.
I am not a zombie.
(If you exclude Se Chan
who is a zombie,)
(Kwang Soo and Sae Ho are human.)
This is bad.
(The zombies are multiplying fast.)
The Judgment Stand is open.
Attendees of Reincarnation Camp,
please gather around.
5 out of 8 people.
I checked another photo.
Really? Let's see.
- But...
- The number is three.
It's a photo of 6 people,
but there are only 3 zombies.
(There are only 3 zombies!)
(Among the 6 in the photo)
There are Se Chan...
- and Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin.
(Exclude Se Chan and Suk Jin
as they became zombies.)
- I am human.
- Kwang Soo.
- No way.
- Then Jae Suk...
(Exclude Kwang Soo
since he was proved to be human.)
There is a zombie
among Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and Haha.
among those three.
- I am human.
- Kwang Soo.
- No way.
- Then Jae Suk...
- There is a zombie among them.
- It's Jae Suk!
- I am not a zombie.
- Jae Suk and Haha...
- Jae Suk.
- I told you earlier...
that I am not a zombie.
Haha and Jong Kook are suspicious.
Haha and Jong Kook.
I guess Jae Suk isn't a zombie.
Let's have a vote.
- You could be someone special.
- There are six humans.
There are six humans.
Where is SUNMI?
SUNMI got infected.
- She got infected.
- What?
- SUNMI got infected.
- Jae Suk, she is walking around...
- in the zombie makeup.
- She got infected.
- SUNMI did?
- Yes.
- When did that happen?
- She got infected.
SUNMI got infected.
- Really?
- SUNMI got infected.
- Whom should we vote for?
- Jae Suk.
Here is what I think.
Pick one
among Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and me.
- Okay.
- But I am not a zombie.
Should I vote for Haha?
(There is 1 zombie among
Jae Suk, Jong Kook, and Haha.)
I honestly don't know
whom to vote for.
- Me neither.
- I don't have a clue.
We need to vote for someone
who has to be a zombie...
and take him out.
I really don't know.
(Among the three of them,
who could be the zombie?)
The result is out.
A member received five votes.
(A member received 5 votes.)
Jong Kook, please enter.
- Is it me?
- Jong Kook,
(Jong Kook received
5 out of 9 votes.)
You received a lot of votes.
Jong Kook...
(Jong Kook went around by himself
away from the members.)
(Did Jong Kook roam the place
as if it's an amusement park...)
(because he is a zombie?)
Jong Kook.
(Could either Jae Suk or Haha
be a zombie?)
If Jong Kook isn't a zombie...
If Jong Kook isn't a zombie,
we can narrow down the candidates.
(If Jong Kook isn't a zombie,
we can narrow down the candidates.)
Let's check.
Please.
Jong Kook is...
(Jong Kook is...)
1, 2, 3.
(Is Jong Kook a zombie or human?)
Three.
(Jong Kook is a high-class zombie!)
We did it!
- We almost made a big mistake.
- All right.
(They can't believe
Jong Kook was a zombie.)
(We almost made a big mistake.)
We almost made a big mistake.
It's no wonder he kept saying
he didn't get the blue potion.
A high-class zombie.
He kept saying
he didn't get the blue potion.
(Jong Kook was looking for a hint.)
No way. No way.
(The band let him know
that he became infected.)
Oh, no. I became infected.
(Take the vaccine in 10 minutes
or become a high-class zombie.)
(In the end,
he failed to get the vaccine.)
(That way, Jong Kook became
a high-class zombie.)
I told you I am not a zombie.
- I am human.
- He became a low-class zombie.
- Jong Kook.
- That's bad news.
All right. Neither Haha...
- nor Jae Suk is a zombie.
- Neither one of them is a zombie.
- No.
- How do you know?
- Neither one of them is a zombie.
There were three zombies
in Do Hyun's photo.
- Suk Jin, Se Chan, Jong Kook.
- You are right!
- He isn't a zombie.
- Right?
- Haha and Jae Suk are human.
- All right.
- Let's go.
- You are right.
(ZICO is thinking hard.)
Jae Suk, can you show me...
the photo?
(He shines the UV flashlight
on the photo.)
Let me see it.
- Jae Suk.
- Hey.
- There are words.
- What?
- What does it say?
- Look.
Thank goodness.
(They shine the UV flashlight.)
There we go. What does it say?
(They find words that were invisible
to the naked eye.)
(Instructions on the Photo Room)
(The number of Human Antibody
and Parent Zombie...)
(are written with a UV pen and
can be seen with a UV flashlight.)
- What does it say?
- Two.
The number of special beings, two.
- That's number two, right?
- Are there words?
I think it's number two.
(The number of special beings: 2)
- The number of special beings, 0.
- 0.
(The number of special beings: 0)
The special beings are
Parent Zombie and...
They could also be Human Antibody.
Then...
Let's find the ones who overlap.
There are no special beings
in this photo.
We can exclude the ones
Let's exclude them.
(Zombie)
The remaining ones are
Ji Hyo, ZICO, So Min...
(The special being candidates are
Ji Hyo, ZICO, So Min, and Do Hyun!)
(Human Antibody and Parent Zombie
are among them.)
(Suk Jin, Se Chan, SUNMI, and
Jong Kook are low-class zombies.)
(1 Parent Zombie and
1 high-class zombie are unknown.)
The ambulance
will arrive in 30 minutes.
(The ambulance
will arrive in 30 minutes.)
(Jong Kook runs
to the makeup station.)
Hey!
(Jong Kook meets up
with Parent Zombie...)
(and hands something over.)
(Parent Zombie brings it back
to the container.)
(Hidden from the others' eyes,)
(Parent Zombie enters
the secret place.)
(But...)
(what is this place?)
(There are 12 boxes
inside the room!)
(Each box has a member's name tag.)
(Parent Zombie can infect a member
by putting an object...)
(he or she touched in a box
in the Infection Room.)
(The object Jong Kook
handed over...)
(goes into Kwang Soo's box.)
- So Kwang Soo is definitely human.
- He is definitely human.
(Kwang Soo is infected.)
What?
What? Did you get infected?
(No way.)
Did you?
(Kwang Soo now needs to take
the vaccine in 10 minutes.)
Did you get infected?
(Haha distances himself right away.)
(The zombies hear the sound
and approach them.)
Why would you leave me?
(Jae Suk quickly leaves.)
There must be a way.
Give me the vaccine.
Go to the Vaccine Room.
See if you can get it
at the Vaccine Room.
I will wait here and give it to you
if you fail.
- Where is it?
- It's right here.
It's right there.
Gosh, what did I do to get infected?
(Good luck, Kwang Soo.)
Here it is.
(Take the steps from 1 to 5.)
(You can retrieve the vaccine
if you pass without breaking them.)
(This is bad.)
Please. This is my last chance.
It's nearly done.
(He passes the 1st step.)
(He moves his foot to the 2nd step.)
(Breaking)
(The dream of vaccine shatters
like the step beneath him.)
(Pounding)
(The zombies heard the sound
and came.)
(This is a disaster.)
You failed.
Come on out.
(Ji Hyo walks around
without making a sound.)
(Hurray.)
What is this?
(She finds something.)
(She finds the vaccine
that was hidden.)
It's a potion.
(She retrieves the vaccine.)
How do you know if you are infected?
(What is Ji Hyo's identity?)
I am not Parent Zombie.
- I really am not.
- I know you are.
I know you are.
- What if I'm Human Antibody?
- Forget it. You're Parent Zombie.
(Could So Min be
Human Antibody?)
(For the humans to win,
Human Antibody has to survive.)
(So Min has been quiet.
Is she really Human Antibody?)
- What if I'm Human Antibody?
- Forget it. You're Parent Zombie.
Jae Suk.
What if I'm Human Antibody?
- I'm Human Antibody.
- What?
- You are?
(So Min tries to convince Sae Ho
that she is Human Antibody.)
Then should I help So Min?
You're Human Antibody?
(Do you mean it?)
Did the staff give you something
before we began?
You can't ask that.
- I'll be honest.
- I can't?
To tell you the truth,
I came 30 minutes early.
I was told to come by 9 a.m.
You guys came at 9:30 a.m., right?
I came at 9 a.m.
What does that have to do with this?
You can't say that.
You'll hurt her feelings.
Then what should I say?
I don't have much experience.
(Right then,
Do Hyun and ZICO join them.)
- You know...
- What is it?
(ZICO approaches Sae Ho
out of nowhere.)
Anyway, I'm not Parent Zombie.
(Knowing ZICO's intention,
So Min disappears.)
Okay. I'm not Parent Zombie anyway.
- She's suspicious.
- She's the most suspicious.
- I know. She's acting strange.
- She's suspicious.
The thing is, there's no reason
why she'd be so upset about this.
You don't watch our show
a lot, do you?
I usually get even more upset
than this.
I tell many petty lies,
but this is big.
I don't lie about these things.
- ZICO might be a zombie.
- Jae Suk.
Stay away from So Min.
Why me? Gosh, this is
driving me crazy.
Why do you always suspect me?
You guys always think it's me.
This is frustrating.
There she goes again.
Gosh, not again.
- I mean...
- Get up.
Don't be lying on the ground.
Get up.
- I know you're innocent, but...
- There she goes again.
Zombies are getting aggressive.
Be especially cautious.
What? What's that sound?
(I'd better be careful.)
(Do Hyun is one of the people
suspected to have a special role.)
(Before he even gets to
open his hand sanitizer,)
(a swarm of zombies
starts coming at him.)
(The zombies become
more and more aggressive.)
(In the end, Do Hyun gets caught.)
(Do Hyun's name tag is
ripped off by the zombies.)
(He turns into a low-class zombie.)
(The zombies are
filled with confidence.)
What are you doing?
Why are you ripping it off?
Hurray!
What's going on?
(Sae Ho turns into
a low-class zombie...)
(because he didn't use
a hand sanitizer.)
(Meanwhile, Haha is
surrounded by zombies.)
(He is the meanest zombie
around here.)
It's fine as long as the name tag
isn't ripped off, right?
(Jong Kook slaps Haha.)
I won't rip it off.
(The mean zombies try to make Haha
make a sound.)
(Haha makes a sound.)
(As soon as he makes a sound,
his name tag is ripped off.)
(After being teased the whole time,
Haha turns into a low-class zombie.)
This is our chance.
(Kwang Soo has become
a high-class zombie.)
Surround him.
Hey!
- Guys, let go of him.
- Hey!
Let go of him.
(The zombies follow
Se Chan's order right away.)
- What?
- I've been infected.
Guys, get him. Squeeze him.
(The high-class zombie, Kwang Soo,
turns into a low-class zombie.)
But I was infected...
It's almost over,
and I have to put on makeup?
Come here.
- Squeeze him.
- Who bit me for real?
Who bit me for real? Darn it.
I have four teeth marks.
Do you want one more?
- I'm infected too, right?
- Yes.
(Se Chan is punished.)
Guys, surround him!
I'm already a zombie! I'm a zombie!
I'm already a zombie!
(They welcome him into the gang.)
Leave him alone.
Guys, leave him alone.
(Kwang Soo kicks the zombies.)
- You mean zombies.
- Good job, guys.
- I'm already a zombie.
- Everyone, follow me.
(They all follow Se Chan.)
What is this?
- Are you their leader or something?
- I'm their leader.
Everyone, walk slowly.
Slowly.
(There are only 4 people left.)
(Only 10 minutes remain.)
(He has to hurry up and find
the Judgment Ticket.)
(He enters the zombie container
to find the last Judgment Ticket.)
(There are only 4 members left.)
(He walks all the way in,
but he finds nothing.)
(He finds a fake wall
at the end of the corridor.)
I found something.
What is this?
There's something here.
(He finds a mysterious door
and walks inside.)
(He finds...)
(the Infection Room.)
(This is where Parent Zombie
produces zombies.)
What is this?
(Why are there boxes
for all the members?)
This is a hand sanitizer.
(There's something in the box for
the high-class zombie, Jong Kook.)
(There are candies
in Se Chan's box.)
(There is a bottle cap
in Kwang Soo's box.)
Parent Zombie comes in here...
and puts things in the boxes
to turn the members into zombies.
(Now that he knows
how people get infected,)
(he has to guess
who Parent Zombie is.)
Ji Hyo has become a zombie.
So has ZICO.
(Ji Hyo's bottle cap
and ZICO's hand sanitizer are here.)
(Inside So Min's box...)
(A card?)
So Min is suspicious.
(The item in So Min's box
has nothing to do with the shoot.)
This can't be from So Min.
I'm not a zombie. I'm not.
(ZICO and So Min wait
for the ambulance in the safe zone.)
- Be honest. What are you?
- I'm human.
You can't be human.
The thing is...
I'm Human Antibody.
Busted.
You're busted.
You're busted. It was you.
Busted. You're busted!
You're Human Antibody,
not just human?
If you'd said you were human,
I would have believed.
But you said
you were Human Antibody.
I know who the real
Human Antibody is.
(This morning)
(Before the shoot,
the staff met with ZICO.)
(ZICO's identity)
(He got eliminated three times
by Jong Kook...)
(and became immune to fear.)
(He was reborn
as Human Antibody.)
- "Human Antibody"?
- Yes.
(Humans' fate depends on
Human Antibody ZICO.)
(Human Antibody ZICO
is safe from zombies.)
(Still, he kept using
hand sanitizers...)
(to pretend to be human.)
(ZICO has been tracking down
Parent Zombie...)
(without being suspected
by anyone.)
(So Min, you're busted.)
I mean... You think I'm a zombie?
- What?
- I'm not a zombie.
Are you saying I'm a zombie?
I'm suspecting you're Parent Zombie.
(So Min might be Parent Zombie.)
I'm not a zombie.
Anyway, I'm human.
- So how...
- No one knows if you're human.
How would I know? Only you know.
- Prove it to me.
- I know who is Human Antibody.
You even got hiccups.
- It's a habit.
- Really?
(So Min got caught telling a lie.)
(What is her identity?)
(Meanwhile, Ji Hyo and Jae Suk...)
Ji Hyo, what is that?
(What is that?)
- It's a vaccine.
- What?
I'd been infected with the zombie
virus, but I got a vaccine.
- Gosh, that startled me.
- You did?
Yes, I just did.
- You got a vaccine?
- I saw zombies.
Yes, I just did.
- This is it. It's blue.
- It's blue.
I'd been infected
with the zombie virus.
- You had?
- Yes.
There was a zombie right there,
so I just got a vaccine over there.
That's a relief.
(If Ji Hyo is telling the truth,
it means she is human.)
- You're not a zombie, are you?
- Seriously.
What's with you?
(The ambulance
arrives at 4 p.m. sharp.)
Oh, my. The ambulance is here.
(Only the last 3 survivors
can get in the ambulance.)
(The result is in the hands
of these four.)
ZICO, come here.
- Jae Suk.
- Now...
I survived.
(Groaning)
(Sae Ho is going too far.)
- Is this wrong?
- What's with you?
- What are you doing?
- It's not easy.
- That's a bit too much.
- I look like an ice witch.
When did you all turn into zombies?
Guys, the ambulance is here.
Three of you can
get in the ambulance.
If Parent Zombie gets in,
the zombies win.
If Human Antibody
and two humans get in,
the humans win.
I was in the room and...
Is Yoo Jae Suk human?
- What is he?
- Is Yoo Jae Suk human?
For some reason,
you feel very familiar.
- I'm not in the mood.
- He sounds creepy.
- You've been a zombie too long.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Even when he goes home,
- He's become a mummy.
he'll be like,
"Hyun Woo, Daddy's home."
- You're busted.
- After enjoying his lunch,
he turned into a zombie right away.
(Hyun Woo's dad, Suk Jin, was
a zombie 80 percent of the time.)
I know how we should decide.
(The last 4 survivors
have to make a decision.)
It's likely that Jae Suk and I
aren't zombies.
We can't let Parent Zombie
get on the ambulance.
We can let either one of them
get on,
- So I...
- but not Parent Zombie.
I went into that room,
and the way you make a zombie...
is...
Why are you listening so intently?
(Focused)
I'm sorry, but we're in the middle
of a shoot. Please step back.
- It must be because you're new.
- Please step back.
The zombie is listening
very intently.
You can't listen to everything
that humans say.
What was useless?
Do I need to step back?
I thought I had to continue acting.
- You thought you needed to act.
- I'm sorry about that.
ZICO, you transformed into a zombie.
I never did.
I never transformed into one.
- Really?
- Because I'm Human Antibody.
- That's strange.
- I'm Human Antibody.
- You're Human Antibody?
- I never transformed into a zombie.
I've never been bitten,
and I don't need the vaccine.
- Because I'm Human Antibody.
- But it's not from getting bitten.
- That's why ZICO never transformed.
- Yes.
- Come here.
- But it's not...
- It's not from getting bitten.
- I'm telling you.
That's why I was telling you that
we have to let one of them get on.
- Hold on. That's what you meant.
- But...
That's why I'm saying one of them
is Parent Zombie.
Yes. I'm Human Antibody.
(Looking around)
Let me tell you one more thing.
Are we just supposed to stand here
like this?
Are we not supposed to do anything
but stand here?
I'd rather be back there
with the other zombies.
At least let us act like zombies.
Let's act like we're burning
in front of this.
- Pardon? Why don't you show us?
- They can put in CGI.
- Go forward.
- Isn't it weird to just stand here?
If you do it first, we'll follow.
You shouldn't have anything.
Can you give me the photo
that the zombies took?
Don't give it to him.
- Don't give it to him.
- You're so obedient.
It's the first time
someone asked me for something.
It's on the basis that you believe
in what I'm saying.
- But...
- Do you want it or not?
Hold on. I don't need it.
Not right now.
You punk.
(His wish is fulfilled.)
- There's a barrier here.
- What was that?
- There's a barrier.
- What did you do just now?
(The veteran zombie gets air time
by making a non-existing situation.)
- There's a barrier.
- That was funny.
Okay, everyone.
(Final decision
on which 3 will get on)
Jae Suk, who has been confirmed as
human, will choose two people...
to get on the ambulance.
If fireworks go off over there,
then the humans win.
If carbon dioxide gas comes out,
the zombies win.
Did you really take it?
I really took it earlier.
Do you see this?
I sucked it out.
Jae Suk.
Do you see it?
(Ji Hyo's mouth proves...)
(that she took the vaccine.)
- You.
- It's red, right?
- Your tongue is blue. Let me see.
- Yes.
I took it.
Hey. You're human.
I told you I took it.
I was carrying it with me before.
Your tongue is blue.
A zombie can take it too.
I'm Human Antibody.
I'm not trying to defend myself.
- Are you really Human Antibody?
- I am.
(So Min lied that she was
Human Antibody and got caught.)
It's highly likely that we'll lose
if we take either one of them.
If I'm Parent Zombie,
there's no reason for me to take it.
It could be for show.
We just took it.
So Min's box had a card.
- I don't know what it is though.
- What are you?
I'll get on the ambulance with
Song Ji Hyo and ZICO.
(Ji Hyo, ZICO, and Jae Suk
will get on the ambulance.)
- Is this final?
- Yes, it is.
(If Ji Hyo is Parent Zombie,
all the zombies win.)
You'll leave
when you get in the car.
- Why aren't you taking me?
- You...
I'm confused between you two,
but Ji Hyo's tongue is blue.
- I was telling you the truth.
- Who is it?
Get in. Ji Hyo, get in.
- It's not ZICO.
- Ji Hyo, get in.
Ji Hyo, get in the car.
Let's get in.
- Get over here, So Min.
- So Min.
Shut the door on So Min.
(So Min, who claims to be
Human Antibody, couldn't get on,)
(and Ji Hyo, who claims
to be human, gets on.)
- If it wasn't for...
- This is driving me crazy.
If it wasn't for Ji Hyo's last
appeal, I would've been confused.
I wonder what was in it.
There were hand sanitizers
and such inside.
Yours was a bottle cap.
(The ambulance leaves.)
I wonder what the outcome is.
Let's go.
(The zombies already know who won.)
(If So Min is Parent Zombie,)
(the zombies lose.)
If there are fireworks, we survive.
If it's carbon dioxide gas, we lose.
(If Ji Hyo is Parent Zombie,
carbon dioxide gas will come out,)
(and the humans will lose.)
(What are the results?)
Nice.
(The humans lost.)
(Parent Zombie is in the ambulance,
so the zombies win.)
Penalty.
(It's carbon dioxide gas?)
(Smiling)
It's Song Ji Hyo.
(Frozen)
(Parent Zombie is...)
(Song Ji Hyo.)
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes?
Today, you are Parent Zombie,
who reincarnated with...
the zombie virus
from episode 277, Zombie Wars.
(Ji Hyo's identity
is Parent Zombie.)
(Ji Hyo was infected with the virus
in episode 277, Zombie Wars.)
(She then reincarnated
as Parent Zombie.)
And the other members
will reincarnate...
from the episodes
where they hurt you.
You will get a chance
to get revenge on them,
so please succeed.
(For example, in the episode that
Jong Kook reincarnated from,)
(Hades Jong Kook eliminated Poseidon
Ji Hyo in the shortest time.)
(In the episode Jae Suk
reincarnated from,)
(Jae Suk coldly pushed Ji Hyo away
when she said she wasn't it.)
(They are all episodes where Ji Hyo
was left with a grudge.)
(This is the special where Ji Hyo
gets revenge for her grudges.)
- It's time to meet your assistant.
- Okay.
You have to bite the one person
who has never been...
a zombie before and turn them
into a high-class zombie.
Let's go meet them.
(Bite that member and turn them
into a high-class zombie.)
(The member who will assist
the half-asleep Parent Zombie is...)
- So Min.
- Hi, Ji Hyo!
- Why are we the only ones here?
- What are we doing?
What's going on?
Is it true?
(Biting)
Why did you bite me?
(The 1st high-class zombie to help
Parent Zombie is Jeon So Min.)
What is this? What just happened?
Are you a zombie? You're a zombie?
Yes, I'm a zombie.
(This is how
their chemistry started.)
- I'm a zombie.
- You're a zombie?
- You're a zombie too, So Min.
- Ji Hyo.
Can you give me something else?
This one.
- This one?
- Yes.
(So Min wanted Se Chan's thing
as soon as they got on the bus.)
(Acting calm)
(Here, Ji Hyo.)
(These two don't walk
when they are nervous.)
(They quietly began to steal.)
(When the swarm
of zombies appeared,)
(Ji Hyo pretended to be abandoned.)
Zombie 31, thanks for your efforts.
I'll see you later.
I'm the leader.
Thanks for your hard work,
Zombie 28.
(She pretended to be abandoned
and went into the Infection Room.)
So this is where these were.
Yang Se Chan.
(She took the jelly candy
that So Min stole...)
Jelly.
(and put it in.)
Thanks, Se Chan.
(And So Min, who gambled and said
she was Human Antibody,)
(continued to steal and give Ji Hyo
infectious agents.)
I hid wet wipes in the grass on
the right side of the first tree...
- near the camera.
- Got it.
Look for it on the right
as you go up.
Okay.
The water bottle cap.
And another one.
There you go.
I brought a picture card of So Min.
(She prepared for suspicions by
putting something in So Min's box.)
(Then she put a bottle cap
in her box as an alibi.)
This will go in my box.
I'm done.
(To be completely undercover,
she even lied about her episode.)
(She cunningly made up
a new episode,)
- I found something.
- Did you?
(but in the tablet found by SUNMI,)
There are zombies.
(there was a video of the real
episode Ji Hyo reincarnated from.)
Ji Hyo.
Are you sure you didn't reincarnate
from this episode?
(SUNMI...)
(The low-class zombies
have arrived.)
(Ji Hyo's secret was revealed,)
I was right, wasn't I?
(so she had the low-class zombies
eliminate her.)
My gosh.
(It was Ji Hyo?)
It was you all along!
(She even took the vaccine
to perfect her act.)
She's Parent Zombie.
Why is it her?
- Song Ji Hyo.
- What?
- Louder!
- Song Ji Hyo.
- What?
- The era of zombies is here!
The zombies won because
Parent Zombie, Ji Hyo,
got on the ambulance.
And ZICO and Jae Suk,
who are on Team Human, lost.
(Jae Suk will get the penalty of
dressing up for a live broadcast.)
He will take the penalty
for his team.
How cool! He's so cool!
My goodness.
- Good job, everyone!
- Thank you!
Good job!
(10th anniversary live broadcast
with the viewers)
(The 7 members were invited to
CEO Big Nose's home.)
(CEO Big Nose, Ji Suk Jin)
(Butler, Yoo Jae Suk)
(Analyst, Kim Jong Kook,
Insurance salesman, Haha)
(Lawyer, Song Ji Hyo)
(Judge, Lee Kwang Soo)
(Detective, Yang Se Chan)
(Gambler, Jeon So Min)
(2 of them are mysterious thieves
who are after the CEO's gold.)
(In this place where everything gets
recorded for 50 seconds,)
(Even the smallest action
can become a hint.)
(If you fail,
your video will be revealed.)
I got it!
(It's the site for the trial
regarding the thieves' evidence,)
(and it's filled with suspicion
and deduction.)
(Also)
(At the final trial
which will be broadcasted live,)
(the viewers will catch
the mysterious thieves.)
(A special live broadcast joined
by the viewers will come to you.)
(The Provocation of Running Man)