Hello.
- Hello.
- The weather is very nice.
There's the life-sized
figure of So Min.
- Gosh, it's So Min.
- What is she doing here alone?
I know.
It's So Min.
So Min is smiling,
but she looks somewhat sad.
This is our 500th episode.
I know.
(Congratulations on the 500th
episode of Running Man.)
Congratulations.
It's the 500th episode.
I'd like to thank
our crew members...
and viewers for being with us
the whole time.
- Thank you.
Stop walking and run, Running Man.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
- This is our 100th episode!
- Yes!
Cha Bum Kun!
- Cha Bum Kun!
- Okay.
Congratulations.
Thank you so much.
It's me!
We did it.
It's the 500th episode.
It's the 500th episode already.
The president of SBS
sent us a coffee truck.
Mr. Park.
Thank you, Mr. Park.
Mr. Park Jung Hoon.
- Thank you.
Please stay healthy.
Are you making a deep bow?
- Your legs must hurt.
- Hey, stop it.
Mr. Park hates things like this.
- Really?
- Why would you try to flatter him?
I just wanted to thank him.
Jong Kook, why are you
holding her arm?
I should take care of So Min.
(Jong Kook, why are you
holding her arm?)
(I should take care of So Min.)
- What?
- I was surprised.
- You're so nice.
- Hey.
Why are you being like this?
She feels lonely.
It's the 500th episode,
but she couldn't make it.
When I talked to So Min
on the phone,
she wouldn't hang up.
- It happened to me too.
- We talked for 40 minutes.
Me too.
So Min asked
a straightforward question.
She asked me not to hang up.
- I was so tired.
- That's true.
I talked to her on the phone
for 30 minutes.
So Min is feeling bored now.
If you want to call So Min,
you have to brace yourself.
You should take some time out.
I know.
Like we just said,
this is our 500th episode.
But our society is
still being cautious,
and So Min is recovering her health,
so she can't join us today.
That's right.
So we prepared a simple but fun
episode instead of something huge.
- That's good.
- We should have fun.
For you guys who've
worked so hard for this show,
we prepared some healthy food
for spring that will boost immunity.
- Healthy food?
- That sounds nice.
Before you start eating,
let me introduce our five guests
with spring-like charms...
who are here to celebrate
the 500th episode.
Guests with refreshing charms.
Please bring in the board.
Let's get So Min away for now.
- Get rid of her.
- So Min.
- Go get some rest.
- See you.
Go take a rest.
- Stay with the director.
- Lie down.
- All right.
- On the board,
there are three questions
about food...
and the guests' answers.
I've picked one already.
- Who?
- Tripe and entrails.
(Guest 4 likes tripe and entrails.)
Did you pick one already?
I like tripe and entrails too.
We have five guests today.
- But there are seven numbers.
- Yes.
One of the numbers is mine,
and one of them belongs to
the writer over here.
- Do you mean Hyo Im?
- Yes.
We should avoid those two, right?
If you choose one of us,
you'll team up with...
- another Running Man member.
- I knew it.
Now, please choose a number.
(Which of the 5 members
will team up with the guests?)
Look at number one.
- Please let me choose number two.
- On a date, she wants to eat...
food made by her mom.
That means she wants to introduce
her boyfriend to her mom.
She wants her boyfriend
to meet her mom.
That can't be Bo Pil or Hyo Im.
- Right.
- Right?
Still, I think we'll get to
eat these dishes later.
So I choose number two.
- Let me choose a number too.
- I choose number two.
I choose number one.
- Number one?
- Ji Hyo, make up your mind.
I choose number six.
- I choose number 3.
- I choose number 4.
- "Tteokbokki".
- "Oysters".
- There's only one number left now.
- That's right.
But I hate every dish
under number seven.
I hate all of them,
whoever that person is.
It's the worst. What is that?
I hate all of them.
You have no choice.
Behind you,
you'll see tents
with a number on it.
Go into the tent with the number
you chose and bring your guest out.
- The guests are in there?
- Where are the tents?
Shall we go?
If the tent is empty, you'll team up
with a Running Man member.
- Which number was it?
- I wonder who it is.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
(Does tent number 2 have
a guest in it?)
Unbelievable.
(The red-haired guest is
covering her face with a pillow.)
She looks so stylish.
- Haha.
- Hey.
What are you doing here, Bomi?
(Yoon Bomi,
the stylish member of Apink)
Haha.
Hey.
Hello. Who are you?
(Suk Jin chose tent number 3.)
(Laughing awkwardly)
What happened?
(Park Chorong,
the pretty member of Apink)
Hi.
(Who wants to eat her mom's food?)
- Hello.
- Oh, my. Hi, Chungha.
Gosh, you surprised me.
- Hi, Chungha.
- Hello.
- How have you been?
- I've been good.
Come on out.
What were you doing here?
I've been waiting for you.
Is anyone here?
(Already three teams
have been decided.)
Someone's here.
Who...
- Hello.
- Oh, my.
(Choi Yoojung,
the rising star of Weki Meki)
- What are you doing here?
- Hello.
I didn't expect to see you here.
- How have you been?
- Come here.
What are you doing here?
- Have you been well?
- What were you doing here?
(There are 3 members
and only 1 guest left.)
We might end up
with another Running Man member.
(Which two members will team up
with each other?)
(She is the last guest.)
- Hello.
- Hi.
Mijoo, it's you.
- Hi, Mijoo.
- He knows my name.
(Tent number 7)
Gosh, I can't believe this.
Gosh, what is this?
(Good job choosing
the producer's taste.)
"Congratulations on guessing
the writer's taste"?
Why on earth would you want
those dishes?
My goodness.
Don't you hear
how happy the others sound?
Bo Pil!
Why on earth would you want tarts?
Se Chan!
- Hey!
- Ji Hyo!
It's Hyo Chan Park again.
- Come here.
- Hi. It's been a while.
(The unhappy Hyo Chan Park is back.)
- Come here.
- Oh, my.
Finally.
I'll make Chorong
the most searched person today.
(The happy 6 teams are decided.)
As this is our 500th episode,
we have very special guests today.
Let's give it up for them.
Yes!
- Let's talk to Mijoo first.
- Hi, Mijoo.
As you all probably know,
she is a very famous
idol group member.
- She's a good talker.
- You could put it that way.
- She's full of energy.
- She's frivolous.
You can say many things about her,
but some think she's crazy.
- I'm crazy.
- She's crazy.
She has way too much energy.
- I'm out of control.
- Especially on her way to work,
- her pictures attract attention.
- Her poses are special.
(Extremely unique)
She makes those poses?
- On her way to work?
- Yes.
- Look at this.
- I thought she was hugging a dog.
Something like this.
(She starts taking
unique poses right away.)
- Look at her.
- Something like this.
That's what she does?
Even if she's my partner,
if she goes too far,
- You can't stand it, right?
- I can't stand it.
- So...
- For example, Mijoo,
- Look at her face.
show us how you drop your bag.
Let's say my bag is sponsored.
- Then I want it to stand out.
- Right.
(Her bag is sponsored.)
(My bag is sponsored.)
The sponsor would love it.
(Mijoo is known for her photoshoots
on her way to work.)
- What's with her?
- Something like that.
- Why...
- Let's say your watch is sponsored.
- Oh, that's right.
- Your watch is sponsored.
(Her watch is sponsored.)
Hello.
(The pose vending machine is
on fire.)
Gosh, my eyes.
- This...
- Like this.
- She's actually good.
- Did you see that?
- She looks so natural.
- It looks so natural and smooth.
(Mijoo finishes up
with her outstanding poses.)
Next up is Weki Meki's...
- Choi Yoojung.
- Yes!
- Yoojung.
- Yes.
Compared to a couple of years ago,
you have a completely different
vibe now.
- I've grown a lot.
- Yes.
You've become a lot more mature.
I read that you're starting
a new drama.
- That's right.
- This is not the time...
to talk about that.
Then when is the right time?
When and to who
am I supposed to talk about it?
Have some class, seriously.
I can't believe him.
(Kwang Soo's unsophisticatedness
irritates everyone.)
Hold back.
Don't be so nosy.
You should be careful
with those questions.
I'm sorry.
(Kwang Soo apologizes
without understanding why.)
I shouldn't have said that.
- Yoojung.
- Yes?
I hear you're starting a new drama.
(What?)
That's right. It's a web drama.
- Nice!
- Well said!
- You're starting a drama?
There's a right time for everything.
- I said it at the wrong time?
- Of course.
- It was three seconds ago.
- It wasn't the right time.
- This is the right time.
- Exactly.
- This is the right time?
- This is the right time.
Next up are Chorong...
and Bomi.
Chorong, you recently visited
Jong Kook's place...
- with the other Apink members.
- Yes.
- Did they say anything special?
- What do you mean?
- The other Apink members?
- Yes.
- About Se Chan or Jong Kook.
- After the shoot...
I'm sure they said something.
Let's hear it.
They didn't say anything?
When the shoot was over,
that was it.
(They keep their work
and personal lives separate.)
- They didn't say anything at all?
- It's so different.
As soon as the shoot was over,
I called Jong Kook and said,
"I'm so happy right now."
- "I'm really happy."
- He talked...
He talked about Chorong a lot.
I thought you had a crush on Na Eun.
- That's not true.
- Why would I have a crush on her?
- He was just joking.
- But you didn't dislike her either.
- I neither liked nor disliked her.
- Right.
(What did I do?)
Hey. If you say that...
If you say that, our next guest
will be Na Eun.
Stop it. I'll act all stupid
around her again.
- In the end,
- Gosh.
nothing will ever happen
between him and Apink.
(Sadly, nothing will ever happen
between Se Chan and Apink.)
Your new song, "Dumhdurum,"
will be released today?
- Yes, today at 6 p.m.
- Today?
- Today at 6 p.m.?
- "Dumhdurum"?
- We have a showcase after this.
- That's right.
- You have a showcase today?
- Yes.
What time?
- It starts at 8 p.m.
- It'll broadcast live at 8 p.m.
That means we'll be finished
before 8 p.m.
(We'll be finished before 8 p.m.)
We'll be finished before that.
- He's getting old. I told you.
- Don't say that out loud.
Don't say that out loud.
Haha is getting old.
(Everyone is secretly happy.)
- He wants to go home early.
- But...
- Stop it.
- The thing is...
Yoojung looks very happy too.
- Actually...
- We'll be finished around 5 p.m.
- We should see their performance.
- Bomi and...
- Chorong, please.
- We should.
("Dumhdurum" by Apink
is topping all the charts.)
- Yes!
- "Dumhdurum".
(The music starts playing.)
This is going to be a hit.
(The melody is catchy
and refreshing.)
Their moves are so full of energy.
Dumhdurum...
I memorized it already.
(Their dance is perfectly in sync.)
That looks so cool.
That's amazing.
(My heart is like, dumhdurum)
It's going to be
the number one song!
- It's the number one song!
- It's going to be a hit.
- The number one song!
- I'm sure of it.
- The song is so nice.
- It's the number one song.
- I love the song.
- Really?
- It's going to be a huge hit.
- I mean it.
Next up is Chungha.
(Chungha, the performance queen)
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
No one can deny...
- that she is the leading...
- Exactly.
female solo singer right now.
- Isn't she incredible?
- I know.
My new song will be released
the day after...
- this airs.
- Can we see it?
- She's going to perform it here?
- Please.
(Chungha performs her new song,
"Stay Tonight.")
(She looks like a different person.)
She completely changes.
She becomes a different person.
(Speechless)
(Everyone is overwhelmed
by her performance.)
(Praying)
(The finishing pose looks
so elegant.)
(Pure perfection)
(Everyone falls love with Chungha.)
She looks like a magician.
(What is he doing?)
- That doesn't look right.
- Look at me.
She didn't do that.
She did.
(Fascinated)
I couldn't even try to copy her.
Such charisma.
The 500th episode's race is...
Did You Even Eat Before the Race?
The winning team of each round...
gets to enjoy invigorating food
in season prepared on the spot.
- Really?
- Spring greens...
- That sounds amazing.
- But...
one of you is greedy...
and wants to take all the prizes.
Again?
(The greedy one
wants all the prizes.)
- Someone is greedy.
- Unbelievable.
We have a greedy one again.
Who is it?
The greedy one wants to
eliminate everyone else...
- and win all the prizes.
- How greedy.
Find and eliminate the greedy one...
in the final race.
The team that eliminates
the greedy one wins the race...
and receives all the prizes.
(The teams will be able to buy hints
regarding the greedy one.)
Each team
will receive 100 dollars...
which you must hide in your tents.
- In our tents?
- In our tents.
After each round,
the winning team will get...
a hint regarding the greedy one...
and time to search for the money
hidden in another team's tent.
With the money you win,
you can buy the meal offered
in the round and more hints.
After the second round,
the top two teams with
the most amount of money left...
will win extra hints regarding
the identity of the greedy one.
Please head to your tents
and hide the money.
- Got it.
- We need to hide the money?
(They'll now hide the money.)
We need to hide it
in a place no one would suspect.
Are you perhaps the greedy one?
If you are, can you rip off
my name tag?
What?
There's only one?
Let's not suspect each other
during the race.
- What? Of course.
- We'll trust each other.
Why would I suspect you?
(He's nothing but suspicious.)
- These spots...
- Is this too obvious?
That'll easily get found.
This isn't easy at all.
(Meanwhile,
Kwang Soo and Chungha...)
- Can we turn off this fan?
- What?
Let's hide it in the fan
and then turn it back on.
Wouldn't the money
fly all over the place?
You're right.
Hold on.
(Se Chan hides the money
in the door frame.)
(He's proud of himself.)
I hid it all.
I'm not suspicious or anything,
but you didn't pocket any, right?
- What?
- No, right?
Unbelievable.
- We're on the same team today.
- Got it.
(They're all done
hiding their money.)
Please gather around.
Your time is up.
Where did you hide yours?
I bet we hid the money
in similar places.
- Right.
- Under the mattress?
- Probably.
- There weren't many options.
- You're right.
- Like always,
Jong Kook's the last one out.
Jong Kook!
Coming!
You can't hide them
separately, right?
Someone should tell him.
Separately?
- What do you mean?
- Can we hide each bill separately?
- Yes, you can.
- We can?
- Why would you hide them together?
- Is that what you did?
- It'll be like hitting the jackpot.
- I hid all of it together too.
- Hold on...
(A little while ago)
Would this fit in here?
(They tried to find a place
to hide all the money in.)
No one would open this, right?
Of course not.
I doubt this will fit.
No way!
No one would find that.
- How...
- We should've kept quiet.
Wait, are you sure?
- I'm heading to Haha's tent.
- For sure.
We can hit the jackpot there.
We only need to look
for one hiding spot.
- Mijoo, over here.
- Where did Chorong go?
Bomi, where are you?
- Bomi?
- Bomi!
- You gave yourself a brow lift.
- Look at you.
- Bomi...
- That's a tight ponytail.
I thought
you were frowning just now.
You look like a warrior
from a period drama.
As you can see,
the chefs over there
will be cooking for you today.
- It looks amazing.
- Thank you!
If only it were a little less windy.
- Exactly.
- I'm starving!
(Their tongues
and stomachs react.)
Let me reveal the first dish
you'll be playing for in this round.
Bring it out.
- Come on out.
- Anything would taste good today.
Everything is better
when freshly cooked.
I see noodles!
- What is it?
- Noodles?
What is it?
- What's that?
- What is it?
- No way!
- I love this.
- What is it?
- I can't see.
- Webfoot octopus ramyeon.
- Webfoot octopus.
- Are those fritters?
I can't see.
- Octopus ramyeon.
- Webfoot octopus.
Is it webfoot octopus?
- And fried webfoot octopus.
- They look delicious.
(Kwang Soo's lost it.)
Webfoot octopus is in season,
you know.
It's in season.
I'm going to have that
no matter what.
The first dish...
is abundant with taurine
which rejuvenates you.
Fried webfoot octopus
and webfoot octopus ramyeon.
I didn't know they were in season.
(He shows his excitement
with a knee strike.)
Jae Suk only does that
when he feels energized.
Why would you kick the air?
I just love webfoot octopus.
The game you will play
is called Dancing Catallena.
One of you will stick a question
on a part of your body...
- and dance to the music.
- Right.
Your goal is to make sure
that only your partner sees it.
Then, it's up to the partner
to answer the question.
Other teams are also free
to answer the questions...
- and score points.
- All right.
- So we need to answer it correctly.
- Got it.
I'm sure the questions
aren't that difficult.
- More or less.
- Really?
- Are they easy enough for us?
- Yes.
- Common knowledge?
- That's right.
- Darn it.
- Common knowledge?
"Hyeongseoljigong"
describes this situation.
Jae Suk, "hyeongseoljigong"...
You're killing me.
This situation...
I searched "hyeongseoljigong"
after watching the show,
and I've never been
more embarrassed in my life.
I still don't know what it means.
(It means
"the fruits of studying hard.")
Be honest.
(The meaning
of "hyeongseoljigong"...)
(Se Chan doesn't know either.)
You two...
- I still don't know what it means.
- "Hyeongseoljigong".
I looked it up and...
Ji Hyo, you know
what it means, right?
I don't.
- You don't?
- It describes this situation.
- This situation?
- Yes.
- Yes, of course.
- That's right.
You know what it means, right?
- No, I don't?
- I see.
(This is exactly what
"hyeongseoljigong" means.)
The teams in the back
can also answer the question...
if you can read it.
- Got it.
- Really?
You must say, "Let me answer" first.
- Sure.
- Got it.
Let the wall go up first.
We won't get to see
where she sticks it on.
You should tell me what you see.
Got it.
- You get the rules, right?
- Right.
- I want that dish badly.
- Go, Chorong.
- Has she stuck it on her?
- Yes.
- Let's do this then.
- Get ready.
Yoojung,
make sure that only I can see it.
(She nods.)
- Let's go!
- Can we answer it too?
- Yes.
- Say, "Let me answer" first.
- I don't see it.
- Where is it?
- There.
- There!
- On her side!
(I see something.)
- Over there.
- I can't see it at all.
It all comes down
to having good vision.
- I can't see it.
- Me neither.
- The letters are too small.
- I don't see a thing.
- I can't see anything.
- She's too far away.
The letters are too small.
(Who founded Goguryeo?)
(The answer is Jumong.)
- No!
- I can't see a thing.
Let me answer!
Magugo.
- What?
- What's that?
The letters are too small.
- Goguryeo...
- Sweet potatoes...
Let me answer!
- Goguryeo...
- Sweet potatoes...
Let me answer!
(Farsightedness caused
a misunderstanding.)
Jumong!
- What?
- What was that?
(Screaming)
(They celebrate by dancing.)
- What was that?
- What did he say?
- What was the answer?
Wasn't I supposed to say
"sweet potatoes" backward?
What?
"Who founded Goguryeo?"
- Really?
- Who founded Goguryeo?
No way.
Let's go for it. Nice!
Gosh.
- What was the question?
- Who founded Goguryeo?
- Wasn't it Wang Geon?
- I thought it was a math quiz.
- What?
- Se Chan said...
that Wang Geon is the one
who founded Goguryeo.
- That's what he said.
- I thought it was Wang Geon.
- He founded Goryeo.
- Seriously?
I bet some are pretending
not to have read it.
- I'm sure of it.
- Me too.
Yoojung did a good job.
- Okay, Kwang Soo's up next.
- Me?
Reading it
doesn't mean you'll answer it.
Jumong...
I would've answered that correctly.
Jumong, Park Hyeokgeose...
You need to have common knowledge.
Reading it
doesn't mean you'll answer it.
Right, you need common knowledge.
Haha, you just need basic knowledge.
Shut it.
(Jae Suk still wants to party.)
Chungha...
Look at him being all silly.
(Why is Kwang Soo
heading over to Chungha?)
Kwang Soo, you can't go back there.
- What are you doing?
- You can't cheat.
What are you doing?
Kwang Soo, are you kidding me?
(He openly gives her advice.)
Give me a signal using your hands.
(What was that?)
- What is he doing?
- Hey.
He said he'd look
when she gives him a signal.
(Se Chan reveals their strategy.)
- That was our strategy.
- Are you kidding me?
How could you tell the others?
Well, I heard it too.
What on earth are you doing?
- What's the meaning of this?
- My gosh.
Cover your behind with your t-shift.
Cover your behind.
I did.
You have no idea how many
clothes Jae Suk has ruined.
- What is this?
- He pulls on mine...
so that it becomes
an off-the-shoulder top.
- Kwang Soo...
- Unbelievable.
All right then.
- Where is it?
- I don't see it.
It's probably on her side.
(Nice!)
(Where did she stick the question?)
It's on the bottom of her foot!
The bottom of her foot.
- What?
- The bottom of her foot.
Let's see.
(It's difficult to see.)
- I can't see it.
- Me neither.
- Stop bouncing!
- The letters are too small.
- Where is it?
- I can't see it.
- Do you see it?
- What's the question?
- I can't see it.
- She looks so cool though.
No, I can't see anything.
- The position of it...
- Hold your foot up and freeze.
Hold your foot up and freeze.
(What's the Korean word
for "a cold?")
(The answer is "goppul.")
(Does Se Chan know the answer?)
Ji Hyo, what's that dish
that was served in the palace?
- What is it?
- I don't see anything.
I think I saw "a bowl of rice."
- Really?
- A bowl of rice.
- Chungha...
- Chorong!
- Chorong...
- A cold...
- Chorong said her name.
- What's the answer?
- Chorong, go ahead.
(What will Chorong's answer be?)
Goppul.
- Sorry?
- Goppul.
She's right.
- She's right.
- What was the question?
- Go, Chorong!
- The archaic word for...
- The Korean word for "a cold."
(Chorong
read the question perfectly.)
- Chorong, nice one.
- The old word for "a cold."
(The question was meant
for Kwang Soo though.)
The Korean word for "a cold."
Why would you ask me
about a dish served in the palace?
Isn't that what it said?
A dish served in the palace?
Oh, the Korean word.
I might have the ramyeon
thanks to Chorong.
I should've gotten it.
You wouldn't have been able
to answer it anyway.
What are you talking about?
I call it a goppul these days too.
You do what?
Are you saying you knew the answer?
That's what I still call a cold.
How did you manage to read that?
- Bomi's ready for business.
- I wonder where she hid it.
Let's do this.
(She lets her hips fly.)
- She's getting into it.
- Yes.
(She's good.)
It's a hit.
She's great.
Gosh, what's up with Bomi?
You're amazing.
Let us see the question now.
(Haha, take a look at my palm.)
What was that?
- It's on her palm.
- My gosh.
Your butt is showing.
(What's Bomi's question?)
What?
(What's the name
of Seong Chun Hyang's mom?)
(She shows it
only to her partner, Haha.)
- Haha, what are you doing?
- We can't see it.
It's about something's name.
(Let me answer.)
Let me answer.
Do you want to see her dance
a little more?
Okay. Go ahead. Let's enjoy.
- Keep dancing.
- Enjoy.
- Did you see it?
She's scary.
Enjoy.
Okay.
- Let me answer.
- He knows it.
(Haha seems confident. Can he
get it right on his first attempt?)
(Haha, I believe in you.)
Mother Ppaengdeok.
Mother Ppaengdeok?
- Let me answer.
Maid Ppaengdeok!
(They all get excited
as Haha gives a wrong answer.)
It's Maid Ppaengdeok.
Maid Ppaengdeok.
- What is it then?
- Let me answer.
Ms. Ppaengdeok.
Let me answer. Housemaid Ppaengdeok.
Let me answer. Kim Chun Bok.
What?
- Let me answer.
- Good.
- Look at her.
- Let me answer.
- What was the question?
- Mr. Sim.
(They give all kinds
of wrong answers.)
Let me answer. Wolmae.
What?
(Jong Kook made a lucky guess.)
- How did you know that?
- What was that?
(It's Wolmae.)
It's Wolmae. I knew it.
- Mom?
- What was the question?
- I didn't see the question.
- Seong Chun Hyang's mom?
It's Wolmae.
I see. Wolmae.
I mean, they are best friends.
It's Seong Chun Hyang's mom.
Aren't Ppangdeok and
Chun Hyang's mom best friends?
You're funny.
The answer is Wolmae.
- Who is Mother Ppaengdeok?
- It's not Ppaengdeok.
Who is Ppaengdeok then?
She's Mr. Sim's wife.
What are you doing?
I didn't even know the question.
I just inferred it from his answer.
I'm so embarrassed.
Did you just hear Haha?
"Do you want to see her dance
a little more? Okay."
"Do you want to see..."
(After he shouted out
confidently...)
(Do you want to see her dance
a little more?)
(It's a tragedy caused
by his overconfidence.)
(He wants to crawl under a rock.)
"Do you want to see more?"
"Do you want to see her dance
a little more? Okay."
Hey, you just put Bomi
in an awkward situation.
"Enjoy, Bomi."
"Let me answer. Mother Ppaengdeok."
What was that?
Haha was being so ugly.
It gives me pleasure.
I'm excited to see Mijoo dance.
(Next up is Jong Kook and Mijoo.)
Let's go.
There she goes.
(She turns around
posing sensuously.)
(Headbanging)
What does it say?
Her hair is covering it.
(Her hair is covering it.)
The capital of Canada.
- What does it say?
- The capital of Canada.
(He eavesdrops on Yoojung.)
What's the capital of Canada?
- Let me answer.
- Let me answer!
- Oslo.
- Let me answer.
- Oslo?
Let me answer!
Ottawa.
Gosh, I knew it.
(Thanks to Ji Hyo's mistake,
Jae Suk and Yoojung got 1 point.)
I knew it.
- What was the question?
- Oslo? Ji Hyo.
- Where's Oslo?
- Did she mean...
a green tea farm?
- No, I said Oslo.
- Did you say O'sulloc?
- It's a green tea farm.
- No.
- I didn't say O'sulloc.
- Why did you say O'sulloc?
- What about O'sulloc?
- Where's Oslo?
It was supposed to be
the capital of Canada.
Did you go to O'sulloc?
- No.
- Jeju Island?
- Do you like green tea?
No, it's not that.
It's not O'sulloc. I said Oslo.
Where is Oslo?
- Where is it?
- What did she say?
There's a city called Oslo.
- Really?
- There is.
Next up is our members.
Okay.
- Is it Se Chan's turn?
- Yes.
Let's do this.
(This song is "Growl" by ECO.)
- There you go.
- It's EXO.
My gosh.
Oh no.
(This is "Snore" by Yang Se Chan.)
Chorong, what do you think?
- What do you think?
- He's cool.
(Is he showing the question?)
- Is he doing it?
- Where is it?
There's nothing.
Where is it?
(Screaming)
(After dancing around a while...)
(He shows his belly carefully.)
(It ruins their eyes.)
(Frightened)
(They can't bear to see his belly,
so they just cover their eyes.)
My goodness.
- I can't see this. You sit here.
- I'll sit.
I'm not watching it.
Look at this.
(Possessed by EXO)
(The guy with a baby belly
is carried away.)
What does it say?
- I can't see it.
- What is it?
What does it say?
- It's...
- What does it say?
- What is it?
- Can I come closer?
They all are asking it.
(Where is the place
Sim Cheong jumped into the water?)
- That's right.
- It's...
- She doesn't know the answer.
- You're almost there.
- She doesn't know.
- 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
- River.
- What?
(Did Sim Cheong dive into a river?)
- A reservoir. Hang on.
What is it?
Let me answer. A lake.
What?
I know what it is.
- What?
- What's the question?
(She didn't even see the question.)
- I know what it is.
- Where did Sim Cheong...
Let me answer. Indangsu.
(Indangsu is correct.)
- I knew it.
- My goodness.
What's the question?
(Disappointed)
She said a river.
What was that? Indangsu? My gosh.
How could you say that?
I couldn't think of the name.
She said O'sulloc and river.
What's with her?
River and sea.
Sim Cheong dived into a river?
Isn't it ridiculous?
- A river? It's just...
- It's Indangsu.
That's right.
You should've said Samdasoo.
- O'sulloc.
- You should've said O'sulloc.
- That was hard.
Gosh, I want to
get the right answer.
- This is fun.
- But I can't see it.
I can't answer when I can't see it.
Yoojung catches it very well.
- I have good eyesight.
- You have such good eyesight.
I have good eyesight.
You're really good.
Please give us an easy one.
I didn't know any of the questions
you just gave.
- Change it with Mijoo.
- He's starting.
(It's Haha's turn to dance.)
Look at his hand.
(She opens her eyes wide.)
- I can't see his feet.
- I guess it's on his foot.
It's on the sole of his foot.
- Hey, I don't see anything.
- There's nothing.
(He shows his feet slowly.)
(I don't see anything.)
Haha.
My gosh.
(It's on his calf, not his foot.)
(Who's the god of the sea
in Greek mythology? Poseidon)
- Let me answer.
- It's Bomi's turn.
(She shouts out first.)
Bomi doesn't know it.
You know it.
(Bomi, I believe in you.)
(What's Bomi's answer?)
- Jesus.
- Let me answer.
- My turn.
(The god of sea, Jesus?)
- I said it first.
- Jesus!
(Upset)
Let me answer!
- Let me answer!
- Jong Kook.
- Let Jong Kook answer.
- Poseidon!
- I said it first.
- Jong Kook.
Poseidon.
- Let me answer.
- Okay. I knew it.
I was faster.
- Okay.
- Gosh, it's Poseidon.
- I knew the answer.
- Jong Kook was faster.
- What was that? Jesus?
- Because he walked on the sea.
The god of sea, Jesus?
The god of sea.
Is Jesus in Greek mythology?
Bomi?
That was close, Ji Hyo.
Don't come too close.
- Okay.
- They all were here.
They all were standing here.
That's because
this smell drives me crazy.
- Okay.
- It smells amazing.
It smells so good.
I like the smell.
We have to eat it, Yoojung.
(What? Yoojung?)
- Me?
- Suk Jin.
Yoojung is my partner.
Really?
I was so surprised to hear that.
What did you say?
Do you know what Suk Jin said?
"We have to eat it, Yoojung."
Why?
- He doesn't even know his partner.
- It's Chorong.
- He's...
- You thought she is your partner...
because she's next to you.
I'm sorry.
- What was that?
- She was standing next to me.
Next up is Kwang Soo.
(It's Chungha and Kwang Soo's turn.)
- Kwang Soo.
- I have to trust my eyes.
Kwang Soo, is it
a difficult question?
You can answer it.
Do you know the answer?
This isn't right.
- What?
- I don't know.
(I don't know.)
I'm sorry.
He doesn't know the answer.
But I'm sure you can answer it.
- You can do this.
- You don't know it?
How can she answer it
when you don't know it?
(I'll try hard to answer it.)
- You can do this.
- Where did he put it on?
Did you put it on the cast?
(He rolls up his pants.)
(Then he lies down.)
- It's coming.
- Good. There you go.
Where is it?
- Where is it?
- Look at his face.
- It looks so annoying.
What are you doing?
What's that?
(Shrieking)
There it is.
(After he draws attention
to his leg,)
(he gives the question
with his mouth.)
(Shocked)
What's that?
(What's the name
of Hong Du Kkae's wife?)
(Go Eun Ae)
My goodness.
(They are shocked
by his way of setting the question.)
Kwang Soo is unbelievable.
- Kwang Soo is Kwang Soo.
- We have to watch carefully.
(They all look
at Kwang Soo's mouth.)
I can't see it.
- Let me answer.
Go ahead.
Go Gil Dong.
- Let me answer.
- No. It's from "Dooly."
Let me answer. Go Eun Ah.
Let me answer. Go Gil Sun.
Let me answer!
(If Jae Suk gets it right,
Jae Suk and Yoojung win.)
Go Eun Ae.
That's right. It's Go Eun Ae.
(Go Eun Ae is correct.)
- It's Go Eun Ae.
- Go Eun Ae?
It is Go Eun Ae.
I was right about Go.
You were right about that.
She's not Kang.
Go Gil Dong?
You guys are unbelievable.
That's right. It's Go Eun Ae.
- It wasn't Go Gil Dong.
- It's Go Eun Ae.
It was so close. It's okay.
It wasn't close at all.
It was close.
Was it close?
What's next?
Let me announce the results.
The winning team is...
Yoojung and Jae Suk.
(The top three couples
who can search hidden money)
Second place is
Mijoo and Jong Kook.
- That's not bad.
- It's still good.
- Thank you. You did a good job.
- This isn't bad.
Third place is
Chorong and Suk Jin.
The top three couples can...
choose a tent
that they will steal money from.
- Which one should we pick?
- Please make a decision.
Do you want to do that?
- We pick Haha's tent.
- What?
They hid all the money in one place.
- Really?
- Shall we do that?
We will go to Kwang Soo's tent.
We pick Suk Jin
and Chorong's tent.
- I'll give you 100 seconds.
- What is this?
- Start.
- Let's go.
- We have 100 seconds.
- Kwang Soo.
- Let's go to Kwang Soo's tent.
- Where is it?
Where did they hide it?
I think we can find it.
(They are busy searching the tent.)
(Find money for a meal
and a hint on the greedy one.)
Where is it?
Where did they hide it?
Gather around.
Time's up.
Did you find our money?
You didn't, did you?
- They must have found it.
- Did you find it?
Look at Jae Suk's butt.
I think they found it.
- It was so hard.
- Jae Suk must have found it.
- He found it.
- His back pocket is full.
Really?
- What is that?
- Did you find all the money?
- What?
- Is that a full envelope?
Did you hide all of the money
in one place?
- Yoojung found it.
- How did you find it?
(Team Haha's 100 dollars
was discovered right away.)
- How are supposed to...
- Jae Suk, I found it.
- Did you find it?
- I found it! How do I go in there?
- Yoojung, where is it?
- It's over there.
- Where?
- Over there.
- Okay. We found it.
- Yes!
(They easily retrieved
the entire amount.)
- I guess people think similarly.
- Yes!
- Bomi. Bomi.
- 100 dollars?
- Yes.
- Haha.
- Suk Jin's team is next.
(They suddenly become dirt poor.)
Us?
(Meanwhile, Suk Jin and Chorong)
Is that it?
- Is that it?
- Where did you hide the money?
Thank goodness. Thank goodness.
You found it
with the toilet paper, right?
- Didn't you?
- Is it with the toilet paper?
(She suddenly confesses
where she hid the money.)
- What is wrong with her?
- Who is next?
- It's with the toilet paper.
Search there the next time.
- Search there the next time.
- What is wrong with her?
- Thank you, Chungha.
- Search there the next time.
Did she reveal it just now?
- What is wrong with her?
- It's with the toilet paper.
Jong Kook's team is next.
What?
(Jong Kook and Mijoo
acquired 67 dollars.)
- Where did you find them?
- Please spread them out.
They scattered them across the tent,
but the hiding places were obvious.
- Were the hiding places obvious?
- They lacked original ideas.
One serving of the meal
you saw earlier costs...
30 dollars.
- We won't be able to eat.
- If you want a hint...
on the greedy one,
it also costs 30 dollars.
- We need to pay.
- Yes.
The team that placed first
will receive a hint.
- Will we receive it?
- Yes.
- A hint on the greedy one.
- I forgot about the greedy one.
The greedy one.
Jae Suk, doesn't it feel strange
to receive a hint about yourself?
(They carefully check the hint.)
(Someone who is a bit hot
and unstylish)
(This person is very interested
in health.)
What does it mean?
It may be wise to keep the hint
a secret...
since you need to eliminate
this person to win.
- How is the hint?
- It's not like how it was...
- in the past.
- It isn't too broad, is it?
(Jong Kook is obsessed
with working out.)
(Is he the greedy one
who is very interested in health?)
I wouldn't say
it leaves you flustered.
(There is another person
who is associated with health.)
Jae Suk is talented
in exercising too.
(Jae Suk looks after his health.
Is he the greedy one?)
Don't you wish
you could see the hint?
(Suk Jin is closely associated
with health too.)
You look ill.
(Suk Jin brags about his health.
Is he the greedy one?)
(All three of them are
fairly unstylish too.)
(Who could the greedy one be?)
You are worried about that.
A serving of a meal
costs 30 dollars.
- Do we have to pay for the meal?
- Yes.
Bomi has a showcase today.
Please give her 10 dollars.
Please give me two dollars.
Please give her two dollars.
She has a showcase today.
- Please give her two dollars.
- But still...
You don't need to give me anything.
- Please give me one dollar.
- Yoojung, I leave it up to you.
- Yoojung.
- Please give her 10 dollars.
Look at Bomi's hands.
(Let's do the same.)
- Chorong has a showcase too.
- Please give me 10 dollars.
- We took money from them.
- But we...
(He spots an opportunity.)
Chungha has a showcase too.
She couldn't tell you before.
She has a showcase too.
Jae Suk, Ji Hyo needs to go
to the river.
- She needs to go to the river.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Please give her two dollars.
- How much did you give her?
We will have one serving.
- Shall we have one each?
- Yes.
- Give us one each.
- They are flexing.
- You are ordering two servings.
- That's right.
- We need a serving each, right?
- Yes.
It's okay. I am not hungry
because I ate at home.
- 60 dollars.
- Thank you for the food.
- How much does a bite cost?
Thank you for the food.
I won't sell a bite.
- Yoojung.
- Yes?
How much does webfoot octopus cost?
It's a hearty meal.
(She doesn't have time to answer.)
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
(He slurps the noodles
with determination.)
(His mouth waters.)
- It was delicious.
- Let's move to the next location.
(They finish eating
and move to the next location.)
- All right.
- It's time for the second mission.
We will reveal the second meal.
Bring in the meal.
I bet it will keep improving.
Gosh, I have to eat it.
This is something I must eat.
What's inside?
Fatsia shoots.
- Bibimmyeon with fatsia shoots.
- Brisket rolled...
- fatsia shoots.
- Fatsia shoots are inside.
Fatsia shoots are good for health.
This is insane.
This mission is...
I Am Coming to Save You.
The couples will take turns
to be an offensive team.
A member of the offensive team
will sit on a conveyor belt.
The other member will play
All-Direction Cham, Cham, Cham...
with five members
of the rest of the teams.
- We have played this game before.
- That's right.
- I remember that.
- It's so hard.
- It's a difficult game.
As the matches take place,
the conveyor belt will move.
It will stop the moment
the player beats all opponents.
The time it took to save the partner
will determine the top three places.
- Okay.
- In that case...
- Top, bottom, left, and right.
(Their eyes go wide!)
My goodness.
(They begin to set up the paints
on the conveyor belt.)
Aren't they soaking the fabric...
too much?
They are completely soaking
the fabric.
Don't go too hard on it.
(Gulping)
Pick the first team.
They should go first this time.
- Haha.
- Haha or Kwang Soo.
- No!
- Jong Kook.
Why should we go first?
- "DADDY FREE", do it.
- Okay!
He is happy.
We need one member from each team
to play the game.
(Haha sits on the conveyor belt
and Bomi goes to play the game.)
- Bomi!
- Okay.
I need to have that meal.
Let's not see each other if we lose.
- That's right.
- Okay.
(I will win!)
Cham, cham, cham
(What?)
(The beat is a bit strange.)
- She can't do that.
- That was a bit off.
(Is that how you play
Cham, Cham, Cham?)
Cham, cham, cham
(She continues to play
Cham, Cham, Cham strangely.)
What?
Hurry up!
(Bomi keeps going.)
- He dodged.
- Cham, cham, cham
(Red paint)
(Green paint)
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
(Hurried)
What? "Hold on"?
What is going on?
- Why did you lie down?
- Hey!
- You didn't say you had stopped.
(He feels victimized.)
- Why did you lie down?
- I kept going since I didn't know!
- I kept going.
- Why did you lie down?
- You were supposed to keep going.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- What?
- You were supposed to keep going.
- You said, "Hold on."
Hey, this is reggae!
- Really?
- Ya man!
(Ya man!)
- Why did you stop?
- He told me to stop.
- This is reggae.
- We will start over.
It's okay. It doesn't matter.
I need to have that meal.
"Dumhdurum".
I believe in you.
Pick a direction on the last "Cham."
- Get ready.
- Bomi, let's go!
Let's go!
Set.
Cham, cham, cham
(Yoojung avoids all attacks.)
(Desperate)
(Here it comes.)
(Fast and precise)
- She is done.
- All done.
(He stopped
right in front of the paint!)
So why do I look like this?
Why do I look like this
when I stopped right in front of it?
No matter how much you like reggae,
you shouldn't be on TV like this.
- You try so hard to stand out.
- Why do you dress that way?
- Was I like this from the opening?
- Yes!
Are you having a showcase today?
- Seriously.
- Why do I look like this?
- 12 seconds.
- You were so fast.
- That's how you should do it.
- I will keep it fast.
- The paint dried.
- You should put more paint on it.
Aren't they...
- Aren't they putting too much?
- Make it perfect.
- Put more paint on it.
- Suk Jin is next, right?
- No, no. Jong Kook is next.
- No.
- The producer confirmed it.
- No, no. Jong Kook is next.
- You are next, Suk Jin.
- The producer confirmed it.
It's you.
Jong Kook is next!
I will go after Suk Jin.
They...
They put too much paint on it.
Why did I suggest it?
Let's go!
I am bad at it. This is bad.
(He sits on the conveyor belt.)
Look at him.
He isn't sitting at the very end,
because he is too lazy
to move the sitting cushion.
Are you serious?
(Suk Jin is unbelievable.)
- All right. Chorong.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yes?
- Let's go!
He is unbelievable.
Cham, cham, cham
- It's moving fast.
- Why didn't you sit at the end?
It's moving fast.
Cham, cham, cham
- Cham, cham, cham
- Your hair looks cool.
She is good.
(Bomi plays Cham, Cham, Cham
haphazardly again.)
(Suk Jin emerges
as colorful as ever.)
(They are absorbed in
Cham, Cham, Cham.)
(Tapping)
- Hey.
- It's over.
- Someone give him a motorcycle.
Someone give him a motorcycle.
(Suk Jin, the outlaw motorcyclist)
Suk Jin, let's go.
Get on that motorcycle.
- His hair looks cool.
- He looks cool.
Sport this look regularly.
It's a good look on you.
- Seriously.
- You look cool.
- Really?
- You look young.
- In that style,
- you look young.
- Do I really look okay?
- Let me see.
- Who wants to go next?
- You look cool.
- This time,
- shall we go?
- Jae Suk.
- This is hard.
- I have no confidence.
- Put yourself at ease.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
- I will put myself at ease.
- Okay.
- Set.
(Yoojung and Jae Suk start.)
Cham, cham, cham
(Yoojung plays the game
comfortably.)
Yoojung! Why is it so fast?
(Look at that!)
- Hey!
- Cham, cham, cham
Cham, cham, cham
- Hey!
- Cham, cham, cham
(Spring and summer collection,
when a handsome face meets colors)
(What is that?)
- Cham, cham, cham
- Hey!
(Peek-a-boo)
Come on.
This is...
- Hey.
- His face became a mess.
(The outlaw motorcyclist
laughs merrily.)
- Hey.
- His face became a mess.
Hold on.
- Didn't you make it too fast?
- Why is it so fast?
It became faster
starting from my turn.
This is...
- It became faster.
- I can't open my eyes!
- I feel bad.
- For goodness' sake.
It was as fast as a roller coaster.
Kwang Soo should go again.
- Kwang Soo should go again.
- Seriously.
- What?
- Kwang Soo, go again.
- You didn't get any paint on you.
- Kwang Soo hasn't gone yet.
I haven't gone yet?
- You haven't gone yet.
- No, no.
Says who?
Who says I haven't gone yet?
You haven't gone yet.
(A bit earlier,)
(Kwang Soo played a boring round
when the paint was dry.)
- Go again.
- Kwang Soo hasn't gone yet.
Don't say he needs to go again.
He hasn't gone yet.
- He hasn't gone yet.
- I am getting a sense of deja vu.
- You haven't gone yet.
- You haven't gone yet, Kwang Soo.
- Really?
- Kwan Soo.
- I haven't gone yet.
- Kwan Soo should go at our speed.
- At our speed.
- Okay.
His name is Kwang Soo, not Kwan Soo.
Suk Jin.
We worked together for 10 years.
How could you call me Kwan Soo?
I mispronounced.
(He learns Kwang Soo's name
after 10 years.)
Paint!
Dip it in paint!
Gather around, Soak it with paint.
Soak it completely.
Soak it perfectly. More!
Get ready. Set.
(Kwang Soo and Chungha start.)
Cham, cham, cham
Kwang Soo, close your eyes.
You need to close your eyes.
- Cham, cham, cham
- Chungha, don't worry about me.
(He keeps his eyes closed.)
- Just think that I am not here.
- Cham, cham, cham
(My goodness.)
Just think that I am not here.
(It's like a car wash.)
- Cham, cham, cham
- Chungha, I am okay.
- Chungha, don't worry about me.
Cham, cham, cham
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
Who is that?
(Trying to figure out
what happened)
He looks scary.
(The colorful monster
charges forward.)
Don't run!
(The outlaw motorcyclist is happy.)
- Chungha, what happened?
- How scary!
- You look scary.
- Decalcomania.
- You look like a work of art.
Isn't this decalcomania?
You look like a work of art.
- You look like a work of art.
- I made you a star.
- How badly do I look?
(The name of the artwork is
"The Bare-faced Star.")
- I made you a star.
- What the...
What is this?
Paint got on my phone!
I made you a star.
Your time is 15 seconds.
- 15 seconds?
- That's right.
Are you saying this happened
in 15 seconds?
- 15 seconds is a short time.
- You did a good job.
How did you get
so much paint on yourself?
Okay!
- 13 seconds.
- Good job.
- 13 seconds?
- You finished fast.
She is good.
Se Chan.
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo go last.)
(Do you want to go
on the conveyor belt?)
Hey.
Hurry up and go, you punk.
Ji Hyo, do you want to give it a go?
- Should I give it a go?
- Go ahead.
- Okay then.
- Go.
(Ji Hyo gets 5 stars
for enthusiasm.)
- What is going on?
- Hey.
- I will do a good job.
- Let's go.
- Ji Hyo is enthusiastic.
- Ji Hyo is cool.
Here I go.
Ji Hyo, that's good.
Okay. Ji Hyo is enthusiastic.
Let's go.
Ji Hyo, I will do this properly.
Cham, cham, cham
Ji Hyo, I will finish them off
in five blows.
- Okay.
- Don't worry.
Let's go. Let's go.
Set.
Cham, cham, cham
- What?
- Cham, cham, cham
- That's good.
(Something doesn't seem right.)
(He got me.)
(To the beat)
Cham, cham, cham
(He attacks with all his force.)
- How is she avoiding everything?
- Cham, cham, cham
(Swearing)
(There hasn't been
Cham, Cham, Cham like this!)
- Ji Hyo.
- That's good.
- Cham, cham, cham
(Gosh, I lost.)
(Swearing)
(The delinquent Ji Hyo is back.)
I can't believe you!
You should have at least fallen
for it once!
You suck!
I can't believe you!
When I went, "Cham, cham, cham,"
you should have fallen for it!
For goodness' sake.
Ji Hyo is cool.
- For goodness' sake.
- You look like Angry Bird.
Ji Hyo,
- I did my best.
- For goodness' sake.
- Ji Hyo, you look like Angry Bird.
- Mijoo, I am disappointed in you.
You should have allowed
an attack once.
They did a good job.
Mijoo, you looked so carefree.
It was like a commercial.
Mijoo is good.
(She is
the Cham, Cham, Cham genius.)
The records are in.
I will give you a chance
to renew the record...
- if you want.
- Should I go?
My partner, Yoojung,
wants to give it a go.
Chungha wants to go.
We will go again.
Ji Hyo wants to go again.
I will show the viewers!
- Ji Hyo is incredible.
- Viewers, just you wait.
I will show you.
Cham, cham, cham
Just you wait.
I told the viewers to wait.
I will show them.
I am angry! Ji Hyo, come here.
Come here.
- Ji Hyo, come here.
- For goodness' sake.
Let's start with Yoojung.
This time, the men will play
Cham, Cham, Cham.
- Okay.
- Yoojung, are you ready?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
(Screaming)
(Yoojung is excited.)
- She is excited.
- It's a good look on Yoojung.
- It's a good look.
- You look cute.
Yoojung, let's make a record.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
Set.
Cham, cham, cham
(Here comes Yoojung!)
(She is carefree despite the paint
on her both cheeks.)
Cham, cham, cham
(The Cham, Cham, Cham novice)
(Se Chan dodges expertly.)
- You punk!
- What was that?
- Hold on.
- You need to play fair!
- Why did you do that?
Why did you hit him?
- Come here.
- Why did you hit him?
(Yoojung reaches the end.)
It's over.
What happened?
Yoojung, you look cute.
You look cute.
- You look cute. You look cute.
- It's okay.
- I am okay.
- Are you okay?
- This is nice.
- Yoojung is okay.
You look cute.
- You should take a selfie.
- Do I look okay?
Yes, you do.
It looks like Yoojung is
at a festival.
(Yoojung looks like
someone at a festival.)
- Who wants to go next?
- Chungha will go next.
Let's get ready.
I am worried!
- Get ready.
- I can't wait.
Cham, cham, cham
(He is off to a good start.)
- He is good.
- Cham, cham, cham
Cham, cham, cham
(Motionless)
(Jae Suk doesn't move.)
(Jae Suk didn't move.)
He didn't play the game.
- Cham, cham, cham
- He didn't play the game.
This is ridiculous!
You can't stand motionless!
- You have to play!
- What?
- Why won't you play?
Come on and play.
You have to play!
- What?
- You have to play.
Come on and play.
You can stay motionless too.
Say, "Cham, cham, cham."
I thought you were
a cardboard cutout for a second.
(Chungha got covered in paint
in the meantime.)
- Is staying motionless an option?
- Then hit me.
- Yes, it is.
It's an option.
Why wouldn't it be an option?
I am sorry.
I didn't know
staying motionless was an option.
Jong Kook, you are up next.
Is it my turn?
- Mijoo, let's go.
- Let's go.
I am scared.
Get ready.
Cham, cham, cham
Okay.
(Hitting)
(Dizzy)
My goodness.
- Cham, cham, cham
- My goodness.
(People fall like leaves in autumn.)
Cham, cham, cham
(It hurts.)
What are you doing?
Come here.
- Cham, cham, cham
- It's over.
My goodness.
- Mijoo.
- She is Harley Quinn.
- Hey,
you look really cool.
You look really cool.
- Hey.
- You look really cool.
- You look incredible.
- My goodness.
- Harley Quinn.
- Team Jong Kook...
had a better record the last time
with 13 seconds.
(13 seconds will be their record.)
What's our record?
- You failed.
- What? We failed?
- Oh, you are right.
Chorong, let's go. Let's go.
We failed earlier.
Doesn't she have a showcase later?
- My goodness.
- She has a showcase later.
- Don't do it.
- You don't need to do it.
No, no. She wants to do it.
If she doesn't do it,
- she will regret it.
- Suk Jin.
- Don't make her do it.
- She has a showcase.
- I am not making her do it.
You should do it once more.
- If I do it once more...
- Do it once more.
- Suk Jin,
Chorong's staff members
are ready to destroy you.
Chorong's staff members...
are sticking pins
into your voodoo doll.
"What is up with that punk?"
I want Chorong to experience
the variety show.
If you aren't going to do it,
let's stop.
In that case, shall we stop?
(He is cool.)
My goodness.
That's not a bad idea.
(Bomi and Chorong of Apink had
a good showcase after the shoot.)
- Chorong has a showcase.
- You are the absolute worst.
- You look cute.
- Give me an opportunity.
- Seriously.
- Ji Hyo.
- Make Se Chan go.
- This time, Ji Hyo should play...
- Cham, Cham, Cham.
- Se Chan will get the paint.
Se Chan, go on the conveyor belt.
Go on.
Ji Hyo, let's do this.
(Her enthusiasm flares up.)
Ji Hyo, let's go.
Let's go! Se Chan, I'll be serious.
- Okay.
- Seriously.
Cham, cham, cham
(She's very passionate
about this game.)
(They dance to
the "Cham, Cham, Cham" beats.)
Cham, cham, cham
(Falling)
Hold on.
- What's going on?
- What's this?
- What do I do?
- That's so weird.
- Your ears!
- Cham, cham, cham
Cham, cham, cham
- Hey.
(She keeps singing to the beat
regardless.)
- Cham, cham, cham
- Hey.
What was that?
- Cham, cham, cham
- Hey.
- Se Chan!
- What was that?
There was a speed bump!
- Why is there a speed bump?
Why did this fall?
What happened, Se Chan?
Your record is unchanged
from before.
Sure.
What?
- Okay.
- What was that?
- Get back together.
- My gosh.
- We might be top three.
You never know.
These are the results of
I Am Coming to Save You.
1st place is
Haha and Bomi with 12 seconds.
(Top three couples get to
search for money.)
Second place is
Mijoo and Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook and Mijoo are
2nd place team.)
- We didn't do bad.
- Third place is...
- Chungha and Kwang Soo.
- Okay!
(Kwang Soo and Chungha are
3rd place team.)
This was doable.
- Let's get started.
- Kwang Soo, did you find the money?
Get started.
- You have to get started.
- Do I go?
(Which team will bring back most
amount of money in 100 seconds?)
There's a bundle here.
(Search time is over.)
First, Team Jong Kook stole
22 dollars.
- That's not bad.
- True.
Team Kwang Soo stole 35 dollars.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- They didn't find anything.
- We had bundles.
They didn't find anything.
- They did.
- They were searching outside.
They found something inside.
I'm so mad.
I found nothing.
- He found nothing.
- Haha didn't find anything.
- Really?
- I thought Bomi found some.
- They found none?
- Yes.
We looked everywhere,
and there was nothing.
- Well, then...
- You get a hint though.
- It's important.
- I'll give you a hint.
Okay.
- Hints are really important.
- They really are.
- You'll find out it's not me.
- I think it is you.
(What is this hint about?)
(Fussy personality with
a nasty temper, Top star)
(Haha...)
- That's nonsense.
- No, it's not me.
We have to eat.
(Is this hint about the greedy one
pointing to Haha?)
(Fussy personality
with a nasty temper)
(Top star pose)
(She's full of doubt.)
This does sound like me, but this is
not what people perceive me as.
You're going to regret it.
I'm serious. I swear.
Kwang Soo.
Three top teams can eat.
Let's see how it tastes.
- This looks so good.
- It looks so good.
(Fatsia shoot bibimmyeon and meat
contain the scent of the spring.)
Excuse me, Yoojung.
- Are you eating by yourself?
- Eat this.
- Okay.
- She told me to eat by myself.
Bomi wants to eat too.
- No, it's okay.
- Have one.
It's fatsia shoot.
This is really good, Yoojung.
How much is this?
I want it for a dollar.
(The combination of bibimmyeon
and rolled meat are amazing.)
Two dollars.
What is this scent?
- Is this fatsia shoot?
- Are you done?
- Yes.
- This is so good.
Let's clean up
and move onto the next mission.
- Okay.
- That was good.
Do you...
Do you have enough ingredients?
No.
I'll pay with my own money.
I want to take it to go.
That was really good.
Do you have some cash?
I didn't bring my wallet.
- Don't be so cheap.
- Go get cleaned up.
Can we get cleaned up?
Bring a camera over here.
Wait. I can talk to them personally.
Do you own a restaurant?
(There are cameras on them already.)
Are you going to eat this?
No.
Are you going to throw it away?
You can throw it away in my mouth.
Is it done?
Here.
It's okay.
(They move onto the next mission
as the staff members are watching.)
This is the final race, Find Me.
(Final Race of Did You Even Eat
Before the Race? Find Me)
"Me"?
The couple that can
put together the hints...
hidden in various places
and eliminate the greedy one wins.
I see.
However, every five minutes,
there will be
the night of the greedy one.
- This is when...
- I'm scared.
everybody will be blindfolded
and freeze on the spot.
Only the greedy one will be free to
move around and eliminate people...
- in the order that they assigned.
- There's an order.
(Eliminate one at a time?)
- In the assigned order?
- They have already shared...
the order with the staff.
- Already?
- We're in trouble.
Jong Kook is number one.
I think I'm near the beginning.
Once it's the night
of the greedy one,
you cannot move or make any noise.
If your name tag gets ripped,
you cannot resist.
This is going to be insane.
If you accidentally rip
the name tag...
of a normal person,
the one whose name tag got ripped
will be eliminated.
Plus, the night of the greedy one
will start immediately.
Oh, dear. You also get eliminated?
The person who attacked will live,
but it'll be night again.
Person who got attacked is
eliminated.
- This is really scary.
- Each couple...
will move to separate spots.
Let's go.
(The identity of the greedy one is
still a mystery.)
The sky is so clear today.
Look, Yoojung.
- It's a clear day.
- Hurrah!
(She shouts "hurrah" for 3 seconds.)
(Her refreshing "hurrah" echoes
in the surrounding.)
You're definitely an idol star.
You definitely are. This is great.
Can't you do that too?
Be cute. Try it.
- Be cute?
- Say, "hurrah".
(Hur...)
Hur...
You have a husky voice.
Your voice sounds like
it got blocked.
(She sounds very husky.)
- That's good.
- Hurrah!
We're enjoying our time too.
- Her tone is different.
- Hurrah!
I know.
There's something stuck here.
(The girl crush comes from
her husky voice.)
Are you very interested in health?
I am, but not excessively.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
They're unstylish, hot,
- They're fussy...
- fussy...
with a nasty temper.
It's Jong Kook. It has to be him
according to the hints.
Is he really interested in health?
Yes, I'm very interested in health.
Very much.
- You're very interested.
- This is really strange.
I'm very interested.
Exactly.
It's you.
It's not.
- Be honest, okay?
- Yes.
- It's not you, right?
- My gosh.
This person is
very interested in health.
I heard...
she's religious about
taking her supplements.
Is it okay to doubt your partner?
- I want to ask you.
- I think it's you.
Bomi and Haha are a team,
but Bomi was
still suspicious of Haha.
- Oh, really?
- She was suspicious of him,
so I am too.
They also had a chance
to find money,
but they didn't find a penny.
That was deliberate.
Also, they put
all the money together.
- That too.
- It's a dangerous thing to do.
If it ends up being you,
I'm going to feel so betrayed.
It won't be.
Think carefully. How many of us
are there including the guests?
- How many teams are there?
- There are around 10 of us.
There are 12 people.
There's only one greedy one.
That one person has to
eliminate 11 people.
Who do you think can do that?
Great reasoning.
Think about it. It has to be
Jong Kook. We have to eliminate him.
(Haha is suspicious of Jong Kook.)
(Is the greedy one among them?)
Let's get started.
- My goodness!
- Race starts...
in 5, 4,
3, 2, 1.
- Race starts.
- Let's go.
(Race starts.)
We're just starting.
We have to find hints.
Chungha,
let's share the hints we find.
Sure. Should we split?
We can split or go around together.
Chungha.
(Did she find a hint already?)
(She finds a hint
as soon as the game starts.)
- This person likes music.
- What?
This person likes music.
Music.
(This person likes music.)
This is insane.
(The greedy one likes music?)
From the members,
Jae Suk really likes music.
Really?
Hey, who do you think it is?
- Suk Jin, we found one.
- A hint?
Yes. I don't think it's you.
I'm not. What's the hint?
This person likes music.
(He shares the hint Chungha found.)
Music.
I think it's Jae Suk.
(Suk Jin is suspicious of
Jae Suk as well.)
- He really likes music.
- True.
He plays music
on his Bluetooth speaker.
What night is it again?
We have to find hints
before that night comes.
- Night of the greedy one.
(Potential candidate for the greedy
one approaches them.)
This is driving me crazy.
Where will the hints be?
How do you find them?
I found it!
(She finds a hint under the shells.)
(What does her hint say?)
I'm certain. This is over.
Right? This reminds me of him.
Jong Kook?
(This person raises their voice
frequently.)
Okay.
(Is Jong Kook the greedy one
because he raises his voice?)
I don't think it'll be here.
Is it not on that side?
We hid some on that side too.
This side?
- Check it out.
- Okay.
(Jong Kook looks for hints
harder than ever.)
- I found one.
- Really?
(Jong Kook finds a hint.)
(He finds a hint under a chair.)
I knew it.
(The hint says...)
(This person has a soft voice.)
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- What does it say?
What does it say?
(What does the hint say?)
"This person has a soft voice."
Mijoo, it's not like that.
It doesn't make sense.
Listen.
It can be anyone. We're all singers.
Am I wrong?
Is there a singer
who doesn't have a soft voice?
But your voice is way too soft.
No, it's not like that.
Jong Kook is getting
more and more suspicious.
I should... Look at him.
He's looking so hard for hints.
(Is Jong Kook the greedy one
and pretending to look for hints?)
- The first night of the greedy one.
- What's going on?
Already?
It's the night of the greedy one.
It's the night of the greedy one?
Really?
I'm too remote.
(A member chosen by the greedy one
will be eliminated.)
(Everyone has to stay
where he or she is.)
Okay.
Please put on your blindfolds.
(Everyone has to put on
a blindfold.)
This is not a bad place to be.
(No one is allowed
to fight the greedy one back.)
(The first night of the greedy one)
(Who is the greedy one
going to eliminate first?)
Gosh, I'm scared.
Please don't rip my name tag off.
(In the darkness, fear creeps in.)
- Oh, my.
- What happened?
Who is it?
Kwang Soo, are you out?
(Kwang Soo's name tag
has been ripped off.)
Unbelievable.
(It happened so fast.)
Who ripped it off?
That means the greedy one
is near us.
He or she is extremely close by.
I'm scared.
Is it morning yet?
When will it be morning?
(Yoojung is about to cry.)
(Everyone is terrified.)
I'm scared to death.
Where am I being taken to?
(Only 5 minutes in,
Kwang Soo is taken to prison.)
I'm clueless. Who is the greedy one?
(The first target of the greedy one,
Kwang Soo, is out.)
You can take off
your blindfolds now.
(The first night of the greedy one
is over.)
Kwang Soo was taken away
right before my eyes.
Gosh, what a scary world we live in.
- Weren't you right next to him?
- I was.
After a ripping noise,
Kwang Soo screamed.
- What happened?
- Unbelievable.
Kwang Soo was right next to me.
- I only heard a ripping noise.
- I heard someone approaching.
The hint I have
points to one person.
- Mine too.
Who are you suspecting?
- One of the members, right?
- Yes.
- Jong Kook.
- Right?
It's definitely Jong kook.
I think so too.
I'm sure of it.
The greedy one is
supposed to have decided...
the order of people
to be eliminated beforehand.
- That's right.
- It was decided beforehand.
I'm sure the greedy one
is Jong Kook.
- I'm sure too.
- Guys!
- Who was near Kwang Soo?
- What?
- The greedy one must be a woman.
- Why?
Don't you think the rules were
made for a woman?
(Jong Kook insists
the greedy one must be a woman.)
(If you think about it...)
But I was next to Kwang Soo.
Chorong and I were next to him.
Chorong too?
- Chorong too.
- Then it could be Chorong.
Really? Then it could be Chorong.
- It could be Chorong.
- No.
(Chorong was
one of the candidates.)
- It could be Chorong.
- Chorong...
Another night of the greedy one
starts in two minutes.
- Let's go.
- Yoojung, where are you?
- I'm scared.
I'm going to go hide.
I think I'm the next target.
- Could there be a hint here?
- Let's hurry up.
Jae Suk.
Where's Jong Kook?
- You know I'm not the greedy one.
- It's obvious.
Look at this.
It's definitely Jong Kook.
- He must have deceived me.
- What did you find?
- He rushed back to where he was.
- Of course.
- I mean...
- That must be it.
I'll pretend I have no idea.
(Mijoo is searching for a hint.)
(She finds...)
(Jong Kook behind the tent.)
(Startled)
What are you doing?
- Why do you look so creepy?
- The thing is,
the greedy one must be checking...
where his or her next target is.
(What's Jong Kook's identity?)
I'm sure Jong Kook is
the greedy one.
He is the only one
who raises his voice.
(What is this?)
Someone already
rummaged through this place.
Could a hint be here?
(Bomi finds a frame
with an R mark on it.)
I wonder...
Wait. What is this?
What does this even mean?
(What does it say?)
(All-knowing and all-powerful)
I mean...
Why is this written
with Chinese characters?
(Why is this written
with Chinese characters?)
(Other tents have...)
(framed Chinese characters too.)
(What's the secret
of these framed Chinese characters?)
What's this?
(Bomi asks Haha
what the Chinese characters mean.)
Do you know what it means?
- This must be a hint. Wait.
- Exactly.
But I can't read it.
Do you have any idea?
What could it be?
What's this character?
(Ignorant and incapable)
I can't read a single character.
(To be honest,
I can't read a single character.)
Let's ask someone like Suk Jin.
Suk Jin!
No.
(The old man, Suk Jin,
is making a guess.)
- It's the night of the greedy one.
- Again?
(It's the night of the greedy one
again.)
Please don't come near me.
(Yoojung overreacts.)
(Who will be eliminated this time?)
Who are you?
(Ripping)
(Mijoo,)
(the greedy one's second target,
is out.)
You can take off
your blindfolds now.
Who was eliminated this time?
Is it over? Was someone eliminated?
Innocent citizen Mijoo is out.
Who?
Mijoo is out.
(Shocked)
Who eliminated Mijoo?
(The greedy one is eliminating
the citizens one by one.)
All of a sudden, Mijoo is out?
Mijoo!
She's not dead or anything.
(Crying)
Yoojung.
Who is it?
Where was Mijoo?
Hold on.
Who ripped her name tag off?
(Jong Kook has been hiding
in a remote place.)
Jong Kook has been very talkative.
(Jong Kook has been very talkative.)
He's been suspicious.
I want to rip his name tag off.
Should we try that?
- I'll try to rip his name tag off.
- Okay.
Suk Jin.
This time, I was hiding.
- I thought I was the second target.
- But...
there is already a list...
- of people to eliminate.
- Exactly.
It's already been decided
by the greedy one.
(Bomi sneaks up on Jong Kook.)
What happened?
Bomi was with us.
(Jong Kook's name tag
is ripped off.)
Whose name tag is ripped off?
(No one saw this coming.)
What did you do?
You're the greedy one.
(Confident)
(If Jong Kook is the greedy one,)
(Haha and Bomi win.)
(If he isn't,
he will be eliminated.)
(Jong Kook shakes his head.)
(What does Jong Kook's reaction
mean?)
(Is Jong Kook the greedy one
as many expected?)
Jong Kook isn't the greedy one.
(Jong Kook is not the greedy one.)
He isn't?
(Then who is it?)
Jong Kook...
But the hints...
The hints were...
too obvious. It can't be me.
Innocent citizen Jong Kook is out.
(Does that mean the greedy one is
one of these three?)
With innocent citizen Jong Kook out,
it's the night of the greedy one
again.
(Everyone is more and more confused
about the greedy one's identity.)
(The greedy one's
third target is...)
(Ji Hyo.)
(The order of elimination is...)
(Kwang Soo, Mijoo, and Ji Hyo.)
(Innocent citizen Ji Hyo is out.)
- Innocent citizen Ji Hyo is out.
- Who?
Ji Hyo is out.
Poor Ji Hyo.
(Ji Hyo is out too.)
Ji Hyo is out.
I knew she wasn't the greedy one.
Jae Suk, I'll say this in front of
everyone. You're the greedy one.
- I'm sure...
- I'm not.
All the hints point to you.
The greedy one is
supposed to be unstylish.
- That's why I suspected you two.
- You're unstylish.
(That's why I suspected you two.)
- I'm so confused.
- Hey.
You're unstylish,
and you love music.
- He's interested in health too.
- You're interested in health too.
But I'm not too interested
in health.
- What about you?
- What about me?
You're not as stylish
as you used to be anymore.
(You're not as stylish
as you used to be anymore.)
You've become unstylish too.
Compared to before...
To be honest, the most unstylish one
is Se Chan.
- When I saw that hint,
- Se Chan's face is unstylish.
- My face is unstylish.
- I thought it meant Se Chan.
- But I'm not the greedy one.
- I mean...
Who is the greedy one?
I have no idea.
I'm getting angry.
Like you said, I think it's a woman.
Is it a woman?
The rules would be too easy...
- if the greedy one is a man.
- It'd be easy to win.
It felt like the person was...
- used to ripping off name tags.
- No.
Apink has been on Running Man
many times already.
Also, none of
the Running Man members...
would rip off a name tag that way.
We don't rip it off so quickly.
- Do you?
- You're right.
- We'd grab the shirt.
- Exactly.
Also, we don't want
the others to find out.
We would have ripped it off quietly.
That's a good guess.
(Is the greedy one
one of the guests?)
You're the greedy one, aren't you?
Goodness. Yoojung, I'm not.
- Do you swear?
- Gosh.
- Hand on your heart?
- I swear.
I don't see a hint anywhere.
I can't believe this brat.
- It's not me.
- I found one.
I swear it's not me.
- It's Jae Suk.
- It has to be him.
I think it is.
I'm sure it's him.
Hey, rip off Jae Suk's name tag.
Should I?
Try ripping it off.
(He looks around.)
(Chorong approaches him alone
so that he doesn't notice.)
Chorong, would you like some water?
- I have no idea who it is.
- Thank you.
(He gives her water
without asking why she's here.)
If you rip off the wrong person's
name tag, you don't die, right?
You don't.
(He answers kindly.)
(Then...)
I'll rip off your name tag then.
(Ripping)
(She ripped off
Jae Suk's name tag.)
I'll rip off your name tag then.
Sorry.
(He got attacked in the blink
of an eye. What is his identity?)
- Sorry.
- Hey!
(He was not the greedy one!)
What's wrong with you?
Innocent citizen Jae Suk is out,
so the night
of the greedy one has come.
I told you it wasn't me, Chorong.
I didn't know.
- Is it really not you?
- It's not.
(Everybody was suspicious of
Jae Suk, but it wasn't him.)
Chorong, you're driving me nuts.
(The candidates get narrowed down
quickly now.)
We're not sure,
so let's narrow it down.
(Chorong is one of the surviving
candidates for the greedy one.)
It felt like somebody
who had ripped off name tags before.
But Apink has been
on Running Man many times.
(Her movement was decisive
with no pauses.)
(Is she the greedy one?)
(The night of the greedy one has
come again.)
It wasn't Jae Suk?
(Sobbing)
(He was a good partner.)
- I told you it wasn't me!
- What now?
(She's really nervous.)
(Ripping)
(Chungha is eliminated
on the night of the greedy one.)
Whoever it is,
their plan is working great.
Trust nobody!
(He gets eliminated by
the greedy one.)
I think it's Chorong.
(Yoojung was wailing every time.)
(She gets eliminated
with a short cry as well.)
You'll move to jail
with your blindfold on.
Okay.
(Running Man is
such a sad variety show.)
Wait. Who's left?
- Haha.
- Haha and...
- Haha, Se Chan,
- Se Chan,
- Chorong, and Bomi.
- It's 1 of them.
- There are 4 left.
- I think it's Chorong.
- Me too.
Who breathes heavily?
- They breathed heavily for me too.
- Haha breathes heavily.
- Like that.
Because he has asthma.
(Haha breathes heavily
from the members.)
(Meanwhile, Haha is...)
It's "all-knowing and all-powerful".
I found it.
All-knowing and all-powerful.
(He interprets the hint
in 10 minutes.)
(They need more hints
to narrow down the greedy one.)
Why is this here? This is so random.
(The shells under the pine tree
are strange.)
What is this?
(The shells under the pine tree
are strange.)
What's this?
What's the R mark?
(He looks closely, and there's an R
which signifies a hint.)
(That means this shell is a hint.)
(Why did Se Chan,
who doesn't like to think, find it?)
Haha!
(He asks Haha
who's slightly smarter.)
What is this?
(They finally turn their eyes
to the hints in the campground.)
(What!)
(There's an R mark on the light bulb
around the tree too?)
Hey! Come here. Quick.
I solved this.
It's all-knowing
and all-powerful. Wait.
This.
This was on the light bulb.
All-knowing and all-powerful?
- What's this?
- What's that?
- A shell.
- A shell?
What's all-knowing and all-powerful?
Where was that?
- All-knowing and all-powerful.
- Chorong. She's Catholic.
No way.
Religion all of a sudden?
All-knowing and all-powerful.
Light bulb and what's this?
- A shell.
- A shell?
Jeon So Ran? Jeon...
- So Ran.
- Jeon So Ran.
- Jeon So Min?
- Jeon So Min.
I told you. Excuse me.
- Right.
- I told you it's So Min.
- How'd she rip off our names tags?
- I told you it's her.
(What is he talking about?)
Suk Jin,
I have this weird idea.
Can it be So Min?
No way. She can't walk right now.
I must be out of my mind.
(His idea was dismissed,
and he left it at that.)
- Shell.
- Shell?
- Haha.
- Light bulb starts with "jeon".
- Shell starts with "so".
- Right.
("Jeon", "jeon", and "so")
(Do these hints point to So Min?)
- I got chills.
- So it's not Chorong?
I don't think it is.
(The identity of the greedy one
finally gets revealed.)
But one of you is greedy
and wants to take all the prizes.
- Someone is greedy. Who is it?
- Unbelievable.
(So Min is the greedy one.)
(All the hints
they had today were...)
"I'm a bit hot and unstylish."
(It's a line
from a book So Min published.)
Excuse me.
I'm very interested in health.
(This person is
very interested in health.)
Why does it have to be him?
(From the series
"Something About 1 Percent")
He has a fussy personality
with a nasty temper.
Oh, dear. A top star is here!
(On "Top Star U-Back",
she said "top star" many times.)
(During the race,
testimonies about the greedy one...)
(This person likes music.)
(This person raises their voice
frequently.)
(This person has a soft voice.)
(These are words
from her manager and stylist.)
(Please tell me
a characteristic about So Min.)
(There were hints around
the campground as well.)
(All these items start with "jeon".)
(All these items start with "so".)
(All these items start with "min".)
(Jeon So Min)
(This is the order I would like.
Kwang Soo first for sure.)
(So Min decided on the order
of elimination as well.)
(Then Mijoo.)
(The judges eliminated people
on behalf of So Min.)
(And then Ji Hyo.)
(Jae Suk then Jong Kook.)
(She had dreams of
becoming the star of 500th episode.)
(We miss the greedy So Min.)
How do we win then?
We have to find her.
How do we find her?
Wait, can she return already?
(He walks toward
the life-sized figure.)
(She can't be here in person.)
This is unbelievable.
- Haha.
- What?
Why? What is it?
- Gosh.
- What? Why?
What's this?
She had a name tag on her back.
860407.
(So Min decided
how the winners will be selected.)
The couple that finds that password
on my life-sized figure...
and opens the safe...
wins today's race.
- It's her birthday.
- Birthday.
- This is her birthday.
- It is.
860407.
(The person
who opens the safe first wins.)
- This is her birthday.
- It is.
I'm getting dizzy.
(Today's winner opened the safe
3 minutes later.)
(Who is today's winner?)
Race is over.
What happened?
- What's going on?
- How did this end?
- I got chills. It almost killed me.
- What is it?
I want to know.
(Nobody but the people involved
know the result.)
- Everybody.
- Yes.
This is the 500th episode,
but she could not join us,
so So Min planned the race herself.
The greedy one was So Min.
(This was 500th episode special
by So Min.)
She is actually the most greedy one.
- Right?
- I know.
She's kind of unstylish too.
We were so confused at that.
She likes music.
The winning couple
of today's race is...
(He announces the couple
that defeated So Min and won.)
The winning couple is...
(The person who opened the safe
and their partner are winners.)
- It's Se Chan and Ji Hyo.
- Come on!
(Se Chan and Ji Hyo win.)
- It's Se Chan and Ji Hyo.
- Come on!
(Se Chan won?)
What happened?
How did that happen?
- Today...
- What happened?
(Thanks to Se Chan,
Ji Hyo won unknowingly.)
(He realized that So Min's birthday
was the password to the safe.)
(He opened it.)
(This is the prize So Min prepared.)
What's this?
What's this? Hold on.
(The prize So Min got is...)
- She sent an invitation as well.
- Okay.
You were like her hands and feet.
No, no.
I also...
"You are invited to So Min's house."
- This is yours.
- I was wondering...
what this was.
"You are invited to So Min's house,"
and her door code is on it.
- Se Chan has to go then.
- Is he going?
You have to go
and take a picture with her.
- What?
- You have to take a picture.
- It's a penalty.
- It is.
I'm relieved I didn't win.
I think this is perfect for Se Chan.
I agree.
This is a great chance.
(They call So Min
who invited Se Chan.)
Jae Suk.
Writer Jeon.
- We're filming.
- Well,
- I can't believe you did all this.
- What is this?
- What was that?
- What did you do?
We spoke on the phone earlier.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- It worked out well.
- Good job.
Do you know who won?
Who?
Se Chan.
(Shrieking)
High tone.
- You sound happy.
- She sounds happy.
What's all this?
She's happy.
Why is it him?
- It just happened.
- It's strange.
- I have a question.
- Sure.
Why was Kwang Soo first?
I want to see his face
the least these days.
I didn't even get a chance to win.
I was eliminated five minutes
into the race.
Everybody is worried about you,
so please say a few words
to the viewers.
Don't worry too much.
I'll get better quickly
and come back.
Thank you, So Min. See you later.
See you later.
- See you.
- Bye.
Anyhow,
thank you to the 5 guests who
joined us for our 500th episode.
- Great work.
- Let's go.
- Good luck.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
Yoojung.
(This is the 1st time in 10 years.)
(1st Running Man Quiz
for the Ultimate Winner)
(They are joined by actors
who played detective roles.)
(Lee Yi Kyung, Kwak Si Yang)
(Park Hyo Ju, Ha Yeon Ju)
(This quiz sums up
the 10-year history of Running Man.)
(For Running Man, By Running Man,
the unprecedented quiz special)
(However,)
(their level of knowledge is
too shallow for the quiz show.)
(Tteokbbokki)
(It becomes a competitive race
to escape last place.)
(Is Cavewoman Ji Hyo the only one
to get the English question right?)
(Somebody here knows
the answers to all questions.)
(Anyone can be a cheater
if they're off their guard.)
(The detectives are out
to single out the cheater.)
(Who are the best members
to answer the question?)
(The 1st Running Man's
Ultimate Quiz Show)