(We are realizing...)
(the value of things that we take for granted.)
- Hello. - Hello.
We're shooting the opening in the open air after a long time.
- The weather is really nice. - It's really good.
(We're thankful of...)
Weather like this doesn't last for long.
(seasons that always come back.)
It's a fine fall day.
- The weather is really nice. - Look at the sky.
Se Chan broke my spirits...
- this morning. - Why?
- He told me some bad news. - Why? What is it?
I promised her to set her up with a guy.
- You mean So Min? - Yes.
But it turns out he has a girlfriend.
(It turns out her date has a girlfriend.)
Hey, why would you set her up with a guy who has a girlfriend?
(That was dangerous.)
- I didn't know that. - He's strange.
So here's what I think.
I think Se Chan has a crush on me.
Gosh, this is what you wanted to say.
(Flustered)
- My gosh. - He's...
- She's scary. - You just can't stop smiling.
Gosh, no.
- I should hide my gums. - I think he likes me.
He keeps interrupting me.
(So Min penetrates through Se Chan's gum.)
I'm not interrupting you. I just didn't know that.
- Why did you not check it first? - Right.
- I was going to... - Ji Hyo is here.
(When the blue sky becomes pink,)
- Ji Hyo is coming. - Hello.
(the rest of the members arrive.)
- Ji Hyo. - Hi, Ji Hyo.
- Jong Kook is here too. - He's wearing long pants.
- Hey. - It looks like a thimble.
I was told to dress like this. A white shirt and jeans.
(Today's dress code: white shirt and jeans)
- A white shirt and jeans. - Jeans.
(The match of century heated up the social media last week.)
Right. I saw that.
What? Did you guys compare your looks?
(Haha compared his looks with Kwang Soo's while drunk.)
(- Haha is good looking. - Kwang Soo is more handsome.)
- He asked who looked better. - Haha posted it...
- on his social media. - Why did you guys do that?
I didn't do it.
(The forever appearance rivals)
- I don't even care about him. - We both think...
- Why did you two do such a thing? - I didn't start it.
(They pretend not to mind each other.)
- I didn't even care. - But he added a comment.
- It ended with my victory. - Really?
(Confident)
(He started it alone and ended it alone.)
Because you started it.
That's because it was your account.
He wrote comments only to those who supported him.
You're the worst.
- I mean... - He's so sly.
(He manipulated the public opinion.)
You're the worst.
He didn't say anything to those who mentioned my name.
(It automatically filtered comments that favored Kwang Soo.)
- I can see that. - And...
I wasn't going to say this,
but you two can't make a bet like that.
You guys can't even make the cut.
- Jae Suk. - You mean their level.
You can't even be compared with us.
I have the rankings of the members in mind.
This is frustrating.
Only those who are high in ranks can do this.
(Ignoring)
- You're mistaken. - It's not that you're ugly.
But you're just okay.
And you're ugly.
Gosh, no. I'm not ugly.
(The appearance match is on.)
Actually, this is what we've been curious about.
I wonder how the two female members would rank their looks.
(Who do Ji Hyo and So Min think is handsome?)
Gosh, that doesn't matter.
- Are you asking seriously? - Objectively...
Are you being serious?
- I know. It can be subjective. - This is hard for me.
I can't decide anything before seeing them naked.
- What is she talking about? - My gosh.
- Hey. - No, that's not what I mean.
(Don't take it wrong.)
- Just consider our looks. - I mean...
You look different only with a hat. Haha is wearing many items.
(I want to rate you by your original look.)
The rankings decided by Ji Hyo and So Min...
(Acting cool)
mean nothing to me.
- That's true. - Right?
At least I can pick the worst member.
(Staring)
Who is it?
(Laughing)
She's looking at Suk Jin.
(So Min thinks Suk Jin is the ugliest in Running Man.)
Suk Jin.
- Come here. - I think...
(She picks Suk Jin with no hesitation.)
Suk Jin.
- Come here. - I think...
- I can't believe this. Hey! - It's just her taste.
Hey, you're really...
(Calm down, ugly man.)
- It's her taste. - You are not objective at all.
Just admit it.
(Jae Suk is ranked 5th.)
- So Suk Jin is the last. - The fifth...
The fifth place is Jae Suk.
Do I look worse than him?
(They're both offended.)
I don't care whom she picks.
The two Petty Gang members are out.
The two members of Petty Gang are out.
(Jae Suk's ranked 5th. Suk Jin's ranked 6th.)
Continue. Who's next?
The fourth is Kwang Soo.
(So Min rates Kwang Soo as 4th.)
Come on.
Gosh, that can't be right.
This is getting more strange.
(They're in the upper ranks.)
Gosh, thank you.
Are they the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd?
The third is Se Chan.
(They're ranked 3rd, 2nd, and 1st.)
The 2nd is Jong Kook, and the 1st is Haha.
- You're the best. - Okay.
(Sullen)
- Third place isn't so bad. - This is ridiculous.
- It's just absurd. - It's not bad.
Are you guys standing together on purpose?
- What? - The three ugly members.
(The 3 ugly men always hang out together.)
- The three ugly members. - I'm not part of this.
- I'm out of this. - If you feel upset about it,
(If you get mad, you lose.)
it means you admit that So Min is right.
- Okay? - No, I don't.
(They're cute.)
You three are the ugly dolls of 2020.
- That's not it. - We want to do it as well.
(Revenge)
We will rank the female members.
(The 3 ugly men rate 2 female members.)
Stop it. Don't do that.
Number one is Ji Hyo.
- Who's the last? - The last is...
(Ji Hyo is ranked 1st. So Min is ranked last.)
- Jeon So Min. - Jeon So Min.
Song Ji Hyo is the best. Jeon So Min is the worst.
(Childish)
- Song Ji Hyo! - Song Ji Hyo!
(Ugly 3, 36, Ugly 2, 49, Ugly 1, 55)
(It's embarrassing to watch the 3 ugly men.)
We're being so childish.
Jeon So Min.
Did you see So Min blushing? She's moving.
Those with bad looks have bad characters.
- You should stop. - She's serious.
(You should stop when I'm still nice.)
Today, after the shoot,
we will wait for you in the alley.
- I will block your car. - We will attack you.
(The ugly men will block her way.)
I will stop your car.
- The ugly ones will get you. - You'll learn your lesson.
(Rank 1 is relaxed.)
They are unsociable.
Because they're unsociable?
Today, your choice will decide your fate.
(Introducing today's race)
It's called All or Nothing Race.
(All or Nothing Race)
You will have to make a choice in each mission.
(You will have to make a choice in each mission.)
According to your choice, you will get or return yut candy bars.
(According to your choice, you will get or return yut candy bars.)
- Candy bars? - The member with most candy bars...
(Top 3 with most candy bars will get a prize.)
will get a prize, and the one with least candy bars will...
(The one with the least candy bars...)
get a cumbersome and tiring penalty.
(will get a cumbersome and tiring penalty.)
- It's something tiresome. - I hate it.
(He prefers short and strong penalties.)
- I hate tiresome things. - It's going to be hard.
- But it can be annoying. - This is...
(They're at the age where they hate a hassle.)
I hate stuff like that.
The penalty is tiresome.
And you failed the mission in the Thief Race.
(Haha and So Min failed the thief mission 2 weeks ago.)
- Haha and So Min. - I've forgotten about it.
- Right. - If one of you...
(If one of them comes in last,)
becomes the last, you both will get the penalty.
(they both will get the penalty.)
And if you both don't become the last,
(If they both don't become the last,)
(the other last place and the person with the least...)
the last and one of you with fewer candy bars...
- will get the penalty together. - I'm getting a penalty today.
(candy bars will get the penalty.)
If Haha and So Min get the penalty together,
it will be best for us.
(Holding grudges)
- I agree. - It's a prize for us.
(The ugly guys aren't cool.)
It's a party.
That's the best gift.
- It's a festival. - Okay. Good.
So now you will make your first choice.
(It's time to make the first choice.)
Your choice will determine your costume for today.
(Choose your costume for today.)
It's called Running Man Haute Couture.
(Running Man Haute Couture)
Before the shoot, the production crew asked you...
(Before the shoot, the production crew asked them...)
to bring your clothes for another member.
(to bring their clothes for another member.)
You told us.
(Announcing the mission)
Hello?
Please bring an outfit of your fashion style...
that you want to recommend to this member to the next shoot.
They're going to wear my outfit?
Yes.
My fashion style is topless.
(Flustered)
Can I bring leggings?
You can bring anything you want.
(Worried)
- Did you bring your clothes? - Yes.
(They'll reveal their sense of fashion.)
- I'm serious about this. - You guys will soon...
choose your outfit randomly...
(They'll choose their outfit randomly...)
between what the members brought and what your stylist prepared.
(between what they brought and what their stylists prepared.)
And you will be wearing the outfit until the end of the shoot.
(They will be wearing the outfit until the end of the shoot.)
All day?
I hate it.
(Worried already)
We will bring in the outfits for you then.
(What do they want to recommend for each other?)
- Seriously, I... - Who brought outfits for me?
I brought a pretty one.
(They always boast before the start.)
- Mine is pretty too. - I brought a decent one.
- Guys. - Mine is just fine.
- I also brought a pretty one. - Mine is not funny.
Kwang Soo, go ahead.
(Kwang Soo reveals his outfit first.)
What's your outfit?
- What's that? - How do you put it on?
- What? - Darn it.
(There are holes.)
Actually, this is...
really good.
What's that? Is it for a beggar?
It looks horrible.
This is the oldest one I have.
(His favorite)
Is this how it's supposed to look?
No. It's worn out.
(Proud)
Are these moth holes?
They are not moth holes though.
(It's not vintage, but it's poverty.)
There's a story behind it.
And this is a zebra pattern. I made them myself in my 20s.
(Zebra pants...)
(Kwang Soo made it when he was in his 20s)
- Really? - Yes.
- Who would wear it? - It's sleeveless.
(Jong Kook likes sleeveless shirts.)
- Who's wearing it? - That's what Jong Kook likes.
- Gosh, no. - It looks cool though.
(You better not.)
Let's see who it is for.
(Who is the vintage outfit for?)
No way. It's Se Chan.
It's Jong Kook.
(Sleeveless shirt lover, Jong Kook)
See? It's for Jong Kook.
Jong Kook, you like sleeveless shirts.
(You like sleeveless shirts.)
He knew this would happen.
But this is too much.
Jong Kook loves sleeveless shirts.
- You'd look good in them. - I do love sleeveless shirts,
(He has his own limit.)
- but I have a standard. - This is your style.
They look better when you wear them.
- What's that? Is it for a beggar? - This is the oldest one I have.
(Kwang Soo's look from his 20s)
I made them myself in my 20s.
(Jae Suk reveals the outfit he prepared.)
Compared to what Kwang Soo brought,
- this is really pretty. I like it. - It's pretty.
- Cycling pants? - You wear them very often.
(Gray hooded shirt and black pants)
- I really like these clothes. - They really are Jae Suk's style.
(It's Jae Suk himself.)
- Jae Suk wears them all the time. - That's right.
- Suk Jin. - Gosh.
(It's for Suk Jin who loves Jae Suk.)
- That style is not bad. - It suits you. You'll look cute.
- I really like these clothes. - They really are Jae Suk's style.
(Jae Suk's style, Want-To-Be-Like-Jae Suk Style)
- Jae Suk wears them all the time. - That's right.
These are limited edition clothes.
(Suk Jin prepared the clothes...)
I brought the clothes I actually wore when I went to the airport...
that I told you about before.
(he wore at the airport.)
(Suk Jin's travel style is always unpredictable.)
(The ridiculous clothes he wore to the airport?)
- Oh, those ridiculous clothes? - Right.
They're really nice.
I remember his clothes...
(He went for the outfit that's kind of dressed up,)
- Look. These are... - That's the worst.
(but this looks like he never dressed up.)
I saw him in these clothes at the airport. He looked terrible.
- This is how I usually dress. - On a plane?
Look at the back of the pants.
(The clothes go to Se Chan.)
- Gosh, no. - Se Chan will wear them.
- You'll look okay. - This is too much.
If you wear them,
- you will look great. - Really?
Suk Jin, what's with this yellow stain?
(Don't get the wrong idea.)
What's with this stain?
Why? What is there?
Why?
(Suk Jin's style, "Am I at the Airport or My House?" Style)
Of course, I washed them.
- At least, they'll be comfortable. - I'm jealous.
First of all...
(So Min will reveal the style she brought.)
- I prepared everything... - What's that?
- What's that? - What's that?
Gosh. Here she goes again.
(What kind of clothes did she bring?)
She's being over the top again.
- This isn't included. - Look at that.
That's ridiculous.
(A skirt?)
- No way. - Are they for Ji Hyo?
- I'm sure they're for Ji Hyo. - She's being over the top again.
(Is that mine?)
- Look at this photo. - I customized this shirt.
(Custom-made T-shirt)
I think they're for Kwang Soo.
I think they're for Kwang Soo. Gosh.
- Is that a skirt? - It's a skirt.
(Sincerely flustered)
Wait. No. It might not be mind.
- Actually... - They're definitely for Kwang Soo.
I'd like you all to know that I even made this necklace by myself.
(She even brought the handmade necklace.)
- But why did you have to do that? - You didn't have to do that.
- I wanted to make him look pretty. - It's definitely Kwang Soo's.
Why would she bring a skirt?
I wanted to make him look pretty.
(Kwang Soo looks great in a skirt.)
Why would she bring a skirt?
I think he'll look pretty.
(She feels a bit sorry.)
- He'll look very pretty. - I don't care.
- Why did you bring me a skirt? - Because you have nice legs...
(She had her reasons.)
(Fishnet stockings)
- But So Min, it's a skirt... - She brought mesh stockings too.
I customized this shirt.
(So Min's style, hand-made accessory and customized shirt)
I even made this necklace by myself.
(Kwang Soo-Is-an-Entertainer Style)
- Next. - I think it's Jae Suk's.
(Se Chan reveals the clothes he brought.)
- I prepared these clothes. - I'm pretty sure it's Jae Suk's.
- What's this? - Or maybe...
(What's this now?)
- What's that? - Haha.
- I prepared... - There's a wig too.
(What is this style with a wig?)
- I like this style. - I brought...
- a suit. - It's nice.
- I wore these... - They must...
- fit me perfectly. - to impersonate Yim Jae Beom.
This is nice.
(Yim Jae Beom Style or Comedy Skit Style)
- On "Comedy Big League". - Oh, right.
This wig must be worn as well.
(One must wear the wig to complete the Comedy Skit Style.)
- It comes with the clothes. - Of course.
- But it must be too hot. - Did you pick Ji Hyo?
(Who will transform into Yim Jae Beom?)
- Did you hold onto it? - Yes.
(Ji Hyo will.)
Ji Hyo? I knew it.
Ji Hyo will wear them?
- Ji Hyo, try them on, okay? - Nice.
- Good choice. - Try them on.
It's perfect for her.
(Se Chan's style, What-Should-I-Do Style)
(Ji Hyo's clothes will be revealed.)
Ji Hyo, who will wear yours?
Ji Hyo dresses nicely in real life.
- They're nice. - It's pretty.
- Awesome. - I like them.
- That's nice. - It's pretty.
This is the best style.
(It's the only clothes they want to wear.)
- This is the ace style. - It's really pretty.
- That's what I wanted. - I...
- I hope it's me. - It's so pretty.
- Oh, it's me. - It's So Min.
(The most normal clothes go to So Min.)
- I like it. - It's cute.
- I might wear Jong Kook's clothes. - So Min is lucky.
(Thrilled)
She brought me mesh stockings. But she'll wear that?
(Control yourself.)
- I really like Ji Hyo's style. - You have nice legs.
I picked something that anyone can wear regardless of age and gender.
(Ji Hyo's style, It's-Pretty-If-It's-Comfy Style)
- Well, I... - Let's check out Jong Kook's.
(What clothes did Jong Kook bring?)
Nothing unique.
Oh, my. Look at that.
(A sleeveless shirt as usual)
- This is... - He brought a sleeveless shirt too.
That's what I wear to bed.
- This shirt... - It's Jong Kook's style.
- with shorts. - Jong Kook.
- The arm holes are too low. - Well...
- It's a good thing. - It looks comfortable though.
(The revealing shirt goes to...)
Could it be Jae Suk's?
(Haha.)
- It's Haha. - Gosh.
- His clothes are... - You like this kind of clothes.
(Jong Kook's style, Just-Jong-Kook Style)
- It's a tough guy style. - It's a sleeveless shirt.
With shorts.
- His clothes must be the worst. - I'm curious.
(It's time to reveal Haha's, and only Jae Suk is left.)
- You see, I... - I really hate his clothes.
To be honest,
I always knew...
that he's envious of me.
(Dumbfounded)
- He acts like this... - That's ridiculous.
- Because he's envious of you. - You know how little boys...
- hit the girl they like... - I know what you mean.
- for no reason. - They'd make the girl cry.
- And they interrupt a game. - Exactly.
I realized how that must feel.
I seriously hate his clothes.
(Haha's recommended clothes that Jae Suk hates)
You all have seen this shirt.
I wore this for the opening.
(It's a see-through shirt.)
- Actually... - He wore that not long ago.
(He wore this exact same shirt 2 weeks ago.)
Actually,
you don't wear anything under this shirt.
Are you out of your mind?
- But I was considerate of him. - Right.
You know he has a physical flaw.
(He let Jae Suk hide his physical flaw.)
I was considerate of him...
and decided to bring a white shirt to wear under it.
- What about the pants? - I brought these wide-leg pants.
(And the wide-leg pants that Jae Suk hates)
What's this?
- That's cool. - Try it on.
(Haha's look,)
I always knew that he's envious of me.
(Conservative Boy's Deviation Style)
Here are the normal clothes that your stylists prepared.
(The normal clothes prepared by the members' stylists)
The person who chooses the clothes sit in the chair.
(If 1 person sits down facing forward,)
The others hang...
(the others will mix the tops and bottoms.)
the tops and bottoms of both styles...
under number 1 or 2 as you like.
Then we could mix the different styles.
- That's possible. - Really?
Both the top and bottom So Min picked for me are weird.
(Kwang Soo's clothes are just a mismatch.)
Cheer up. You never know.
Okay.
(Se Chan goes first.)
- Choose anything. - My clothes are not imposing.
Is it stretchy?
Yes, it's stretchy.
(Interested)
It can stretch a lot.
I think Jong Kook actually likes my clothes.
- He checked the fabric... - Hey, it wasn't like that.
(Touching)
- I want to know if it fits me. - It'll fit you.
Of course, I considered things like that.
(What will happen to the zebra pants?)
I don't think it'll fit me.
Trust me. It's stretchy.
Se Chan's clothes are not so different from each other.
(Suk Jin's clothes and the stylist's clothes)
- They're similar. - As for the top,
I choose number two.
And as for the bottom...
(Walking toward the clothes)
Wait. Are they allowed to change it after I pick the number?
Can't we just pick the clothes for you?
- But all of them are nice. - It'll be never-ending.
So you're not allowed to change it after the choice is made.
- They're all nice. - As for the top,
- I choose number two. - Okay.
(The top number 2 and the bottom number 1)
And number one for pants.
- Really? You made a good choice. - He picked my pants.
- Is it a good choice? - Indeed.
- He picked my traveling clothes. - He picked the whole pair.
My traveling clothes.
- This and that? - He picked both.
Okay. That's cool.
- A celebrity's traveling style. - Exactly.
(It's the perfect outfit for a celebrity going to an airport.)
You picked a celebrity's traveling style.
Suk Jin posed like this in those clothes.
(He posed as other celebrities do in those clothes.)
His pants were slipping down.
(Kind of like he's wearing it)
- That's the key point. - I see.
(Se Chan chose his clothes.)
That's confirmed. Who's next?
- I'll go next. - Nice. This will be interesting.
(It's followed by Jong Kook's turn.)
- The zebra print pants. - Finally.
- I chose the clothes carefully. - I hope he'll choose these.
(The trap of the white sleeveless shirt with holes...)
He's going to smile happily.
(and the zebra pants)
- I picked them very carefully. - They look so weird.
- He's going to smile very happily. - How can I wear them?
- Those pants... - Those clothes have good memories.
(I'm starting to feel bad.)
The sleeveless shirt is not so bad.
I hope he'll choose the pants.
I don't care about the shirt.
(Pick the zebra pants.)
I really hope...
- he'll wear the zebra print pants. - Exactly.
(Serious)
It's made with thick fabric.
- He can show off his fit body. - He'll look fashionable.
If the pants don't fit you,
- you don't have to wear them. - You can see them, right?
- Exactly. - Just draping them?
- Make your choice wisely. - Just like Justin Bieber.
(His choice will decide...)
(whether or not he will turn into a zebra.)
Let's go!
- I picked the wrong ones. - Be quiet.
(Please choose at least one of them.)
We're in the middle of a shoot.
I have a feeling that I should choose number one...
for both top and bottom.
(He chose number 1 for top and bottom.)
- What? - Number one?
- Number one. - Are you sure?
(He won't be fooled by Se Chan.)
We're happy with your choice.
- Number 1. - Number 1.
(He chooses number 1.)
- Number one? - Yes.
(He chooses Kwang Soo's sleeveless shirt with holes.)
- That's nice. - He'll look great.
I like them.
- He picked half wrong. - That's right.
However, where should he put his microphone?
- Right here. - Where?
(It looks a bit too loose to put a microphone on it.)
- On his back. - Like this?
- On his forehead. - On the back like this.
- He can put it on his back. - Like a musical actor.
He can put it on his forehead like a musical actor.
- Or give him a handheld microphone. - Exactly.
I think it's inappropriate for a TV show. Is it okay?
(Worried about the censorship as it's too revealing)
- Yes. Don't worry. - I'll go next.
(Ji Hyo must choose from the Yim Jae Beom Style.)
Look at that.
Gosh, this is...
Ji Hyo, to be honest, Se Chan's clothes are nice.
- They're not bad. - Really?
- Yes. - They'll be too hot though.
They look sophisticated.
(He spoke without thinking much.)
I choose number two from top to bottom.
(She quickly chooses number 2.)
- Okay. - Okay.
That's perfect.
(Where are you?)
I choose number two from top to bottom.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Oh, you were all number 2.)
- That's perfect. - Good choice.
- What should I do? - What should I do?
- Ji Hyo, you made a good choice. - She picked the whole set.
- That's perfect. - Good choice.
(She'll turn into Yim Jae Beom due to a single decision.)
Ji Hyo, good job.
(The other members also chose the clothes to wear.)
- Number 1 for the top. - Number 1.
- Number 1. - Number 1.
(What clothes will they wear?)
- No. - Number one.
(So they've finished choosing their clothes.)
(Walking slowly)
Someone asked me if I had changed my clothes.
I said, "These aren't my clothes."
(He obviously didn't dress up today.)
"I'm wearing them for the show."
They suit me so well, right?
A celebrity's travel style.
(And someone is coming in.)
(It was Kwang Soo wearing the miniskirt prepared by So Min.)
The pants are a little too big for me, right?
(His long, skinny legs are covered with red mesh stockings.)
I mean...
Why must she have gone this far?
(Why does So Min...)
- You look great, Kwang Soo. - He does have nice legs.
- You have such pretty legs. - You have nice legs.
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
So Min said she wishes to have legs like yours.
(So Min wanted to have his legs.)
It suits you well.
You should dress like this more often.
(Upset)
Hey, Ji Hyo.
(Then Ji Hyo enters.)
Sing a little bit of his song.
Look at her.
(Geeky)
- She looks great. - What should I do?
- Ji Hyo, you look great. - Don't I...
(Her younger brother)
Don't I look like Seong Mun?
- Ji Hyo, you look great. - I like how she looks.
(It's somewhere between Seong Mun and Jae Beom.)
Ji Hyo, you should get a short cut only in the front like this.
You look really great. I mean it.
You look perfect.
(She perfectly pulls off the wig.)
They look like a couple.
(The flashy fashion style reminds us of Generation X...)
Can I trust you, staff members?
(at the end of the century.)
Can I?
You're the worst dresser I've seen so far this year.
(He broke the worst fashion style record of 2020.)
- That's a terrible style. - Why?
(They broke the worst fashion style record of 2020.)
(Their poses and fashion styles remind us of the late 1990s.)
Why?
(And then, a zebra entered.)
- Jae Suk. - You look great.
He liked those pants.
I like these pants so much, so I borrowed them.
(The zebra pants that Jae Suk wanted)
(Haha's see-through shirt and Kwang Soo's zebra pants.)
- Look at the pants. - He looks like a hair stylist.
(He looks like a rich hairdresser from a hair salon.)
- Exactly. - They're just like my own clothes.
They really look like your own clothes.
(His stylist chose the top and he got Jae Suk's pants.)
- Exactly. - You should buy those pants...
- from Jae Suk. - They feel like my own.
- He looks like a vice president. - These are nice pants.
Who lives in Gimpo.
(He looks like a vice president in the IT industry.)
Look at Jong Kook.
(Jong Kook is the last one to enter.)
(Half muscles and half clothes)
Look at Jong Kook.
- Why are you carrying it like that? - What's that?
(He put the mission bag on the right spot.)
- Take the bag off. - I'll carry it.
Put it down.
Are you going to a battlefield?
I thought it was a different type of microphone.
(The fashion leader is armed with the mission bag and microphone.)
No, it isn't.
I can't put it on anywhere else.
- I look the most stylish among us. - That looks good.
(So Min looks relatively okay with the Tiger Moth style.)
- So Min looks cute. - He's tall.
- She looks too pretty. - So Min...
But if you look at her face...
and her head, she looks like a baby octopus.
- Like the baby octopus alien? - Exactly.
(She looks like a baby octopus.)
- Like the cartoon character. - Doesn't she look like that alien?
(The baby octopuses criticize her outfit.)
She looks like the baby octopus alien.
- Did I really wear them? - I can't believe...
these are a celebrity's traveling style.
- Suk Jin actually wore them. - Isn't that Se Chan's?
(The fashion calls for an ID check.)
My goodness.
- It looks like Se Chan's. - It is shabby indeed.
(She's satisfied with the fashion she recommended.)
I know a guy from Gimpo who looks like this.
It left marks on your forehead.
(They have a bonding moment talking about their fashion.)
- I don't know how to wear it. - Do you not wear beanies?
Suk Jin, you can sit in the middle now.
(They all take their seats.)
The rest of you will sit on the red chairs.
Why is he sitting in the middle?
- Ji Hyo, come here. - Sit modestly.
My gosh.
(The thimble guy covers Kwang Soo's legs in an onion net.)
It's a pantskirt.
It looks like he's the head of a department.
I don't know which company this is, but we're having a talent show.
(They are the top talents for the talent show.)
Exactly.
All right. This is your first choice.
(The first mission: Make your choice: Show-terview)
You know the balance game that's been popular these days?
One of you will come on up and answer...
(The game will proceed similar to the balance game.)
a question prepared for you.
(Each has to choose between either A or B.)
The rest of you will...
guess the answer that the member chooses.
(The rest of the members will guess the answer chosen.)
If you get it right, you get candy bars. If you don't, you return them.
(The number of yut candy bars will be calculated later.)
You will pick an answer all at the same time.
- As you count to three? - I should pick what he'd choose.
(It's important to read the mind of the member.)
- I will pick answers as I feel. - Okay.
Just the way I feel.
I should read his mind.
- I think I can get it right. - Sure.
(Confident)
- We know each other very well. - That's true.
All right. Please show the question.
Okay.
(If I was born again?)
- "If I were born again?" - "A senior respected by Jae Suk".
(A senior respected by Jae Suk)
(An older brother that Jong Kook is afraid of)
My gosh.
- It's so hard. - Good.
(Even the first question is very difficult.)
"An older brother that Jong Kook is afraid of"?
Gosh, this is too hard.
- This is tough. - It's hard to choose.
- It's hard for me too. - This is too hard.
You gave him this question because he's none of them.
"A senior respected by Jae Suk"?
- Gosh, this is hard. - A senior that Jae Suk respects...
(Will you be a person of admiration by Jae Suk?)
or my older brother whom I'm afraid of.
(Will you rather be a person feared by Jong Kook?)
This is tough.
So let's say he's having an interview.
(Suk Jin's imagination)
They'd ask whom he respects the most.
Then he'd say, "It's Ji Suk Jin."
I get to hear that.
(Suk Jin's imagination)
Or I tell Jong Kook to come to see me tomorrow by 2pm.
And Jong Kook is so worried.
"Why does he want to see me?"
(It can happen only in his imagination.)
Then...
he calls Haha.
"Why do you think Suk Jin wants to see me?"
He's so terrified that he peed in front of your house.
- Trembling in fear. - Gosh, it's confusing.
(They even added the scene where Jong Kook wets his pants in fear.)
This is really hard. It's interesting.
In fact, he respects me.
No. I like you, but I don't respect you.
You fool...
He's just a friend.
- He's a good funny friend. - A close friend.
(A good person, a fun person)
- Right. - I've never respected him...
not even a single time.
- Darn it. - Seriously.
(Jae Suk never respected him.)
- Not even once? - There was a time...
when I realized that I can't respect him.
(Why Jae Suk decided not to respect Suk Jin)
When we were younger,
(It happened only a few years after their debut.)
we went through hard times together.
- That's what's real. - We went around...
(Suk Jin went to three different used car places with Jae Suk.)
three used-car markets in Seoul.
- Why? - And on our way home,
he bought a new car.
(This one episode reflects...)
And you were there the whole time?
I did it for three days.
(A weak sense of finance, easily persuaded, likes to boss around)
(The 3 reasons why Suk Jin lost Jae Suk's respect)
- It took him three days. - Really?
This is what happened only 30 minutes ago.
(Another report)
Before the opening,
I was sitting under a parasol.
(An assistant director walked by Suk Jin and Kwang Soo.)
- Oh, that one. - And Hyeong Gu walked past him.
"Hyeong Gu, come here and have a seat."
(Kwang Soo stood up to give up his seat, but Suk Jin did too.)
Then he stood up.
- He rarely leaves his seat. - Right.
(He stood up as if he'll give up his seat.)
It turns out he picked up his chair like this and moved to a shade.
Moved to a shade.
(Coincidentally, he moved to shade with his chair.)
He moved into the shade like that.
Hyeong Gu had no chair.
I thought he was giving his chair to Hyeong Gu.
(It's a sad story of an assistant director who stood under...)
He brought his chair with him, so Hyeong Gu...
had to stand there like this.
(the scorching sun for a long time.)
It's not like he can sit on a transparent chair.
He was standing like this.
- Hyeong Gu, I'm sorry. - He's the worst.
(There are many episodes on why Suk Jin lost his respect.)
What do you think, Ji Hyo?
(What does Ji Hyo think?)
I think, if I were Suk Jin,
I would want to be someone...
- whom Jong Kook is afraid of. - You relate to him.
(She put herself in his shoes.)
- Right. - You empathize with him.
- I will beat up Jong Kook someday. - He didn't ask about your opinion.
That's her answer.
- What about you, Se Chan? - I'll definitely choose Jong Kook.
(There's one more person who'd pick option B.)
"Come here."
"Come here. How dare you."
"Relax your muscles."
(Se Chan, you seem excited.)
It's just my imagination.
- What about you, Haha? Is it B? - Of course.
(It's the same for Haha.)
"Pick it up."
(They all let their imagination run wild.)
"Yes, Haha. Here."
That's right. It sounds so good.
(I really enjoyed it.)
(Enjoy the moment.)
- I've made up my mind. - I know his choice.
(What will Suk Jin choose?)
- I've made up my mind. - 1, 2, and 3.
- B. - B.
(B, an older brother that Jong Kook is afraid of)
That's right.
(So Min is the only one who got it wrong.)
So Min picked A.
Even if he respects me, it's just useless.
But bossing him around can be very useful.
- Exactly. - It will be very fun.
(A very useful younger brother)
He can be very useful.
- Let's move on. - There's a lot to talk about this.
- What if you get to pick only one? - "I get 100,000 dollars,"
(What if you get to pick only one?)
(A, I get 100,000 dollars,)
"and Jae Suk gets 10 million dollars without thanking me."
(and Jae Suk gets 10 million dollars without thanking me.)
"None of us gets any money."
B sounds like throwing a tantrum.
(B, none of us gets any money)
B is just like throwing a tantrum.
- "I get 100,000 dollars..." - B is just like throwing a tantrum.
(He feels excited already.)
B is just like throwing a tantrum.
So I get 100,000 dollars.
You will make 100,000 dollars anyway.
And Jae Suk gets 10 million dollars.
- I don't thank him at all. - But he's not grateful to me.
- He gets the money because of you. - Let's answer it right away.
(It's very brutal for a small investor like Suk Jin.)
Let's put it this way.
Suk Jin got me some information.
"Jae Suk, I heard this one is good."
(Jae Suk invested money based on Suk Jin's tip.)
And he invested little money.
(Jae Suk earned 10 million because he put in a lot of money.)
- And I invested huge money. - So you made 10 million dollars.
That's how you made 10 million dollars...
(But Suk Jin earned only 100,000 dollars.)
Suk Jin invested 10,000 dollars...
(He's already upset.)
- while I invested one million. - It increased tenfold.
That's how it feels. You talk to me.
(They try a skit to better understand the situation.)
I made 10 million dollars, but I didn't even thank you.
I heard you invested one million dollars.
(Suk Jin, trying hard to maintain his cool)
You gave me the information.
(Jae Suk, Shameless)
I know. You should at least buy me a meal.
- Or give me 30 percent... - I invested my own money.
- It's your money, but... - You didn't give me the money.
(Losing temper)
But I gave you the information.
It was my choice that I made the investment.
(They just started the skit for fun.)
I invested huge money in it. You didn't give me the money.
(He's upset for real.)
- But I gave you the information. - It was my choice...
- that I made the investment. - Exactly.
- Your choice. - Let's do it right away.
Let's do it right away.
- I can't stand this anymore. - Count to three.
It's really upsetting to watch it.
- Please count to three. - Did it help?
- A lot. That's enough. - Did it help?
1, 2, and 3.
Darn it! I'm so furious.
(Everyone chooses B.)
(B, none of us gets any money)
- Did it help? - I'd rather not get the money.
They both shouldn't get money.
- I don't want to be jealous. - I understand.
(It's better to starve together than be jealous.)
- I don't want to be jealous. - That's worse.
- I would hate him. - Right. We would starve together.
- Right. - I'd end up hating him.
- It's Se Chan's turn. - Is it me? Okay.
(It's Se Chan's turn.)
- This is fun. - That was a good one.
Yang Se Chan.
- This is fun. - You have to imagine it.
(First question)
- Balance game. - This is the first question.
This one is tough.
(What if he must date one?)
I know what he'd choose.
(A, Song Ji Hyo, B, Jeon So Min)
Gosh, this is too hard.
- What if you date one of them? - Hang on.
(Thinking)
This is hard because it's so serious.
No, I'm just doing this for fun.
(Everyone else but the two got very serious.)
- This is a sensitive issue. - By the way...
- It's only for dating. - It's only for dating.
(It's only dating.)
Only for dating. Okay.
- Hang on. - This is hard.
Gosh.
This is such a happy problem.
- You're right. - I know. Thank you.
- You're so lucky. - Wait. But...
(Acting cute)
This is too hard.
(Laughing)
It's only for dating.
Ji Hyo just made a cute face.
I guess she forgot that she's wearing a wig.
(She's a cute Yim Jae Beom.)
It's just dating.
- You date one of them. - I just tell my friends...
(Se Chan is facing a dilemma that will never happen to him.)
- that I'm dating her. - Right.
I know whom you will pick.
- All right. 1, 2, and 3. - I will support you.
(Who will Se Chan choose?)
I wonder which one would make me happier.
Three.
- A. - That's right.
(B, Jeon So Min)
- My gosh. - Se Chan!
Thank you, Se Chan.
(Smiling)
Why?
Look at her. So Min seems happy.
- Do you like it? - If I date her,
(The Love Frog wants to be the best when it comes to love.)
I think it will be more fun.
- Of course. - What about Ji Hyo?
(What about dating Ji Hyo?)
If I dated Ji Hyo,
she wouldn't even be interested in me.
She'd just go her way.
(She'll love in her own way.)
- She doesn't even answer calls. - I know. We should play games.
How do you break up with your boyfriend, Ji Hyo?
I just tell him that we should stop seeing each other.
What if you say that...
and your boyfriend...
(What if he wants another chance?)
What if he asks you to give him another chance?
I will give him a chance.
- Just once? - Yes. Just once.
What about you, So Min?
- She is... - I...
I give countless chances.
(She gives unlimited chances.)
- I... - She wants to see the end of it.
I break up with someone only after I get sick of him.
(She gives enough chances.)
- After you get sick of him. - Right.
- And do you take your revenge? - I take my revenge.
- I knew it. - To the bitter end.
That's how she dates a guy.
(She gives both enough chances and revenge.)
She takes her revenge? That's funny.
Let's move on to the next question.
(Which situation do you hate more?)
- This is so fun. - This one is really tough.
"Which situation do you hate more?"
(A, my girlfriend goes on an overnight trip with a male friend)
"My girlfriend goes on an overnight trip with a male friend."
Gosh, this is a popular question.
(B, my girlfriend drinks all night with an ex-boyfriend)
Which situation do I hate more?
- Both of them sound horrible. - It's a difficult question.
I really hate it.
(Everyone gets angry.)
Going on an overnight trip?
Only two of them? That's crazy.
Hey, A is a male friend and B is an ex-boyfriend.
How could she go on an overnight trip with a male friend?
(Hitting)
With an ex-boyfriend, if something goes wrong...
An overnight trip is just as bad.
But it's her ex-boyfriend.
- But it happens... - It's her ex-boyfriend.
(Jong Kook persuades at close proximity.)
- It still happens... - Look at them.
- If her ex-boyfriend... - Jong Kook isn't explaining it.
He's forcing him to choose one answer.
(Is he a detective?)
Then you should sit there and give your answer.
That's not it. A male friend is...
I just can't pick what I want.
Nothing might happen with a male friend, but...
But the thing is they drink together all night.
(Jae Suk refutes.)
And the other is going on an overnight trip.
What happens after drinking?
(Flawless defense)
It doesn't say what happens next!
I know. But you can imagine.
That doesn't say what happens afterward.
(The hairdresser bursts with anger.)
- All night... - Does it say that?
It just says they drink together.
But why would they drink together?
Why are you being like that in a sleeveless shirt?
(The hairdresser loses temper at the sleeveless' dictatorship.)
You should think about it.
We should keep the possibility open.
(It was a heated debate.)
- 1, 2, and 3. - A male friend doesn't sound right.
(What will Se Chan choose?)
- I hate both. - I choose A.
- My answer is A. - A is worse.
(A, my girlfriend goes on an overnight trip with a male friend)
- Really? - Because it's an overnight trip.
(He explains the danger of an overnight trip.)
I should choose what I hate more. I was mistaken.
Now I understand why Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo... Now I know why Ji Hyo doesn't hear what we say.
I can't hear with the beanie on.
- Are you okay? - I can't hear very well.
(Ji Hyo's beanie has an excellent noise-canceling feature.)
I just can't hear you.
- Did you feel the same? - It's hard to hear, right?
(She's happy to meet a friend.)
Yes. I can't hear well.
Now I understand why she was being like that.
(The two sisters bond over a beanie that gets in the way.)
This is the last question.
(What if a thug spits on your girlfriend's face?)
You need to imagine the scene.
I know this one.
(A, let it slide, B, come at the thug)
This is obvious. He will definitely come at the thug.
- One... - Hang on.
Why are all the questions for me like that?
All my questions are so lame.
- Because you're single. - Because I'm single?
- Hey, just enjoy it. - It's just a game.
(It's just a game.)
It's just a game.
- Spit on her girlfriend's face? - I'd let it slide if it's my face.
- But it's my girlfriend's. - You're lying.
(He pretends as if he puts love above everything.)
It's not going to happen to you anyway.
So you're pretending to be tough.
(Spitting)
(He hits him right away.)
- Why did you do that? - Stop it.
(Jae Suk hit him right away.)
Why did you hit me? You said you would hold it back.
You said you would hold it back.
You said you'd let it slide if someone spits in your face.
How dare you spit at me?
(Yelling)
He didn't do as he said he would.
(He's not exactly patient.)
If someone who is dressed like that...
If someone who is dressed like that spits at me,
- I would let it slide. - Me too.
- I would be so scared. - I would let it slide too.
(The man is somewhat threatening.)
Things like that scare me.
Se Chan, what if the thug is as big and muscular as Jong Kook?
You should say something before throwing a punch.
I bet he has no experience.
(It's obvious that he doesn't have much fighting experiences.)
- It's obvious. - You should say something first.
- Say what? - "Hey, you punks!"
"Hey, you punks!"
(It didn't sound intimidating at all.)
- Don't come near me. - You would get beaten up.
(He has the voice of a person who can't fight.)
You should say something like that first.
His mouth would dry out right away if he were in such a situation.
Because he's too nervous. "Why..."
"Hey, you punks."
(His mouth is dry.)
- That's funny. - I bet Se Chan would let it slide.
- It's scary. - He would let it slide.
Even if you end up getting beaten up... If you let it slide,
(If you don't do anything, you'll be over with your date.)
- your relationship would be over. - Absolutely.
- Right? You should do something. - But...
maybe your girlfriend did something to deserve being spat at.
Maybe your girlfriend did something to deserve being spat at.
Suk Jin, it's not...
(Suk Jin tries to secure the escape route.)
- For example... - I mean...
(How could he justify it like that?)
What are you talking about?
What could she have done to deserve it?
Let's say she said to the thug, "Hey, you jerk!"
- My gosh. - "What is wrong with you?"
Or she spat at the thug first.
Sometimes, when she's drunk,
(Maybe it was the thug's self-defense.)
- she does unusual things. - That's possible.
- That's nonsense. - "Hey, you scumbag!"
- Maybe she said that. - "Stop it."
(He's proud after finding the cases where he'd let it slide.)
- The situation might be... - I think he would let it slide.
Let's say So Min... I mean, your girlfriend...
said to the thug, "Hey, you pig with a tattoo."
(So Min provoked the thugs first.)
- She provoked him first. - Okay.
- I would try to stop her. - So...
(The thugs spat at So Min.)
- the thug spat at her. - "What? Did I say something wrong?"
So the thug spat at her.
Then I would spit at her too.
Hey.
(How could you?)
Gosh.
To survive. I want to live.
(He will be excessively loyal to the thugs to stay alive.)
- "Sir, didn't I do well?" - "What is wrong with you?"
"Come to your senses."
(He would spit at her too.)
- One more time. - "Take this."
(It's fun to make fun of So Min.)
"Get it together. Sir, I'll be off."
(He would save his own life and go home.)
- Gosh. - I can imagine that.
(Se Chan is unbelievable.)
- Are you ready? - Yes.
- Okay. 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
I knew it.
(B, go after them)
I wouldn't let it slide.
(So Min's the only one with A.)
- This one is easy. - Even if I get beaten up...
- What? - Did you pick A?
I think he would let it slide.
- Nonsense. - He wouldn't.
I would throw a fit.
(Next is Jae Suk.)
- Me? - It's Jae Suk's turn.
- I know everything about him. - Okay.
(Jae Suk's best friend)
My head itches because of the hat.
- Put it back on. - The forehead too.
- That's why Ji Hyo scratches often. - Right?
Ji Hyo.
(Itchy)
She must be used to wearing a wig. She seems comfortable.
It's so comfortable.
Let's begin.
(Which one do you regret more?)
- "Which one do you regret more?" - "Not scolding Suk Jin."
(A, not scolding Suk Jin when he was a newcomer)
"B, not taming Jong Kook when starring on 'X-Man'".
(B, not taming Jong Kook when starring on "X-Man")
- That's an interesting question. - It's difficult.
- My gosh. Hang on. - Which one of them...
"Not scolding Suk Jin when he was a newcomer".
(I have to think about it.)
- Let me think. - I already made my choice.
- You did? - I made my choice.
- It's difficult. - This is a hard one.
- How harshly would he scold him? - How would he scold him?
(How would he scold Suk Jin?)
Actually, I had a few chances.
- You lost your chances. - He's your junior comedian, right?
(He missed the chance to teach Suk Jin a lesson.)
- Yes, he is. - That one is also funny.
- "Not taming Jong Kook". - "Not taming Jong Kook".
(He also missed the chance to train Jong Kook.)
He used to walk on eggshells around you.
Honestly, both are right,
but if I must choose one, I would choose this.
(I already made my choice.)
- Okay. - As soon as I read it,
- I thought... - I know his answer.
(They can't wait to find out Jae Suk's choice.)
- I've been looking at the answer. - Don't say that now.
All right.
I see which one he's looking at.
I know his answer. I'm sure of it.
- Start counting, please. - 1, 2, 3.
- Then answer is B. - It's A.
(Only Suk Jin and Ji Hyo picked B.)
- It's A. - Of course, it's A.
Of course, it's A.
A? No, it must be B.
(Denying the reality)
Since "X-Man", Jong Kook has always been...
- behaving well. - I'm always polite.
Did Suk Jin address you as his senior comedian at first?
(Did Suk Jin address Jae Suk as his senior comedian?)
- Or did he talk casually to you? - No, I didn't.
(Or did he talk casually?)
At first, when we were alone together,
- he called me by my name. - I see.
But when our senior comedians were with us, he said, "Hello, Mr. Yu."
- Really? - I can't believe it.
(Suk Jin couldn't call Jae Suk by his name.)
- It's hard to believe. - Really?
I didn't know he used to do that.
- You should've scolded him then. - When everyone gathered.
- "Hello, Mr. Yu." - But he didn't bow deeply.
"Hello, Mr. Yu."
(He didn't bow deeply to keep his pride.)
Let's move on to the next question.
"How would you be born in your next life?"
(How would you be born in your next life?)
(A, an ugly but popular show host)
"An ugly but popular..." That's who he is now.
- Okay. - I think I know the answer.
(B, a handsome but ordinary man)
- This is... - "A handsome but ordinary man".
- "In your next life". - I don't...
I don't like this question.
(What's wrong with the question?)
- A describes his current life. - That's a weird question.
(It's obvious.)
Hey. A is my current life?
- You're living as the A type. - But A...
(Ugly Jae Suk in current life versus hot Jae Suk in next life)
- That's my current life? - Yes, correct.
Would you live as Yoo Jae Suk again in your next life or...
(In other words)
- Hey. - It's either your current life...
- or a different life. - What are you talking about?
(Currently ugly Jae Suk is upset.)
Think about it. You want to live as an ugly man again?
You little...
(Will you live another life as an ugly man?)
- Jae Suk, that'd be boring. - Gosh.
(Angry)
When we went to a club before he became popular,
(The ugly friend's testimony)
ladies hated him so much.
(Jae Suk dropped the club level.)
They didn't hate me.
- Like those losers at a club. - They weren't interested in me.
I know how sad that feels.
(Objection)
- They weren't interested in me. - I know how that feels too.
(His justification sounds sad.)
- I wasn't... - All right.
- Okay. - If I could choose...
- I can relate to that. - If I choose B,
I need some guarantee.
- Zo In Sung... - Absolutely.
Park Bo Gum or Zo In Sung...
- If I'm as handsome as they are... - He looks happy.
(Scoffing)
- Or Gang Dong Won. - What?
And let's say the ugly man in A is like...
(The example of ugliness in A is...)
- Kwang Soo or Suk Jin... - No, it's you.
- Jae Suk, come on. - It's you.
(He kills his own team.)
- It's you. - It's not me.
(Denying)
Would you be Yoo Jae Suk or Zo In Sung in your next life?
(In short, who will he be born as?)
- All right. - Okay.
- You don't even need... - 1, 2,
- Three. - Of course, it's B.
(Jae Suk chose B.)
- He picked B? - Of course.
- He picked B? - Of course, he picked B.
(Only if he could live as Zo In Sung for one day.)
- Of course, I picked B. - He must want that life too.
I want to live as In Sung or Bo Gum in my next life.
- Of course, he wants that. - I want that kind of life.
Of course. How can he live like this again?
- What did you just say? - I'm sorry, Jae Suk.
(The person who lives like that is angry.)
- Please don't be mad. - All right.
Here's the next question.
(What makes you popular?)
"What makes you popular?"
- "A, the intelligent-looking face". - What's that?
(Embarrassed)
None of those is true.
- This isn't true. - None of them is true.
(Shy)
Pick the one that you think had even a little influence.
(A, the intelligent-looking face)
(B, the perfect body for a suit)
- But... - "Intelligent-looking"?
- I mean... - "Intelligent-looking"?
(The handsome middle-aged man can't help but smile.)
That bothers me.
That word itself makes me cringe.
- "Intelligent-looking"? - My gosh.
(It makes everyone cringe.)
The questions should be made based on facts.
(It must make sense.)
- Don't you think so? - There's no fact in there.
(Complaining)
Do you mean that he's good-looking?
You can say it's true because some people...
- say that on the internet. - That's not true.
Did you make the question based on those silly comments?
Why would you call them silly comments?
(Jong Kook thinks they're all silly comments.)
People call that kind of comment silly comments.
Let's make it simple. My face or my body?
- Okay. - It's simple.
- So we can accept it. - My...
- My face or my body? - Or your body.
- 1... - 1, 2, 3.
- My face. Why? - Gosh.
(The intelligent-looking face)
(He chose his face with confidence.)
- That's not true. - That's total nonsense.
(There's a riot.)
- You know that's not true. - Gosh, seriously.
- Jae Suk, you can't do that. - You must've lost your mind.
(The boy he couldn't tame during "X-Man" goes out of control.)
- Jae Suk. Come on. - How could you?
- This is not right. - Darn it.
- Have you... - The answer should be B.
- Have you lost your mind? - Wait.
(Torturing the ugly brother)
I knew he thought that way.
- I can't believe this. - What's the problem?
(Audacity)
- You agreed to tell the truth. - What's wrong with my answer?
(Everyone resists except for Jae Suk himself.)
My gosh. It turns out he was satisfied with his face.
(My goodness.)
- What's wrong with my answer? - I'm shocked.
(Brazen)
- Why? - I'm shocked too.
Wait. Se Chan, why is your chair attached to your pants?
(The chair is stuck on his butt.)
What?
- I've been looking for the chair. - It's perfect for traveling.
(Why is the chair stuck here?)
- What happened? - Gosh.
(The strange encounter between the chair and his hips)
- Gosh, seriously. - That's total nonsense.
- He must be out of his mind. - Gosh.
(The chair has been hanging there like a fruit on a tree.)
(What? Where did my chair go?)
- What's the problem? - You agreed to tell the truth.
What's wrong with my answer?
(After looking for his chair for a long while,)
Wait. Se Chan, why is your chair attached to your pants?
(he found his chair suffocated by his hips.)
What?
Here goes the final question.
(Last question for Jae Suk after saving the chair)
(Which body part would you cover if a public bath is on fire?)
- It's a difficult one. - That's easy.
(A, the face)
- That's easy. - It's a difficult question.
There's nothing to cover.
(B, the private part)
- He doesn't need to cover it. - I'm sure...
(He's certain.)
My goodness. Have you lost your mind?
(We don't know what it is, but he doesn't have to cover it.)
- It's so cute. - What kind of question is that?
Seriously, what kind of question is that?
(Flustered)
Honestly, if he comes out covering his face,
people would think he's a little boy...
I mean, people would know he's an adult...
- Are you insane? - So they would help him...
(Angry)
Have you lost your mind?
- I'm telling you, - Gosh.
it wouldn't be visible if he runs fast.
(I have a lot to say, but I won't say anything.)
Trust me.
(The visibility would change depending on his running speed.)
Gosh. All of you are insane.
Gosh, seriously.
Imagine that situation.
(What does Jae Suk choose?)
- Okay. - 1, 2, 3.
(I've made up my mind.)
- He would cover his face. - It must be A.
(Jae Suk chose A.)
- Of course, he'd cover his face. - Of course.
- I thought about it. - Why...
I would be so embarrassed if I come out like this.
- Of course. - Right?
(It's like telling everyone that he's Jae Suk.)
- It's better to cover your face. - Next up is Kwang Soo.
- That was ridiculous. - Okay.
- Kwang Soo... - I think it'll be difficult.
Be honest with us, okay?
- I'll be honest. - Be yourself.
(The professional backstabber is worried.)
- I promise. - Don't lie.
- I won't. - Don't lie.
(Which situation would you avoid?)
- "Which situation would you avoid?" - "Having Jong Kook..."
(A, having Jong Kook bathe me)
- "bathe me". - My gosh.
"Having Jong Kook bathe me thoroughly".
(B, bathing Suk Jin)
- My gosh. - Hold on.
(Everyone is exclaiming as they read the question.)
Why would Jong Kook...
bathe me thoroughly?
- That's so funny. - What kind of question is that?
(That's too much.)
- Why must I choose any of those? - That's hilarious.
I bathe Suk Jin?
(It's a perfectly balanced question.)
Do I wash his entire body?
Not just his face? Do I give him a bath?
- Don't you think that's too much? - Can I wear rubber gloves?
(Not with my bare hands)
- I can take a bath by myself. - My gosh.
(What's wrong with you?)
I just pictured it for a moment.
Wait. Excuse me.
- No. - Just a second.
- No. Don't touch me. - Just a second.
- I said no. - Let me just imagine it.
Gosh, no. Go away.
- Oh, man. That's disgusting. - Which would be worse?
- I pictured it for a moment too. - Both are disgusting.
(The biggest worry in his 36 years of life.)
- Exactly. Which one should I pick? - How disgusting.
Hey, you don't know my hands...
(Appealing)
At least, doing B would be fulfilling.
(Which situation would you avoid?)
- I imagined the B situation. - Yes.
I thought it could happen in the near future.
- You're right. It'll be sad. - Hey. That will never happen.
I can do it for him.
(He means it.)
- That won't happen. - It'll be sad.
- I'll be happy to do it for you. - It will never happen.
I pick what's worse, right?
(Forcing himself to shed tears)
- Did you make your choice? - Okay. Yes, I made my choice.
1, 2, 3.
(What does Kwang Soo choose?)
- I think that would be worse. - Of course, he picked A.
(He chooses A.)
(Suk Jin feels bitter but accepts it.)
- If I were... - Let's move on.
- Goodness, you brat. - Stop it!
(Scrubbing his body roughly)
This is unbearable.
(The muscular scrubber could peel Kwang Soo's skin off.)
- You brat. - Stop it.
(Kwang Soo's last question)
Here's the last question.
(Which would be worse?)
- "Which would be worse?" - "A, playing games with So Min".
(A, playing games with So Min all night long while drinking)
"B, listening to Jae Suk's dating advice all night over tea".
- Dating advice? - A is better.
(B, listening to Jae Suk's dating advice all night over tea)
- Of course, A is better. - This is a tough choice.
(The toughest choice in their lives)
Haven't you had drinks with her before?
Don't be ridiculous. I'm fun to be around!
- Both will be painful. - Kwang Soo.
- I think I know his choice. - My dating advice helped, right?
I'm fun to be around.
I know because I often have drinks with her.
(He washes his face to get rid of anxiety.)
I'm good company.
Both situations are painful.
(It's too difficult.)
- Did you wash your face? - Hold on.
Kwang Soo, I always give you good dating advice.
(The worst dilemma that makes him feel stressed)
Keep your head on straight.
What a tough choice.
(Sighing)
You must endure it all night.
I'm fun to be around!
I can shake up the choice of teas.
Chamomile and so on and so forth.
- It's the worst! - I can shake things up.
(It's already tiresome.)
- The tea can be swapped. - Still...
(Both choices are exhausting.)
1, 2, 3.
(Which one will Kwang Soo choose?)
- This must be it. - A.
(He chooses B.)
- What? - It's B.
- Unbelievable. - Seriously?
- It's disappointing. - How can this be better?
- Why? - I'm choosing the worse one.
(What's wrong?)
- He chose you over Jae Suk. - He chose you.
(It took her a second to understand.)
- Right. Yes, of course. - Drinking with her all night?
I give out great dating advice.
(Disappointed)
I haven't given you any lately...
- because you're seeing someone. - You see,
I've actually tried both.
Personally though,
Jae Suk's advice ruined things for me.
(It was a mess.)
Just the result alone, I mean.
(He was a counselor of break-ups.)
Kwang Soo.
Things wouldn't have gone very far with her anyway.
(Later...)
Stop it!
(The advice only hurt Kwang Soo's feelings.)
- Ji Hyo's next. - Right, Ji Hyo.
It'll be fun.
(Next is Ji Hyo.)
- She's tough to read. - I'm clueless when it comes to her.
- She could be easier to read. - She's hard to understand.
Ji Hyo's hard to read.
(You can never tell what Ji Hyo has in her mind.)
But she's also quite simple.
- Right. - Yes, I don't think too much.
What's worse?
(Which is worse?)
"A, being in a room filled with cockroaches for an hour".
I know the answer to this. I know!
(She hates cockroaches.)
- Choosing B would be weird. - I know!
(A, being in a room filled with cockroaches for an hour)
What Ji Hyo thinks about cockroaches...
It'd be weird if Kwang Soo guessed B.
(B, going out with Kwang Soo)
We don't even need time to think.
(Confident)
How can you compare Kwang Soo to cockroaches?
(That's mean.)
- I mean... - It's fine.
- You and cockroaches... - This...
is a mistake on their part.
- Okay. - All right.
Is it one cockroach or...
- A room full of them. - Multiple cockroaches.
You've got this, Kwang Soo.
(What did she say?)
Ji Hyo loathes cockroaches.
- It's not like you must kiss one. - Hold on.
Why did you ask how many cockroaches there were?
(How many cockroaches are equal to dating Kwang Soo?)
I know for a fact that you hate cockroaches.
You're not dating one, okay?
Wait, hold on.
(Enraged)
Ji Hyo...
- I keep going back and forth. - Ji Hyo, look at him.
(He loses his reason as he's treated the same as a cockroach.)
I thought for a second that she had to date one.
- It's Kwang Soo you're dating. - It's only for an hour.
(Correcting)
An hour with cockroaches or with Kwang Soo forever.
You have to be in that room for an hour.
(Think this through.)
You crouch and cry when any bug approaches you.
(Ji Hyo usually drops down at the sight of a bug.)
- It's just for an hour. - She knows.
(Will she choose A as everyone expects?)
1, 2, 3.
- Cockroaches, of course. - She chose B?
(In a twist of events, she chooses B.)
1, 2, 3.
- Cockroaches, of course. - She chose B?
(Dating Kwang Soo is worse?)
She chose B?
(You hate me more than you hate cockroaches?)
- A. - A, of course.
(My mistake.)
Of course, she'd choose A.
Kwang Soo was extremely shocked just now.
- I... - I thought she really chose B.
(Their 10 years of sibling love could have been ruined.)
Of course not.
- I absolutely loathe cockroaches. - Exactly.
(She merely hates cockroaches.)
Here.
(Who would you marry?)
- This is a tough one. - Who would you marry?
(A, a playboy, B, a mama's boy)
- It's not easy. - Don't you hate both?
- Me too. - They're both awful.
- Mama's boy is the worst. - Tell me about it.
Would it be like this?
(Let's elaborate on a mama's boy.)
When out on a date,
- this man would call his mom. - Right.
"Mom, I'm on a date with So Min."
"A movie or coffee? A movie? Okay, thanks."
(A mama's boy that consults what to do on a date?)
- For instance... - That's how he makes up his mind.
He must go on a date that his mom planned for him.
(That's awful.)
- But a womanizer... - At least it means he's charming.
(At least a playboy is charming.)
A womanizer is charming...
but he's seeing about five other women.
(But he's got complicated relationships with women.)
Would that be all right?
- Suk Jin, which would you choose? - What?
- Out of the two... - Me?
Well, I used to be a womanizer briefly.
That's not what I meant.
I...
When were you a womanizer exactly?
Why were you one?
- Why do you lie all the time? - Why were you one?
It's a lie.
- Well... - He's never been young enough.
He always looked like a middle-aged man.
(He's always been an uncle.)
- It's true. - You see,
it's like this.
(Suk Jin deludes himself even when everyone denies it.)
Being popular among women...
turns you briefly into a womanizer.
I apologize to Suk Jin's wife.
(Sudden)
I set you two up, didn't I? I'm sorry.
(Suk Jin)
(Jae Suk is always a sinner in front of Suk Jin's wife.)
I'm so sorry.
- So Min? - Well...
(What does the dating expert think?)
It's too hard of a choice.
The womanizer is probably handsomer.
She...
Don't consider those variables.
- Not the looks. - Why would you consider that?
(She just chooses the handsome boy.)
You're not just dating this person.
(The point is that she has to marry him.)
- You're marrying him. - Mama's boy is the worst.
- It's not so bad. - This is a tough choice.
(Which one will Ji Hyo pick?)
A mama's boy for life?
- One... - You can't handle a mama's boy.
- 2, 3. - Tell me about it.
(She chooses a mama's boy instead.)
A mama's boy is the worst though.
I hate both.
It's So Min.
(Next is So Min.)
Here we go.
Here's your first choice.
(Who would you date?)
Who would you date?
(A, Se Chan who loves me)
This...
(B, Dong Jun whom I love)
The answer is obvious.
- The answer is obvious. - Of course, it is.
(He knows So Min well.)
This will be easy for anyone...
- who knows me. - Exactly.
- Come on. - This?
I see I'm up against Dong Jun...
when someone was up against cockroaches.
Someone had to compete with cockroaches,
(Lee Kwang Soo, defeated a cockroach in a match)
but I'm up against Dong Jun.
- Gosh, thank you so much. - Lucky you.
(Se Chan gives thanks to the staff for putting him against Dong Jun.)
Someone had to compete with cockroaches.
(An honor for his family)
- Okay, then. - Okay.
(Grunting)
I was up against an hour with cockroaches.
(You still won.)
- Okay, good. - All right.
1, 2, 3.
(Who will So Min choose?)
- Of course, it's A. - It was too easy.
(A, Se Chan who loves me)
So Min likes those who only have eyes for her.
- Of course, it's A. - The guy loving me...
(They all got it right.)
is more important.
Ji Hyo...
(Ji Hyo is the only one who guessed wrong.)
She doesn't know So Min at all.
Ji Hyo?
(She doesn't know about So Min.)
- Did she choose Dong Jun? - She doesn't know So Min at all.
That wig is hilarious.
(Meanwhile...)
I thought about what So Min would like.
The wig and that answer go so well together.
She looks like a thug, right?
(Feeling hurt)
Would you choose B?
- You'd choose A too, right? - That's right.
(Ji Hyo would have chosen Se Chan if it was her problem.)
Rather than the guy I like,
I'd like to date someone who loves me.
- That's how it should be. - Right.
(He can't hide his smile.)
Let's move on.
(Which is worse?)
Which is worse?
(A, Jong Kook's suspecting you when you're the spy)
I know the feeling!
(B, Jong Kook's suspecting you when you're not the spy)
It's the worst.
I know the feeling! I know it so well.
(Shaking his head)
- My gosh. - This...
- is the worst. - It's hilarious though.
(Just thinking about it...)
- It's the worst. - It sure is.
(This guy has his head down.)
In situation A,
- He stresses you out. - you'd rather just die.
(A victim's testimony)
(A victim's testimony 2)
Remember last time?
(Rise, victims!)
Can't you look over this way at least once?
Just get it over with.
(The cutting problem brings chaos to the studio.)
We won't know until we take a look.
This...
(Just thinking about it gives her a headache.)
1, 2, 3.
- A. - My gosh.
(They all choose A.)
Still, it's nice because he shows interest in you.
You have no idea how angry I get...
(Totally sincere)
when situation A happens.
- Recently, you and Haha... - I...
(He admits it as well.)
That situation. Yes, I know it too.
- I mean it. - Me too.
- I never let it go. - It makes you so angry.
(The recent victims remember the days.)
I wanted to claw at him.
- I never let it go. - He checks your hands too.
Situation B only happens on camera.
Meanwhile, situation A happens off camera too.
He keeps smirking at you.
(Even when the cameras aren't rolling...)
(Smirking)
(Grinning)
It's the worst.
(Even Jong Kook admits it.)
Here's the next one.
- That was hilarious. - What would you like...
your boyfriend to say tonight?
"A, something sexy in a sweet voice".
"B, something sweet in a sexy voice".
(Thinking)
- Something sexy in a sweet voice. - I think I know.
Something sweet in a sexy voice.
What kind of voice do you find sexy though?
- Something sweet in a sexy voice. - The voice...
Who has a voice...
(She needs to get into character.)
that isn't pleasant?
- Him saying something sweet. - There's Cho Sae Ho.
(Husky voice)
- "Hello." - Him saying something sweet.
"Did you sleep well? I love you."
On the other hand, Lee Sun Kyun...
- will say something sweet. - "I said I love you."
(The perfect example to help you imagine)
"Come on."
"I love you, darn it."
(The whispers of love that hit your eardrums)
"I said I love you."
- Then we have our answer. - Let's do it.
- Do you want an example? - Sure.
(To help them decide,)
(let's hear the sweet voice and the sexy voice.)
Say "Hello" is a sweet voice and then in a sexy voice.
(Suk Jin's sweet voice)
- In a sweet voice? - That's right.
- "Hello." - Now, it a sexy voice.
(Suk Jin's sexy voice)
"Hello."
(It's overly corny!)
No, that's not it!
(Shock and terror)
One would end the call immediately.
You seemed sick to me.
(Suk Jin's sick but sexy voice)
What's a sexy voice though?
- Jae Suk, what about you? - What's a sweet voice?
(Next is Jae Suk's sweet voice.)
- A sweet voice. - My sweet voice?
- "Hello." - He can be very sweet.
(Clean)
- What about your sexy voice? - I've never tried that before.
(Expectant)
(Exhaling)
No, that's not it.
- I'll pass. - What's with the breathing?
(She skips it.)
That sounded disgusting.
(His unappealing heavy breathing)
Aren't I allowed to breathe?
(Enraged)
Even his breathing sounded ugly.
(No way.)
- What? - Even his breathing sounded ugly.
(You could tell that he's ugly from his outbreathing.)
- You... - From what I could hear,
- his breathing sounded ugly. - It sounded ugly?
(The ugly one flies into a rage.)
- That's how it sounded. - Gosh.
(Next is Se Chan's sweet voice.)
Let's hear from Se Chan next.
Cover your face.
(Se Chan's sweet voice)
Your sweet voice.
"Hello."
And your sexy voice.
(Se Chan's sexy voice)
- Stop it! - "Hello."
- Why are you breathing like that? - But...
(Loathing)
"Hello."
Are you awake?
(He learned it the wrong way from the comedy skits.)
- What on earth is that? - Gosh.
- Jong Kook's sweet voice. - "Hello."
(Jong Kook's sweet voice)
(Jong Kook's sexy voice)
- And your sexy voice. - "Hello."
- Put more thought into it. - Actually, this...
(The two sounded the same.)
- You shouldn't try so hard. - I agree.
Kwang Soo, you go ahead.
- "Hello." - Next.
(Sweet)
Did he get it wrong or something?
- Next. - Did he get it wrong or something?
(Another incident where Jae Suk...)
(comes onto Running Man just to tease Kwang Soo)
What do you mean?
Weren't you done?
(Another clip added)
- Of course not. - The sexy one.
- "Hello." - And the sexy voice.
(Kwang Soo's sweet voice)
The sexy voice.
(Kwang Soo's sexy voice)
"Hello."
(In a low voice)
(Emotional)
You forgot you're in a skirt again.
- Must I wear this all day? - Cover yourself up!
Must I wear this all day?
(His thin calves are sexier than his voice.)
- Just put on some pants. - But...
Wear the pants you brought with you today.
(Yim Jae Beom bursts into laughter.)
- What about Haha? - He has a nice voice.
(Admitting)
Be sweet first.
"Hello."
(Haha's sweet voice)
- Was that your sweet voice? - Yes.
(Haha's sexy voice)
- The sexy one. - Your sexy voice.
- "Hello." - Oh, that was sexy!
Oh, that was sexy!
(A sexy low tone)
- What a great voice. - The tone must be lower.
The sweetest voice was Jae Suk's...
(So Min chooses Jae Suk's sweet voice and Haha's sexy voice.)
while the sexiest voice was Haha's.
I made up my mind.
One...
The keyword is "tonight".
(Reaffirming)
- Yes, tonight. - Tonight?
- 1, 2, 3. - The man of the night
- B. - B.
- Nice! - I choose B.
(B, something sweet in a sexy voice)
- B. - B.
(They all choose B.)
- Nice! - I choose B.
Since it's "tonight".
I think I'll get a full score with Jong Kook's choices.
I'm going to keep it real...
(Next is Jong Kook.)
and choose whatever I want.
(What would you choose if you have to choose either one of them?)
What if you had to give up just one thing?
(A, losing muscle mass)
Gosh, this is a tricky one.
For Jong Kook, it'll be B.
- Gosh, this is a tricky one. - Goodness.
(B, staying single forever)
For Jong Kook, it'll be B.
You must be honest.
(Agonizing)
The keyword is "forever".
"Losing muscle mass" is just a funny way to put it.
- Jong Kook, look. - How is this a hard choice?
(Standing up)
Look at how I am.
You'll end up with my body.
(Dangling)
(He hates it.)
No, don't show him that.
(Will he choose marriage and Haha's wiggly arms?)
- His body... - Your body will become like mine.
I'll think about it right now.
(Or will he choose muscles and live single forever?)
- If you're as muscular... - Right away.
- as Jong Kook, - You can't exercise forever.
- he has to continue exercising. - I can't exercise forever.
- Isn't it better to... - This is a good question.
(Impressed)
Isn't it better to have flabby arms...
- than to never date? - This is so funny.
- You really don't know me. - It's A.
(Firm)
You're contemplating it, aren't you?
You don't know how big of a deal it is to us.
- It's really... - Losing muscles...
(Us means workout addicts.)
This is really... You must not understand.
(To Jong Kook, losing muscles...)
If I lose that, I'm losing everything.
(Serious)
This is just a game.
You don't have to get this angry.
(Calm down, Jong Kook.)
- This is... I imagined it, - Just imagining it upsets you?
- and it's really horrific. - Is it?
(What will Jong Kook choose?)
All right, let's just do it.
- 1. - 1, 2, 3.
- It's B. - It's A.
- It's B. - No, it's A.
(B, staying single forever)
- No, he said it's B. - I have to change it.
- It's B. He doesn't understand. - Right.
Are you giving up on love, you punk?
- Is that what you'd do? - I'll give up on love.
(He gives up his love.)
- You're choosing muscles? - I'm sorry, but this isn't...
- something I need to think about. - Why not?
It's not logical for us.
(I'd rather lose love than muscles.)
- It's like love to Jong Kook. - What's wrong with losing muscle?
A doesn't make sense.
- Let's move on to the next one. - Exercising.
(You're just amazing.)
(Which lover is better?)
"A lover who uses up an entire box of tissues when she blows her nose".
"A lover who sucks it in because she doesn't want to waste tissues".
(A, a lover who uses up an entire box of tissues...)
(when she blows her nose)
She sucks in her snot?
(B, a lover who sucks it in because she doesn't want to waste tissues)
Hold on. This is too extreme.
- I think I know what you'll choose. - She uses an entire box?
- Gosh, this is... - She sucks in her snot like this.
(Sucking in)
- Like this. - No.
Her nose is running, but she does this.
- Or she does this. - This?
(A snot eating show)
Seriously?
(It's just horrible.)
I don't want a sister-in-law like that.
I don't like either one.
- I'll choose. - 1, 2, 3.
(He decided.)
- The better one? - Gosh. It's better to use tissues.
- Seriously? - It's B?
(B, a lover who sucks it in because she doesn't want to waste tissues)
- 1, 2, 3. - The better one?
- Seriously? - It's B?
- B is better? - Isn't that cuter?
If she uses a lot of tissues, you can recycle them.
(Rebutting)
No.
- How is that cute? - She might have a cold.
(It's a very heated debate.)
- There's cold season. - That's for the rest of her life.
He's not even dating anyone,
so why are you all getting so worked up?
Was this game supposed to be so serious?
(We're too into it.)
The next person is the last person. Haha, you're last.
(Haha is the last one.)
I can choose really quickly.
(Confident)
Haha, this is your first question.
(If you had to choose one.)
"If you had to choose one, Jong Kook will be your business partner,"
(A, Jong Kook as a business partner but lose money)
- "but it won't go well." - This is hard.
(B, Don't see Jong Kook forever but have a successful business)
"Don't see Jong Kook forever but have a successful business."
Gosh.
Haha has big dreams when it comes to running a business.
Right. He's very ambitious.
- He's ambitious. - He is.
So he has to choose between Jong Kook and business.
- Right. - Right.
- This is... - It's easy.
- Is it Jong Kook or business? - It's not hard.
- You lose Jong Kook. - You won't see him again.
- You'll lose him as a friend. - Will he choose money or me?
Will he choose money or me?
(In extreme...)
- He said it's money or him. - Will he choose money or me?
(Business partner Jong Kook pressures him.)
He has a lot of people connected to his business.
(But Haha has other business partners too.)
- Right. - A lot of people are involved.
I'm connected to that too.
You said you'll make your decisions quickly.
(What are you doing? You said you'll choose quickly.)
How can you do this in your first question?
This is just the beginning.
(It's just the first question.)
- How big is the business? - I'll give you two candy bars.
Pass.
(He thinks on it hard again.)
- This is... - Darn it.
- Hold on. - Think about it realistically.
- Hold on. - 1, 2, 3.
(Haha encounters his first dilemma.)
(Regardless of how business goes, will he partner with Jong Kook?)
Think about it realistically.
- Okay 1, 2... - 1, 2...
(Or will he consider his family and coworkers and choose a business?)
- 3. - 3. Isn't it B?
- 3. B. - 3. Isn't it B?
- I choose A. - Why?
(Haha is the only one who chooses A.)
- Everyone chose B. - Why?
He's trying to have an easy day today.
- Why? - I'm being serious.
(I didn't know, brother.)
- He wants an easy day. - I'm being honest.
- I thought about his family. - I can make money in other ways.
(I was serious.)
I can't imagine not being friends with him.
While you were thinking about it, Jong Kook crushed this.
You must've been nervous.
(Crushed)
(While Haha was thinking about it...)
This is...
- Think about it realistically. - Gosh, I...
(Jong Kook was the only one who couldn't be realistic about it.)
Think about it realistically.
- You must've been nervous. - I was.
(Jong Kook was nervous.)
It's the next question.
(If Yang Se Chan and Jeon So Min get married.)
"If Yang Se Chan and Jeon So Min get married..."
(A, as the groom's guest, B, as the bride's guest)
Who will you attend for?
- For the congratulatory money... - Who will you attend for?
and where you will sit.
- He can't do half and half, right? - Right.
- This one is hard. - I think I know.
This is for real, right?
- He must choose one no matter what. - I'll be sincere.
Hold on. Give us a moment.
(He thinks hard again.)
- This is a hard one. - How can he choose one?
I think it's easy.
Who will you choose?
(Curious)
- This one is easy for me. - Who will you choose?
- Suk Jin, who will you choose? - Pardon?
(Who will he choose?)
- Who will you choose? - It's not your question anyway.
- I would choose B. - But I'm so close with him too.
(He chooses to attend as So Min's guest.)
I think he'd be understanding.
I'm touched. But I am understanding too.
(Losing temper)
My gosh.
- I don't think you will be. - I would be.
(For some reason...)
- Se Chan would be understanding. - Me too.
I think I should choose B too.
She won't be understanding.
- Se Chan would be understanding. - He would be.
(After Suk Jin's comment, everyone attends as her guests.)
- I'm understanding too. - She wouldn't.
- She will write down their names, - She'd get revenge.
and be like, "So you didn't come, right?
- Se Chan would be understanding. - He'd be understanding.
(Looking)
Right.
Okay, then. 1, 2, 3.
- B. - It's B.
(So Min is the only one who picked A.)
- This is the correct answer. - Right.
Se Chan would be grateful...
- that I considered his wife. - I would be.
He'd be very grateful.
- She's... - It's not because you're stingy.
(He makes excuses.)
- I would sit on So Min's side... - But I...
What's scary to me is...
So Min put up A.
(Chills)
Gosh, my image is a mess, isn't it?
No, that's not what we mean.
So Min doesn't have a lot of friends in the entertainment industry.
Right. I really don't.
(That's true.)
- Right. - If I had to choose one,
(It's Jae Suk.)
- I must give So Min more support. - You need to support her.
- I need to support her. - Right.
(Thank you, Jae Suk.)
- I need to... - How nice of you.
What about Ji Hyo? Where would you go?
(Will Ji Hyo really attend as So Min's guest?)
- Right. Where would you go? - I'd go for So Min.
(She chooses So Min without any hesitation.)
Right. Ji Hyo would do that.
If this situation applied to you guys,
would anyone choose Se Chan?
I think I would choose Se Chan.
Jong Kook.
- It's because of this. - No.
(This is why they chose B.)
(Calm down, So Min. It's just a game.)
The groom's side...
Why don't you guys start by dating?
We'll sit in the middle.
(His pink gum is exposed again.)
The first mission is over.
(The first mission result)
I got a lot wrong.
I got all of Haha's wrong. I had a good run before then.
(Current Number of Candy Bars)
- You don't know Haha well. - Right.
- What is this? - Aren't we doing a race today?
(It's time to do the final race in the clear weather.)
- What is this? - Why are we in the woods?
(Why were they asked to go into the woods?)
Hold on. Isn't this the Reserve Forces Training Center?
(The men are familiar with the place.)
1, 2.
- What is this? - This place is for survival games.
(What will be the mission that will unfold in this place?)
You're right, it is.
I think we came here once on Running Man.
- What? It's like a training center. - It's like guerrilla training.
- Director. - Yes?
Someone stole all of my candy bars.
You must take care of your things.
(Suspects are Se Chan, Haha, and Kwang Soo)
It's either Se Chan, Haha, or Kwang Soo.
- I told you. It isn't me. - It's not me either.
(The three deny the accusation.)
It's not me. I never touched yours.
(To be honest, between the three of them, the real criminal is...)
(30 minutes earlier, during lunch, Haha filmed this video.)
(He takes the candy bars out of So Min's bag.)
(He's blinded by the desire to win, so he filmed himself...)
(adding to his candy bars)
(She found out later and was angry.)
Give it back.
(Is it you?)
Stop playing around and give it back to me.
Next.
(Then he casually begins to film someone who looks suspicious.)
I promise. It's not me.
(Brazen)
- Did you film it? - Yes, I did.
(Was it Kwang Soo?)
(He doesn't know what's going on and gets framed.)
It's him.
I never touched yours.
(I never touched yours.)
(It was a perfect crime that he was never caught.)
- Don't cry and stand in your spot. - Gosh.
It's time for the final race.
(It's time for the final race.)
Before we start the race, I'll give you a chance...
(But there's a preliminary mission.)
to get yut candy bar, which you need for the game,
(It's a chance to earn candy bars and bullets for the final race.)
and bullets, which you will use in the game.
- Bullets? - Bullets?
- We need to shoot something. - It's a survival game.
(His eyes get big at the news of a shooting game.)
There are chance cards hidden around this place.
(It's a treasure hunt mission.)
The cards state how many yut candy bars and bullets...
(They will need to find papers...)
- you got. - Okay.
(that notes the number of yut and bullets.)
There are minus cards as well. What's important here is that...
(There are minus chance cards.)
if you touch it, you must take it.
(They'll own the card as soon as they touch them.)
You can give it to someone else without their knowledge.
- The minus cards? - Yes.
- Without their knowledge? - Whether it's their clothes or bag,
(It can't be thrown away, but can only be passed to another.)
you have to give it to them without their realization.
(It's important to transfer the minus cards unknowingly.)
- You can't hold onto it. - If you find it,
you can't throw it away.
You have to pass it on to another person or hold onto it.
(It'll work as a great advantage if they do this mission well.)
- Okay. - You can find it easily.
(He suddenly laughs.)
Why do you keep laughing?
What? It's not that.
I can't stop thinking about the people who just tuned in.
(I keep thinking about viewers who'll see us like this.)
I feel like I need to stand next to someone dressed like this.
(There's a reason we're dressed like this.)
You can see everything.
Ready, set, go.
(They only have 10 minutes.)
I don't think I can go up high.
(The treasure hunt begins.)
(Get the good chance cards and give the bad ones to others.)
Where are they?
I feel like it's somewhere here.
There's one here.
This is amazing.
"Plus one yut candy bar".
(He gets a candy bar.)
There's one here. I found one.
(So Min finds a card too.)
- Can we go up this way? - Okay.
"Minus three bullets".
(Why did she pick up minus 3 bullets?)
Where did they hide it?
(She needs to give this minus chance card to another person.)
Jeon So Min.
(Following)
So Min, what happened?
Jae Suk.
(So Min's target is Jae Suk.)
- I can't see it. - It's upsetting.
(She must give the chance card without Jae Suk knowing.)
- Jae Suk. - What, So Min?
- Gosh, there it is. - Where is it?
(Interested)
(He figured out her trick.)
- Jae Suk. - You have been waiting for me.
Forget it.
(It wouldn't work with 10 years of experience in Running Man.)
Why can't I find a single one?
There it is. I found one.
(Suk Jin finally finds the first chance card.)
This is...
(Minus 3 bullets?)
I can give it to someone else.
(I'm doomed.)
There it is.
(He hasn't learned much during his 10 years on Running Man.)
He is a fool. Suk Jin is a fool.
It's a bad one, right?
(How did she know?)
We can't throw it away, right?
- You can't throw it away. - You can't throw it away.
(At that moment)
(Mesh Boy with a chance card appears.)
What? Hey, don't do that.
(His target is foolish Suk Jin.)
Hey.
(He tries to subdue Suk Jin.)
(Shoving it in forcibly)
You can't do that. Hey!
You can't shove it in like that. Hey!
(Mesh Boy leaves after giving him a big gift.)
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk found something.)
- There is one here. - Where?
(His satisfied facial expression...)
(makes the hyenas gather.)
- I can't show you. - Let's see it.
I can't show you.
(He steals the chance card.)
(Laughing)
Come here.
(Men with the average age of 52 play tag.)
(He is happy to run around with Jae Suk.)
My goodness.
(Tag ends on a happy note.)
It looks like they are playing a game on their own.
(People with minus chance cards gather around Suk Jin.)
There are no chance cards. Did you find one?
(Every viewer knows what this look in his eyes means.)
(He must have a minus chance card.)
Let's catch him. Let's put one together.
Hey, what are you doing?
(Bursting into laughter in an emergency situation)
Hey.
(Giving the chance card forcibly)
This is a chance to lose your minus chance cards!
Give it to him!
(See-Through Boy gives one to Kwang Soo.)
What is up with him? What is up with him?
- A chance card dropped. - Can I put two on him?
(They have 2 minutes left.)
(He must give the minus chance card to someone else in 2 minutes.)
Run from Suk Jin. Run from Suk Jin.
(Suk Jin only has one rival.)
Suk Jin, don't be like that. Don't be like that.
(He plans to give it to So Min.)
Don't be like that. I am serious.
(When two rivals are fighting,)
(he appears again with the crazy look in his eyes.)
- Please. - Get him.
Please. Please.
(Laughing)
(He bursts out in laughter for the 3rd time.)
(In a critical situation,)
(he bursts out in laughter again.)
My goodness.
(The best men laugh in times of struggle.)
- It dropped. - It dropped.
(With Suk Jin's laughter virus,)
(the preliminary mission ends.)
- Time's up. - Kwang Soo, you dropped this.
- Time's up. - Why would you give that to me?
(What are you doing?)
Why would you give that to me? You dropped it.
(He was happy.)
Starting from Jae Suk, show us the chance cards you have.
(Settling the chance cards they obtained)
- I got 3. - 3 of what?
(Jae Suk gets 3 bullets.)
Three bullets. Keep it.
Next, So Min.
Steal five yut candy bars from the member of your choice.
(She got a chance card.)
- Kwang Soo. - Why me?
(She chooses Kwang Soo who she believes stole.)
You stole my candy bars.
I really didn't.
(Holding his laughter)
- Five candy bars. - Do I give them to her now?
(So Min gets 5 yut candy bars from Kwang Soo.)
Minus three yut candy bars.
How about the card for the bullets?
(Minus 3 yut candy bars and minus 9 bullets)
Minus 12 in total.
- He failed to give one to me. - Really?
It's over for him.
- Minus nine bullets. - The card for the bullets.
(The result of settlement)
- It's over for him. - I know.
(The result of the preliminary mission)
You can only attack the color of your choosing...
(Final Race)
in the Selective Survival Game.
(All or Nothing Race, Selective Survival Game)
Choose a color from red, blue, yellow, and black...
(Selective Survival Game)
(Choose the color of hat they want.)
and wear a hat in the beginning of the race.
Then spin the roulette...
(Spin the roulette to choose the target color.)
to choose the target color.
(Shoot the balloons with a toy gun.)
You can only attack the color you got on the roulette.
(You're out if all 10 balloons pop.)
You are out if all 10 of your balloons pop.
(Out)
The colors will get taken out 1 by 1 after 20 minutes.
(The colors will get taken out 1 by 1 after 20 minutes.)
10 balloons?
We will give you the candy bars in accordance with the rankings...
(They must choose the hat and the target color carefully.)
and decide who gets a prize or a penalty.
- It sounds hard. - So there are targets.
(The same colors must unite.)
There are targets.
There is another thing. If you want to change...
(And)
your color or the target color,
(If you want to change your color or the target color,)
pay with a candy bar at the voting booths...
(pay 1 candy bar at the voting booth,)
and receive a chance to change it.
(and receive a chance to change it.)
You only get 10 bullets in the beginning,
(You get 10 bullets in the beginning.)
but you can purchase more with a candy bar.
(You can purchase more with a candy bar.)
- How many for a candy bar? - Three bullets for a candy bar.
(3 bullets for a candy bar)
- Three bullets for a candy bar. - Yes.
You can also pick up other members' bullets.
(You can also pick up other members' bullets.)
I have minus candy bars.
(Whining)
- We get 10 bullets. - 10 bullets.
(Laughing at So Min)
It's best to save up on the bullets.
We need to save up on the bullets.
(Save up on the bullets,)
This is complicated. I am conflicted.
(and survive as long as you can.)
- Please go to your respective spot. - Okay.
(Who will be the survival of the heartless survival shoot?)
(Current Number of Candy Bars)
How many bullets do you currently have?
(Kwang Soo must hand in 9 bullets out of 10.)
Minus nine bullets.
Then you will start with one bullet.
That's so annoying.
(Loading)
You can simply take them out.
(9 bullets get removed.)
Why... You can simply take them out.
(Highly disappointed)
Here you go.
Hold on. Can I buy the bullets right away?
(Bullets)
- The game needs to start first. - Then I can buy the bullets.
(Kwang Soo plans to buy more bullets upon start.)
You will first select the color of your hat.
(They choose their hat color first.)
From red, blue, yellow, and black, select a color.
(They can select the color of their hat...)
(from red, blue, yellow, and black.)
- Red, blue, yellow, and black? - Yes.
I choose black. I bet a lot of them will choose black.
(Suk Jin chooses black.)
(The members who get black as the target color...)
(can attack him.)
All right.
I bet people won't choose this color.
(Haha and Jae Suk wear a black hat as well.)
I will select blue.
(The hat color)
This wig is so funny.
(She wears a blue hat over the wig.)
It's the color of passion.
(Red hat of passion)
Red.
I see why I selected red.
(He's wearing red stockings of passion.)
I had my eyes on the red hat for some reason.
(He matches the color with the stockings.)
Okay.
(Kwang Soo's wearing red.)
Kwang Soo.
- We are on the same boat. - That's right.
(Kwang Soo.)
Now, please spin the roulette and choose your target color.
(The target color is decided...)
Okay, I got it.
(by spinning the roulette.)
(Jong Kook's target color is...)
(black!)
- It's black. - Okay.
Gosh, I should have gotten red.
(What a bummer.)
(Thankfully, Kwang Soo won't be attacked by Jong Kook.)
(Kwang Soo's target color is red.)
It's red.
(Jong Kook?)
(Will Kwang Soo be able to attack Jong Kook?)
(Everyone spins the roulette and gets a target color.)
The race starts.
Here comes a gunman!
My target color is black.
(Confident)
I need to find a black hat.
(They all move to find their targets.)
If I am at the bottom, I will use up my candy bars...
and go out with a bang.
(Suk Jin carefully enters the battlefield.)
Where are they?
(Let's see.)
Suk Jin is wearing a black hat.
(He is my target.)
My first target is Suk Jin.
(They keep their target color a secret.)
Suk Jin.
(While looking for a red hat, Jae Suk finds Jong Kook.)
Jong Kook, is your target color black?
(Suddenly polite)
What?
You kept looking this way.
(He can attack Jae Suk.)
I looked since your target color could be red.
No. I am not attacking you.
(Kwang Soo hurriedly purchases bullets.)
Then why...
(They are each other's target.)
I want to pass through.
Where are you going?
What? Can't I pass through?
Even if I am wearing a black hat, you shouldn't shoot me now.
Excuse me?
Is there such a rule?
Are you going to shoot?
Since when did we have such a rule?
(They're getting closer with tension.)
- Are you going to shoot? - A black hat...
(Red Jae Suk, Black Jong Kook)
You aren't going to shoot, are you?
- What? - I mean...
I guess red isn't your target color.
(Jae Suk attempts to attack.)
You shot at me!
(Jae Suk's camera)
(He can't help but go backward since Jong Kook's guards are up.)
Hey.
(Giggling)
(Kwang Soo finished loading up the bullets!)
Why does it keep coming off?
(Kwang Soo joins.)
This... Hey.
Why does it keep coming off? This... Hey.
(He approaches quickly...)
(and shoots Jong Kook without hesitation.)
(He takes out 3 of his balloons.)
(This is good.)
(Jae Suk uses this chance to run away.)
Gosh, Jae Suk.
(That's too bad.)
- Haha. - Gosh, Jae Suk.
(Then Haha who was hiding appears.)
Haha's color is black too.
I will take out Haha. I will take out Haha.
(Haha appeared as an easy target...)
(just when Jong Kook was motivated.)
My goodness.
(Screaming)
(He chases after him mercilessly.)
- Come on! - Suk Jin's hat is black too.
(Suk Jin's hat is black too.)
(He hits 2 targets with 1 bullet.)
(Haha and Suk Jin quickly lose their balloons because of him.)
Okay.
I should change my hat.
- I would like to change my hat. - Turn in one candy bar.
(Jae Suk changes the hat color, so Jong Kook can't attack him.)
I will change it...
to yellow.
(He changes to a yellow hat.)
- I will change the color of my hat. - Okay, to which color?
- A yellow hat, please. - I will change my hat.
(Haha switches to a yellow hat.)
I will change my hat.
Yellow.
(The symbol of the weakest members, yellow hat)
No one is wearing a yellow hat.
(They leave the voting booth.)
- Let's be allies. - Why are there so many yellow hats?
What?
- Why are there so many yellow hats? - What?
Why are there so many yellow hats?
(It's the color of cowards.)
There are so many yellow hats.
Then yellow will be the target color.
(The lack of communication made them all wear a yellow hat.)
All of them changed to a yellow hat.
(I see.)
Shall I change my target color? How much is it?
I will change my target color. I will take my chances.
(Jong Kook wants to change the target color to yellow.)
I will take my chances. 1, 2... Please let it be yellow.
(If he spins to yellow, he can attack all yellow hats.)
Yellow, yellow, yellow. Yellow.
Gosh.
(He gets red instead.)
- Did I get red? - Your target color is red.
I can spin it again, right?
I will spin it again.
(He pays the candy bar to try again.)
All right.
Hold on. Blue? I don't see any blue hats.
(This time, it's blue.)
(Gosh. There's no blue.)
I will spin it once more.
(Tenacity to get yellow)
I see how people lose their fortune by gambling.
This will be the last time.
(Unlike his wish,)
(he keeps getting different colors.)
It won't be entertaining unless I get the color.
It's black again. This is driving me crazy.
I will spin it again.
(He lost 7 candy bars to the roulette.)
(Finally, it's yellow.)
I got yellow this time, right?
Okay. How many candy bars did I use?
(Now Jong Kook can attack yellow.)
8 candy bars? 7 candy bars?
- Seven candy bars. - For goodness' sake.
(He used 7 candy bars for a right to attack the yellow hats.)
I should change to a blue hat.
(His target Haha hovers around him.)
Is he coming toward me?
Haha.
I should take out Haha.
(He charges toward Haha.)
He is coming this way! I need to change my color!
Stop, Jong Kook. Let me go this once.
(He was flustered that he ran to a dead end.)
Let me go this once. I will give you bullets.
- I will give you a candy bar. - How many will you give me?
(Explosive situation)
- Give me candy bars. - Two candy bars.
(He tries to negotiate with candy bars.)
- I need at least 3. - I can't give you 3.
- I used 7. - Jong Kook.
- I used 7. - Let's go with 2.
(Please)
- Jong Kook, I... - Otherwise, I will take you out.
(Surprised)
Hold on.
- 2. - Give me 3.
(Then give me 3.)
Give me 3. I will leave if you give me 3.
- Jong Kook. - Hurry up.
- Jong Kook. - Give me three.
- I used seven. - We run a restaurant together.
- Give me 3. - 2 bullets and 1 candy bar.
(He hears nothing.)
Give me three.
You will find more yellow hats down there.
(Throwing a bait)
- I know. - Please, Jong Kook.
- Please, Jong Kook. - Should I finish you off?
All right, all right.
(The deal is about to fall apart.)
(He loses 1 balloon by stalling.)
All right, all right. Two candy bars.
One.
- Give me 2. Hurry up and give me 2. - What?
- Give me 2. - 2?
- Hurry up. - Will you give them back?
Give them to me.
- You seem like a bully. - Give them to me.
(Jong Kook's camera)
- Then... - I could take you out.
(The sleeveless-shirt man was trembling.)
- All right, all right. - Hurry up and give them to me.
(He offers 2 in front of the gun.)
- Go now. - All right. You can go ahead.
I will be smiling.
It's the first time I got candy bars stolen.
(New experience)
- I got two candy bars. - This is so annoying.
(Jong Kook's first sacrifice is Haha.)
Hey, I used seven candy bars.
I swear.
It was so hard to get yellow.
(He moves quickly to find the next target.)
(Ji Hyo lost 7 balloons to Se Chan's attack.)
I didn't know you could attack the same color.
Ji Hyo.
I only have a few candy bars.
(It's so sad.)
(At that moment)
(Kwang Soo ambushes her.)
(He takes out the rest of the balloons.)
(He takes Ji Hyo out instantly and runs away.)
Who was it? Who was it?
(She didn't even see him.)
Jong Kook?
Gosh.
(Ji Hyo is out 8 minutes into the race.)
(After eliminating Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo went to the voting booth.)
I will spin the roulette.
(Kwang Soo's target color is...)
Please.
(red.)
- Red. - Red.
(Popping)
(Why did his balloon pop?)
(His balloon got caught on the tape.)
(Who was that?)
Why did it pop? Why?
(He becomes confused after attacking himself.)
(While Kwang Soo is in a daze from losing a balloon,)
Stop it.
(the two youngest members are having a love quarrel.)
(As a result, So Min has 1 balloon left.)
I have one balloon left.
(She accepts her fate.)
(Popping)
So Min is out.
(Devastated)
Look at So Min who is knocked out.
(Shooting)
(I am so annoyed.)
What should I do? I am so angry.
You lasted for a while.
(She is too upset to leave.)
(Kwang Soo approaches her.)
(He collects her bullets.)
- Stop it. - You don't need them.
(The hyena in survival games doesn't miss any unused bullets.)
(Haha was picking up bullets like Kwang Soo.)
Hey.
(Jae Suk appears.)
Give them to me.
Give them to me. They are mine!
(He's brazen as if he's getting back the money he borrowed.)
How are they yours?
What is going on? Everyone is stealing things from me.
(Whining)
I am sorry. I am sorry.
(While Haha's getting stolen...)
(20 minutes have passed.)
Now, black will disappear.
Black will disappear among the hats and target colors.
(Black disappears among the hats and target colors.)
(The members whose hat color or target color is black...)
(select a different color.)
I will change my hat color too.
(Jae Suk, Suk Jin, and Se Chan unite with a red hat.)
Was your hat color blue?
Let's go.
What's your target color?
- What's your target color? - Yellow.
(The target color)
- Are you sure? - Yes.
- Is it yellow? - Yes, I changed it.
We should take out Jong Kook first.
(The yellow hat)
- But Jong Kook... - We shouldn't fight.
(Suk Jin wants to get rid of Jong Kook in a yellow hat,)
- Jong Kook is on his first vest. - Really?
(but his target color is actually red.)
- You are on your first vest, right? - Yes.
I tried to pick it up earlier, but...
(Popping)
Gosh, you startled me.
All right. Change into your second vest.
(Suk Jin's ambush)
Gosh, you startled me.
All right. Change into your second vest.
Is his target color red?
(The target color)
Change into your second vest.
Give me a vest.
(He talked about taking out Jong Kook together.)
How...
- Change into your second vest. - That was too low.
Jae Suk, I won't shoot you.
(Relaxed)
- Se Chan. - My target color is yellow.
- I can't shoot you anyway. - It's yellow, right?
(Suk Jin's happy that his strategic play succeeded.)
It isn't red, right?
It isn't red. My target color is yellow.
(Happy)
(However)
- Okay. - What?
(Se Chan shot Suk Jin.)
(Startled)
- Okay. - What?
- Suk Jin. - Be careful not to show your back.
(Se Chan said his target was yellow,)
Suk Jin is out.
(but it's actually red.)
For goodness' sake.
(Suk Jin is eliminated by Se Chan.)
Suk Jin is out.
Is your target color red?
(After taking out Suk Jin,)
I will change my hat color to yellow.
(Se Chan switches to a yellow hat.)
I put in one candy bar.
(One man watches Se Chan...)
(as he takes his chances.)
Suk Jin is out.
(This man in a sleeveless top dreams of turning the tables.)
What?
(Haha's location)
Hold on. I will take Jae Suk out.
(5 people remain.)
All right.
(Current target state)
(Jae Suk catches a breath.)
(One man aims his gun at him.)
(Haha's camera)
(The sniper in a sleeveless top)
(He shoots.)
We need to join forces.
- What? - Is someone there?
Haha is there. Haha is there.
- Haha's hat is yellow. - Haha's hat is yellow.
(He missed two shots.)
Shall we go and take him out?
- I will enter. - Okay.
(I scared them.)
(Meanwhile)
So Haha is still alive.
(Jong Kook and Se Chan gathered to unite.)
We need to figure out the color of Haha and Kwang Soo's hats.
(He's curious of other three's hat color.)
If their target color is yellow... I mean, blue... No.
Would you go and look at the drone?
Go and look at the drone?
- I mean... - Drone.
(He really calls it.)
I mean,
find the person who is flying the drone...
(Will he be the first one to patrol with a drone in Running Man?)
and figure out the color of their hats.
- I see. Where is the operator? - It's a good idea, right?
(Interested)
Hold on. It's coming this way.
(The drone flies to Se Chan.)
Operator.
Where are you?
(He tries to talk to the drone.)
Where are you flying the drone?
(Follow me.)
He is here. The operator is here.
Sir.
(Jong Kook found the drone director.)
Please go to the battlefield...
and see their hat colors.
(The patrol drone is dispatched.)
This way.
(A drone gets dispatched for the children's shooting game.)
It's like a war movie.
I just need to see their heads.
(Se Chan is the commander who leads the drone.)
Go up higher.
(It flies high...)
There we go.
Please go closer.
(and approaches closely.)
I see one yellow hat. If we go diagonally...
(Yellow, blue, blue)
One blue hat. How about the other one?
Kwang Soo still has a blue hat.
This is really good.
(Amazed by the new technology)
This must be how they use a drone for a war.
(He observes everything with a drone.)
Red will disappear.
- Will red disappear? - Yes.
Red disappeared, right?
(Jong Kook and Se Chan's target is red.)
Blue still exists.
(They need to pick between yellow and blue.)
(Now, blue and yellow are the only colors.)
(It's time to make a decisive move.)
(The ones who usually hit and run have a face-off.)
- Okay. - Haha.
It would be our loss if we go against each other.
That's right. Let's not shoot at each other.
(They pretend to have a ceasefire.)
Give me one bullet.
(At that moment)
(Popping)
- Gosh! - Okay!
(Jong Kook appears.)
(Jong Kook figured out the situation through the drone.)
Let's not shoot at each other. Give me one bullet.
(Jong Kook's camera)
- Yes! - Haha is out.
(Haha is out.)
Haha is out.
(It's you again?)
Okay. Kwang Soo remains.
(His next target is Kwang Soo.)
(He tries to corner him.)
What? I have no one to shoot.
- I have no one to shoot. - Why?
(Kwang Soo's target is blue, but he's the only blue.)
No one else has a blue hat.
Your target color is blue.
- What's your target color? - Blue.
Are you sure?
Se Chan, take the right.
(The Drone Squad works together one more time.)
- Okay. Go. - Go.
- Jong Kook. - Move out of the way.
(The target is Kwang Soo.)
- Move out of the way. - Let's go together.
(He approaches Kwang Soo and shoots mercilessly.)
(But...)
(Jong Kook's balloons pop.)
Hey, you punk.
(Popping)
Let's go together.
(Se Chan pretended to go after Kwang Soo.)
(His real target was Jong Kook.)
(He easily takes out two balloons.)
(When he spun the roulette for the target color earlier,)
(he got yellow.)
Yellow?
- What's your target color? - Blue.
(Brazen)
Are you sure?
(He fooled Jong Kook...)
(and shot at his back.)
I popped two of Jong Kook's balloons.
(Jong Kook's first vest is over.)
Run!
- Se Chan, okay. - Kwang Soo.
Okay, Se Chan.
(Yang Se Chan, the master of fooling Kim Jong Kook)
- Kwang Soo, run. - Okay, I got it.
(Jong Kook's weakness is that he trusts Se Chan too much.)
I can't believe him.
I can't trust Se Chan anymore.
My love for Se Chan is over.
(Jong Kook becomes furious.)
(Without a care for his balloons,)
(he succeeds to take out Se Chan.)
Okay.
(Trembling)
Am I out?
Take him out.
(He takes out Kwang Soo mercilessly...)
(when he falls down.)
Take him out.
(2 people are out. 2 people remain.)
Se Chan is out.
Now...
(Jae Suk with double guns appears.)
Look at Jae Suk.
- Double guns. - Double guns.
(Double guns...)
He has double guns.
(versus Double muscles)
Let's shoot from a long distance.
(Boasting)
- Shall we do that? Okay. - Okay.
- I will load up on the bullets. - Okay.
(There is a reason why Jae Suk suggested a long-distance match.)
(Long-distance shooting is Jae Suk's forte.)
(He takes out a balloon with his double guns.)
(Jae Suk's camera)
Jae Suk's hit rate is no joke.
(My goodness.)
(Jae Suk sometimes becomes cool when he has a gun in his hands.)
Gosh, Jae Suk. Hold on.
(Jong Kook gains energy when he wears a sleeveless top.)
(Jong Kook's camera)
(They are neck-and-neck.)
Why are you using double guns?
(Jae Suk with 3 balloons...)
(versus Jong Kook wth 1 balloon)
(At that moment,)
(Jae Suk's balloon pops.)
(Now, it's 2 balloons versus 1 balloon.)
Okay.
(He used one of his balloons as bait...)
(and targeted Jong Kook's last balloon.)
Okay.
(Yoo Jae Suk wins.)
Yoo Jae Suk wins, and Kim Jong Kook is in second place.
(Jae Suk, who won, and Jong Kook, who fought from a long distance,)
(both put up a strong fight.)
- This was good. - It was at a long distance.
(It was a fair fight, which is hard to see on Running Man.)
- It wasn't a cheap fight. - Right. It was good.
The zebra pants I'm wearing today...
(The zebra pants were perfect for the mission.)
I was like a zebra running around in an open field.
I know.
(It was a clean fight that made them proud of themselves.)
(It's time to hand out the candy bars.)
This is the final result.
Jae Suk came in 1st place, and Jong Kook came in 2nd.
Really?
1st place gets 20 candy bars.
(The number of candy bars given)
2nd place gets 15, and 3rd place gets 10.
- The others will get 8, 6, 4, 2, 0. - We used a lot.
(It's time to announce the rankings based on the result.)
- I'll announce the results. - Okay.
- With 32 candy bars... - Someone got that many?
(Will the winner be among the 1st and 2nd place winners...)
(who got 20 and 15 candy bars?)
- It's Kim Jong Kook. - Me?
(Kim Jong Kook wins with 32 candy bars.)
- I came in first place? - He got a lot.
- It's Kim Jong Kook. - Me? I came in first place?
He got a lot.
- I used a lot. - You didn't exchange them.
(The 2 candy bars from Haha were crucial to his victory.)
- I exchanged 10. - With 31, Jae Suk is in 2nd place.
(Yoo Jae Suk wins 2nd with 31 candy bars.)
How disappointing.
That last one.
(The 3rd place that can win 1 prize is...)
In 3rd place... The person in 3rd place can choose 1.
Is it me?
It's Haha, who has 26.
(Haha with 26 candy bars.)
What?
- Really? He has that many? - He has 20 on him.
- He didn't exchange a lot. - Why does he have so many?
In 4th place is Se Chan with 22.
That's too bad.
In 5th place is Ji Hyo with 11.
- In 6th place, Suk Jin with 9. - I have 11?
- Gosh. - What?
In 7th place is Kwang Soo with 8.
In 8th place is So Min with 3.
- Hold on. - So...
(If that's the case.)
since So Min came in last place,
Haha loses his spot in 3rd place and will get the penalty too.
(Haha loses his 3rd place and receives the penalty.)
- So who's in 3rd place? - Se Chan is in 3rd place.
(1. If So Min or Haha comes in last, they both get the penalty.)
Yang Se Chan is in 3rd place.
(2. If they don't, the one with the lower score will get the penalty.)
(Se Chan wins 3rd place.)
- So I don't get the penalty, right? - You don't.
Okay!
- See? You can't steal mine. - It's a difference of one.
Weren't we competing against each other?
- You had to take care of her. - You're right.
(He would've avoided the penalty if he didn't steal her candy bars.)
We could've avoided it if I gave her three.
First, we'll have...
(It's time to reveal the prizes.)
the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd place winners roll their balls first.
The tablet.
(It's pinball lottery today.)
Where's the tablet?
I would like to get the massage gun.
(The gift list)
Is Kwang Soo's life-sized cardboard cutout still here?
(Clothing care machine, Tablet PC, Turntable, Photo of staff,)
The photo of the staff is much better...
(Kwang Soo and So Min's life-size figure, etc.)
than a life-sized cardboard cutout of Kwang Soo.
I want to cheer for you guys.
(1st place gets 2 balls,)
I'll start now. In 1, 2, 3.
(2nd and 3rd place get 1 ball each.)
How will it go?
(It's lucky Se Chan's turn.)
- Let's go. - Go to the right.
(What will Se Chan, who came in 3rd place instead of Haha, get?)
Go to the right.
- Go to the right. What is it? - A dud.
- A dud. - It's a dud.
- A dud. - Serves you right.
(There are only 2 among 20, but he got it.)
I feel better now.
(That's good.)
- It's possible to get a dud. - I feel better too.
I got a dud?
(It's a talent for picking a losing lot.)
A dud came out among all of these.
Ji Hyo, I'll drop one here.
(It's Jae Suk's turn. He aims for the tablet PC.)
What if you go more that way?
- This way. - Drop them both at once.
Should we go for the tablet PC?
(He let go of the ball.)
(Jae Suk never won any good prizes.)
- What is it? - It's going this way.
It's coming this way.
(What will happen this time?)
Did it come this way?
It's the tablet PC.
(Did he get the tablet PC?)
- It's the tablet PC. - What?
(Eyes opening)
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(He's really surprised.)
(I'm really jealous.)
- Gosh! - Oh, my.
I must be going crazy.
- This is crazy. - That's incredible.
- What's with you? - You're lucky.
How did you get the tablet PC?
Why would you use your luck here?
How can someone unlucky get this?
(It's a miracle that's worth his 1 year of luck.)
This is insane.
(After Jae Suk, it's Jong Kook's turn.)
This won't do.
- Should I go for the tablet PC? - Of course.
(Jong Kook gets 2 balls.)
- Should I go? - Yes.
- It's heading for it. - It's the tablet pc.
(The 1st ball takes off.)
It's going to end up at the tablet PC.
- It's heading for it. - It's the tablet pc.
(He dropped his ball in the same place Jae Suk did.)
It's going to end up at the tablet PC.
- It's the tablet PC. - It won't go there.
(Will Jong Kook also win the tablet PC?)
It's going to end up at the tablet PC.
- It's going. - Tablet PC.
It's the group photo.
- Tablet PC. - It's the group photo.
(It's the photo of the crew,)
(which is next to the tablet PC.)
It's the group photo.
It's meaningful.
Our writers came out so nicely.
(It's for the members who always think about the crew.)
- They came out nicely. - How does it look? Let me see.
You should've added your names.
(It's unnecessarily in high quality.)
Min Hee is sitting in the front.
(It's framed so he can't just throw it away.)
We're grateful that you care so much about us.
- That's too bad. - This is...
- I'm going again. - It's so funny.
(Jong Kook tries his 2nd ball.)
- It's going in that direction. - Right.
(He tries again from the same spot.)
- Oh, no. Where are you going? - Goodness.
(Wait.)
- No. - It's going far.
(It's headed toward the right.)
- Oh, no. Where are you going? - Goodness.
No.
- Dud or clothing care machine. - Or Kwang Soo's cardboard cutout.
(What?)
(The ball is between the photo and the clothing care machine.)
No.
(Where will the ball go?)
- The clothing care machine. - Really?
(His eyes open wide just like Jae Suk.)
- Really? - What is this?
(He wins the clothing care machine.)
- What will you do? - Bo Pil is crying.
(As the members win two expensive prizes,)
SBS will go broke.
- He's crying. - Bo Pil is crying.
- It costs 1,500 dollars. - Really?
(we didn't know what to say for a second.)
What will Bo Pil do?
I'll go easy on you and just get the massage gun.
- The massage gun is nice. - Really?
(Really?)
I didn't tell you the penalty.
(It's time to announce the penalty in the midst of expensive prizes.)
- What is it? - You're right. Haha and So Min.
The penalty we've prepared for you is...
(The inconvenient and exhausting penalty for today is...)
I told you already that the penalty is inconvenient and exhausting.
You must make mask straps out of beads for the members.
(to make mask straps for the members out of beads.)
- Goodness. - Out of beads.
(It's the worst penalty...)
(of making gifts they won't want to give.)
It really is an annoying penalty.
This is going to be hard.
Okay, then. Goodbye.
(Excluding the two who will receive the penalty,)
Goodbye.
- Good job everyone. - Good job everyone.
(Jae Suk and Jong Kook who pitied the crew members...)
No, you don't have to give it to me.
(politely decline the prizes...)
- Take it with you. - Right.
(so the crew changed them into something else.)
- Do you want the massage gun? - Sure.
- I don't need the machine. - It's fine.
(We'll come up with a more realistic prize next time.)
You just need to put it in after you design it.
(So Min and Haha start to make beads bracelets.)
You can design it with the ones you want.
Who will you guys give it to?
I'll make it for...
(They decided who they'll give the bracelets to.)
(The process of making it and the people they will give it to...)
I should make it with the big ones.
(will be revealed next week during the gift-giving ceremony.)
This is nice. I like it. Isn't it pretty?