I'm here.
Am I the first one to arrive?
I'm sure I came first.
- Come on out. - I'm the first.
Move over.
I'm here, everyone.
I'm the first to arrive.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Well done today.
Guys, you should come by 9:30am tomorrow.
But if you arrive early, you will have some advantage.
What time are we supposed to get there?
- I'll be there at 8am. - What are you trying to do?
I'll be there at 8am.
The cameras aren't ready yet.
- We haven't even started. - You told me to come early.
This is nice.
You didn't know I'd come this early, did you?
Am I supposed to pick one?
My heart is racing. What should I do?
I really want to go to the ladies' room,
but I'm afraid someone would arrive while I'm gone.
But I want to pick one when others are watching.
To wind them up.
What's going on? Did anyone come already?
Yes. Someone's here already.
There was a camera in the parking lot.
So I was going to show myself...
Why are you trying so hard?
Why are you being like this?
Why did you come so early?
Why did you come an hour earlier?
You guys are unbelievable.
Gosh, you persistent ones.
- It's Se Chan. - Goodness.
- Did you guys not sleep at all? - I couldn't sleep.
Why did you come so early?
- Are you the first to arrive? - Yes.
She got here first.
Seok Jin doesn't sleep much.
Isn't he supposed to get here first?
- Let's make a bet. - That's a good idea.
I bet Jong Kook is next.
Jong Kook? Okay.
- Do you want to bet on Ji Hyo? - Are you kidding me?
- I bet on Haha. - Haha?
I'll go with Jae Seok.
Someone's coming.
It's Ji Hyo. I can't believe this.
Guys! Ji Hyo is here!
This is amazing.
She arrived even before the appointed time!
- It's never happened for 10 years. - Hey, Ji Hyo.
- Hurry. Song Ji Hyo! - Song Ji Hyo!
- Song Ji Hyo! - Song Ji Hyo!
This is unbelievable.
- You better return it now! - Why?
- What? - Why did you come so early?
- What's wrong? - Did you sleep here?
- Ji Hyo, did you... - Did you sleep here?
What happened?
I just came early. Why?
I just wanted to come early.
Did you drink last night?
I'm sure you did.
I'm not even fully awake.
I came really early.
My goodness.
- I came really early. - My goodness.
- Will you go over there and do it? - Why?
I'm just putting on a microphone. What's the problem?
I can see your belly.
Will you go to a sauna with me this weekend?
She's still half-asleep.
You all are still half-asleep.
You pretended not to care about this yesterday.
My gosh.
I just saw you come walking.
Why did you pretend to run right here?
- Why does your flag say Big Nose? - Why...
- It's already set. - I don't know what this is.
- What's that? - What is it?
Am I supposed to pick Big Nose...
no matter when I arrive?
Today, each of you will take on a special role...
and have a race.
And each role has different benefits.
So you should pick one carefully starting from number one.
- By the way, Seok Jin will... - Yes?
play CEO Big Nose...
no matter what he chooses.
- Am I a CEO today? - Is he a CEO?
- Hey, stand straight. - CEO?
Stand upright in line.
He's a condescending CEO.
- What are they? - What?
There are a judge and a lawyer.
All right.
I guess some of them don't know what an analyst is.
- What is it? - An analyst?
- What is it? - What do you think it is?
Is it a person who arranges lists?
- What's an analyst? - An analyst.
- Isn't it a bad thing? - An analyst.
It's a person who analyzes companies.
- I see. - Something about companies.
- Like an industry analyst? - Yes.
- Gosh, this is... - Why do we have an analyst here?
A detective.
Jong Kook should be a detective.
- A lawyer. - Everyone.
- 10 years ago today, - Yes?
we filmed the first episode of Running Man.
- I see. - My gosh.
It's a meaningful day.
We had Hyo Lee in our first episode.
And Jung Eum.
Stop walking and start running. We're Running Man.
Hello, dear viewers.
- Hello. Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
My name is Lee Kwang Soo. And I'm 26 years old.
Kwang Soo is crying.
It's like a scene from a drama.
This is the 10th Anniversary Special.
You will pick a role and have a race...
- with your own benefits. - Really?
So you should choose your role carefully from number one.
- This is... - So Min, pick one.
I mean, this is so...
I can tell a judge and a lawyer are the good ones.
- Right. Pick something like that. - It's better than a butler.
- But I'm... - A gambler might be a good one.
- I agree. That can be right. - Right.
The good ones might be...
You like to bet.
Then I'll...
- Pick a gambler. - That's right.
- I knew it. - Look at her.
Once you pick one, you can't change your choice.
All right. Next up is number two.
- She's unbelievable. - It might be a good one.
- I know. It's possible. - I pick the judge.
- I'll go with the judge. - You're a judge?
- That doesn't sound right. - It doesn't suit you.
- I don't think it'll be fun. - That doesn't suit you at all.
- If you... - He's a crazy judge.
- All right. Se Chan. - It's me. What should I pick?
You should be a butler.
I might look like a lawyer in a suit.
- Just give it a try. - He's a judge,
and you're a lawyer?
- What? Why? - How would you clear up a case?
- What's wrong with that? - It will be a mess.
- It will be terrible. - We will take bribes.
All right then. I'll be a detective.
- Okay. - Okay. It sounds about right.
- A detective sounds good. - Ji Hyo.
What about a butler?
- A butler? - Yes.
- I will... - I like your clothes today.
Isn't it funny that Ji Hyo reaches out to the lawyer?
It's a mess. We are a judge, a detective, and a lawyer.
Go for it.
- We can work together for justice. - Go for it. This is funny.
Who are you going to defend?
- I'll pick a lawyer. - Okay.
- This is fun. - Jong Kook.
- We are professionals. - What should I pick?
The insurance salesman sounds suspicious.
I pick the analyst.
- Get ready to be a butler. - A butler?
- You're a butler. - It works for you.
- Don't make me a butler. - Butler Yu.
It suits you.
- All right. - Good.
- Okay. - You're a butler.
- It's settled. - He's holding it.
We don't know what it is yet.
We don't know how it will work.
CEO Big Nose just got a warning letter.
- Okay. - Oh, no.
Am I CEO Big Nose's butler?
- Yes. - Of course.
- Really? - What about the detective?
Why am I worried about Seok Jin?
- Really? - You'll see what will happen.
A warning letter.
"CEO Big Nose, there will be a party..."
- "to wish you good health today." - It's a party?
"During the party, I will take the gold bars..."
"you've been bragging about."
"So make sure to stay vigilant."
"From Thief Running Man."
My gold bars? The gold bars from my life savings?
This is the 10th Anniversary Special,
Running Man Thief Race.
And you guys are invited to the party...
to wish good health for the richest man...
in the country, CEO Big Nose.
But there are two thieves who are going after...
- CEO Big Nose's gold bars. - You see?
- There are thieves. - I knew it.
You have to arrest them all to win the race.
- Those who arrived early... - Wait.
- I agree. - Right?
- You got a mission, right? - You got one.
- Why else would they come early? - This is frustrating.
- When did you give the mission? - It's strange...
- that they voluntarily came early. - You'll go to Big Nose Mansion,
and there is a room of gold bars.
Before the mission, each member will get to...
search the room for 50 seconds.
During the time, the thieves can move the gold bars in the safe...
into the thieves' safe.
Once all the members leave the room,
you will carry out the mission.
And the videos of two members with the lowest records...
will be revealed after the mission.
After watching the videos, you will have a vote...
and single out the thieves.
Now we will reveal the benefits of each role...
you just picked.
- Let's open CEO Big Nose first. - What's my benefit?
I don't even know what my benefit is.
CEO Big Nose can deprive the butler of the right to vote.
Gosh, what is this?
- The butler? - Take away the right to vote?
- Hey, fan me. - So you don't get to vote?
- I don't want to. - Just do it.
- No. - I'll take away your right to vote.
- I don't care. - Just do this!
- I said no. - Do this.
The butler.
- I think the butler is a good one. - The butler.
I knew it.
If he knows the passcode, he knows everything.
If he doesn't share it with us, it means he's the thief.
The CEO is nothing without me.
- It means he's... - He can't do anything without me.
I must know the passcode. I should know that.
- You don't. - Only the butler knows it.
I don't know the passcode of my own safe?
You don't know.
- I told you. - What kind of CEO am I?
- I mean... - If I don't know it...
And he knows it?
- The passcode of my safe? - How can a CEO not know?
- So you should be nice to me. - It doesn't make sense.
Jae Seok is the influential one here.
- The judge. - It doesn't make sense.
- The judge gets two ballots. - Two ballots?
We should be careful around him.
- Detective. - Detective.
- I'm the detective. What is it? - Kwang Soo, take my side.
He can watch any video for 20 seconds.
Am I supposed to share it with others?
It's up to you.
If you're innocent, you'll share the correct information with them.
If you're a thief, you will hide what you saw.
The lawyer.
She can rule out a suspect she wants...
- at the first trial. - It's not bad.
- It's a good one. - Because she's a lawyer.
- She can exclude a suspect. - That's right.
- That's right. She can rule it out. - Okay.
- The insurance salesman. - It's me.
He can find out the number of stolen gold bars?
- He knows how many are stolen. - What's that?
It's the worst one.
- Why would you want to know it? - It's the worst.
We will find it out eventually.
Why would you want to know about what's already stolen?
I'm just like a viewer here.
The insurance salesman can see...
how hard the thieves worked in each round.
- That's right. - In each round.
The gambler.
The prize and penalty are doubled?
- Whatever it is... - In the live broadcast,
if you think your team will win, you can double your bet.
- Whatever it is, I can double it. - It's a good one.
- I like that. - The prize can be doubled too.
- That's amazing. - It's a nice one.
The prize can be doubled.
- That's not bad. - The penalty is doubled too.
Analyst.
"Guess the thief chosen by viewers..."
If the analyst successfully guesses who will get the most votes,
he or she wins a penalty transfer card.
And the card can be used the same day.
- That sounds fun. - Really?
- So I have to say it at the end? - The analyst is pretty good.
- Yes, at the end. - At the end.
Okay.
Just so you know, the thieves heard about the roles...
- and the capabilities beforehand. - Really?
The thieves can be caught...
through three trials.
In the first trial, the members will take a vote to choose two suspects.
And I will tell you...
if any of the suspects are thieves.
- Okay. - Thieves...
In the second trial, you will take a vote to choose one suspect...
and see if he or she is a thief.
Okay.
The final trial will take place...
during the much-anticipated live broadcast at the end of the show.
The viewers will have the same information as you have...
while watching today's race...
and can vote by sending a text.
The identity of the suspect chosen by the viewers...
will be revealed during the live broadcast.
Got it.
There's a penalty?
Among the viewers who successfully guessed the thief,
one gets a massage chair,
and 10 get name tags signed by the members.
Kwang Soo, can you demonstrate?
Can it be used by someone who is 2m tall?
- I pushed the button. - It's extending.
- Here... - It even massages your feet.
There you go.
These days...
- I pushed the button. - It's extending.
- It's extending. - Look at this.
Even Kwang Soo can fit?
How does it feel? Does it massage here too?
- I definitely want this. - It massages here too.
- How does it feel? - It must feel nice.
It's very relaxing.
Is it working?
- Just stay still. - Stay still.
- You should test it. - We'll give the thumbs up.
Thank you so much for your love and support...
- for the past 10 years. - Thank you!
- We can't thank our viewers enough. - I know.
Please watch the show carefully and text the name...
of the most suspicious one before the final trial.
The member who gets the most votes...
from the viewers will be put on Judgment Stand...
- I see. - during the live broadcast.
Dear viewers, please find the thief...
with your sharp eyes.
- Let's get started! - Yes!
Let's go!
The place looks fancy.
- Welcome to my house. - What's with that portrait?
- This is just 1 of my 99 rooms. - Oh, my.
Really?
Butler Yu, please show them around.
- I'm a judge! - I'm a detective!
I'll talk to the detective about that.
- I want to look cool. - Come on.
Guys, you're not allowed to sit on the sofa.
It's just for show. It's expensive. Don't sit on it.
- Everyone, have a seat. - Okay.
- Don't sit on it. - Everyone, have a seat.
Okay.
- I'll listen to the butler. - Gosh.
- Let's sit down. - My goodness.
I'm so glad to have you all here in this humble house.
Why don't you put that glass down?
- What? - Put that glass down.
He carries around the glass...
because he's petty.
Hey!
- His business is petty too. - He's petty.
- CEO Petty. - Yes, CEO Petty.
- His nickname is Petty. - I disagree.
- He's petty. - It's a crystal.
- Welcome to the Big Nose Mansion. - It's huge.
- There will be a party here? - Enjoy yourselves.
The first room search will begin shortly.
- Already? - Yes.
Each of you will search the room...
for 50 seconds in the order chosen by CEO Big Nose.
Each of you will search the room for 50 seconds.
According to the mission results, the videos of the bottom two...
will be revealed for 20 and 30 seconds each.
They will be revealed to the viewers as well.
- The videos will be revealed? - Hold on.
The passcode for the safe is supposed to be only known to me.
Do the thieves know it too?
- Yes. - Really?
The thieves know it when I don't?
- You'd know it if you're a thief. - I see, if I'm a thief.
- That's right. - Is that possible? You're the CEO.
The CEO might be one of the thieves.
There are 100 gold bars in total...
- distributed in 3 safes. - 100 gold bars?
That means the thieves can win up to 3,000 dollars.
Plus the massage chair.
One important thing to remember. Five additional ballots...
are hidden in the room.
- We can find them? - In the room?
- In the room? - Yes.
The more ballots you have,
the easier it'll be to catch the thieves without getting chosen.
That's right. But the thieves want to steal the gold bars,
so they'd want to buy time.
I'm suspecting those...
- who came early today. - Right.
The staff must have said this.
"To have an advantage over the others, come early..."
- "and be the judge or detective." - No.
- Right. - To be honest,
I'm not sure if the judge has any advantage over the others.
You do. You can cover up...
- for your teammates. - Right.
You have an advantage when picking out thieves.
- Of course. - You do.
How can you say the judge has no advantage?
Isn't it better to search first if you want ballots?
- If you want ballots, yes. - Right?
- Then I'll go first. - What?
- Does he get to decide everything? - You?
- Fine, go ahead. - You want to go first?
I'll go first and take a look.
- I have 50 seconds? Okay. - Yes.
The next person is Se Chan.
- Me? - And then?
And then Ji Hyo.
- Hold on. Why... - Why?
Those two won't be able to find anything anyway.
Those two won't find anything.
- You chose the stupid ones first? - That's why I chose them.
You should send me in after them...
so that I can see if any gold bars have been taken.
- You think so? You'll do that? - Yes.
If I go into the room...
after Ji Hyo,
- Me and... - Se Chan, and the CEO,
and no gold bar is missing,
that means the ones that enter after me could be the thieves.
- That's right. - You'll be able to figure that out.
That's why you should go in in the middle.
The butler is the most powerful.
Why does the butler have so much power?
- I should have become the butler. - What is this?
- I should have chosen it. - I could have chosen it.
Why didn't you become the butler?
I'll go in and take a look.
I'm too curious.
So this is it. This is the room.
This is my room.
My 3,000 dollars.
So this is the safe.
What is this? Time passes too fast. I couldn't do anything.
- Is this it? - It starts as soon as I enter?
My goodness.
- Seeing how Jae Seok is quiet... - What took you so long?
Is anything missing?
- There are gold bars missing. - There are?
My goodness.
- That means a thief has been there. - A thief has been there.
- A thief has been there. - A thief has been there. Who is it?
- Detective, Lawyer, - The stupid ones...
Judge, and CEO Big Nose.
- One or more of you... - One or more of them are thieves.
- are thieves. - It could be you too.
- That's right. - Is one gold bar missing?
- No. - How many were missing?
There are three safes,
- and I opened all of them. - Okay.
And gold bars were missing from two of them.
- Two of them? - They were broken into?
It could be you.
- It could be him, right? - I can check the videos.
If I check Jae Seok's, we'll know.
You'll see in my video.
I only checked the safes as soon as I entered the room.
Detective, let's do it like this.
I can find out the number of missing gold bars.
- The number... - And we'll say it at the same time.
You want to do that?
Everyone is so serious today.
I have no idea who are the thieves.
- Haha, go. - You should go, Haha.
All eight of you have searched the room.
- Insurance salesman Haha, - Yes.
come forward so I can tell you.
That's pretty useful.
It was a good one after all.
- Haha. - It's a good one.
That's the most important information right now.
- He's so cute. He looks like a kid. - You look so cute.
How many gold bars were missing?
When I checked, 3 or 4 were missing at most.
You can decide if you want to tell the number to the others.
Here's the number of gold bars taken by the thieves.
You should tell me, at least. I'm the CEO here.
Jae Seok said about four were missing.
How many were taken?
Haha, is the number higher than you expected?
What do you think?
Hold on.
- What happened? - Is the number high?
Why?
What's wrong? Tell us. I'm curious.
- Can I decide not to tell them? - Yes.
- Tell us. - Can he lie too?
- Yes, he can. - If he is a thief...
Tell us.
It'll help when we vote.
All right. The thing is, if I tell you the number now,
it can cause a bit of trouble.
You should tell us the number...
so we can compare...
I'll talk to the detective about that in private.
Bye, then.
Sir! Wait!
Take my business card, at least.
- Take my business card. - What is he doing?
What is he trying to do?
I don't know exactly what you're trying to do,
but it suits you so well that it drives me crazy.
- It suits him too well. - His hairstyle...
- It's perfect for him. - It suits him perfectly.
How many are missing?
- Right now... - You should tell me.
I can't tell you right now.
- You have to tell me, so... - Haha, tell me later.
- You have to tell me. - That was my decision.
- I'm so frustrated. - Goodness. Now...
Now it's hard to tell because everyone's so good.
We'll start the first mission where you will be able to see the video...
- of the members searching the room. - Okay.
It's called Catch Me If You Can.
- What is it? - For this mission,
we've invited a specialist to help CEO Big Nose...
improve his ability to react quickly to things.
- What is it? - Please come out.
- Who is it? - Is someone joining us?
It's a foreigner.
- Is he a Turkish ice cream vendor? - Turkish ice cream.
- Hello. - Hello.
Isn't he from Itaewon? Are you from Itaewon?
- Yes, I am. - I see.
- Come here. - Come here.
Come here.
It's impossible to grab the Turkish ice cream.
I've never done this before.
- Is it hard to grab? - You will go one at a time.
The order will be determined by how fast...
- you grab the ice cream. - I'm in trouble.
If the cone breaks,
the clock will still run as he changes the cone.
- I'll go first. - Have you done this before?
No, I haven't.
- Welcome. - Hello.
- What flavor would you like? - Vanilla, please.
- Vanilla? - Yes.
- It started. - Okay.
- Has the clock already started? - Yes, it has.
- Okay. So time is passing. - You don't...
have to play tricks. You can just give it to me.
- You can... - I'll give you everything.
- Okay. - Okay.
He said he's going to give you everything.
- Here you go. - This is...
What are you doing?
How is that possible?
- That's nice. - I don't have time!
- You have to grab it. - What are you doing?
That's nice.
- That's so cool. - Isn't the clock running?
That was so cool. The whole thing came out.
The whole thing can come out.
- Now... - He's focusing.
- I think he'll be able to grab it. - You have to grab it.
- Is this what you do? - Here.
It looks like it's going to fall.
- Darn it! - That's it.
- This is the funniest. - That makes you so angry.
You will never be able to grab it.
- There's no way. - There's no way.
It runs away.
That can make you angry.
Hit him on top of his head.
- It slipped out of his hand. - He's just putting it in his hand.
- Why can't you grab it? - He's just putting it in his hand.
Why can't you grab it?
I grabbed it!
He pretty much just gave it to you.
- It took 1 minute and 35 seconds. - Okay!
- He practically gave it to you. - Thank you.
- You have to grab it in one try. - Thank you.
He managed to succeed.
- Goodness. It's possible to get it. - He looks really upset.
Dondurma.
- Dondurma. - Dondurma.
- Kaymak. - Dondurma.
He learns all these random things while roaming around.
- Please give me vanilla. - Okay.
- I need to grab vanilla. - Okay.
I need to catch the vanilla ice cream quickly.
- Okay. - Dondurma.
- You have to grab it. - It's like "Comedy Big League".
- It's here. - It's here?
- It's here. - Where?
- It's here. - Where was it?
- Was it here? Should I grab it? - Here.
- Yes, grab it. - Grab it?
- Put it here. - He's getting annoyed by Se Chan.
- Put it over here. - Okay.
- You need to grab it. - His face is getting red.
Grab it.
- I can't grab it. - You have to grab it.
You have to do it slowly.
- Okay. - Go slowly.
- This is hilarious. - I'll go slowly like this.
- Like this. - The vendor is getting angry.
- Slowly. Like this. - Like this.
- This is hilarious. - You should give me a chance.
- Like this. - You should give me a chance.
You should give a chance. I missed my chance.
- I missed the chance you gave me. - You should've grabbed it.
I missed the chance you gave me.
- You should've grabbed it. - I missed the chance.
- Be honest. - Here.
You planned this skit with him, didn't you?
You met with the vendor, didn't you?
- Right? - Did you?
This is hard.
It seems like you planned out your lines too.
This is hard. You are good.
Dondurma.
- Dondurma. Kaymak. Grab it. - Dondurma. Kaymak.
Kaymak.
- He got it. - He got it.
- He got it. - He did it.
He got it.
It took 1 minute and 18 seconds.
Dondurma!
That was amazing.
How do you do it?
This is hard. What should I do?
- Welcome. - Hello.
What flavor would you like? Chocolate,
- vanilla... - Please give me vanilla.
- Vanilla? Okay. - Yes.
- Here you go. - You're giving me so little.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- What is he doing? - What is he doing?
Are you just giving it to me?
What is this?
I'm sorry, but...
- What is this? - What's going on?
- What are you doing? - Excuse me.
I'm not here to collect money.
- You shouldn't do that. - What is he doing?
- What are you doing, sir? - I'm not here to take...
- your money. - What are you doing?
He's a bit scary.
He could hit me, so I'm scared.
- Nice. - Here you go.
- Thank you. - Kim Jong Kook. 14 seconds.
- Everyone. - Yes.
I'll show you 20 seconds of Haha's entrance video.
It's okay to see my video.
Play the video.
- He doesn't go near the safe. - He doesn't go near it.
The safe is right there, but he's not going near it?
It might be on purpose.
- Could that be it? - He's not going to the safe?
He's searching... He must've planned it.
He must've planned it.
I'm sure Jae Seok will go to the safe.
We'll watch Jae Seok's video next.
- I go straight there. - I'm sure.
Because I need to check.
If we're lucky, we might get to see the inside of the safe.
It might be caught on video.
Play 30 seconds.
Look at that.
Press start.
The passcode shouldn't come out.
- Bottom, top. - I can't tell.
- Side, top. It's too long. - So Min, try to see it.
It's too long.
That was pretty much the same.
Shouldn't you have checked the thieves' safe?
I don't know the passcode to the thieves' safe.
So you can't see it.
- It was missing. - It disappeared.
- The 1st one still had it. - The 1st one still had it.
It was missing from the 2nd and 3rd safes.
The viewers are voting right now,
and they have seen this video as well.
We're going to vote on the first trial.
For the first trial, please write the name...
of the people you deem suspicious...
on your basic ballot and any additional ballots you have found.
- Did you find any? - No, I didn't.
And according to the results,
the two people with the most votes will be put on the Judgment Stand,
and you will be told whether or not there is a thief among them.
- Goodness. - Goodness.
I haven't told anyone yet,
but can I choose to tell a couple of people?
- You can do that if you want. - Who?
You said you would tell the detective.
- Tell me. - Detective.
- Yes. - You're not going to tell me?
- Okay. - The insurance salesman...
The insurance salesman must tell me.
- Since I'm the detective, - Hold on.
- I will decide. - I'm the judge,
- why aren't you telling me? - It's my gold bar.
Excuse me, insurance salesman. The gold bar is mine.
The detective and...
I have three ballots.
- I have more ballots. - And the judge. These two.
- No. - The judge.
I'm positive the thieves are in that group.
The analyst is included, but the butler is not?
- What's incredible... - Yes?
- How many disappeared? - right now is...
Jae Seok said that...
- they were missing, right? - Right.
- I checked it. - Right.
I checked the safes,
- the gold bars... - Are they still there?
They're still there.
I opened all three safes,
- two of the safes were empty. - Two of them?
They were all stolen?
This is how many gold bars there are.
- How many were stolen? - Were there a lot stolen?
I'm telling you exactly what I saw.
That's why I didn't announce it in front of everyone.
- I see. - Right.
It must be what he saw earlier. About the gold bars.
There must've been a hint.
I think we have to vote for Jae Seok.
- For now. - In this round.
- For the 1st trial. - Since it's the 1st round.
- Since we know. If we fail, - We should vote for him.
that means he was just mistaken.
I think we should vote for him.
- Okay. - Okay.
The detective can choose any member...
and watch 20 seconds of their video.
- I can? - Yes.
And the lawyer...
can take one person off the list of suspects.
- Okay. - That's right.
- Whose video should I watch? - Tell us.
You don't have to say it out loud.
We have something we're basing things on.
- You guys must be onto something. - Yes, we are.
Whose video do you want to see?
Did Haha find out something incredible?
It's not that I found something,
I'm moving according to the information I received.
It gave me goosebumps.
It is really surprising.
Really?
- I really got chills. - Did you really get chills?
What is it? I'm curious.
- Goodness. - That's incredible.
- Did you see something? - It's...
- My gosh. - Did you see something?
- Are you onto something? - It was...
It was short,
but the person was headed to that direction when it got cut.
- I see. - So I... Gosh.
- I see. - Yes.
There's someone you're suspicious of.
Lawyer Song can choose one person...
to be removed from the first trial.
I need to know something to take a person off the list.
You can choose yourself.
Really?
If I were to choose one person aside from myself...
Who would you choose?
I...
choose Kim Jong Kook.
- You'd take Jong Kook out? - Why would you take him out?
This is a weird choice.
She could take herself out, but she didn't.
I'm just saying we shouldn't waste ballots.
- This is too weird. - This is weird.
Isn't this strange?
Those two must be the thieves.
This could be it.
- This... - That can't be it.
How can you say that when you didn't even hear what I had to say?
You didn't even hear what I had to say.
This is nice. It's funny. Do this a bit longer.
- How do you know if it can't be? - Do it a bit longer.
This could lead to us finding both thieves right away.
- Tell us. - How? Tell us.
If she were to remove herself from the list,
then she can't remove herself...
- next time. So for her to... - Right.
To show that she's not a person of interest.
- Yes, that could be her plan. - Right, that's possible.
I'm not saying it is. I'm just saying it can be.
- That could be her plan. - Exactly.
Lawyer Song made her choice.
It means you can't choose Jong Kook as a suspect.
Unbelievable.
You will all now get to vote.
- The judge gets two votes. - Right.
We all get one vote?
There's a thief among those that went before us.
Before you and me, Se Chan, Kwang Soo,
- There's one among them. - and Ji Hyo went in.
It's one of the three.
Ji Hyo? But she...
Did you search the room after she did?
Yes, she went in before I did.
Right, so it's one out of the three.
- Then... - So Min, join us.
Who should I suspect?
I can't believe you're grouping up by yourselves.
It hurts, right?
What are you talking about? Can I hear it too?
- Whatever. - Why does it matter to you?
- Seok Jin... - You never listen to us anyway.
I suspect Haha, that's why.
Fine, be suspicious of him someplace else.
- I'll do as you say. - Then join us.
I'll add my vote.
Since we suspect Jae Seok as one of the thieves,
we should put someone up with him that seems innocent.
- To know for sure? - Right.
- That's right. - We need to be sure.
What if we put Kwang Soo on the chopping block too?
What if none of them is a thief?
- Exactly. - Then,
- the heat will be on Haha. - Yes, I'll be the next target.
- Because he threw us off. - I'll have to defend myself.
Exactly.
Please write down the name of a suspect.
Okay, there he goes.
Off he goes.
He's been given...
- an adorable character. - I know.
He was given a character we can only love.
I wouldn't mind signing 10 insurance contracts with him.
- Guys. - Yes?
- We have tallied your votes. - Sure.
CEO Big Nose can choose whether or not...
to nullify his butler's vote.
- Is that important? - It's up to you to decide.
- My butler's vote? - Yes.
- The one he voted... - Jae Seok's vote...
- will be nullified. - His vote...
It could change who takes the stand.
- Exactly. I will... - Right.
- Sir. - Yes?
You must leave my vote as is...
to catch the thief.
Well, it's all due to the fact that you seem quite suspicious.
Unbelievable.
Is this what you all want?
I will nullify Jae Seok's vote.
That seems like the right choice. I have serious doubts about him.
You've got to be kidding me.
- With his vote nullified... - Yes?
Here are the two...
- on the chopping block. - Okay.
Jae Seok...
Yu Jae Seok and Lee Kwang Soo.
Me?
- Yu Jae Seok and Lee Kwang Soo. - Me?
Kwang Soo too?
Please take the stand.
- It's not because we suspect you. - Jae Seok,
- it'll be Kwang Soo. - We know it's Jae Seok.
That's why we chose an innocent person to join him.
- But he... - If...
there turns out to be a thief among us...
The viewers are joining us for this race.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo have been chosen...
as the suspects in the first trial.
Is there a thief among them?
There is.
There is a thief among them.
See?
- You jerk. - Hold on a second.
There is a thief among them.
See?
- Haha, gosh. - Hold on.
- What did I tell you? - Okay.
- Okay, fine. - Seok Jin, we told you why.
Why do you think Jae Seok is a thief?
- We already told you. - When?
- I'll say it again. It isn't me. - Seok Jin.
- There's only one more to go. - Is it really him?
- Like I said... - It's him.
Let me tell you why I suspect the butler.
- Right. - Sure.
Jae Seok told us that the safe was empty.
Yes, tell everyone that.
The information given to me...
revealed that the gold bars hadn't been moved.
- What? - So...
- That doesn't make sense. - See?
It's like this. Jae Seok...
told us his version of the story knowing that the other thief...
will take the gold bar.
- It was a signal. - That's right.
But the other thief couldn't take it due to the circumstances.
Let me tell you my side of the story.
Sure, go ahead.
We were told that the number of gold bars...
averaged around 33 to 34.
So the thief would've only taken about 3 to 4.
Not a lot could've been taken.
So the safe wasn't fully stocked...
- with the gold bars. - No.
I didn't have the time...
to actually count the number of gold bars.
You could've thought that some were taken when they were not?
I could've easily been mistaken.
- That could've happened? - Yes.
- That's reasonable. - I see.
Kwang Soo, it's your turn to defend yourself.
- Me? - Yes.
Why me?
Because Jae Seok makes a reasonable case.
In what way?
He could've been mistaken due to how the bars were stacked.
That I understand.
- Exactly. - I agree.
- At this very moment... - Hold on.
Let me say this one thing.
We have our thief.
- Kwang Soo. - It's him.
Let me defend myself too.
See? We have our thief.
I had a total of three ballots.
I had two to begin with, and I found another one in the room.
Would I have had the time...
to find the extra ballot...
- and open the safe? - He wouldn't have.
- It doesn't make sense. - He didn't have enough time.
- There's not enough time. - Right.
Couldn't they both be the thieves?
- Exactly. - That could be true.
- It could be them both. - Right.
- Right. - That could be true.
- They both could be thieves. - That could be true.
- Just admit it, you jerk! - What?
- Say that it's you! - You're the thief!
- Unbelievable. - Haha...
I'm not saying this because he's my butler,
but because I've known him for 30 years.
Jae Seok's definitely telling the truth.
- I don't detect a lie. - Exactly.
It's just how I feel.
- I'm confused. - Tell me about it.
Jong Kook won first place in the previous mission,
so he'll decide the order in which you'll search the room.
- Me? - We're going in again?
- I need to be smart about this. - Please decide on the order.
Keep the order similar to how it was before.
- Similarly? - Ji Hyo...
I saw the video of Ji Hyo, remember?
It got cut as she was about to reach the safe.
I can't wait to find out who the thieves are.
- Ji Hyo will enter first. - Sure.
- Got it. - Who'll go next?
- And then Jae Seok. - Sure.
Kwang Soo, Seok Jin,
- and then So Min. - You must not doubt us much.
I'll go, and then Haha will go.
- That's the order. - Sure, Ji Hyo, you first.
I can't believe this.
- You know... - You're really suspicious of me?
We're not 100 percent sure that you're the thief yet.
We'll decide after the second round.
I can be sure this time...
because I'm now aware of how the bars are set.
None were moved, so I'll know for sure this time.
Of course.
- I'll know for sure. - Shouldn't you take your time?
- Why wait? - Exactly.
- He needs to prove his innocence. - That's right.
No changes have been made to the safes.
- He's back. - How were they?
- What did you see? - I didn't notice a change.
They were exactly like what I saw during the first search.
Jae Seok should've entered last.
- But he's the thief. - Guys, be on alert.
The thieves will now make their move.
They'll just steal the bars?
- Hold on. And that's me? - Yes.
- Of course. - I'll make my move this time?
Yes, this time around...
From what I can tell, he already made his move.
- I'm sure of it. - He already made his move.
I'm sure of it. Just you wait and see.
- Only Haha will know. - This is getting interesting.
The insurance salesman...
will be told how many gold bars were stolen.
- Sure. - This is the most important round.
You're playing a pivotal role in this game.
- Tell me about it. - It's more crucial than I thought.
He was given one of the best abilities.
He holds the power to manipulate the public.
- His ability... - Exactly.
He can manipulate us all if he chooses to lie.
That's right.
What happened?
I bet many were taken.
It doesn't make sense if none were.
It happened exactly like how I suspected.
- How? - I'm sorry,
- but can you take off your cap? - Take off your cap, Haha.
- There he is. - Look at him.
I'm a fan!
Everyone.
It happened exactly like how I suspected.
- How? - Which is what?
- A lot of gold bars... - I knew it.
- were stolen. - See?
- A lot of gold bars were stolen. - I knew it.
See?
What did I tell you? I was right, wasn't I?
The number of stolen bars indicates that the thieves...
- were in a hurry. - Right.
This fact tells us one thing.
- That's right. - What's that?
That only one of the thieves made a move.
We need to catch who that person is.
- It has to be Jae Seok. - We can guess...
depending on the order we went in.
I conclude my briefing.
- This is crazy. - Gosh.
We'll move on to the next round.
I have the result.
Haha came in 7th, so you'll see 20 seconds of his search.
Ji Hyo came in 8th, so you'll see 30 seconds of her search.
Yes, we should get a look at Ji Hyo's search.
- Go ahead. I have nothing to hide. - They aren't the usual suspects.
One of them could be the thief.
- I'm suspicious of Haha. - Yes?
- Let's take a look. - Play the video.
I checked the safe after entering the room too.
- Isn't he too calm though? - There's nothing here.
The extra ballot isn't important anymore.
- The extra ballot. - That's not what's important.
He heads toward the safe.
Next is the 30-second video of Ji Hyo's search.
- Yes, Ji Hyo's search. - Play the video.
Ji Hyo is one of the names in the suspect pool.
- Yes, she's on the list. - Of course.
- Where's the extra ballot? - She went in first.
She's definitely not a thief.
She can't be a thief. She is too relaxed.
She went before me.
Ji Hyo didn't steal the gold bars. Jae Seok said nothing had changed.
I checked. Ji Hyo didn't steal the gold bars.
But she could still be a thief.
That's right. Perhaps she pretended to be innocent.
I'm not a thief.
- I'm not a thief. - I don't know anymore.
- Was that 30-seconds long? - Yes.
- She had 20 more seconds afterward. - That's right.
In 20 seconds, you can punch in the passcode,
open the safe, and take out the gold bars.
- It's entirely possible. - It's entirely possible.
She would have needed to move them to a different safe.
Listen. I went in after Ji Hyo, right?
Everything was the same.
- But... - Please prove my innocence.
like I said, there is a possibility only one thief made a move.
So it's not definitive evidence.
- I'll check a video as a detective. - Okay, you can go ahead.
That's a good benefit.
Whose video will you watch?
This step is really important.
- This step is really important. - That's right.
I will watch it carefully.
Perhaps Jae Seok thought he would get caught anyway...
and moved a lot of gold bars.
- Jae Seok? - Yes.
Then watch my video.
- You should watch Kwang Soo's. - You can watch mine.
We will learn about their identities soon.
A thief among the two of us will get caught anyway.
Whose video should I watch?
Did you see anything suspicious?
- Not at all. - Not at all?
- Whose video did you watch? - Seriously.
So Min's video.
Why did you watch So Min's video?
- So Min's video is meaningless. - I said she isn't a thief.
Perhaps he checked it to be certain since no one was suspecting me.
She didn't do anything suspicious.
We are aware of the fact that only the first 20 seconds get revealed.
- So the thieves... - They wouldn't do anything.
would only get to work...
after 20 seconds pass.
- The last 30 seconds matter. - That's right.
Then they would run around.
This is your last chance to apprehend a thief...
before the viewers vote.
Whom should we put on the Judgment Stand?
If you fail to catch a thief this time,
the viewers' votes will determine the two suspects.
Then the likelihood of catching the thieves will fall.
- Let's put Jae Seok on the stand. - Put me on the stand.
Let's take Kwang Soo out.
- Listen to what I have to say. - Okay.
If we must choose one of them to put on the Judgment Stand,
it has to be Kwang Soo.
- I agree. - Listen to what I have to say.
Walk us through your reasoning.
- It's him. - He is a thief.
The only thing Jae Seok can hope to achieve at this point...
is making people continue to suspect Kwang Soo.
If people continue to suspect Kwang Soo,
his fellow thief will have a higher chance of survival.
- This is driving me crazy. - Am I right?
Let me tell you what I think.
I'm not on Jae Seok's side or anyone else's side.
- I just want to catch the thieves. - That's not true.
You are on Jae Seok's side.
Do you think I am on his side?
- It's obvious. - I'm beginning to get upset.
- This is too much. - I'm not on his side.
I can tell you this much.
We got divided up because of you.
- That's not true. - CEO Big Nose is on my side.
- That's true. - I am not on your side!
I just want to catch the thieves.
Is he the butler?
- What? - Who is the butler?
He is the butler.
It's rather confusing.
- Actually, I am Batman. - Hey!
This is driving me crazy.
You're Batman?
- Hey! - He is Alfred.
He enjoys the 4 major insurances and annual salary of 33,000 dollars.
I'm the one who pays him.
- Jee-fred. - Jee-fred.
- I even give him incentives. - Jee-fred.
Wait outside, Jee-fred.
- Wait outside. - This is how Jee-fred is.
We should put Kwang Soo on the Judgment Stand.
That's right. Let's put Kwang Soo on the Judgment Stand.
If he is innocent, we will know that Jae Seok is a thief.
That's right.
Let's have a vote then.
- Okay. - One of us will go up on the stand.
- Okay. - Whom do you want on the stand?
- Let's begin. - I will cast my ballot.
I will announce the result. The one who received the most votes is...
I want to go up on the Judgment Stand.
- Then people won't suspect me. - It would be faster...
if I go up on the stand.
- Kwang Soo, please come forward. - All right.
- What was the difference? - I can't tell you.
Why did people choose Kwang Soo?
- It would be better... - That's right.
to catch a thief.
- If Kwang Soo isn't a thief... - Then we know that Jae Seok is.
Then we will know one thief for sure.
You should have chosen Jae Seok to know the truth, you fool!
For goodness' sake.
Kwang Soo received the most votes in the second trial.
He is...
He's a thief.
- He is... - He's a thief.
- He is a thief. - There we go!
No!
- You thief! - You should have chosen Jae Seok.
- You thief! - For goodness' sake!
Things became more confusing.
We should have put Jae Seok on the Judgment Stand.
Tomorrow, there will be a party to wish for the health...
of CEO Big Nose, the richest man in this country.
You are the thieves who are after his gold bars.
I pick the judge.
- I'll go with the judge. - You're a judge?
- Since I'm the detective, - Hold on.
I'm the judge, why aren't you telling me?
- It's my gold. - I have three ballots.
And the judge. These two.
- No. - The judge.
Things became more confusing.
We should have put Jae Seok on the Judgment Stand.
You...
I can't believe I went up the stand as the control.
I can't believe I went up the stand because I was too trustworthy.
- Tell us who the other thief is. - I was right!
- Let's put an end to this. - Jae Seok wasn't...
I can't believe I went up the stand because I was too trustworthy.
The two of them are the thieves.
- The two of them are the thieves. - I was right!
Isn't it too early to say that?
You could be wrong.
It's a possibility for now.
This is incredible.
Let me tell you this once more.
One of them...
is a thief.
We have it harder now.
- To be honest... - He is so smart.
I see why the production crew was nervous.
- Seriously. - We have it harder now.
I see why they were so quiet.
There is another possibility...
of both of them being the thieves.
- I get it now. - We should have chosen Jae Seok.
I am telling you...
- that we should see... - That's right.
who is swaying the public.
- A thief is behind it. - I'm truly glad...
- that Kwang Soo got caught. - I think...
I think...
I can steal the gold bars once more, right?
Kwang Soo will steal in the open now.
What?
You need to wait.
Hold on. Someone stop him. He lost control now.
You succeeded to arrest a thief.
The arrest of the remaining thief is up to the viewers...
who will send in their votes after watching the show.
- I hope they watch carefully. - I bet they will be confused.
- It's time for the last search. - All right.
The winner of the second mission, Jong Kook,
will decide the order once more.
- Will we go in there again? - Yes.
It will be the last search.
In that case, Kwang Soo should go...
before Jae Seok.
Kwang Soo?
- Yes. - Before Jae Seok?
- Let's have him go before Jae Seok. - That's just wrong.
Then another suspect should go after Jae Seok.
- A suspect should go before him. - Then Haha...
A suspect should go before me.
What's the point...
- of having me go after Kwang Soo? - There is no point.
Jae Seok should go first.
If both Jae Seok and Kwang Soo are thieves...
- There is that possibility. - There is that possibility.
Such a possibility is incredibly low.
Jae Seok, Haha...
Let's do this.
I can't make a single comment!
- Say something. - Seriously.
- I can't make a single comment. - Say something.
They keep going back and forth.
- Stay seated! - This is driving me crazy.
Let me say this.
- Does anyone have an opinion? - Haha...
I have an opinion!
We have an opinion!
- The three of us have an opinion! - I want to talk too.
I am the one who gets to decide on the order,
- so tell me what you think. - Okay.
- For goodness' sake. - Haha is the one...
- who set up this situation. - That's right.
Since he provided a crucial hint, I think...
- he should be included. - This is hard.
- Kwang Soo, go first. - Okay.
Then Jae Seok will go next. The rest doesn't matter.
If Kwang Soo is determined, he will steal all the gold bars.
- I will give it a try. - Let's see...
- what happens. - That's right.
Let's study the situation.
- Then... - Kwang Soo,
you were a judge before you became a thief.
- That's a judge's clothing. - Me?
I'm just a thief in a judge's clothing.
Why won't they go in?
Hold on!
- I'm sorry, but... - Yes?
- Did you create a mess? - Did you break something?
The other thief should do the work.
- You didn't get to move a lot. - The gold bars...
are all over the floor.
What is this?
- If the room is clean... - Hold on!
Everyone should count the gold bars on the floor.
What do you think? If the number...
remains the same until the end,
- it means Jae Seok is a thief. - Jae Seok.
Right?
Let's see what happens.
How am I doing? Do you still suspect me?
Why did you come back so soon?
As Kwang Soo said,
the gold bars were scattered...
- all over the floor. - What did you do with them?
- I thought about it. - What?
- If I put them back in the safe... - You shouldn't do that.
- Did you put them back? - Yes, I did.
- What? Where did you put them? - There were many gold bars.
How did you do that in such a short amount of time?
- I could only move a few. - Where did you put them?
You put them back?
- One safe... - That's what a thief would do.
You shouldn't have.
- You shouldn't have touched them. - One safe... Why not?
- We were going to count them. - We were going to count them.
Had the numbers changed, we would have been able...
- to single out a thief. - No, no.
I will tell you why I put them back.
- One thief remains, right? - How did you do it so fast?
Transferring the gold bars on the floor...
- to the safe... - That's right. You did a good job.
wouldn't have been too easy for the remaining thief.
That's right. I will be back.
Please check the state of the room.
Okay.
I did wonder if I should leave them as they are...
- or put them back. - Seriously.
- Jae Seok. - What?
What's the point of putting the gold bars back in the safe?
Why?
You kept the safe open.
I didn't have time to close it.
- You should have closed it. - He said he closed it earlier.
There were gold bars all over the place.
You made it too easy for the thief.
So what did you do?
- What? - Did you close the safe?
How can I close it? I don't know the passcode.
I'm the only one who doesn't know it.
Can't you close it without knowing the passcode?
- You can't do that. - Jong Kook.
- It's open. - It's...
the perfect test.
I agree.
- What do you mean? - It's bait.
Then we can count the gold bars.
- We can count the gold bars. - That's right.
Counting them...
- will take up the time. - It will be hard to steal them.
- No one will be able to touch them. - That's right.
The safe on the right is untouched.
It's untouched.
- It's locked. - A thief couldn't get to it.
He only touched the other two safes.
The next person should count...
- That's right. - how many gold bars are in there.
We need to know the number.
- The next person should count. - Let me go.
- The next person should count. - Let me go next, Jong Kook.
- Go ahead. - Okay.
Let's go in this order.
Hold on.
- Count the gold bars. - Someone else should go.
- Why? - It's strange that you volunteered.
- You should go first, Se Chan. - For goodness' sake.
We can't make her the first person to check the number.
- Right? - I can count!
- She could move the gold bars... - Count well.
- I will count well. - to the thief's safe.
You said I am not...
- a suspect. - Don't complain. Se Chan, go.
I can't do anything today!
I am not a thief!
- That's right. - The analyst...
Okay, okay.
Let's write down the number.
- Yes. Everyone should do it. - Write down the number.
Don't show it to anyone.
- Add the numbers. - Should I add them?
- One. - They aren't ready.
- Did you write it down? - Yes.
In 1, 2, 3.
Their numbers match.
- 11 plus 12. - 23.
- The numbers match. - The numbers match.
- Listen. - The thief didn't steal them.
I told you earlier.
- Those safes weren't touched. - In that case...
The information Haha hears will tell us what happened.
Then it's a matter of whether I lie or not.
- That's right. - If Haha had been a thief,
he would have counted the gold bars and stolen them anyway.
The insurance salesman, Haha.
It has been added to the number you saw earlier.
- Okay. - This is the total number.
- CEO Big Nose, do something. - Hey.
You should reveal the information now.
How many were stolen?
Did more gold bars get stolen than earlier?
- I guess I can reveal it now. - Yes.
- Did more gold bars get stolen? - So far,
the thieves stole a total of...
- 44 gold bars. - I knew it. I was right.
I said the number will be somewhere around 40.
44 gold bars.
This is confusing.
Haha...
The last mission will help CEO Big Nose stretch his wrists.
It's called Spin and Spin.
Turn the glass upside down and spin a ping-pong ball inside.
Transfer as many balls as you can to the cups on the other table.
Shall we have Kwang Soo go first?
- He doesn't need to go. - He doesn't need to go.
- You don't need to go, right? - But there is my video.
- Oh, right. We have that. - We don't care about your video.
We don't want to watch it.
If I take the last place,
- the other thief's video... - Right.
- won't be revealed. - I get it now.
I get it now.
Start.
Does he have one minute?
Gosh, he is something else.
- Will he take the last place? - Yes.
- He will do that on purpose. - Does he have one minute?
Gosh, he is something else.
- He wants to save the other thief. - Seriously.
- He is the worst. - He is stooping so low.
- Seriously. - He is the worst.
He should look back upon himself for the 10th anniversary.
Just stop if you are going to be that way.
It has been 10 years.
How could you be so bad at it?
- How could you be so bad at it? - He will take the last place.
Kwang Soo, you moved zero balls.
- Zero balls. - Okay.
This man has been on the three major TV stations...
for 10 years.
It won't be easy.
- Yu. - Jae.
- Seok. - Let's go.
I will show you what it takes to be on the three major TV stations...
- for 10 years. - Show us!
Get ready.
You just need to do it lightly.
He is really good.
This isn't hard.
My goodness.
Your heart is pounding now, right?
- I bet your heart is pounding. - That came out of nowhere.
I bet he became surprised when he did a good job at first.
"Am I good at this?"
This is...
- He must feel nervous now. - Why am I so bad at it?
- Four, - No one is chasing after him.
three,
- 2, 1. - He got another one.
For goodness' sake.
- Eight points. - What were we supposed to see?
- This is hard. - It's seven points.
Get ready. Set...
- What? - He is bad at it too.
- You should spin it as you move it. - He is bad at it.
- He is bad at it. - There is something he is bad at.
- We will see his video. - This is funny.
He won't be able to move one ball.
- What is going on? - He is bad at it.
- Look at his right hand. - Look at that.
Look at the way his right hand shakes.
Gosh, he is terrible at it.
- My goodness. - That's right.
There is something Jong Kook is bad at.
- He is bad at it. - Why can't you do it?
His strong arms are wasted on him.
- Why can't you do it? - I can't do it.
He should do better with his strong arms.
2, 1.
Jong Kook failed.
My goodness.
I can't do it.
That's not how you do it.
20 seconds of Kwang Soo's video and 30 seconds of Jong Kook's video.
Let's watch 20 seconds of Kwang Soo's video.
- It will be something. - It will be funny.
We should have watched 30 seconds of his video.
- It's war. - Look at him.
Look at him.
- He is good. - That part must have been hard.
- How did he go about it? - That must have taken up time.
He opened two safes.
- He opened two safes. - One safe was left untouched.
He didn't open the third safe.
That safe was completely full.
- He should have piled them up. - I get it!
The gold bars were left like that.
- What is it? - What about that safe?
- He opened it too. - Really?
I get it now.
Now comes Jong Kook's video which is 30 seconds.
It was clean.
- The black one. - That's right.
I'm sure it was also like that.
- Who is that? Jong Kook? - Jong Kook.
I counted slowly.
He didn't do anything.
I told you so. I simply counted the gold bars.
It's easy to count them.
Did he open the third safe now?
He had 20 seconds left.
- All right. - Oh, he didn't.
I counted the gold bars twice.
Maybe he got to work afterward.
- After that... - I was the last to go in.
- You never know. - After that...
Are you saying he stole them in 20 seconds?
The person who came in after me counted too.
Maybe he looked at the camera...
and grinned.
- Gosh. - Maybe he did that.
- Maybe he did that. - I am so glad...
we got to watch...
- Kwang Soo's video. - Why?
- Don't you get it? - No, I don't.
Kwang Soo dropped much more gold bars on the floor...
than the ones we saw in the two safes.
- So... - So...
it makes no sense the safes only had 11 and 12 gold bars respectively.
- There were so many on the floor. - That's right.
That means...
someone put some gold bars in the thief's safe.
And Jae Seok went in after Kwang Soo.
- The gold bars. - He is unbelievable.
- Right? - He is unbelievable.
- I can see the videos, right? - We already did.
- I can because I'm a detective. - Yes, you can.
- Can I do that? - Of course.
- "Can I do that?" - I want to see...
- either Jae Seok's or Haha's. - Right.
- You don't have to see mine. - Why not?
You...
Think about what's more important.
You... Let me tell you this.
Listen to me.
All you have to do is count the gold bars on the floor.
Just count them quickly.
- Do you think that's easy? - I mean...
- How can I... - What I mean is...
Can you count the balls on the floor now?
- Hey. - It's impossible.
Jong Kook is the judge, the detective...
How many jobs does he have?
Can you count the balls on the floor now?
- What is he talking about? - How many jobs does he have?
- Hey. - Seriously...
- Somebody stop him. - What I mean is...
- What I mean is... - How can I count them?
What I mean is...
He has eight jobs!
He is the detective, the judge... How many jobs does he have?
- He is CEO Big Nose as well! - What is he doing?
- Right? - Those two are losing their cool.
- That's the proof. - They left their seats.
No!
Se Chan, he has a point.
Count the gold bars.
Gosh, I feel betrayed by Jae Seok.
He could be a thief. I'm getting confused.
This is why I told you to put me on Judgment Stand.
- What do you mean? - But that's already...
- This is why... - That's already over, you punk.
- I mean... - What's with you?
- I'm getting upset. - We're just trying to guess.
I'm getting angry.
Aren't you the one who talked about your friendship of 30 years?
I'm just angry!
I'm getting suspicious of you at the last minute!
- Hold on. - Hurry up and do it.
Go! I'm so angry.
We've been friends for 30 years!
- Se Chan. - I get it.
- Hurry up and check the video. - Check my video.
- I'm so angry. - Check my video...
and prove my innocence...
so that the viewers can suspect...
someone else.
So go check my video right now.
- Your video? - Check my video.
Can the viewers see what Detective Yang sees?
No. They have to rely on what the detective says only.
I see.
- He could be a thief too. - That's right.
- Count the gold bars on the floor. - Okay.
- Just count them quickly. - Check Jae Seok's video.
I'll count them quickly.
By the way,
I wonder why Jong Kook is trying to frame me.
I'm just being objective.
- I don't think so. - Jae Seok.
- There are many, right? - No?
This is strange.
Jae Seok, I only saw 20 seconds of it.
Did you say you put all of them back in?
There were about 15 on the floor.
What?
That's because...
the video got cut off. I put all of them back in later.
There were about 15 on the floor.
- Only 15? - On the floor.
What about when he first came in?
About 15.
- On the floor? - Yes, about 15 were on the floor.
There weren't many. Kwang Soo put most of them back in.
- I told you. - I saw 20 seconds of it.
I'm telling you the truth.
- He's not a thief. - That means you're not a thief.
- Why? - Because you're telling the truth.
Yes, there were 15.
It's either Jae Seok or Jong Kook.
I've been suspecting Jong Kook, but...
There's something that bothers me.
Let's say I'm innocent and Jong Kook is...
- trying to frame me. - I mean...
That means he's trying to sway us.
So who is the thief?
Welcome to my house.
I can decide, right? Then I'll go first.
- What? You? - Does he get to decide everything?
- Fine, go head. - Can he be a thief?
- Yes. - But he's the CEO.
Detective, go check the video.
- Whose video did you watch? - So Min's video.
- Why did you watch So Min's video? - So Min's video is meaningless.
I said she isn't a thief.
- You go in first. - Gosh.
- 1, 2, 3. - I told you.
Here's the number of gold bars taken by the thieves.
He holds the power to manipulate the public.
- He can throw us off the track. - That's right.
1, 2, 3.
- 11, 12. - 11, 12.
If Haha is a thief, he could have taken the gold bars.
Will I lie or not?
Exactly.
Lawyer Song can choose one person to be removed from the first trial.
- I choose Kim Jong Kook. - You'd take Jong Kook out?
Why would you take him out? This is a weird choice.
She could take herself out, but she didn't.
- This is too weird. - This is weird.
Am I the first to arrive? Then I'll pick...
- Pick a gambler. - That's right.
I didn't have the time to actually count...
- the number of gold bars. - That's reasonable.
- And open the safe? - He wouldn't have.
- It doesn't make sense. - He didn't have enough time.
- There's not enough time. - Right.
I opened all of them, and gold bars were missing...
from two of them.
- Two of them? - They were broken into?
- The gold bars are still there. - Are they still there?
- How many were on the floor? - About 10.
- Are they still there? - I put them back in.
- What are you talking about? - You put all of them back in?
- Are you so neat? Why did you? - You put all of them back in?
I did.
Hold on. Come here, three of you. Wait.
Let's count the gold bars on the floor.
Jae Seok and Kwang Soo...
- may be thieves. It's possible. - Just in case.
- It's unlikely. - What are you talking about?
If Jong Kook is a thief, he must want to frame me,
- who is being suspected. Right? - That's possible.
All right. Running Man 10th Anniversary Special Live Broadcast.
We will catch the last suspect...
with the viewers...
right here.
The text voting ends...
in five minutes.
Everyone, let's get started!
Hello, viewers.
- Hello. - Hello.
Running Man 10th Anniversary...
Special Live Broadcast has started.
- Nice to see you all. - Nice to see you all.
Jong Kook, you look so creepy.
- We... - Please explain why.
There's a reason why...
Jong Kook and I look like this.
I'd like to apologize.
- It's a penalty. - This is our penalty, right?
- Yes. - That's right.
Jae Seok is supposed to be...
- a zombie. - From the Joseon period.
- From the drama, "Kingdom". - That's right.
But he just looks like a tired man in the woods.
- That's right. - The thing is...
- I was going to wear contacts, - Exactly.
- but... - It'd look too scary.
many people watch our show.
- Many children watch it too. - That's right.
- So I didn't wear them in the end. - Exactly.
- That's why I just look tired. - You look like an ascetic.
But I wanted to look like a zombie.
- A zombie from "Kingdom". - But...
- Look at this arrow. - Yes, look at this arrow.
- He's been shot with an arrow. - It looks so cute.
You'll know if you've watched "Kingdom".
- You're Huh Joon Ho. - Without the contacts...
- I'm supposed to be Huh Joon Ho. - You're Huh Joon Ho.
- But I look like a tired ascetic. - You look like an ascetic.
- Please understand. - He looks cute.
Jong Kook, you are...
- I'm Kaonashi. - That's right.
- I'm Kaonashi. - He's the most scary-looking...
- He looks horrifying. - He looks creepy.
- He looks so creepy. - He looks awful.
- He looks scary. - Even my outfit is not straight.
It makes my body look crooked.
Anyway, we're dressed like this...
- because this is our penalty. - That's right.
We'll soon catch the culprit, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
We've been watching the show here in the studio...
- and guessing the whole time. - We've been guessing too.
- But we have no idea. - We don't.
We have no idea who the culprit is even though this is a live show.
Anyway, the text voting will end soon.
Some of you may already have voted,
but I'm sure...
- some are still not sure. - That's right.
As Kwang Soo has already been caught,
he will be excluded.
- Hold on. - He didn't even have to come.
- I don't get to say a single word? - Why did you come?
- I mean... - You got caught.
Kwang Soo has already been caught as a thief,
- and there is one more thief left. - That's right.
Since we don't have much time...
- and this is live, - Yes.
- let's hurry up... - Yes.
and try to defend ourselves one by one.
- Okay. - Kwang Soo messed up.
Haha, please defend yourself.
Hello, everyone. I'm an insurance salesman.
- Take off your cap. - There is only one thing...
I want to tell you.
I didn't lie about the number of gold bars.
And that means...
- That's right. - I can't be a thief.
- 10 seconds is up. - Stop.
- Believe me. - Next up is Se Chan.
Hello, I'm Detective Yang.
I believe the thief is...
either Jong Kook or Jae Seok.
That's my honest opinion as a detective. Thank you.
Next up is Ji Hyo.
The detective shouldn't pick people out.
I can't wait to find out who the thief is.
Anyway, I'm not a thief.
- She's suspicious. - I don't know what else to say,
but I'm really not.
I suspect So Min and Jae Seok.
- Really? - All of a sudden?
- So Min, all of a sudden? - Right?
- So Min? - Jae Seok and...
- So Min? - It's possible.
- She didn't say much. - So Min, defend yourself.
I'm glad that you guys are suspecting me,
but I'm not a thief.
I suspect Jae Seok, Haha,
- and Jong Kook. - That's right.
- I didn't do anything suspicious. - Why me...
- That's right. - That's why.
- That's why you're suspicious. - That's why you're suspicious.
- That's why you're suspicious. - We want to be careful...
because according to the voting results,
someone will be penalized.
- That's right. It's incredible. - That's why...
we want to be careful with what we say.
Next up is CEO Big Nose.
- I can't be a thief. - Okay.
- I... What are you doing? - Go on.
Why would I steal my own gold bars?
Does that mean I made up the whole thing?
Isn't that too predictable?
I... Stop staring at me.
I'm definitely not a thief.
- You're not? - No.
Seeing how you're dressed, it feels like we're shooting at your house.
- This is my house. - He's at home.
This is not Seok Jin's house.
- This is our studio. - All right.
- I'll defend myself quickly. - Sure.
I was watching what was going on in today's episode,
and many people are suspecting me.
I am definitely not a thief.
There is one person that I am very suspicious of,
but I'm scared that I am choosing the wrong person.
- Who is it? - Tell us...
- Right? - who you think it is.
- I think that it's Jong Kook. - I think that it's him too.
- Right. - On the day of the shoot,
I could've gone up the Judgment Stand, but he stopped me.
That's what made me think it was him too.
There was a reason behind that.
If you watch the whole thing, then you will know.
From my perspective,
I did that because I believed the thief was Jae Seok.
Our perspectives were different.
I was adamant that it was Jae Seok,
- He looks scary. - but I'm not sure, to be honest.
- I'm going to focus on... - Okay.
who you guys vote for.
- You guys look so funny together. - Right now.
- It's scary. - It looks like a comedy show...
with the two of us in the frame.
It looks like we're doing skits on Running Man now.
Don't show off your arms.
Kaonashi is supposed to have its arms covered,
but I didn't cover them because this was funnier.
Okay. This is important, everyone.
- The texting votes will end soon. - It will end soon.
- Let's start the countdown. - We're very curious too.
We're doing a special live broadcast to celebrate our 10th anniversary.
We've done live broadcasts in the past,
- but this is the longest one. - Right.
- It's our first time. - Right.
- We are very curious too. - We can't wait to find out.
Your mustache is falling off.
Is that on purpose?
- No. - I think that...
you should watch TV together.
- It's fun. - It's so much fun.
- It was a lot of fun. - It was a lot of fun.
I've said this before,
but I always felt weird when I was watching Running Man.
- It's because we know the ending. - Exactly.
But since we don't know how it will end today, it's so much fun.
The Chief Director joined us today.
- Yes. - She seems very pleased.
- She's happy. - It's a party here.
Many people may have heard of her.
- Chief Director Choi Young In. - Chief Director Choi Young In.
Thank you for joining us on a Sunday.
We're working really hard.
We will end the voting period now.
- Let's count down. - Shall we count down together?
- 5. - 5.
- 4. - 4.
- 3. - 3.
- 2. - 2.
- 1. - 1.
- The end. - It is now closed.
- I want to know quickly. - I would like to thank...
all the viewers who have tuned in to our show today,
and I would also like to thank everyone...
who sent in a text with their vote once again.
The results of the votes will be revealed shortly.
- That's right. - We are so curious as well.
We're all so curious.
- This is real. - They won't tell us who it is.
This is important.
To the viewer who guessed the last thief correctly,
we will send them a luxurious massage chair.
- It is refreshing. - Will one person receive this?
Yes, one person will receive it.
We will also give 10 people autographed Running Man name tags...
and a group photograph as a gift.
Haha has been on a lot of...
- home shopping shows. - It's like a home shopping show.
- He's good at it. - He's different.
He's been on a lot of home shopping shows.
I don't know if we'll get a chance to do this again in the future,
but if we do, we'll prepare a lot more gifts then.
- Yes. We'll prepare them. - Yes.
We'll prepare a lot more gifts and give them to more viewers.
- We're going to find out... - Right.
if Kim Jong Kook the analyst and Jeon So Min the gambler will bet.
- They should bet. - This is important.
What will you do, Jong Kook?
I will be strategical, and since it's our 10th anniversary...
I'm sure a lot of people have voted for Yu Jae Seok.
Of course, I have my suspicions about him.
But according to the flow of everything,
I think a lot of people voted for Jae Seok.
We don't have a lot of time left, so please...
- Neatly. - shorten what you're saying.
I will choose Yu Jae Seok.
- So the analyst will choose me? - Yes.
- If I am the thief, - Yes.
you get a penalty transfer card.
It doesn't matter if you are the thief or not.
I get it if you have received the most viewer votes.
- It doesn't need to be right. - I can be wrong.
- The person with the most votes. - That's right.
Who the thief is doesn't matter to me.
- So you chose me. Okay. - Yes.
What will you do, So Min?
I think that we will catch the thief...
- no matter what. - Right.
- So I will bet on it. - Okay.
If we catch the thief, then So Min will...
- We will get double the prizes. - Double.
If her bet is wrong, then instead of two people getting the penalty,
- 4 people will get it. - 4 people.
I hope that our viewers will...
- catch the thief. - Please catch the thief!
- Please catch the thief! - Please catch the thief!
- Please. - Please catch the thief!
- I'm so curious. - I hope they catch the thief.
Please clear me of these false charges.
- Please. - "Please clear me."
- Please, save me. - You really look desperate.
- It doesn't matter to me. - You look desperate.
- I hope you all voted for Jae Seok. - Please save me.
He just needs to get all the votes to benefit me.
We need to announce the results now.
Since I'm one of the main suspects in this case,
the veteran host, Jee Seok Jin,
- will take over for me. - Yes, of course.
Will it be okay for Seok Jin to do it?
- He's a veteran host. - In any case,
- Seok Jin... - just trust me.
Back in the day, according to the history of show hosts,
he started off as a host at Everland.
- He has strong foundations. - He does.
- He is. - He has a lot of experience.
The results of the viewers' votes will be given to me shortly.
It's coming.
- It's here. - It's here.
- It's here. - I'm so curious.
CEO Big Nose, you have to announce the results quickly.
Don't improvise and just announce it.
I'm so curious.
- Please clear my name. - Why isn't there...
Why isn't there an envelope?
Tell us who received the most votes.
That's the most important thing for me.
Running Man's 10th anniversary live broadcast.
We had over...
- 230,000 people vote. - Goodness.
- A lot of people voted. - That's a lot of people.
- That many people voted? - It was over 230,000 people?
The results are... Gosh, it's this person.
- Out of all those votes, - Please.
- about 59,000 votes... - 59,000 votes.
- If you receive the most votes, - It is this person.
- you will go on the stand. - I just need to get this right.
- Please. - We have to get them right.
I just need to guess the right person for this.
I'm not looking.
- The thief needs to go up. - Hurry up.
- The viewers selected... - It's not here.
- Who is it? - Who is it?
Who is it? They said it's there.
It's not here. It's not written here.
- Hey. - Okay.
Who is it?
It's not written here, so I will just call their name.
It is...
Yu Jae Seok!
- I'm exempt from getting a penalty. - It's not me.
- We all knew it. - It's not me.
- We all knew it'd be Jae Seok. - I'm exempt from getting a penalty.
- This is driving me crazy. - I'm exempt from getting a penalty.
It's not me.
- Kwang Soo is happy. - Kwang Soo looks happy.
- Regardless, I will... - Hold on.
It looks like Kwang Soo is happy, so Jae Seok might not be the thief.
- That's possible. - I'm not happy about this.
- It doesn't matter. - Out of the 220,000-some odd votes,
- I got the most votes... - 50,000.
which is over 50,000 votes.
I am standing on the stand.
Everyone, it's not me.
- Then first... - Okay.
- Whether or not it's me... - It will be revealed.
- It's.. - It's inside here.
- It will say "thief" if he is one, - Right.
or "citizen" if he is not.
- Let's find out. - If I am a thief,
- I will take it off myself. - We're curious too.
- He looks happy. - It's not me.
- 1, 2, - Who is it?
Three.
Oh, my gosh.
- Who is it then? - It wasn't me.
- It's not me. - Who is it?
- I told you. - Then is it Jong Kook?
- The viewers chose... - Look at his hair.
Yu Jae Seok as the thief,
- but it turns out he's not a thief. - Now,
- Who is it? - since it's not me,
we failed to catch the thief.
It's unfortunate, but there's nothing we can do.
That's just how life is.
- Who is it? - Lee Kwang Soo, the thief,
will announce who the other thief is.
The other thief did an incredibly good job that it gave me chills.
I will announce the thief.
Honestly, I thought it could be Jong Kook.
- It's not me. - Is it Jong Kook?
- It's not me. - Okay.
- Who is it? - My partner-in-crime is...
- Who is it? - He's standing next to him.
Yang Se Chan!
We did it.
If you thought it was Se Chan, you should've said it.
It was Se Chan?
- It was Se Chan? - I had no idea.
- To be honest, - I really had no idea.
- he didn't do anything today. - He didn't do a thing.
- Okay. We're all curious. - This is unbelievable.
- He was not a suspect at all. - This makes no sense.
Let's take a look at his performance.
- Let's watch it. - Let's watch it.
- We had no idea. - We were all fooled.
You guys are guests at a party,
as well as thieves who are after gold bars.
You and I should be a judge. I think this is a good role.
From here, we're going straight to tomorrow's opening.
You guys are unbelievable.
Gosh, you persistent ones.
It's Se Chan.
- This is incredible. - I pick the judge.
- This was all planned. - I'll be a detective.
It doesn't matter to me.
Nobody suspected him.
Se Chan didn't act suspicious.
- He was never a suspect. - But he did his job.
- He did a lot. - I did a lot.
How did he do it?
He did that?
The number of gold bars increased.
- I see. - Since he was the detective,
we never really suspected him.
And gold bars were missing from two of them.
Two of them?
I moved the gold bars into the other safe,
and Jae Seok got confused and thought they were stolen.
I suspected Haha,
but he wasn't lying.
I only told the truth.
And Jae Seok didn't lie either.
- Right. - It was all true.
- Se Chan did a great job. - He did a good job.
- Go in first. - Okay. I'll use it well.
This is shocking.
We narrowed down our deductions too much in the beginning.
We were too focused on certain people.
We didn't take a broader look at things.
- Also... - He didn't act suspicious.
To be completely honest,
I didn't suspect Yang Se Chan, not even once.
- Me neither. - That's what I'm saying.
Se Chan did a great job.
- I didn't suspect him too. - We never even mentioned him.
- Right. - Right.
Why?
The two of you...
- There was no chance... - You must've been happy.
for anyone to suspect him.
We didn't even give him a chance to talk.
- I was lucky too. - I agree.
We suspected Jae Seok too much.
Jong Kook kept saying it was Jae Seok.
When someone says they're not, believe them.
Believe in them! Why are you always suspicious?
- Believe in them. - All right.
- So... - This is...
This is quite disappointing, but none of us...
- thought it was Se Chan. - None of us knew.
- Not even the slightest. - Not at all.
Who would've thought the thief was our youngest member?
- Right. In such a big project. - As a result,
the thieves...
The thieves have won!
- So what's going to happen? - Unfortunately,
we failed to catch both of the thieves.
We failed to catch 1 of the 2 thieves,
so the two of them will take the prize.
Also, the 1,320 dollars from the gold bars the thieves stole...
and the proceeds from the songs from Nine Years of Running Man...
will be donated to where they are needed...
under Lee Kwang Soo and Yang Se Chan's name.
That's nice.
As a result of So Min the gambler's bet,
the number of members...
- to be penalized... - It should be doubled.
- has been doubled to four. - Right.
And the member with the most votes is...
- That's right. - I got the most votes.
- You did. - And I will...
call the names one by one now.
I'm the 1st. Jong Kook is the 2nd.
Haha is the 3rd. Kwang Soo is the 4th.
- Me? - What?
But they knew Kwang Soo was one of the thieves.
It's Ji Hyo. I meant Song Ji Hyo.
What are you talking about?
The votes I got have been nullified.
Kwang Soo is arrested.
- I'm just... - Next.
Ji Hyo is the fifth...
according to the number of votes,
but she will get the penalty...
instead of Kwang Soo.
- Then... - All right.
If I refuse to get the penalty, who's next?
You have the penalty transfer card.
Then the person who comes next will get the penalty, right?
If you refuse to get the penalty, the next person will get it.
- That's nice. - You should get the penalty.
- So are you... - I'm thinking...
- Just do it. - whether I should wash my face...
- or take a shower. - Just take a shower.
- What are you hesitating for? - It's a pleasant concern.
I have to wash my face anyway.
So I should probably take a shower as well.
- Exactly. - I'm thinking of taking a shower.
So aren't you going to use the card today?
I won't use it today. I'll just get the penalty.
Okay. Good. You should use the penalty transfer card...
- you won today in three months. - Okay.
All right. If you forget to use it, it will be canceled.
- I hope it will happen. - In three months?
- It's too soon. - We should get the penalty now.
- Take off the microphone. - Before we do that,
we'd like to thank our viewers for the 10th anniversary.
Shall we say a few words? Kwang Soo, you can go first.
Okay. I hope you enjoyed our show.
Thank you for the last 10 years.
And I'll work even harder for the show.
- Seriously... - He's a bad speaker.
Jae Seok, you should say it for him.
- This is a live show. - I'm nervous.
- If we had... - Thank you.
enough time here,
we would've taken turns to say thank you.
But we have to get the penalty too.
So I will give a speech on behalf of them.
Why don't you thank our viewers, CEO Big Nose?
- Right. - You're the oldest one here.
- You should do that. - You should.
Thank you for your love and support for the past 10 years.
We don't even know how to thank you enough.
We will work even harder in the future.
Please keep loving...
- and supporting our show. - You're talking too much.
- Thank you. - Thank you!
Dear viewers, thank you for being with us for the past 10 years.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - The losers.
- Let's do this. - Take off the microphone.
- Take off the microphone. - Take it off. Get in there.
Here we go. Make sure to take off the microphone.
- Take it off. - Gosh, today...
we have mud.
- It's mud. - Thank you.
Those who have survived should stand here.
- All right. Today... - We're running out of time.
We couldn't even imagine that Se Chan was the thief.
I asked you many times.
- Come this way. - I was really surprised...
when I heard it was you.
All right. Come over here.
Those who are not getting the penalty...
- should stand here. - Okay.
It might splatter on you.
- Move over. - Okay.
- All right. - I'm so glad I'm not one of them.
Come here.
He seems happy.
Be careful.
- All right. This is live. - Right.
- All right. - This is live.
The writer is telling us to hurry.
- Okay. - Okay.
Because this is live.
- We should do this right. - Brace yourselves.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
Let's begin then.
After this show, All the Butlers is up.
Please watch it as well.
We will keep running hard and fast in Running Man.
Please give us a lot of support.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you!
Look at Jong Kook.