(A cool breeze is blowing.)
Hello.
- Hello.
Ji Hyo is like the actress
from the movie, "Bichunmoo".
- A slave hunter.
- It's "Bichunmoo".
She doesn't like her bangs.
Ji Hyo, you look
like a school bully...
from the 1980s.
They wear bangs like yours.
- Either put your hair up or down.
- That's what old ladies did.
- Right.
- They went to a salon for that.
- This is in style now.
- Look at the hair claw clips.
(- This is in style now.
- Look at the hair claw clips.)
- Look at the hair claw clips.
- Earlier in the waiting room,
how did you guys hold out
without talking about it?
- We were waiting.
- I wanted to say it here.
I was waiting to mention it here.
- We just bite at each other.
- It's the retro trend.
- I see.
- She says it's retro.
That's funny.
(There's news about Jae Suk
taking 1st place as always.)
It's about Jae Suk.
- He took first place again.
- "Korea's most influential people".
- That's right. Thank you.
- You're unbelievable.
"Korea's most influential people".
- You're a great man.
- The most influential person.
There will be a biography of him.
Aren't you sick of taking
first place in stuff like this?
He even ranks above BTS.
- This is unbelievable.
- He's even above BTS.
- He got a lot more votes than them.
- Even BTS?
It's not like that. Anyway,
it was a weekly newsmagazine.
Did you call people around you
for the poll?
Who would he call?
- What is he talking about?
- Why are you being so sarcastic?
- What's wrong with you?
- Just congratulate him heartily.
What's with the sarcasm?
- It just doesn't make sense.
- Just be happy for him.
Why does it not make sense?
- This is too big a deal.
- Just congratulate him.
Why is he being like this?
It's just too hard to believe.
You should be happy
that he's our member.
We are very proud.
- I guess you're right.
- There's one more thing.
- That's right. Suk Jin.
- What?
- He's got more than...
- It's about "Ji Suk Jin World".
- 100,000 subscribers.
- Over 100,000 subscribers?
- That's right.
- He's got the silver button.
It's about 150,000 people now.
- The silver button...
- What is it called?
- What?
- Silver...
- Silver town?
- Isn't it a silver town?
- Like a town for the aged?
- He's in a silver town.
- He can show it live.
- He got into a silver town.
- Did you get into a silver town?
Why did you go to a silver town
instead of getting a silver button?
Town. Haha, you have
more than 100,000 subscribers.
- That's true.
- He does?
- Right.
- When Haha...
first started his channel,
he was a little...
- He did all sorts of stupid things.
- Exactly.
He has a lot of
painful memories about it.
- It was ridiculous.
- He feels bad about it.
He made his videos like a film,
but no one watched it.
- "Daddy Free".
- It didn't get him subscribers.
- In short...
- No one watched it.
He had no idea about
what things were like in the field.
- He was so out of touch.
- I need videos that fit YouTube.
He just started it
without knowing what's what.
I'm a YouTuber now.
I was really surprised
when he started his channel.
I'll try some eating show next week.
That was funny.
Kwang Soo, you should
also start something.
- Start what?
- YouTube.
You should start working.
I'm working now.
- Really?
- I'm working now.
- These days...
- Kwang Soo will...
start Haduri.
- Why would I start Haduri?
- It's SkyLove.
- That was a long time ago.
- He will start SkyLove.
With a lighter.
Why would I start Haduri
with a webcam?
You can use Cheollian.
Or Nownuri.
With the COVID-19 spreading,
picking up private hobbies...
is more important than ever
these days.
- I agree.
- Exactly.
Today, you will get to learn
different hobbies and win a lottery.
- A lottery?
- That sounds nice.
It's called Lucky Hobbies Race.
"Lucky Hobbies?"
There will be three different
one-day classes today.
- That's nice.
- You'll be divided...
into two teams for each class.
And we will give you lottery tickets
according to your performance.
The lottery works
in the same way as Lotto.
But you have numbers
only from 1 to 10.
That sounds good.
How many numbers should we guess?
We will choose six numbers.
And you will get prizes
according to the results.
- It's worth a shot.
- That sounds great.
There's a way to increase
the chance of winning.
The teachers of each class
will select the best student.
The member who gets picked can
select one of the winning numbers.
That's really good.
We can select a number?
We will draw the winning numbers
with a few of them selected.
I've never bought
a lottery ticket before.
After the class,
you will perform as a team.
And the winner will be decided
by the living legend...
of variety shows,
Camera Director Kang Chan Hee.
(The legend of variety shows,
Camera Director Kang Chan Hee)
(Camera Director Kang Chan Hee
has 35 years of experience.)
I've seen him in variety shows
for over 25 years.
I remember seeing him
in "Dream Team".
He will decide the winner.
He is a legend.
You should be
on "Immortal Songs" soon.
What are they going to do
with his episode?
They usually have legendary singers.
They can sing
Director Kang's favorite songs.
- He's a legend.
- He really is.
He might be a big fan of BTS.
Once Director Kang
picks the winning team,
they will select the best student.
And the losing team will
select the worst student.
- That sounds fierce.
- And...
the best student gets one extra
ticket while the worst returns one.
Oh, no.
Let me show you today's prize then.
- I'm curious.
- What is it?
They offer great prizes these days.
The fact that they're
revealing them now...
- It's Korean beef.
- What is it? Meat?
- It's gold.
- Do we get gold?
- Seriously?
- If you get all six numbers right,
you will get 40g of gold.
- Really?
- Yes.
How much would this be?
If it's 40g,
it's about 3,000 dollars.
If there's more than one winner,
they will have to share the prize.
We should share the gold.
Those who get five numbers right
will get Korean beef.
- Even second place is good.
- And third place...
gets a box of peaches.
- Do we really get the prizes?
- Sure.
- And we don't have guests today.
- We have no guests today.
- These are for us.
- Right.
- I'll give you three tickets each.
- It will be fun.
You get three tickets each.
Just get me one.
Three tickets per person.
- Three tickets each?
- Yes.
- Here you are.
- Okay.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Okay.
- Are they three?
- Yes.
I guess I'll get
a few numbers right.
- Are they three?
- Yes.
- The number...
- We have leftovers.
- Really?
- You didn't give me mine, you fool.
(You didn't give me mine, you fool.)
- Why are you swearing at him?
- It's not like that.
Why are you so upset?
I wasn't swearing.
I was being friendly.
- You don't have to be upset.
- You didn't get one?
Let's go take our first class then.
- Okay.
(They head to
the first hobby class.)
(What is the first class about?)
- Is this it?
- Yes.
What's what?
(What's all this?)
What's going on?
(Some people greet
the members shouting out loud.)
Hello, ma'am.
- Who are they?
- The other day...
Hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
(The first class, yodel)
(Lee Eun Kyung is the doyenne
of Korean yodel songs.)
("Park Sung Ho Became a Yodel Singer
Thanks to Lee Eun Kyung")
("Lee Eun Kyung Works to Improve
the Status of Korean Culture")
(She was also Pengsoo
and Haha's yodel teacher.)
(Kang Dong Hye and Lee Eun Kyung)
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Attention.
- Yes, ma'am.
(Is this a close-order drill?)
- Yodel.
(They thought they would
learn how to yodel.)
- At ease.
- Yodel.
- Attention.
(The teacher seems
somewhat extraordinary.)
Bow.
- Hello.
That was so cool.
- You guys are the best.
- She sounds cheerful.
She's very energetic.
- You guys are the best.
- Thank you.
- You're the best.
- So...
Ms. Lee Eun Kyung is
Pengsoo's yodel teacher.
- I see.
- Right.
I used to be in a children's show,
"Ppoppoppo".
"Ppoppoppo?"
Do you remember her now?
How long have you been doing this?
It's been only 38 years.
- Really?
- Yes.
(She has 38 years
of experience in yodel.)
I started it
when I was in her belly,
- so it's about...
- Are you her daughter?
- Really?
- Yes, I am.
It's three generations old.
Will you stay quiet?
- Just stay still.
- It's three generations.
So three generations
of your family are doing this?
That's what I just said.
- Stay quiet.
- Yes, that's right.
And you did this.
What's the difference?
- They are yodel masters.
- Right.
So you're her daughter.
Yes. Nice to meet you.
Let's hear the teachers yodel first.
Let's do that.
(Excited)
This is really nice.
You can dance.
(Jaw-dropping)
(Clapping her hands)
My goodness.
Her falsetto voice is impressive.
(Her yodel captivates their eyes
and ears from the beginning.)
- She's amazing.
- It's unbelievable.
(The yodel master steps up.)
All right. Let's walk together.
(Fascinated)
(They are so into
the charm of yodel.)
(They are done...)
(falling for yodel.)
Yodel! Yodel!
- Yodel! Yodel!
- I love it.
- I got goosebumps.
- That was amazing.
- Yodel!
This is really exciting.
It was the best.
- Thank you.
- They are great.
You will put on some costumes...
and learn how to yodel.
So Min looks good.
- You look beautiful.
- It fits you nicely.
She's pretty.
- Now you should learn how to yodel.
- Yes.
Yodel is all about making
a good chest voice.
- Yo, yo, yo.
- Ya, ya, ya.
- Ye, ye, ye.
- This is the chest voice.
- Let's do this.
This time, let the air
through your nose.
(Singing together)
My goodness. That's good.
- Perfect. That's how you do it.
- Ms. Lee.
Yes, you can ask me any questions.
- Am I doing it right?
- That's good.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
Hey, stop it.
You two, stay away from each other.
- Why? Are we too loud?
- Se Chan, come over here.
- Come here.
- I'm sorry.
They do that
whenever they're standing together.
(I'll see you again soon,
my brother.)
- They're both great. That was good.
- Yes.
- The most important thing is "ay".
- "Ay".
Once you master singing "ay",
you're ready to yodel.
- "Ay".
- Watch my mouth.
(They're trying to sing as she did.)
One of you didn't smile.
- Who?
- Kwang Soo didn't smile.
- Hey, Kwang Soo.
- Me?
- Hey, smile a little bit, will you?
That's good. Great job.
You should always smile.
- Of course.
- Stop smiling.
- You should smile while yodeling.
Se Chan, your gums might dry out.
What is wrong with him now?
Move aside.
Repeat after me.
(They put a smile on their faces,
and class began again.)
(Ho-ho-ho, yo-yo)
Now, try this.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but do people usually learn to yodel
in a large group like this?
- Is this normal?
- My ears hurt.
- My ears hurt so much.
- I mean,
- does everyone learn this way?
- I have something to say.
- I'll tell you one thing.
- Go ahead.
I met her not long ago.
I took her class
with six-year-old children.
And we're learning
exactly the same as I did then.
- It's exactly the same.
- Can we get another teacher?
- I know.
The average age of us is 40.
- That's so funny.
- Together.
(The yodel lesson that covers
all generations resumes.)
This is yodeling.
You've learned everything.
All you need to learn is
how to sing "ay" and "oh".
One more important thing.
"Yo-la..."
(Yo-la-la-la-di-oh)
- Good. You've learned everything.
- Yes.
- You can start singing now.
- Really?
- Are you sure? Already?
- You're ready now.
- I don't think we're ready yet.
- You've learned everything.
- You don't think you can?
- No, I don't.
She's like a gambler.
It feels like she's skipping
several steps.
I'm so anxious. I feel like
I'm being chased.
My back is sweating.
- You see...
- I'm feeling so hot right now.
- I'm sweating a lot.
- She's moving on so fast.
- Of course. We don't have time.
- That's true.
- Shall we try to sing?
- Okay.
I bet you all have heard this song.
It's a very famous yodel song.
- Yes, I know this song.
- It's an Austrian folk song.
I'll sing it for you first.
Listen carefully.
(Listen carefully
since you'll perform later.)
(Searching for a mountain valley)
(Where water flows)
(I walk in the forest)
(It always makes me so happy)
(I sing a joyful song)
This is the hardest part.
There she goes.
(Yodel-lay-di-oh, lay-di-oh,
lay-di-oh, lay-di-oh, lay-doo-ri-di)
That's all.
(She sang such a difficult song
effortlessly.)
- That was fantastic.
- She yodels so easily.
- That was beautiful.
- Indeed.
- She sang it so easily.
- Really?
- That tickled my ears.
- That was beautiful.
- Really? Was it beautiful?
- Yes, it was perfect.
The two of them...
look like a newlywed couple...
who are visiting Austria
on their honeymoon.
With her?
- In Austria...
- He's a photographer.
Right?
They look like a newlywed couple.
The husband seems rich.
- He looks rich?
- He looks rich.
I'm a rich man.
(Love? I'll buy it with my money.)
Are you going to learn how to yodel?
- Yes.
- I see.
You're all too talkative.
- You're more talkative than us.
- Focus.
- Oh, I didn't know that.
- Jae Suk is right.
- She's our guest, but...
- She keeps complaining.
- Jae Suk.
- Yes?
(Repeat after me.)
Oh, my. I sang with Jae Suk.
I'm so happy.
- Really?
- Of course.
I enjoyed singing with you as well.
- I love you.
- Likewise.
I don't think he did so well.
I see. Okay. Let's move on.
- "I see."
- Let's sing.
(She responded half-heartedly.)
(Kwang Soo got upset.)
- She won't listen to you.
- Gosh, I'm so upset.
- I'm so jealous!
- Calm down.
- She doesn't care.
- Your words don't mean anything.
But how could she...
- Just don't say anything.
- I'm so frustrated.
(The 36-year-old Kwang Soo
wants attention like a little boy.)
This song has every element
of yodeling.
And what we're going to do
at the end is...
to imitate animals you like.
- Animals?
- Yes, animals.
- Any kind?
- Any animal you like.
- I'll imitate an elk.
- I'll do a pigeon.
Show me. Ready, go.
That's great.
Imitate an elk for me.
(Imitating an elk)
(He's the first person to imitate
an elk on a TV show.)
- An elk actually makes that sound.
- It's true.
- Right.
- Really?
- But can the elk smile?
- Yes?
(He's smiling this time.)
That's great.
- That's how an elk actually sounds.
- Okay. Which animal?
- I'll be an elephant.
- Okay. Ready, go.
(An elephant is here!)
- Good job.
- Is this...
Is this a talent show or what?
- He's trying to impress Ms. Lee.
- That's not true.
He's showing off.
- We're all so enthusiastic.
- Which animal?
- A dolphin.
- A dolphin? Ready, go.
(She's making
a high-pitched scream.)
- Did you imitate Jeon Do Yeon?
- That was good.
I like that.
- "I can shoot you."
- She's a pretty dolphin.
Let us divide into teams now,
Ms. Lee.
- Will you?
- Yes.
Ms. Kang, please help them.
(Team Lee Eun Kyung,
Team Kang Dong Hye)
(The two teams are practicing
separately.)
(They learn to sing
the easy part effortlessly.)
- Where water flows
(He's making nasal sound
while singing.)
(Team Jong Kook is
practicing hard as well.)
(Extremely enthusiastic)
- Hey, be quiet.
- What?
We're practicing here.
- We're practicing too.
- We're practicing here.
- Do not interfere us.
Which family restaurant
do you guys work at?
(Their clothes look like a family
restaurant's staff uniform.)
We don't work at a restaurant.
We're preparing for the contest.
- He has a point.
- Outback Steakhouse.
We'll start practicing.
So please keep it down.
We need to practice too.
- Then...
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
Together.
(Team Jae Suk starts
practicing again excitedly.)
Let's sing the next part together.
(Yo-ro-ro, lay-di-eh, ee-di-oh-oo,
di-eh-ee-ri, oh-oo-di-eh)
(He sticks his tongue out
while lip-syncing.)
(They've reached
the first difficult part.)
(And the song continues.)
- This is really difficult.
- Yes, indeed.
In 3, 4.
(They're practicing
the difficult part intensively.)
(My gosh. What are they doing?)
- Do something funny instead.
- Okay.
- How about this?
- Yes, I'll do that.
Okay. We're done, right?
- Next...
- What's the melody in this part?
Please let us listen to the melody.
(Team Jong Kook is
practicing the latter part.)
Just make sure
to make plosive sounds.
It sounds like a techno song.
I like it.
- 1, 2. Don't you like it?
- Indeed.
(They suddenly start
doing techno music dance.)
(Shy)
(The last few bars are
their favorite part.)
Put emphasis on the last bar.
We should practice that part too.
- Okay.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
(They're walking
toward the other team.)
Stop. What are you doing?
(They're trying to
strike sparks off each other.)
You shouldn't cross the line.
Ms. Lee, please let us
do the same thing.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Let's go.
(Counterattack)
(The elk is running forward.)
(They look like they're playing
a children's game.)
(Jae Suk kicked Kwang Soo's hips.)
- All right. Good job, everyone.
- That was good.
(They're practicing again
after the war of nerves.)
(Looking serious)
- This is really difficult.
- Shall we try singing together?
- Let's sing together.
- It's so difficult.
(So Min and Se Chan are
practicing the hardest part.)
That sounds so creepy.
(They just need to nail that part.)
(They're confident in singing
the last part.)
- Okay.
- Great.
- My, that was good.
- I can sing it now.
The competition will begin shortly.
Just as I said earlier,
Director Kang
will decide the winning team.
It's Immortal Chan Hee.
- Immortal Chan Hee?
- That sounds nice.
- Right?
- Immortal Chan Hee.
Regardless of the result, your
teachers will pick the best student.
- You go first.
- It's okay. Don't worry.
Oh, my. My adorable team.
- You can do it.
- Should I lift it up like this?
Please move a half step back.
(They practiced as hard
as they could in a short time.)
- Will you play it for them?
- We practiced with it.
I'll do that.
(Will they be able to
shine on stage?)
The first performance
will begin shortly.
(The long-awaited first performance)
(Searching for a mountain valley)
(Where water flows)
(Flaring his nostrils)
(I walk in the forest)
(It always makes me so happy)
(He doesn't look happy.)
I sing a joyful song
(They finished the first verse
smoothly under So Min's lead.)
(Terrible body roll)
Why is he dancing like this?
(Se Chan sang Kwang Soo's part
by mistake.)
(He forgets his mistake
and concentrates again.)
(They have reached
the most difficult part.)
- I feel dizzy.
- Good job.
(It's hard to catch your breath
or control your tongue.)
This is the difficult part.
(Will they be able to
pull off this part?)
(It's a total mess.)
(They lost motivation.)
(They're singing the wrong lyrics.)
This is a total mess.
(Is this a newly developed
yodeling technique?)
(Yodel-oh-hoo-hoo, ri-oh-lay-di-oh,
yodel-oh-hoo-di-ri, ri-oh-lay-di-oh)
(What's that?)
(When it's too difficult to sing,
he imitates an elk instead.)
(It's a disaster.)
(Finally, they're singing the part
they're confident in.)
(They recovered their confidence
while dancing a techno dance.)
That's not yodeling.
(The ones that are watching them
feel embarrassed.)
That's embarrassing.
(She goes overboard.)
(The Alps girl has turned
into the Techno Amazon.)
What's this mess?
This is ridiculous.
(They finish the performance
with some animal noises.)
We will show you
what real yodel is.
Let me show you. Just move over.
We will show you what real yodel is.
Gosh, this is...
Do you think this is a joke?
I get that we didn't have
enough time, but you can't do this.
It's harder than you think.
You should try.
- I've never heard the MR.
- Why did you dance techno here?
- Don't belittle our performance.
- I didn't know when to start.
- Me neither. I didn't do it right.
Immortal Chan Hee,
please enjoy our performance.
This is "Immortal Songs"
with Kang Chan Hee.
We should say hello first.
Please push the key.
Good.
Chan Hee.
Kang Chan Hee!
(They are trying to flatter him.)
Why are they
flattering him like that?
They are pulling off some tricks.
Why would they say Kang Chan Hee?
- You can't do this.
- Why not?
Can we say hello in a yodeling way?
(Without flattering)
Bow.
(They've been saying hello
for 5 minutes.)
Kang Chan Hee
Please live a long and healthy life
(I just want to
hear you sing yodel.)
(Searching for a mountain valley)
(Where water flows)
(He's too into the song.)
Gosh, it's a mess.
(I walk in the forest)
My gosh.
(It always makes me so happy)
(I sing a joyful song)
(The middle-aged man
with a nasal voice steps up.)
(This is exciting.)
They can't pull this off.
(They are reaching
the most difficult part.)
(Se Chan had a meltdown
singing this part.)
(We will show you
what real yodel is.)
(They give up too soon.)
(Let's just move on like this.)
(This isn't right.)
I can't believe this.
(It's a mess.)
(This is the part
that they are most confident at.)
(It's time for the finale.)
Kang Chan Hee! Kang Chan Hee!
Kang Chan Hee
That was amazing.
The best student of the winning team
will get an extra ticket.
- Okay.
- The worst student will return one.
All right.
Director Kang Chan Hee.
(It's time to make a choice.)
Please pick the first winning team.
Please just consider
our singing abilities.
- Based on our singing abilities.
- Please make a fair decision.
- With no flattery.
- Sure.
He will zoom in. Be ready.
This is the old way.
(He will pick the winning team
with the camera.)
Are they the winners?
- Which one?
- We used the MR.
(The team caught
in the camera wins.)
Which team?
(Team Jae Suk wins.)
- I think...
- Kang Chan Hee
- A long and healthy life
You can't score us
based on flattery.
- Kang Chan Hee
- He fell for their flattery.
I didn't know
you liked stuff like that.
- We had no idea.
- You just like to be flattered.
If I knew, I would've
prepared some money.
- Bring some money.
- He's right.
He likes flattery.
It wasn't because of flattery.
- That's not it.
- Tell us why you picked them.
Suk Jin might know this,
but back then,
we used to have a lot of
yodel show when we were young.
- Like children's shows.
- That's true.
- And it was always fun.
- I agree.
Both teams weren't
good enough to be examined,
but Team Jae Suk
made it sound more similar...
to real yodeling songs.
Immortal Chan Hee!
Thank you
We should've done things like that.
We should've made
deep bows and everything.
I should've tried
something like camera dance.
- I should've done something.
- I know.
(I didn't pick them
because of the flattery.)
Now the teachers will
have a discussion...
and pick the top student who gets
to choose a lottery number.
Meanwhile, the losing team
will pick the best student,
and the winning team
will pick the worst student.
(The winning team gets to pick
the worst student.)
Then we should...
Is it Se Chan or So Min?
- So Min was a little over the line.
- I agree.
(They are discussing seriously.)
We should mention
Suk Jin's name first.
They seem very serious.
They are serious.
All right. Should we announce
the best student first?
- We were unanimous on this.
- It was very close though.
- We picked the one who sang well.
- We picked it seriously.
1, 2, and 3.
- Ji Suk Jin...
- Okay. Thank you.
- is out.
(Ji Suk Jin is out.)
- You're out.
- He's out?
You're out.
- Is he out?
- This is fun.
I hated it that he sang well.
- You were so good that I hated it.
- That was close.
- Is he out?
- He made it so close.
- By only 1 vote.
- This one is real.
- We will announce the real one.
1, 2, and 3.
- Haha!
- Haha! Congratulations.
Really?
I can't believe this.
- Well done.
- What's the reason?
- Did he sing well?
- He didn't show off.
He didn't overstep the line.
He didn't show off.
I'm disappointed.
We agonized between two members.
- 1, 2, and 3.
- Jeon So Min, it's you.
(The worst student
of the yodel class is Jeon So Min.)
- Me? Really?
- My gosh.
Yes. We hated the techno dance.
- I hated the dance.
- Why?
(It's because of
the ugly techno dance.)
The thing is...
Right. I hate it so much.
- Me?
- It didn't sound like yodel.
I agree.
What do you know about yodel?
Why are you being so serious?
- You even bit your lips.
- I know about yodel.
I learned it
from these two teachers.
- I did learn it.
- It's Yudel for you.
- Yudel.
- Yudel? That makes sense.
So Min, you should give
one ticket to Haha then.
(One of So Min's tickets
goes to Haha.)
And the top student
selected by the teachers...
- can pick one lottery number.
- This is the most important one.
You can pick one student
regardless of the results.
(Who will be selected
as the top student by the teachers?)
Here I go.
Who will it be?
(Singing)
- What?
- So Min?
It's Jeon So Min!
(So Min is picked by the teachers.)
Let me tell you the reason.
- So Min was good though.
- She was very passionate.
- And I appreciate her creativity.
- Thank you.
It was really cool.
- Congratulations.
- You're at an advantage now.
Right.
So Min, you can pick a number now.
You better not share it
with other members.
Pick your favorite number.
So Min, pick seven.
- A number? What were the numbers?
- From 1 to 10.
(She has the privilege
of picking 1 of the 6 numbers.)
(The number So Min picks is...)
So Min has picked a number.
You will be divided
into two teams for the next class.
And here are the key words.
What are they?
You can pick
either Brazil or Hawaii.
- Samba!
- Brazil.
(They each pick
a key word they like.)
(Brazil: Jae Suk, Haha,
So Min, Se Chan)
(Hawaii: Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
Kwang Soo, Ji Hyo)
(Suk Jin, Jong Kook, Jo Hyo,
and Kwang Soo picked Hawaii.)
(There's a beautiful beach
next to the blue Pacific ocean.)
- Where is it?
- Over here.
(What is the class
for the members who picked Hawaii?)
Okay.
(They are surprised
as soon as they come in.)
- Gosh.
- What?
Hello. Aloha.
(Hula dance teacher, Che Che)
- As soon as I walked in,
- Hello.
- I smelled the tanning lotion.
- I bet you went to a tanning shop.
It's the smell of a tanning shop.
Did you go there today?
- Did you get tanned today?
- Ma'am.
Yes.
- Hello.
- I can smell that.
It's the smell of tanning oil.
How many awards have you won?
It's from 2008 to 2019.
From 2008 to 2019?
- You have an impressive record.
- Thank you.
She's the best hula and Tahitian
dance teacher in Korea, Che Che.
We're meeting a legend.
- She's Che Che.
- Thank you.
I'm really curious.
Can we really do this?
Of course you can.
Because I'm teaching you.
To be honest, all of us
except one are horrible dancers.
- Who's the one?
- Because...
You can do this.
I will try my best to teach you.
We need to learn the basics.
Let me tell you about hula first.
Hula dance was considered
a religious and linguistic...
performance dedicated to ancestors.
Ancient Hawaiians had no letters.
- Instead of using letters...
- They used body language.
Right. They communicated
with gestures and songs.
About 250 years ago, they started
to adopt the Western culture.
You know about a ukulele, right?
- We know it.
- I love ukuleles.
They developed the hula dance
with the ukulele, guitar, and piano.
It's called Hula Auana.
Today, you will...
Excuse me, but you're out of breath.
Do you want some water?
- You're talking a lot.
- You need to breathe.
You can take your time.
I know you are a good speaker.
- She's speaking without resting.
- I know.
- I guess you do this a lot.
- She's like a machine.
I wanted to tell you
all this before I forget.
- Before you forget?
- I see.
- Drink some water.
- Please drink some water.
Okay. Thank you.
She sounds very polite.
- Well...
- Gosh.
Hang on.
She's a lot of work.
She just spilled
a lot of water here.
She just had a sip of water,
- I know.
- but she spilled almost half of it.
My gosh.
(Shy)
- Wipe it.
- I was nervous.
I like the look on her face.
Are you always like that?
Is it something you need for hula?
You can't deliver your message
only with hand motions.
For example, do you know
the word, "aloha"?
This is the hand motion for "aloha".
- It's like covering your heart.
- It's love.
And you can't do it
with a straight face.
- You look scary.
- It's scary, isn't it?
So you should do it
with a big smile on your face.
Think of your family or lover.
(Thanks to the hula class,
they greet each other with a smile.)
Good. That's nice.
By the way,
why does he look so scary?
- What's his problem?
- He seems nervous.
- I think he looks nice.
- What's with him?
- Will you dance looking like that?
- You look scary.
It's terrifying.
The guys should
wear a little makeup...
for hula dance.
- Really?
- Hula makeup?
She will put it on you.
You will be
performing hula later.
So I'll make you look
more like Hawaiians.
- To have a strong impression.
- Okay.
A strong impression.
I've never done this before,
- so I'm a little worried.
- Should they look scary?
Hang on. I just heard you mumble.
I heard you say you're worried
because this is your first time.
Did I mishear it?
Because most students in my class
are women...
- That's okay.
- Don't worry. Relax.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
- This is the most nerve-racking.
- Oh, my.
My, it seems so difficult.
You poked my eye about 30 times
in such a short moment.
I guess it really is her first time.
- I thought she has a lot of...
- The eyeliner?
experience as she talks so well.
- She hasn't put makeup on others.
- She poked my eye 30 times.
Suk Jin, please sit here.
I'll do it for you.
- Me?
- Yes.
I think you're applying eyeliner
too thick.
This is how you should
apply eyeliner.
- It's not bad.
- I'm done.
- Hey.
- Honestly, it's not bad at all.
- Suk Jin.
- Am I a beggar?
- It doesn't look bad.
- Darn.
Jong Kook doesn't need to look
any tougher than he does now.
Aren't his eyes too small
to put makeup on them?
That's not true.
- Really? It must be hard.
- Yes.
Your eyes look really wide.
It's no joke.
We thought you guys only have
a vague idea of hula dance,
so before the class,
she'll give a demonstration.
- She'll give a demonstration.
- Yes.
- Okay. It's a beautiful dance.
- I saw the dance only once...
when I went on a trip to Hawaii.
Right? We rarely get to see it.
(What song will Team Hawaii dance to
to compete against Team Brazil?)
- I even like the song too.
- It's a hula song.
("Ulupalakua")
(A song about Mount Ulupalakua
where a cowboy's house is)
(Her smile and gentle hand movements
bring Hawaii into the studio.)
This makes me feel so relaxed.
(Relaxed)
(Smooth movements
as if water is flowing...)
(and nonstop gentle steps are the
elements that make hula special.)
I've seen this dance move before.
(Hula, hula)
- Look at her smile. It's pretty.
- She's amazing.
She won't stop smiling.
We're going to have to smile
the whole time.
(Facial expressions to express
love and gratitude...)
(make hula charming.)
(They're trying to dance like her.)
Oh, I have to lift my leg up here.
(This is "Ulupalakua",
the song they'll dance to.)
- I've only seen it in a movie.
- Exactly.
If we pull this off...
- But it seems so difficult.
- I know.
- You use your whole body to dance.
- Right.
I think all of you are good at using
your bodies and will learn fast.
However, describing what lyrics say
with your face is important too.
- So we're going to practice...
- We have to smile.
- doing that first.
- I'm sorry,
but is he doing it right?
Gosh, what a sight.
- Gosh, seriously.
- What a sight.
- I think...
- That's a weird smile.
You look unusually ugly today.
- If you could...
- Your eyes are not visible.
- His eyes are almost closed.
- He looks so ugly.
That's funny.
That's how she looked earlier.
I think that's a good start.
I'll tell you
a few different emotions...
so you can practice to make
facial expressions to describe them.
- Understood.
- Okay.
First, describe
love, joy, and gratitude...
without using your body.
Try to describe it
only with your facial expression.
- Love.
- Right. Love.
(Love)
Joy.
(Joy)
Gratitude.
You can't use your body.
You shouldn't use your body.
She's pickier than expected.
It's to focus on your face.
- Shall I give it a try? Love.
- Yes.
Oh, that's how much
you love your wife.
- I express my love just this much.
- No wonder...
- you never get a call from her.
- Please try to express more.
Subtle expressions of love
help your relationship last longer.
- Express joy again.
- Joy?
Imagine your wife is away
to visit her parents.
(Imagine your wife is away
to visit her parents.)
(Exhilarated)
I knew it. You look so happy.
- That's how joy should look.
- I did it unintentionally.
It's hard to describe emotions.
Ji Hyo, it's your turn. Love.
What's that?
- What's that?
- That's love?
- That's not love.
- Why are you giving a signal?
- To whom...
- It's because it's all dried up.
But I think she did a good job
in making eye contact.
- I see.
- I got a compliment.
- Kwang Soo.
- Last but not least.
Love.
(Love)
- Joy.
(Joy)
Gratitude.
(Gratitude)
(He opened his eyes and mouth wide
to show his gratitude.)
- He looks so ugly.
- What's that?
- What's with the hunched shoulders?
- To show my gratitude.
- To show your gratitude?
- Look at the hunched shoulders.
Hey, you can't use your body.
- I didn't use my body.
- I mean...
- What has gotten into him?
You look like
you're buttering up someone.
- What's with him?
- I didn't use my body.
- I didn't change the pose.
- Love.
- Joy. Gratitude.
- Here he goes again.
(He's doing it all over again.)
You shouldn't watch this
when it airs.
- Seriously.
- Is there something in your eyes?
- I wanted to express gratitude.
- I see.
- I'm overwhelmingly touched.
- Some people do that.
Exactly. I'm overwhelmingly touched.
You're overwhelmingly grateful?
(Kwang Soo described gratitude
in a pitiful way.)
Could you show us how to
describe love, joy, and gratitude?
- Well...
- Love.
Joy.
Gratitude.
- Wait.
- What's the difference?
Gratitude.
(She repeated showing
the same facial expression.)
Wait.
Can we describe love together
just once?
- Just once, please.
- She's taken aback.
- Ready, go.
- Ready, go. Love.
(Love)
(His eyelids are shaking
as his heart is fluttering.)
- Joy.
Gratitude.
(Gratitude)
(The weird look
that has never been taught)
- Am I doing it right?
- Kwang Soo is...
on a roll today.
- Am I doing it right?
- Gosh, that's hilarious.
(Lee Kwang Soo,
the maverick of hula dance)
That's so funny.
We have to describe the emotions.
Sadness? Okay. Sadness.
I'm excited to see
Kwang Soo's facial expression.
It's Kwang Soo's turn.
I'm sad. I don't have to cry, right?
- Correct.
- Don't make any sound.
(How will Kwang Soo
describe sadness?)
What has gotten into him?
(I am sad.)
(Stunned)
- What's with his face?
- Joy.
(He changes his facial expression
right away.)
Sadness. Sadness.
(He's describing sadness again.)
Joy.
You're happy and sad
at the same time.
(I am happy and sad
at the same time.)
(He can describe any emotion
like a vending machine.)
- My gosh.
- Hey.
(The emotion is fading gradually.)
- Sadness is hard to describe.
- You're a genius actor.
- Hey.
I bet no other actors
can do it like he does.
My gosh. I'm impressed.
- The last one was the best.
- I mean, he is...
- I tried to show a mixed feeling.
- Your facial expressions...
have never been this funny.
- Really? Do I look funny?
- That was impressive.
- You look funny whatever you do.
- Exactly.
- Is it because of my makeup?
- He can describe a mixed emotion.
Your facial muscles are
warmed up enough, right?
- Yes, I laughed so much.
- Yes.
- That was hilarious.
- Then let's begin...
- with basic steps.
- Okay.
Basic steps.
Stand with your feet straight.
For men, it's okay if your feet
are turned slightly outward.
You move to the right side first
in every dance move.
To move to the right,
rest your weight on the left side.
Slide to the right side slowly,
moving your weight to the right.
To the right. To the left.
To the right. To the left. Okay.
While shifting your weight
to the sides,
move four steps to the right.
Start with your right foot.
- Smile.
- Okay. Smile.
- Smile. Try to look happy.
- Okay.
(To the right.)
(To the left.)
(Kwang Soo is getting ahead.)
Look at Kwang Soo's face.
- His face looks like Hahoe mask.
- Exactly.
My, look at his eyes.
He looks just like Hahoe mask.
Open your eyes wide. Good.
(He's opening his eyes wide.)
- Okay. You're doing great.
- Thank you.
- Next, we'll learn ha'a.
- Ha'a?
This dance move...
is to sway your hips 360 degrees
like when you hula hoop.
Okay. 1, 2, 3, 4. 2, 2, 3, 4.
3, 2, 3, 4.
Your hips should be pushed back
and swayed to the left at first.
- 1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4.
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
1, 2, 3, 4. 1, 2, 3, 4.
You're like a hula dancing machine.
He's like a machine. He's amazing.
- That's good.
- I think he's a natural.
- It rarely happens.
- Gosh, seriously.
I can't look at his face.
- He's like a dancing machine.
- This is driving me insane.
This is unbelievable.
- Let's move on to the fifth step.
- Okay.
- It's called ku'i.
- Ku'i.
Step with your right foot
and kick with your left foot.
- Good. Step and kick.
- Wait.
- Step and kick.
- When you kick,
make sure to keep your upper body
still and straight.
- 1, 2.
- Just move the legs.
1, 2. Kick it like this.
Kwang Soo, your upper body
is not moving at all.
Look at his upper body.
It's not moving at all.
He's a hula dancing machine.
His upper body is not moving at all.
You should get a license.
- Take some private lessons.
- He's discovered a new talent.
(He's smiling happily
as he discovered a new talent.)
Exactly. You're talented.
This is so much fun.
- I mean it.
- He's a natural.
Imagine a vast grassy plain.
1, 2, 3. To the other side.
2, 2, 3, 4.
- Next, describe Mount Ulupalakua.
- Yes.
- Imagine a tall mountain.
- A mountain.
You know the gesture people make.
"Look at this view."
Right. And they strike
this pose too.
That's helpful.
- It's so easy to understand.
- Good job.
You look around
when you buy land.
As if your skin is tingly.
- To describe feeling cold?
- It means it's cold.
It's cold after sunset.
It's cold in the evening.
It's a fragrant flower. Move your
arms down with your palms down.
Lift them up and make flowers
with your hands.
We're going to leave in 10 minutes.
- Gosh. We're in trouble.
- Oh, no.
Okay. At first...
I'm confused about the second move.
- The second move?
- Move to the right and to the left.
- Ji Hyo is good at memorizing.
- Oh, my.
- She memorized the moves quickly.
- They're so confusing.
(They're checking the moves
they're confused about.)
What should I think while
performing? That I'm beautiful?
Che Che, should I think
that I'm beautiful while dancing?
"I am beautiful. I am attractive."
Suk Jin, just focus on
memorizing the order.
- Facial expressions are important.
- Don't think about anything else.
We can offset our mistakes
with our facial expressions.
- "I am beautiful."
- Try to enjoy it.
Let's go.
Their samba dance will be
lousy too anyway.
(Meanwhile, Jae Suk, Se Chan,
So Min, and Haha chose Brazil.)
(The scorching sun and blue ocean!)
(Brazil, the country of passion
and cheerful energy!)
(What kind of class awaits them?)
- I'll go in and have a look.
- Hey.
(The teachers are welcoming them
with a big laugh.)
- It's been a long time.
- The real deals are here.
- Oh, my.
- It's so good to see you again.
How have you been?
Have you been well?
- Hi, Ji Woo. It's been a while.
- How have you been?
- It's been a while.
- Hello.
- It's good to see you.
- It's Ji Woo.
- It's been so long.
- Ji Woo...
Goodness.
We met him for the first time...
during a Latin dance special
on a variety show in 2007.
Yes, on "Infinite Challenge".
I remember.
Haven't I aged a lot?
- No, you're the same.
- You look even better.
- Do I?
- Yes.
We all say that when growing old.
- Among ourselves...
- Not to embarrass each other.
- "You're looking good!"
- "You look even better."
- "You haven't changed."
- Today, you'll learn the samba.
- The samba.
Let me first introduce you...
- to your teachers today.
- Of course.
- It's good to see you.
- Hello.
- They all look amazing.
- Kim Ung Gyeom and Um Hye Ri.
Um Hye Ri, I see.
This is Ryu Ji Won.
Hello.
- She's my wife.
- Oh, really?
- I see.
- How fascinating.
I used to be her teacher.
That's how you got together.
(Romantic stories
always intrigue Love Frog.)
- It brought you together.
- Love was in the air.
- First...
- Go ahead.
- You'll be on your way to Brazil.
- Yes, Brazil.
Before you dance the samba,
you should see
how it's supposed to be.
Yes, of course!
- The two of you.
- I'd love to see it.
The two over here...
are the Korean champions.
They'll show you what real samba is.
- Shall we?
- Let's samba!
(They can't wait.)
This is going to be cool.
- To this kind of music?
- No way.
Nice!
She looks like Kim Se Jeong.
How cool.
(Eyes open wide.)
(The samba energy
leaves them gaping.)
My gosh.
Keep an eye on their expressions.
(Their expressions
are dynamic and alive.)
This is so cool!
(Cheering)
(Stepping backwards)
(However, his teeth
want to step forward.)
(Wow!)
Aren't they amazing?
(Beware of imitations.)
(This is samba.)
Samba!
- Nice.
- Samba!
- I knew it.
- Aren't they amazing?
- Latin dancing sure is cool.
- Unbelievable.
Did you see
their lively expressions?
Their expressions were incredible.
That was so cool.
Their gazes were like...
(Glaring)
That's right.
(This is probably
what he's mimicking.)
It's as if they were
going to eat you up.
I can hold that gaze too.
(On fire)
The samba
you'll be learning today...
- is an easier version.
- Of course.
What you saw earlier
was for master dancers.
- He made it just for us.
- Could we learn it?
You should be glad...
that you're with the skilled dancers
of Running Man.
That's for me to decide.
- Even the toughest choreography...
- 1, 2.
Some can already do
the simple steps.
(All four of them are confident
in their dancing skills.)
So first, let the four of us
show you...
- what you'll be learning today.
- Sure thing.
Finally, this is it.
You're married, right?
- How beautiful.
- Amazing, right?
- Yes.
- You can be just like them.
- Se Chan and So Min...
- Exactly.
They're married.
Cue, music.
How cool.
(What will the members learn today?)
Is this the samba?
Check out their lines.
- This is what we'll do?
- This?
- It's too difficult.
- Hold on.
That's unbelievably cool.
Oh, no.
- How can we do this?
- We can't possibly do this.
How on earth can we do this?
(This is what
they're supposed to do?)
No way.
How sexy!
(The samba dance gains another fan.)
Seriously?
(Close distance)
(How can one do this?)
(It's all about the chemistry
between the partners.)
- We can't do this.
- There's no way.
We should get going.
- Bye, everyone.
- Well done.
I still have it, don't I?
- You were gliding on the stage.
- The feel of it...
- It was amazing.
- You still have it.
- You're just the same.
- You're not like others.
You were gliding just now.
This is what we also say...
- as we grow old together.
- Which is what?
"You're still the same."
(You're still the same.)
- Exactly.
- "You've still got it."
The years were good to you.
"You haven't changed."
- How can we dance that though?
- That was amazing.
It's too difficult.
Latin dancing...
- is all about the partnership.
- How can we do this though?
- This links couples together.
- Yes, that happens.
- That's what happened to you.
- Right.
While dancing...
- While dancing?
- It's quite common.
- Which moment exactly...
- They're sort of stuck, you see.
You'll learn that
as you dance the samba today.
- Couples...
- No one can actually tell you.
Many couples end up together.
(Love Frog is only interested
in romance.)
- Then...
- I'm in big trouble.
- There's an issue though.
- What is it?
- How can we partner up?
- Beats me.
One of you guys...
needs to take on the woman's role.
We know who we're
partnering up with.
Exactly.
It'll be the two of you
and those two over there.
- His physique...
- It's feminine.
- Right?
- Hold on.
See? You're just as slender.
- Wait.
- You have the same physique.
- I can't.
- You can!
- You do it then.
- No, you.
- You do it!
- Anyone can tell...
- Ji Woo, you tell him.
- No way.
- Are we partners?
- We have no choice.
(Mr. Gums and Ms. Frog
will dance together.)
(Se Chan's thrilled about
not dressing up as a woman.)
- Lead me well.
- Got it.
It's not about the moves themselves.
Only the feel of them counts.
- The feel!
- That's all that matters.
So to the music,
show me how you each
feel it yourselves.
- How we feel it?
- Alone?
- Yes, alone.
- But it'll be embarrassing.
Cue, music!
Feel it!
(The music plays,
but no one steps forward.)
I can't believe we'll dance
the samba. Will you give it a go?
Feel it! Get ready.
(What are you three doing?)
- Go ahead.
- 2, 3, 4.
(Swaying)
(The bold Jeon So Min)
(Slip!)
(Her boldness malfunctioned.)
No, please keep going.
(When boldness meets the samba)
- Bravo.
- No, that's enough.
Enough!
(Tension overload)
This is too much.
- She...
- What on earth are you doing?
Stop it.
That's enough.
- Please, stop.
- I can't do this.
Why bother Chan Hee like that?
I can't be partners with her.
What's wrong with you?
She always wants more.
(She's as passionate as
the Master of Samba.)
That was the best.
I know what she's capable of now.
- Play the music for them again.
- Haha.
Show us.
- He'll do well.
- He's a good dancer.
(The arrogant Haha)
- How cool is that!
- Conga!
- Isn't he amazing?
(He even throws off his cap.)
(Full of arrogance)
- He's really good.
- He should be the female dancer.
Look how good he is.
(He's taking the moves
from his Z-KIRI days.)
Haha, wait.
- Hold on.
- He's quite good.
- You...
- How are you this good?
You're trying not to be
the female dancer, right?
It's why you're dancing
with so much force.
(That was him rejecting
the role of a female dancer.)
- That's why.
- Once more. Cue, music.
- Show us.
- He's unbuttoning his shirt.
(Mr. Gums, Yang Se Chan)
Give me the same song, please.
No, the one before that.
- The earlier one?
- Yes, I like it more.
Se Chan knows the feeling.
Just a second. Wait.
My gosh.
I want to pat off my sweat!
(Where do you think you're going?)
My gosh.
(He won't let his teacher
pat off his sweat.)
Nicely done. Good job.
(The samba battle suddenly begins.)
(He flashes his pale complexion
and challenges his teacher.)
Nice!
(Yang Se Chan, tofu vendor)
Go on.
The mouth. Look at our mouths!
(Please buy a block of tofu.)
- Nice!
- Good one.
(Here's some soft tofu.)
He knows how to enjoy the music.
(The body language of two geniuses)
Nice. That was amazing.
- You were great. What was this?
- Se Chan,
why were you cursing though?
No, I wasn't cursing.
My emotions were bursting out.
It means I was having fun.
- You were swearing.
- He was having fun!
That was hilarious.
Did you see his teeth?
(This is him having fun.)
- Se Chan's a good dancer too.
- That was exhausting.
Our true colors come out.
I'm curious as to
who'll play the female dancer.
(Meanwhile, the whole nation
knows of Jae Suk's love for samba.)
(Who will play the role
of the female dancer?)
The picture has been
painted in my head.
We'll do as you say.
- I wonder who.
- Got it.
It'll be Haha.
- What?
- You were chosen.
What? Me?
- Good.
- I think you'll be great.
- Also, Haha's a great dancer.
- He is.
He's a talented one.
That much I can probably do.
We'll start with two feet together.
Step out with your left foot
and come back.
Step back with your right foot
Let me show you.
1, 2, 3.
(They begin with the basic steps.)
Next, bend your knees as you do so.
And bend.
We get it.
(It's all about the quick and slow.)
Once more.
Se Chan, ready, go!
Your lips. Your beak.
He said I have a beak.
(Did you say beak?)
(When he criticized his beak...)
- Sir, I have lips.
- Not beak,
- My lips.
- I meant lips. Get ready, start.
Look at his lips.
- You should relax your lips a bit.
- Does that look more natural?
That's right. Okay.
Ready. Start.
(Mr. Gums is warming up.)
- Look at his lips.
- Let's start with your left foot.
Ready, start.
1, 2, 3, 4.
- 2, 2, 3, 4.
- They look like Namolla Family.
They look like Namolla Family.
(They call upon Namolla Family
in the middle of their lesson.)
What?
Our teacher is really funny.
- We're making progress.
- We are.
He's just going through it
because he doesn't have time.
- Do you think we got it right?
- He's just going through it.
Don't you know how scary he is?
- This usually takes about a week.
- Right.
- Okay. The second one.
- Okay.
Partner up, and follow what we do.
Come here.
He said to partner up,
and I came here.
The guys will cross their arms.
Don't try to do well.
(Clenching his teeth)
- Is it annoying?
- It's annoying.
Bring your outstretched hand
and cross it above your head.
It's hard.
- You look pretty.
- Put your arms behind your ears.
- I can't do it.
- Stick out your bottom a bit.
- It's not easy.
- Stick your bottom out towards me.
- The line isn't pretty.
You should look in the mirror.
Lower your body a bit.
(Dying)
Straighten one leg.
Straighten this leg.
- Straighten one leg.
- How?
Straighten this leg. Right.
I want to knock him over
with a flying side kick.
Like this.
He's wearing a skirt.
(Sexy and seductive)
Okay.
- I can't look at him from behind.
- He's good.
You look forward from here.
Hold onto your partner.
- Okay.
- This?
The guys will bend down, and
the girls will move their left foot.
- Left foot.
- What came after this, So Min?
What is this?
- This is a handle.
- It's a handle?
It's so easy to hold onto.
- I can hold onto this part.
- Hold tight.
- Right.
- These are handles.
- I won't fall.
- Handles.
You'll hold onto her waist.
Se Chan, do you remember?
You have to twist her waist.
Don't twist me too much.
- Go easy on me.
- Okay.
- If she's going left,
- I'm embarrassed.
but you twist to the right,
you'll be in trouble.
Okay. We'll start.
(Se Chan's hands can't get close.)
Ready, go.
(So Min doesn't mind him at all,)
(but he's dying of embarrassment.)
Again.
Gosh, So Min.
Can you give me some sticks?
- Hey.
- We'll start.
- Ready.
- I'm embarrassed.
Get ready. Hold onto her waist!
I'll move. Just follow me.
- I'll do that.
- Ready, go.
- Slow, slow. Quick, quick, quick.
- That's right.
(He exposes his gums widely
as he's embarrassed.)
Start.
(The part that was particularly
hard for Se Chan ends.)
Okay.
We'll start from the top until here.
I can't hold onto her waist.
Hold it. Hold onto it.
- Hold onto my waist.
- I can't.
- Just hold it like this.
- Oh, my.
- Why can't you just hold it?
- Try it.
Just hold it like this.
- Why can't you just hold it?
- Go away.
- Look over here.
- Okay.
So Min, try it.
(Ji Woo will take Se Chan's place.)
Start with this leg first.
- It's slippery.
- Ready, start.
Slow, slow.
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
(What?)
Hey.
(Vocalizing the rhythm)
Is this dancing?
- She's going to break.
- What was that?
We aren't tap dancing.
(Her face expressed the passion
of samba first.)
The rhythm was too fast.
Okay, then. From here,
the girls will return to the guys.
- Turn and hold.
(Turn and go into their arms.)
(It's one hardship after another.)
(He punishes Haha
for coming into his arms.)
He got slapped in the face.
(Coy)
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Haha. This is...
- for Se Chan and So Min.
- Right.
If this were a movie,
you and I are just extras here.
- Right, we're extras.
- Right.
- Hold my neck.
- Hold her neck with your left hand.
You will spin her like this.
Hold on.
- Gosh.
- Spin me around.
- Spin her.
- Spin me.
- That's right.
- Like this.
- Raise your heels.
At this point,
the girls' right hands...
- will go on the guys' shoulders.
- This isn't right.
What's most important here is,
you have to change your hands, and
the left hand will go on their neck.
Something keeps touching me.
(Unpleasant to the max)
Let's not do this.
What are we doing?
I can't say anything. Gosh.
(It's unpleasant,
but they can't talk about it.)
- This is so unpleasant.
- Gosh, Jae Suk.
Jae Suk.
(Dancing the samba with friends
could be unpleasant.)
- This is so unpleasant.
- Face each other.
- You have to face each other.
- Okay.
Okay. Pay attention.
The next movement is a body roll.
You will do it together.
(They do a body roll
as they face each other.)
Ready, go.
(Gosh)
I've known him for a long time,
- but I've never been this close...
- Me too.
- for this long before.
- It's my first time too.
- Hurry up. We need to do it.
- I've never been so close to him.
We have to do it. Hurry up.
- She's too aggressive.
- We have to do it.
- Face each other.
- It's out of control over here.
Se Chan became timid.
- Hey.
- She's so aggressive,
so I'm so embarrassed.
My gosh, I seriously...
Your left side will show soon.
(Unlike its owner,
Se Chan's left side is aggressive.)
- This is fitting for samba, right?
- Hey.
- Let's button up a bit.
- No, it needs to be open.
- Gosh, it's hot.
- Let's do it again.
- You separated here.
- Okay.
Three and shake it.
Girls turn around.
(The samba class gets heated up.)
(Doing his best)
(What kind of samba performance
will they put on?)
- Body roll.
- Separate.
(After 1 hour)
(Hula versus Samba)
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I'm sure the samba
will be a mess too.
- I'll be sad if I mess up.
- I know. It'll be a waste.
You could forget the steps
all of a sudden.
Focus.
I'm covered in sweat.
- We only have one chance.
- We only do it once?
- It's time for the second match.
- Right.
Che Che is the teacher for the hula,
and Park Ji Woo and Ryu Ji Won
taught the samba.
- Park Ji Woo and Ryu Ji Won.
- Nice to meet you.
I asked Director Kang,...
what he wanted to see in advance.
- Right.
- He wanted to see Hawaii first.
They'll have a hard time because
they'll be discouraged.
- Okay.
- I'm excited.
I'm curious. Let's go over there.
Why do you have such dark circles
under your eyes?
- They did my makeup like this.
- Our teacher did it.
- We need to take our shoes off.
- Goodness.
(They go barefoot to make it
seem like the beaches of Hawaii.)
Let's do it!
- We can do this.
- I'm nervous.
- Are we starting right away?
- We're starting.
- Mind your facial expression.
- Let's do it.
Are we starting right away?
(Their toes show their nervousness.)
Mind your facial expression.
Are we starting right away?
- Your silhouette looks nice.
- Yes.
Mind your facial expression.
Music, cue.
(We invite those who are restless
from being home to Hawaii's beach.)
How cute.
(We invite those who are restless
from being home to Hawaii's beach.)
(The scent of Hawaii spreads
in Deungchon-dong Open Hall.)
They're so cute.
Aloha.
This is nice.
The hula is a cool dance.
(You can feel the leisure of Hawai
from their fingertips.)
(Kwang Soo's face
is filled with happiness.)
They're so good.
(They make mistakes, but
their expression is professional.)
They're so cute.
(The hula mister is off-beat.)
(Come to Bugok Hawaii.)
Their teacher is really cool.
It's really cute.
They look incredible.
- Their smiles.
- It's so still.
(The smile of the hula swindler
makes you zone out.)
(The members are starting to give
off the smell of tanning lotion.)
They dance well now.
Isn't Suk Jin's smile awkward?
(His smile isn't awkward.
He's expressing happiness.)
(They are each
expressing happiness...)
(in their own unique way.)
They're good.
(Hula)
(They keep their perfect smile on
until the end.)
(Clapping)
It didn't seem like...
- a couple's dance.
- It was a simple dance.
(They used
their facial muscles the most.)
We did well, right?
- We did well, right?
- You know...
We did a great job.
It was the best we have done.
- We didn't make a mistake.
- The song put us in a good mood.
The dance was nice.
- I know.
- We did a great job.
- It's time for the next team.
- It's our turn.
- My goodness.
- Will we able to do well?
- Let's go.
- I am nervous.
Then comes...
(She makes a fuss from the start.)
So Min is motivated.
So Min is motivated to do well.
She is the main dancer.
- Really?
- Just look at So Min.
- Stop it. I will be too nervous.
- I wonder what kind of dance...
So Min and Se Chan will show.
- Se Chan, you look sexy.
- I unbuttoned my shirt.
That style suits you.
You should go around that way.
- Should I go around this way?
- Yes.
- It looks nice.
(He has a pale chest
without a single strand of hair.)
Get ready.
(They get ready
for a samba performance.)
Music,
- cue.
- They look like proper dancers.
Let's see it.
Look at Se Chan's eyes.
(Burning)
(The passionate female dancers
come forward!)
(However)
Jae Suk, what are you doing
with your mouth?
Stop sticking out your mouth!
(Sticking out his mouth)
(Smile.)
(Se Chan and So Min look like
a couple from Brazil.)
(It's the male dancers' turn!)
(They let go of their shyness...)
(and take the stage
with bulging eyes.)
(And...)
(the dancers get close.)
(Her heart beats fast.)
(The youngest members' samba
makes everyone smile like a mom.)
(Haha steps up his game.)
(They do a body roll
at the same time.)
(It's my turn.)
(Rolling)
(Dream's dad and Ji Ho's dad
are completely absorbed.)
- They are good.
- I know.
(Explosive charisma)
Yang Se Chan!
(Laughing)
(Their passion makes them continue
to do the body roll.)
Look at Se Chan.
(The 4 dancers break away
from their everyday lives.)
(It's like Rio de Janeiro here.)
What was that?
(The perfect finale)
It was cool.
It was as good as our performance.
(The passionate
samba performance...)
(heated up the atmosphere.)
It was cool.
(The two dads did their parts
as main dancers.)
When I saw So Min take the stage
with gritted teeth,
- I knew that she was determined.
- "I will rip the stage apart."
"This is my stage.
I will give the best performance."
It was cool.
- It was cool.
- She danced with gritted teeth.
(I can give an encore performance.)
- It's time to check who won.
- Okay.
The legend of the variety shows,
Director Kang...
Immortal Chan Hee.
(Immortal Chan Hee time)
- He is moving the camera.
- Come on!
- Oh, yes!
- Se Chan and So Min are on fire!
- Come on.
- Kang Chan Hee.
- So Min...
- Where are you going?
The camera will go up and zoom in
on the winning team.
- It will come this way.
- Our performance had a story.
- Come on.
- There he goes.
(The passionate samba won.)
(They give a ceremony.)
(It's too bad.)
- It's all right.
- My goodness.
- Come on.
- So Min is ridiculous.
Teachers, please pick...
one top student.
Meanwhile, the teams will pick
the best student...
and worst student.
One member stood out.
- That's right.
- It will be you, So Min.
- No, it will be someone else.
I was named
the best student earlier.
1, 2, 3.
- So Min.
(Is the best student So Min?)
- Actually, Se Chan.
Am I the best student? Okay!
(Actually, Se Chan is
the best student.)
So Min did well,
but she was an eyesore.
- Thank you.
- She worked too hard.
I hate that facial expression.
So Min, please stop.
(So Min, please stop.)
Seriously.
- It's our turn.
- Okay.
2, 3.
- Suk Jin.
- Suk Jin. It's you.
- Why is it me?
- You were the worst.
Why am I the worst student?
I did so well.
He was the worst.
Suk Jin, that's not right.
You do it on the outside.
- How could you figure that out now?
- Seriously.
You aren't checking your pulse.
The dance is really hard.
You should try it.
Suk Jin, give Se Chan
one of your lottery tickets later.
- Okay.
- Now, please pick...
- the top student from each team.
- The top student?
Everyone did well,
but one student stood out.
(Expectant)
Despite being nervous,
- she practiced hard until the end.
- Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
(He uses his entire face to show
that he is sullen.)
Kwang Soo is sullen.
Please pick the top student
from this team as well.
Taking the lead
and expressing yourself matter,
but creating a certain vibe
matters the most.
Thus, I will pick So Min.
- She is cool.
- She got chosen twice in a row.
- I know.
- She is good.
- What is up with her?
- Stop doing that in front of me.
- Stop showing your armpits.
Stop showing your armpits. Go.
Why do you keep doing that
in front of me?
- Seriously.
- Am I the top student again?
I think I might be able
to win today.
- Hey.
- So Min is the best...
- today.
- Seriously.
- So Min might win.
- At the very least,
she will get the Korean beef.
- I know.
She already got two numbers.
(Ji Hyo picked 10,
and So Min picked 5.)
(10 is the number
So Min picked in Round 1.)
Let's give the three teachers
a round of applause.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
It will be cool.
(A cappella by EXIT)
Are they making the sound?
(That's incredible.)
Their voices are like
musical instruments.
I thought they were playing
Their voices are like
musical instruments.
- Seriously.
- They are only using their mouths.
(This performance
consists of voices only.)
(That's insane.)
They are building up a harmony.
(It's a treat to the ears.)
(The five voices brought
the cool breeze of fall.)
(Here are the teachers
for the 3rd class.)
- That was nice.
- That was so cool.
Their mouths are like
musical instruments.
(The voice band, EXIT)
(They are a popular group...)
(whose YouTube videos get
millions of views.)
Listening to them
makes me want to go...
- to a concert.
- It was so nice.
- That will be therapeutic.
- Seriously.
They exceeded my expectations.
Please step back a little.
I was saying something important
and impactful.
- No, you weren't.
- I was saying something important.
It didn't sound very important.
For goodness' sake.
- Their teamwork was incredible.
- Seriously.
Will we be able to learn a cappella
in a short amount of time?
You will only learn what you can.
That's good.
You will learn the OSTs
of "The Lion King".
It's my absolute favorite.
(The music reminds them
of the savanna.)
- We will sing the songs first.
- Really?
Then you will learn them.
("Circle of Life",
OST of "The Lion King")
(They get goosebumps
from the start.)
(No musical instruments were used
for this performance.)
(My goodness.)
(The echo makes them feel like
they are at the savanna.)
- I got goosebumps.
- They are incredible.
(They get goosebumps as a group.)
(Today, they will learn
"The Lion Sleeps Tonight".)
- Yes!
- This is it!
(The melody,)
(bass, drum,)
(and chorus are piled up
for this song.)
(The song they will learn today
is familiar and upbeat.)
(The sound of the savanna...)
(makes this giraffe miss home.)
(The animals are having
a festival here.)
(Wimoweh)
That was incredible.
"Isn't She Lovely" is much easier.
- This is too hard.
- I know. This is too hard.
We heard so many animal sounds.
This one is much harder.
- What are the parts?
- Solo, chorus,
- bass, and drum are the four parts.
- bass.
Drum.
Is there a part you want?
- Bass.
- You want to be the bass.
Then we will test
your vocal range first.
He was born to be the bass.
It's his top choice.
- Do, ti
- Here I go.
Lower your voice like that. 3, 4.
Do, si
(His voice wavers.)
Fa, mi
(His voice stabilizes
as it goes lower.)
Re, do
(He is good.)
- That was good.
- You should be the bass.
He is good.
Haha will be the bass.
- Thank you.
- Let's pick the other parts.
Who wanted to beatbox earlier?
- The drum.
- Se Chan, you can do it.
- Se Chan can do it.
- Please raise the volume.
I can do the basic beats.
- I bet he will do well.
- He got it.
He got it.
(The beats are basic,
but he is pretty good at it.)
I can do this much.
- That's more than enough.
- I pass, right?
- Yes. That's more than enough.
- Okay!
Can anyone in this team beatbox?
(Haha attempts to beatbox.)
That's good.
- I am jealous.
- He is good.
(He adds his whiny voice.)
(A broken flat gong jumps in.)
What is that?
- What is that sound?
- What are you doing?
(What is he doing
in front of the teachers?)
(He shows off his old trick
in front of the teachers.)
What are you doing?
(Will So Min give it a try
this time?)
(She is practically spitting.)
- You are good.
There she goes again.
- We shouldn't let her do that.
- She is becoming ambitious again.
Do the drum.
(Drum roll)
You are good.
- That really sounded like a drum.
- Now,
- who will sing the melody?
- Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook?
- I will do it.
- Jong Kook can sing the melody.
From our team,
Kwang Soo should sing the melody.
- I will be the bass.
- Bass.
Will you be the chorus?
- Chorus.
- Okay.
(Sh agrees without knowing
what it is.)
How will you test my vocal range?
I will check if you can do
do, re, mi, fa, sol, la, ti, do.
Do
- Re
- Do
Do, re, mi, fa, sol, la, ti
Do
(Humming)
(He is taken aback
by the new vocal range.)
- Ji Hyo, why don't you try it?
- Try it.
You will be surprised.
Do, do, do, do
How many times...
(She runs into a problem
from the first note.)
What's the point of this?
- This won't do.
- She was serious.
- Why did you ask her to do it?
- Ji Hyo can't do it.
- I can do the chorus.
- The chorus?
Why don't you make a monkey sound?
(Why don't you make a monkey sound?)
- I can imitate a dolphin.
- She is good at it.
A dolphin.
Let's divide the teams that way.
(Team Kwang Soo, Team Suk Jin)
Let's start from "In the jungle".
3, 4.
(Kwang Soo and Jong Kook
got the melody part.)
(The lion sleeps tonight)
Now comes...
(Breathing hard)
Am I supposed to feel dizzy?
This song doesn't give you time
to catch your breath.
You need to breathe
whenever you can.
(Meanwhile, Jong Kook...)
(hits the high notes
without any problems.)
- You don't feel dizzy, do you?
- No.
Let's keep going.
(This person is
as bad as Kwang Soo.)
That's do, right?
Do, re
- Do
- Do, re
(For 10 minutes, she has been trying
to get the 1st note.)
Don't harmonize with me.
You keep harmonizing with me.
- I am trying to find the note.
- Okay.
Do
No.
Do, do
(Repeat after me.)
I am becoming weird.
(I am becoming weird.)
(Ji Hyo makes even a musician
tone-deaf.)
(Thanks to the teachers
who don't give up,)
(So Min and Ji Hyo learn the chorus
little by little.)
(People doing the drum and bass
are learning diligently as well.)
- Where is my team?
- Shall we go?
- Are you guys coming?
- Suk Jin.
(In the jungle, the mighty jungle)
(The lion sleeps tonight)
Hold on.
What?
- You can't sing at all.
- Hold on.
(He got found out
after singing a single line.)
I just need to drink some water.
I practiced too hard.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Kwang Soo needs to do well
to make the performance shine.)
Let's try it.
(Meanwhile, Team Suk Jin finishes
a successful practice.)
(That was nicer than we thought.)
That was nice.
This has always been my dream.
- Really?
- Haha is really excited.
- He is really excited.
- I was like that when I danced.
I must have been like him
when I danced earlier.
(The atmosphere is serious
with this team.)
Did something bad happen
in the savanna?
- Was it too depressing?
- Don't do that.
I wanted to build up emotions.
Did everyone else die
in the savanna?
Your emotions are nice,
- but please pick up the speed.
- I need to sing faster.
Let's begin.
(However)
- Hold on, Kwang Soo.
- Hey.
The song doesn't sound fun
when he sings it.
It's depressing.
I am trying to save my voice.
(Kwang Soo keeps saving his voice.)
- Hold on.
- Hey. You are going too fast.
Are you eating ice cream
or something?
- I am sorry.
- What was that sound?
I can't roll my tongue.
- I can only do it shortly.
- We need to sing at the same speed.
You have less than two minutes left.
(Since 40g of gold depends
on the last match,)
(the members practice hard.)
(Which team will win
the a cappella match?)
Please add more echo.
(Team Jae Suk goes first.)
Please increase the volume
for the bass.
You sound like an expert.
(They keep increasing
the volumes of their microphones.)
(It's time to unleash his voice
for the real match.)
It's like a concert.
- Tell us when you are ready.
- We will begin.
We will begin.
(Their seriousness made the practice
go on for longer than expected.)
- From the beginning.
- Yes.
(They even prepared a dance routine
for the first a cappella stage.)
- We will begin.
- Okay.
(The teachers and the rivals
become nervous.)
(Tuning)
- Get your hands ready.
- Okay.
("The Lion Sleeps Tonight"...)
(by Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo,
and Se Chan)
Ji Hyo, move.
I am sorry.
Please let us start over.
(Ji Hyo just stands there.)
I am sorry.
Please let us start over.
- You were supposed to move.
- I forgot.
(They don't disappoint.)
I don't want to be the first one.
- Start over.
- I don't want to be the first one.
- Go to the front.
- When am I supposed to come out?
- Should I go first?
- Yes.
I will go first.
(They resume after changing
the order.)
- We are sorry.
- We will start over.
Start after 2, 3.
2, 3.
("The Lion Sleeps Tonight",
the final version)
(She stifles her laughter.)
(Ji Hyo and Jae Suk
finally open their mouths.)
(Look at him.)
(It sounds like
Kwang Soo will stop breathing soon.)
(In the jungle)
(The mighty jungle)
(The lion sleeps tonight)
(The teachers can't help
but hang their heads.)
(Bursting into laughter)
(Chuckling)
Hold on.
I practiced too hard.
- Give us another chance.
- Listen.
- Hey.
- Let me get a sip of water.
- Listen.
I am so sorry.
- Let me get a sip of water.
- Kwang Soo.
- It's over if you do badly.
- It's over.
I will do better.
- Without the melody...
- I could hit high notes earlier.
Say, "2, 3."
We will do it for real.
("The Lion Sleeps Tonight",
the real final version...)
(by Jae Suk, Ji Hyo, Kwang Soo,
and Se Chan)
It's worse than before.
(Singing)
(The melody is off,
but the other parts come in.)
(He is singing very diligently.)
(Let's stay calm.)
(Singing)
(Kwang Soo's vocal cord
stopped functioning properly.)
(He begins the part
he has a problem with.)
(His high notes moves
Immortal Chan Hee.)
(Singing diligently)
(Something must have happened
in the jungle.)
(Other parts sound great
in comparison.)
(It's the magical Kwang Soo effect.)
(He is confident.)
(Kwang Soo's high notes
make the rivals grin widely.)
What is that?
(Anyone would be afraid
of hearing this melody in a dream.)
(Shocked)
(Kwang Soo doesn't stop...)
(summoning a ghost.)
We are ruined.
They made it funny.
(There must be a drought
in the savanna.)
(His teammates avert their eyes
as he summons a ghost.)
(The first a cappella performance
ends.)
(They clap hurriedly
so that he wouldn't sing more.)
- Director Kang Chan Hee!
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
- We love you.
- For goodness' sake.
- I can't believe him.
(Chan Hee smiles
now that the song is over.)
How could you lose your voice
from practice?
You did well.
I could hit the notes earlier.
We did our best.
- I can't sing anymore.
- Thank you.
Hey, hey.
(Everyone is looking forward
to Team Suk Jin's performance.)
(Unlike the other team,
they practice in a stable way.)
Suk Jin, good luck.
- I hope Suk Jin makes a mistake.
- Suk Jin.
(Beatboxing)
You are confusing me. Stop it.
- Stop it.
- Add it to the performance.
Suk Jin.
(Adding weird beats)
(The old beats stick
to Suk Jin's ears.)
You are confusing me.
- The mountain rabbit.
- That's right.
Hold on, I am doing this wrong.
- Are they allowed to do that?
- I got it.
- Did you get it?
- Shall we begin?
- Yes.
("The Lion Sleeps Tonight"...)
(by Suk Jin, Jong Kook,
Haha, and So Min)
- His voice doesn't waver.
- I added vibrations too.
(Jong Kook leads with the melody...)
(and the performance goes
without a problem.)
(The birth of a 4-member
a cappella group)
(Impressed)
(Jong Kook shows
the importance of the melody...)
(which leads the chorus,
drum, and bass.)
For goodness' sake.
(They're quite harmonious
considering they just learned it.)
(She's excited.)
(The teachers are enjoying it,
unlike earlier.)
(Let's add a spoonful of
a sweet voice.)
(Good for you!)
(They even had the leisure
to add choreography.)
(I wish we did that too.)
(Wimoweh)
(Howling)
(Exclaiming)
(Shouting)
(They even succeed in
the hard part.)
They're really good.
(The winner
has already been decided.)
(Wimoweh)
(Sighing)
Kang Chan Hee
(The a capella is complete.)
(Unlike the previous team, they
didn't worry as they watched.)
Wimoweh!
Kang Chan Hee's the best.
We did so well.
(Bass Haha fulfilled his wish.)
Gosh. It was so exciting.
We did well. It wasn't bad.
- You guys were so cool.
- I got excited.
You were so cool.
Our main melody was a mess,
so how could we do well?
- He can't sing, so how could we?
- Our main melody...
- was a complete mess.
- The problem wasn't me.
He said that he's not the problem.
- He said he wasn't.
- Gosh.
- With Jong Kook at the center...
- We did really well.
With Jong Kook
setting everything up...
We need to check who the winner is.
The team that Director Kang
shoots is the winner.
We don't know how Chan Hee feels.
- We could be chosen out of pity.
- Kang Chan Hee
It will be a controversy
if he chooses them.
- That's right.
- A controversy?
Director Kang's choice is...
(Who will
Director Kang Chan Hee choose?)
- Choose the team you like more.
- He's moving.
- He's debating.
- Kang Chan Hee
(All eyes are on him.)
(Team Suk Jin's high quality...)
(versus Team Jae Suk's
scratchy voice)
(Where will Director Kang Chan Hee's
camera go?)
Okay!
(Team Suk Jin wins!)
(Nice!)
We got it.
(Smacking their lips)
Do we choose the best student?
This team will choose
the best student first.
The best student?
- We have a person in mind.
- 1, 2, 3.
- Jong Kook.
- Kim Jong Kook.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- We acknowledge it.
1, 2, 3.
- Lee Kwang Soo.
(Worst student, Lee Kwang Soo)
- The difference is in the melody.
- This couldn't be helped.
This is the most important. The top
student chosen by the teacher.
(Who is the top student
chosen by the teachers?)
- They watched us carefully.
- Musically,
- this part was really hard.
- Right.
And it's hard to stay centered.
But he did a great job. It's Haha.
- I knew it.
- Thank you.
All right!
(Sulky)
He could become
a professional bass vocalist.
- He was so excited.
- I was really happy.
- His dream came true. He likes it.
- Singing in a capella was my dream.
- He has a great bass voice.
- Thank you.
Honestly, we were worried and
wondered if the eight of you...
would be able to divide up
into different parts.
I can't say which team is which,
but there was a team
who was good musically,
and there was a team
that took the music...
and changed it into
an artistic satire.
I never did that.
- Just stay quiet.
- He said we made it into satire.
- My gosh.
- You ruined the mood.
It was so much fun.
- It was really fun.
- We enjoyed watching it.
(The third class is over.)
While you're doing that,
Haha will come up and pick a number.
That's right.
That could be.
Right? Because there are 10.
(Haha wrote 1
for his winning number.)
Are you choosing the numbers
for the lottery randomly?
- Yes, we are.
- It's random?
Oh, okay then.
Gosh, I don't know.
I'll just choose anything.
I would love to come in first place
just once.
- It's a miracle to get it all.
- I wish I could get it once.
I'll tell you the winning numbers
that you all chose first.
So Min chose two numbers.
- One of them is five.
- Okay.
(Number 5)
- The other is 10.
- Is that what she chose?
(5 and 10 are her winning numbers.)
- The other is 10.
- Okay.
I didn't choose 5 and 10 together.
- Song Ji Hyo also chose 10.
- Really?
I was so surprised
when you said that.
Haha chose one.
In other words, 1, 5, 10
are winning numbers.
If you get all 6 of them right,
we prepared 40g of gold for you.
- Gosh.
- If someone gets all six right...
- Right. Take it.
- Who could it be?
The first number is...
(The lottery starts.)
(The first number is...)
Three.
(The first number is 3.)
(The current winning numbers are
1, 3, 5, 10.)
I have 1, 3, 5.
Really?
We have two more numbers left.
I have 3, 5, 10.
If I get 1 more right,
I have a total of 4.
Me too.
I need one more as well.
- Can I write on this?
- Yes, you can.
- Six.
- I'll choose the next number.
7, 8.
The fifth number is...
- 7, 8.
- 7.
(The fifth number is 7.)
I got it.
(It's number 7.)
- I got it.
- My legs are weak.
- I got four.
- I got it.
- I got 4.
Me too.
- I have 7 and 10. I just need 6.
- Look. I just need 8.
- If I get one more, I win.
- I...
If you chose 8,
I'd have won 1st place.
I have the ball in my hand.
(It's the last number in
the 6 number lucky lotto!)
(If number 6 comes out,
Haha comes in 1st place.)
(If number 8 comes out,
So Min comes in 1st place.)
(The last number is...)
Two.
(The last number is 2.)
(Nobody gets the 40g of gold.)
(Disappointed)
I got the first 4 numbers right.
Really?
- I got 5, so I get the Korean beef.
- Is that the prize?
You're so lucky.
Jae Suk came in third place once.
That's too bad.
Suk Jin came in
2nd place and 3rd place.
Haha came in 2nd place 3 times.
You came in 2nd place 3 times?
Haha will take home
three Korean beef sets.
- That's incredible.
You own a pork restaurant, so why
are you taking home so much beef?
Kwang Soo came in third place twice.
Yes!
Se Chan came in third place once.
So Min came in 2nd place
and 3rd place.
Ji Hyo came in third place once.
Jong Kook came in third place twice.
We'll give you your prizes
during the next shoot.
Okay.
Today's winner is...
Haha.
He came in first place!
Nobody got the 1st place prize.
It's too bad, isn't it?
- Good job, everyone.
(A few days before the shoot
in Mok-dong SBS)
(Hello?)
(Jae Suk received
a mysterious phone call?)
(Bring an outfit that...)
(you would like to recommend
to another member.)
(Haha, Gets teased for his fashion,
Byword of see-through looks)
(It's finally time for me
to get my revenge.)
(There's a fashion style
I've been pushing for.)
(It's a pair of balloon pants
and no top.)
(Ji Suk Jin, Mr. Origami)
(They won't be able to
pull off my fashion style.)
(I'm ahead of the times in fashion.)
(A fashion show...)
(where they wear each other's
clothes is coming soon.)
(Fashion Choice Race,
All or nothing)